Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Gu Ae Jeong?
- Yes, Gu Ae Jeong's amazing.
All right. It's Gu Ae Jeong
versus Shin Min Ah!
Ok, what's your choice?
Gu Ae Jeong!
-This is...
-It's totally ridiculous.
Seems like after he went through
that life-changing event,
Dok Go Jin's taste has changed.
In any case, we got it.
Now, let's proceed to the final round.
No one expected Gu Ae Jeong
to reach the final round.
- That's right.
- Yes, Gu Ae Jeong's reached the final round.
Yes, for the final round, it's
Jeon Ji Hyeon versus Gu Ae Jeong!
And your choice is?
- Gu Ae Jeong!
Is he serious about it?
Lady, how can you...
You're Dok Go Jin's ideal type?
You must be very famous!
My gosh!
He chose Gu Ae Jeong.
From the look of this,
her luck has improved lately.
My ideal type is Gu Ae Jeong.
We know that already.
Yes, we do.
She's not just my ideal type.
The person whom I love
right now is Gu Ae Jeong.
We have a pretty sensitive question next.
In that case,
I'll ask you once more.
Are you and Gu Ae Jeong mutually
in love and in a relationship?
You're right, we are in a relationship
where we are mutually in love.
This is ridiculous.
Are you Dok Go Jin's girlfriend?
Yes.
That man is my boyfriend.
Are they putting up a show?
What is happening?
How can this be true?
Yes, let's take a look at some data
on Gu Ae Jeong.
We know that she was a member
of the National Treasure Girls.
That's right.
The National Treasure Girls
had a hit song called "Heartbeat".
- Dok Go Jin is really cool.
- The person who made my heart race
by singing that song is Gu Ae Jeong.
Although you've revealed
your relationship with her,
it's quite hard for the public to accept.
News of your romance will probably be
the focus of all the media outlets.
I'll use this opportunity
to ask everyone for their blessing.
I hope that everyone will give us
unconditional support.
Yes, we understand.
Where is Ae Jeong right now?
At the potato soup restaurant.
What?
Does she know that you were
going to reveal the relationship?
She does not know.
She's probably in great shock right now.
It's not just Gu Ae Jeong who is in shock.
I think the entire nation
is in shock right now.
Actually, we also feel that things are
getting a little unbelievable right now.
That's right. I'm very curious.
I'm sure everyone watching is very shocked,
especially all the female viewers.
They must all be sighing right now.
Did you know about it long ago?
I'm sorry.
We'll have to fight another battle again.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you answering the call?
What shall I say?
They had developed feelings for each other
and became lovers not long ago.
We hope everyone will give them support
so that their relationship
can develop smoothly.
Ok.
Yes, Reporter Lee.
Yes, yes, I wanted to call you too.
Yes.
Oh, about that?
- Yes, Reporter Choi.
- They developed feelings for each other.
Of course.
- Yes, they are deeply in love.
- They became lovers not long ago.
All right, Dok Go Jin,
Which part of Gu Ae Jeong
captured your heart?
Firstly, she's pretty.
She's extremely pretty like an idol singer.
I fell in love like I was under hypnosis,
and couldn't control myself
like I had broken down.
Even if it ended just like this,
I think I'd still be happy.
That's how great it is.
Gu Ae Jeong...
is the greatest love that I,
Dok Go Jin, have found.
Gu Ae Jeong,
I love you.
Dokko is Ae Jeong's present.
I've clung onto you again this time round.
Having revealed everything in the program,
I can't take back what I said.
Take responsibility for that!
This is the future that I can give you.
Accept it.
Have you caught hold of me properly now?
You've finally been properly
caught hold of?
Don't try to escape and ask me
to let go of you again.
Escape?
Don't even dream about it.
I'll definitely not let go.
Because you are my man
Because you are my love
After sending you away and letting go,
you still remain and make me cry
Because you are my man
It's because you are still my man
I can't hold back...
Dok Go Jin, I saw potato flowers today.
Where?
There was a photo of potato flowers
at the potato soup restaurant.
Do you want to see it?
How I hope our potato will flower too.
But why does it look like that?
Because it was thrown around,
stamped on and hit a few times.
Will it flower safely?
It'll flower if we wait.
It fits just nice.
It's beautiful.
[Shocking! Dok Go Jin and Gu Ae Jeong
passionately in love]
[Dok Go Jin's girlfriend is Gu Ae Jeong?
Dok Go Jin's fans are astounded]
All the reports have words like
"shocked" and "astounded" in their title.
No...
Are we committing an affair or something?
Is it that shocking and astonishing
that we are going out?
This is all within expectations.
Top star Dok Go Jin's girlfriend
is neither Shin Min Ah nor Han Ye Seul.
It's Gu Ae Jeong.
If they accepted it without feeling shocked,
from my perspective,
it'd be a blow to my pride.
It's great that you managed
to protect your pride.
They've also posted a lot of comments
on the reports, right?
What did they say? Did they scold me?
It's better not to see them.
It feels like you've received a massage,
being beaten every inch of your body
from hand to toe.
Feels great.
But don't worry, Gu Ae Jeong.
I have reliable fans
who will be our protectors.
They stayed up all night
when I was undergoing surgery
They are faithful fans who support me
every single day.
Those fans will be able to
defend us to some extent.
Ok, here.
What are you doing?
If I post this up,
fans who like me will
post their reactions, too.
When we see that,
we'll feel slightly better.
Now, smile. Gu Ae Jeong, smile.
Smile.
Gu Ae Jeong, if you still have a conscience,
leave on your own accord!
Even if we don't take action,
it seems like they'll break up soon.
It's understandable for a fan to get
jealous like that. Tolerate that much.
This one.
I think you two look good together.
See!
My fans have unconditional trust
and love for me.
Dok Go Jin, I'm disappointed with you.
You're an embarrassment.
The pitiful Dok Go Jin
is seduced by Gu Ae Jeong, the fox.
They're also scolding you.
Are you sure these are your faithful fans?
There are also fake fans.
This is no big deal.
Did Dok Go Jin lose his sexual ability
after the heart surgery,
and is feigning a relationship
with Gu Ae Jeong to hide that fact?
I have to sue all those
who wrote this kind of comment!
Don't read anymore too.
It's better to just not read
or listen to their comments.
Gu Ae Jeong, leave a comment there.
Say that it's not true. Quick!
Hey, hey, hey, it's not true, right?
Do you want to self-destruct?
You have to get your senses together, too.
It's just starting,
and you're already reacting like this.
Dokko, you were really cool
on yesterday's show.
As a woman,
although it may feel like
Gu Ae Jeong's quite shameless,
I'm envious of her.
However, as the representative
of the management company,
I think your current situation
is the worst possible.
This is something I've set out to do
even if it means risking everything.
All right, I've prepared myself for it,
so just let me know. How bad is it?
Of the eighteen advertisements that
came to us, seventeen have been lost.
Which is the loyal one that still remains?
An advertisement for moneylenders.
" When you're going through the
lowest point in life, we'll look for you. "
Something along that line.
That one is a money lending advertisement
which you have never thought of doing.
Once my image recovers, those advertisements
will come sticking to me again.
If my next movie becomes a hit,
it'll recover.
There is no next movie.
What?
Even if the Cannes movie is lost,
there are still many other scripts, right?
There isn't any now.
Those producers who used to keep
calling me won't answer my calls now.
Dokko,
didn't I say that this is
the worst situation ever?
Here.
It's really beautiful.
Ae Jeong, I'll have to
congratulate you now, right?
Unni, I've received a marriage proposal,
and it's from the person I like best.
I don't care about what other people say,
but my family has to congratulate me,
that's for sure.
Congratulations, my daughter.
Aigoo. It must be a difficult time for you.
Are you all right?
Father, please ask me if I'm happy,
since I've received a marriage proposal.
Ae Jeong, are you happy?
Yeah, I am happy.
Hap... py.
Ae Jeong, you have to start preparing
for the wedding from scratch now.
No matter what other people say now,
once you two get married,
what can they do?
Ae Jeong unni received a marriage proposal.
They'll probably be holding the
wedding ceremony within this month.
Did you come deliberately
just to tell me that?
Well, you looked quite calm
while watching the program yesterday.
I'm telling you all that because I think
you've managed to put away your feelings.
I've almost finished putting everything away.
I've started making preparations to leave.
Are you really leaving?
I'm also going to start having
activities in China regularly.
You mean you're going to China?
Yes.
I'm in this movie which has
filming locations in China.
Well, since we'll be close by
each other, let's meet up often.
You'll be staying in Beijing, right?
Yes.
The place where I'll be is about
two hours from Beijing by train.
It's really far away.
China is an extremely large country.
Drink this, it'll freshen you up.
We're really sorry that it messed up
the filming of the program.
It's not like Gu Ae Jeong committed
a vice like gambling or adultery.
To receive a confession from someone
she likes isn't messing up the filming.
Thank you for saying that.
I was worried that this incident would
cause her to be fired from this program.
Viewers on the program's
online message board
say that if Ae Jeong is not fired
from the program,
they will not watch this program again.
This is strange.
The viewership for Gu Ae Jeong's
segment on the program has doubled.
Are they watching her
even as they scold her?
You got fired from the advertisements
and the movie offers,
but I'm still able to continue with my
"Searching for Tastes" program. I'm sorry.
You've got to earn
some money on my behalf.
Hang in there and persevere
in keeping your work.
I will.
I like that program very much.
I like working with my colleagues,
and getting to meet people
as we head to the market.
The people I meet there
treat me really well.
They call me Mat Jang Geum, Mat Jang Geum. *
( * The Taster Jang Geum )
Mat Jjang* Geum? ( * best )
Is she Dae Jang Geum's friend?
"Dae Jang Geum" means "The Great Jang Geum",
a fictional Korean cook and the King's first female physician.
You can call her one of the imitations
of Dae Jang Geum* .
The Mat Jang Geum who is better than
Dae Jang Geum in searching for good food.
Oh, Mat Jjwang* Geum.
( *Jjwang is a colloquial expression for "awesome" )
The great Mat Jjwang Geum,
please give me an autograph.
All right then.
[Marriage Registration Form]
Here.
Are you asking me to sign on this paper?
Please sign it quickly.
Mat Jjwang Geum.
Is it ok to progress so quickly?
When I first met you,
I gave you an autograph without much thought,
and we ended up coming all this way.
Mat Jang Geum,
shouldn't you put aside your worries
and just follow along?
Why are you rushing like this?
I studied the public's reactions,
and the most common remark
is they don't think we'll last.
To show them we're more serious
than boyfriend and girlfriend.
I'll make you my wife.
[Marriage Registration Form]
[Husband: Dok Go Jin]
You've already signed it?
When you first gave me
your autograph back then,
you told me not to hover around
and to go away.
Because you didn't go away
but instead, hovered around steadily,
congratulations for becoming
Dok Go Jin's wife.
There are many things to prepare
for the wedding ceremony,
so let's start off with
registering our marriage, ok?
Here.
[Husband: Dok Go Jin]
[Wife: Gu Ae Jeong]
Know that it's an honor.
Dok Go Jin and Gu Ae Jeong
have registered their marriage.
What is the public's response towards this?
We're going to find out now.
I thought they wouldn't last long.
This is really shocking.
I still cannot believe
that they are getting married...
This is a crazy pairing.
I prayed for him every day when he was
about to undergo the heart surgery.
I think Gu Ae Jeong and Dok Go Jin
look quite well together.
What do you mean?
He looks better with Kang Se Ri.
Why is it Gu Ae Jeong?
You first revealed the relationship
on the TV talk show.
Now you're even announcing a wedding.
Every time you reveal something, the
entire nation falls into a state of panic.
Why are you straining yourself so hard?
Only if I keep on revealing things
will the arrow be directed towards me?
Things have developed as you wished.
The scandal has been mainly
about you recently.
I can put up with those scandals and rumors,
but I'm really upset that people
are looking down on you.
How can my Dokko be mocked
by elementary school kids?
Even if I sued those elementary
school kids, they won't be arrested.
Children of that age are rash like that.
While you're going through all these,
Kim Joon Sung has won the best actor award
at the International Film Festival.
Kim Joon Sung?
If only we could win the role in Director
Kim Ki Wook's new movie and advance to Cannes.
I've read the script for that.
No matter who takes that role,
it'll surely be his first step
towards the red carpet at Cannes.
Since you're not doing it,
Kim Joon Sung will surely get the role.
It's Kim Joon Sung?
When did the photo label change?
Advertisers react the fastest.
Oh gosh, this nickname...
This person posted a strange comment again.
[Die, Gu Ae Jeong, die! Die!!
How dare you stick to Dokko oppa?! - Dokko Love]
There are people asking them to die.
There are a few people who keep
posting comments asking her to die.
What kind of people are they?
Shouldn't we hunt them down and sue them?
Doing that would have the opposite effect.
Rumor has spread that the two of you
are preparing for a new program.
Our company has many artistes
in Candy other than Harumi.
Please include the rest in the show, too.
Ok, if Harumi agrees to participate
in it, we'll accept the others too!
One of the members, Min Ki,
seems to be very talented.
Min Ki is really charming.  She's really
outstanding. I'll leave her in your care.
Ok, let's meet again
during the next program.
Yes.
- Goodbye.
- Yes. Goodbye.
There are comments saying that
Dok Go Jin has shot some adult video.
That kind of rumor is bound to happen
once or twice when someone is famous.
But there is indeed a video
of Dok Go hyung.
Really?
Have you watched it before?
It's not the kind of video
you are imagining.
- Dok Go Jin's video?
- Look at yourself.
It's this kind of curiosity
that gives rise to rumors.
You must have watched a lot of porn.
How interesting.
- Oh gosh!
- It's Dok Go Jin. It's Dok Go Jin.
Oh my!
Why are they together?
She's driving me crazy.
What's wrong with him?
It feels really odd to be together
in such a crowded place.
I feel like I have to hide
and conceal myself.
I revealed our relationship
so we could go out like this.
If we can't even do this,
it'll be too unfair.
I am the Dok Go Jin
who does whatever he wants.
Oh...
Seriously!
Which movie shall we watch then?
[Phungsan Dog]
Seems like it's a story about a dog.
I like stories about dogs.
How about this?
Well, the lead character is similar
to a dog in that they both don't speak.
Let's watch this.
[Phungsan Dog]
Do they still want to behave
like that despite being scolded?
If it was me, I'd just stay at home.
They're trying to gain attention
by getting their photos taken.
You over there...
Don't listen to them.
Since they're doing that so I can hear,
shouldn't I listen?
Don't listen to words that make you upset.
How about listening to me sing "Heartbeat"?
I haven't sung it to you live before.
Will you sing it for me?
Ok, sing it then.
At first, we didn't get along
We only fought and frustrated each...
It's ok.
It's so strange.
Suddenly our hearts connected.
When you're not around,
I miss you like crazy.
My special someone.
You scared me.
Don't hover around here and move away.
You have to be careful
in front of me from now on.
I'll just go and...
Do you get it?
Dok Go Creep.
It was a fib.
I'm going to call them
and tell them everything.
- Come here!
- What are you doing?
Come over!
I fell in love like I was under hypnosis,
and couldn't control myself
like I had broken down.
Even if it ended just like this,
I think I'd still be happy.
That's how great it is.
Gu Ae Jeong...
...is the greatest love that I,
Dok Go Jin, have found.
Gu Ae Jeong.
I love you.
...and my eyes closed
and that you'll act first
to give me a hug.
You sang it well, Gu Ae Jeong.
You should have sung for me sooner.
[Bon Entertainment]
Representative Moon,
do you remember the CD which Dok Go hyung
entrusted to you before his surgery?
Yes, what about it?
Because of the rumor about his video,
there are a lot of people saying
ridiculous things about it.
I want to show them the video.
Dok Go Jin's video?
When said in such a way,
it does sound very exciting.
Among the rumors
surrounding the two of them,
there's also one which says that
they shot a video together.
Yeah, that rumor has been floating around.
Dok Go Jin's video.
Please lend me that video.
They must be expecting a porn video
so they'll be shocked when what
appears is as innocent as *Pororo.
(*A Korean cartoon character)
Have you told other people
about the content of the video?
Don't tell them, ok?
Ok.
You may leave first.
Thanks for the hard work.
Dok Go Jin's video?
It sounds exciting.
It'll succeed.
Dok Go Jin's video?
Is there really such a thing?
There's a rumor that you are
in it as well. Are you?
What did I film?
If we were to select the top three rumors
surrounding Dok Go Jin's video,
the first version would be
you co-playing as Sailor Moon.
Dok Go Jin,
in the name of love and righteousness,
I will not show you any mercy tonight.
That's just my wish!
I like that.
Why am I Sailor Moon?
What else is there?
In the second version,
you are holding something.
What am I holding?
A rope.
He's tied up by a rope.
Dok Go Jin,
I'll tie you up with a rope tonight.
How do you like that?
I like that, Gu Ae Jeong.
What are you doing it so softly?
Do it more strongly.
More strongly!
Is Dok Go Jin some sort of pervert?
As for the third version,
it'll make you even more amazed.
Unni, don't tell me!
We never shot anything like that!
In any case,
the focus is now on Kim Joon Sung,
since he won the best actor award
at the International Film Festival.
Dok Go Jin must be upset about that.
Especially since
he's caught in the video rumor.
Why isn't the situation gradually improving?
Instead, bad things just keep happening.
They must want to see you completely ruined
in order to feel good.
I'm here.
Are you watching the TV?
What are you watching?
Why did you switch it off?
Because it's airing something
I don't want to see.
It must be Kim Joon Sung's
award ceremony airing on TV.
He seems upset.
Do you want to go for a stroll?
Shall we go and get some ingredients
to make kimbap for tomorrow's picnic?
No.
Gu Ae Jeong, cling onto him.
What's the matter?
Recharge.
Aren't you upset
because of Kim Joon Sung?
Why would I be upset because of him?
He received a much coveted award,
but you're stuck here with me,
getting scolded every day.
I'll surely go to Cannes in the future.
I'll bring you there too,
and show you how great I am.
Here.
I'm glad that you are still
as conceited as ever.
I'm angry. MBS is annoying me.
Why?
The program you filmed with that anyone
Oriental physician was just aired on TV.
I think they're airing it on purpose.
I looked up the program schedules.
If you combined the airtime here and
there, it's airing for the entire day.
Was the program you were
watching Couple Making?
That's right!
Why is it aired so frequently everywhere?
Complain and make them not air it.
Sue them for infringing
your portrait rights.
Did you get angry after watching that?
What, are you mocking me?
Why are you so happy for?
No, you got jealous because
you like me, so of course I'm happy.
I was watching the program,
and in order to impress
the Oriental physician,
you wore a helmet
and did a really sexy dance.
Do that once in front of me.
I don't want to.
Why not?
I'll lend you the helmet which you said
you wanted to borrow from me that time.
Do it explosively.
I don't want to wear the helmet now.
Do you want to wear a cap then?
The cap you signed on.
When did I sign a cap for you?
I have one.
Here!
I shall now reveal my identity.
I was the only person who supported
Gu Ae Jeong in Couple Making.
I'm DK1974.
I participated regularly
in the popularity polls.
That's why I even won such prizes.
The popularity polls took place
during the start of Couple Making.
Did you like me even then?
Gu Ae Jeong.
Shall we put this on and go for a picnic?
To somewhere with great scenery.
All right, let's go somewhere
with great scenery.
Gu Ae Jeong.
I'm saying this since
the atmosphere is becoming better.
You didn't have any feelings for that
anyone Oriental physician back then, right?
Am I right?
It's ok, I won't get angry.
I won't get angry.
- So?
- Hmm...
A little...
A little what?
I won't get angry.
I won't get angry about that
anyone Oriental physician.
Are you angry?
I won't get angry.
- Do I look like I'm angry?
- Are you angry?
No, I'm not angry.
That anyone Oriental physician.
Disappear! That anyone Oriental physician.
It's ok.
Yes, I'm on my way
to the filming location.
Where is our Mat Jang Geum
heading to today?
Do you like buckwheat noodles?
Yeah, just bring some back first.
After I've tasted it,
I'll comment on our Mat Jang Geum's
capability as a food gourmet.
I'll finish filming
and return around dinner time.
Goodbye.
Hey, are those potato flowers?
Yes, our potato is flowering.
But this is not the season
for potato flowers.
No, our potato flower is in full bloom.
Ahjussi, what is the meaning of 'ho gu' ?
( Korean for 'pushover' )
What?
Everyone is saying that you're a ho gu.
Ding Dong, ho gu is short for
*ho rang i mok gu meong.
(*Korean for 'tiger's throat')
If they get trapped in there,
they'll surely die.
Post this in response to the comment.
Ok.
What's the matter?
Huh?
Gu Ae Jeong.
Gu...
Dok Go Jin.
You must be very shocked.
I'm al...
Thank goodness.
Thank you, Gu Ae Jeong.
Thank you.
My Dokko must have been really worried.
I wasn't just worried.
I thought my heart was going
to burst and I was going to die.
Are you all right?
It's thumping too quickly.
Is it?
Quickly try your mind control.
Oh, mind control.
I'm all right now.
Those scornful comments...
They're posting them again.
I brought some things from home.
Check if there's anything else she'll need.
Got it, wait a moment.
What are you doing?
There are some people who keep posting
scornful comments about Ae Jeong.
How can they say such things to
a person who just had an accident?
I'll report them to the website
and get those comments deleted immediately.
Are they that harsh?
Why are you...?
[What a pity, she could have died.]
[Do you think Dok Go Jin is also
regretting it, and wishing that she'd died?]
[Why didn't she die?!]
[We could have sent her off at one go
via the accident, what a pity.]
[It'd be great if Dok Go Jin
could make a comeback soon.]
[I don't like seeing Gu Ae Jeong. Guess she
won't show her face for the time being.]
[Is this heaven's punishment
for stealing Dokko oppa?]
[Isn't this the curse from Dok Go Jin's fans?]
[Gu Ae Jeong, just disappear!]
I won't put up with it any longer.
Track them all down and sue them.
Even if we tracked them down,
all we'll do is give them a verbal
warning before letting them off.
If we resort to taking
legal action against them,
we'll be under fire by the public again.
It's better to just let it pass
and not make a fuss.
I won't let it pass!
I'll sue them and make them
receive punishment.
What action will Dok Go Jin take
against them?
Please let us know.
Please express a stand.
Please give us some information.
Please turn towards us.
[Notice of lawsuit]
I'm Shin Bo Yang.
Shin Bo Yang.
What's your name?
- I'm Go Mi Gyung.
- Go Mi Gyung.
Was there any basis for what you wrote?
I heard that you work
at a large corporation.
Why did you post this kind of comment?
I'm sorry.
You've got a good career
and look so refined.
Why did you do such a thing?
Why did you do that?
What's wrong with you?
What do you work as?
I'm just an office worker.
After tracking them down,
we're even more speechless
about the situation.
The ones who kept asking her to die
are actually junior high school students.
The one who accused her of unwed
pregnancy is a normal housewife.
I read from the news articles that
a few are even university lecturers
and employees of large corporations.
Seriously, why did they do it?
Do they have some vengeance
against the two of them?
[Bon Entertainment]
All of them said they wish to meet
with you personally and apologize.
They said they won't do it again
and asked that you let them off.
Are you going to sue them?
I understand why you're angry.
You're trying to use this opportunity
to put an end to all of this so that
it won't be repeated in the future.
But I'm sure you know that's impossible.
Why did they do it?
No particular reason.
They said they did it
without giving it a thought.
They said they're sorry.
Just withdraw the lawsuits.
Never.
I'll sue them till the very end.
I'll continue to sue anyone
who does it in the future, too.
Then, what will happen to the
kind Dok Go Jin people see you as?
That's why I'll just be the
righteous Dok Go Jin instead.
You're lying here right now.
Is this time to worry about image?
Hyungnim!
Erm, more trouble's happened.
What again?
What's happened this time?
Dok Go Jin's video is the top search phrase.
That kind of thing doesn't exist.
This must be another prank.
Whether it's real or not, once news of it
spreads, it'll definitely affect them badly.
Even when photo-shopped nude photos
of female celebrities get circulated,
those celebrities' image will plunge.
Aigoo, should we try to watch it then?
It's widely circulated all over already.
We can watch it right away.
Are you going to watch it?
I'm going crazy, seriously.
Shall we take a look
at the hot topic for today?
It says Dok Go Jin's video here.
- Where?
- Over here, over here.
- Search that phrase.
- Ok.
- Dok Go Jin's video.
It says Dok Go Jin's video here.
Come quickly.
- Dok Go Jin!
- Dok Go Jin?
Have you watched this video?
Which one?
Where, where?
It's all over the internet,
come and watch it quickly!
- Dok Go Jin.
- Over here, over here.
What's this?
It's the hottest thing right now.
Is that so?
What is it about?
Did he really film it?
[Dok Go Jin's video]
If this video is made public,
the heart surgery most probably has failed,
and I'm no longer of this world.
To the many of you who loved me,
I wish to entrust to you
the person I loved.
In a way,
I received love from many of you
because I, Dok Go Jin,
was very well-managed.
On the other hand, the woman I loved
was disliked by many of you due
to all sorts of misunderstanding.
But if you get to know her,
she, Gu Ae Jeong, is a very good woman.
Because she'll receive scorn and be
misunderstood no matter what she does,
I'm leaving this as evidence.
Dok Go Jin truly loved Gu Ae Jeong.
Please watch over her so that
she won't be scorned or misunderstood.
I'm asking this favor from all of you.
This...
I left this just in case something happened.
But the 'just in case' didn't happen,
so why are you watching this?
That's true.
Whether you live or die,
you'll still confess your love for me.
Just how much do you like me?
Know that it's an honor.
Don't forget me
Even if I only lived for a second
Gu Ae Jeong.
I'll be the one and only heart who loves you
For that one and only,
I've concealed sorrowful tears and left
So please remember me
Representative, Representative.
The number of viewers for
Dok Go hyungnim's video has now
exceeded a hundred million.
It means that many people have seen
Dok Go Jin's real feelings.
Many more people must have
heard of it, too.
But then...
why did talk about Dok Go hyungnim's
video spread so quickly?
Isn't it a bit strange?
Is it?
I catch the smell of oil
being added to fuel the fire.
The smell is really strong.
Watch me and learn, Kim Jae Seok.
Moon Jin Young is the best
image maker in showbiz.
Thanks everyone.
Since the National Treasure Girls disbanded,
this is the first time
we're linked together in good news.
There was an article saying that although
the National Treasure Girls have disbanded,
the sense of loyalty, which is as valuable
as a national treasure, has gathered again.
Have you read it?
Seriously speaking, it was a tough
decision for me to be your bridesmaid.
With me agreeing to be your bridesmaid,
you won't be scolded that harshly by fans.
- You're right.
- That's right.
You did something great, Kang Se Ri.
But then, Mi Na,
what made you change your mind
and return to Korea to be her bridesmaid?
That's the least I should do.
Are there a lot of reporters outside?
Of course. Dok Go Jin called them,
and the whole bunch of them came.
But seriously!
Why are all the bridesmaid's
dresses so old fashioned?
This looks like what we wore when
we were in National Treasure Girls.
Sorry about that.
Hey!
Shall we meet up occasionally?
It'll be fun if we form an informal group!
I am a top star.
Yeah, you're great.
Well, since you rose to the top position
through the National Treasure Girls,
I'm also a little proud of you.
Of course you should.
I was the key member of
the National Treasure Girls.
If you acknowledge that,
I'll consider joining your informal group.
Let's have some snacks.
Aigoo. I bought this.
What is it?
Clover.
Do you remember?
We have to share the good fortune
so that all things good
will happen to us.
Here.
One, two, three.
It's tasty.
It's really tasty!
- It tastes the same as before.
- Yes.
It was also tasty back then.
I love this...
Memories from the past are coming back.
- You can't eat this.
- Ae Jeong unni, you can't eat it.
What if you can't fit into the gown?
Which gown are you wearing?
- Really.
- Definitely you can't.
- You won't be able to fit in if you eat this.
- Unni, wear the gown for us to take a look.
Gu Ae Jeong,
I see you on the news every day.
- You're getting married, right?
- Yes.
Aigoo, congratulations.
Thank you.
Go your way.
Goodbye.
Gu Ae Jeong.
It's been a while.
Seems like your leg is ok now.
Yes.
This time round, it has healed nicely
without any lingering pain.
I took your advice
and paid more attention to it,
so it healed nicely.
I'm glad that it's not
painful for you anymore.
It's not painful anymore.
I'm glad to see Nina smiling
like this at the end.
I'm leaving for my studies
in a few days.
Oh... Are you going this time?
I'm not using it as an excuse
or as an escape this time.
I'm joining a research institute
which I really want to be a part of.
That's a great thing for you since
you find studying easy and enjoyable.
I...
Can you do me a favor for the last time?
Please press at my Shin Jung* acupoint.
(*In ep. 4, Yoon Pil Joo said pressing
this point helped soothe heartache)
Here?
Now, I've really put away all that
had happened and calmed down.
Thank you for everything.
Thanks to you,
the feeling of my heart racing
as I entered into a really strange world,
is now imprinted here.
If I try to take it out sometimes,
it'll probably hurt a little.
But it'll all be washed away one day.
Yoon Pil Joo...
I'm really thankful
for your feelings towards me.
Hearing those words from you
makes me happy.
Said to be the wedding ceremony
of the century,
Dok Go Jin and Gu Ae Jeong's wedding
is about to start.
We are now in front of the hotel
where the wedding is being held.
Although the wedding ceremony
is closed to the public,
the groom and the bride will come out
and say a few words to their fans
before the ceremony starts.
Let's take a look at the wedding gown
that Gu Ae Jeong is wearing
at the wedding ceremony of
Dok Go Jin and Gu Ae Jeong,
one of showbiz's most talked-about couple.
Contrary to expectations, Gu Ae Jeong
will be wearing a wedding gown
designed by a local designer.
Let's take a look at the scene right now.
Why is it so tiring?
It's draining all my energy
before the wedding ceremony.
It was difficult and exhausting
to get to this stage, right?
But thanks to my excellent charger,
my battery didn't die,
and I managed to gain energy
to come to this stage.
I'll also sing you a song of encouragement.
Shall I also show you a song
of encouragement to give you energy?
What?
Here, look at this.
What is this?
A song of encouragement
from fans around the world.
From fans?
Yeah.
You're no longer the Gu Ae Jeong who's
disliked by people no matter what you do.
There are also many people
sending us their blessings.
Gu Ae Jeong.
We conquered it.
Conquered.
You did that well.
Dok Go Jin, Gu Ae Jeong,
Congratulations on your marriage.
Please be happy.
I love the both of you!
Congratulations on your marriage.
- Hello.
- Be happy.
We love you so much.
Dok Go Jin, Gu Ae Jeong,
Congratulations.
All right, we'll have another
round of shots.
Great.
Look here.
Please show the hand phone.
Please give another pose.
Ok.
Once more.
One more.
Yes.
- Great job.
- Ok.
- Thanks for the hard work.
Hyungnim, you looked really cool today.
Don't say such unnecessary things...
Thank you!
Hyungnim, Ginny said
she wants to buy you dinner.
I'm going back first.
You take my place and enjoy dinner.
We can leave together.
Are you in a rush?
Yeah, I'm rushing to do
something very urgent.
You poor youth.
Ok.
Ah, is that Dok Go Jin?
It's Dok Go Jin.
Dok Go Jin, Dok Go Jin!
Please look here!
Excuse me, please look here!
Because of you my chest,
my heart goes "thump"...
Hello, Director?
Yes, I've looked at the script.
Yes, I'm going to the studio now.
Ok.
I'm going for a shoot.
I might be back late.
Ok?
The image that Dokko needs right now
is the image of a warm,
approachable family-oriented man.
So look for a way to build up that image.
Ok, we got it.
Representative,
I heard that one of cable programs on
infant care is looking for a new host.
It'll be great if Ae Jeong noonim
gets that role.
Good! We have to catch hold
of this opportunity.
Manager Kim Jae Seok, great job.
Ma-Manager?
Yes.
Manager Kim.
Ma-Manager?
You...
You mean me?
Oh! Thank you, Representative!
Thank you!
I'm Manager Kim, I'm Manager Kim!
You're so dead.
Cheers!
Thank you.
Jae Seok, congratulations.
In that case, you'll be able
to talent scout fresh faces,
and do things like venture into Japan?
I guess I'll slowly take over those roles.
There's still a long way to go
before you get to do those things.
I was a manager when
I joined this management company.
But up till now, I've only been tasked
with handling Ae Jeong's schedule.
Our work experience is different.
I passed through the official interviews
and entered the company
as an official employee.
But you?
You pulled strings to enter.
Although I pulled strings, I still
have greater influence in the company.
Do you know that the management company
is controlled by Dok Go Jin?
Dok Go Jin is my brother-in-law.
If you want to put it that way,
I have influence too.
Other than Representative Moon,
the person whom Dokko hyungnim
trusts most is...
me.
Hey.
Jae Seok.
Do you actually think that the
second-in-command at the company is you?
In the future, please call me Manager Kim.
Manager Gu.
Why are the two of you
fighting over this?
Just act like how you usually do.
Fight over me.
- Over me.
- Stay out of this!
Noona, stay out of this!
Doctor, do you have a girlfriend?
I don't.
My God, how old are you this year?
I think you're just the person
for my daughter.
[Resume]
What is this?
Many people asked me about it,
so I've prepared this in advance.
Fill in your daughter's details
at the back of this,
and send it to this address.
My mother will contact you
within a week.
But... This...
I am going to start with the acupuncture.
Please don't talk. Here.
She's so pretty.
Unni, you're so pretty.
Unni, you're really pretty.
I'll always support you.
Thank you.
- Hello.
What is your name?
Noona, you're really pretty.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
The Kong Jin Pills haven't been
selling well recently, have they?
Yes.
We can't let this continue.
I've got to gather more friends
and promote it to them.
My God, Dok Go Jin's
father-in-law is here.
I came to confirm something.
Confirm what?
I heard rumors saying that my son-in-law
ate medicine from your hospital
and had my granddaughter.
Did you spread this rumor?
No, I mean, the herbal soup
I gave them for free the last time,
didn't they say that it was effective?
They said that
it was effective in curing colds.
Did they say that it was effective
in other areas?
Please don't spread
this kind of rumor again.
Ok?
If it spoils my daughter
and my son-in-law's image,
I'll sue you for doing that!
Seriously!
Why is he so arrogant that
he has a top star as son-in-law?
Don't attend to that person or give
him free herbal soup in the future!
I heard that Kang Se Ri comes here often.
Give it to Kang Se Ri. Kang Se Ri.
Give Kang Se Ri a lot of the herbal soup!
Ok.
Unni, hiking the first thing
in the morning
is really killing my legs.
Will Yoon Pil Joo really come here?
I confirmed it
with the staff at the hospital.
Hey, if we just stand here,
it'll be obvious what we're up to.
Let's go up there before we descend.
Hurry, hurry.
He's here!
Where?
Aigoo.
What should I do?
Let's go down.
No, if I start to descend,
I can't hike up with him.
Unni, he's heading that way.
Are you ok?
I saw you heading
in that direction just now.
Did you run all the way here?
Of course you'll fall if you
ran on the mountain slope.
You saw it all?
So you saw me standing there
and headed this way
to avoid me deliberately?
Hold my hand.
This route is steep and rough,
so it's not easy to climb up.
Do you still want to go by this route?
Yes, I want to.
Isn't it beautiful?
It's really beautiful.
Yoon Pil Joo, I brought
a portable gas stove and pan.
Let's have some ramyun here.
We're not allowed to cook
on the mountain.
Let's just descend and cook it
somewhere else. All right?
The scenery is really beautiful.
I'm so happy to have come
to such a place with you.
What is this?
Read it, this.
Shi Hyun, Shi Hyun,
repeat after me, repeat after me.
Goldfish, goldfish.
Uncle, I think
Dok Go Shi Hyun is a fool.
She can't say a single word.
Ding Dong, the intellect of a baby
who is only ten months old
cannot be measured using
that kind of picture flip cards.
Look at me.
(Baby talk) Ga ga.
(Baby talk) Bu dik gu bi di di
di dik di dik...
(Baby talk) Gu gu...
Aigoo.
See? She's a genius. She's normal.
Hyung Gyu, drink a glass of milk.
Here. Drink a glass.
- Oh, it's the milk Uncle endorses.
- [Korean Milk]
My friends only drink that milk every day.
Is that so?
I'll send you a few boxes of the milk,
and sign my autograph on the photo label.
Distribute them.
Ok.
Whenever your face is printed
on a merchandise,
it has the same marketing effect as launching
an extensive advertisement campaign.
Of course. I am Dok Go Jin.
My body is so perfect from head to toe,
such that I'm the number one married man
whom women want to steal away.
I also top the ranking for fathers
who are helpless towards their daughters.
You really drive me crazy
whenever you open your mouth.
The perfect Dok Gok Jin,
did you see the article
talking about us in the newspaper?
What did they write about again?
That we're facing marital discord?
That we're getting a divorce?
That we're getting a separation.
[Dok Go Jin and Gu Ae Jeong
in the midst of a separation?]
Didn't you stay at a hotel at the city's
outskirts while filming your new movie?
They wrote that we've already
separated for three months.
We'll have to go for a picnic again.
We have to appear in front of many people,
and show ourselves to them.
I think a picnic might be too weak.
In that case, what would be better?
Celebrities with a lot of children
seem to have been better received
by the public recently.
Oh, ding dong!
Gu Ae Jeong, let's start
on managing our image right away.
Then I'll have to recharge
your battery to full.
Recharge.
In the process of recharging.
Fully charged!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Ding Dong!
Shi Hyun!
Aigoo, aigoo.
Father and Mother are here.
Look at me, look at me.
Shi Hyun! Shi Hyun!
(Baby talk) Bang bang bang bang bang...
- I'll carry her.
- Shi Hyun, Father's going to carry you.
- All right, your father will do that.
- I'll do that.
Know that it's an honor
to have watched such a drama.
Conquered!
- Conquered!
Shi Hyun.
Conquered!
Thank you to all who loved and
supported The Greatest Love.
Main Translator: karened
Timer: dizzybugs
Editor/QC: Dimples
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com
crunchyroll.com