(The first date after moving in)
Cheers.
(I like it.)
(I like looking at his face.)
(I was happy that I got a chance to talk to Cho A.)
(If you feel like you'll get frostbite, ask me for help.)
(I'll lend you my natural hand warmer.)
(I really liked it at that moment.)
(On the bookshelf in the basement...)
(An unidentified album hidden in the house)
(It's finally here.)
- Really? - What is this?
(Is this your job?)
(Their jobs were revealed in the album.)
It isn't a hobby.
(How could there be such a character?)
(And the Introductions written by their siblings)
(We were close siblings who cherished each other.)
(I had a quick flashback of those memories in my head.)
(I went back to that time.)
(Their feelings started to shift.)
(I had to think about to whom I should send the message.)
(After sending the message,)
(I couldn't look Cheol Hyeon in the eye.)
(This is fun.)
(They got to know more about each other that night.)
We're getting started now.
- Good night. - Good night.
I'll arrange the glasses first.
Thank you.
- We get to do this here. - Gosh.
- I really think that's important. - It feels very honest.
- I mean it. - Yes, truly.
- Are you cold? - Yes, I'm very cold.
Are you Cho-ld?
You're witty.
Cho A, are you Cho-ld?
- Are you Cho-ld? - You guys are great at puns.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Can you give me an estimate of my diet plan?
- An estimate? - Yes.
There's nothing for me to make an estimate of.
That's not true.
There's nothing to estimate.
- No way. - I think you take good care...
of yourself.
Don't say that.
Why are you whining?
When did I whine?
How dare you whine?
I suddenly see Han Seok Kyu in you.
My goodness.
I really enjoyed that film.
- What's the one in prison? - "The Prison."
"I'm the king of this prison."
You're really good.
- No, there isn't. - Why is your voice so sweet?
Is that so?
- Can you sing us a song? - Yes.
- What song? - Are you Sung Si Kyung?
"Good night."
You're working from 10am to 10pm tomorrow as well, right?
- Yes, 11am to 10pm. - From 11am to 10pm?
Are you going to work tomorrow?
- I'll be staying here tomorrow. - At 9am.
- Will you be staying here? - Yes. I'll be waiting for you.
Come back quickly.
Do as you like.
My goodness.
(BamBam)
- Goodness, she's annoyed. - Really?
I've never seen her making that face before.
Exactly.
- Only her lips are smiling. - Yes.
He seemed to be curious...
about Cho A.
He seemed to have a lot of questions for her too.
To be very honest,
of course I am attracted to Se Seung,
but I do want to talk to others too.
The person I would like to get to know more about...
among other people...
is Cho A.
I want to talk with her.
Your name "Cho A" is...
It's pure Korean, right?
- Originally... - It uses Chinese characters.
- Does it use Chinese characters? - Does it use Chinese characters?
- Yes, Chinese characters. - "Cho" for grass?
- Grass? - Pardon?
Pardon?
Is "Cho" for grass the only "Cho" that you know?
"Cho" for grass is the only "Cho" that I know.
If you use "Cho" for first and "a" for me,
it could mean "the first me."
Like "the first me."
But it has a Buddhist meaning...
of overcoming myself.
I used to hate that sometimes.
I sometimes make myself tired from being too harsh...
on myself.
"Is that because of my name?" I wondered sometimes.
Is it that bad?
So I used to think...
about changing my name.
Shall we wrap it up now?
I'll have this as my last glass today.
(Cheol Hyeon)
(Ju Yeon)
(Jung Sub)
(Se Seung)
(Cho A)
(Yun Ha)
(Jae Hyung)
(Yong Woo)
(My Sibling's Romance)
(A rainy morning)
I should wash the dishes.
I'm really good at washing the dishes.
I'm good at it too.
Seriously, I'm really good.
Aren't you going to use the dishwasher?
- I won't use it. - You're going to wash them?
- I'll just wash them. - Let's do it together then.
Sure.
You want to wash the dishes together?
Yes.
One can wash them with dish soap...
and the other one can rinse them.
- I see. - Is it too cramped?
No, I think it's fine.
I cleaned it. Where should I put it? Here?
Stand here.
- What do you like? - Me?
Yes.
I like everything.
Between a mountain and a sea, you chose a sea.
Between jjamppong and jjajangmyeon, you chose jjajangmyeon.
Should we go to a seaside jjajangmyeon restaurant then?
How can he say stuff like that?
He remembers everything.
The only thing I could think of was,
"Should I cook jjajangmyeon with seawater for you?"
How can he do that?
I'll eat jjamppong.
A restaurant that sells both jjamppong and jjajangmyeon?
It's good to share.
It would be nice to go to a place like Namyangju again.
Namyangju is nice.
- But you know, - Yes.
it was fun at that moment too,
but it felt even better when I thought back to it...
after I came back.
- Did you think it over? - Yes.
I normally don't say stuff like this.
Darn it.
What do I do with the food waste?
- I'll clean it. I can. - Teach me. I want to know too.
- Do you want to know? - I want to know.
- I'll teach you. - Anyway,
the food waste isn't important.
What's important?
What you like is important.
What I want to do next?
I want to talk again.
- Really? - We now have more things...
to talk about.
That's right.
You worked hard.
(That night)
Se Seung.
Is there anything you would like to eat?
What are you going to have?
I'm not sure, but probably makgeolli.
- Makgeolli? - Yes.
Are the four of you going to do something...
that everyone was supposed to do together?
(They decided to have makgeolli and pajeon on a rainy day.)
What should I do?
What?
Guys need to go hang out once.
- That's right. - I think now's the time.
They need to decide the hierarchy.
- "Decide the hierarchy." - "Decide the hierarchy."
I mean, decide their feelings.
What are you doing tomorrow?
We're going to have some girl time.
Really?
I'm kidding.
So what are you doing tomorrow?
- What day is it tomorrow? - It's Friday.
I don't have any plans.
Shall we have dinner tomorrow?
- Dinner? - Yes.
(They suddenly become silent at Cheol Hyeon's appearance.)
So what do you like?
At 6pm?
- At 6pm? - I need to go to work tomorrow,
and I need to work until 5pm.
Are you, Yong Woo, and I going?
Yes. I think Jae Hyung will join halfway...
when we're there.
At 6pm.
(They planned a date tomorrow evening.)
I was happy.
After the first date, he kept having positive feelings towards me.
I was thinking about how nice it would be...
to have some time on our own for a conversation.
He asked me out on a date first,
so I was happy.
Why? Are you cold? Would you like one?
- He must be very handsome. - What's this?
- Gosh. - She's staring at him like that.
I think I'll feel shy.
It might be a bit too much.
Exactly. There's nowhere for him to look at.
She either loves him or has bad eyesight.
- What? - Right?
She either loves him or has really bad eyesight.
(Feeling shy)
What is it?
Just because.
You're staring at me.
Did I stare? I'm sorry.
When you stare at me so intensely,
I don't know where to look.
A bright-eyed lunatic.
- I didn't hear you. - Seriously.
Your eyes are so big.
- But Se Seung is in love. - She's in love.
It won't be easy for her to go to someone else.
- Exactly. - And she's very affectionate too.
Do you stare into someone's eyes...
when you're head over heels for someone?
If you like someone a lot, you end up looking at them...
- without realizing. - You look at them.
- You keep... - Your eyes are drawn to them.
You take an interest in them.
And she said he was very handsome.
- That's right. - She said that she kept staring...
at him because he was so handsome.
If she's at that point...
She really fell in love with him.
(Yong Woo comes back home.)
- Hey, what's up? - You're back.
I heard the news, Yong Woo.
What news?
I heard that the three of you were going to go out...
and leave me alone in this big house.
I heard that too.
Although I'm a part of that plan.
It was supposed to be top secret. Who told her?
Were you going to fool me and go out then?
Find the person that leaked the information...
and persecute him yourself.
Okay.
Bang.
It's too slow for a pilot.
You're right.
We'll get going, Se Seung.
- Have fun. - We'll get going.
See you.
(A bar in Sinsa-dong)
(Thank you for always staying by my side.)
It's warm.
I really like this kind of vibe.
The old restaurant vibe.
(Jae Hyung heads to the restaurant after his work too.)
- Jae Hyung is here. - He came right away.
- Hello. - You're here.
Good job today.
- You worked hard. - It's very cold, right?
(He sits down in the midst of everyone's attention.)
We men somehow came here together.
Exactly. I was fed with lots of hate...
because only men were going out.
I'm so full right now.
Se Seung is left behind alone.
- Exactly, she's left behind alone. - I feel bad.
Se Seung was alone at home when we left.
- Really? - Yes.
Did you hear that? When they said that Se Seung was alone, he said,
- "Really?" - "Is that so?"
- He's not interested. - Do you get what I'm saying?
Whether she's alone or not is none of his business.
- He doesn't care at all. - He's not interested.
As expected.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Do you like ketchup? - Ketchup?
I think Yong Woo is going to say, "I can't get enough of it."
Are you Yong Woo?
You were momentarily taken back, right?
I wasn't taken back, but I thought that we interacted a lot.
It feels good because I keep making you flustered.
You're so cute.
- Me? - You're so cute.
This is our fifth day.
As we're living together,
is there anyone...
that you feel more comfortable with?
I know whom my sister likes...
more or less now.
Using this occasion,
I wanted to ask naturally about what kind...
of personalities they had and what kind of women...
they liked.
I have a fantasy about my brother-in-law.
There's a scene I have imagined in my mind.
After Cho A gets married,
I will enter her house.
The floor is warm, the dinner is ready,
and there's a TV. As we watch the TV,
we'll eat dinner together and have a drink.
That's my dream.
- His imagination is... - He already...
- He wrote a drama. - wrote a scenario.
This is a new way of viewing it.
That's together with Cho A. With my brother-in-law,
if Cho A does something wrong,
we'll talk bad about her together.
If my brother-in-law does something wrong,
I'll tell him, "You were wrong."
If he tells me, "Cheol Hyeon,"
"don't do that to my wife, it's upsetting,"
I'll tell him, "Okay, I'll try harder."
I'm an open-minded person like this.
Anyway, I have a fantasy...
about small things like these.
(Laughing)
"Who..."
"can fulfill my fantasy?"
I'm observing them very intently.
- Someone I feel comfortable with? - Yes, or...
After yesterday, I really feel...
The feeling of unity?
That too.
Although we haven't talked, you feel close to them internally.
- Yes. - You feel that on your own.
The feeling of closeness grew a lot.
Was there anyone that you didn't get to talk to?
- There is, naturally. - Me too.
Jae Hyung, who did you not get to talk to?
I've barely talked to Cho A.
In a place with everyone,
I said, "Welcome back. Did you have dinner?"
We did have light...
and conventional conversations,
but I didn't get to talk with her properly.
If I have the chance, I would like to talk with her.
It's Cho A for me too.
I physically had less time...
- to talk with Cho A. - That's right.
I think everyone agrees.
- Since she comes back late. - That's right.
What about you, Jung Sub? Generally everyone?
- It's Cho A for me too. - Cho A?
Cho A? I see.
Just how charming is Cho A?
No, it feels like...
they're saying that because they know he's Cho A's sibling.
- Is that so? - Still.
But psychologically, men won't say that...
just for that reason.
Not completely.
- They even mentioned her name. - Yes. Mentioning her name means...
- they're interested. - Yes. They won't just mention it.
I wanted to give Cho A a piece of advice.
And I wanted them to know more...
about Cho A...
so that she wouldn't get hurt.
But I think Cho A feels bad...
about that the most.
She must feel bad about it the most.
I think she's the type to have fun...
- when she actually gets to join us. - She has fun.
Then...
is there someone that you would like to talk with?
Someone that I would like to talk with?
Someone you would like to know more.
For me, it's Yun Ha.
- Yun Ha? - I didn't get to talk...
- with her much. - Yun Ha...
was also very busy throughout.
I think so.
I really would like to have some time...
to talk with Cho A. Seriously.
Yong Woo. By the way,
it looked like you and Cho A got to talk for a bit yesterday.
- Yes, we did talk for a bit. - Right?
- Yes. - Wasn't that the first time...
- you had a serious talk with her? - Right.
Come to think of it, I didn't get to talk to Ju Yeon a lot either.
- Ju Yeon? - Yes. Yesterday...
Gosh.
Why did he mention his sister?
- What was that? - That's his sister.
- Seriously. - Don't say anything.
- They might figure it out. - Oh, no.
- They're mentioning their sister. - This is getting confusing.
- It's getting confusing. - Do they end up doing it naturally?
- Right. - I guess so.
It happens naturally around other people.
If I were to be one of them,
would I end up mentioning my sister?
- Right. - I think so.
- Yes. - Gosh.
When you're with other guys...
- Of course. - That's interesting.
You want the other guys to like your sister.
- I'm fascinated by what they did. - The thing is...
you might bicker and fight with your sibling at home.
- But once you go out... - Right.
They're your biggest supporter.
- Of course. - Gosh.
This is hilarious.
Come to think of it, I didn't get to talk to Ju Yeon a lot either.
- Ju Yeon? - Yes. Yesterday, I went out...
to have a cake with Yun Ha and Se Seung.
But I didn't get to talk to Ju Yeon.
(Meanwhile, Se Seung's brother is busy eating.)
The grilled squid in butter from the bar was really tasty.
(A while ago)
What's this?
- Gosh, this looks amazing. - This looks so good.
(The food is to his liking.)
This is good.
(It's very hot.)
Gosh, this is really good.
(He can't stop eating the squid.)
(He keeps on eating despite the burned roof of his mouth.)
It was the best.
(Feeling happy)
Cheers.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
By the way, I suddenly got curious about this.
When you're looking for someone to date,
is there something you consider important?
Like it can be her personality.
- For my relationship? - I see.
Yes. Something like that.
The interview isn't over yet.
He only cares about his sister.
I think he's asking questions like that...
- to help his sister. - Right. I think so too.
He'll get the answers and tell his sister.
When you're looking for someone to date,
is there something you consider important?
Personally,
- her vibe is important to me. - Her vibe.
What kind of vibe do you look for in a woman?
Everyone has their own aura.
Some are aware that their aura is what makes them attractive...
and know how to express themselves through it.
I find people like that cool.
What about you, Jae Hyung?
What do you look for in a woman?
You're the hardest one to figure out.
- Same here. - As for me,
I must be the first one with bigger feelings for her.
- Then you're interested. - That works for me.
Here's a thing about my personality. My likes and dislikes are...
- very clear. - I see.
I don't stay in the middle.
"Should I give it time and see where it goes?"
I rarely do that.
- When I get this clear feeling... - Right.
that she's the one for me,
- I turn into a bulldozer. - You go all in?
I go all in.
I really hate it...
- when people play hard-to-get. - Right.
You're just like me. I'm like that too.
I'm straightforward with my feelings.
There are women I can stay as friends...
and women I might have romantic relationships with.
- You can clearly categorize them. - There's a clear division for me.
What about you, Yong Woo?
- What about Yong Woo? - What was the question?
- I'm sorry. - Let's go over it again.
- Okay. - What's the most important thing...
- you consider when looking... - Right.
- for someone to date? - The most important thing?
So far, I mostly dated women...
who gave me the spark instantly.
(Especially paying attention)
- For example, - Yes.
there was a woman I dated when my feelings weren't clear.
- Seriously. That relationship... - It didn't last long.
was a bit disappointing in the end.
When I got the spark from my heart...
and followed through, those relationships went well.
- Right. - I enjoyed such relationships...
a lot more.
But trying to describe...
- this heart-fluttering feeling... - Trying to explain that...
- That's really hard. - It's really not easy.
- Right. - So...
By the way, Brother Yong Woo...
Brother Yong Woo? I mean, Yong Woo...
- Brother. - I...
I had a slip of the tongue and addressed him as my brother.
But addressing as my brother felt so natural.
"Brother Yong Woo. Gosh, that felt so natural."
- Brother. - Yes.
- Are we going to reveal it now? - Yong Woo...
- Yong Woo... - I just...
Did something happen when I was at work?
We decided not to talk about this.
Wasn't that supposed to be a secret?
It was a secret.
- Seriously. Goodness. - Yong Woo...
Yong Woo. Then how about this?
Here's what I've learned about you from observing you so far.
You get along with everyone and have a kind personality.
- It's because you are that person. - Well...
- Is that so? - Yes.
You guys should clink your glasses.
- Should I not be on this show? - Clink your glasses.
(The house in Seorae Village)
(Se Seung is alone in the kitchen.)
I'm not good at cooking.
But I wanted to cook spicy braised chicken.
I thought a lot about it before cooking it.
I decided to try braising just one chicken.
Yes. Next...
Should we cook spicy braised chicken?
(Sounding surprised)
- Do you know how to cook it? - Yes.
(Surprised)
- Please cook it for us. - Sounds good.
I really like that dish.
- How about it? - Should I try cooking it?
Think briefly, and act fast.
- Okay. - That way, you don't have regrets.
- Just try it. - Okay. Fine.
Potatoes and carrots.
Cook the chicken.
Okay.
I'll have a lot to clean up afterwards.
- What should we have for desserts? - Desserts?
- Ice cream sounds good. - Should I go and buy ice cream?
I want something refreshing.
Have you been the Watermelon Prince?
You totally look like the Watermelon Prince.
You totally look like that now.
By the way, my birthday is in summer.
- On my birthday, - The watermelon?
I finish the entire watermelon all by myself.
- No. Not that. - Watermelons...
The boat...
(Only Jung Sub gets a message.)
My maternal family is...
(Shush! This is a private message only for you.)
(A female participant requests to talk to you in private.)
(Tell the guys you're going to the bathroom...)
(and secretly go to the 19th floor of the adjacent building.)
- "Shush! This is a private..." - A talk in private?
- A talk in private? - What?
- Hold on. But... - Is it Se Seung?
Se Seung is cooking spicy braised chicken at home.
What's going on?
Is it Cho A?
- I don't think it's Se Seung. - Right.
Did she send the food via courier?
No way.
So he can have it on the 19th floor.
It's an ocean in the countryside.
- Where is it? - It's in Namhae.
- Namhae. I've been there. - Yes.
- Namhae... - Namhae, South Gyeongsang Province.
I got a text message that made my heart flutter.
It was so fun.
It was so heart-fluttering.
I wonder who it could be.
Namhae is really nice.
- The ocean... - In Namhae,
- there's the German Village. - There's the German Village.
I went to the German Village during Chuseok this year.
I had a drink with my mom and my sibling.
- Really? - Yes.
(Taking something out)
(Meticulously securing a hand warmer)
It's hot.
I took care of it.
- Excuse me. - Sure.
- Sure. - Sure.
I wondered, "Who requested to see me in private?"
First of all, I didn't think it would be Se Seung.
I already asked her out on a date.
Then it meant it wasn't Se Seung. It had to be someone else.
"Who could it be? Cho A? Ju Yeon?"
"Cho A?"
- Wait. - No?
- Isn't that a new participant? - Isn't that Yun Ha?
- Yun Ha? - Wait.
- I think it's a new participant. - It's a new participant.
- What? Really? - Isn't that Yun Ha?
- That's Yun Ha's hairstyle. - Seriously.
- No! It's someone else! - Yun Ha...
- Who is it? - It's someone else!
- I knew it. - Who is it?
That was so sudden!
- Oh, my! - Why? Why so suddenly?
What? Who is it?
- You must show us her entire face. - Wait.
- Who is it? - Don't tell me...
she's another sister.
Isn't that Yun Ha?
Three siblings?
- That's a new silhouette. - She's a new participant.
- Who is it? A new participant? - No.
- It's a new participant. - It's a new participant.
That was so sudden.
Excuse me. The camera is out of focus.
But that's Yun Ha's hairstyle.
- Right. Yun Ha got a haircut. - Right.
It's a new participant.
Gosh. I knew it.
(You have 10 minutes to talk to each of the 4 men.)
(After 10 minutes, you can choose to continue or stop the talk.)
(The total amount of time you have is limited to 60 minutes.)
(The first man will enter now.)
I didn't see this coming at all.
The moment I got the message, I got nervous.
I thought this might be fun too.
The four of them will keep it a secret from each other...
- and talk to her for ten minutes. - What is this?
That's right.
This is crazy. Seriously.
This is a great chance for the new participant.
Since she's moving in later than the others, she has a benefit.
When I first walked in and looked at her,
I thought it was my sister.
She resembled my sister from the back.
I thought it was silly.
"Why does she want to talk to me secretly?"
I sat down across from her while thinking that.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
"Hold on. Then does this mean..."
"there's a new participant?"
The whole situation was really fun. I mean it.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Ji Won.
- Ji Won? - Won. Yes.
- What's your name? - My name?
My name is Jung Sub.
Jung Sub.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
You must be flustered.
Yes. Aren't you cold?
I'm all right.
- You're not cold? - No.
Here.
Thank you.
What were you doing before coming here?
We...
Hold on.
Take your time.
He's so cute.
- He must be so flustered. - He must be shocked.
- It must be so awkward. - Oh, no.
This came out of the blue. Seriously.
I was having dinner with the guys.
We had a drink.
Hold on. Your name...
- Was it Ji Won? - Ji Won.
- Ji Won? - Yes.
I thought she was a foreigner at first.
She had such distinct facial features.
So I thought, "Gosh, she has strong facial features."
She sort of resembles an actress.
She looks like a foreign actress.
Moni... Wait, no.
Was it Monica?
Anyway, she does resemble someone.
(The silence is suffocating.)
- What's this? - Gosh.
It was funny to watch him so flustered.
I was flustered too.
But when I saw that he was more flustered than me,
I was sort of relieved. That's how I felt.
It's awkward, right? It's awkward for me too.
Why are you moving in so late?
- Me? Right. - Yes.
When did you move into the house?
It's been a while for us.
- A while? - Yes.
- How long? - Our time there is almost over.
It's almost over?
I'm in trouble.
Is today my only chance?
But seriously. How many days has it been?
You'll find out about it over time once you move in.
- Over time? - You'll find out soon enough.
Did you prepare that for us?
This? Yes. I prepared this for us.
- Really? - I cut everything on this plate.
- The drink... - You cut this?
- I'm joking. - Really?
By the way, can you drink?
It's totally fine with me. I was having a drink anyway.
- Should we have a drink? - Shall we?
Your name was Jung Sub, right?
Yes. It's Jung Sub.
Jung Sub.
(There's another silence.)
Hold on.
What's going on?
What should I ask you?
Can I ask you what you do for a living?
My job? We...
We did reveal that.
Is it a secret?
I don't want to tell you everything about me in our first meeting.
You're not telling me anything about yourself. Nothing at all.
You only told me your name so far.
Jung Sub.
- Jung Sub. - Yes. It's Jung Sub.
Okay.
You weren't in the photo album yesterday.
- A photo album? - Yes, there was a photo album.
(He teases her again.)
You're already clearly drawing the line between us.
I'll tell you what we did yesterday.
Yesterday, all of us looked through a photo album which had photos...
of our childhood.
That must've been fun.
It really was fun.
Why are you moving in so late?
I was working.
- You were working? - Yes.
What do you do for a living?
I work in the entertainment business.
I oversee artists' development.
- In the entertainment business? - Yes.
I work in the entertainment business.
I work in the Artist Development Department.
Overall, the melody instruments sound pretty weak.
I think you moved forward too much.
You shouldn't put it in the middle. People can't see it then.
First of all, I love music.
I find joy in supporting other people...
and helping them shine. That brings me happiness.
So I started out as a manager.
I worked as a manager for over two years.
Now, I started working on developing artists which had been my dream.
I started to grow my career on this path.
(Ji Won, the team leader of Artists and Repertoire)
So you oversee their development. What do you develop?
Do you develop everything?
I help my artists produce albums.
Artists as in musicians?
- Yes. That's my department. - I see.
When she explained about her job,
she was very calm.
Her calmness was different from Cho A's calm vibe.
I thought, "I didn't know she could be this calm."
"How interesting."
- Do you like to cook? - I do.
- Really? - But I'm not good at it.
- I like cooking too. - Are you good at it?
But I didn't get a chance to cook a proper meal here.
What kind of food can you cook well?
- I want to try cooking pasta. - Pasta.
I can grill some steak too.
I'll enjoy that.
When I talked to Jung Sub, it was clear that...
he was good...
at making his conversation partner feel at ease.
I thought we would be able to bond while living together.
I think I felt less nervous...
because Jung Sub was the first guy I talked to.
- Cooking aglio e olio is hard. - Is it?
You need cooking oil for that.
Did you get a call?
- I got a message. - Is that so?
(10 minutes have passed.)
(Will you continue your conversation with Jung Sub?)
(You now have 50 minutes left.)
She must decide whether to continue it or not.
Deciding whether to continue it or not...
It looks like she won't do it, right?
- I don't think she will. - I think she will.
- I think she will. - I think she will.
- No, I don't think she will. - I don't think so.
I could tell earlier that she liked him.
- I don't think she'll continue. - This is her first day.
I think she has to meet as many men as possible.
They'll text Jung Sub now.
"Come out."
"Go back to the bar where the guys are."
(10 minutes have passed.)
(Will you continue your conversation with Jung Sub?)
(You now have 50 minutes left.)
(Ji Won texts back without hesitation.)
(And Jung Sub is clueless.)
(She's done responding to the message.)
So you should cook aglio e olio for us one day.
(She goes back to talking about aglio e olio.)
I'll try cooking it.
- I'll cook it one day. - I'll look forward to it.
You can.
Excuse me.
(The secret conversation is over. Please leave the bar.)
It's over.
- I told you. - For real?
What is this?
- I feel bad for him. - "Please leave the bar."
Isn't that too mean?
They tried to be as polite as possible.
I don't think that means she didn't like him.
- Right. - Of course not.
That makes me curious, though.
(The secret conversation is over. Please leave the bar.)
Our allotted time...
for conversation is up here.
It's a shame.
I'll see you there.
I felt like we talked for like five minutes.
It was such a short conversation.
It was my first time meeting her,
and in terms of looks,
she gave off such a different vibe.
She was really chill and calm too.
I liked her at first sight...
because of the vibe her looks gave off.
Anyway, it was an impressive encounter...
in many ways.
It was a good stimulus.
I'm going to go now. See you later.
(Ji Won and Jung Sub's secret conversation has ended.)
I felt like I figured him out...
from the vibe I first got from him.
He seemed too flustered.
He seemed to be struggling more than I was.
I was mostly thinking that I should send home quickly.
That's why I didn't extend the time.
(Meanwhile, the men have no idea.)
Where is Jung Sub, though?
I know. Where is he?
Did he get lost on his way?
I hope he brings ice cream as a surprise.
(Coming back empty-handed)
You're back.
I almost called the police...
- I'm sorry. - to report you missing.
- Where is ice cream? - I'm so sorry.
- Were you on the phone? - What happened?
I had a stomach ache.
- An upset stomach? - Yes.
- Are you okay? - I'm good now.
You look pale now.
Take it easy.
The bathroom outside was too cold.
(I see.)
I thought something happened to him...
or he had an upset stomach.
- What were you talking about? - We weren't talking.
We almost reported you missing.
I'm so sorry.
- Promise not to do it again. - I promise.
So you feel better now, right?
Yes. I feel much better.
(Successfully overcoming the crisis)
(Shush! This is a private message only for you.)
(A female participant requests to talk to you in private.)
(Tell the guys you're going to the bathroom...)
(and secretly go to the 19th floor of the adjacent building.)
I was holding it this way.
- This way? - Right.
I thought it was the other way.
- No, it was like this. - Like this.
(He's busy alone.)
- Let me go to the bathroom. - Yes, go ahead.
That's cute.
It's so obvious.
He picked it up.
- Look at his face. - He knows what's going on.
- Look at his face. - "Here it comes."
- This is so much fun. - This is killing me.
- Let me go to the bathroom. - Yes, go ahead.
Jae Hyung was obviously awkward.
When he said, "Let me use the bathroom,"
it was so awkward and unnatural.
I thought he was going to meet her too...
and wondered what kind of conversation they'd have.
I think Ji Won's sibling could be Jae Hyung.
They look similar in a way.
I thought the crew also sent Jae Hyung...
to confuse us.
Jae Hyung has strong facial features.
Since she also did,
I thought they had similar vibes.
Did you really have an upset stomach?
- Yes. - Okay.
Okay, what?
(Entering the building carefully)
When I only saw her from the side and the back,
I thought it was Yun Ha because of the hairstyle.
I never thought it could be someone new.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Ji Won.
- Ji Won? - Yes.
- What's your name? - Jae Hyung.
My name is Jae Hyung.
- Jae Hyung? - Yes.
Happy to meet you.
Who are you?
- "Who are you?" - "Who are you?"
Who... Oh, dear.
- Well, I arrived today. - I see.
She's moving in.
Someone new is moving in.
I see.
I heard you were having a meal.
Yes.
Have you eaten?
Yes, I have.
My first impression of her was intense.
She had smoky eye makeup on,
and the tone of her voice sounded quite serious.
Also, her outfit looked a little hip.
You must be thrown off.
Well, yes.
- It's a little fun, though. - Really?
(Becoming serious)
- Shall we toast? - Shall we?
Is this wine?
Yes, white wine.
I feel like I'm pretending to be elegant.
Do you like wine?
Yes, I do.
Can you hold your liquor?
I enjoy drinking, but I can't drink a lot.
Do you enjoy drinking?
I do enjoy it too.
I see. What's your favourite drink?
My favourite is soju.
- Do you like soju? - Yes.
You're the first person I've met who said they liked soju.
- Have some. - What is it? Jerky?
Yes.
It's so good.
- Have you tried it? - I have.
You did.
Am I the first participant you met?
- I met Jung Sub earlier. - You met Jung Sub?
Yes. Jung Sub.
So...
who is the woman you want to be the closest to?
Do I have to name her?
- I will just say there is one. - What?
I'll just say there's someone I want to be close to.
Okay.
(Brother-in-law Hunter wonders who it could be.)
(Cheol Hyeon suddenly leaves.)
- Now only the two of us are left. - Yes.
So why don't you drop me a hint?
Jung Sub, you might know who she is.
- What? - You might know...
- even without a hint. - I don't think so.
- You don't? - I have no idea.
(They don't back down.)
(Cheol Hyeon returns quickly.)
(Quiet)
(Jung Sub couldn't figure it out in the end.)
Did you all get closer?
At least, the men are quite close.
Some of us...
are close to the women, and some are not.
It hasn't been that long since we moved in.
She must feel thankful...
- for him to say that. - Right.
- It will put her at ease. - Yes.
Are you a good cook?
- Making food? - Making food?
- I'm good at making food. - As in meal kits?
Yes. I'm an amazing meal kit cook.
Are you good at cooking?
No, but I like cooking.
When I cook, it's edible.
I'm better at making Korean food...
than Western food.
- Is Korean food your favourite? - Yes.
- Is it your favourite cuisine? - Korean food is my favourite.
(10 minutes have passed.)
(Will you continue your conversation with Jae Hyung?)
(You now have 40 minutes left.)
In that situation, she would extend the time...
- because she feels comfortable. - Right.
Also, she's smiling a lot more than when she was with Jung Sub.
- I don't think she would extend it. - Extend it.
(10 minutes have passed.)
(Will you continue your conversation with Jae Hyung?)
(You now have 40 minutes left.)
What's your favourite food?
I like meat.
Is there a specific cut you prefer...
like pork belly?
- I love beef the most. - Beef.
Yes. I like pork too.
I'm also good at grilling meat.
You are?
Yes.
(The secret conversation is over. Please leave the bar.)
They told me to leave.
- Why is he just sitting there? - He's saying that...
to the person who made him leave.
I like that he's frank.
Gosh, Jae Hyung.
They told me to leave.
(Ji Won didn't continue her conversation with Jae Hyung.)
They did? I guess time is up.
- I'll see you later. - See you.
I wondered why the conversation was too short.
(Ji Won and Jae Hyung's secret conversation has ended.)
Jae Hyung is the person who got me flustered the most.
It made me miss Jung Sub a little.
Jae Hyung...
seemed like a free spirit.
I saw a lot of similarities...
between him and the men I had dated.
His carefree nature...
made me think we were different.
When I first saw Ji Won,
I was a little startled.
Her hairstyle,
outfit, and makeup...
reminded me a lot of my ex-girlfriend.
It made me remember...
the unpleasant memories...
from my past relationship.
With those memories overlapping our conversation...
I wouldn't say I didn't like our encounter,
but those memories just occurred to me.
So it made me feel emotionally closed off.
That's how I felt.
- At the first encounter? - That changes things, then.
They would never end up together.
How can they both see their exes in complete strangers?
- That's possible. - Were they too hurt?
- There's no chance between them. - But it might...
rather make them attracted to each other more.
- What? - As they spend time together.
- Really? - Yes.
That can happen.
It's fascinating how they thought the same thing.
- It really is. - At the same time.
(Trying to keep a straight face)
You're back.
Is it cold outside?
Yes. They said my mic was weird.
- I see. - Right.
Gosh!
(He can't hold his laughter.)
Jae Hyung's unique way of handling things...
seemed to backfire.
He was overacting.
I wondered if he was acting like that on purpose...
after meeting his own sibling.
(The house in Seorae Village)
(Yun Ha returns home.)
- Hello. - Who is it?
It's Yun Ha.
Are you alone?
- Were you bored? - I'm alone.
- Really? - Yes.
You must've been bored.
I'll make something delicious for you.
- You'll eat now, right? - Yes.
Did we finish the perilla leaves?
- I think so. - We did?
It's quite bland.
- Bland foods are healthy. - It's a little bland.
- Is it good? - It's tasty.
- Really? - Yes.
It's not bland.
- For real? - Yes.
I'm glad.
Do you know where the men went?
No. Only they know.
I see.
It's their own secret.
What time will everyone be back?
- But it was so... - You got a message.
(Shush! This is a private message only for you.)
(A female participant requests to talk to you in private.)
(Tell the guys you're going to the bathroom...)
(and secretly go to the 19th floor of the adjacent building.)
I wondered who it could be for a moment.
I didn't think it was Ju Yeon.
I thought it'd be Se Seung.
- Cheol Hyeon, go! - Cheol Hyeon is coming.
This is your chance to turn the tables.
- Things are going well for him. - This is fun.
They don't expect to have a new participant at all.
I...
- Go ahead. - Yes. Go ahead.
(Cheol Hyeon leaves.)
I want to go to the bathroom too.
(Yong Woo also leaves.)
You've been there, right?
I don't know what you mean.
We both went there.
I went to the bathroom.
(Laughing)
(Avoiding eye contact)
(Checking outside again)
There's always something every day.
Every single day.
It's better to stay alert.
Right.
(Closing his mouth shut)
It's so close, right? It's right here.
- Yes. - The bathroom.
(Meanwhile, Cheol Hyeon)
(This is the entrance.)
(Thankfully, he found the building.)
When I went into the bar,
I thought it was Yun Ha from a distance.
"Is it Yun Ha? She looks like her from the side."
"Yun Ha wanted to see me."
"Why did she request to see me?"
"We barely talked."
"Okay. Let me take this opportunity to have a talk with her."
That's what I was thinking, going in.
As I got close to her,
- I realized she wasn't Yun Ha. - Hello.
- Hello. - Glad to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
My name is JI Won.
- Ji Won? - Yes.
- My name is Cheol Hyeon. - Cheol Hyeon?
- Cheol Hyeon. - Cheol Hyeon? Good to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I thought she was hip.
She seemed hip.
She seemed fashionable.
I thought we could have a lot...
to talk about in that sense.
When I first saw Cheol Hyeon,
I thought his bob hairstyle was stylish.
"I'm glad I don't have a bob haircut."
I thought that because it really suited him.
I was like, "I would have lost."
I see.
You don't seem too confused.
- I'm very confused. - Is that so?
You barely touched this.
No. I had some.
You're wearing the same colour as I am.
- That's true. It's similar. - Right?
- But your outfit looks warmer. - Is that so?
Aren't you cold?
I'm good. What about you?
I feel so warm.
- I'm wearing lots of layers inside. - Lots of layers.
Did you adjust well?
Yes. Everyone is so nice.
I have a good feeling about them.
He looked at her while taking a sip.
We have plenty of time, so let's enjoy ourselves.
Are you going to stay with us?
Then...
Then why would I be here?
Did you think I would leave after seeing you?
- I was curious. - I see.
Were you wondering who I was?
- Yes. - I get it.
- Right. - I'm moving into the house...
- I'm glad to have you. - to stay with you guys today.
- Nice to meet you. - Happy to meet you.
- Please take good care of me. - Me too.
Oh, my!
(Exclaiming 3 times)
Are there any sports you enjoy?
- Badminton and tennis. - Tennis.
- I enjoy bowling too. - How about soccer?
We went bowling two days ago.
- You did? - Yes.
It depends on the day.
When it goes bad,
- it goes bad until the end. - Right.
When I get a strike, I'm on a strike streak.
- I totally get that. - So...
- I think you got a message. - Let me see.
(10 minutes have passed.)
(Will you continue your conversation with Cheol Hyeon?)
(You now have 30 minutes left.)
It looks like all of you got quite close.
I'll adjust quickly too, right?
I'll help you along.
Thanks.
He had lots of questions.
Cheol Hyeon asked me so many questions...
that ten minutes passed the fastest when I was with him.
(Ji Won extended her time with Cheol Hyeon.)
- She extended the time! - Good job.
That was the right move.
- You should ask lots of questions. - That went well.
- I knew they would hit it off. - Right.
- They have similar tones of voice. - They're similar.
Ji Won is an attentive listener.
Our conversations went well. I'm curious about her.
It seems she's interested in fashion.
That's the impression I had.
I think we'd get along well.
She left a good first impression.
(The conversation between the 2 lasted for an extra 10 minutes.)
Shall we take a picture?
- Sure. - Sorry?
- Let's take a picture. - Let's do it.
- Should we take a photo like this? - Did you bring the Polaroid camera?
- This angle would be better. - What?
It's so random.
In 1, 2, 3.
Done.
My mouth is twitching.
Cheol Hyeon took longer to come back...
than I had thought.
"What? He's taking a very long time."
"They're talking for a really long time."
That's what I thought.
You have a stylish hairstyle.
- I do? - You look better with a bob...
than women do.
I'm not that good at styling my hair.
How do I look today? Do you think it's done nicely?
- Yes, it is. - Is it okay? Is it not flat?
It's voluminous.
- It is? - Yes. I think it's done nicely.
Has someone other than me visited you before?
Yes.
I talked with 2 people 1st.
You're the third.
I think I was given a chance to talk to everyone...
as I came late.
What is it like living in the house?
They're nice people. It's great.
You'll feel it immediately when you come to the house.
You'll know they're good people.
- I can feel it. - Is that so? That's great.
It seems you really like people.
- Right? - I think so.
I've been thinking that a lot since I moved in.
I love people.
- I see. - I'm sad when each day passes.
That's nice.
- I do think I'm different... - I see.
when I work and when I don't.
(10 minutes have passed.)
(Will you continue your conversation with Cheol Hyeon?)
(You now have 20 minutes left.)
(The secret conversation is over. Please leave the bar.)
It's over for me now.
- I see. - Let's drink one last time.
See you in the house.
- Yes. That's great. - Please help me a lot.
- See you then. - See you.
(Ji Won and Cheol Hyeon's secret conversation has ended.)
I didn't know that much time had passed.
I think we had a nice conversation.
Cheol Hyeon seemed to be very sensitive as well.
I thought we could talk about many things...
as we're like-minded.
(He returns after 20 minutes of secret conversation.)
- It was fun. - You ordered more food.
- We ordered just now. - It took really long.
Where have you been?
We ordered as many as two more dishes...
- as you were not coming. - Right.
They reheated it a little. It's delicious.
(He's quiet unlike usual.)
- The squid was so good. - Yes.
It was so good...
- that I'm still thinking about it. - It was so good.
The squid with whole heads of garlic was amazing.
I do want to eat it again.
- Squid with garlic, please. - Let's order just one more.
- One squid with garlic, sir? - Yes. Thank you.
I heard some places bone it for you.
(Shush! This is a private message only for you.)
(A female participant requests to talk to you in private.)
(Tell the guys you're going to the bathroom...)
(and secretly go to the 19th floor of the adjacent building.)
Only then the puzzle pieces came together.
Each of them went somewhere.
I don't think any of them can become an actor.
They were coming in while acting so awkwardly.
(I have a stomachache.)
(You have a stomachache?)
"What's the matter with him?"
(He made a strange excuse somehow.)
"Does he have something to do?"
(He was quiet, which felt strange somehow.)
We ordered as many as two more dishes.
"Are they hiding something from me?"
I did have thoughts like that, to be honest.
(Who was the most obvious?)
Cheol Hyeon.
When I'm with him...
Our eyes meet the most often...
when we open the pink envelope.
I think we look at each other almost at the same time.
I can see his facial expression at that moment.
And it happened several times.
So I know the face he makes...
when he has concerns or questions.
He can't hide it.
I saw that facial expression.
So I knew something was going on.
Excuse me for a moment.
- Sure. - Yes.
Should I get you Melona? Or is it Haagen-Dazs?
Haagen-Dazs, please.
(He's leaving in a relaxed manner while making a joke.)
Gosh.
- Will he talk with her... - He's the last one.
more than ten minutes?
- Somehow... - I think he will.
She knows he's the last one anyway.
- And she has enough time. - Right.
I had no idea.
"It must be one of the girls in the house."
"But who would it be?" That's exactly what I thought.
I think the other guys had thought the same way.
I thought it might be Yun Ha.
She had long black hair.
She had bangs, she had a high nose too.
"Is it Yun Ha?" That's what I thought at first.
- Hello. - Hello.
"What? Did I come to the wrong place?"
I'm Ji Won.
- Ji Won? - Ji Won.
- It's nice to meet you. - What's your name?
I'm Yong Woo.
- Yong Woo? - Yes.
- It's nice to meet you. - It's nice to meet you.
Who are you?
- I'll be living with you... - Okay.
starting from today.
- Is that so? - Yes.
I'm glad to meet you.
- Please help me a lot. - I'll need your help too.
If I were to talk about her image, she was like Cleopatra.
With black straight hair and bangs.
She looked exotic.
And the place was amazing.
It was located on a high floor. It was on the 19th floor...
with an open view of Han River.
I think it was a city view.
She was sitting there alone,
crossing her legs with a glass of wine.
She looked charismatic at that moment.
This place is beautiful.
- Right? - Yes.
I was enjoying it.
- I see. Shall we? Yes. - Shall we have a drink?
- It's nice to meet you. - It's nice to meet you.
What is it like living in the house?
It's very fun.
I'm having a lot of fun.
Can I call it home?
- It feels like home now. - Already?
- I sleep more deeply... - You do?
than I did in my home.
I've been nervous since this morning.
The anxiety tired me out now.
- You were nervous. - I'm not nervous because I'm tired.
Make yourself comfortable now.
- Ji Won. - Yes.
I'm pleased to meet you.
Can I ask you a question now?
You met me, who has been living there.
How do you feel now that you've seen me?
- I'm relieved. - You are?
- It seems you've been doing well. - Yes.
I think you feel very comfortable in the house,
which makes me think living there would be better than I thought.
I'm so excited.
- And now that I'm looking at you, - Yes.
How is it?
- I feel very comfortable now. - you look very relaxed.
I came out nonchalantly.
So I was a little surprised.
Who were you expecting to see?
I couldn't imagine.
It got more complicated in my head.
Because it might mean one of their siblings...
hasn't come yet.
I started to have complicated thoughts,
so I stopped thinking about it.
- Do you like travelling? - I love it.
Can I ask...
- which place was your favourite? - Well...
I went to Europe by myself...
when I was a junior in college.
Was it just a while ago?
What? Well...
It's a joke.
I almost answered it.
What do you do?
I'm a pilot.
- You are? - Yes.
- It suits you. - Do you think so?
I'm working hard to become an aviation instructor...
in Korean airlines...
and aviation academies in America.
- I see. - That's what I do.
I'm working...
- for an entertainment company. - An entertainment company?
I'm working in the artist production team.
So you're producing singers...
- and artists in the team. - You're right.
Excuse me.
(10 minutes have passed.)
(Will you continue your conversation with Yong Woo?)
(You now have 10 minutes left.)
(I will continue.)
Yes.
He seemed strong-minded...
with a lot of experience.
It seemed he was the most mature one among the four.
I thought he was someone...
I could rely on.
- She felt it at that moment. - I think everyone said so.
Because he looks reliable.
Right.
It was the first time we met,
but I wondered if I was too comfortable around her.
I felt very comfortable...
when we were talking.
(Meanwhile, Cheol Hyeon really went to the restroom.)
I was so surprised.
You're so cute.
I was shocked.
I felt a sudden surge of energy inside.
- Right? - I felt a dopamine rush.
Right.
- It got me so surprised. - It's so interesting.
The night view was amazing.
I even took a photo.
This is fun. It suddenly became so interesting.
You felt a sudden dopamine rush, didn't you?
Yes.
I asked her...
if she had talked about MBTI with others. She said no.
So I asked what type she was.
She's ENFJ.
Isn't it so interesting?
- Everyone is a judging type. - Someone else is the same type.
- ENFJ? That's Se Seung. - Yes.
I knew it.
If she's the judging type as well, Yun Ha is...
the only one who is a perceiving type.
Cho A is the only introvert while the others are all extroverts.
It's like living on an island by yourself.
But this new person must've come with someone.
I know.
It suddenly came to my mind.
Who would it be?
She said...
I was the least perplexed one.
- So you were calm? - When I first entered the place...
I wasn't calm.
I didn't think she would be living with us.
I was just like, "What's going on?"
Right. "What's going on?" It was more like that for me too.
She had long black hair...
with bangs.
I thought it was Yun Ha.
- Oh, right. - Me too.
- "Is it Yun Ha?" - Me too.
I was like that when I entered the bar, but I was wrong.
- When I entered, I thought... - Everyone had the same thought.
- it was Yun Ha. - I thought it was Yun Ha.
Yes. Me too.
When I saw this part of her face,
- I realized she wasn't Yun Ha. - Right.
- Right. - It was the same for me.
- I was like that too. - "Who are you?"
- Right. - "Who are you?"
Everyone had the same thought. That gives me goosebumps.
Is there a room for her?
No, there isn't.
- Does it mean... - No one knows.
Is there a third floor?
- There might be basement level two. - Now, something...
I didn't even imagine is happening.
I see.
If it's your fifth day,
have you developed feelings for someone?
It's hard to say I have feelings for someone.
But there is someone I'd like to talk with more.
- There's someone... - Yes.
- you'd like to talk with more. - Yes, there is.
Is there someone you wanted to talk with more?
Yes, there is.
There is someone I'd like to talk with more.
What do you like to do...
when you have free time?
I just like meeting my friends. Talking...
and eating delicious food.
You can't resist good food.
Does it suit your taste?
- This? - Yes.
- It seems you didn't eat anything. - You didn't eat anything, right?
No, I didn't. Have you?
- I've tried this and this. - I see.
Which one is better?
This one.
- This one is the best? - Yes.
- I'll go with this one then. - Try this.
Let me have a bite too.
I think it's the snack I know.
(Savouring)
Do you like sports?
- Truffle. - Sorry?
- Truffle. - Truffle?
- Yes. - I asked about sports.
- Sports? - What did you hear?
I must be crazy about food.
I thought you said sauce.
Sauce?
- Sauce? Oh, my gosh. - Sauce?
Isn't his attitude a little different...
from when he's with other women?
He became suave somehow.
- I know. - Yes.
It seems he likes to look more masculine...
- rather than being kind... - Right.
to her.
I can't believe he changed so much.
So your favourite sauce is the one with truffle.
I know you didn't ask.
I run a lot these days.
How about you?
Sports? I like racket sports.
- Like tennis. - Tennis?
I do want to try tennis...
- and see how it is. - It's fun. You'll be good at it.
How long have you been doing it?
I haven't done it long enough to say.
I'm just doing it for fun.
That's what you say, but...
- You might smash the ball. - I might spike it.
You might smash the ball onto someone's face.
No.
Unlike her appearance that reminded me of Cleopatra,
she talked gently and humorously.
Although she was wearing a shy smile,
she wasn't really hesitant to speak her mind.
I enjoyed the conversation.
People who don't...
(The secret conversation with all male participants has ended.)
(You can choose one of them to go out with tonight.)
(You will also have a Benefit Date with the participant tomorrow.)
(Send the name of the participant you want.)
- What? - With one of them?
- Right away? - What?
- Tonight? - Oh, my gosh.
As she came late, she received great benefits.
- I know. - Yes.
But I think it's reasonable.
- Honestly. - Five days have passed.
- Yes. - They should make up for it.
Absolutely.
- It must be confusing. - Who would she choose?
Yong Woo.
Don't you think she'll choose Cheol Hyeon?
- I think she'll choose Cheol Hyeon. - It'll be Cheol Hyeon.
You think so?
It'll become legendary if she chooses Jae Hyung here.
(He's a legendary fan of Jae Hyung.)
- She'll never choose him. - Thinking about the old memories.
Ji Won, can you please choose him?
(The secret conversation with all male participants has ended.)
(You can choose one of them to go out with tonight.)
(You will also have a Benefit Date with the participant tomorrow.)
(Send the name of the participant you want.)
(Yong Woo received a message as well.)
(The secret conversation is over. Please leave the bar.)
I guess you received a text. I received one as well.
I think they're closing the bar now.
Yes. I'll see you again in the house.
I'll get going first.
See you in the house.
- See you. - Yes.
(Ji Won and Yong Woo's secret conversation has ended.)
Was there a long line...
- for the restroom? - You're back.
I left just now.
Did something happen?
- Oh, my. - He's better than us.
(Ji Won is contemplating alone.)
I contemplated a lot.
I was torn between Jung Sub and Yong Woo.
- What? - It wasn't Cheol Hyeon?
- Wait. - I think I'm so oblivious.
Wait. Jung Sub?
He was the first one she met, and he wasn't bad.
I guess she moved on for no particular reason then.
After meeting everyone, she compared them.
And she thought about the first person she met.
Really?
- It would be Jung Sub, right? - Yes. She talked with Yong Woo...
- for twice as long. - Right.
I liked...
their calm energy.
I'm more drown...
to a calm and strong-minded person...
these days.
Rather than those who were bright and bubbly...
based on the first impression,
I preferred...
the calm ones.
If Jung Sub hadn't been the first person I met,
I would've wanted to continue the conversation.
(She's writing a name after much consideration.)
(Ji Won made her choice.)
I don't know.
- The time... - It'd be the standard time, right?
- I got a text. - What?
I received a text.
- Oh, gosh. - Oh, gosh.
Oh, my.
(Ji Won, the new female participant...)
(you had a secret conversation with today, chose Yong Woo as her date.)
(Yong Woo, please move now.)
We received the same text, didn't we?
I think we did.
- Yong Woo? - Yong Woo?
Really?
- I didn't expect this at all. - All my predictions are wrong.
- He's busy. - Yong Woo is so popular.
I was honestly bewildered.
It seemed like I was the only one who was going somewhere else.
It felt good,
but at the same time, I think I was a bit puzzled.
I wonder why.
I'm going to...
- You should get going. - I should... Yes.
I'll get going now.
- Yes, see you. - All right.
And he was never seen again.
Well, I'm going to go now.
- Yes, see you. - Bye.
(Yong Woo gets up first.)
I felt...
- the confidence of a winner. - His confidence.
He's amazing.
The four of us were reading that text and we went,
"I see."
"I see, so this is what it's like."
That was it, and Yong Woo...
Yong Woo must be feeling good.
"It's me again."
What kind of conversation led the new participant...
to choose him after such a short time?
To be honest, I kind of...
wanted to see what he's like.
I wanted to watch and learn what I could.
(Maybe she chose him because he fits her ideal type?)
That could be it, but...
You're right.
That could be it.
Right, I didn't think of that.
Anyway, I guess I felt a bit disappointed.
I thought we connected.
I think I was in denial.
Gosh, this is interesting.
How could they send the text like that?
I guess letting us know like this is better.
Amazing.
Interesting.
(With the exception of Yong Woo, the men head home.)
I think Cheol Hyeon tends to say...
"interesting" when he's in a bad mood.
It's like a rock...
- fell into a calm lake. - Yes.
- Right. - He thinks it's interesting.
Gosh, this is so interesting.
- What's going on? - This is really interesting.
(Cheol Hyeon and Jung Sub are laughing.)
(Jae Hyung is laughing.)
I feel disoriented.
It's late at night. Yong Woo should...
hurry home and go to sleep.
He's my roommate.
If he comes back in the middle of the night,
- he'll wake me up. - I have work tomorrow.
I have to go to work tomorrow.
He'll be rustling about late at night.
I feel...
so good.
- The food was good. - Right. The food was good.
We can come back for the squid.
- I'm never coming back. - I won't.
Really?
I really enjoyed the squid.
I guess Yong Woo would come back.
I see.
Was I too caught up in the squid?
When three or more men are gathered together,
their collective intelligence tends to drop.
It drops accurately, little by little.
Is that why the three of us are like this right now?
It drops.
So what should we say?
- What? - Where's Yong Woo?
He had some personal business to take care of...
His own personal business?
- Yes. Personal business. - Well, it is personal.
His actual personal matter.
- It really is personal. - Right.
- Gosh, this is nice. - Gosh.
(Jung Sub is thinking.)
(Cheol Hyeon is sighing)
We're here.
(They feel bitter tonight.)
(They arrived home unenthusiastically.)
(The door won't open.)
We're at the right place, right?
(The gate is locked.)
Please open the gate for us.
- What? - Hello.
- Are you finally back? - Let us in, please.
I mean, excuse me, guys.
It's past curfew, so we locked the gate.
- We're sorry. - You were taking too long.
- I see. - We were hanging out by ourselves.
They're finally home.
They were so late, and they even broke curfew.
It was past midnight.
(You have a curfew?)
No.
That's how I let them know I was disappointed.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Where have you been, Cheol Hyeon?
(They're in trouble as soon as they're inside.)
We just had dinner.
- What did you do, Jung Sub? - We ate and had drinks.
- We had dinner, - Yes.
- and we had drinks and snacks. - I see.
- It was great. - We had such a good time.
- I see. - Yes.
Sounds nice.
(They managed to pass one obstacle.)
Did you have a good time?
The food was very delicious.
What did you eat?
- We went to some kind of tent bar, - What...
- I see. You're back. - We just ate...
- a variety of food. - Hi, Ju Yeon.
- Hello. - But the best one...
- was the squid. The whole squid. - Hello.
Squid and garlic?
Was it delicious as you ate without us?
- Yes. - I see.
No, it wasn't delicious.
(He seems a little drunk.)
Where's Yong Woo?
We were drinking together, but Yong Woo...
had to go somewhere...
because of personal business.
Something personal came up so he had to go.
(I see.)
I thought he got into trouble.
I thought maybe he pretended to be busy and went somewhere.
(Yong Woo is busy.)
Hello. Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you too.
The door is closed now.
You seemed too cold.
I see. Me?
- Yes, so I closed it. - Thank you so much.
Do you want a hand warmer?
No, you keep it. I'm fine.
- You don't need this... - No, I'm good on the hand warmer.
Touch it. You're going to want to use it.
You want it right? I have one too.
Thank you so much.
- We'll each have... Yes. - We'll each have one?
We've met again. Sooner than expected.
You're not tired, are you?
- Me? - Are you tired?
No,
- I slept well today. - Are you okay?
I think I feel great today.
It's cold, so I thought about just letting you go home,
but still, I thought we didn't talk enough.
- So I requested to talk with you. - Gosh.
Cheers.
Recently, Ive been feeling like...
I want to meet someone...
I can rely on.
It seemed like Yong Woo had the traits of someone like that.
I think that's why I felt comfortable with Yong Woo,
but also a little tense.
I think I chose him because...
he's someone I want to like,
someone I want to experience liking, and someone I want to date.
Were you nervous on the first day?
Of course. I was nervous before entering the house.
I still remember how I felt.
I loosened up quicker than I had expected.
You feel like a veteran right now.
- Me? - The veteran of the house.
Are you ready?
Are you ready to introduce yourself and showcase your talents?
Showcase my talents?
Show me what you showcased first.
Me? That's why I'm a veteran.
You can't see mine.
Wouldn't that be condescending of you?
- You got me. - You're being condescending.
You got me right here.
He's very different.
How he talks is different.
Do you have any talents to showcase? Are you good at anything?
No. I'm not good at anything.
You're saying no because you don't want to do it.
I learned that this is how you deal with condescending people.
There must be a lot of them around you.
(Right here)
No comment.
It feels like I'm somehow drawn into Ji Won.
- Right, she has a magnetic charm. - Yes.
- Something about her. - When she speaks,
I find myself focusing on her.
To be honest, I like to tease people.
- I like messing with people. - Messing with people.
You're very mean.
- No, I'm not mean. - You're such a mean person.
You teased me by saying I was condescending.
- Well, this could be tension, - Yes.
or it could be discomfort since I'm with a condescending person.
Is there one nearby? I don't see any.
Is someone else here?
I thought it was just the two of us.
Do you hear that often? That you're condescending?
I think this is the first time I'm hearing it.
- Really? - But it's rather funny...
- That can't be. - because of that.
Here you go again.
- So this is how it is. Got it. - Wait.
- You're starting to tease me. - Yes.
Condescending people are good at teasing.
- Wait. - I like this.
They're going back and forth between speaking casually and formally.
- Freely. - Back and forth.
He's showing off his charms.
- He's so charming. - It feels like there's...
nothing Yong Woo can't do.
I'm really getting drawn into him.
I like this side of him so much.
Patricia, are you into him?
I think I like this side of him.
How so?
- Doesn't he feel manly? - Like he's in control.
Yes, like he's in control of the situation.
But we're not here to find your match, Patricia.
- So you should... - Right, I just meant he seems nice.
- I... - You have orange on your mouth.
What's going on?
- You could have told me in private. - Orange?
You have orange on your mouth.
- There's orange. I'll get it off. - It's cute.
That hurts. Stop it.
- It hurts? - Yes.
Between older, same age, and younger,
which age difference do you prefer?
I say it doesn't matter to me,
but in reality, I think I've dated older women a lot.
I don't know why exactly,
but looking back, I think that was the case.
Now that a little time has passed,
I don't think it's really that important anymore.
Do I seem older or younger?
You could be a lot younger than me in age,
but something about the way you think and speak...
feels a little sophisticated.
- You wrapped it up nicely. - Was it all right?
- Nice. - It was a success.
That was nice.
What about me?
Something about you makes me feel like we're the same age.
- You think we're the same age? - Yes.
I feel neither uncomfortable nor comfortable.
That energy people who are the same age feel.
Then which one do you prefer?
I've never given much thought to guys who are younger,
but age isn't important.
- You sound like you're my age. - That's what...
- I know. - You're saying...
- the exact same thing I said. - We sound the same.
That's why I said I felt like we were the same age.
So you didn't just copy what I said just now?
No. I've been feeling the exact same way.
I think we'll be similar in age.
- You think we'll be similar in age? - Yes.
We'll see.
I almost forgot. It's supposed to snow tomorrow.
- Right. I heard it's going to snow. - There's going to be snow tomorrow.
It'll be amazing if it really does.
Right.
It'll be so pretty, right?
Cho A, are you just now eating?
- Yes. - Gosh.
Someone's here.
(It's not the one he's been waiting for.)
(Smiling awkwardly)
Jae Hyung is checking who comes in.
He knows someone has to arrive.
Yes, right. He's hoping it's Ji Won.
What? Are you making rice?
(He's almost like a meerkat.)
I guess she's not.
- Mapo tofu? - What?
"Mapo tofu?" I mean, what did you say just now?
- I guess she's not. - "I guess she's not."
- That was funny. - I must be hungry.
Maybe you're sleepy.
- Mapo tofu was funny. - That might be it.
Where's Yong Woo?
- He had some personal business. - I see.
It was really personal,
so he left in a hurry, all of a sudden.
Yong Woo didn't come home.
They kept saying something came up.
I was curious about what it could be,
and I was worried about him. That was how I felt.
They believed me.
My acting was good at the time. It was really good.
- You must all be tired. - We're okay.
We all had a good time.
What? It's here.
(On the fifth day, who made your heart flutter?)
(Cho A sighs.)
(Typing)
(Someone is being loud again today.)
Who keeps typing loudly on their phone?
Me.
I just sent what I really felt.
I really wanted Yong Woo to return quickly.
I was quite conflicted.
I think I was conflicted for a second.
I just sent a message to the person I had feelings for.
What kind of food do you like?
I like spicy food.
What kind of spicy food is delicious?
Do you eat chicken feet?
I do eat boneless chicken feet.
What else is spicy?
What is this?
We both got messages at the same time.
(On the fifth day, who made your heart flutter?)
(Send the name and message, and we will deliver it anonymously.)
(Yong Woo is having a hard time typing his message.)
He's conflicted because of Ji Won.
It used to be Cho A. His heart was set on Cho A.
Right, from the very beginning.
How would Cho A feel?
To be honest, he did talk to Ji Won a lot more today.
Yes. He could choose Ji Won for the day.
- Right. - They send messages every day.
Still.
(Smiling)
It takes me a while to understand.
There's someone called Cheol Hyeon.
- Yes. - Whenever we get messages,
we look at each other.
Is it like, "Did I get this right?"
No. It's about who's going to ask twice first.
(He's saying anything.)
(So far, there was no hesitation for him.)
I think I was seriously conflicted at the time.
(To. Cho A)
(You did good...)
- Gosh. - Don't erase it.
He erased it.
(To. Ji W...)
(After thinking for a long time, he sends his message.)
(Everyone's feelings have been sent.)
What time's your presentation tomorrow?
By 11am tomorrow,
I have to be standing there.
Are you ready?
- I'm always ready. - Gosh.
- Always. - Always.
- That's cool. - That's amazing.
He sounds like a professor.
I'll be presenting about the research I've done...
- So you have it all in your head. - It's all in my head.
- Can you show us? - Goodness.
The goal of this recent research I've done...
is Lead Identification.
Gosh.
- He really did it for us. - Continue, please.
- "Lead?" - Lead Identification.
Are you presenting in English?
I can present in Korean tomorrow, so it won't be too hard.
That's cool.
Let's check.
(I want to spend time with you.)
We were home, and we weren't doing anything,
so I thought we'd be able to spend a lot of time together.
But that didn't happen, so I was very disappointed.
If it snows tomorrow...
That's right.
(I'm looking forward to our date tomorrow!)
I sent mine to Se Seung. Yes.
We barely spent time together today, so I was disappointed.
(Jung Sub and Se Seung sent messages to each other.)
Gosh, now they're just...
Isn't she basically his girlfriend now?
Those two are very solid.
- I think so too. - I'm worried, though.
If it doesn't work out between them,
they could get hurt badly.
On my way here after work... Was it Shinsegae Department Store?
(Thank you for the book.)
(I will read it and leave a book report.)
I sent a message to Cheol Hyeon today.
I continued to feel like his feelings were hurt.
There were things I felt bad about and grateful for,
so I sent Cheol Hyeon a message.
As for the other days...
We can go out on Friday.
Monday and Thursday don't work.
(She waits, but doesn't get a message.)
I gave it some thought.
"Even if I end up changing my mind and complicating things,"
"I should follow my heart." I had that thought.
Was he very disappointed?
Was there another reason?
Was he curious about someone else?
Did he develop an interest in someone else? I was curious,
but I didn't ask.
I didn't tell him about my honest feelings either.
(To whom did Cheol Hyeon deliver his feelings?)
I want to keep it gentle.
(How was your alone time today?)
I sent Se Seung a message to express my interest.
She read a lot of the book I gave her.
(The 2nd floor living room, this afternoon)
This book is fun.
Is it fun?
Please lend it to me after you are done.
I will read it quickly.
Take your time.
No. I will read it quickly.
Read it quickly then.
I am only human.
Since she showed an interest in something I gave her,
it was nice.
(Who do you think sent the message?)
Cheol Hyeon?
"When I spend time alone,"
"it's nice to read a book while enjoying the sunlight."
I told him that.
I was happy about the message,
but I also felt puzzled.
How did I make his heart flutter?
It was an unexpected vote.
(Two people chose your sibling.)
I gave it a lot of thought.
One message must be from Jung Sub.
But I really don't know whom the other message is from.
(No one chose your sibling.)
I had this thought.
"Is there a change in Ju Yeon's thoughts?"
"A change in Ju Yeon's behaviours..."
"could have led to such results."
That thought occurred to me, and things became a bit interesting.
(I had so much fun today. Perhaps we are the same age.)
I think it was Ji Won...
because she seemed to be the same age.
I sent it to Yong Woo.
Yong Woo seemed like someone who was the same age.
So I went, "Perhaps we are the same age."
(It's cold today, so rest in a warm place when you come home.)
(Let's listen to carols again when it snows tomorrow.)
We listened to carols as a group,
so I wondered who sent the message.
I think it's Cho A.
I sent a message to Yong Woo.
We listened to carols on the day we had our first date.
What? Isn't it a Christmas carol?
Aren't we going to make a tree?
Shall we do that?
Shall we do that? Let's make a tree.
- That sounds nice. - A tree.
I have fond memories of that day.
(To whom did Yong Woo deliver his feelings today?)
(You did well today.)
I sent a message to Cho A.
He sent a message to Cho A.
- I got goosebumps. - I am so touched.
Seriously, Yong Woo...
- Yong Woo is different. - I know.
I sent a message to Cho A.
Ji Won is very charming,
and I have an interest in getting to know her more.
But I felt like I connected to Cho A...
more than Ji Won.
I will lend you a natural hot pack.
But to me,
it was a fascinating day.
I did it...
out of habit, so to speak.
Cho A's name came to me naturally.
But that day,
the message asking me who made my heart flutter today...
really made me think.
It was specified today.
Today, I didn't see Cho A once.
I only spent time with Ju Won.
There was a bit of a conflict.
So for the first time,
I had to think hard.
In the previous messages, the sentences had wit.
They made me certain that there were from Yong Woo.
They were like that.
But I couldn't guess the sender this time.
It was a bit puzzling.
What is this?
The warmth she always received from him disappeared.
That detail disappeared.
- The detail. - I got goosebumps.
Women's hunch is incredible.
He used to put his emotions...
- into the messages. - That's right.
- But the new message was very dry. - That's right.
It made her think, "What's this?"
Isn't it okay to send, "You did well today?"
- No. - He wasn't like that before.
Think about the messages he sent before.
- That's right. Yong Woo... - He always looked after her...
- with consideration. - You are right.
She should have known then and there.
"This jerk is with another woman."
She should have known right away.
- That's right. - Come on.
That's right. The day before, he sent a message about...
- his side fat and such. - You are right.
As he conveyed the message of "I chose you,"
he made an effort to be witty and make Cho A laugh...
- in his text. - That's right.
Today, it was just, "You did well today."
Yes. She thought it was puzzling.
"What's up with him?"
"You did well today" is...
a message I get from Korea Music Copyright Association.
- That's right. - Seriously.
He said it was out of habit.
He always wrote Cho A.
But he erased it.
For the first time that day,
- he went, "Is this right?" - He began...
- He began to rethink his choice. - He became thoughtful.
Had they received the instruction 30 minutes later,
things might have been different.
(I am disappointed that our time was short and cold.)
(Let's talk next time.)
Still,
I received one.
To be honest, I thought no one would give me a message.
I was very thankful that someone did.
I think...
it's from Jung Sub.
He is someone I talked to for the shortest amount of time.
I messaged Ji Won.
I just messaged someone I wanted to message.
I wanted to talk to her.
She has a similar vibe compared to my ex-girlfriend.
But she must be different.
To be honest, I want to check that.
Did you watch it?
- Yes, I did. - Did you watch it?
(Welcome back home. I hope your allergy gets better.)
I sent a message to Jae Hyung.
I liked the date we had together.
I also think...
we will get along.
So I sent him another message.
(All messages have been sent. Have a good night.)
(No one chose your sibling.)
All right.
There were no events.
So a part of me thought...
that it was understandable.
We are only on our fifth day.
There will be a lot of opportunities.
- It's time to go. - Yes.
I will go now...
and meet the female participants.
You are right. You will meet everyone.
- It will be fun. - That's right.
Yong Woo is a cool person.
He showed a sense of humour like a friend at times,
so spending time with him was fun and comfortable.
But it wasn't complete comfort. There was...
a good kind of tension.
It was very nice.
I had fun until the late hours.
I had fun thanks to you too.
(They walk out of the building amidst the wind storm.)
- I think that's the car. - I see.
- Is that car yours? - It's very...
- Okay. - Small.
It's cute.
It's small and precious.
- It's small and precious. - Watch the car.
This way. I will get in the other way.
Okay.
I will scoot over.
- Will you do that? - Yes.
It will be cramped.
- Go inside first. - I will do that.
- See you inside. - Take a half-bath too.
- Okay. Thank you. - Go on in.
(Yong Woo returns.)
It can't be easy to do that.
It's Yong Woo.
- What? - Is it Yong Woo?
- Did the work end well? - Did you take care of it well?
You left in a hurry.
Were all of you guys...
waiting for me?
You cried somewhere, right?
- Me? - Yes.
When I checked my pocket,
I saw the letter from yesterday.
- I... - You kept it.
I couldn't help but cry again.
He left saying that it was a personal matter.
He left like this.
You guys are so mean.
It's no joke.
(How did it feel when Yong Woo came home?)
I was happy to see him.
(After checking her hoodie,)
(she comes downstairs with a smile.)
That's right.
- Where did you go? - Me?
I had to take care of a business.
- Are you okay? - Now? I am okay.
I am okay.
You are wearing comfortable clothes today.
You are wearing a hoodie.
It's my first time seeing you wear a hoodie.
That's right. It's your first time.
(She is happy that she tidied up clothes before.)
The hoodie makes your neck appear...
really slim.
- Really? - It's a boxy hoodie.
Gosh, she waited for him.
- How nice. - She received a message too.
Ju Yeon, when did you come today?
I worked until late today, so I came at 9pm.
At 9pm?
It's at Sinyongsan.
Sinyongsan.
Did you come at 10pm today as well?
Today, I came past 10:30pm.
Aren't you exhausted? I would be...
so exhausted.
- I am exhausted. - Seriously.
In which neighbourhood is your workplace located?
City Hall.
- City Hall. - City Hall.
- It's close to my workplace. - City Hall.
- Are we in there as well? - I am not sure.
Cho A, are you good at gonggi?
Gonggi? I haven't played it in a long while.
My hand... Let me try it.
Back in the day, I held the pieces like this...
at Two Years.
- Two Years. - That's right.
- I haven't heard that in a while. - Two Years.
(The game brings back memories.)
There were so many fun games.
- Let's go. - What is it?
It's late at night.
Is there something else?
Come upstairs.
We just received this.
- It just arrived. - Did something come?
- Did the doorbell ring? - Yes.
- Is it a new one? - Yes.
It just arrived.
"A new participant who chose Yong Woo..."
- "as a date..." - I knew it.
- "arrived at the door." - I knew someone would come.
"Please go to the door and welcome her."
There is a new participant.
- Let's hurry up and go. - Really?
- Really? - Let's hurry up and go.
"And welcome her."
- How does she know Yong Woo? - Who is she?
What's going on?
It's so...
- It's so exciting. - What?
(She becomes startled and runs away.)
- I knew it. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Come on in. - It's nice to meet you.
- Hello. - Come on in.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
I saw people rush over...
and wondered if I should run.
- Hello. - Come on in.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
What's your name?
- My name is Ji Won. - It's nice to meet you.
- Welcome. - Thank you.
Welcome.
- You must have been nervous. - Seriously.
You are nervous, right? Sit down. Put yourself at ease.
My first impression of her was...
that she seemed haughty.
She is very hip and stylish.
A very pretty woman...
who resembled a cat was standing there.
She seemed like a cold city girl.
She seemed like a woman...
with an unrivalled aura.
I thought that she was my brother's type...
the moment I saw her.
- She realized it right away. - Seriously.
He said she resembled his ex-girlfriend.
How scary.
Yes.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
Thank you.
I thought you would be asleep.
- We were waiting for you. - Really?
- I am glad I didn't go to bed. - Seriously.
Thank you.
How did you know Yong Woo and pick him?
Are you supposed to keep it a secret?
Well...
- To be completely honest, - Can you tell us?
we said hello earlier.
- Really? - I met men one at a time.
I knew something was up.
Only men knew about it.
That made me go...
(I see.)
It was like that.
How else would she suddenly choose Yong Woo?
She had met him.
The puzzle pieces came together.
It was a bit like, "I can't believe these punks."
Everyone seemed to be surprised,
but my sister showed big reactions.
(His sister's reactions in 3 steps)
She was like this.
It was fun to watch her.
I thought Ju Yeon's eyes...
would pop out.
(He watched from the 1st row.)
"A new participant who chose Yong Woo as a date..."
"arrived at the door."
"Please go to the door and welcome her."
It's funny when you know it.
It's like a sitcom.
My goodness.
- I met them one at a time. - One at a time?
- Yes. - One at a time.
I see. Okay.
At first,
I thought they had met together.
But she had talked to them 1 at a time for 10 minutes.
So I had two thoughts.
"One at a time?"
The 2nd one was, "Just 10 minutes?"
I don't know if I should be relieved.
I was a bit flustered.
I was like, "How did they know?"
You had received a letter.
When I saw her,
I thought that Jung Sub might like her.
She isn't the type Jung Sub usually dates.
But...
she is the type Jung Sub wants to date,
I think.
Yong Woo was the one...
she picked from the start.
To both of them, the date... Maybe not both of them.
To the woman,
the date must have been nice.
I thought that might be the case.
He is the man who looks good in my eyes,
so it might be the same for other people.
I didn't think Cho A was bothered...
because it was Ji Won's choice.
It was Ji Won's choice.
What would Yong Woo think...
about the new participant, Ji Won?
Does he find her favourable?
Perhaps the first impression wasn't that great.
Yong Woo is the one who will be my brother-in-law.
He is one of the candidates.
My sister can't lose him.
I hope my sister hurries up and goes on a date with him.
I need to see her go on a date with Yong Woo...
to alleviate this resentment.
All the male participants said...
that the female participants were very nice.
So I came here with ease.
The house is very nice.
- It's pretty, right? - It's nice.
- Why don't you have a house tour? - Why don't you have a house tour?
- That's right. - Let's have a house tour.
(She first checks out the pride of the house, the basement hideout.)
This is incredible.
This is the Telephone Room.
The Telephone Room. Who can we call?
We can call whomever we want.
We can call our parents.
That's your bed.
When will you unpack?
You should go and wash up now.
I am going to go to bed right away.
(People who need to go to work get ready for bed.)
Hold on. We should write her name.
- That's right. - Look over here.
Now,
- we need tissue paper. - Tissue paper?
- Please bring it. - Tissue paper?
From where?
I am ordering you around.
To keep the spacing consistent,
we should erase everything.
I don't need to write it prettily, do I?
- You need to write it prettily. - Really?
Yes. Do you go to work tomorrow?
I have a brief meeting, but...
A meeting.
I wrote it like this. Do I get a pass?
My goodness. What was that?
- She thinks it's a nuisance. - What was that?
What was that smirk?
Hold on.
- The angle was so funny. - It looked like...
she was thinking, "Give me a break."
Se Seung is a bit...
- Se Seung is annoyed. - She is jealous.
- It bothers her. - "What is going on?"
- I think it looks nice. - Hold on.
Where is it?
You failed.
How could you say that?
I wrote it well.
(Ji Won)
- It's nice. - It's nice.
I will go and wash up.
I need to go to bed early today.
That's right.
Go and wash up.
Yong Woo is lucky.
- What? - Yong Woo is lucky.
I am jealous.
(The house fairy wants to hang out with the new participant.)
Can I ask you why you chose Yong Woo?
Well,
he was the last one I talked to.
It seemed like the conversation ended fast.
- You were disappointed. - I felt like it got cut off.
(Yun Ha joins them.)
Welcome to the Study Time on Ji Won.
Then you didn't have a group meeting,
- just 1-on-1 meetings. - That's right.
- That's right. - It must have been very awkward.
Yes.
What am I going to do if I already feel this way?
It's okay.
It's only your first day.
The first day is very hectic.
From the second day onward, it becomes insanely fun.
You adjusted well in five days.
In any case, our siblings are here.
So the atmosphere is set up to bring us close.
Everyone is warmhearted. Seriously.
The female participant I get along with...
is Se Seung,
I think.
The participant my brother would like...
is Yun Ha.
Her eyes...
Her eyes are very pretty when she laughs.
She has a bright energy.
But she seems to have...
sturdiness and strength inside.
I think my brother will get along with her...
and like her very much.
I had that thought.
(Who do you think are siblings?)
I think Jung Sub and Se Seung are siblings.
One time, I set between them.
The alarm didn't go off.
Give it to me.
No, it's set up correctly.
- Maybe you slept through it. - Really?
They definitely spoke to each other with the siblings' tone.
So I was showing a meaningful smile.
They are getting to know each other.
- They aren't siblings. - She thinks they are siblings.
It must be really confusing.
Okay. See Ya.
- See Ya. - Bye.
Have a good night.
I think the two of them are...
siblings.
- You have gone on a date, right? - Yes.
How was it?
At first, I wondered what I would do if things were awkward.
But it was fun.
We became close and comfortable around each other.
But we couldn't let people know whom we went on a date with.
It made things more fun.
We became close,
but we couldn't show it.
We can't show it...
because then it becomes obvious that those two aren't siblings.
That's why we can't show it.
Isn't it fun?
(Cute)
(In capital letters. C, U, T, E.)
(My heart got knocked out.)
(I finally listened to Jae Hyung sing.)
Really?
(I heard the speaker rip.)
(She can't school her face.)
(Se Seung and Cheol Hyeon take a walk together.)
- Are you a model? - You are so pretty.
(You are really pretty.)
(My dad said, "Find someone like your dad.")
(Is that Cheol Hyeon?)
(What did you do today?)
(I went on a stroll around the neighbourhood.)
(- With whom? - Cheol Hyeon.)
(I see.)
(Just the two of you?)
(I began following them with my eyes.)
(I am jealous.)
(Of course, I am jealous.)
(It would be funny to explain myself.)
(He isn't my boyfriend.)
(I don't think she had fallen for him...)
(completely.)