(Gosh, look at their legs.)
(They're like Yun Jae.)
(This was the most fun I had since we started filming.)
(He was the type of person that I was naturally attracted to.)
(At that moment, I thought, "She's the one.")
(After the dates, they had to choose someone for the text message.)
(Jae Hyung and Ji Won chose each other.)
(Should I make kimchi for you?)
(When I received the text,)
(it didn't sound like Yong Woo at all.)
(What does he mean by that?)
(They weren't on the same wavelength anymore.)
"To make your decision without any regrets..."
(They will go on a date with someone...)
(they haven't gone on a date.)
(Sighing)
(Whom will he choose?)
(Number 1, Ju Yeon.)
(Yun Jae and Ju Yeon will be going on a date.)
(Due to the first decision made by Yun Jae,)
(the rest of you were automatically matched as couples.)
(This could cause some confusion.)
(To determine the date budget ranking,)
(the Women's Chicken Fight Competition was held.)
(I looked at her with killing intent in my eyes.)
(I thought, "I must win.")
(Let's end it fast.)
(Ji Won and Jung Sub get 50 dollars.)
(Cho A and Jae Hyung get 100 dollars.)
(Ju Yeon and Yun Jae get 300 dollars.)
(Yun Ha and Yong Woo get 500 dollars.)
(Se Seung and Cheol Hyeon get 1,000 dollars.)
(It came with a luxury date.)
(I was really excited about that.)
(I am glad that I got a good rest yesterday.)
(Their third dates in Singapore will begin now.)
- It's so hot. - Are you going to wear that?
- Yes. Why? - Okay.
Do you want to wear a matching outfit?
- Yes. - Okay.
(Yun Ha begins picking out her outfit for her date.)
(The first outfit: The off-the-shoulder blouse)
- Do I look okay? - Yes. Not bad.
What else do you have other than the black blouse?
I have a dress that looks super girly.
(The second outfit: The super girly dress)
Hey.
What's the white thing underneath the dress?
It's a Western-style dress. A dress from the Wild West.
Here's why. Wearing a shirt...
- Let me see. - How do I look?
No.
You look like a girl in "Indiana Jones."
Or what about this? This doesn't look bad, right?
- That's nice too. - Right?
But it looks similar to the outfit I wore yesterday.
Hurry up.
(The fifth outfit: A loose maxi dress)
Jung Sub.
Yes.
Great. You look very nice.
- Really? - Yes. You look great in white.
The shoes too.
(She picks out a cardigan too.)
Gosh. This is too white.
- How beautiful. - Does this look better?
Yes.
(She finally settles on the outfit after contemplating for 40 minutes.)
This room is nice and breezy. You guys have a fan too.
Let me go down and see what we have in the fridge.
Gosh.
- Jung Sub. - Yes.
Do you like cream pasta or tomato pasta?
I like TP.
TP? Okay.
(He's hovering around her again.)
- Then what should we do first? - What are you doing?
Steak and pasta.
(Ji Won wants to put on an apron.)
- What is this? - What are you doing?
- How do I put this on? - Something went wrong big time.
That's right.
This is right.
Then I should tighten these.
What is this?
- I see. This is it. - I see.
Okay.
(Groaning)
That was a sharp scream.
(Shrieking)
Thanks.
This is nice. It's like I'm going to cook something grand.
- That's how it feels. - You're building up expectations.
I should watch you cook before I go.
Gosh. He's glued to her when Jung Sub is there.
Seriously. He keeps circling around her.
He's building a barrier between Jung Sub and her.
- Oh, no. He's... - This feels weird.
Those two will go on a date.
Their date already has begun.
- I think it already started. - Yes, it already started.
Will the three of them go on a date?
(A three-people date in the kitchen)
Are you going to add the steak to the tomato pasta?
Tomato pasta with meat?
- I'll cook them separately. - Separately.
- Yes. I'll try to make it tasty. - Do you have something in mind?
I'll try to disappear.
- Ta-da. - I'll try to do a good job.
- I'll try... - I'll give it a try.
- to become a pencil. - I can't wait.
I'm guilty of losing the Chicken Leg Competition.
I'll cook for us.
- Gosh, no. - But it's nice...
we can go on a date with someone we like.
Right. That's true.
Only the people in last place got that chance.
Don't say we came in last.
We came in fifth place.
Out of the 5 teams, the team in 5th place got the benefit.
Aren't you envious?
- The chance to go on a date? - Yes.
Yes.
- I want to pick my date too. - You sound...
- Do you know whom you'll pick? - Yes.
Too bad. You don't have that chance.
Are you studying how to be annoying?
I want to marinate the meat. The meat...
Does the meat want to meditate?
Yes. The meat is in the mood to meditate.
- I should do it here. - Am I distracting you?
Yes? Am I distracting you?
- Do you hold a grudge? - Me?
Yes.
- For a long time? - I hold grudges for a long time.
He keeps following her.
- Right. - That's so funny.
I thought the two of them would go into the cupboard.
Look. They went inside.
If I were him, I would have gone inside for a bit.
- If I were him. - What?
But there are shelves.
I can be in pain briefly.
(Am I distracting you?)
(Do you hold a grudge?)
(Me?)
(For a long time.)
(I hold grudges for a long time.)
What's going on?
What are you doing in that awful outfit?
That doesn't suit you.
- Shush. - Shush.
When I grind black pepper like this, do I look like a good cook?
No.
(Chuckling)
You look like a good cook.
Can I eat with you guys?
- Eat with us? - Yes.
Sure.
Can I eat with you guys?
- Eat with us? - Yes.
Sure.
Well done.
(Glancing)
(He takes out more meat from the fridge.)
- Excuse me. - Okay.
That's it.
Did you do it?
- Gosh. - Good.
Yes? Pour it? How much?
- Can we add one more piece? - Sure.
Actually, I wanted to eat some too.
Yong Woo asked if he could have some of the food.
I suddenly thought,
"Should I have some before I go?"
Then everyone came down.
So I grilled the steak.
When we were cooking, it felt like...
she was trying to take care of me.
She put the apron on me.
You have to pull the upper straps a lot.
(Hitting)
Wait. This...
He's knocked out.
But people were watching us.
I'm a shy person.
So it made me blush.
- Were you secretly resenting me? - I'm done. What?
- You teased me a lot today. - Yesterday...
Wait. I didn't wipe off your makeup, right?
I get the feeling that this is a lot of food.
Let me taste it.
Gosh. He's feeding her.
- What? They're on a date. - He's feeding her.
(Approving)
- It's tasty. - It's tasty.
- Gosh. But... - The colour looks amazing.
- It's tasty. - I knew it.
(Humming)
I knew it.
(Communicating with humming)
I thought I was at your recital again.
- It smells great. - Come and try some.
Ju Yeon. It's hot. Try it.
- Should I cut the sausages? - Yes.
No.
- Nice. You make a mean pasta. - Can I have some?
Well, I used the pasta sauce from the store.
- Shush. - Shush.
- Is it good? - It's so good.
(Slurping)
- It's tasty. - We can't eat a lot, though.
I trying hard not to.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
- Go ahead and swim. - I'll swim.
(Glancing)
- I see some belly fat. - Belly fat?
Did you come down after doing some push-ups?
I have a lot of belly fat now?
You seem to have a lot of belly fat now.
- I look slim? - I see a lot of belly fat.
A lot of belly fat...
Oh, no. What should I do?
(He takes his sister's advice and changes his outfit.)
- You're wearing swimwear. - Why do you look shy coming down?
- Why do you look so shy? - You look so shy.
(Surprised)
Wait.
(Taking it off)
Can we watch him swim?
I don't know.
Are you having fun?
Seriously. That kid is having so much fun.
- Shall we go? Bye. See you later. - Bye.
- Bye. - See you.
(Cheol Hyeon)
(Ju Yeon)
(Jung Sub)
(Se Seung)
(Cho A)
(Yun Ha)
(Jae Hyung)
(Yong Woo)
(Ji Won)
(Yun Jae)
(My Sibling's Romance)
(Episode 13: Waking up)
(Cho A and Jae Hyung in 4th place begin their date.)
Hi.
You can go right now.
- I hope it doesn't rain. - Right.
- It's my first date with you. - That's right.
This is a date with someone we haven't gone on a date.
- Didn't you mostly go on a date... - Yes.
with Yong Woo?
Yes. Right.
Who else did you go on a date other than Yong Woo?
Jung Sub.
- I see. In Gangwon Province. - Yes.
Right. We went on a double date in Gangwon Province.
I thought talking to her would be nice.
I thought she would be comfortable around me...
and treat me nicely.
So talking to her was comfortable.
Actually, I wasn't sure about my feelings or what I wanted...
- before then. - I see.
Because of the environment and situation we were in,
I felt like I had to choose someone for the sake of choosing.
Because of that, I felt really uncomfortable.
But after coming to Singapore, this kind of frustration I had...
is getting relieved. That's how it feels so far.
I don't feel uncomfortable or feel the pressure...
of making up my mind.
I can do that now naturally. It's a genuine act now.
I now have someone...
I want to send my text message to...
even if we don't go on a date together.
- Because of that, I feel at ease. - Really?
(It starts pouring down.)
It's raining intensely.
- What about you? - Yes?
Are you certain about what you want?
- After coming to Singapore, - Yes?
things got hard emotionally.
There was a moment that made me hesitate...
for the first time. That happened in Singapore.
To be completely honest, it's hard...
to show yourself 100 percent while filming the show.
- Right. - Our siblings are here too.
- Right. - Despite that,
I do believe that...
she knows that I've made up my mind.
That she knows how you feel?
I became soaked little by little.
You became soaked...
- little by little. - Yes.
- I didn't know when it drizzled. - Yes.
At one point, it feels like my entire body is soaked.
That might describe my feeling now.
Now that we're here, it stopped raining.
(Cho A and Jae Hyung, Tiong Bahru Hawker Center)
What a timing.
- Can we get out of the car now? - Okay. Thank you.
It feels liberating to talk about stuff like this with you.
It's different from talking to your sibling.
- It's different. - Yes.
Is this the food court they were talking about?
What do you want to eat? I see skewers!
I want chicken rice.
- Dumplings sound tasty. - Dumplings sound good.
Do you have the money...
- the staff gave you? - Yes.
Let's take a look around.
(He takes their precious money.)
The money.
- That looks good. - It's xiaolongbao.
- Really? - Amazing.
That looks good. Right?
Thank you.
Like the Vietnamese coffee with condensed milk.
- Three coffees? - Yes.
- They look like fishcakes. - I think so too.
- It's 5.50. - Okay.
(Total balance: 77.1 Singapore dollars)
- Do you have chicken rice? - I think it will be tasty.
- It's 3.50. - It's 3.50.
(Total balance: 73.6 Singapore dollars)
There are vegetables too. This looks good.
Because it's raining today, the fried food might taste better.
You're just like my cousin.
- Let's eat. - Let's enjoy the food.
She must have been attracted to your cute side.
Who do you think she is?
- Can I say her name? - Sure.
- Ji Won? - Yes.
I asked her what her ideal type was.
- You asked Ji Won? - Yes.
Are you curious?
Ji Won's ideal type?
We talked about that when we were on a date yesterday.
Each other's ideal type?
What did she say to you?
She said a cute guy who works hard at his job.
I'm pretty cute.
You are.
Jae Hyung is cute indeed.
What about you? What's your ideal type?
Appearance-wise, I think I'm attracted to masculine guys.
- Right. - But personality-wise,
I'm attracted to sweet guys.
(I see.)
(He remembers someone.)
I think he's a good match to your ideal type.
- Who? - What?
Who?
- Is there someone like that here? - Should I not name him?
- Don't name him. - Okay.
- I'm shy. - Okay.
I'm curious about how you express your affection.
- Me? - Yes.
When I'm in a relationship, I'm not indifferent or anything.
Actually, it's the contrary when I start dating.
- I guess you change. - I'm really sweet.
- He's so different. - Right.
- I think that's the right thing. - Once he's certain.
Well, I shouldn't say a behaviour is right or wrong.
But their behaviour can't be the same around everyone.
Shouldn't they behave differently around their significant others?
- Right. - They should. Of course.
Jae Hyung's behaviour is visibly different.
We didn't see him go on dates with someone he liked.
But when we saw him go on a date with a girl he liked,
he suddenly became so attractive.
You became his fan last week.
Right.
- I'm the president of his fan club. - Did you forget that?
Right. I forgot about that.
I'm kind of shy before I start dating.
I think I'm shy because people might see how I feel.
- That might be one reason. - I see.
You're the type to act with certainty...
once you make up your mind.
I think so.
- Shall we go? - Let's go.
Your shoes look cute.
- Right? - Yes.
They're the perfect shoes for today's date.
Gosh. Here comes the rich couple.
They have 1,000 dollars. What will they do with that money in a day?
(The benefit of winning 1st place in the chicken fight)
(They have a luxury limousine service.)
(A professional chauffeur)
The car is here.
- Even their car is different. - Their car is different.
They have a chauffeur too?
- Gosh. Cheol Hyeon... - That's...
will lean toward her even more now.
- He'll see her as wife material. - Seriously.
What a lucky guy to enjoy all this.
- Seriously. - Exactly.
Thank you.
What a great service!
- Cheol Hyeon. - This is the best.
I told you to believe in me.
Let's have fun today.
I get to have this luxury thanks to you.
- Se Seung, it's great to be out. - Right?
We're in a great car on a rainy day.
- Was he locked up somewhere? - This is his first time going out.
He only stayed at the accommodation.
Really?
This is his first date. So it all worked out for him.
He wore a white outfit and stayed inside like a Buddhist monk.
He only stayed indoors.
Let me comb my bangs.
Look at my bangs today.
See you after the date.
Bye.
You'll have fun.
- You're still here. - Yes.
(Ju Yeon and Yun Jae are in the living room.)
Should I wear this pair of shoes?
Or should I wear sneakers?
- They look cute. - Wear these instead.
It's raining today.
If you wear sneakers, they'll get soaked.
- Will they be better then? - Yes.
- They match your bag nicely too. - Yes, they match better.
Don't wear sneakers. It's raining.
- Right. It's raining. - Yes.
Look at Yun Jae right now.
Check out his facial expression as Yun Ha gets ready to go out.
- Look at him. - He's bothered by her date.
He looks so unhappy right now.
But he's still worried that her sneakers might get wet.
- He told her to wear sandals. - Right.
(Will they be better then?)
(- They match your bag nicely too. - Yes, they match better.)
(Don't wear sneakers. It's raining.)
(Yong Woo comes down too.)
Okay. See you later.
See you later.
See you later. Have a good time.
Enjoy your date.
(Were you bothered that Yun Ha and Yong Woo went on a date?)
Oh, that date... Yong Woo and Yun Ha...
I wasn't bothered because she went on a date with Yong Woo.
I wasn't bothered because it was Yong Woo.
I wouldn't have felt good whoever her date turned out to be.
To be honest, I don't know...
to whom she'll feel attracted. So that's why...
I hated everything about it.
- Should I get in first? - Sure
Hello.
(Yun Ha and Yong Woo in 2nd place set out.)
Today,
we somehow ended up...
- winning second place. - Yes.
Don't you think we got a spacious car?
Don't you agree?
- There's a lot of space here. - Seriously.
So you're responsible for making our date great.
I worked hard.
- You made our date great. - I worked hard.
So we got to go on a date in the end.
- We ended up with a date abroad. - Yes.
When we first started, I chose Yong Woo...
as the guy I was interested in.
(Yun Ha sent her Cupid Message to Yong Woo on Day One.)
(Thanks to you, everyone got along well today.)
(Let's have fun getting to know each other.)
- Nice to meet you. - I felt that...
he had a kind face.
I like funny guys.
So I became slightly interested in him.
I liked Yong Woo.
He has a very likeable face.
I sent the message to Yong Woo.
(She also sent her first text message to Yong Woo.)
(I had so much fun thanks to you. Let's keep having fun.)
After a lot of time had passed and many things happened,
I finally had a chance...
to go on a date with him.
Wait. Can this date potentially cause changes?
A bit?
Gosh, no way.
After this date,
Yun Ha might start having...
- It might confuse her. - something... Right.
- She might develop some feelings. - That's not entirely impossible.
Things can change...
- Right. - in a day.
Anyway, Yong Woo was Yun Ha's type, appearance-wise.
- Right. - Yes.
I have a funny episode about us.
In the beginning,
we had to answer the phone to pick our date.
I thought my date was you.
- Really? - Yes.
The lady who answered the phone sounded so bubbly.
I was kind of lost. On top of that, I'm not sharp with things like this.
- I sort of noticed that. - Right.
- You're kind of slow. - I realized that too.
- That's your charm. - Is that so?
- Yes. - That's a relief.
So who was the lady you went on a date with?
- It was Cho A. - I see. Cho A was bubbly?
She's more expressive on 1-on-1 dates.
This show is fun.
I'm finding a lot about myself here.
It's the same with me.
I don't think things were awkward between us...
from the get-go.
It wasn't awkward at all.
So I found myself talking a lot more naturally to her.
We teased each other a lot too.
She was so cheerful and made me feel comfortable.
So I ended up talking a lot.
On that note, what's your ideal type?
What kind of type are you attracted to appearance-wise?
Han Go Eun is my ideal type, appearance-wise.
How would you describe your ideal type in detail?
- He must have a beautiful nose. - The nose.
Is it because your family has a beautiful nose?
Am I attracted to someone similar to me?
- That's possible. - I think so.
You need to have some things in common.
In the past, I started relationships...
thinking I could accommodate her...
even if we didn't have anything in common.
But it wasn't easy.
That's really nice of you.
The fact that you dated someone with that mindset.
Do you know what's really interesting with them?
No other couples can have conversations like them.
- Right. - They're talking so politely.
- They're using honorifics. - Yes.
Using honorifics means...
they aren't so close.
- It can make their hearts flutter. - Yes. Because they're not close...
- There's definitely that chemistry. - They have no history right now.
It's a blank slate.
- Right. - Their relationship...
- That's when anything can happen. - Right.
This is interesting.
I think we're almost there.
- There are so many people here. - Right.
(An oasis in the heart of Singapore downtown)
(Gardens by the Bay)
Have you been to a botanical garden like this?
I think I've gone to a botanical garden in Korea.
I don't think...
I've been to a botanical garden that resembles...
- a pretty amusement park. - Right.
- Shall we go down this way? - Sure. Shall we?
By the way, why are you speaking with honorifics?
- Me? - Yes. Are you uncomfortable?
No. Speaking with honorifics is more comfortable.
- Is that so? - Yes.
- I'm comfortable with being casual. - I...
- Let's talk casually then. - Yes.
Is this our 1st time talking 1-on-1 like this?
It's our first time talking casually like this.
Really?
(Cloud Forest)
Our outfits were perfect for this.
Because it's so colourful,
- white outfits will look good here. - Right.
Should we try it here too? Will it open up?
- What's this? It's so fascinating. - It's so beautiful.
I didn't know there was a huge structure like this here.
This is so beautiful.
- By the way, this is so cool. - Right.
Why don't we put our heads together?
Put our heads together? Like this?
Put the tip of your hair on mine.
On your hair like this?
(Successfully putting their hair together)
To be honest, I didn't know it would be this big.
- This place is beautiful. - Right.
I guess we can go up through that.
- Look at the background here. - This is scary.
Here?
- Are you afraid of heights? - Yes, a bit.
This is so beautiful.
The sun is going down over there.
- Gosh. How stunning. - This is beautiful.
I don't want to admit it. But maybe, I'm getting old.
I like plants nowadays.
(He takes a lot of pictures with the plants he likes.)
It's like we're taking pictures in a jungle.
(Taking a photo with the plant through the mirror)
(Cloud Theater)
This is so beautiful.
How about a video of you doing a kick?
This is the camerawork for a movie.
Is that the bird we're seeing?
In a way, it felt like my last date.
- So I tried to take... - Try to tap on it.
as many fun pictures as possible.
He took so many amazing photos of me.
When we went to Gangneung,
Ju Yeon took such great photos which surprised me.
I guess that skill runs in the family.
- I got you the best photo. - Thank you.
I never look good in Polaroid pictures,
so I always hated that.
I'm kind of proud of this one.
(The team in last place leaves the house.)
By the way, we picked good matching outfits.
- Totally. We look like a set. - The belt, sandals, and the bag.
Seriously.
(Disappointed)
- Ji Won, look at this. - Someone just threw it there.
(Only one bill is left in the taxi.)
Fifty... Do you know the old show? "Happiness With Ten Dollars?"
I know the show. It feels like we're filming that show.
We got into the taxi. On the backseat,
we saw a bill. It was as if someone had just thrown it.
(Chuckling)
The bill was on the backseat.
I saw the 50-dollar bill.
I thought to myself that we had to be very frugal today.
The 50-dollar date is kind of romantic.
I decided to enjoy...
this romantic date to the fullest.
They really gave us only 50 dollars.
I see a lot of restaurants...
with tasty food at the West Coast Park.
- But I guess... - Yes.
we can't afford those places with 50 dollars.
We'll spend some time there.
- Then we'll go to a food court. - So...
- We'll look at some food. - We'll keep saying,
"That looks good."
We'll just drool at the food.
We'll have to ride it in the rain.
- Are you okay with that? - I'm fine.
- Really? - Yes.
(Raising his arm)
(Pretending to ride the bicycle in the rain)
With one arm?
I wonder how it looks there.
Is it by the beach?
- It must be by the beach. - Ride the bicycle by the beach.
Yes. It's quite romantic.
Let's have fun and take a shower when we go back.
- Sounds good. - Good.
(Ji Won and Jung Sub, West Coast Park)
I guess we'll be riding that.
(There's a roof over the bicycles.)
That must be why we can still ride it in the rain.
(Surprised)
- This is nice. - It's cool.
It's so cute.
- Hello. - Hello. Hi.
To rent the bikes, it'll be 15 Singapore dollars.
- Fifteen Singapore dollars? - Yes.
- I see. Okay. - Okay.
- Should we spend our money now? - The money?
This is our precious money.
- First of all, he said it was... - We have to spend...
- fifteen Singapore dollars. - fifteen Singapore dollars.
- Okay. - What's our balance? Ta-da.
- Ta-da. - It's 35.
(Total balance: 35 Singapore dollars)
- Okay. Thank you. - Thank you.
- Gosh, that's... - Seriously.
- They spent a lot of money. - Right.
They'll run out of the money once they rent it three times.
Right.
This is so cute. I've never ridden a bicycle like this.
- Right. - What's this?
(They can't stop laughing.)
This is really fun.
- Go? - Go.
- Here we go. - Wait. No?
Slowly.
(Exclaiming)
(They smoothly curve the bicycles.)
(This is funny for some reason.)
- This is so funny. - What is this?
- Hey, Jung Sub. - What is this?
I see an uphill path.
Let's not look so silly, though.
- Okay. - Okay?
- Let's make it look romantic. - Romantic? Okay. For the that vibe.
It's right here.
Pedal hard.
Clench your molars.
(Clenching)
It's like riding a rickshaw.
- This is so fun. - Yes, it's fun.
The vlog on the road.
(Filmed by Jung Sub)
(Running)
(Impressed)
She's going faster than us.
- Running is faster than this. - Right. It's much faster.
- Is this similar to a pedal boat? - Totally.
(Slow)
It's fascinating...
- that there are bicycles like this. - Should we pedal fast?
- Super fast? - Super fast.
Okay.
(Pedalling super-fast)
I can't keep up with your pedalling speed.
(Pedalling furiously)
This is crazy.
I can't see her.
(Amazed)
- It's cool and breezy. - It's cool and breezy.
You're pedalling way too fast,
so my pedals are spinning on their own.
They're spinning on their own.
(The runner already turned at the halfway point.)
- Seriously. This is so funny. - Goodness. Why is it so funny?
Hey, Jung Sub.
I can barely see your feet right now.
I can't see your legs.
We were riding the bicycles at the park.
We were laughing a lot.
We pedalled really fast. We tried to pedal as hard we could.
We were like swans.
We pedalled hard with our feet just like the swan.
We had to pedal a lot to ride the bicycle.
But it was really fun.
It wasn't romantic or anything.
We were like comrades. We pedalled powerfully...
when we rode the bicycles together.
Ji Won. Aren't you comfortable now?
It's really comfortable for me.
You're pedalling for both of us.
It's like you're competing...
- in the Summer Games. - The Summer Games.
You look like a cyclist participating in the Summer Games.
An energetic cyclist.
I want to have some coffee. But we don't have any money, right?
I'm glad we brought water.
Since we don't have money, let's drink water.
Can't we stop...
for a moment and look at the sights or something?
- Ji Won. Check out the view. - Sure.
- We're not in a race or anything. - Right.
(Surprised)
- What happened? - Oh, no.
- Why did it splash only on you? - Only me...
- I'm okay. - Are you okay?
- I went there on purpose. - Jung Sub.
How come your pants are clean?
- You... Hold on. - Wait. Seriously.
How come my pants are so clean?
What's going on?
- You're the one driving this. - This...
- Hold on. - The muddy water splashed on me.
I'm sorry.
- Gosh. - Do you want to drive this?
So it's fine as long as your pants are clean?
So you're going to start driving it now.
What if the muddy water starts splashing the other side?
- I'd rather have mud on both sides. - What if...
(Surprised)
- This is fun. - I'm the best driver.
I think we already arrived.
Did we already arrive?
- We already arrived. - It's shorter than I thought.
Gosh. It was really fun.
Let me see your pants.
- They're already dirty. - Seriously. What is this?
(Jung Sub checks Ji Won's pants.)
- I'll go to the restroom. - Okay. Go ahead.
- I'll see if I can wipe it off. - Okay.
Are you okay, Ji Won?
- Me? - Are you okay, Ji Won?
(Chuckling)
- I'm not okay. - Really?
Do you need something to cover up? I brought a shirt.
There's nothing I can do with the bottom part of my pants.
- It's the back side of the pants. - Let me see.
It's fine as long as they don't mistake it for something else.
- I don't make that kind of mistake. - If people start whispering...
- Tell them that's not it. - "Look at her."
Or do you want to tie something around your waist?
- What kind of shirt is it? - I...
- I don't care if stuff gets on it. - But...
- Let me go and check it out. - Okay. Go ahead.
- But with this around my waist, - If it's hot... Are you hot?
it makes me look like I have more stuff on my bottom.
- I think it's better this way. Yes. - Like you're doing it for real.
It looks like I'm trying to cover up something really big.
Some muddy water got only on Ji Won's pants.
I wanted to cover it up, so I gave her my shirt.
But when she tried to cover it up with my shirt,
it made her look like she really soiled her pants.
So I couldn't help her. I felt bad about that.
I saw how worried Jung Sub got about me.
He was always sweet to Yun Ha.
So I was fascinated and envious of her.
That occasion made me realize...
that he was a lot kinder and more thoughtful...
than I initially thought.
- So... Let me see. - We can just go. I'm okay.
It doesn't look weird.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Should I wear my bag like this?
Yes. Then it's completely covered up.
It shows very slightly.
No. It's fine as long as you don't get the wrong idea.
- I love everything. - We'll finally go.
Which yacht will it be?
I'll be happy with any yacht.
Is that the one?
Today's date is amazing.
We'll get to experience this?
I'm a bit scared.
It's scary.
- Shall we check out the view first? - Yes. Let's go.
- Are we setting sail now? - We're setting sail now.
It feels great to be out on the water.
Smell it. This is great.
- Gosh. This is amazing. - It feels great to be on the water.
Gosh, Cheol Hyeon. You look so photogenic here.
Should I take a picture of you?
The breeze feels so cool.
I'm in a great mood.
The scenes I saw in movies are flashing before my eyes right now.
Getting the ocean breeze on the yacht...
felt great. It was so refreshing.
I had been wanting to ride the yacht.
It felt great.
You look great in the pictures.
- This is beautiful. - Isn't this great?
Can we really enjoy this luxury? Is it okay to be this happy here?
Gosh, I'm so happy!
I guess...
- some people go to this island. - You're right.
- I wanted to lie down here. - Go ahead.
It's so comfortable.
I feel like I don't know where I am.
It's raining. Sailing on a yacht in the rain.
It'd be nice to lie down here too.
- Can I lie down here? - Cheol Hyeon!
You're the Korean Timothee Chalamet!
- That's the vibe I got from you. - Come on.
I'll give you a nickname. The Korean Timothee Chalamet.
- You mean, Timothee Salami? - Salami?
Timothee Ham.
(The sun starts to set.)
When it's pretty, you should enjoy it with your eyes.
Se Seung.
I got my hair on my face, right?
Yes. You got a lot of it.
It covered my entire forehead.
Aren't you cold? Is it okay?
- I'm good. Are you cold? - No. I'm okay too.
It's so nice as it becomes night.
They say Singapore is more beautiful at night.
Really?
Now that you're holding a beer, you look like you're from the sea.
Look over there!
There are two colours now.
- Oh, dear. - Goodness.
Look at that reflected in the ocean.
Money is indeed the best.
It's so nice with the sunset.
It's super nice.
Who said you can have a romantic day with 50 dollars?
Money is indeed the best.
- Money rules. - Now, that's romantic.
Yes. That's romantic.
I should work hard.
It's so beautiful.
"Will I have this kind of experience again in my life?"
It felt liberating.
By the way, the sunset is beautiful only for a fleeting moment.
I guess we've come all the way for this moment.
- Are you enjoying this enough? - Totally.
- Are you enjoying this moment? - Two hundred percent.
Me too.
We took a lot of photos of each other.
It was romantic.
You look pretty.
You're a good photographer.
Why do I look so tall?
Let's say you're tall.
My hair looks like a palm tree.
Look at my hair.
I feel like I'm going to fly away.
You look like a doctor.
That part looks like a sail.
- The cafe sells kaya toast... - Yes.
sweet coffee in Singaporean style.
(Located in Chinatown)
(An old cafe that opened in 1973)
- It has a Hong Kong vibe in a way. - Yes.
I know.
- The colour reminds me of Venice. - Yes.
(Cho A and Jae Hyung at Nanyang Old Coffee)
After you.
"Nanyang Old Coffee." This is it.
It's here.
It's super antique.
(Kaya toast and Singaporean local coffee)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Do you dip it in here? - Yes.
What does it taste like?
(Exclaiming)
It's so rich.
I must take a photo of this.
Which date was your favourite date so far?
I feel like I know, though.
Me? The date yesterday.
I don't know why I'm so confused...
as if I was a teenage boy.
But I feel like...
- this is my first time dating. - Does it feel like that?
Really?
- For real? - His heart is fluttering so much.
- Was he that nervous? - I didn't know that.
The way he put it...
- sounds so genuine. Right? - Yes.
Jae Hyung, for real?
He's completely different from the beginning.
Yes. I can feel his sincerity from his words too.
I realized again...
that I treat my female friends differently...
from the girls I'm interested in.
Once I like someone romantically,
I can't be myself around them.
- I become stiff. - Right.
- You feel like you become a fool. - Yes.
Now that I think about it,
I wonder if that was why...
- I was uncomfortable around her. - Right.
For some reason, she didn't make me feel comfortable.
I think he liked her from the start.
We didn't know what Jae Hyung was like,
so we simply thought he gave up on her,
- but he didn't. - No.
Do you think he liked her when they met at the rooftop?
Yes.
He talked about the squid for no reason.
When the men had a choice to choose their date in Gangwon Province,
he didn't pick Ji Won because he felt uncomfortable.
- Right. - That feeling was...
Come to think of it, he was uncomfortable...
- because he was into her. - Right.
Right. When you like someone, you become tense.
- Yes. - You can't be yourself.
I wonder if that was why...
- I was uncomfortable around her. - Right.
For some reason, she didn't make me feel comfortable.
Right.
(Laughing)
I feel the same way.
I always thought that feeling stable was the most important...
and that I preferred someone comfortable...
- before I moved in here. - I see.
When we all first met, I liked someone else.
I sent my text to them.
Then I realized I was wrong.
I want to feel a little tense and nervous...
around the person I'm into.
- That's really important. - I think so.
You might feel that way as soon as you meet the person...
- Right. - or later.
- You can't even say that for sure. - Right.
Could there be someone...
whose choice changes completely within these three days?
I'm not sure. That might be a little hard.
You...
Can I ask you this?
Between your feelings for the person...
and their feelings for you,
which one do you think is stronger?
Well, we can tell...
whose feelings are stronger.
I thought I could tell too.
Yes.
Then recently, I thought...
that might not be true.
"Because I was so certain about him,"
"did I interpret his behaviour..."
"based on how I perceived it?"
I wondered.
In terms of the density of my feelings,
I'm completely packed.
- Really? - When it comes to density.
But recently, I experienced something that shook it up.
You and Se Seung...
- Are we similar? - said...
- Is that so? - something really similar.
She said something like that too.
"Was I so focused on one person..."
- "that it just went this way?" - It just went this way.
She said something like this.
I thought it was the opposite.
That Yong Woo's feelings were stronger.
One of the things she said...
was that it was her whose feelings were stronger.
She had deeper feelings for him.
It sounded like Yong Woo was taking his time to open his heart.
Here's something fascinating.
In one of our conversations recently,
he said he was doing things for me...
that he didn't normally do.
He told me this directly.
- Okay. - But why does it make me...
feel more insecure?
I don't know why.
So here's what I think it is.
I was completely absorbed in my feelings,
- Then you snapped. - then I snapped out of it.
I might have been interpreting him...
based on what seemed fitting to me.
- That kind of feeling. - As soon as I felt that way,
the way I expressed my feelings became a little cold.
I see.
I think it's kind of a catalyst...
- to talk more to him... - Is that so?
and get to know him better.
I carefully assume that you're in that process.
That's what I think.
I felt the way I felt because he said this.
"I spent many opportunities..."
- "going out with one person." - Right.
He mentioned that yesterday.
Then he asked if that was okay with me.
I see.
That question stirred up a lot of emotions in me.
- I see. - Yes.
- "Was he really worried about me?" - Right.
- "Or..." - Or...
- "Did he ask that..." - Right.
- "because he felt that way?" - Yes.
- That comment... - That's...
would have hurt her feelings deeply.
To be honest, he meant the latter.
If he really liked her, he wouldn't want to let her go.
She knew why,
- Of course, she did. - so her heart must have sunk too.
- "Was he really worried about me?" - Right.
- "Or..." - Or...
- "Did he ask that..." - Right.
- "because he felt that way?" - Yes.
That question stirred up a lot of emotions in me.
I'm not sure what Yong Woo meant, but...
I mean I don't know who he is.
Usually, what men say is...
straightforward.
If a guy asks if you're okay, he just wants to know if you are.
- Is that so? - Most of the time.
He doesn't seem...
the complicated type.
Right.
- He's very simple and clear. - You're right.
He must've been considerate of you when he said that,
but in a way, he might have wanted to check...
if you were feeling the same way.
I was in a somewhat confusing situation...
when I was on a date with Jae Hyung.
So I asked him for advice.
It'd be nice to talk to him more.
Let's go.
(Ju Yeon and Yun Jae in 3rd place take off.)
By the way, I really want to have chilli crab.
I know. I hope we can have that for dinner.
You said you liked shellfish.
We can't go out tomorrow.
I must enjoy today.
Right. You were in the house all day yesterday.
We're the ones who should have the most fun today.
- Let's have a lot of fun. - Let's do that.
(Entering Sentosa Island)
"Sentosa?" What was this place?
(Going further on tree-lined road)
What is that?
- That beach. - Beach?
It's stunning.
- It's so beautiful. - It looks like a painting.
Look at the clouds.
- They look so pretty. - It's amazing.
It's super nice.
Isn't it cold?
- Is it okay? - Yes. The water is warm.
You look like...
- a senior in college. - A senior in college?
A senior who takes good photos of his juniors?
Yes.
You look so good in photos today.
It's hard to stay at home all day.
Ju Yeon loved the ocean...
and took lots of photos.
Seeing her like that, I thought I should...
make the date enjoyable and fun for her.
- Like this? - J looks already cool.
- It looks pretty good. - Good job.
(Ju Yeon and Yun Jae in Sentosa)
- Well written. - Yes.
- I did a great job. - Well done.
It's right in front of the ocean.
(Did you miss Yun Ha during the date?)
Yes, I did think of her from time to time.
When we were on the beach,
I thought, "I'd love to come back here with Yun Ha."
(Hortus)
The flowers look beautiful.
This place makes me feel like using my arm strength was worth it.
- It's gorgeous. - I know.
- There are lots of good dishes. - Is that so?
I get to enjoy this luxury thanks to my partner.
Jung Sub let me win so you can go to a nice place.
- Yes. My brother is like that. - Our Sub.
He yields and lets me have everything.
- Good job raising your brother. - Right?
Well, you did a much better job.
Raising my sister?
I should've taught her how to do chicken fight better.
Let me serve your appetizers.
Enjoy.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Open your eyes wide.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Enjoy.
What is this?
It tastes a little like...
- Hummus. - Hummus?
Chickpeas.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
During my short stay overseas,
I loved how the food suited my taste...
even though it was completely different.
Especially the places like Chipotle.
Chipotle.
When did you first go abroad?
In 2016.
What about you?
It's similar. It was around 2017.
Now that I think about it, Yong Woo and I are...
the oldest children in our families.
We also lived abroad for a long time.
We have lots of things in common.
Things are different there,
so you shouldn't react there the way you do in Korea.
- Right. - They don't really like...
- quiet students. - True.
I've been to New Haven.
Really? Nobody knows New Haven.
- They say even Americans don't. - Right.
When I first went there, I couldn't even order coffee.
Drive-through orders are even harder.
When you're looking at the person,
- Right. You can feel something. - you feel something.
Can you finish a pint-sized mint chocolate chip ice cream...
by yourself?
I totally can.
So did you find a Han Go Eun in our house?
In our house?
Someone seems to have a similar vibe.
Did you find someone with a nice nose?
Well, they all look good.
- Their noses? - Yes.
Did you find someone good on the inside too?
Someone with good qualities...
- I think everyone is. - Everyone seems good?
Yes. That's what I think.
- Everyone has their own colour. - Everyone...
is charming in their own way.
Have you had many changes of heart here?
- So many. - Really?
What about you?
- Me? - Yes.
To be honest,
- I didn't try not to, - Okay.
but I haven't.
- For real? - Yes.
In retrospect, it must have been hard.
I guess I've had strong feelings.
You seem so relaxed.
- I am all of a sudden, right? - Yes.
I'm surprised too.
Is that how you could handle every situation so calmly?
Was there a situation where I remained calm?
I think you've always been stable.
You didn't seem to have many emotional ups and downs.
Your feelings seemed consistent.
I could see other people's feelings fluctuate.
You know you can notice those things.
So are your feelings stable these days?
It's almost like...
- Do you feel stable now? - This is...
You know this is...
- one of the variables. - Right. Today's date.
- This could become a rebellion. - Right.
(Gasping)
Yun Ha...
- Really? - Yun Ha.
So are your feelings stable these days?
It's almost like...
- Do you feel stable now? - This is...
You know this is...
- one of the variables. - Right. Today's date.
- This could become a rebellion. - Right.
(Gasping)
Yun Ha...
- Really? - Yun Ha.
- This date could become... - What?
She used a very important word, "rebellion."
When does a rebellion happen?
They happen during times of peace.
Things are stable and peaceful,
and this variable can turn everything upside down.
I feel like there'll be a turmoil once they receive the text,
"Who made your heart flutter today?"
- I'll concentrate. - Let's go. Let's concentrate.
Let's go.
They're talking until the sun goes down.
Will they conspire in treason together?
Treason.
You know this is...
- one of the variables. - Right. Today's date.
- This could become a rebellion. - Right.
- You might suddenly feel something. - Right.
- That could happen. - Yes.
I can't believe we only have three days left now.
- I know. - I can't believe it.
Who did you talk to the most among the girls?
- Among the girls? - Yes.
Your ex-roommate?
- Cho A? - Yes.
But she went to work every day, and I always went out too.
You couldn't spend much time together.
I love everyone,
but I got closer to Ji Won lately.
- Really? - We got closer.
It's so funny how it works here.
Spending time with different people can really change...
- Right. - how close you feel to them.
- You're right. That's true. - That plays a big role.
What you said is so right.
It's just about that.
It's about how much you spend the most time with.
I had...
- some kind of an enlightenment. - Realization?
You look like you got hit by something.
Something quickly passed through my mind.
You're right.
The person you spend the most time with...
becomes the brother of the person you're into.
- They could be their sibling. - Yes.
You're right.
- So I got a lot closer to Ji Won... - Ji Won.
because we spent a lot of time together.
When did you spend time together?
- Me and Ji Won? - Yes.
We came to Singapore together.
- Right. - Our rooms are close too.
- We talked a lot too. - Right.
Ji Won is fun...
- when you talk to her. - She's easygoing.
She's a fun person.
Actually, I've even had this thought.
Since a certain point,
that person and I...
only spent time with each other.
I wondered if that wasn't good and if it was restraining them.
I told them too.
What I felt was...
- I said I came to a realization. - Yes.
Here's what I meant.
- I rarely drink. - Okay.
I suddenly thought,
"Who did I drink the most with?"
"I spent quite some time with this person."
These thoughts suddenly came to mind.
I see.
Jung Sub was always there.
Right.
Yun Jae and Ji Won were always there.
- Right? - It's true.
- Cho A didn't really join us. - Right.
She wasn't at home most of the time anyway.
Yes.
When was your favourite moment since you moved in?
- Since we came to Singapore, - Singapore?
- I've been having a lot of fun. - Is that so?
- More fun than when you were there? - Yes. What about you?
I liked every moment, but what was memorable was...
- Gangneung? - Yes.
I had a lot of fun in Gangneung too.
"Have we not talked at all?"
Surprisingly, we barely talked before.
Since I first met him,
I knew that we were very similar.
I guess that's why I picked him...
based on my first impressions.
Now we're not far away...
from the final selection date.
When it comes to feelings...
If we had more time,
I could develop feelings for him, to be honest.
"If we had more time,"
"could things go differently?"
Did you expect...
to go on a date with me?
- Yes. When we got a call... - The Ring-ring Date.
- During the Ring-ring Date. - You expected it then?
From what I think,
I tried going out with different people,
but then at some point, I only went on dates with one person.
- Is that so? How many dates? - Four dates.
Well, so I feel like we went back to the beginning.
- I see. - Yes.
I went out with someone else after a long time.
That's why every comment...
felt new and refreshing.
I kept having moments...
when I looked back on my past weeks.
She's the best.
She makes me feel like I can tell her everything.
- Shall we get going? - Yes.
I enjoyed the meal.
- It was a good meal. - Yes.
- It was delicious. - I know.
(Ju Yeon and Yun Jae are headed to the next location.)
Yun Jae, you remind me of a character.
- Character? - Has anyone said that?
- Otter? - Otter? You look like an otter.
- Otter. - I see the resemblance.
- Bonobono. You look like it. - Bonobono.
Right. You look like Bonobono.
Bonobono is a sea otter, but...
You kind of look like Chipmunk.
You look like Chipmunk.
- It's the pink one, right? - Chipmunk. Wait.
Right.
- You're Chipmunk. - What does it look like?
Well, I guess I do look like it.
- You're Chipmunk. - I see the resemblance.
It's hilarious.
Something weird was added to the list.
I think it's here.
Isn't it a night market?
- Yes. Shall we go? Thank you. - Thank you.
- I can't get used to it. - This place is exotic.
I know. This is nice.
(Haji Lane)
(A narrow alley where diverse cultures coexist)
(A place where you can find colourful pubs...)
(and vibrant murals)
It's so pretty.
Yun Jae. We should...
- Swimwear. We should really get it. - We should definitely get it.
I like this better.
This is better? Okay.
Should we buy something like sandals?
It sounds good.
- Like matching items. - Right.
The bracelets look good too, right?
- You have pretty hands. - I do?
- Should we get this? - This one?
We got matching bracelets to remember today.
(They got matching bracelets although they speak formally.)
I've been wearing it since that evening.
I got a good one thanks to you.
- Let's get out. - Yes.
(Mandarin Oriental)
Gosh.
- I'm so glad it's outside. - It's so nice.
- It's a relief. - The weather is also great.
- Should we sit here? - This is the prettiest spot.
- Oh, my. - Gosh.
What's behind you is the view of those buildings.
There's a swimming pool right here.
Is it okay for us to enjoy such a luxury?
It's thanks to you.
You're the best.
- That looks so pretty. - Seriously.
The night view is amazing.
Let's eat a lot of delicious food.
Let's eat a lot.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Let's enjoy the luxury.
Here it is.
- Thank you. - It's chicken.
It looks good.
People told me to take pictures earlier.
"Take pictures of what you eat."
It looks good.
- Let's enjoy it. - Let's enjoy it.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
What was the name of this pasta dish?
- Bolognese. - Bolognese.
- It's so good. - I'm so happy.
- I'm so happy. - I'm so happy.
Do you have an English name?
- My name? - You look like a Max.
Or an Andrew.
- Me? Andrew? - Yes. You look like an Andrew.
- I need to change my name. - So what is it?
- It's James. - James?
James sounds...
- a little cheesy to me. - "Cheesy?"
Cheesy.
But James is the name my mom thought of.
Your mom?
That's such a cool name. Why?
You mom gave you the name?
Yes. My mom likes James Bond.
"Let me call you James." That's how it happened.
James suits you so well.
What's your English name?
Me? Elly.
- Elly? - Yes.
- How about Kelly? - Kelly?
- The delivery. - Kelly?
(He blurts out anything as he's hungry.)
(Growling)
- Kelly. - My stomach growled.
Was it you?
I thought it was the car.
(The sound was quite heavy.)
It wasn't that loud.
It was a cute sound.
- Right. - Why am I so hungry?
The place we're going to is...
I should check the prices.
It's from 20 dollars to 30 dollars.
We'll barely eat.
"Per person?"
Per person?
(They only have 35 dollars left.)
We're doomed.
Now, we...
(The place they arrived at while feeling hungry)
(A night market that opens among skyscrapers every night)
(Lau Pa Sat Satay Street)
(During the day, it's a road where cars pass by,)
(but every evening from 7pm, it's closed off for skewer stalls.)
(Ji Won and Jung Sub in Lau Pa Sat)
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
- This is crazy. - This is amazing.
- Gosh, it looks so good. - It looks delicious.
- Oh, my. - It looks so good.
- Oh, my gosh. It looks so... - I...
- I want to try the chicken skewer. - It's so nice.
It'd be amazing just to smell it.
I honestly like this kind of food more than expensive ones.
- It's the real deal. - It's the real deal.
- We have pho, sister. - It looks good.
His Korean is so good. "Sister."
- Did he say "sister?" - He called me sister.
I'm not going there.
It looks so good.
The shrimp look delicious.
I love it. This is crazy.
Thank you.
(The food that makes their eyes widen)
- This is for two people. - I think we should eat this.
- This is for three people. - Is it...
- I think we should eat this. - This one is for how many people?
- It's for 2 people. - For 2 people?
- It's nice. - Yes. It's nice.
It's 28 Singapore dollars, and we got 35.
Then we'll have seven Singapore dollars left.
Okay.
(They'll have as much as 7 dollars after ordering a set for 2 people.)
Excuse me.
What can we buy for seven dollars?
Seven dollars? Nothing.
(7 dollars? Nothing.)
- "Seven dollars? Nothing." - "Seven dollars? Nothing."
Okay.
- "Seven dollars? Nothing." - "Nothing."
Okay. So sad.
Wait. It's here.
- It's 11 dollars? - It's 11 dollars.
We can't.
We have only seven dollars.
- Chocolate drinks. - Or we could get a Coke Zero.
It's two dollars.
We can afford it if it's two dollars.
Let's get two of these and set A from earlier.
- That will do. - We'll have three dollars left.
- We can get something we want... - For three dollars.
for three dollars.
We were so frugal.
I like things like this.
Spending within the budget.
We have three dollars left.
- I'm so sad. - We have three dollars left.
- This is nice. It smells so good. - It smells amazing.
- We smell it instead of eating it. - That's what we're doing.
(They're eating the smell.)
- It's so delicious. - Yes, it's so good.
- Shall we try it? - Yes.
Let's eat quickly. Here.
Thank you.
Gosh.
(Lightheaded)
What's this?
- It's so good that it makes me mad. - This is insane.
Would you like to try the meat I'm giving to you?
Yes.
- Oh, my. - How is it?
The shrimp is crazy.
(Laughing)
Is it crazy?
Let's put them together.
It does look like a heart.
(A shrimp heart)
In 1, 2, 3.
This is the best shrimp I've ever had in my life.
- It's so good. - It feels like a paradise...
as I'm eating this...
in a state like this.
- It's interesting. - Yes.
Eating skewers among tall buildings.
That's what I'm saying.
Lau Pa Sat...
had the atmosphere I really like.
It's a skewer street,
but it's surrounded...
by fancy skyscrapers,
which was very interesting and fun.
You can't say you visited Singapore if you haven't been here.
- Right. I want to come again. - Yes.
We're surrounded by tall buildings and...
How much is it?
Three dollars.
(They only have 3 dollars left.)
- How much is this? - Two dollars.
Two dollars?
- She gave it to you. - Thank you so much.
Okay.
- Two dollars? - Yes.
An old lady came.
People should peel the shrimp.
So she was selling wet wipes there.
She knows how to sell.
She came where people needed wet wipes.
I'll give it to her.
Two dollars? Thank you.
(They pay 2 dollars to the genius seller as if they're in a trance.)
- We're spending wisely. - Yes.
We spent exactly within the budget.
- We didn't even leave a coin. - We didn't even leave a coin.
We have one dollar.
- We have 1 dollar left? - Yes. We have 1 dollar left.
- I'm still hungry, though. - The shrimp is so good.
Can we not eat this part?
I don't know.
(He eats the shrimp head.)
You can't eat it, can you?
Can you eat it?
I just tried it.
I think I can eat it.
(He chews the shrimp tail.)
Jung Sub tried hard...
to eat every part of the shrimp.
I felt bad for him.
Eat this.
Really? Thank you.
(Eating)
(Someone sits next to them with broth at that moment.)
I want to order a lot of shrimp.
- I know. - Beer and shrimp.
- We... - It looks so good.
If she was Korean, I would've talked to her right away.
Now that I ate some, I can see...
- the surroundings. - I know.
(Glancing)
(Their eyes are fixed on the next table.)
It'd be amazing if she could give us...
a bite of noodles.
Should we push our table a little bit?
(Trying to sit together)
- That's a good idea. - Put them together.
Put them together.
(Shaking)
I kept looking at the table next to us.
I kept looking.
The lady who sat at the next table...
and I made eye contact about 15 times.
But she didn't give anything to me.
It was my ninth time I made eye contact with her.
She might give it to me soon.
I'll make something good at home.
- Let's have a second round at home. - Let's do it.
You ate only a little.
I'm full just by watching you eat.
Oh, my gosh.
Going out with Ji Won...
for the first time,
I thought we were like-minded.
It became clearer.
I had a lot of fun during our date.
Me too.
- What did the others do? - What did they do?
Everyone might come at 12am.
You're going out on a date tomorrow, right?
Yes.
Who are you going to choose?
Me? Well...
I'm curious.
I want to leave no regrets.
You want to leave no regrets.
- Someone else... - I have an idea.
It'd be fun if we go out...
with Yun Jae and Yun Ha.
Has their relationship become stable?
I don't know.
- Right. It could change. - I have no idea.
Yes. It might completely change.
They went out...
- with different people today. - Right.
No.
- No! - Stop!
Stop!
- I think I have good instincts. - Stop the drama!
When I talked to her on the first day,
I asked if there was anyone she hasn't talked with.
She said she hasn't talked with Yong Woo.
I asked if she regretted it.
"I don't have regrets for now."
So I was relieved.
- But eventually, they went out. - It became like this.
- It happened. - So...
No!
- Please! - Please!
Stop.
(The younger siblings are worried a lot.)
Yong Woo...
is fun, reliable,
and has a lot of experience.
But my brother...
would be sweeter to her, right?
I see.
Yong Woo is such a nice person.
Yes. He's nice.
But it feels like...
Unless they flirt like crazy...
"Unless they flirt like crazy."
Unless they're unbelievably flirty,
unless an unexpected event occurs...
Should we make an unexpected change?
How can we make an unexpected change?
We can't.
Why can't we?
Is there someone who can do that?
- It's so interesting. - I know.
- It's so fun. - It's so fun.
(Marina Barrage)
(If you go up along the walk,)
(you can see the open night view.)
(They're going on a picnic.)
It was in the back on the first day.
- Yes. - Is that the moon?
- Where? - Over there.
I've never seen the moon this close.
Look at the back.
Gosh.
It's amazing.
- Oh, my gosh. - It's wonderful, isn't it?
Oh, my.
- Sitting on a mat like this is... - Yes.
Having a budget of 100 dollars...
- is nice in its own way. - Yes.
Jung Sub and Ji Won had a budget of 50 dollars.
So they said they were going to ride a bicycle.
Right.
Did they ride a bicycle?
But it rained.
- I suddenly want to play music. - It's a good idea.
- It's good, right? - Yes.
- Is it nice when you lie down? - Yes, it's good.
Gosh.
Why are they not doing the tree show?
I think that's the show.
Oh, my.
You got up at the perfect time.
It started just a minute ago.
Tonight, we present the enchanted forest.
Grab your cameras and enjoy the show.
(Gardens by the Bay Supertree Show is held twice every evening,)
(creating a mystical atmosphere with lights and music.)
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
This is like "Avatar."
I know.
It's so pretty.
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
- It's so impressive. - It's so cool. Oh, my gosh.
- I play this every day. - You do?
With the orchestral piece of music I play often...
and beautiful lights moving around,
it was fantastic.
- I heard... - Yes.
it's best to enjoy while lying down.
- It sounds amazing. - Yes.
Yong Woo...
spread the shirt he prepared.
He prepared it.
I was so thankful.
I was touching, to be honest.
He was thoroughly prepared.
That's more romantic.
They're lying down together then?
This is bad.
This is getting worse.
What should we do with them?
- But it looks amazing. - It's so cool.
I want to go there. I'll go.
I should go to Singapore.
This is unbelievable.
Is this right?
- Sorry? - Is this how you do it?
Two, three, four.
Yes. This is how you do it.
The Supertree Show...
was just as impressive and beautiful...
as the flamingo...
from the day before.
It felt like the climax had begun.
It was perfect.
It was wonderful.
Gosh.
- Oh, my. - This is crazy.
This is insane.
Gosh.
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
It really makes you say, "Oh, my."
- Amazing. - Amazing.
- That's Marina Bay. - Yes.
Gosh.
This is nice.
I think you're the type who has a lot of thoughts.
- Me? - Yes.
I don't have that many thoughts.
I'm quite simple too.
What was my first impression?
Oh, my gosh.
I have the same feelings I had...
in episode 2 or 3.
- Right. - Right.
- Is this allowed? - It's starting again.
It feels so weird to see them talking about things people say...
- when they start getting to know. - Yes. It's so weird.
It's like it's the beginning of the show...
when they met first.
What was my first impression?
You seemed very bright...
and energetic.
I see.
How about me?
I usually don't ask these questions to people.
- You don't? - No. So I don't really know.
- Most of the time... - You're not so curious about it.
No. I don't really ask questions like this.
"How was I today?"
You don't care about those things?
- Are you always confident? - I...
But you put it nicely.
- I rarely asked those questions. - Okay.
Then I heard people talking about me...
as I came here.
- How you see yourself... - Yes.
and how others see you are different.
Yes. It was the first time I got to hear about it.
- It must've felt new. - About their opinions on me.
- It must've been interesting. - Yes.
So what was my first impression?
You seemed...
very cool.
You left a good impression on me.
That's a relief.
It seemed you didn't care...
- about others' opinions. - Me?
Should I put it this way?
You didn't seem nervous.
That's what I felt.
You didn't look nervous.
I think I'm good at pretending to be like that.
- It left a positive impression. - I see.
If you think about it, first impressions are very important.
Because you have a feeling.
- Right. You do. - You know...
if you'd be compatible or not.
I didn't know in the past because I didn't meet many people.
But now, I can kind of predict...
- the result. - Yes.
- You have a feeling, right? - Yes.
When it feels like we're not compatible,
I slowly close my mind.
My heart is open at first,
- but it closes later. - Yes.
It felt like she was saying it on purpose.
"When you're not compatible, you're not compatible."
It felt like a perfect prescription for me.
Today,
after reviewing a lot...
- with a different person, - Yes.
I have a lot of thoughts I didn't have before.
- You do? - Yes.
There were things I didn't see on purpose.
Now, it feels clearer.
What is clearer?
I'll give you some time to organize your thoughts.
Let me appreciate the moon.
I haven't gone out on a date with someone else...
- for a long time until today. - Yes.
The recent few days felt long to me.
It felt very long.
I went out on a date with someone else because I wanted to.
- When we came here earlier, - Yes.
I said I tried to cater to the other...
- even when we weren't compatible. - Yes.
I think this is the difference.
As time goes by,
I see both the parts that I like and find attractive about the person...
and the parts that don't match...
- my expectations. - Right.
So it's about if I focus on the attractive side...
or...
if I care more about the negative side.
I think I found the answer today.
- After talking with me? - Yes. After talking...
with a different person.
I guess...
- it opened your eyes to it. - Yes. It opened my eyes a little.
You might've not known that you were worried about it at that time.
- You just let it pass by. - Yes.
- You adapted to it. - Yes.
That's why you didn't know.
- It was something like that. - Right.
You really got me.
Should I say he's quite defensive...
about showing his feelings?
I thought we were similar in that sense.
He was thinking a lot.
I wondered what side of me...
made him think so much,
which made me have a lot of thoughts.
The clouds over there are moving fast.
Right.
- The wind is blowing. - Yes.
I thought it became a little hard to be in a good relationship...
before I came here.
Pure and romantic love.
"We can love each other..."
"just the way we are."
I think...
I want to have something like that.
I keep wanting things like that.
I want it more...
because of my ex-girlfriend.
At first,
my ex-girlfriend and Ji Won looked so similar.
So I became a little cautious.
I understand.
My ex said...
I wasn't her priority.
If I meet...
someone nice here...
and like her,
I want to experience...
a serious and valuable relationship.
That's why I said...
I was extremely careful...
about the final decision earlier.
I was very certain...
- about my feelings at first. - Yes.
So I didn't think...
of getting to know someone else.
Once I look at something, I go without looking at other things.
I go straight.
But I do wish...
that I had talked to other people back then.
- I see. - Yes.
The person you like versus...
the person who likes you. Who would you choose?
- The person I like. - Right?
- I'm like that too. - Right.
People say that those who are on...
the receiving end of love are happier.
I think that's what differentiates the two...
for me.
- I get what you mean. - Yes.
He... I mean, that person...
- is sweet and gentle... - Yes.
- and kind and treats you nicely. - Yes.
But he has a big ego.
I'm not sure who the one...
who's expressing his feelings toward you is, though.
It's either Yun Jae or Jung Sub.
Those are the only options.
What? Yun... Is it Jung Sub?
What made you feel that way?
He told me.
- He told you? - Yes.
Then it must be Yun Jae.
Why? Is Yun Jae the one who would actually say something?
No, it's just that Jung Sub...
has been sending messages to Se Seung the whole time.
Wait, what? Are there six guys?
I can't figure this out.
- Well... - So the two of you spoke?
- Yes. - Since we got here?
No, it was before we came here.
Really?
Wait, this is so confusing.
Well, anyway. That's just how I feel.
I was a bit surprised...
because I didn't expect that at all.
I was slightly shocked...
since what I heard was new to me.
Gosh. It's not over until it's over.
I feel like you could be the one...
whose feelings change within the next three days.
That's why I told you earlier...
because I feel like there could be people...
who make completely different decisions.
Wait, then...
But I'm not sure. But women have intuition.
Women's intuition.
- Yes. - I think that's very scary.
I really think that it's so scary.
A woman's hunch is very accurate.
It's right every time, not just most of the time.
That's why I feel like...
he's conflicted between me and someone else.
I think all you have to do...
give Ji Won assurance and it'll be okay.
- Ji Won? - Yes.
I don't confuse people.
- It seems like it. - Right.
I'm not sure myself,
which is why I don't know what to do.
I'm not the type to weigh my options...
once I am sure.
I really thought you two were clearly into each other.
But you're saying that might not be the case.
This is going to be quite interesting.
This is interesting all of a sudden.
Thank you.
(Jung Sub and Ji Won quickly returned to the house.)
- The house looks silent, - What?
- Jung Sub. It's silent. - I see.
It's very quiet here, right?
Let's go wash our hands.
The shrimp...
The shrimp probably still remains.
I'm going to wash my hands and change my clothes.
Sounds good.
Gosh, this is much better.
(Takes a seat)
- This is nice. - This is nice.
Cheers.
(They're finally drinking beer.)
That's good.
What was your favourite date so far?
Today was... The first date.
But that wasn't a date, though.
The first date?
- That was really... - I knew it.
What? What first one?
The first one. Your very first date.
My very first... No, I meant the first one here.
- That wasn't a date. Yes. - The first one here?
Are you talking about the date I went on with Yong Woo?
- Yes. - I see.
Because you chose him at first glance.
That means a lot.
That's why I said that nonsense about leading people on.
"Nonsense."
"I should talk to more people,"
was how I used to feel.
But that's when I started to think...
that could make some people feel uncomfortable,
- and... - Gosh, really?
I'm so sorry.
No, you don't have to be.
At the time, I did think that I made a mistake.
It's like I felt chills.
I was like, "That's not what I was trying to say."
There's no reason for you to be sorry...
because since Gangwon Province,
I became curious about Jae Hyung.
So I decided that...
that's who I should focus on.
Hi.
(Yun Ha and Yong Woo head home.)
Spending this time with you...
helped me process the dilemma I had this morning...
throughout the day.
And I think that's right.
- I've actually said it once. - Yes.
I once said that you're like the salt and light...
- of our group. - Me?
- Yes. - Gosh.
- That's so touching. - Seriously. Like we need you.
You made that analogy?
Yes.
She has a great personality.
She livens up the mood and responds really well.
So she's like the salt and light that we need...
within this group.
I could be wrong, though.
What do you mean? I was tearing up just now.
I said something along these lines.
If we're having this much fun,
you make the fun this big.
You really think I'm important...
He said I was important.
He thinks of me as an important person.
I was thankful. I was so moved...
that I almost cried at that moment. I choked up a bit.
But then he started talking about something else,
so I was just like, "I see."
I think I had a lot...
on my mind yesterday.
- Really? - I didn't even realize but I did.
I guess I need to practice thinking about these things.
You know why you're like that?
Because you've lived alone for a long time.
I've been living with my family this whole time.
- Still. When you were abroad... - When I was abroad.
I see.
And you just take care of things on your own.
It's become a habit. I'm kind of like that too.
- I think I'm like that too. - Yes.
This is the first time I've even thought of it.
That it's because I've lived alone for a long time.
- Stop. - You're right. That's crazy.
- Stop. - What are you?
Can you read minds?
I feel like we haven't been on a date until now...
so we could talk at this moment.
- Really? - Yes.
(Gosh)
Have you ever felt this way before?
This person is very similar to you.
So similar that...
you feel like you shouldn't be with them.
- Do you get what I mean? - Yes.
- I feel like you might. - Yes, I have.
I feel like the way we think is very similar,
and we're just the same from A to Z.
So for me, this could actually be...
- this... - Poison for you.
That's how I feel.
- That's why... - You could butt heads a lot.
- That's right. - Or like each other even more.
What are you?
But I feel like even if you may butt heads,
being similar is better. That's just me.
Right.
We're so similar...
that I feel like I've turned my back on her a few times...
thinking this won't work.
But why? What scared you that you turned your back on her?
It's not like I was scared.
I think she felt so similar to me...
that she started feeling less like someone I could date.
So it's not like you were reluctant.
It just naturally happened...
(Thinking)
because you're too similar.
That's something I should... You know?
- You should think about it. - I need some time to do that.
Yes. I'll give you time.
I'll just leave you alone.
He kept saying things I couldn't understand at all.
He would start saying something and then he'd stop all of a sudden.
So I look at him, and he's lost in thought.
"I see. He needs time to think."
"Go ahead. Think."
And I'd just stare out the window.
Yong Woo and I had a lot of incoherent conversations,
but it was nice.
So we had fun at that moment.
I do feel like there are times I feel very confused,
although I probably shouldn't.
It's always really unpredictable.
- Right. - Yes.
It's really unbelievable.
Are you crying?
I was just moved when you said "unbelievable."
So when did you go to China...
and for what?
After I completed my Master's,
I was the principal cello at an orchestra there.
That's an amazing career.
I just worked hard as if I was studying abroad.
I like Yun Jae because...
I can tell he's an easy-going person who studied abroad.
Why would you talk about that all of a sudden?
Since we were talking about studying abroad.
Yun Jae was abroad the longest with Ji Won.
In the hideout at night,
- a few of us meet up for drinks. - Right, I heard.
And the more I see Yun Jae, the more he seems like a good person.
I was just reminded of him all of a sudden.
So are you saying you're pushing Yun Jae away because you're similar?
What?
That's what you sounded like just now.
No. Wait, say that one more time.
You were attracted to Yun Jae because you were similar,
but you pushed him away?
So did I push Yun Jae away because...
I felt like we were too similar?
Isn't that what you were saying?
You're like a genius.
Only a genius would interpret what I said like that.
I can't seem to grasp the flow of your logic.
You're jumping from here to there.
In conclusion, thanks to you, I was able to look back at myself.
So thank you. That's it.
Yun Ha must have thought to herself, "What's wrong with him?"
But I was thinking about these things by myself in the car.
I couldn't really tell her everything,
so I was just thinking to myself.
I just understood the situation...
off of the things she said...
and how she responded to what I said.
I just organized my thoughts.
Well, you might have noticed,
but I was thinking about how I spent most of my time...
with just one person despite the opportunities that I was given.
But then, I was looking back,
thinking about who I talked to the most in Seoul,
who I spent the most time with,
who I had fun being around.
All of those things kind of hit me in the head,
now that I was thinking about it.
So I came to some kind of realization...
thinking, "Yes, that's right."
There must have been some parts...
that I had pushed aside and didn't realize.
Those thoughts came to me, perhaps a little too late.
I was thinking until the very last moment when we got out of the car.
So what I realized was that there are parts where we butt heads,
but it's not like either one of us is wrong. We're just different.
That's when I felt at ease and made up my mind.
I thought that now was a great time...
for me to speak with Cho A.
We dressed well today.
Yes, your outfit was amazing.
Anyone there?
- Is anyone there? - Yes.
- You're back. - Hi.
Hi.
We didn't have enough money,
- so we came back early... - You came back early.
- and we're eating food... - We didn't have money,
- that we had here. - so we're eating food here.
That's nice.
- Money is... - How was it?
Today was insane.
- Really? - Yes.
They're here to brag
Are you here to brag?
- Get out. - What?
- Get out. - Get out.
- I don't want to look at you. - That reminds me of Jung Sub.
- This is Jung Sub. - Yong Woo, your lats...
Do you know what I realized today?
I should work out my arms harder.
Yong Woo. You almost lost,
- you know that right? - I was so surprised earlier.
I couldn't move my wrists for a while once it was over.
Why did you buy these when you were broke?
- We weren't given mercy at all. - Really?
We couldn't even drink beer because we didn't have money.
I really considered panhandling.
- I like your outfit today. - I see.
We're like the rebellion of the youngest.
You two are on the floor and we're on the couch.
The rebellion of the youngest.
We're actually more comfortable on the floor.
That's right.
Were you born in the Joseon Dynasty?
You're not a pilot from the Joseon Dynasty, are you?
(He passed the pilot's state exam in the Joseon Dynasty.)
She was practically like Dr. Oh Eun Yeong today.
- What do you mean? - Really?
Did you have a therapy session?
She really heard me out.
I didn't expect to open up...
and talk to her the way that I did.
You're kind of dressed like a shaman today too.
"Tell me, child."
- Tell me. - Tell me what's on your mind.
(Ju Yeon and Yun Jae are back.)
I'm going to keep it safe.
- Welcome. - What?
You came back early?
Yes, we came back early.
Se Seung must be having the time of her life.
This is Ju Yeon's.
I thought you said "kissing."
- I thought you said "kissing" too. - "Se Seung must be kissing."
- Hello, everyone. - Hello.
- Gosh, you look so pretty. - Gosh.
You look so pretty.
Was that your outfit when you left?
- It's so nice. - I was so curious about...
what you did today.
Me? Us? We're hungry right now.
The bikes were 15 dollars.
- That's expensive. - So we had 35 dollars left.
And then we were so hungry...
that we started frothing at the mouth.
Sir, your order of soju is here.
- Goodness. Thank you. - Gosh.
- I saw the table... - And...
fried fish. It was a combination of the four.
That must have been delicious.
You went to the beach.
(Ju Yeon and Yun Jae, Sentosa)
- But I... - You went to Sentosa.
We went here and there.
The place we went to yesterday.
At night, we went here.
I want to see that picture too.
Gosh, the vibes are great in this picture.
Let me see.
What? You look like newlyweds.
You look like newlyweds who live in Pangyo New Town.
Pangyo New Town.
That's where I got the tetanus shot.
Right, I'm sorry.
(Cho A and Jae Hyung are on their way back to the house.)
About what the others are saying.
- You're curious? - It's driving me insane.
I'm curious too.
I wonder how their dates went.
They must have sides to them...
that are different than what we see when we're all together.
I, myself, am very different.
I heard that from both of them.
I see.
- You've been on a date with him... - Of course.
- already. - Yes.
That must have been a good experience.
I was very surprised.
- That's when you talked. - Yes.
So like... How deep was it?
Enough for me to want to avoid talking about it.
Really?
Yes. So I think...
my heart was heavy at the time.
(Cho A and Jung Sub's date in Gangwon Province)
(I really like the smile you show me...)
(when our eyes briefly meet.)
(I don't really want to give up.)
(The honest and direct way Jung Sub expressed his feelings...)
- Jung Sub. - Yes.
(had made Cho A feel uncomfortable.)
Back then, my feelings were already...
noticeably leaning toward one person,
so my actions made that very clear.
I think he was kind of hurt by that,
the way I saw it.
After some time passed,
I started feeling bad about it.
The way I understood it was...
that she was telling me the reason why her feelings toward...
one person was wavering.
There's only one person she has feelings for right now.
And that would be Yong Woo.
But I think she's aware of it, herself.
Choosing the other person...
wouldn't be because she wants to date him.
The next three days are about to be difficult for everyone, then.
From my perspective,
there are so many things that are new to me.
Both Yong Woo and Jung Sub...
seemed to be sure about their feelings.
But everything's complicated now.
It's like, they seemed like...
they were placid because they were sure.
But on the inside,
there was a storm brewing.
I wonder what's going to happen and how.
I really can't predict anything.
I used to have an idea, but now...
Me too. I thought I was the only one who wasn't sure.
I thought I was the only one who was confused.
But everything's messed up now.
(Cho A and Jae Hyung are back.)
Thank you.
- I had fun. - Yes. Talking to you...
helped me organize my thoughts...
and it was fun.
They're in here.
- They're in there? - Hi.
- You're back. - Hi, hello.
- I see you had a lot to drink. - Yes, I did.
We didn't get to have dinner.
Really? We didn't...
have a lot of money to eat either.
That's why you shouldn't have lost.
We bought the most things.
We had the least amount of money but we still bought the most things.
What did you buy?
Did you ride the bike?
Yes. The bike.
- It was more like a rickshaw. - A rickshaw.
- Duck boat. - You won't be able to see our feet.
It's very visible, though.
Okay.
The reaction I expected from Jae Hyung was...
"Really? We were fourth place too, so..."
"we weren't able to do this and that."
But instead he said, "That's why you shouldn't have lost."
So I was a bit taken aback and hurt.
All right.
- I don't think it's me. - Then...
- it's probably about tomorrow. - It's the two of them.
Should we all head downstairs...
- Let's go downstairs. - together? Okay.
(Se Seung and Cheol Hyeon at Mandarin Oriental)
Let's go swimming.
(Gosh)
- Gosh. - Really?
- They're going for a swim? - They look so happy.
- Gosh. - They get to go swimming too?
They're really spending the day as rich people.
It must be so nice.
The pool is 1.2m deep. How tall are you?
I'm 1.64m tall.
It's cold. It's so cold.
Here.
- I want to dunk you. Yes. - Me?
- Go ahead and try. - Push you down.
Go ahead and try.
Se Seung and I played around,
and the vibes were great.
I can't say it didn't affect how I feel in any way.
But I wasn't sure if I should send...
Se Seung a message once today's date was over.
I had such a great time from start to finish.
You're getting water on me.
Gosh, that feels great.
That night view is...
The vibes are there.
I like seeing Cheol Hyeon...
be confident like that.
- He hasn't been this way before. - Right.
The hotel pool was so romantic.
The scenery was beautiful, we could even see the moon.
Gosh, Cheol Hyeon. Look, the moon.
Breathe.
No, breathe.
- Relax? - Yes, relax.
I was going to hold you up.
Your lips are blue.
They are?
I'm not cold, though.
Are you having fun?
I feel like water must have gone up your nose.
Totally. It feels like I had wasabi.
- When we go to the pool... - Will you teach me?
That was fun.
I'm craving some ramyeon.
- I feel fresh. - I'm happy.
- Right? - Yes.
Money is scary.
This is why we have to work hard to make money.
I'm going to live diligently from now on.
Money can buy you all types of emotions.
- I mean, - Money is...
who says you can't buy happiness with money?
Right. They bought love with money.
No. I still have faith in that.
No.
Let's work hard, everyone.
We have to live diligently.
- After you. - Shall I get in first?
(They head home.)
Time passes so quickly.
Is there anything you regret?
- Anything I regret? - Yes.
There is nothing I regret. But there is some disappointment.
I wasn't like this in the past.
If I have a good memory,
it makes me thoughtful.
I think to myself, "Why was it like that?"
Let's get some sleep.
Shall we get some sleep? Let's do that.
Let's sleep for ten minutes until we reach home.
(Se Seung can't fall asleep.)
Oh, my gosh.
- Oh, my gosh. - My goodness.
- Look at that. - This is insane.
- Stop. - That facial expression...
It's a deja vu.
- I thought... - The way she looks at Jung Sub.
I thought she only made that face when she looked at Jung Sub.
- Seriously. - It was like that.
What is going through her mind?
She is confused about her emotions.
She thinks the current situation...
is wrong, but...
Doesn't it seem like she is thinking about Jung Sub?
- She is thinking about him. - She probably feels bad too.
She really liked today's date.
- Really? - Yes, that might be the case.
Let's keep watching.
- There is a chance... - Let's keep watching.
- we are confused. - Okay.
Let's keep watching.
This is driving me crazy.
- Is everyone back? - What?
Is everyone back?
(Yong Woo is sitting at the terrace.)
- Why aren't you eating? - This place is nice.
Yes, it's nice.
It's pretty. Shall I take a photo of you?
It's pretty. The lights were off yesterday.
I know.
Did rain come in?
Cho A, I have something to say.
- What? - I have something to say.
- To me? - Yes.
- What is it about? - Sit down for a second.
What is it about?
- What do you think it's about? - What?
It's something very serious.
What is it about?
After my feet got better today,
- I walked around. - Yes.
I felt grateful for yesterday.
It was a precious day,
but you looked after me by my side.
I wanted to thank you.
I see.
And if we think about it,
we kept choosing each other for the dates...
after one point.
Today, I went on a date with someone else.
It was refreshing in a way.
I don't know if it was the same for you.
And... How should I put it?
Do you remember what we talked about in the car?
Yes.
Since there was someone I held dear to my heart,
I wanted to live by her words...
even though it wasn't my style.
I wanted to do that.
I made an effort to do that...
in the past days.
But I think it didn't suit me in some ways.
I didn't know that at the time.
After living in the first-person point of view,
I took on the third-person point of view.
Had it been my usual self, I would have jumped into action...
without saying something like this.
But you know me now.
So I thought to have a conversation with you...
on my way here.
I think honesty is the best solution.
After having these thoughts,
I realized that I should relay them to you.
I wanted to have a conversation too.
Is that so?
At first, I was a bit surprised.
Like a fool,
I thought he would say something nice.
I expected him to go, "I had a date today, but..."
I sat down expecting him to say something nice.
So the effect was greater.
To be honest, I had this thought too.
This is precious time,
but you couldn't even have a meal because of me.
You did that for me,
so I hated myself for having such thoughts.
I felt like I shouldn't do that.
But that's my honest thought too.
Yes.
So I wanted to tell you about this side of me too.
I thought about the ways...
I could sugarcoat the words, but that wouldn't be right.
- I think honesty is the best. - That's right.
I am not talking about a parting.
A meeting is very important.
I think it's important...
to talk about these things.
I don't understand what he is talking about.
He isn't being honest.
- I know. - He is pretending to be honest.
He isn't the type to have a way with words.
When you talk, what's important isn't the words that come out.
What's important is...
how the other person understands those words.
He doesn't have a way with words.
It must be very difficult for Cho A.
I don't think she understood.
- He is confusing her. - Yes.
His words are hard to decipher.
Why does he keep making her think alone?
It's like, "What is he getting at?"
I am not talking about a parting.
A meeting is very important.
I think it's important...
to talk about these things.
- So... - At first, I was like,
"How am I supposed to decipher his words?"
"How am I supposed to understand his words?"
"Did I understand him correctly?"
"Did he mean what I thought he meant?"
Perhaps he liked me...
but came to change his mind because an action of mind...
caused a misunderstanding.
Perhaps he is yielding...
in order to give me more chances...
because he is considerate.
Perhaps it comes...
from an instinctive, honest pull. That's what I am curious about.
It's strange, but for the first time upon joining the show...
and coming to Singapore,
the content of my message...
might change.
So I wanted to tell you that.
It's understandable.
What are you supposed to say upon hearing those words?
You can't give an answer.
I would go, "So what?"
It's as MIYEON said. You can't say anything to that.
If he wants to send a message, he should just go ahead and do that.
- That conversation... - I don't understand.
The person who heard those words would feel powerless.
I don't know what he wants her to do.
So he wanted to have a conversation like this.
But a conversation is all about exchanging words.
He simply went, "I don't think I will send you a message today."
It was a bit like that.
It feels like she got all the burden.
Cho A did.
I thought about it a lot.
I did feel it little by little.
Feel what?
- The change in your mind. - Really?
So I did expect this outcome...
- somewhat. - Really?
Your intention matters the most.
I hope that you will be honest to yourself.
That's what I am doing.
(Cheol Hyeon comes back after a date.)
- Hello. - You are back.
Yes.
So...
during the remainder of our time, you and I...
It feels like I am breaking up with you.
I think I was the most honest one...
in here.
So I wanted to share how I felt.
I have a question.
You told me that you hated yourself for acting...
a certain way.
Which aspects did you hate?
When I was with other people...
How should I put it?
I felt good emotions and excitement.
- So to you, - I see.
I expressed my feelings...
as if they were saved somewhere.
But now that I was faced with the moment...
the means and results of my expressions could change,
I hated myself for some reason.
I don't understand myself either.
Okay.
To be honest, I felt shocked.
Although I was feeling the change in his behaviours,
it was quite shocking to hear it...
in definite words.
I wanted to ask him about everything,
but it was a bit hurtful.
I didn't want to hear it directly.
It seemed like he no longer had feelings for me.
Asking him if he no longer had feelings for me...
would have been hurtful.
Having that confirmed right away would have been hurtful.
So I said, "Okay." I accepted what happened.
Shall we go and eat something?
Okay.
Go ahead.
Shall I go ahead? Okay.
(Yong Woo leaves first.)
Did you have a good date?
- Did you have fun? - I had fun.
What was the conversation about?
Did you have a good time?
I had a good time.
People were eating delivered food.
I should go and steal a bite.
(Cho A becomes thoughtful on the terrace.)
(She leaves after pondering for a while.)
She must be really hurt.
She must be really upset.
Had I been Cho A, I would have bawled.
Gosh, it's sad.
A woman's hunch is...
- It's so scary. - I know.
It's because of his sense of responsibility.
He thinks he needs to be...
responsible for his choice.
Yong Woo is someone who is very sensitive...
about being responsible.
- This is quite open too. - Yes.
So he suppressed his honest feelings for other women...
because he valued his sense of responsibility more.
I think this happened because he felt like...
he should maintain his initial feelings until the end.
I am amazed by the extent of his cluelessness...
which stemmed...
from his sense of responsibility...
- overshadowing his feelings. - It's understandable.
I can't do this. I am so stressed out.
- I don't know. - MIYEON is stressed out.
Had they had this conversation sooner,
things wouldn't have gotten so bad.
Yong Woo kept up the facade for too long.
Since he is doing this toward the end,
I don't understand him.
He could have been more free.
That's right. I agree.
He didn't know about his true feelings...
until now.
But because of something or someone,
Yong Woo faced a side of him he didn't know about.
Since he didn't want to deceive the other person,
he honestly revealed how he felt.
He can't hide his feelings...
and make the other person think that he continues to like her.
I think this is better.
Why isn't Cho A coming downstairs? We need to eat.
Cho A, hurry up and eat.
It isn't popular.
Hurry up and eat.
- Ju Yeon. - Yes?
Come here for a second.
(Yong Woo calls over Ju Yeon.)
- What is it? - What? It's nothing.
Today, I had a refreshing moment after going on dates...
with the same person.
Yes.
It was nice, wasn't it?
It was nice, but the point is a bit different.
I thought my decision wouldn't change,
but waves came.
I see. Was it because of the date you had today?
Yes. But it didn't happen because I had someone.
It went from yes to the middle.
(I see.)
Do you understand?
The new date was like a big day.
To be honest, I don't understand...
what you are talking about.
I had a talk with Cho A just now.
The message I will send today...
might be different from the last time.
I told her everything honestly.
I also had...
Was there a change in the atmosphere?
- Things have been quite one-sided. - Yes.
It was like a one-way street.
Talking to Yun Jae...
made me see the sides...
I wouldn't have seen if it weren't for today's date.
- I saw those sides of Yun Jae. - I know. I had the same thought.
You are like me.
I see that our faces weren't the only thing we had in common.
I can't believe it.
I hope you won't do this.
Even if your feelings haven't changed,
the little damages...
you might not want to tell me about could pile up.
Those damages might make you close up...
(He is worried about Ju Yeon making a dishonest choice.)
because you don't want to get hurt.
But if you do that...
You will regret it later if you live that way.
You need to be honest with yourself.
Otherwise, you might meet the best person...
and fail to show your best self.
Then you will end up running away with an excuse.
I did that many times.
In retrospect, I regret...
every single one of those occasions.
In retrospect, there was someone who could have been my spouse.
So I regret it.
You don't want me to jump to conclusions...
and run away in order to avoid getting hurt.
That's what usually happens. I have done it before.
Understood?
You told me what I needed to hear in this situation.
- Okay. - Okay?
Yes. Good luck to you too.
Good luck. Let's go and eat.
You changed many things...
in my opinion.
That might be the case.
- Se Seung, was it good? - These four...
Did you enjoy spending money?
It wasn't easy to spend money.
Just how much did you drink?
Did you drink outside?
- Did you drink here? - I drank.
We came back early and drank.
Jae Hyung.
Please don't look at me as if I am worthless.
That isn't true.
- I looked at you like this. - I see.
All right.
Here.
That's a bit... It's like this.
- It's... Yes. - Isn't it Jung Sub?
- The latissimus dorsi. - Jung Sub.
All right.
(You have 3 days before making the final decision.)
(Who made your heart flutter today?)
(Send the name and message and we will deliver it anonymously.)
It's a war.
It's a ruckus.
- I know. - I am excited and scared.
Today, it's really hard.
- Seriously. - Today, it's really hard.
All right.
(You have 3 days before making the final decision.)
(Who made your heart flutter today?)
(Send the name and message and we will deliver it anonymously.)
I had many thoughts.
It wasn't after a date with someone...
who liked me.
The message came after a date...
with someone else.
So I was curious about the result.
(To Ji Won, I want to have a time I won't regret.)
I sent it to Ji Won. "I want to have a time I won't regret."
I sent that message.
It felt so strange.
Sitting there was so hard.
(Yong Woo gets up.)
(He takes out beer.)
I thought you weren't going to drink.
Today, I can't help but drink.
Are you drinking in the end?
- Why? It's so sudden. - Is it okay to drink?
Did you have a change of heart?
It's for circulation.
Should you be drinking?
(Everyone's feelings have been sent.)
(Unsure)
I really can't predict the results today.
I mean everything.
(I want to have a time I won't regret.)
I was certain that it was from Jae Hyung.
"I want to have a time I won't regret."
That was the message.
The emoji was a must.
It showed how I felt.
After the date and before the message,
she didn't talk to me much.
I felt like she was sullen.
It felt a bit strange, so...
What? That was how I felt.
What?
(She received a message with Jae Hyung's feeling.)
(Why are you being curt?)
He broke down.
- Seriously. - He is so easy to read.
That's a facial expression I haven't seen before.
Jae Hyung is so funny.
Was I being curt?
I sent, "Why are you being curt?"
I waited for Jae Hyung to come back.
We were talking about how the date was.
(They were talking earlier.)
We didn't have much money to spend on food.
No one told you to lose, okay?
"No one told you to lose, okay?"
That was the first thing he said to me.
You won't see our feet.
I can see them fine.
It hurt my feelings.
I felt a bit embarrassed.
I was quite upset.
I didn't think that I was being curt.
Did she become sullen because of that?
I wanted to clear up the misunderstanding.
(Despite being upset, they chose each other.)
(I want to know if you had fun and if you didn't have regrets.)
I sent it to Se Seung.
I wanted to know how her date was.
(Jung Sub chose your sibling.)
I guess Jung Sub still likes Se Seung.
Perhaps he wavered for a short while.
They aren't in a relationship.
It was...
a week after he met Se Seung.
Since he sent her a message,
I thought, "I guess there aren't any major changes."
Se Seung, are you tired?
- No. - Are you okay?
You look soft.
Se Seung has so much stamina.
That's right.
I could see that during the final of the chicken fight.
The swimming pool was about to close,
but she swam diligently...
to digest the food.
Seriously.
(Thank you for giving me a fun day.)
(Let's enjoy the remaining days so that there won't be any regrets.)
(Se Seung sent a message to Cheol Hyeon.)
I sent it to Cheol Hyeon.
When we looked at the sunset on the yacht,
I thought it was nice...
to be with someone who had the same sentimentality...
and depth.
If the date brings me happiness and joy,
I think it's right to send a message to the person...
I went on a date with.
I don't know how Jung Sub will take it.
(Jung Sub doesn't receive a message.)
He sent me a message, but I didn't send him one.
My heart ached.
It wasn't like that.
I don't know how to solve this problem.
Not receiving any messages put me in a bad mood.
(No one chose your sibling.)
Cheol Hyeon and Se Seung had a great date,
so I wasn't surprised.
But the message still made my heart ache.
(Se Seung chose your sibling.)
"Did the date bring changes to their relationship?"
"I hope it goes well." I had that thought.
(Ji Won, let's go on a date!)
I sent it to Ji Won.
On the terrace, I told Ji Won that I wanted to go on a date with her.
I had never gone on a proper date with her,
so I had regrets.
I think it's Cheol Hyeon, the one I talked to the day before.
I understand why Cheol Hyeon sent Ji Won a message.
- Yes. - That's right.
- She was on his mind. - Yesterday...
But he said the date was good.
He has more feelings for JI Won.
- More feelings. - That day...
(Jae Hyung and Cheol Hyeon chose your sibling.)
Thank goodness. All right.
Now, she will do well on her own.
(Glancing over)
What are you looking at?
The two of you have similar facial expressions.
You probably do too.
It's my first connection with Ji Won.
It happened with my looks.
What an honour.
(Let's go to the gallery!)
There was a gallery she wanted to check out.
I sent her a message to go there with me.
While spending time at a bar...
What is that? It looks like a coconut.
It's a museum.
- It would be nice to go there. - Right?
"It would be nice to go there next."
We had that conversation.
I didn't have any second thoughts about sending a message to Yun Ha.
Not at all.
I like Yun Ha.
I don't think that will change.
If I get a chance to choose my next date,
I will choose Yun Ha.
I like Yun Na no matter what right now.
(It was nice to become close to you, Mr. Chipmunk.)
I think it's from Ju Yeon.
Chip... Chap?
- Chipmunk. - Yes. She called me Mr. Chipmunk.
I think it's from Ju Yeon.
I was thankful for Yun Jae.
Through Yun Jae,
I could free myself from thoughts and have a good time.
So I sent it to Yun Jae.
I had a date with Ju Yeon,
so I felt bad for her.
I was sitting next to Yun Jae.
I could feel that he felt bad.
(Laughing)
But it's nothing to feel bad about.
(No one chose your sibling.)
I think it's like that.
- You know about Jjokki Jjokki. - Jjokki Jjokki.
You know about Jjokki Jjokki.
(Did you have a good time with Dr. Oh Eun Yeong?)
He received a message.
He received it from the one next to him.
She listened to his worries.
"Did you have a good time with Dr. Oh Eun Yeong?"
- It's Yun Ha. - Yun Ha is referring to herself.
- Yun Ha. - "I am Dr. Oh Eun Yeong."
She was saying, "I am your Dr. Oh Eun Yeong."
"How was your time with me?"
"I will solve all worries."
That's right. She wants him to come closer.
Dr. Oh Eun Yeong takes care of all worries.
Their date was like a therapy session.
(Did you have a good time with Dr. Oh Eun Yeong?)
(Well)
I thought very hard about that matter.
Even while having a strange conversation,
I thought very hard about it.
I wanted to send it to Yong Woo.
Due to various situations,
I couldn't help but worry.
(Yun Ha sent a message to Yong Woo after many thoughts.)
I received a message from Ju Yeon, but not Yun Ha.
Still, I made my choice.
Yun Ha made her choice.
I think I need to accept it.
I wasn't happy with it.
I am anxious that Yun Ha might not send me...
more messages.
(Ju Yeon chose your sibling.)
Firstly, learning that Yun Ha didn't send him a message...
made me very worried.
I felt like he would be anxious and hurt.
After the messages, Yun Jae's face fell.
You know,
this time is so dizzying.
- I feel the same. - I think I am going to throw up.
Back then,
the air felt so heavy.
Yong Woo was to my left and Cho A was to my right.
Seriously.
- This is too... - Oh, no.
- It's too much. - How did they sit like that?
It's like getting caught...
- between the parents' fight. - He looks like their son.
I know. The son.
Se Seung and Jung Sub were sitting there too.
It was like that.
The tension in the air was hard to take.
(You really are a big sister.)
(Thank you so much. You are unbelievable.)
I sent Yun Ha a message and thanked her.
I received a very hip message.
He wrote "Thank you so much" in all caps.
It was very refreshing.
(Yun Jae and Yong Woo chose your sibling.)
- What? - It's like a music video.
- Is this a music video? - Seriously.
Did you see that?
- "How dare you choose..." - "How dare you?"
- "my sister?" - I thought it was like this.
"I knew it." It looked like he was having that thought.
"Finally, my sister..."
I thought it was like this.
- "After all this time?" - That's right.
- "I said she was the prettiest." - Seriously.
"I knew it."
His facial expression looks so cool.
(Yun Jae and Yong Woo chose your sibling.)
I became very surprised upon receiving the message.
Two people sent her a message.
I was like, "What?"
Yun Jae and Yong Woo sent her a message.
What happened...
that he sent my sister a message?
(Thank you for your honesty.)
It was a message from Cho A.
She thanked me for telling her...
in her message.
I was about to have a mental breakdown...
while sitting there.
I didn't have any thoughts. It was so hard.
(All messages have been sent.)
I didn't receive a message.
It was my first time.
I couldn't describe my feeling.
No.
I felt a bit like...
I was betrayed.
But at the same time, it was as if I shouldn't feel that way.
"Who am I to feel this way?"
"We simply chose differently..."
"while getting to know each other."
But I still felt disappointed.
(No one chose your sibling.)
It was my first time receiving that message.
"What is this?"
I had that thought.
Really?
Is this about what you told me recently?
Cho A sat to my right.
She typed "A woman's hunch is indeed science" on her phone...
and showed it to me.
It was suffocating.
(All messages have been sent.)
- A few of them... - Se Seung.
Can we talk for a second?
(Cheol Hyeon asks Se Seung for a conversation.)
Let's talk later.
I am so exhausted.
- Who sent me a message? - Ji Won.
- To whom did you send a message? - Ji Won.
What she wrote was a bit strange.
She asked me why I was being curt.
- To whom did you send a message? - Cheol Hyeon.
It seemed that way.
Who sent me a message? Who was it?
Jung Sub.
I didn't think Jung Sub would send me a message.
There is a really interesting story.
Let's go.
(Jae Hyung and Se Seung go to their room.)
What's wrong with you?
I just followed my heart today.
Today's date was so nice, okay?
What was nice, the person or the date?
The date.
Then you should have sent it to the person you liked, you fool.
What is the interesting story?
- Who is it about? - It's so different...
- from what we thought. - What?
Cheol Hyeon asked me to talk to him.
I need to hurry up and go.
I will tell you at night then.
It's unrelated. Go ahead.
How many... Right, you received one message.
What does he want to talk about?
I don't know. But that doesn't matter.
Cheol Hyeon doesn't matter right now.
What am I going to do about Jung Sub?
What?
Jung Sub chose you nonstop,
but there was a time he wavered.
I know. That was why I had a hard time.
- But it wasn't Ji Won. - It was Cho A.
- How do you know that? - Jung Sub and I talked about it.
- I see. I thought you didn't know. - Was he in it deep?
Then you should tell him...
before you ask him out on a date.
You asked him out on a date, right?
I don't know. Hold on.
Was he in it deep when he liked Cho A?
- No. - It happened in the beginning.
- In Gangwon Province. - That's right.
He told me that he wasn't even confused.
- Cho A... - But Cho A felt differently.
Did Jung Sub make many moves on her?
She told me that he was very forward.
- During the date? - Yes.
She told me that she almost wanted to hide.
It's so different from what Jung Sub told me.
What do you mean?
What do you mean? Let's talk later.
It was like a bolt out of the blue.
I felt like the foundation was falling.
I thought Jung Sub was giving me the same kind of certainty.
I thought my feelings for Jung Sub grew...
because he gave me certainty.
But if that never existed, why did my feelings for him grow?
I became confused.
I had to go to Jung Sub and clear up his misunderstanding.
But what happened in the past...
pulled me down.
The misunderstanding is growing.
That's why you can't tell a secret.
- It spreads right away. - Seriously.
I am a bit frustrated.
It's a repeat of the same situation.
- It would be the best. - We can visit a Korean store...
and get two days' worth of food.
I want to eat kimchi stew.
Did you go there?
(Yun Ha joins the table.)
Sit down.
All right.
- I am going to get some rest. - I like it.
- It's a bit... - Are you going to get some rest?
All right.
- I am going to get some rest. - I like it.
- It's a bit... - Are you going to get some rest?
Yun Jae, what's up with you?
I am tired. I sweated so much.
I need to wash up.
(Yun Jae leaves.)
I always hung out with the others downstairs.
But I wanted to go to my room right away.
(Jae Hyung comes downstairs after talking to Se Seung.)
(Lurking)
(He calls Ji Won over.)
You don't smoke, do you?
- What? - Do you smoke?
No.
Why are you hiding?
- What is it? - A present.
- A present? What is it? - Yes.
Did you buy it on the date?
- Yes. - I see.
This must be Chinatown.
(They visited a souvenir store.)
Are these magnets?
You should buy a present for Ji Won.
I will...
- It's pretty. - I will get this.
- That one? - This is mine. This is a present.
Let's see.
- Will you get a present too? - Yes.
- A present. - Whose present?
It's a secret.
To whom will you give it?
When we drew on chocolate,
we drew the sky that was coloured by the sunset.
So I chose a magnet that depicted a sunset.
Is it a magnet? What is it?
Where did you go?
I got it in Chinatown.
It's pretty. It's pink.
It reminds me of our drawing.
That was why I bought it.
- Really? - Yes.
It's similar to our drawing.
Thank you.
Are you sullen?
- No, I am not sullen. - Then why did you write that?
It seemed like you were being curt.
- Really? - Yes.
- I... - Is that your usual self?
No, it isn't.
I don't know. I thought you were being curt.
- Really? - Yes.
I think I was a bit embarrassed.
Were you being curt because you were embarrassed?
I was very happy to see you when you came back.
I showed my happiness too.
- You showed your happiness? - During mealtime,
- you didn't look at me. - You didn't do that.
I was like, "What?"
- "Did she have a change of heart?" - A change of heart?
No, I didn't.
I answered brusquely...
since I was playing around.
That made her feel like I was being curt.
But it wasn't like that. When there are other people,
I find it hard to be affectionate.
I was embarrassed.
He was like a boy who was going through puberty.
He was being curt because he was embarrassed? Okay.
- Were you embarrassed? - Yes.
(Chuckling)
All right. I won't do that.
Okay.
Thank you.
Did you do it?
What?
- The date? Yes, I did. - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
Really? Who did you ask out on a date?
(Laughing)
I should do it now.
Do you want to go on a date with me tomorrow?
Do you get to ask in person?
- Right now, I am asking in person. - Really?
Yes.
What is this?
My goodness.
Seriously.
How cute.
I am suffocating. I am jealous.
I feel weird.
- Didn't you want to see this? - I did, but I feel weird.
Why?
- I don't know. - Why do you feel weird?
It's because I am alternating between hot and cold water.
It does make me wonder if I can laugh.
Shall we laugh?
(Laughing)
What?
- My goodness. - Other people need to live...
and be happy.
I should do it now.
Do you want to go on a date with me tomorrow?
Do you get to ask in person?
- Right now, I am asking in person. - Really?
Yes.
- You aren't tired, right? - That's right.
Let's go on a date tomorrow then.
I should take a shower early tomorrow.
I was sitting there for a reason.
Until today, Yun Ha and my brother...
messaged each other.
But today, he didn't receive a message.
Yun Ha asked me to drink with her.
So I wondered if she had...
Right now,
- things are really dynamic. - Seriously.
That's why I am there, okay?
- Let's talk tomorrow. - Okay.
After talking to Yun Ha,
I will go back to my room early.
- I wasn't being curt. - What?
- I wasn't being curt. - Stop being curt.
This is... Hold on.
It doesn't open easily.
(I was having a mental breakdown.)
(I continued to feel anxious.)
(You know...)
(Glancing over)
(I focused on 1 person for the past 16 days.)
(But it changed today...)
(for the very first time.)
I had that thought after going on a date with Yun Ha.
I felt like...
(I felt like I couldn't handle the situation.)
(Cheol Hyeon and I are the same.)
(So the date was nice.)
(But I am not the type...)
(to like someone who is exactly like me.)
(I understood what you meant. I got it.)
(It suddenly made me thoughtful.)
(I didn't wear contact lenses.)
(Your natural eye colour is more beautiful.)
(I thought, "So this is how I feel.")
(Do you want to stay here longer?)
(I want to stay here a bit longer.)