Senior Sister.
Senior Sister, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
What were you two doing out so late?
Didn't you say you don't like him?
Senior Sister, don't misunderstand.
I was really just investigating about my father.
Stop making excuses.
I heard him say he likes you with my own ears.
Senior Sister,
you don't happen to like him, do you?
Whether I like him or not,
he cannot like you,
and you definitely cannot like him,
because you are my junior sister.
Miss Yan, to be honest with you,
I like you.
So she entered the palace for revenge.
It's good that someone is helping her.
But why me?
Whether I like him or not,
he cannot like you,
and you certainly cannot like him,
because you are my junior disciple.
I thought I was the only one in a bad mood,
but it seems you are too.
I heard from the palace servants that
you used to be the Crown Prince,
but now you've become a prince.
Does that bother you?
I haven't been back for ten years.
And now that I've returned,
I barely recognize the paths in the palace anymore.
Just like how I couldn't read people's hearts back then.
I was sent to the mountains when I was one,
and returned at seventeen,
but before my father and I could properly reunite,
we were already separated by death.
Years ago, my mother sacrificed herself
to protect me,
how is that any different from your father?
My father loved me,
otherwise he wouldn't have sent so many clothes up to the mountains.
A fallen prince
and a homeless young lady.
How fitting,
how fitting.
Fellow souls cast adrift in this world,
cheers.
Your Majesty.
In your heart,
I am merely the Empress.
From the day you married Liu Le,
we were destined to be ruler and subject,
nothing more.
What you say
is exactly what I think.
From now on,
no more letters,
no more intimacy.
I chose this path myself.
Having become the Empress of Dajing,
and the mother of Shi'er,
I will walk this path with dignity.
Dajing is fortunate to have an Empress like you,
indeed.
May you be well,
take care.
May Your Majesty be well,
Please be seated, Your Majesty.
His Majesty is mindful of your hard work
and has sent these gifts especially for you.
The Empress doesn't look well,
something's troubling her.
Where did you go at midnight last night?
Look at these treasures,
I sent someone to deliver them last night,
but the eunuch said you weren't in the palace.
I was feeling distressed,
so I went for a walk.
Chen.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Summon the imperial physician to examine the Empress thoroughly.
Just send for Physician Yan.
Very well.
Has Your Majesty been feeling irritable lately
with difficulty sleeping
and loss of appetite?
You're right.
Congratulations to the Empress,
and to Your Majesty. It's a pregnancy pulse.
Excellent! I shall have another prince.
Your Highness, after investigation,
this deficit is the worst in the history of the Great Jing Dynasty,
with military expenses alone exceeding one million taels.
The accounts are unclear,
the army's morale is unstable,
there have been no wars in recent years,
no troop increases,
so where has all this money gone?
I never expected the army would harbor such a greedy rat like you.
You're truly audacious.
This old servant admits his wrongdoing.
Since you admit your guilt,
then atone with your life.
Prime Minister, I shall atone with my life.
Prime Minister, you seem rather impatient.
What do you mean by that, Your Highness?
I'm anxious for His Majesty
and for Great Jing's welfare.
Your Highness, something has happened to Imperial Physician Yan.
Physician Yan,
what exactly did you give me to drink?
What's going on with Physician Yan?
I...
I must protect this pregnancy
to give Shi'er a little brother
and make His Majesty happy.
Guards, take her away
and interrogate her thoroughly
until she confesses.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, there must be a misunderstanding
please release Physician Yan.
Careful investigation.
She killed my child,
and you want me to spare her?
During the previous epidemic in the city,
Physician Yan risked her own life
to save others,
rescuing thousands of citizens.
Think about it,
would someone willing to sacrifice herself for strangers
harm the Empress who bestowed her title as royal physician?
She killed my prince!
Am I supposed to believe her
just because of your word, Brother?
The Emperor and I have longed for this child for so long.
It's because she caused the death of my child.
Even if the Prince begs for mercy,
I will never agree.
If Your Majesty wants to prove your innocence,
then summon the Imperial Physician for an examination.
If anything unusual is found,
I request Your Majesty to sentence me to death.
Guards,
summon the Imperial Physician.
Yes, Your Majesty.