What's up there?
Thank you, bigfoot.
For giving me good dreams.
This must be the best solution.
I'm sorry, dad.
Who are you?
Kim lost some of his memories.
And I hope that...
The coming of his friends
will bring back his memories.
Kim.
Kim!
How are guys here?
Well...
[Kim]
Hello, Kim!
Kim!
Sun.
It's Payoo.
Payoo.
Er...
How's Kim?
We can't contact him.
Right.
Where's Kim?
Er...
Sun.
Please tell everyone
that Master Kim is safe.
Payoo said Kim is safe.
Sun.
Please turn on the speaker.
Okay.
I want you and Kim's friends to come here.
Where?
Chiang Rai.
That's it.
So we...
came to see you here.
How are you?
I'm fine.
But I still stand by my words.
I'm not okay for you all to stay here.
Er...
Everyone, let's get your stuffs to your room.
Payoo.
Uh...
I don't think it's possible to travel now.
I'll arrange their trip later.
- But...
- Okay, everyone.
It's self-service.
We have no staffs here.
Let's go.
Tony.
Let's meet in the dining room after this.
Payoo will...
Take you on a tour around this villa.
Yeah.
We have a lot to see.
Don't forget.
Everyone.
Hurry up.
What?
Why so hurry?
Thanks, Toy.
Is there something up there?
I'm Sun.
I remember.
I'm Kim.
I know.
It'd be horrible If I don't know the owner of the house
and come here.
So can you tell me
what's up there?
A promise.
I think
it's a promise.
With whom?
About what?
Can you tell me?
I don't know.
If I know,
I won't tell you.
Otherwise, it's not a promise.
Right?
How do you know Payoo?
Well...
From his relationship with my brother.
Rain?
You know him?
In this university,
there's no one who doesn't know Wasan Kannakul.
And...
Do you know
Kimhan Kannakul?
Heh.
Zombie?
Everybody knows.
Seems polar opposite.
Seems like...
You can remember your distant past.
Someone who had stories
and interactions with you.
Do we have any
stories or interactions?
Judging from your face,
I guess it's not a good one.
You think so?
You keep staring at them.
How do you feel?
Hurt?
Snow White.
Who's there?
Master Kim.
It's me.
Payoo.
Why are you here?
Uh...
I... heard Snow White's neigh.
So I came here.
I'm worried about pythons sneaking in.
I saw some in the forest the other day.
So...
Did you find any?
I've looked around and found none.
Good.
We should go back.
It's dangerous here at night.
Let's go.
Okay.
Breakfast's ready, guys.
Wow.
Looks delicious.
Baibua's amazing.
Your boyfriend will love you to death for sure.
Ahem!
Hey, I can't just love anybody.
Actually, I didn't cook these.
Payoo did.
Wow.
Then...
Your boyfriend will love you to death for sure.
Ahem!
Wow!
Simple dish with magnificent scenery.
So beautiful.
Where's Kim?
He's not eating?
He's the home-owner.
And...
He always isolates himself.
I think he's at the pen in this early morning.
Wow, Tony!
That's so beautiful.
We haven't posted any photos...
I forgot.
We don't have our phones.
It's fine.
We'll just...
keep this in our memory.
Wow.
Wise word.
I love you to death.
That's enough.
You're so persistent.
Like a disease.
Damn you Oh!
I'm not a disease!
Let's eat.
That's not good.
Don't tease me so much.
Just let me be.
Trot.
Good.
Walk.
Hold.
Hi, Kim.
What can you not do?
You do everything so well: studying, music, and sports.
Remembering, I guess.
I've never touched a horse.
Is its skin rough?
Don't be afraid.
Try touch it.
What's its name?
Snow White.
Why's that name?
Because it likes apples.
Try touch it.
If you want to be familiar with it,
you have to touch it.
Then, there'll be trust between you two.
Try it.
So soft.
I feel...
What?
Safe.
You can feel that much?
It lets me touch it.
Can I ride it now?
Sure.
Come.
Hold.
Easy.
Okay?
Go.
You keep staring at them.
How do you feel?
Hurt?
And you?
How do you feel?
Honestly?
Yeah.
Nothing.
Why?
Because...
He's the way he is.
It's always been like that.
Really?
How about you?
How do you feel?
Uh...
I...
I'll go back.
Uh...
I think I heard Oh call me.
I didn't hear a thing.
But I heard it.
I'll go now.
Someone's selling 2 million stocks.
Buy them all.
It's so much higher than the par value.
I'm worried you'll buy the overpriced.
I said buy them all.
And...
Your budget in the portfolio is empty.
Hold on.
Yes, president?
Come inside.
Is my OD transferred to my bank account?
It's just transferred.
Transfer it to my portfolio. STAT!
Yes, president.
It'll be ready in 5 minutes.
Buy them all.
Go all in.
Be ready.
Yes, ma'am.
Calm down.
Doctor.
We've spent almost 3 months on this case.
The conclusion we have is worth our time.
That's right.
We have many fortunate events,
especially about the bodies of the victims.
They haven't been cremated yet.
It's a well-laid plan.
The criminal swapped pilot's body.
If we didn't figure out the identity of the co-pilot,
we couldn't solve this case.
Business benefits
can turn someone into an evil easily.
I have to thank you
for helping us solve this case.
My pleasure.
The evildoers must be punished for their crime.
Order our agents to follow the suspects immediately.
Then issue the arrest warrant
before those criminals do anything further.
Roger that.
Do you think...
Kim will remember you?
And if...
He can't remember you forever
Will you... forget him?
Hold.
Thank you so much.
It was amazing.
Thank Snow White
not me.
Thank you, Snow White.
Come.
I'll help.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Then...
I'll go take a bath.
Okay.
Where have you been?
I tried horse riding.
Wow.
Didn't know you can ride a horse.
And...
How's Kim?
Same as ever.
Always keep his cool.
Do you think...
Kim will remember about you and him?
I don't know.
It's hard to guess.
We can only let it be.
What if...
Kim will never remember you,
what would you do?
I've never thought of that.
Okay, then.
If Kim can't remember you,
will you forget about him?
To forget someone
is painful.
Well,
If I were Kim,
I'll never forget you.
Thank you.
I must excuse myself.
I can't wait any longer.
Calm down, boss.
I now know where Kimhan is.
What?
Someone used Kimhan's phone to contact someone in Bangkok.
I ran a check.
So I know he is now hiding in the safe house.
Chateau Villa in Chaing Rai.
He's more clever than I thought.
It's right under my nose.
That's why I can't find him.
Great.
You wait there.
Sure, boss.
Kimhan.
Even if you have wings,
I'll clip all your wings.
Secretary.
Yes, president?
Cancel the board meeting tomorrow,
and book a private jet for me, STAT.
I'll leave tomorrow morning.
Where to?
Chiang Rai.
Cook one for me.
Here.
For not handsome man.
What if he's handsome?
What more will you give?
This one.
A bonus.
Aww, Baibua.
Meanie.
It's fine.
For you,
I'll eat this.
Wow.
Hehe.
I'll grill for you.
Looks yummy.
Looking for me?
No.
Looking for Kim.
Yeah.
I'm hurt.
Satisfied?
No.
We haven't gone on a trip like this for a while.
And?
I think it feels nice.
How do you feel?
You're all in your head.
You're smiling!
No!
I didn't.
I'll refill my cup.
Want anything?
Can I have you?
Piss off!
Pervert!
No!
I mean...
I want the same as you.
Damn you.
What the hell?
I'm serious.
There'll be rumor if someone sees this.
Why do you care?
Why can't you care about me,
like you care about others?
Enough.
Or...
What?
Or Kim will see us?
Yeah.
You think I'm hurt?
Yes.
Well.
I didn't feel a thing.
But it was okay.
Say it again.
Say it,
and I'll kiss you again.
You kiss
doesn't mean a thing.
So what?
The best you can do?
If you want me to notice you,
you have to be brave.
You can't do any better.
That's why...
You want me to be hurt.
Now I am.
Here.
Thank you, Payoo.
Not having fun?
Oh, no!
I'm just lost in my thoughts.
Payoo, wait.
I'm sorry.
For what?
That night,
at the sea,
I knew that you saw me and Rain.
It's your rights,
your heart.
I don't want to get in your way.
You're amazing.
I respect you.
If you ask me
am I still missing Rain?
I won't lie.
Everyday.
Especially,
today.
Do you think time will help?
Time
is just a clock ticking.
It's nothing to do with your heart.
Some day,
you'll find the right one.
The one who belongs to you.
The one
who makes you proud to tell others that
he's the one.
How about you?
Are you proud to tell everyone
that he's the one?
It may sound rude.
But I want everyone to leave as soon as possible.
Better yet, tomorrow.
This must be your gratitude
from my wish.
What did you do?
What have you done?
I'm sorry, dad.
I made a rash decision.
Why didn't you discuss this important matter with me first?
I know they are Master Kim's true friends.
And I want Master Kim to recover.
Because there's no other ways.
You need to be more careful.
Be more cautious.
You can't act without consulting me first.
Because this is for the safety of Master Kim.
I'm sorry.
Retrieve every phone.
Remove their SIM card.
All the while they're there.
Don't contact anyone else.
Because it's a safe house.
Okay.
I'm sorry, dad.