[Episode 4]
If I remember correctly,
at this time in the previous life,
The Imperial Guard caught a Qinglan felon.
If I can find him,
and convince him to help me
decode the Qinglan cipher,
I would surely know
who is after the Wen family.
Young man,
I'd like to ask a favor of you.
In the Imperial Prison,
it's better to find me than him for help.
Your Highness.
I just want someone to buy me
some quality food and wine.
I won't trouble Your Highness.
Are these enough?
Is this an inn or a prison?
The Imperial Prison never mistreats prisoners.
The evidence is conclusive
that Su Xuanjing framed a meritorious official.
His Majesty has ceased to pursue
your fault in killing him.
Why do you still choose to stay
in the Imperial Prison?
The Imperial Prison is cozier and safer
than an inn.
I wish to stay a few more days.
Are you treating me as your guard?
Your Highness, that Qinglan prisoner
in the dungeon is causing trouble again.
He's clamoring to see you.
Give me the key.
I will meet him in person.
I am encumbered with official duties today.
I won't disturb your dinner then.
Your Highness, why not stay for a drink?
Your Highness once said that the man I married
was not a good-hearted fellow.
Now he's dead,
shouldn't we celebrate?
Last time I drank your wedding wine,
I still remember how I came to bad end.
I won't use the same tactic twice.
Especially, the wine today
is brought by you.
And what is this for?
I haven't thanked Your Highness
for what happened outside Flower Pavilion.
So, this is your purpose in approaching me.
Your Highness do know how to play drunk.
If I don't get drunk, the wine might run out.
If Your Highness knows my purpose,
why do you treat me with false courtesies?
Miss Wen, please do not be annoyed.
I wish to cooperate with you.
[Prisoner]
The clouds part to reveal Qinglan.
Iron cavalry breaks through Da'an.
You're a person of Qinglan?!
I am the crown prince's secret agent
in the capital.
I thought the crown prince had abandoned me.
If you have confessed,
I am here to kill you today.
Of course, I haven't.
Regarding his business of coming to the capital
to meet with the noble,
I haven't said a word to anyone from Da'an.
That is awesome.
Do you still remember the names
of those people?
[Seeking Fragrance Feast Name List]
How could the noble's name be on the list?
You are not from Qinglan--
You do have a strong sense of caution.
Did he admit?
He only mentioned a noble in the capital,
who would work with the Qinglan crown prince.
Lady Wen really has a good strategy.
Clues that I couldn't find out
even with all my efforts,
you elicited them with just a few words.
It's just a trick.
Your Highness could try it out next time.
You are really drunk?
Go sober up. I still have things for you to do.
Let's go over there.
Alright, let's go.
Your Highness, why come here all of a sudden?
Investigate a case.
Investigate a case?
There is more to Lady Wen
killing her husband in public.
Su Xuanjing has a list in his hands.
This list is of great importance.
Have you heard?
The granddaughter of Lord Wen
killed her husband in public,
because she discovered a list
in Su Xuanjing's hands.
It is said that this list is critical.
She wanted to present it personally
to the Emperor.
You must get the list.
You're dead if you fail to do so.
As you command.
Fire! Hurry and put it out!
Help!
Help, please!
I haven't opened the door here yet.
- Quick!
- Over here, over here!
- Over here!
Hand over the list you have.
What list?
Quit playing innocent.
Surely it is Su Xuanjing's
list of the Seeking Fragrance Feast.
I know nothing
about the Seeking Fragrance Feast.
He did give me a list.
Is this the list you are looking for?
Has anyone else seen it?
That's good.
Help!
Fire! Hurry, put it out!
Have you looked over the list?
No, I dare not.
You've done a good job.
I believe only dead people can keep secrets.
She is dead,
and you still have the nerve to stand here.
I know I am guilty.
This is the granddaughter of Lord Wen.
I will immediately dispatch someone
to investigate.
We will surely capture the murderer
and bring them to justice.
Is that all?
Well, Your Highness's intention is…
Increase manpower,
and closely monitor all parts of the city.
One must have the order
from the Imperial Guard to enter and exit.
As you command.
Everyone's gone, you can get up now.
How is your wound?
I have practiced martial arts
since I was little.
Use this minor injury
to lure out the true mastermind.
It's very thoughtful of Your Highness.
Because your opponent is Sun Cheng.
Sun Cheng…
What is the deal with
the Seeking Fragrance Feast?
I'm afraid only upon your death
that Sun Cheng will reveal
the Seeking Fragrance Feast.
And he is cunning by nature.
He will personally confirm your death.
Therefore, I need a funeral.
Master Wen,
please bear your sorrow and accept the change.
Your health is of utmost importance.
[Hall of Yanming]
How is it going?
Your Highness, rest assured.
I have personally inspected it.
Wen Wan is indeed dead.
The Seeking Fragrance Feast…
Yes, we must hold the feast,
and hold it with grandeur.
If she were alone,
how could she possibly send the message
out of the prison.
Your Highness wants to catch a turtle in a jar?
You must remember,
anyone who knows about this list must die.
In just a few days,
you have managed both a wedding and a funeral.
Do you have any plans
for dealing with Sun Cheng after this?
I have thought long and hard.
Your Highness is royal
with a conspicuous status.
You're really not suitable to get involved in
the right and wrong of our Wen family.
You are trying to draw a clear line with me.
I have already died once.
I am not afraid to die again.
But you are different.
How do you know that I haven't died?
I am not talking about
the kind on the battlefield.
Neither am I.
In any case, you have saved my life.
I definitely cannot abandon you
at a time like this.
When have I ever saved your life?
Do you really not remember?
Back then, I was being hunted down.
If there is a future, I'll repay with my life,
and pledge myself to you.
Here is a dagger for you.
If you can really make a name for yourself,
be sure to come back to the capital,
and repay the favor.
Okay.
It was just a child's jest.
How can I possibly exploit the favor for gain?
Why can't you?
I will obey any command for your sake.
Stop, stop, stop.
How come I've never seen you before?
You do look good, though.
It would be a waste to send you
to the Seeking Fragrance Feast. How about…
My lord, she is just a blockhead.
Let me serve you instead, my lord.
As long as you tell me, my lord,
what exactly
is this Seeking Fragrance Feast about?
Serve what! Just go back and get ready.
Not one of you can be missing
from the Seeking Fragrance Feast.
Thanks a lot.
Someone like you can't be a dancing girl.
Let's go.
Stop right there.
Tonight's Seeking Fragrance Feast is critical.
I must oversee it myself.
There are calluses on your hand.
I remember that the ladies
of Flower Pavilion never wield swords.
♫ The light of the fireflies scatters away ♫
♫ Swaying in the wind within wind ♫
♫ The wind and the moon arrive
as promised on long nights ♫
♫ Granting me dreams within dreams ♫
♫ Words ready to be spoken
ultimately fall silent ♫
♫ Reunite with you after lives apart ♫
♫ Love and hate pass by in haste ♫
♫ Winter has its arrival,
flowers have their withering ♫
♫ The light in your eyes remains evergreen
through the years ♫
♫ Just like the wind blows out the flames
into ashes ♫
♫ Recognize you beneath your name ♫
♫ Willing to write for you,
against the current ♫
♫ Spring has the intention to come,
you have the intention to return ♫
♫ Two flustered souls meet ♫
♫ The foreshadowing has been set ♫