[Episode 15]
How is it going? Did you find him?
I got this map
from the craftsman
who repaired the Eastern Palace.
We have searched
all the rooms and secret chambers on it.
There's no trace of your uncle.
Could there be secret chambers
we haven't discovered?
Then it will be hard to find.
It's almost dawn.
You take your men back first.
I'll stay behind and take my time to search.
You must be careful.
Why doesn't Your Highness have them arrested?
Trespassing the Eastern Palace…
This crime, for them,
is too trivial.
In the dead of night,
it is inevitable
that they trespass the Eastern Palace
and are mistakenly killed as assassins.
They killed the one I love.
I must give them a taste of it too.
Only then is it a tit-for-tat.
Beloved one…
His Highness actually has beloved one?
Why are you exerting so much force today, Ziyu?
Why is it you?
I was overwhelmed by wine last night,
leaving you to the empty room alone.
It was my fault.
Tonight, I will make it up to you properly.
There is never any affection between us.
Why put on an act and play tricks here.
I have promised you
that the military power of the Wen family
will not be in the hands of others.
From now on,
you should live in the side chamber.
This is the Eastern Palace.
Then I'll go to the side chamber.
If it weren't for you and Xiao Chen
poisoning me last night,
I wouldn't mind spend the night with you.
Don't forget
you also have weaknesses.
Your Highness.
You can't even handle such little thing right.
There's no place for you in the Eastern Palace
from now on.
Your Highness, are you trying to drive me away?
Yes.
No, your mother asked me
to stay in the Eastern Palace
and protect Your Highness.
I cannot leave.
Do you listen to me or my mother?
Of course,
I obey the commands of Your Highness.
But I've grown up in the Eastern Palace
since I was little.
Where can I go if I leave the Eastern Palace?
It's up to you.
It's fine as long as you're not by my side.
It's best for you to leave the capital.
Miss!
The Crown Prince drove the lady musician away.
He drove the lady musician away?
This is odd.
We must find my uncle as soon as possible.
Such a big guy needs to eat and drink.
Where could he be hidden?
Go check the accounts of Eastern Palace.
- Hurry!
- Yes.
What brings you here?
I just saw the Crown Prince's carriage pass by,
so I wanted to come see you.
Candied hawthorn.
I saw it on the street.
I remember you like it,
so I bought it for you.
Anything wrong?
It's the Crown Prince again, isn't it?
I'll go find him.
You be falling into his trap
if you go like this.
Are we just going to let him
bully you like this?
He's just taking advantage of
having my uncle in his hands.
That's why he dares to treat me this way.
Once I get my uncle back,
I will definitely let him suffer a lot more.
I will rescue your uncle as soon as possible.
I've checked the accounts.
Starting three months ago,
the kitchen has been preparing meals
for one extra person.
But no one knows where the meals are sent.
That's the Crown Prince's study?
Exactly.
Your Royal Highness, you are back.
What are you doing here?
Where is the Crown Princess?
I've said before,
I don't like others touching my stuff,
especially in the study.
I just thought it was a bit messy.
I wanted to help you tidy up.
I won't do it again.
Are you alone?
Or what?
Lunch is ready.
Let's have lunch together.
[Hall of Yanming]
Wan!
What are you doing here?
His Highness has brought
a storybook for my lady.
Storybook…
From now on, let servants send these things.
There is no need to bother my seventh brother.
The Old Marquis told me
to deliver it to her personally.
Did the Old Marquis ever say
that Wan is the principal wife of me?
As her brother-in-law,
you should keep a distance.
Lest it leads to misunderstandings.
I haven't heard him mention that.
The Old Marquis only said
that the daughter of the Wen family
has the freedom to marry.
Should she become a widow,
she can remarry.
From now on, the Crown Princess will be
taken care of by my people.
I am the handmaid
who accompanied my lady during her marriage.
Why won't you let me serve her.
I am merely asking you
to return to the Wen Residence.
If you dare to disobey again,
I'll make sure you don't return alive.
What do you want to do?
You and I are now in the same boat.
Please properly perform your duties
as the Crown Princess.
Why is he acting so out of character?
Could it be that he has discovered something?
Lady Wen,
long time no see.
If you really have my uncle,
let him go.
Our Wen family will give you whatever you want.
Miss Wen is virtuous and generous,
gentle and honest.
I want you to be the Crown Princess.
You can't even handle such little thing right.
There's no place for you in the Eastern Palace
from now on.
It's best for you to leave the capital.
Could it be that he also…
♫ The light of the fireflies scatters away ♫
♫ Swaying in the wind within wind ♫
♫ The wind and the moon arrive
as promised on long nights ♫
♫ Granting me dreams within dreams ♫
♫ Words ready to be spoken
ultimately fall silent ♫
♫ Reunite with you after lives apart ♫
♫ Love and hate pass by in haste ♫
♫ Winter has its arrival,
flowers have their withering ♫
♫ The light in your eyes remains evergreen
through the years ♫
♫ Just like the wind blows out the flames
into ashes ♫
♫ Recognize you beneath your name ♫
♫ Willing to write for you,
against the current ♫
♫ Spring has the intention to come,
you have the intention to return ♫
♫ Two flustered souls meet ♫
♫ The foreshadowing has been set ♫