[Love Song in Winter]
[Episode 10]
Nice shots,
Wang Qiang.
Wang Qiang!
Stop there!
Don't move!
Get down!
Let go of me!
-Get down!
-Let go of me!
Don't move!
Handcuff him and take him to the car.
Sure enough, at this critical moment,
it has to be Professor Yu who steps in.
How did you know it was him?
When I was touching up my makeup earlier,
I observed everyone.
What if he wasn't even
in this cafe?
That's possible too.
But
when I walked into the cafe,
everyone looked at me
except for him.
Alright.
You have a way with it.
Humans are visual animals,
especially men.
Men are more likely to choose younger,
healthy,
and energetic individuals as partners.
So men are more easily attracted to
beautiful and sexy appearances.
This is the nature of men.
Got it.
But this time,
really,
thank you so much
for helping us.
Professor Yu.
Captain Jiang.
What brings you here?
Not busy, huh?
The class just ended.
Is something wrong?
Yes, I have a small favor to ask.
What is it?
What do you mean by "us"?
I'm just helping you, Jiang Chengyi.
Here you go again.
Forget it.
I was just kidding.
I just wanted to see
if you're still thinking about
your ex-girlfriend.
I'll go take the guy back first.
Let's grab a meal sometime.
I don't have time to eat with you.
But if you have any psychological issues,
you can reach out to me.
Thanks.
Bye. See you.
Sir,
what have I done
to get arrested?
You're not admitting it, huh?
Admit what?
See for yourself.
It's too dark to see clearly.
Can't see clearly?
Here, look at this.
I can't even see the face...
Did you look carefully? And still, you say you can't see it?
I can't even see the face clearly.
How could it be me?
What about this one?
This is the one you bought, right?
Wang Qiang,
why did you follow that girl?
Which girl?
I don't understand what you're saying.
I'm talking to you properly now.
You'd better tell me everything you can.
Why were you following the girl
in the photo on your phone?
Was anyone directing you?
No one directed me.
I've never done
anything you're talking about.
We found a large amount of evidence
on your computer and phone.
There are numerous photos of women you've secretly taken,
records of trafficking,
and banned drugs
you've purchased.
How many years do you want to be sentenced to?
Let me ask you again.
Why were you
following that female doctor?
When I saw attractive girls,
I'd casually take their photos,
then edit their faces
onto explicit images
and
sell them online for money.
That day,
I happened to run into that female doctor.
I thought she looked good,
so I casually took a few photos of her.
But I haven't had the chance
to edit the photos yet.
They're still on my phone.
You can check them if you want,
sir.
I saw them.
So you were the one
in the alley that day.
Right?
What were you planning to do that day?
I saw that
no one was in the alley,
so I... I just wanted to…
take advantage of her.
Do you know her?
I don't know her.
I take so many photos every day.
How would I know who she is?
You don't know her.
Why did you repeatedly follow her?
I just thought she was attractive.
[Ninghai Anshan People's Hospital]
Yan.
This place is crowded.
I don't want to eat at the cafeteria.
Wen.
What brings you here?
I came to bring you
movie tickets.
What movie?
It's a movie produced by our company.
Tomorrow night at 7:30.
I'd like to have my friends over
to watch and critique the movie.
Wasn't this movie
awarded at a film festival before?
It was just a small award.
You're being too modest.
Will Feng be coming?
He's filming, so he probably can't make it.
Okay.
What do you think? Are you free?
Tomorrow, we're on the day shift,
so we should be able to go.
Great, then.
I'd like to thank you in advance
for coming.
I'll ask the driver
to pick you up tomorrow.
No need.
We'll just take the subway.
The subway?
Has the person been caught?
I believe
Captain Jiang will catch him.
Are you two
rekindling your love?
Nonsense.
Alright.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Bye.
Why don't you
ask Captain Jiang
to go with you?
To the premiere.
["Half Love"]
Anyway,
you are
into him now,
aren't you?
What nonsense is that?
It's a great opportunity for you
to watch a movie together.
Don't you want to watch it?
Didn't we agree
to watch it together?
But Feng isn't involved in this.
Why should I go?
I'm a true fan.
If I go to see other handsome guys,
I'll feel guilty.
I'll hit you. Believe it or not.
Can't you watch with me?
You've gone crazy chasing stars.
I'm not!
I want to eat this.
You can have all of it.
It is indeed unrequited love on my part.
But...
But you're different from me.
Mutual affection—
how rare it is.
You should cherish it
and create more chances to be alone together.
Got it?
No.
The thing is...
I don't know
how the other person feels about me.
So,
that's even more reason to go watch the movie.
Watching a movie
is basically a date.
If he agrees to go with you,
what does it mean?
It means
he still has feelings for you.
But you see,
we've just
started reconnecting,
isn't going to watch the movie
too fast
of a step?
What's wrong?
Didn't you watch movies
when you were together?
Really.
Yan, I'm telling you,
both our profession
and his
are very unique.
You know that, right?
You're a doctor,
and he's a police officer.
At every moment,
we face numerous dangers
and the threat of death.
We never know which will come first:
our tomorrow, or our end.
So,
when you get the chance
to grasp happiness,
make sure you hold on to it tightly.
Hold on tightly, do you understand?
No matter
what the result is,
but
at least
if you've tried,
you won't have any regrets.
Right?
["Half Love"]
Go.
Senior.
As for the photos taken by Wang Qiang,
the ones on his phone and computer,
I went through them, and there are over ten thousand.
I estimate he's photographed
more than a thousand girls.
So disgusting.
Yeah.
Wang Qiang especially likes to take pictures
of people on buses
or subways.
Senior,
though Wang Qiang
is quite a troublemaker,
I think he's telling the truth
in this case.
He definitely didn't know
Dr. Lu before.
Don't worry.
Transfer him to the detention center.
Okay.
Alright.
Yue.
[Anshan Criminal Investigation]
Smell this bread.
Do you think it's gone bad?
Smell my shoes. Do they stink?
If it wasn't Wang Qiang,
then who else could be
pretending to be Deng Man?
[Huiting Complex]
["Half Love"]
Hello,
the subscriber you dialed
is busy now.
Please try again later.
Hello?
Why can't I
get through to your phone?
I...
I've been calling you,
but it seems the line is busy.
Yes, I've been trying to call you too.
Well...
Why are you calling me?
I...
I just wanted to ask,
did you catch that bad guy
from last time?
Weren't you in a hurry to leave?
The person's been caught.
Don't worry.
That's good.
So is that person
the one pretending to be Deng Man?
It wasn't him pretending.
I'll keep looking into this.
No worries.
Thanks.
Hello?
Are you...
Are you still there?
I'm still at the bureau.
Are you busy
tomorrow as well?
Do you have anything
planned for tomorrow?
No big deal.
If you're too busy, it's fine.
I'm free.
Let's have dinner together tomorrow night.
Here's the thing.
Wen gave me two tickets
for the movie premiere.
And
tomorrow at 7 p.m.,
I was wondering if you...
No problem.
Send me the time and location,
I'll go with you.
That's it.
Alright.
Okay.
Good morning.
You need to fix this.
You have these
dark circles.
Come on.
Lift it up.
Enough, I was born with them.
You need to cover them up.
Okay.
What are you wearing today?
I'm just wearing what I came in.
What you came in?
That won't do.
You...
You'd better hurry
and go buy a dress.
Do I have to buy a dress?
Of course.
You can't go to the movie date
without a dress.
You need to look good,
okay?
Yan.
You're actually putting on makeup?
This makeup looks like
you're not wearing any at all.
Dr. Huang,
do you know that,
as a guy,
having high EQ
makes it easier
to win a girl's affection?
Don't touch my stuff.
Such a big setup,
are you going on a date?
Of course.
You think it's for you?
Don't tell him,
or everyone in the hospital
will know by tomorrow.
You're right.
That's for sure.
Since I saw this,
I have to tell everyone.
I've got to live up
to my reputation as the king of gossip.
My goodness.
I'm speechless.
Do you know
why Matron Qiao
always ignores you?
Why?
Because
you talk too much!
Talk too much?
Lipstick.
Do I?
Purse your lips.
Take a look.
Not bad.
I think it looks good.
It's quite natural.
What do you think?
Is it too red?
I personally think it's a bit too red.
The eye makeup
could be more intense.
As for the blush, it's actually unnecessary...
Why are you asking him?
He knows nothing.
Hurry up.
You still need to buy a dress.
Oh yeah.
I'll head out first.
Good luck, Yan!
Buy a nicer dress.
Alright.
♫When we're hand in hand, even the equator possesses♫
♫Beauty like the aurora and white snow♫
♫You close your eyes and make a wish, completely defenseless♫
♫I kiss your face secretly♫
♫I want to weave a beautiful dream for you♫
♫What we lack is not just time♫
♫Losing sight of the world and our default end point♫
♫As we write every page of our love by hand♫
♫How should I describe love, my perfect dear?♫
♫Romance only exists with you♫
♫Forever and ever into the future♫
♫Let's be super sweet lovers♫
♫How should I describe love, my perfect dear?♫
Hello.
Is there anything you'd like to see?
Do you have any recommendations?
♫It's my privilege to make you happy♫
♫Endless loving and longing♫
These are all new arrivals.
But I think this dress
suits you perfectly.
♫Loving you, every day is Valentine's Day♫
This one?
Would you like to try it on?
Can I try it?
Of course.
Okay.
The fitting room is over here.
Thank you.
I'll get you a new one.
The mirror is over here.
♫Holding hands while heading to the best outcome♫
Well...
♫Learning the beauty of waiting♫
I feel like
it's a bit too tight.
♫You know me best, I don't need to speak a word♫
I'm not really...
I can't put it into words.
It fits really well.
♫A special thing only you know it♫
This piece
is part of our Winter Love Song collection,
specially designed for girls
to wear on dates.
♫I want to weave a beautiful dream for you♫
I think you look great in it.
And for dates,
♫I'll engrave every fluttering moment♫
we should
dress up beautifully.
Are you going on a date?
No.
♫I kiss your forehead, as starlight caress your white hair♫
Well, kind of.
♫I want to hear you say you don't regret♫
♫How should I describe love, my perfect dear?♫
That's perfect then.
In SC,
we also have a matching fragrance from the same collection.
♫Romance only exists with you♫
It's also designed for dates.
Would you like to try it?
No.
♫Forever and ever into the future♫
Actually, about the dress,
do you have another style?
♫Let's be super sweet lovers♫
I don't feel comfortable wearing it.
This one then.
It looks nice.
♫How should I describe love, my perfect dear?♫
You...
Why are you here?
I was just passing by
♫It's my privilege to make you happy♫
and happened to see you.
Do you think
♫Endless loving and longing♫
it's okay?
It looks really good.
♫Loving you, every day is Valentine's Day♫
Alright then,
I'll go pay now.
Okay, this way please.
I've already paid.
Let's go.
You bought it?
Yeah, it's so beautiful.
Thank you.
Let's go.
We still have a date to go to.
May I ask Director Jiang
what your thoughts and reflections
are on this film?
["Half Love"]
Our movie
is about love.
Mr. Wen.
I personally think
love
is adapted from real-life experiences.
Forget it,
I won't spoil it.
Hi there.
Captain Jiang.
Why isn't Qianqian here?
Something came up.
She said she couldn't make it.
That's right.
I'm here to keep her company.
Captain Jiang's vacation
is unusually long this time.
Yeah.
Well, let's get together more often.
Sure, depends on the schedule.
The movie is about to start.
Shall we go in first?
Let's go.
Row 3.
Seats 15 and 16.
Be careful.
Mr. Wen.
Long time no see.
Come on, take a seat.
Okay.
I apologize for the lack of hospitality.
Mr. Wen.
Hello, Director.
We're all waiting for you.
Here.
Have a seat.
Director, have a seat.
Mr. Wen,
shall we start now?
Yes.
[Performing with a mask on]
Enjoy the movie
with Officer.
Hope things progress quickly
for you both tonight.
[My promise, waiting to be spoken]
Dad.
You're back.
I got the exchange spot.
Get me a glass of water.
Dad, water.
You know it's hot, and you still pour it for me to drink?
You're trying to burn me, aren't you?
You blockhead.
What did you just say to me?
What are you going to do?
I...
I got the exchange spot.
I can go study abroad now.
You, study abroad?
You're just like your mom, a real handful.
My mom has always been good to you.
Has your mom been good to me?
Hasn't your mom been good to you too?
She's good to you,
so why doesn't she want you anymore?
so why did she leave with someone else?
Remember,
I've been taking care of you
since you were little
and have raised you to this point.
I put you through college,
and now you want to leave me?
Listen.
You're not going anywhere.
If one day I don't want to live anymore,
you'll have to die with me!
Do you understand?
Get lost!
[Dangerous Water Depth, No Swimming]
What are you doing?
Wen.
The sign over there says:
"Dangerous Water Depth."
You...
What's wrong with you?
Can you hold my umbrella?
I'll perform something for you.
Hold this for me.
Do you know how to skip stones?
Let me show you.
[Dangerous Water Depth, No Swimming]
I'm not good at it either,
but I just managed to hit two skips.
Did you see that?
Let me share
a little story with you.
Actually, I've been pretty dumb
all my life.
Like, really dumb.
How dumb was I?
Well,
I couldn't even memorize
the multiplication table.
My mom was so angry
that she chased me around to hit me.
But it didn't work.
I was still that dumb.
But later,
I learned a saying:
"A slow sparrow should make an early start."
I was willing to be that slow sparrow,
so I studied quietly and in secret.
And in the end,
I was the one
who got into Ninghai University.
I was so proud of myself.
But then, when I came to this school,
I found out that everyone around me
was better than me.
There were academic stars everywhere,
just like you.
Do you know what they call you
in our class?
They call you a genius.
Even Teacher Han is totally smitten by you.
He praises you every day at school—
both in class
and outside of class.
Your exercise book
has even been circulated among our batch.
I might not be as amazing
as you think.
You're being modest.
I know,
smart people like you,
born to be excellent,
are just like that.
You can't even see
how great the shine is
within you.
Are you feeling a bit happier now?
Look,
I'm so dumb,
but I still live happily.
Don't be upset, okay?
Let me secretly tell you
a little secret.
Actually,
a lot of people see you
as their target to catch up with.
Feeling a bit happier now?
Wen,
you're amazing.
Don't be unhappy.
I'm off to evening self-study now.
See you.
Your umbrella!
It's yours now.
[Silence]
Yan.
Wen.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing much.
Just...
Zoning out, throwing little stones.
Do you like lakes?
I feel that looking at a lake
can make the heart very peaceful.
I really want to visit
Lake Baikal.
I've heard it's called
the "Pearl of Siberia."
Coincidentally, Teacher Han and I
are going to Russia for an academic conference
this weekend.
If I have time,
I can go take a look at it for you.
Really?
Then take my eyes with you.
Just kidding.
Lu Yan,
would you like to
go with me
to visit Lake Baikal one day?
Lu Yan!
Keep going!
Lu Yan, come on!
Come on!
Keep going!
Lu Yan, come on!
Come on, Lu Yan!
Keep going!
Lu Yan.
["Half Love"]
Alright, next,
let's give a warm round of applause
as we welcome our publisher
and producer,
Mr. Wen Peng,
along with our production team.
Please come on up.
[Premiere in Ninghai]
Come on, guys.
Alright, welcome.
Welcome, everyone.
Thank you.
Go ahead, Mr. Wen.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm very glad you could come and watch the film.
Actually, we should have the director speak first.
Director, please go ahead.
No.
What I want to say is,
first of all, thank you all for your support.
This film
is actually based on
Mr. Wen's own story.
I think it should be Mr. Wen who shares it.
Don't you all agree?
Yes.
[Premiere in Ninghai]
Yes, Mr. Wen.
And as we saw
just now
in the film,
the male lead has a segment about
the bittersweet memories of his first love.
The kind of regret from a love that couldn't be realized
was very sincere,
especially in the scene where the girl gave him an umbrella.
I believe many of you here
are as curious
as I am,
and I'd like to ask Mr. Wen,
was this scene
based on
your own real experience?
Yes.
Okay.
In the heavy rain,
the girl gave the boy
an umbrella,
and her radiant smile
became something
the boy would remember for a lifetime.
I remember this shot
was handled very beautifully.
So, I'd like to ask Mr. Wen,
is there anything else
you would like to share with us?
In my university days,
there was
once a girl who,
on a rainy day,
unknowingly
appeared in front of me
and gave me warmth.
Is this girl
your life partner now?
Not yet,
but I will work hard for it.
Alright.
Let's wish Mr. Wen the best of luck,
and let's give a round of applause
for the success of the new film,
hoping it achieves even more
in domestic awards.
Would you like to go to the bathroom?
No.
Then wait for me.
Okay.
Yan.
How's the date
with Officer?
You're so busy that you don't even have time to reply to me.
You must be really happy, huh?
We were watching a movie,
okay?
How was I supposed to reply to you?
You're here too.
The movie was really good
It was enjoyable.
Thank you.
If you like it,
please help us
promote the movie to others.
Sure.
I'll go first.
I'm done.
I'm thinking of
saying goodbye to Wen.
-Tell him we're leaving first.
-Sure.
Wen, we're heading out now.
Everything went smoothly today.
Congratulations.
Are you hungry?
I'm not hungry,
but I feel like going for a walk.
Did you drive?
We can walk;
it's not far.
Let's walk.
["Half Love"]
What do you think of
today's movie?
I think it was really good.
It felt like he put a lot of effort into it.
He really did.
All those years ago,
a girl gave him an umbrella,
and he still remembers it,
even turning it into a film.
[Wang Qianqian] [Answer] [Decline]
Is there someone
who you've been thinking about for so many years?
Yes.
Have you been alone
all these years?
What about you?
Me?
I've pretty much been the same,
around the same.
[Wang Qianqian] [Answer] [Decline]
Fine.
You'd dated so many after me?
Things seem to be going well for everyone.
You must've had many suitors too.
Of course.
They'd have to line up from here
to all the way over there.
What are you doing?
Lining up.
As I can see,
there's no one here today.
Can you let me cut in line?
I still have to work tomorrow.
Stop messing around.
I'm going upstairs.
I'm heading back now.
Lu Yan.
Is the CCTV
running low on battery?
Let me check for you.
You...
You can sit down.
Should I put your things here?
Okay.
Why are you standing there?
Do you want something to drink?
What do you have?
Water.
Let me see.
Your place has a nice view.
Not bad, right?
Whenever
I'm feeling down,
I just stand there and look outside.
Lu Yan,
I want to tell you something.
Actually,
all these years,
other than you,
I've never loved anyone else.
What you just said,
about one, two, three, four, five, six—
weren't they people?
Then what you just said,
about the whole street lining up,
is that true?
All these years,
♫As the city flickers♫
I haven't come back.
♫It's as gentle as wind wrapping around rain♫
First, I'm a bit
angry,
because back then,
♫And you, who loves to smile♫
you didn't even see me for one last time.
♫Always offering your happiness to me first♫
Secondly,
♫The humor of time♫
I'm also worried.
I worry that there's someone else by your side.
♫No one to blame for breaking the promise♫
♫It's because we met too soon that we missed each other♫
I also worry
that you don't want to see me at all.
I'm afraid you've forgotten about me.
♫We're stranded at sunset♫
♫My sunburnt face doesn't mean a word♫
I...
♫The stubborn me♫
I haven't forgotten you.
♫I always think of the far future♫
♫I walk willfully♫
Lu Yan.
It's been eight years,
♫Like a star revolving around♫
and I've thought about you every day.
♫I turn around♫
♫But you're not behind me♫
I miss you a lot too.
♫Losing you♫
♫It's so unreal♫
♫I hurt my love♫
♫But still hope to♫
♫Start anew♫
♫There's a certain kind of squander♫
♫Where I'm late to know who loves me♫
♫When you're not here♫
♫Life becomes aimless♫
♫I miss you♫
♫It's so real♫
♫The person I trust♫
♫Insists on separating♫
♫Who can explain?♫
♫I'm not afraid of your happiness♫
♫I'm afraid you'll forget me♫
♫To feel my heartache♫
♫When I no longer have the best♫
♫I miss you missing me♫
[Lu Yan, help me]
[We were watching a movie, okay? How was I supposed to reply to you?]