[Love Song in Winter]
[Episode 9]
Lu Yan!
Freeze! Police!
Lu Yan.
Where are you hurt?
Ether.
What?
[Emergency Department]
[Medical Records Room - Go up to the fourth floor from here]
As for the patient in Bed 32,
you need to pay special attention to his blood pressure.
If anything happens,
let me know immediately.
Okay, I understand.
Matron Qiao,
I'll go up first then.
Go ahead.
Mr. Wen
Why are you here?
Matron Qiao
[Medical Records Room - Go up to the fourth floor from here]
I'm here to look for Lu Yan.
Is Lu Yan in the duty room?
She’s off work.
Off work?
Doesn't she work night shifts?
We just changed
our shift schedule two days ago.
Are you...
looking for Lu Yan for something?
Nothing much.
Doctor.
Lu Yan passed out from being drugged.
Lu.
This way.
Hurry.
[Emergency Department]
Her heartbeat and breathing are normal.
She'll be fine
after taking a rest.
There wouldn't be any after effects, would there?
There wouldn't be.
Then I'll trouble you two
to take care of Lu.
Dr. Wang and I
will take a look at the medical examination report.
Okay.
Hello?
Hello, Senior.
We are heading to the crime scene
to see if there are any clues.
Okay.
Let me know if you have any news.
You're awake.
How are you?
Do you still feel dizzy?
Do you feel like vomiting?
Doctor.
She's awake.
Dr. Lu.
You're awake.
Your report is normal.
You'll be fine after some rest.
When can she be discharged?
Once she finished the IV drip
and feels no discomfort,
she can go back.
Alright.
Thank you.
Wait a little longer.
I'll send you home later.
Did you catch him?
Don't worry about that.
We'll definitely catch him.
Close your eyes for a while.
[Huiting Complex]
Slowly, slowly.
Still dizzy?
You guys go home first.
I'll send you in.
You...
You're not leaving?
I'll stay with you outside.
Have a good rest.
Call me if you need anything.
I’m in the living room.
Tang Jie will be here soon.
You guys can go back first.
Let's wait until she comes.
Go to sleep.
You're not leaving?
Leave. Stop looking.
I'm worried
to leave Yan
to someone unrelated to her.
You are the unrelated one.
Mr. Wen.
I’ve bought everything as you ordered.
Okay.
I'm downstairs.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay, thank you.
Go ahead.
There are no surveillance cameras in that alley.
You know that.
But, I've arranged people
to expand the scope
to investigate the stalker.
Lu Yan said
the person used ether.
Investigate this line.
The scene is still under investigation.
But based on the clues
provided by Dr. Lu,
I've also arranged a team
to look into all of the illegal stores
that sell ether.
Senior,
the several cases of rape
and kidnapping women
that we cracked previously
used this too.
Okay.
Let me know if you have any news.
She needs to sleep.
Is it appropriate for you to
create so much noise
in the middle of the night?
I'm afraid she'll be hungry when she wakes up.
Sure.
Then hurry up.
Leave once you're done.
Why aren't you leaving?
Are police officers all so free?
You don't need to work?
Have you found the person who hurt Lu Yan?
Which department do you lead?
So much unnecessary talk.
Mind your own business.
You...
Why are you two still here?
Did the noise wake you up?
Your Senior
is showing off his cooking skills at your house.
Are you hungry?
I made you some porridge.
Thank you for today.
You guys should go home now.
Let me take a rest.
Okay.
Rest assured.
We're leaving.
Don't stay here.
Hurry up.
You even made porridge.
You're all fired up as soon as I'm back,
aren't you?
I've been taking care of her for the past eight years.
I wonder
what you've been doing these eight years.
What feelings do you have for her?
Exactly what you're thinking.
You were kicked out
and you still feel that way?
Jiang.
Why are you two...
I'm leaving.
Goodbye, Wen.
I seem to smell
a strong scent of gunpowder.
Did you two fight?
What are you two doing here?
My wife is here to accompany Lu Yan.
I'm here to accompany my wife.
I told you you don't have to come.
No way, it's so dangerous.
I can't let you
leave my sight by even a bit.
Are you living here?
I'll sleep on the sofa.
Don't worry.
I'll help you protect Lu Yan.
Sure.
Then go upstairs quickly.
Tang Jie,
I'll trouble you
to pay extra attention
and take good care of her.
Don't worry.
Go back and rest.
I'm leaving.
Honey.
Why are they here together?
Right?
[Huiting Complex]
Where are you going?
You're awake.
I have an operation today.
Are you still going to work?
You're indeed this.
The most dedicated and professional employee.
Wait a while.
I'll buy you breakfast.
No, no.
I'll eat in the hospital.
Lie down, lie down.
Look.
Some people
promised to buy us breakfast.
Now he's sleeping like a pig.
He's tired.
Don't see me off.
You two can continue sleeping.
Alright.
I'm going to work.
You two take a rest.
I'll pick you up after work tonight.
No need.
Didn't Jiang Chengyi installed a camera
at the gate?
I'm leaving.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Who is it?
Don't touch my wife!
Honey.
Where is Lu Yan?
She went to work.
You scared me.
Get some more sleep.
-Give me a hug.
-Thank you.
It must be hard to sleep in this spot all night.
Our home is more comfortable.
Morning.
You...
Why are you still here?
I'm here....
To...
Execute a mission.
That's so tiring
What mission?
Well...
We have a case here.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Okay.
That's good.
I'm going to work.
You...
You can keep waiting here.
Okay.
Let me see you off.
No need.
You didn't sleep well all night.
Keep waiting here.
Hello.
Captain Jiang,
we have a new lead.
Come back to the team soon.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Through our investigation at the crime scene,
we found that
it's indeed ether.
Dr. Lu
is indeed an anesthesiologist.
She told us in advance that they used ether.
She saved us
a lot of time.
Yes.
We have been checking
all of the surveillance cameras
at the areas he have possibly been to.
Together with our investigative visits,
we've preliminarily identified
this man.
His name is Wang Qiang.
He is 24 years old this year.
He's not a Ninghai local.
His registered residence is in Huozhou.
[Personal information of Wang Qiang]
Unemployed.
A socially idle person.
[Personal information of Wang Qiang]
Wang Qiang went to jail twice.
The first time he was sentenced to two years
for theft.
The second time was
due to infringement of personal information.
The case is very serious.
He was sentenced to a fixed-term imprisonment
of more than three years and less than seven years.
He sells secretly filmed footage?
Yes.
[Anshan Criminal Investigation]
Wang Qiang
has many alternative accounts
that are created specially to sell
secretly-taken
photos
and videos
of girls.
But he's very cunning.
He deals with people on foreign websites.
If anything happens,
he deletes his account and disappears.
So, it is quite difficult to deal with.
Where does he live?
We found a rental house.
The landlord said
he hasn't been back for a long time
and he also hasn't paid the rent
for months.
I guess he's out of money.
We have also checked all hotels,
motels
and hostels
in the city.
There are no registration information of him.
[Personal information of Wang Qiang]
I have a direction.
Doesn't he like taking pictures of girls?
Let's search at places like
universities,
where there are many girls around.
What do you think, Senior?
He must need to find a place to spend the night.
Look for internet cafes
and budget hotels
around his activity area.
See
if he registered using a fake identity.
Got it.
Okay, let's go with that.
Time to work.
[Personal information of Wang Qiang]
[69 Lane, Gao'An Road]
Is anyone here?
Sir, do you need to fix your car?
[Daily Goods, Welcome]
Is this surveillance camera yours?
Yes.
Can I have a look?
Are you crazy?
Not here to fix the car, but to watch my camera footage.
Do you think you're a cop?
[Loading]
[Pay]
You've received 10,000 Yuan.
What do you mean?
Boss, it's inappropriate.
The CCTV footage is private.
You've received 10,000 Yuan.
Can I buy this video?
Boss, wait a moment.
I’ll get it for you.
Hello, Mr. Wen.
If someone wants to see me, tell them I’m not here.
Got it, Mr. Wen.
Stop playing with your phone.
Let's eat.
Come on.
Stir-fried beef.
Your favourite.
Let me tell you.
I followed every step
of your stir-fried beef recipe exactly,
but I just can't get the same taste.
I won’t teach you.
It is an exclusive recipe
only my son.
Exclusive recipe.
There's also a soup.
Don't wait for me. Eat it while it's hot.
See?
Your dad
needs to be praised more.
When he is happy,
he'll do all the chores at home.
He even told me about his unique skill.
Do it himself if it's so unique.
What is this called?
The more capable you are, the more you work.
Why am I telling you this?
Later,
I'll teach it to my daughter-in-law.
Tell me.
what is your progress
with Lu?
She's facing some troubles
recently,
so...
We didn't get to talk much.
What is it?
I'll tell you later.
Why are you still sitting here?
If something happened,
you should go and keep her company.
Listen.
girls need company the most
whenever they face problems.
Hurry up and go.
Dad made a whole table of dishes.
It's okay. I'll explain to him.
Go now. Hurry.
There's traffic jam at this hour.
Will this work?
Yes.
Go.
I'll go then.
Hurry up.
-Comfort her well.
-I’m leaving.
Silly girl.
Who closed the door just now?
Son.
Where did he go?
He got a call and went on a mission.
This fellow left just like that,
wasting my effort
to cook so many dishes.
He's so...
You're scolding him now.
Weren't you like this too back then?
Disappeared with just one phone call.
When he had appendicitis,
you didn't come back no matter how much I called.
I carried him
to the hospital alone.
At that time, my back...
Come on.
Eat while it's hot.
My back still has problems from that.
Is it delicious?
Yes.
Do you want to learn?
I'm not teach you.
Come on, eat it while it's hot.
Annoying.
Let me get you some soup.
Come on.
[Emergency]
[Ninghai Anshan People's Hospital]
[Access Point]
[Outpatient]
[[Outpatient]]
What are you doing?
I'm just passing by.
Uncle was discharged.
Liu Yuming was discharged too.
You...
Who are you waiting for?
Waiting for a fool.
Who are you calling a fool?
I wanted to see you
but I'm worried you're busy,
so I didn't call
and came directly.
If you need anything,
I'll be here.
You...
How long have you been here?
Not too long.
I brought you some food.
Eat if you got hungry while on duty.
You're hungry already?
Yes, I haven't had dinner.
Have you eaten?
No.
Is it sweet?
Hello.
Captain Jiang.
we’ve located Wang Qiang.
We’ll go there now.
Okay.
Send it to me.
I'll be right there.
Well,
go back first.
I have a mission.
Go ahead.
I'm leaving.
What a crappy place!
It's so narrow.
My car almost got scratched.
Are you dissatisfied?
Move away your hand.
Move away.
How about
we meet at the police station?
This is too little!
Are you bargaining with me?
I got injured.
Isn't it okay to ask for more?
Besides,
there's always a cop following her all the time.
It's too risky for me.
You're only giving this much.
Who's willing to do it?
I'll give you another 50,000 Yuan when the job is done.
Get the job done neatly.
You promised.
50,000.
Not a penny less.
You took so much money from me
and you didn't even take a single photo.
Can you do it or not?
She was lucky last time.
What grudge do you have
against her?
Do you have to do this to her?
Don't ask what you shouldn't ask.
Remember to take more frontal shots.
I want the face to be clear.
I want
her reputation ruined.
But that girl
is quite pretty.
It's a pity
to only take pictures.
If you want to do something with her,
that's your business.
I don't care.
As long as it doesn't involve me.
You really hate her, don't you?
Captain Jiang.
[Please come in for internet access]
[Pisces Internet Cafe]
Where is he?
We won't leak any information.
Only the three of us
are aware of this operation.
Go and ask the front desk.
[Top up your game account and receive a Mimosa VIP membership]
Police investigation.
Where's the guest at computer No. 38?
No. 38?
I didn't see him getting off the computer,
and didn't see him leaving either.
Check the CCTV for me.
[Lobby] [Stairs] [Reception]
Is that him?
Yes.
He left through the back door.
Captain Jiang.
He sneaked out from the back door.
Where is the back door?
Go straight this way.
Let's go.
Yes.
Split up!
Stop!
[Energetic Light Meal Alliance]
Excuse me.
Be careful. Make way.
Stop chasing.
Let's go back to the Internet cafe
and search for his personal information.
Okay.
[Energetic Light Meal Alliance]
Who is it?
[Resource Sharing Group 1]
Are there any new ones?
Are there videos of the women's locker room?
The quality is so bad.
So boring.
Refund!
Refund? I can't return a little.
Suit yourself.
[Please don't smoke in bed]
[Rich and handsome]
These women.
[A new hotel I stayed at on a trip. The environment is good.]
[Joy of buying a car hahaha. I'm so cool.]
Sucking up to me once I change my profile picture.
What is this?
Can we get to know each other?
Sure.
Are you in Ninghai?
I'll be on a business trip to Ninghai in a few days.
We can meet if it's convenient for you.
Sure.
This girl is nice.
Hello, young lady.
What would you like to drink?
Ice latte, thanks.
Okay, hold on.
What the hell.
She looks prettier than in photos.
This is quite a beauty.
I'm kneeling.
Can you take a few more photos of her legs?
I love long legs.
Miss, your coffee.
Enjoy.
Can I sit here?
Sure.
What would you like to drink?
I want
to see the photos you took just now.
Sure.
Nice shots.
Wang Qiang.