[English subtitles are available.]
[Ji Chang-wook]
[Kim You-jung]
[Backstreet Rookie]
This is how you're going to congratulate
the best employee?
What more do you expect?
I think I've done enough.
Gosh, forget it.
My gosh, what do you expect?
Is this what you want?
-Is that for me?
-Yes, it's for you.
Take it.
I'm so happy.
Now, you just need to give me
a piggyback ride.
You still haven't given up on that?
Of course. I don't give up that easily.
That's how I became the best part-timer
among millions of part-timers
in this country.
I'm sure you know how hard it is
to become that
since you used to work
at the headquarters.
Okay, fine. I'll give you a piggyback ride
just this once for one second.
-Forget it.
-Okay, fine.
Three seconds. No more negotiating.
Three seconds. Deal?
Come here.
Gosh, you're unbelievable.
Wait. Let me get my knees ready.
-Okay, come on.
-It's just three seconds.
In 1, 2, 3.
Okay. Now, 1, 2, 3. Get off.
-Hurry up and get off.
-Try and make me.
Are you kidding me? Hey, get off me.
Hey, you'll get hurt if I use my strength.
-Get off me.
-No!
Gosh, will you please get off me?
Yeon-joo.
Sorry, did I interrupt you two?
Interrupt? No.
Are you going to stay there?
My goodness!
I'm fine. The floor is also fine.
Yeon-joo,
I know this looks bad,
but it's not what you think.
Of course. I trust you, Dae-hyun.
-You're congratulating her, right?
-Yes.
Yes, he was congratulating me
for becoming the employee of the month.
I was just joking around
and asked him for a piggyback ride.
Ms. Employee of the Month,
you can get to work now.
Yeon-joo, why don't we step out?
We need to congratulate her properly.
Would you like to join us for dinner?
-Sorry?
-No, no.
We can't just leave the store empty.
♫ No, woman, no cry ♫
What?
Are you sure about this?
This place is expensive.
It's fine.
-Welcome.
-Hello.
It's been a while since I saw you two.
-Yes.
-Hello.
I'll take you to a table for two
by the windows.
-We're a party of three today.
-Sorry?
All right. I'll take you this way.
Dae-hyun, we haven't been here
in so long, right?
Yes, this is our first time back
after our second anniversary.
-Is that right?
-Thank you.
-Take a look at the menu.
-Okay.
[Main Course]
[Traditional beef steak]
[Fish of the day]
I've never been somewhere so fancy,
so I wouldn't know even if I looked at it.
You can order anything for me.
I can eat everything just fine.
I love all sorts of food.
Which wine would you like, then?
I love all sorts of alcohol as well.
I loved the wine that we had
for our second anniversary.
Did you mean,
Marchesi Antinori Tignanello?
Sorry?
Yes, that's probably it.
I think
the one I had with my father last time
would be better.
The one that Dr. Yoo absolutely loved?
Yes, it was Ghost Block
Oakville Estate Cabernet Sauvignon.
Excellent. I'll get that ready for you
right away.
Yeon-joo, you're such an expert on wine.
We had it last time.
-Did we?
-Don't you remember?
I don't remember wine names.
All wines are the same to me.
[Gosh, I feel so small.]
Enjoy your evening.
-Thank you.
Saet-byul, congratulations on becoming
the employee of the month.
[Why is he taking such little sips?]
-It's great.
-Do you like it?
Yes.
I'm getting goosebumps.
The wine is quite bitter,
and I get goosebumps when I eat
or drink something bitter.
Look at my arms.
I have goosebumps all over.
Stop it and put your arm down.
Why are you telling us to look at it?
My glass is empty.
-Dae-hyun.
-Sure.
I hope you'll continue to work hard
for Dae-hyun's store.
You want me to work harder to promote
products and also for the store?
I became the employee of the month
by working hard to promote products.
How can I work harder than that?
I'm just asking you to keep up
the good work.
You know, just work.
I see. I work hard for everything.
For my job and for everything else.
And also,
I had something to say to you today.
What is it?
I misunderstood you at the bathroom
at that weird bar back then.
"Misunderstood"?
I was just very anxious.
I hope you understand.
She's still not going to apologize?
Saet-byul probably knows
that you didn't do that on purpose.
Right?
Yes, probably.
She understands.
I appreciate your understanding.
I could keep chugging the wine
with you at the table with me.
I love it. The wine tastes great.
[She's no ordinary girl.]
It's delicious.
It's so nice to come back here in so long.
-It is. I really enjoyed the meal.
-Right?
-Excuse me.
-Sure.
Hello, sir. How have you been?
What makes you call at this hour?
Sorry?
Butter soy sauce beef triangular gimbap?
Why?
Is it the manager?
No, we'll just take what we ordered.
We ordered Spicy Fire Chicken
-And the beef ones.
-and the gochujang beef ones.
Dae-hyun, can you keep your voice down?
There are people here.
Customers at our store only love
spicy ones,
so items like butter soy sauce beef
triangular gimbap always expire.
Butter soy sauce beef ones are a bad idea.
I made myself clear, yes?
-What did he say?
-Saet-byul,
make sure to tell the delivery man
when you get the orders.
He won't listen because I'm a part-timer.
So, you'd take butter soy sauce beef
triangular gimbap for our store?
-No!
-You wouldn't, right?
-I wouldn't.
-Absolutely not.
-Understood?
-Okay.
-Yes?
I mean, yes.
I'm sorry the call went on for so long,
Yeon-joo.
-Let's get going.
-You can go to the store and sort it out.
-Sorry?
-I don't mind,
so you go to the store and sort out
whatever you need to.
Franchise owners need to stand up
to the headquarters at times too.
Then how will you get home?
You think I can't get home without you?
-I should still...
-Ms. Yoo?
Director Cho.
-Hello, Director Cho.
-Hello, Mr. Choi.
Ms. Jung, you're here as well.
Hello, sir.
How do you know her?
She's the employee of the month.
She's the promotion queen who made
our private label products sold-out.
You must be here to dine as well.
No, I'm just heading back after a workout.
A workout?
I didn't know people worked out at hotels.
I'm going home. Did you drive here?
That's great. Can you give me a ride?
You shouldn't have let your girlfriend go
like that.
What are you talking about?
Look who's talking.
You shouldn't have done that earlier.
What are you saying?
No idea. Let's get back
before the truck arrives.
Mr. Choi, why don't we take a taxi?
Just the two of us. How romantic.
Should we?
-Really?
-30 seconds.
-Until what?
-Until the bus arrives.
Seriously? Wait for me!
Come on, run! Hurry!
No, don't leave.
My gosh.
-For two, please.
-Tab your card.
I don't know her.
Sorry.
You could've paid for me. Move over.
Stop it!
Why do you have to sit here
when there are so many seats?
It's too cramped now.
There were so many taxis.
We should've just taken one.
Did you not notice how they were
all deluxe taxis?
Stingy, as always.
I haven't had a meal that expensive
in so long, but it's all digested now.
You should be honored.
You got a good meal,
all thanks to Yeon-joo.
You saw how great Yeon-joo is, right?
Don't you ever dare to bother her.
Let's never do anything that could
ever create any misunderstanding. Good?
Why aren't you answering me?
I was just kidding.
You don't have to be so serious.
Don't you think
you're a little too serious?
Just don't cross the line.
-What line?
-Don't you see this?
There are many lines between us
like these.
Don't cross any of them.
They're electrical wires too.
Look at me crossing them!
Gosh, that hurts!
Now I'm not crossing them.
Stop it.
I wouldn't want to cross any.
You're so petty.
-Goodness.
-That's great.
Thanks for moving away.
I love having the whole seat to myself.
Bye now.
Yeon-joo,
can I ask you what's wrong?
Nothing is wrong.
There's just a lot going on in my head.
Relationships don't always go as expected.
Good night.
-Here you go.
-Please take these.
-I'm serious.
-You may go.
-Thank you!
-You can't do this to me.
Bye now.
-Drive safe. See you tomorrow!
-Thank you.
Drive safe.
You saw that?
What would you do without me?
You couldn't have done that alone.
Nonsense.
Whatever.
Just make sure you place
our spicy ones out nicely.
-You're not going to do it with me?
-No.
You can do it all by yourself,
Ms. Part-timer. I'm leaving now.
Bye!
I'll take a Ghost Block Oakville Estate
Cabernet Sauvignon.
Why do wines have such long names?
These wines are perfectly fine.
Why was that one so expensive?
It didn't even taste good.
I need some soju bomb on a day like this.
I would've been drinking soju right now
if I weren't the employee of the month.
But I shouldn't.
♫ Hello ♫
I can't draw if you keep watching me
like that.
I'm sorry, that wasn't on purpose.
My drawing is quite eye-catching, I know.
Some say that it's like a vacuum cleaner.
That means they want to clean it
because it's so dirty.
No, I'm just kidding.
Dal-sik, did you think about what I said?
Of course.
My friend is getting an interview,
so how can I just sit still?
What is it?
-The keyword I thought of
-Yes?
-is lighthouse.
-Lighthouse?
You wouldn't want to see anything
but a lighthouse
when you're in the deep, dark seas
at night, right?
Yes, you're right.
A convenience store that's open
for 24 hours
[is like a lighthouse.]
[It's a place for the hungry, the lonely,]
[and those who are afraid of the dark.
It's a place for everyone.]
Your convenience store equals
-a lighthouse.
-A lighthouse.
Your interview will turn out well
if you go in this direction.
Gosh. Dal-sik.
-That's not a bad idea.
-It's good, isn't it?
Here.
-What are these?
-They're all for you.
I'm leaving now.
Butter soy sauce beef? This one is rare.
My stomach hurts.
Did I eat something bad at the hotel?
Oh, right.
[Yes, Saet-byul?]
-Did the package arrive?
[-What package?]
Why are you asking me?
I'm asking because you're home.
Aren't you home?
What are you saying? Of course I'm home.
I'll go and check with the security
and see if they have the package. Good?
-Did you eat?
-I ate ramyeon.
Hey, it's not like we have nothing to eat.
If you say that 1 more time,
it'll be your 100th time saying that.
[Why do you always eat ramyeon?]
Fine, fine!
I have to go and study. Bye!
-Look at that.
-That must be nice.
You're making all of us,
the sister-less ones, really sad.
Eun-byul's sister is really scary.
-That's right.
-Scarier than me?
-No!
-No.
Let's go back to practicing.
Eun-byul, you're good,
but you need
to make your moves bigger and clearer.
Understood?
Yes!
-Yes!
Cue the music.
♫ Where are you? ♫
♫ Are you hiding somewhere? ♫
♫ Are you back because you love me? ♫
[Yeon-joo, you got home safe, right?]
[She hasn't responded for 2 hours
and 10 minutes.]
-Get off me.
-No!
Gosh, will you please get off me?
Yeon-joo, I know this looks bad.
You're congratulating her, right?
I'm just asking you to keep up
the good work.
You know, just work.
That's great. Can you give me a ride?
Gosh.
Good morning, Yeon-joo.
Here, get in.
I know that you're not
in the mood to talk, so just listen.
I only realized how frustrated and annoyed
you must have been when I got home.
I think I was
always proud of you.
But I failed to understand
how you must have felt.
I will never do something
that might give you the wrong idea.
I'm really sorry about yesterday.
My gosh. If I were you,
I would have knuckled
a boyfriend like me on the head.
I can't believe
you put up with a guy like me.
Do you want me to do that now?
Assaulting the driver is dangerous. No.
You can pull over.
You'll be late for work. No.
-Choi Dae-hyun!
-Yes?
Can't you figure it out sooner next time?
Right. I should be quicker
next time, right?
From now on, I'll learn
to read the situation and become
the quickest-witted man.
I'm not the same guy anymore.
Call me Mr. Quick-witted.
Come on, Yeon-joo. Smile for me.
-Gosh.
-Let's start our day with a smile.
[Security Guard Office]
Darn it.
I liked the wine,
but my body doesn't like it.
I don't care for that fancy wine.
[Bills]
[Priority Package]
Nice.
What's this smell?
Gosh, she reeks of sweat.
She didn't even take a shower
before going to bed.
She's disgusting.
Okay.
Okay. Perfect.
I'll crush this outfit.
All right.
Today, I'm going to cook kimchi stew.
Watch and learn.
Hello.
I'm the editor at "Part-time Korea".
Oh, yes. Hold on. Wait.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm the general manager
of Shinseong-dong convenience store.
[Shinseong-dong]
My name is Choi Dae-hyun.
My team will be on their way soon.
Are you ready for the interview?
Of course. Don't worry.
During the interview,
our store will be closed.
You don't have to do that.
Oh, right. Should I prepare some snacks?
No. You guys must be hungry.
I'll prepare a meal for you.
No. It's all right.
Then, do you need anything else?
My entire family has been getting
ready for this since the morning.
Not at all. Just make sure the store
manager is ready for the interview.
You got it. Don't worry.
-Good luck with the interview.
-Okay. Thank you.
Bye. Let's do this!
Shinseong-dong!
Hello. I was picked
as the store manager of the month.
My name is Jung Saet-byul.
What are you doing?
None of your business.
I'm surprised you cooked breakfast.
You should learn to cook
when you can. Okay?
-Why would I do that?
-When you graduate, you'll move out.
You'll make money to support yourself.
Hey, think about everything
I did to support you.
You ought to serve me
three hot meals a day.
You're nagging me again.
Eat a lot and study hard. You can do it.
Wait, do you know what today is?
Never mind. Nothing.
What's today? What is it?
Something is fishy.
What are you talking about? It's nothing.
If you come clean now, I'll spare you.
What are you talking about?
If you cause trouble, I'll kill you.
"If you cause trouble, I'll kill you."
♫ I like Superman ♫
Darn it. She's making me angry again.
Hey, you'd better clean this up!
Thanks for this!
Darn it. Come on.
What is this?
[Priority Package]
Darn it. That wench.
Darn it! I'm going to kill you.
Hey!
Darn it. Come on.
I have to wash up now
if I'm going to get there on time.
Darn it. What am I supposed to wear?
Come on.
Take a look.
Mom, pick an outfit you like.
Don't even check the price tag.
Will you buy it for me?
I believe that when the occasion is right,
I ought to spend money.
-Hurry up.
-Hey.
Do you think I'll say no to that?
What a surprise.
-My gosh. Who is this lady?
-Do I look good?
-Do I look okay?
-Outfits can change people.
You look like someone else.
Really? Should I buy a pair of pants too?
Yes. Let's get one too. Go and change.
Okay.
Try on a new pair of pants too.
Did you see my daughter here?
She was right here.
She said something urgent came up,
so she left.
Did she pay for the clothes?
Hold on.
It's 317 dollars.
Will you pay it with cash or a card?
Hold on.
This one says it's only 67 dollars.
I see. The total price includes
the clothes your daughter took.
She took a blouse.
So yours is 67 dollars.
And your daughter's blouse is 250 dollars.
Your daughter's blouse
is slightly more expensive.
Is that so? I won't take this.
How much was her blouse?
250 dollars.
Come on, Mom. Don't tell me
you didn't buy the shirt.
You said you were buying, you wench.
I said that? When?
You said when the occasion is right,
you ought to spend money.
Why would you say something like that?
Why do you think I said that?
I don't want you to penny-pinch.
-My gosh!
-You're here.
Gosh, this must have been expensive.
When did you buy that?
This? I didn't buy this.
I think Dae-hyun bought this for me.
Dae-hyun?
What about me? Where's mine?
-What is it? What's wrong, Mom?
-Darn it.
You punk.
You should have bought one
for your mom too.
Dad. This sweater...
My daughter extorted money out of me.
My son looks down on me.
What's the point of living?
Hey, are you going to wear that
to the interview?
What? You want me to put on makeup?
Forget it. Whatever.
I don't want to do the interview.
Ma'am, I'm here.
Hi, Saet-byul. You're here.
What happened?
Do I look okay?
You look cute.
My gosh. Goodness, Saet-byul.
Congratulations, Saet-byul.
This is wonderful!
-Who...
-Wait, you don't know my sister?
Hello. It's nice to meet you.
I'm Jung Saet-byul.
Gosh, you're unbelievable.
This is a talent.
How could you do that
to someone you just met? Gosh.
No, we met before.
I saw you before
when I was passing by here. Right?
Right.
Hello, we're journalists
from Part-time Korea.
-Hello. Welcome.
-Hi.
An applicant from our website was
selected as the employee of the month.
So we are very happy for her.
My gosh, yes.
Who's the store manager?
-Me.
-Right here.
Her name is Jung Saet-byul.
And I'm the general manager.
And this is my family.
-My dad, my mom, and my sister.
-Yes.
-Hello.
-Hi.
It's an interview for your employee,
not your family.
-Well, we're like a big family here.
-Yes.
-That's right.
-We're like her parents.
Okay. Do a pose?
-Just be natural.
-Okay.
I just feel great
when I stand at the counter.
[Shinseong-dong]
Why?
People don't judge me
based on their opinions.
They just see me as a part-timer.
I see. I heard there are a lot of
customers especially during your shift.
Why do you think you're so popular?
"Kindness". "Good service".
My pretty face.
-I have to agree with you on that.
-Right?
[Shinseong-dong]
I heard you talk to your customers a lot.
Is that your effort to stay popular?
It's nothing like that.
When customers walk in,
I say hello with a smile.
And when they ask me questions,
I answer them.
And I also have a lot of questions,
so I ask them questions too.
[Shinseong-dong]
That's how I end up getting close
to customers and talk to them a lot.
Here's my last question.
What does a convenience store mean to you?
Pardon?
"A lighthouse".
Your back?
-A piggyback ride?
-"A lighthouse".
Excuse me. I need time to think.
A lighthouse.
-A lighthouse.
A lighthouse!
You know, there's a lighthouse
at the ocean.
Right. A lighthouse.
This is nice.
It's like playing a group game.
Right.
A lighthouse. I see.
It's nice, isn't it? Please write that in.
We dressed up today.
We ought to take a photo.
Yes, just do it for the sake
of the convenience store.
No. I can't give her a piggyback ride.
I'll never do it. Why must I do that?
What if someone sees the photo?
I won't do it!
Who's going to see it?
What's wrong with it?
She has a point. It's not that hard
-to smile.
-You don't know anything.
-How dare you?
-Hey.
For us to be in the group photo,
you have to give her a piggyback ride.
My friend, Hwang-tae, took a newspaper
photo with his son for the Marines.
He still brags about it.
Hae-suk had the highest sales
a decade ago.
She still carries around that photo.
It's so annoying to look at that.
The title is, "Lucky Charm Part-timer
Deserves More Than a Piggyback Ride".
-Why can't you do it?
-Even so, I can't do it. Never.
Forget it. I'll do it.
What are you talking about?
The general manager has to do it!
Unbelievable! Just forget it!
Your parents are asking you to do it!
But you can't even do that.
You're not our son!
Forget about taking the photo!
Let's close down the store
and quit everything!
-Mom! What--
-Stop it!
Hello, Dae-soon.
Wait, everyone is here today.
I see. You came here
because of the interview today.
It's been a while, Dal-sik.
You didn't have time to wash up
because you worked all night.
You're on your way to wash up now?
I had a good night's sleep.
And I just came out of a sauna.
-You look very clean.
-Yes.
-Mr. Choi.
-Hey.
We can wrap up here after we take a photo
in front of the store.
-Okay. You know what?
-Okay, okay.
By the way, do we have
to give her a piggyback ride?
Can we do it just standing up?
How can you be so uncooperative?
We're doing this to help your store.
You said this article would
circulate strictly internally, right?
It will be a small article
on the back of the company magazine.
The company magazine.
It's to encourage job-seekers, you know.
The headquarters won't see it, right?
This article will be printed in books.
They would never get to see it.
-You're certain, right?
-Of course.
-Really?
-Gosh.
Hey.
Is there something wrong?
Get on my back.
-What?
-Get on my back.
Why would I? I don't want to.
-It's already decided.
-What do you mean?
-Yes, give her a piggyback ride.
-Yes.
Get on his back.
-I guess I'm pretty heavy.
-Goodness.
Hurry.
Gosh, I really don't want to do that.
I don't want to do it either. Just hurry.
-I guess I have no choice.
-Yes.
My husband is about to pass out. Hurry up.
-All right.
-I'll take the photo now.
In 1, 2, 3.
[Backstreet Rookie]
Yeon-joo, I'm done now.
It went very well.
Yes. I'm calling you
as soon as the journalists left.
Yes.
[Shouldn't you be working?]
[I will after this call.]
Don't you know me?
I was very calm throughout the interview.
Of course. I'm the lighthouse
of my neighborhood.
[I did the interview, not you.]
[She didn't see it. So what?]
[Unbelievable.]
Yeon-joo, this interview was
to circulate only internally.
I don't think
you'll get a chance to read it.
[My gosh, you're so petty!]
[Don't cross the line. Go away.]
Okay, Yeon-joo.
I'm going to work really hard now.
I'll keep opening up
more convenience stores.
Just watch me.
I hope a lot of good things
come from the interview.
You don't have to call me that often.
Okay. Have a good day. Bye.
Okay, thank you.
Ms. Yoo. CQX will accept our offer!
-Congratulations.
-Amazing!
-My gosh.
Even other companies gave up on them.
They are known to be so picky.
How did you win them over?
Tell me your secret.
I can't tell you here.
Does it mean you will tell us
at tonight's team dinner?
You're so quick-witted as always,
Director Cho.
We're having a team dinner today!
-My gosh.
-Mr. Choi.
I guess you're not going to work.
The sales during the afternoon
were low for a reason.
We have so much work to do.
But you were on the phone.
You're taking it easy
while drinking coffee.
You were the cause.
Gosh, Saet-byul.
If you're jealous, you should just say it.
It's not my fault
that you have no one to call.
I have people to call.
I have friends too.
I see. Your high school friend?
Shouldn't she be in school right now?
You should call during her break.
Do they get ten minutes for their break?
It's not her.
I have another friend. It's a guy friend.
He's a celebrity.
My gosh, a celebrity? Goodness.
Who is it? Who's the guy?
-You're unbelievable.
-Goodness. He's...
It's him. It's this guy.
Kang Ji-wook? He's your friend?
He's my friend.
No way. Saet-byul, I know you've been
working as a promoter for a long time.
You must've felt so close to him,
so you thought he was your friend.
You're fooling yourself.
It's true.
If he's really your friend,
ask him to come and join us
for our get-together later.
You think I can't?
Go ahead.
I'd like to see him if I get a chance.
You don't know what you're asking for.
All right. Wait.
Gosh, you're a big mess.
Saying something
you can't take responsibility for
because you have a temper
is a very bad habit.
Fix it before it develops
into a habit. Okay?
So go back home for now.
I'll see you later tonight.
See you later.
Darn it.
-Come on, Puppy.
[-The phone is turned off.]
[You'll be connected
to the voicemail box.]
[-After the beep...]
-I'm going to crush you.
Come on. Why isn't everyone picking up?
Hey!
Hey, bro. Sorry. I was in class.
I was actually going to call you.
Why?
Eun-byul didn't come to school.
Is she okay?
What? She didn't go to school?
She's fine.
I saw her leave after breakfast.
I'll go ahead and ask the girls.
Okay, bye.
Eun-byul, that brat.
No wonder she seemed a bit weird.
Why am I having such a bad day?
[Daily Guru]
[Daily Guru!]
[Today's Horoscopes for Saet-byul]
[You will get disappointed by someone,
so be careful.]
[Something bad will surely happen.]
My gosh, this guy is a fortune-teller.
How did he know I'd get disappointed?
Gosh, I wonder what's going to happen.
Cut!
Okay! That was amazing, Ji-wook.
Okay, let's get ready for the next scene.
-Ji-wook, are you okay?
-Yes.
-My gosh, you came out amazing.
-Oh, really?
Ji-wook, you got a missed call.
-Really? Excuse me for a second.
-Okay.
[Saet-byul]
Hyeon-ji, listen to me carefully.
What is it?
I went to the dermatologist
and paid for ten laser treatment sessions.
-But I don't think it works on me.
-What?
But I can't get a refund.
[Porcelain Skincare,
Special Voucher]
So I'm looking for someone
to transfer this to.
Here.
You even get skincare
after the laser treatment.
Do you want to keep your freckles,
or do you want to become like this?
It's yours.
Really?
Geum-bi, Eun-byul went to an audition.
What? "An audition"?
Hello, I'm Jung Eun-byul,
applicant number 12.
I'll do my best.
[Preliminary Girl Group Audition]
[Park Si-hyung, Yang Hyung-sik,
Lee Su-mun]
[Preliminary Girl Group Audition]
Number 13, Park Seo-hui.
Good luck!
Hey! Hyeon-ji!
I passed the audition!
They asked me to come
to the second audition in two days!
Where are you?
Why can't I hear you properly?
[Eun-byul]
[Where are you?]
Eun-byul, Geum-bi ended up
finding out.
[Porcelain Skincare]
I didn't say anything.
I don't understand how she found out.
Hey! I told you to keep it a secret,
you dumb fool!
My sister will kill me if she finds out!
You know what? Just hang up.
Jung Eun-byul!
Hey!
Hey, stop right there!
Would you stop if you were me? Move, move.
My gosh, that brat!
Hey!
[Hey!]
[I'll tell the world how brutal you were
when I appear on a talk show later on!]
I'll tell the world how brutal you were
when I appear on a talk show later on!
"Brutal"? Are you serious?
["Brutal"? Are you serious?]
I guess you need a beating again.
Come here! Get over here!
[I guess you need a beating again.
Come here! Get over here!]
I'm just trying to succeed
so I can give you a better life.
[I'm just trying to succeed
so I can give you a better life.]
Don't you get it?
[Don't you get it?]
[No, I don't!]
No, I don't!
This is my school.
You're not a student here.
Are you a student here?
I'm in class 3-1.
My name is Jung Eun-byul.
I passed the preliminary audition.
If I pass the second audition,
I get to be a trainee.
Saet-byul, I swear I can do this.
I got so many compliments today.
Shut your mouth and get ready
to get a beating later on.
Will you please just trust me?
[May he rest in peace.]
Saet-byul. Eun-byul.
I'll take care of you guys.
You girls should come live with me.
My goodness, I feel so bad for you girls.
My gosh, I can't believe
you have to go through this.
My gosh, you poor girls.
I let you live with me,
so you should at least earn your keep.
I used to work at a factory
when I was your age.
My goodness, I even paid
for your dad's college tuition.
[Jung Saet-byul]
I didn't even get that much money
for his death benefit,
but you guys eat so much.
It's unbelievable.
As soon as I buy some rice,
you both finish it all. How shameless.
What will you two become
after sucking me dry?
My gosh, you girls are so shameless.
Eat up.
[Jung Saet-byul]
Don't worry. I'll make money
so you can finish school, okay?
It's okay. Let's go.
[Jangpung Chinese Restaurant]
-Here's your jjajangmyeon. Enjoy.
-Thank you.
Saet-byul, one bowl of jjajangmyeon
for Busan Mart.
Got it.
-I'll be right back.
-Okay, see you.
[Saet-byul, I'm sorry.
I was busy shooting earlier.]
[I'm on my way to the convenience store
to see you.]
[Puppy Ji-wook]
♫ Let's eat noodles ♫
Hey, Kang Ji-wook's friend is here.
[You just wait and see.]
The products are here.
Organize the storage,
Kang Ji-wook's friend.
Look at her pretending to be upset.
My gosh, she must be angry.
Should I not have come right on time?
It's better than being late.
Welcome.
What do you need?
Well... I...
My gosh, you're Kang Ji-wook!
You're Kang Ji-wook, right?
Gosh, I can't believe this.
You're the guy who was in that movie
with Ma Dong-seok, right?
Yes, that's right.
My gosh, this is amazing.
I really enjoyed that movie, "Black City".
You know that action scene
where you fought with Ma Dong-seok?
My gosh, this is unbelievable.
You're so tall in real life.
My goodness, you're so handsome.
But do you live nearby?
I've never seen you in this neighborhood.
I'm here to meet someone.
Who?
Your girlfriend?
-Hey, Puppy. Carry this for me.
-Okay.
-Where should I put it?
-Over there.
Ji-wook, you shouldn't be...
Hey! What are you doing?
Don't you know who he is?
My gosh, he's Kang Ji-wook,
-the movie actor!
-That's right!
It's Kang Ji-wook! How did he come here?
-Do you know what's important?
-He's so handsome.
What?
Mr. Choi, you crossed the line.
Saet-byul, have you been well?
Yes, I've been well.
I'm surprised you actually came.
Of course I came.
What? You guys know each other?
We were friends since elementary school.
See? I'm friends with a celebrity.
Gosh, you weren't kidding?
I can't believe you guys are friends.
Then I should introduce myself.
Hello... No, wait.
Let me sanitize my hands first.
Hello, I'm Choi Dae-hyun,
the manager of this store.
-Will you excuse us?
-I'll excuse my...
-Hey.
-If you stay, he'll feel uncomfortable.
-It's uncomfortable, isn't it?
-No way.
-No, he's fine.
-Just a little.
See? He feels uncomfortable.
-I guess you felt uncomfortable.
-Give us some space.
My gosh, you really are handsome.
Ji-wook, we're going to have
a team dinner later on.
You should come if you have time.
-He can't. He's a busy guy.
-I'm not busy.
He said he's not busy. You should come.
-We're having tripe.
-Tripe. Got it.
Gosh, you're making him
feel uncomfortable.
My gosh.
Yeon-joo, you know how Kang Ji-wook
models for our private label product?
He's at my convenience store right now.
Yes, he's even going to join
our team dinner later.
So why don't you come
to our team dinner as well?
Then you can meet Kang Ji-wook
and have tripe with us.
I'm also having a team dinner right now.
Remember when my car broke down
and you came running for me?
I managed to sign a huge deal
with the client I met that day.
Oh, really?
That's great. Congratulations, Yeon-joo.
It's all because you came
and helped me that day.
Have fun at your team dinner
and call me later.
Okay, bye.
[Coffee]
Saet-byul, what did you mean
by what you said last time?
-What?
-You said you used to have a dad.
Three years ago, my dad passed away.
What? What happened?
A car accident.
-Where is his grave?
-At the memorial park.
Who are you living with?
I live with my little sister.
I see.
What's with that look?
Hey, don't give me that look, Puppy.
Sorry.
I shouldn't call you Puppy anymore.
Right, Mr. Kang Ji-wook?
Just be yourself.
Saet-byul, it's time for your team dinner.
-Hey, you're here. Let's go.
-Hello.
-Who is he?
-My friend.
Let's go. Thank you.
Bye.
You're not allowed to date
in our convenience store.
Enjoy the tripe. I love tripe too.
-Hello.
-Hello. Here you go.
-Sir.
-What?
-What are you doing here?
-My friend...
That's not important.
How is "Her Reggae Boy" doing?
I bet people love it.
The editor-in-chief and I
drank so much today because of that.
-Does he like it?
-He cussed all night
saying it rarely gets any views.
You think it's funny?
Why don't just draw
what you're supposed to draw?
It's supposed to be erotic, not romantic.
You see, deep down inside,
I'm a very romantic guy.
You draw for an adult webtoon website.
It needs to be erotic to get many views.
Be better with erotica
if you want a chance to draw romance.
Come on. You're not a virgin.
I'm sure you've dated a lot of women.
You're not a virgin, right?
I am a virgin.
Oh, really?
Then there will come a day
when you're no longer a virgin.
Think about that day
and make things more erotic.
More erotic?
Make it more steamy.
Sir, wait.
You need to pay...
That jerk.
-Cheers!
Great job, Saet-byul!
-Thank you.
-Great job, Saet-byul.
Welcome to you too.
-Cheers!
-It's so nice to meet you.
Mr. Choi, don't you have
anything to say to me?
You know, the more I think about it...
My gosh, this is unbelievable.
It's very surprising.
-Right? I'm full of surprises, aren't I?
-No, not you.
The fact that you're friends with him
is really hard to believe.
-Ji-wook...
-Don't cross the line.
What are you saying?
I was right here.
You were the one who crossed the line.
-Gosh, forget it.
-Whatever.
I'm only letting you off the hook
because we're having a team dinner.
Sure. Whatever.
Ji-wook.
-You model for a hangover cure, right?
-Yes.
My girlfriend is the team manager
of the PR Team at that company.
By any chance,
are you talking about Ms. Yoo Yeon-joo?
Yes, how did you know? That's her.
-She's my girlfriend.
-Hey.
Don't talk to him.
Let's all take a photo.
Everybody, look over here.
In 1, 2, 3.
-There.
-Great.
My gosh, the photo came out great.
My goodness, you look so handsome
in this photo.
[Only Ji-wook shines at this team dinner.]
When are we going to get that photo
for the interview?
He said he'll send me a photo
before he uploads the article.
I see.
That must be it.
Speak of the devil.
-Let me see.
-Let's see.
Let's see.
[She's not just a part-timer to us.]
[She's like our lucky charm.]
Why did he cut us out?
-What...
-What's wrong with the photo?
What's this?
Gosh, this isn't what we asked for!
-Darn it.
-What about the rest of us?
-Gosh, what is this?
-Hello?
I'm the manager of the convenience store
who did the interview earlier.
Why did you crop out the rest of my family
and just leave the two of us in the photo?
[First of all, congratulations.]
[Your photo will be on our website for PR
starting from this month.]
[-It'll also be on social media.]
-"Social media"?
[-I'm getting a call right now.]
-You never told us that.
[-I'll call you back.]
-Hello?
Hello? Sir?
He just hung up.
My gosh.
My gosh, why won't she pick up?
[Dae-hyun]
Thanks to all of you,
I'm really happy today.
Cheers to all of you!
-Cheers!
-Congratulations!
This is great.
Gosh, this tastes great.
-Sir, let me pour you a glass.
-Okay.
Director Cho,
aren't you drinking a bit too much today?
We're here to celebrate,
so I should be drinking.
I hope we get to celebrate more often.
Sir, you're amazing.
What? This is Choi Dae-hyun.
Hey, hurry up and search
our company name online.
Hurry up, you guys.
Yeon-joo, you don't need to bother.
I'll show you. Here.
[She's not just a part-timer to us.]
I can't believe Dae-hyun did this.
[She's like our lucky charm.]
Look at him carrying the part-timer.
They're so close together.
Sir, look at this.
Isn't this unbelievable?
My gosh, how did he think
of doing something like this?
Does he not care that you might see this?
Look at it again.
[One free bottle of soju
for customers who come before 6 p.m.]
Hey, Seong-tae.
What? Everyone at the team dinner saw it?
I like it here.
-Okay, I'll be right there.
-Hey, give more beer here.
Mr. Choi, where are you going?
The team dinner isn't over yet.
I need to go somewhere for a moment.
-His style is different from ours.
-What do you know about fashion?
What...
What was that?
Saet-byul, are you okay?
What? Yes, I'm okay.
What about you? Do you feel uncomfortable?
No, I'm okay.
Hey, why didn't you
pick up your phone earlier?
I almost beat you to a pulp.
Do you know that?
Ji-wook.
Sir.
Come here.
What are you doing here?
How did you find me?
You're all over the social media.
[Only Ji-wook shines at this team dinner.]
You promised not to do this. Let's go.
Let me spend more time with my friend.
Ji-wook.
I think we're going to go home soon.
I'll go after we're done. You should go.
Saet-byul, I'm sorry.
I'll call you next time. I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
Bye.
-My gosh! I can't talk to you!
-What do you mean?
Then are you not going to
talk to me at all?
-Seong-tae.
-Hey, Dae-hyun.
Hey, what happened?
Where's Yeon-joo? Her phone's turned off.
She left with the director.
I bet they went to drink some more.
Oh, really? Thanks.
Bye.
[I'm back at the store.
I'm starting my shift.]
I'm just asking you to keep up
the good work.
You know, just work.
Oh, right. Gosh, let's just delete it.
[I'm back at the store.
I'm starting my shift.]
[This message was deleted.]
[It was for someone else.]
You must have had a fun dinner.
Thanks for helping.
[Expired]
I can only afford to eat jelly.
Didn't you eat?
Don't even ask. I starved all day.
I had no energy to take down the parasol,
so you can do it yourself.
See you. Thanks.
Seung-joon, do me a favor.
Give me a piggyback ride.
-What?
-Give me a piggyback ride.
Do it for me just this cone.
There we go.
During my entire life,
no one has ever given me a piggyback ride.
Not even when I was young
because my mom thought
it would make my legs bend outward.
Seung-joon, you're the first person
to give me a piggyback ride.
Go back to where we started. Come on.
There you go.
Good job.
I guess this is how it feels
to get a piggyback ride.
I also got myself a piggyback ride.
Is this why you wanted to get off here?
Yeon-joo?
Gosh, how did you know I was here?
-Let's go inside.
-Okay. Hey, come on.
Yeon-joo, why did you drink so much?
Professor Kim,
should I give you a piggyback ride?
My goodness, Yeon-joo. Hey, what's wrong?
Mom, why didn't you give me
a piggyback ride when I was young?
What?
Seung-joon was the first person
to give me a piggyback ride today.
My gosh, I barely got to find out
what it feels like
to get a piggyback ride today.
My gosh, Choi Dae-hyun!
Why do you keep
giving her piggyback rides?
Why did you have to give her
a piggyback ride again?
You mean jerk.
He should've started
a convenience store from the start
instead of working at the headquarters.
What is she saying, Seung-joon?
"Choi Dae-hyun"?
Is that whom she's seeing?
I think you should ask her instead.
[She's not just a part-timer to us.]
[She's like our lucky charm.]
Darn you!
[Backstreet Rookie]
[-Nurse, prepare for surgery.
-Yes, Doctor.]
Gosh, no.
-Did you dream of something?
-Yes, a dream.
Who's at the convenience store?
-Saet-byul!
[He was the one who started it.
Everyone knows that.]
Yeon-joo. Can you spare me some time?
Sorry. I already have plans.
Do you make deliveries?
No, this isn't a supermarket.
[How much do I need to buy?]
[Jjajang Time]
Hello, ma'am.
[Saet-byul, I think you...]
I'm here to see you, Saet-byul.