[English subtitles are available.]
[Ji Chang-wook]
[Kim You-jung]
[Backstreet Rookie]
Hello?
What do I do?
Goodness.
Is he okay?
I got it!
He's out.
Are you okay?
Can you take care of this kitten?
-I'm running late.
-Okay.
I'm almost there. I'm sorry.
I can see you!
I'm so late!
-Saet-byul!
-Jung Saet-byul!
She's here.
Hey, Wonder Woman.
Hey.
You brats.
My friend!
Hey, you. Bring me some water.
Hey!
I'm out of breath because I ran,
but I'm also all warmed up now.
That means that you're screwed.
-You're scared, aren't you?
-Aren't you?
This is getting fun.
You know what China pink symbolizes?
Whoever gets this right,
I'll let you off the hook.
-Disrespect?
-Wrong.
-Facebook?
Stop guessing.
Don't embarrass me.
We easily outnumber them.
Girls, form the crane formation.
[Crane formation]
What's a crane formation?
It's a type of formation, you idiot.
A formula? I knew that.
Five, four,
-three, two,
-They're all here.
-That's right. You're exempt.
-Nice.
[China pink symbolizes rejection.]
Hey. Attack!
Girls, don't get scared. They're nothing.
Focus!
-Take this!
-My gosh!
Hey!
Okay, stop. Let's end it here.
I won't ask you to join our crew anymore.
It's improper for women
to beat each other up.
Let's talk.
I get it, you're good at fights.
No, a real woman speaks with her fist.
You're so cool.
Saet-byul, I really learned
my lesson today.
I'm the prettiest girl,
and you're the strongest girl!
-Are you kidding me?
-I'm serious.
Did you see those girls back there?
Did you see those stubby legs?
So short!
-And what's with the crane formation?
-What was that?
-What's that supposed to be?
-A formula!
What? Do you know this person?
He's so handsome.
He looks like a celebrity.
Shut it. I'm looking at the flowers.
Your gaze is definitely not going
to the flowers.
-You're definitely looking at the guy!
-Come on.
It'd be so nice to get flower bouquets
like those.
I bet women love money bouquets more.
I love flowers more. I want to open
a flower shop and live an elegant life.
Call me Florist Jung.
-Nonsense.
-Then I'll become a money-ist.
Can you not smell anything?
-I can smell it a little.
-Right?
-Dae-hyun,
-Yes?
did you really have to be like this
on a day like today?
What was it today, a puppy?
Or did you fix a swallow's leg?
How did you know? It was a kitten.
A kitten?
It fell in the sewer.
You're a great guy. You're great,
but you're not for me.
No, I think we're a great fit.
No, that's what you think.
What I think?
I should return your baby to you, right?
Hold on.
I wish the best for you. Goodbye.
Jung-eun,
don't leave.
As if.
-Hand me one.
-Okay.
I'm feeling a menthol cigarette today.
Right? Hey, do you have
a menthol cigarette?
I did yesterday.
Darn you. How could you smoke it alone?
-What is he doing?
-What's that?
You look like you're laughing at me.
You're a great guy.
You're great, but you're not for me.
If a great guy isn't for you,
then would a bad guy be for you?
Is that what it is?
Is he drunk?
Goodbye.
He's so handsome.
Such pathetic souls.
Well, I guess
I'm the most pathetic one here.
You know, handsome guys like him are
surprisingly innocent and easy to control.
What am I supposed to do? Just leave?
Should I go around?
I can totally smell the dumb guy smell
from him.
-Ready or not, rock, paper, scissors!
-Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes! Perfect.
Excuse me,
could you spare me a moment?
Could you get us three packs of
Soboro Menthol from the convenience store?
-Please?
Kids,
are you crazy?
Such nonsense.
You look like a kind man.
I'm not a good man.
Handsome man, please.
Hey! You little brats.
You think I'm joking?
You think this is a joke?
How dare you ask me to buy cigarette
for you?
Just once, please.
Just once.
Try to quit if you can.
It's bad for your bones.
-What is this?
-My goodness!
-What's this?
-What's with that man?
Kids, you can smoke
when you're all grown up.
Try to put your youth to good use.
Understood?
Stop there.
Stop, my foot. What?
Thanks for worrying about me.
You're the first one who ever told me
to quit smoking.
What's your number? 010...
-736-5186.
-736...
No, wait. That's not my number.
Why are you asking?
You told me to put my youth to good use.
-Okay, then.
-Don't save the number.
What are you doing?
-Hey,
-What?
-be careful.
-Of what?
What is it?
I don't know
what I'm going to do to you.
What do you mean by that?
I'm just kidding. You're hilarious.
Are you scared?
No, not at all.
I'll call you at night,
so don't block my number.
I'm very busy, so bye.
[Backstreet Rookie]
[Three years later]
Welcome!
That'll be ten dollars.
Would you like a bag?
No, we're good.
A photo? Would you like a photo?
-Yes!
-Then
can I take it with these?
These are on promotion right now.
Of course! Can I upload it
on my social media?
Yes, that'd be great.
I'll make sure to promote them a lot
on social media!
Give me a moment.
-Make sure that the products show.
-One, two, three.
-Thank you.
Goodbye!
[With the handsome
convenience store owner]
Us, too!
We're just buying this pack of gum,
but will you still take a photo with us?
-Please!
Of course I will.
I'm taking it now.
-One, two, three.
-Two, three.
-Thank you.
-Thank you!
-Come back again.
-Thank you.
-Sir,
-Yes?
you're incredibly handsome.
I'll be back again.
-Thank you!
-Don't forget about me!
I'm so sorry.
-Study hard. Cheers!
-Will do!
-Good luck!
-Cheers!
-Dae-hyun,
-Yes, Dad?
-is that all they bought?
-What do you mean?
Kids like them share their photos
all over social media,
which is a good way to promote our store.
Right.
We can pay for our electricity
because of your teenage fans.
That's true.
Do you still feel unwell?
Watching the store all night is
no easy work.
Getting back to work is a lot for me.
Hey, hire a part-timer.
Then I wouldn't be in so much pain.
Dad! Hold on.
Are you okay? What's wrong?
Dad, Dad.
It's acute gastritis caused by stress,
and we're using MPO
with hydration treatment
to make him feel better.
Doctor, I have no idea what you just said.
Please make it easy for us to understand.
He's experiencing indigestion.
My gosh. Indigestion?
You were just fine being at home all day,
and you just get sick like this
as soon as you start working?
-I'll be going now.
-Okay, Doctor.
-Dae-hyun.
-Yes?
Did you close the store?
The headquarters might give us
another warning if we do!
I'll watch the store. You come back
with your father later.
-You can work tomorrow morning.
-Darn you.
Prick your thumb
if you're experiencing indigestion.
-Mom, calm down!
-You'll be fine in minutes.
-What nonsense.
-Dad.
You brats!
-What was that?
-What did she say?
Who does she think she is?
You.
Fine.
Fine. Let's have at it. Let's do this.
You said a real woman speaks
with her fist.
Do you know what wild roses symbolize?
Why is she asking me about such nonsense?
What is it?
Do wild roses stab you in the heart
or make you cry your eyes out?
What does it symbolize?
Ask the Grim Reaper.
You'll be the one meeting the Grim Reaper.
[Wild rose symbolizes
the love between sisters.]
Dad, make sure
you regularly take your medicine.
-Okay. Why does it hurt so much?
-Goodness.
You startled me!
You got caught red-handed.
Where did you go this morning?
Why didn't you invite me?
-What is it? You don't have side dishes?
-Gosh.
Put the food on the table.
Or I'll call the cops.
Cops? Go ahead.
I'll report to the police how you didn't
pay me back for my investment.
I told you I'd pay you
at the end of the month!
Dad, what happened to your arm?
Did you hurt your arm?
You can't be sick for my sake.
You're the only one looking out for me.
I'm all right now.
Are you sure? You're sure you're okay?
Of course. Don't you know who I am?
I, Choi Yong-pil,
am a real man from Busan.
Look at you overreacting. You're okay.
But you still gave me a scare!
That hurts!
I thought you wouldn't be able
to make kimchi.
What? Kimchi?
Dad, hurry and make kimchi.
Your son-in-law is making a fuss
because he wants to eat fresh kimchi.
-Dad, use Korean chili pepper powder.
-Dae-soon.
Hey, put them all back.
Don't take all of the seasoned seaweed!
You thief!
Dae-hyun.
Dad, get some rest.
I'll go and take over the store for Mom.
I'm sorry.
You didn't get any sleep because of me.
No, it's okay. Rest up.
-Bye.
-He's handsome.
-Look at him.
[7:30 a.m.]
Mom.
Excuse me. Mom.
-Hey, you.
-Wake up. You need to go to work.
-What time is it?
-It's 7:30 a.m.
7:30 a.m.? My gosh, my back hurts.
-Gosh. Did you sell a lot?
-My back aches.
I only had one customer.
One customer?
The customer wanted a refund.
I didn't know how to do it,
so I put the stockings up there.
This? Wait, I taught you
how to do it before.
-How to register refunds.
-When did you teach me that? Bye.
Seriously. I taught you at least 10 times.
[4:20 p.m.]
How's the business going?
-Business is bad all around.
-Is that so?
Well, it's the same for everyone.
My gosh, the school is out.
Hello, welcome.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Your classes ended early today.
Sir, which snack has
the buy-1-get-1-free deal?
The chocolate sticks have the deal.
-I want chocolate sticks.
-Chocolate sticks.
What do I do?
[1 a.m.]
[Expired]
Why are there so many?
[Sales for Dae-hyun's convenience store,
Average sales in Jongno-gu]
My gosh. The sales are awful.
[8 a.m.]
Look at him. Hey, wake up!
Wake up now. Hey, wake up.
Goodness. Customers might walk in.
Hey, wake up.
[He's been working by himself
without a break for 24 hours.]
-Wake up.
-Take over now, Mom.
[He's been working by himself
without a break for 24 hours.]
What are you talking about?
I brought you underwear.
-Why? Why did you bring this?
-I'm going to Busan.
Why would you go there?
My cousin wants to buy
an insurance policy.
Of course, I must go.
I'm ranked last in sales this month.
Mom. I've been working
for two days without a break.
Get a part-timer.
What part-timer? We're about to starve
because we're not making any money.
How many customers were there?
-One?
As for the refunded stockings,
I bought them in the right color.
But the customer's gone anyway.
I'm leaving.
Why are you leaving?
Mom. This is Dad's!
That looks sexy too. Put that on.
Why do I need to look sexy here?
This doesn't look sexy at all!
[2 p.m.]
-Hello!
-Hi.
It's buy 1 get 1 free.
It's 2 dollars, right?
-Here.
-My gosh. Look at him.
Can you take a photo with us?
-Sure. The promotional event.
-Let's take a photo.
-That's for the event.
-Okay.
In 1, 2, 3.
-Thank you. We'll be back.
-Thank you.
In 1, 2, 3.
Gosh, I have to hire a part-timer.
[Part-timer Wanted]
[8 p.m.]
[He's been working by himself
without a break for 36 hours.]
Who are you?
I mean, welcome. How can I help you?
I'm here for the interview
for the part-time job.
Part-time job? What part-time job?
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
Can you sit here for a bit?
Let me bring a drink for you.
[I'm getting the chills.]
[It feels like a dagger pierced
through my heart.]
Could you get us three packs of
Soboro Menthol from the convenience store?
She's...
I'm good.
[Choi Dae-hyun]
[You're good? I don't feel good at all.]
What do you mean?
I already have a drink.
I see. It's a drink.
[Resume]
[Name: Jung Saet-byul]
[She doesn't seem to remember me.]
[What a relief.
I should send her back quickly.]
-The position is for the graveyard shift.
-I'm a night owl.
-But a woman to run the store alone--
-I'm good at fights.
-You live far.
-I don't need to go home.
Darn it. I slipped.
That's a mistake?
[Given the way she talks]
[and the Band-Aid on her face
which is a symbol of violence,]
[I won't hire her for the job.]
[She's out. She failed. It's over for her.
She's out.]
Out.
Sir, you look very exhausted.
Try some of this.
This herbal tea helps you
recover from fatigue.
What is it? Do you think I gave you
undrinkable tea?
Well, it smells quite fragrant.
It tastes better than it smells.
I see.
Can I use your restroom?
The key is over there.
You can go around the building.
Okay. Have your tea.
Something is definitely fishy.
[Spicy Ramyeon]
-Sir.
-Yes?
Why are you up? Go back to sleep.
It's all right.
What are you eating?
What are you doing here?
This? I don't know.
Your part-timer made this for me.
It's amazing.
You picked a good one.
What?
What's happening?
My gosh. Wait.
-Hey.
-Enjoy it.
-What's this?
-Thank you.
Wait. What's going on?
Sir, I can start tomorrow, right?
Wait. You know,
I have another interview tomorrow.
I'll call you later.
-Oh, no. I feel awful.
-What's going on?
Why are you crying?
[Backstreet Rookie]
Wait. You know,
I have another interview tomorrow.
I'll call you later.
-Oh, no. I feel awful.
-What's going on?
Why are you crying?
The interviewee won't have
any shot at getting the job.
I'll end up getting the job.
[I should have fired this time bomb then.]
-Hello.
-This is Jung Saet-byul.
She's the new part-timer
for the graveyard shift?
She's a temp. She's like an intern.
She's not a regular employee.
My name is Jung Saet-byul.
I hope you can teach me a lot.
You're pretty just like your pretty name.
So was it Jeung Saet-byul?
Mom, it's Jung Saet-byul.
Exactly. That's what I said. Gosh.
Mom, it's not Jeung Saet-byul.
It's Jung Saet-byul.
That's what I said.
Goodness, you're gorgeous.
Wait, you're not his older sister?
You're really his mother?
I thought you guys were siblings.
I get that often.
People think I'm his sister.
[-What's her deal?]
-Really?
[She already knows how to flatter people.
She's only 22.]
But there's no temp or intern
for positions at convenience stores.
No. You don't know about this industry.
You're on probation for three months.
Depending on your performance,
you either get fired
or become a regular employee.
What do I need to do
to become a regular employee?
Well, it's pretty simple.
Increasing sales, good customer service,
your attitude,
cleaning, getting regulars,
facing up products,
organizing the storage, no tabs,
and throwing out expired food.
If you don't meet any
of these requirements, you'll be fired.
You get it, right?
That's really simple.
I'm done with this.
Let's see.
First, I'll show you
how to work the cash register, POS.
POS stands for point of sales.
So P, O...
You can't just do that.
Have you worked at a convenience store?
Yes, briefly.
Briefly? You know
all the cigarette brands, right?
No.
Why not? You're a smoker.
I don't smoke.
Hey, you...
Hey.
[Do you think I'll fall for your lies?]
[You asked me to get cigarettes
three years ago.]
Why are you staring at me?
No, it's nothing.
Convenience stores sell
over 2,000 different products.
And cigarettes are the only ones
customers don't have access to.
Do you understand what that means?
So is this what I do?
Why are you grabbing my hand?
What are you up to?
My gosh, you're no fun.
I was just playing.
We just met. Why would you do that?
Is this a joke to you?
Anyway, look at the shelf
and memorize every single one.
I'll go stock up the drinks. Got that?
-Yes.
-Memorize all of them.
Who does she think she is?
Sir, I'll be back later.
She's leaving already?
Hey, where are you going?
Did you memorize all of them?
-Mr. Choi.
-What?
-Aren't you going to take that down?
-What? This?
Of course, I should take it down
when I officially get a part-timer.
You will take it down soon.
-I'll be back tonight.
-Okay.
Hey, the bills are about to fall
from your back pocket.
If they do, I'll keep them.
That's a slick ride.
My goodness. Something is fishy.
Something feels off.
What a surprise. You're already up.
I'm going to a part-time job.
-Bye.
-I cooked.
Make sure you eat that
and put it in the fridge.
Okay. Have fun at work.
Sir, wait. I'm right here.
Hey, where were you?
-I had to make a delivery.
-I see.
There we go.
Okay then. What can I get for you, sir?
-Here's what I need.
-Yes, what is it?
-Here.
-Okay, let me see.
-Can you exchange this money for me?
-What...
-Oh, okay. Do you want one-dollar bills?
-Yes, ten of them.
Okay, ten one-dollar bills.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
No problem. Bye.
My goodness.
What the... What?
[I'm sure I counted the cash
and put it in the machine.]
No one paid in cash after that.
And even if someone did pay in cash,
it still shouldn't be empty.
Where did it go? What happened?
Hey, the bills are about to fall
from your back pocket.
No... No way.
Jung Saet-byul, that little...
I'm going to kill her.
What? Why... Why can't I see anything??
Wait a minute. Is this... What...
Doing this won't help me see better.
[The phone is turned off.
You will be directed to voicemail.]
Gosh, why... Why is her phone turned off?
What is it? Do you think I gave you
undrinkable tea?
Gosh, she totally got me.
I can't believe this.
Jung Saet-byul, that horrible brat.
Wait a minute.
[Cash stolen
by convenience store part-timer]
[My life revolves around
convenience stores.]
[Hello, I'm the Convenience Store Guru,
a guy whose life]
[revolves around convenience stores.]
[All About Convenience Stores]
[I've been working
at a convenience store for 15 years,]
[and I'm going to tell you
about how my part-timer]
[stole cash from the store last week.]
[Part-timer burglary case]
[Listen to me, J!]
[You showed up out of nowhere
saying you want to work part-time!]
["J" aged 22]
[-How dare you turn off your phone]
-"J"?
[-and tell me the wrong address?]
-Wait a minute. "J"?
[-If you run a convenience store,]
-Jung Saet-byul.
[make sure you check the address
if a part-timer seems suspicious.]
[Make sure to check their addresses.]
[If it turns out to be wrong,
it's a scam.]
[-This is all for today.]
-Her address. Wait a minute.
Jung Saet-byul, you're dead.
Wait. What if she's not alone?
[No credit. Cash only.]
Did you come to die?
Sorry.
My body still remembers how to fight.
Come on out.
-Oh, my gosh!
-Are you here to pay money for sex?
-No wait. What in the world...
-Hey, stop.
You're under arrest.
-For what?
-You can hire a lawyer,
-and you'll get a chance to explain.
-About what?
-Did you make a reservation for 7:00 p.m.?
-No.
You came just in time.
No, that's not it.
I'm just here to find Saet-byul.
I have tons of names.
Pink, Cherry, Tsubasa, and Mika.
They call me whatever they want.
I guess he likes Saet-byul.
What are you talking about?
The part-timer at my convenience store
is Saet-byul!
Will you please let me go?
Stay still, sir.
No, wait. Officer.
Please look inside my pocket.
-Here?
-Yes.
Gosh, you put it in so deep.
Take a look. I'm telling the truth.
This is the address,
and her name is Saet-byul.
[Standard labor contract]
[Jung Saet-byul]
What did I tell you?
She's our new part-timer.
And she ran off with 500 dollars
while I went to receive training.
I called, but her phone was turned off,
so I thought I'd go to her house.
But what is this place?
-Does it hurt?
-It hurt a lot.
Hello?
Mom, are you at the convenience store?
What? No, I'm home.
Saet-byul came and took over.
What? Saet-byul is back?
Yes, she came early
to organize the cigarettes.
What? "Organize the cigarettes"?
What do you think is the first thing
part-timers steal? It's money.
[All About Convenience Stores]
[No.1 Cash]
And the second thing on the list
is cigarette. Do you know why?
[No.2 Cigarette]
Because they're expensive and light.
They're easy to sell.
[The ones over here]
[Costs about 10,000 dollars]
No. No way. My gosh.
Thank you.
What... What is this? Why is it locked?
No! My cigarettes!
My gosh, I can't believe this.
Dad! Dad, do you have
the convenience store key at home?
Yes, I need it right now!
Dad!
-Dad!
-Hey! Dae-hyun!
Over here! Give me the key!
Here.
-Give me that.
-Is there something wrong?
-Later. I'll tell you later.
-What is it?
Mr. Choi, you're here.
Hey! Get over here!
-Did you...
-I organized everything.
I found 1 pack of Camel Blue
and 2 packs of Essence Soo.
That's three packs in total.
I'm good, right?
-What in the world...
-Didn't I do a great job?
Hey, what... How...
What's wrong?
Why did you leave it open?
It'll get dusty inside.
-This isn't a rice cooker.
-It's similar.
But what brings you here at this hour?
What? Well, I just came.
By any chance, are you here because...
Because what?
Did you run over here
because you missed me?
I guess you ran because you missed me.
Gosh, you fall for people so easily.
[Fall for People Easily]
I can't believe this.
[FFPE]
There must be
something wrong with your head.
The ER is open 24 hours a day
just like our convenience store.
My dad just got discharged,
so they'll have an empty bed.
I bet it's hard for her
to keep that smile on her face.
Her plan got ruined because I showed up.
My gosh, look at this.
Dae-hyun, here's your tip!
I don't even want to think about it.
Thank goodness I got here on time.
Hey, you're the convenience store owner
I met earlier, right?
-So I guess this is yours.
-Yes.
What happened to the part-timer?
Was her name Saet-byul?
-The thing is--
-Do you know me?
-It's nothing.
-Are you Saet-byul?
-No, it's not her.
-Yes, what's up?
No, it's nothing.
-He said you stole 500 dollars.
-No, no.
-No, don't.
-But the address was wrong...
What? You came to my house?
-No...
-Why was the address wrong?
We were on a stakeout in Unit 1000.
I live in Unit 1006.
-She lives in Unit 1006.
-Show me what you had earlier.
-What?
-The employment contract.
-Why would I have that?
-It's in your back pocket.
No, it's not. Hey, don't touch me.
Look. It's Unit 1006.
Gosh, it's hard to tell
if the last number is a 0 or a 6.
Yes, you're right.
So did she steal your money or not?
My gosh.
Saet-byul, it's not what you think.
No, wait.
Saet-byul. Hey.
Hey, stop. Saet-byul, wait.
Your mother took the money
because she urgently needed it.
Then you could've at least told me.
Your mother told me
she'll speak to you herself.
And I don't interfere
in other people's family issues.
This isn't a family issue.
If you had told me, there wouldn't
have been a misunderstanding.
You're just like the others.
-What do you mean?
-You jumped to conclusions
without even bothering to ask me.
It's okay. I'm used to it.
Saet-byul, wait.
Don't follow me if you don't want to die.
You did well, Dae-hyun.
♫ I prefer the clown that's smiling ♫
[Score: 100,
Don't be too surprised.]
Nice!
You guys, aren't I so good?
Don't you think I should become a singer?
Of course. Your voice is so nice.
I'll treat you guys to some drinks
since I got a perfect score!
-What do you want?
-Cider!
Sir, can we get some cider in Room 19?
-Eun-byul.
-Yes?
Get a perfect score on your grades.
Aren't you a senior?
We're done now,
so I was just about to go study.
Come with me.
You're not hanging around
with a bunch of bullies, are you?
What do you take me for?
People easily get suspicious
of people like us
even if we don't do anything much.
Eun-byul.
Who do you think will be sad
if people start being suspicious of us?
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
Let's go.
Saet-byul.
Jung Saet-byul.
Is she not home?
Saet-byul.
Today, let's pitch camp here.
This place is known to be
pretty difficult.
Don't you know me?
I always stick by my word.
Okay.
Then I got your back.
[Manse, Hangover Cure]
You won a beer cocktail!
-Drink up, sir!
Here you go.
-It works wonders.
-Thank you.
Here.
-Can we have some too?
-Give us some.
Sure. Try it out.
If you like it, you can get it
at the convenience store.
-This is nice.
-Over here!
-I'll go there next.
-Come here.
Here you go.
-Bottoms up!
[Manse, Hangover Cure]
We did great today!
Saet-byul,
you really are the queen of sales.
Let's eat dinner.
I'll treat you to something nice.
I need to go to a part-time job.
I'll buy you beef.
"Beef"?
[My name is Han Dal-sik.]
[My dream is to become
the best webtoon writer in Korea.]
[Although I dream of getting incentives,]
[I can barely even afford to pay rent.]
[I dream of writing about romance,]
[but I find myself writing erotica.]
Go ahead and live.
It itches so much.
It's been like this for months.
[Therefore, just like any other day,
I sit down and draw]
[naked bodies.]
[Pen name: Fire Volcano]
The pain...
...of creativity.
The pain of creativity
is this very moment where we become one.
The moment we intersect.
That is when we become one.
The writer needs to get turned on
in order to produce horny illustrations.
99.8.
99.9.
100!
["Her Reggae Boy" Episode 38]
["Her Reggae Boy" Episode 38,
Uploading]
My work is done.
["Her Reggae Boy" Episode 38,
Uploaded Successfully]
Dae-hyun.
What's with you? How do you always show up
whenever I'm eating?
Hey, I don't show up
whenever you're eating.
You're eating every time I show up.
Same thing.
You even added a sausage.
-How was your day?
-Don't even ask.
I almost ended my life
while you were busy working.
Why? What happened?
Listen to me.
You know how...
The part-timer came here and...
So she did this...
-Then she just left...
-She came and then...
That's what happened.
So you mistook
your part-timer for a thief.
But she found out, got angry, and left?
-Yes.
-You're a real...
A real human.
Anyone could've thought that.
-I understand.
-Right?
She was like that
even when she was young. I know her.
My hunch as a writer tells me
that she won't come back.
-What was her name again?
-Saet-byul.
If Saet-byul comes back, I'll hang my--
Hey, Saet-byul.
What time is it?
Do you not keep track of the time?
You're here a minute early.
I didn't want to be irresponsible,
so I even gave up on eating beef.
He's my friend.
Get out of here.
Hey, Saet-byul.
This is a beef lunchbox. Do you want one?
Gosh, beef.
There... There's a lot of beef inside.
-Is that Saet-byul?
-Yes.
Go hang yourself, you punk.
Get out of here.
[Warm Beverages]
Are you keeping an eye on me
because you don't know what I might steal?
Saet-byul, what's wrong with you?
Let me make myself clear.
Listen.
Do you or do you not know
that I'm a pro at cleaning microwaves?
I clean them spotlessly.
Look at this. Watch carefully.
Gosh, look at this.
It gets really dirty like this.
-Shoot!
-"Shoot"?
Come on! Shoot!
Nice!
Shoot.
I'm not doing this because I'm sorry.
I'm doing this because I'm good.
It just shows that I really love coffee.
I'm good at this.
The coffee will taste amazing today
because I cleaned the coffee machine.
Get ready to get tons of customers.
The AC filter seemed really dirty.
Saet-byul!
Okay, fine. I was suspicious of you.
How could I not be suspicious
after I noticed that the cash went missing
on your first day?
It's partly your fault.
Why did you turn off your phone?
It ran out of battery.
Then what about the address?
I don't write neatly.
Who writes six like a zero?
I do.
Good for you.
Shouldn't you apologize
instead of getting angry at me?
I'm sorry.
That was pretty quick.
I tend to put things into action
very quickly.
You want me to stop
giving you the silent treatment?
Of course.
Okay, then I'll let it go
if you organize the storage room
and fill up the refrigerators
with all the beverages. Deal?
Saet-byul, are you kidding me?
I love doing that. I'll do it.
Do you want me to help?
-No.
-Why not?
[GS Retail]
Yeon-joo!
Dae-hyun.
Hello.
You should've called.
What if we didn't cross paths?
Then I would've waited
until you passed by.
Yeon-joo, let's have lunch together.
I'm starving.
-"Lunch"?
-Yes.
Ms. Yoo, we'll be waiting for you there.
Enjoy your lunch. Bye.
I'm sorry. I have a lunch meeting.
It's okay. I'm fine.
You should go to the meeting.
The fact that I got to see you
is already enough for me.
But I think I'll have time tonight.
"Tonight"?
Why don't we meet tonight
at Kosirado Hotel?
A hotel?
See you later.
Oh, my gosh.
Hey, Saet-byul. You have no idea
how much I waited for you to come. Hurry.
Mr. Choi.
Mr. Choi, did you put on perfume
to impress me?
I love this scent.
-No.
-Don't lie to me.
I promise. My girlfriend got this for me.
She told me to wear it on our date.
I sprayed it on my wrists and my neck.
You have a girlfriend?
Of course I have a girlfriend.
But why do you sound so angry about it?
Don't tell me... My gosh, are you jealous?
No, I just feel bad for your girlfriend.
Why do you feel bad for her?
Because you'll have to see me
every day now.
And in the end, you'll fall for me
and get sick of your girlfriend.
Don't forget to tell her
that I'm sorry in advance.
My gosh,
you have a really serious condition.
Aren't you a bit too young
to have dementia?
Saet-byul, get to your senses.
You can do this.
Stay focused and work hard, okay?
I'll see you then.
-Bye.
-Okay. Just know that I'm watching you.
[That day,
I shouldn't have told Saet-byul]
[about Yeon-joo.]
[Yeon-joo, I'll show you]
[what kind man I am today.]
This is where you wanted
to have fun with me tonight?
Yes, it's open 24 hours.
So this is what you wanted to do
to get covered in sweat?
-You wanted to work out.
-That's right.
What's going on? What were you imagining?
-Dae-hyun.
-Yes?
-Get to your senses.
-Okay.
You seemed really tired
when I saw you earlier.
You can't do anything without stamina.
You even hired a nighttime part-timer.
You should get some good sleep at night
and work out from time to time.
Let's warm up before we start working out.
-Are you okay?
-Of course, Yeon-joo.
[Can I go to the bathroom?]
[Why are you asking me? Just go.]
[Because I don't want you
to get suspicious.]
[I won't ask you anymore
if you promise not to get suspicious.]
[What are you doing, Mr. Choi?
I'm working.]
[Are you ignoring me because you're busy?
Why are you busy?]
[A customer just bought
a pack of cigarettes.]
[He gave me 5 dollars in cash,
so I gave him back 50 cents.]
[Here's a photo to prove it.]
My gosh.
Who are you texting?
The part-timer.
Hey, Dal-sik.
Dae-hyun, do you remember
our field trip in middle school?
It was at Mount Songni.
We had to sleep at a youth hostel,
but we stayed up all night
because people were so loud there.
Yes, but what about that?
I'm experiencing the same thing.
Your part-timer invited her friends
to the convenience store
and are having a darn party
beneath the parasol.
I feel like I'm at a mud festival
at Daecheon Beach.
What?
Saet-byul, why do you keep bringing one?
Beer doesn't taste good when it gets warm.
The manager filled up the fridge,
so don't worry.
Your manager does that?
Then who else would do it? I made him
organize the storage room and clean.
You really are something.
Or do you think
this place has good feng shui?
Should I ask my dad
to just buy this building?
My gosh, let's drink to that.
-Do you have anything with broth?
-Something warm.
Go and get what you want.
This place is your fridge.
Take care of your fridge.
Saet-byul, you brat.
I'm starting to really like you.
Is this what you were talking about?
No, I was talking about the new one.
-Is this it?
-Yes, that's it.
What the...
My gosh, I can't believe that girl.
-What? Wait a minute. They're...
-This is nice.
Try to quit if you can.
I... I remember those girls.
Yes, you got it right.
Are they serious right now? My gosh, okay.
Is she trying to suck me dry?
She's unbelievable.
I'll put an end to you girls today.
You darn parasites.
Let me get you guys some more beer.
Will that be enough?
You should drink some hard liquor
since it's going to be your last supper.
Mr. Choi?