Use sincerity to express
Easy to express
She is a flower that smells of incense
Will it be afraid
She has also asked herself
Zipadia
The one who is passionate
Only thinking
Will melt
Zipadia
The one you love
Love is complicated
Have a smile to answer
The Long Ballad
Episode 16
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Why are you so late, Monkey?
Although I'm late,
look who I brought.
Simple rice noodles?
Sit down.
Hello.
Simple and rice noodles are here too.
Come with us.
Come, sit together.
Come, Simple, sit with us.
Can I sit here?
Yes.
Before the entrance examination,
we have to supervise each other.
No one can be wronged.
Especially you, Monkey.
I know. I know.
I will try my best.
Monkey, my English is not bad.
If you have any questions,
just ask me.
Okay.
Then my English is up to you.
No problem.
I'm coming.
Yuan Sen, you're amazing.
You used the form of comics
to solve the problems.
It's even more...
I think it's easier to see
if you draw it like this.
It's easy to understand.
If you need it,
I have some over there.
I can give it to you.
Oh my god.
Yansi,
you've said so many words.
Are you the Yansi I know?
It's too noisy.
Let's change the place.
Interior innovation
classified new life
Sherry,
I don't think
I can type and answer.
Help me see.
B against a button.
Let me help you.
Okay.
All of you,
you're here.
You're here.
Okay.
I see.
Let's go.
En Tong, what did you want to say?
I wanted to say
I want to drink with you.
Take the bill.
It's open.
Okay.
Why are you standing there?
What color do you want?
Black.
I...
What kind of music do you like to listen to?
Metal music.
Me too.
What kind of movie do you like to watch?
A quiet one.
I like to watch a quiet comic book.
I don't like action movies.
Me too.
Are you still drunk?
So에서XD
I see.
villagers teacher to failing ones
Write this as the ordinary famous
plural of the street
Strawberry
We're going to buy some cupless coffee
The vending machine is there
Foreign?
Foreign math books have
Peter Glass,
Ajimid and Ola.
Which one do you want?
None.
Then, domestic math books have
Huaruo Geng,
Zuchong Zhi, Chen Jingrun.
These math books
have been written too many times.
I want to write something special.
For example,
female math books.
I'll recommend this one to you.
The first female mathematician
in human history,
Seppadia's book.
It records the story of Seppadia
and his father,
Ogilide, when they were young.
It also talks about
how he fell in love with math
and how he became a female mathematician.
I like his book very much.
He is my favorite female mathematician.
It sounds good.
Have you read it?
What a coincidence.
Remember I told you
that my pen mate
and I are through this math mathematician.
Then, you and your pen mate...
He is afraid of darkness too.
Oh, no.
My imagination is going to be ruined.
What's up?
The door is locked.
But I've already called the Department of Defense.
Someone will open the door later.
Hello?
I don't know how long it will take.
I'm scared.
Okay.
I have a few more questions to do.
I'll go on.
Okay.
Why is there a button missing?
Did you just ask me to take it off?
It should be here.
No need.
I'll find it myself later.
Write the questions first.
Okay.
What's wrong?
I cried because I was stupid.
Apple?
What's wrong?
Minquality.
I'll fix her husband now.
I'm doing it first.
Then I'll do the rest.
But,
As a mother of my 3 children,
usually,
I'm most important.
But it's not easy for me to continentally
I'm sorry.
Send someone over.
You said
you knew Bill through this book.
Are you curious
who he is?
Of course I am.
I can't find a Bill who is straight forward.
He left me a call.
But I can't see the last two.
I'll check the basic labels in 가지고.
are you reallyTPH hair strength?
I'm telling you.
It's you.
She is a simple flower
Be brave
She also asked herself
Zipadiya
We are always together
The one who is passionate
Only the summer
Will bloom in the mountains
Zipadiya
The one who is clear
Love like a wind
With a smile
Zipadiya
The one who is passionate
Knowing that I am your best friend
Isn't it very lucky?
Why are you so selfish?
But
To be your desire
I feel very lucky
With a smile
Zipadiya
The one who is clear
Love like a wind
With a smile
Zipadiya
The one who is clear
Love like a wind
With a smile
Zipadiya
Lao Han, do you have any humanity?
Today is the weekend
When you hang up, you will know
I have no humanity
Or the score is not human
Hello
This is the store for the shoes
You bought a pair of shoes a few days ago
When is it convenient to come and get it?
Ok, I'll go now
I have something to go out
I'll let you go first today
Hello, I'm here to pick up the goods
You are Mr. Han, right?
You came last time
No. 36's food is sold out
We just sent you a pair from other stores
Come, look
Is there any problem?
No problem
Hang up
Ok
Wait a moment
Here you are
Thank you, young man
You are welcome
Young man
How do you go to the girls' dorm?
My granddaughter also studies in this school
She is a psychology student
Have you contacted your granddaughter?
The school is very big
If no one takes you there, you may get lost
I'm sorry
No
I want to give her a surprise
Ok, I'll go with you
Thank you so much
Let me do it
Thank you
Go this way
Grandma
We are not far from here
This is a new pair of shoes
It's for delivery
It's a prize for giving your girlfriend's shoes
It's not a good idea
The farther she goes, the more she runs away
It's not for giving my girlfriend's shoes
It's just a normal friend
You give your shoes to a normal friend?
I think you like it and you don't want to show it
Grandma
What's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
I'm old and useless
I only took a few hours' drive
I feel dizzy
Let me help you rest
No need
I haven't seen my granddaughter for a long time
I'm anxious to see her soon
It's ok
Go
Ok
Director
Jian Dan
Your grandma is going to school
She should be here soon
Grandma is here again?
She said it's next weekend
I heard you hurt your foot
So I came a week earlier
Don't forget to remind her
Wait for me at the school gate
I'll drive and pick her up
Ok, director
Hello
The phone you dialed is power off
Why is it power off?
She doesn't have a phone, does she?
I'm sorry
I have to go
Bye
Ok
Young man
There are so few young people
who are honest and enthusiastic like you
You have a girlfriend
Otherwise
I have to introduce my granddaughter to you
My granddaughter is so beautiful
I have a grandson
He is so handsome
He is so talented
He can swim
He swims faster than fish
People in our village like him
You will like him when you see him
By the way
He also told me
He joined a swimming club when he just entered school
He said that the director cared about him
He likes him very much
Grandma
How do you know my granddaughter's name?
You don't know her?
Grandma
I'm the swimming club director
that your granddaughter cares about
Han Yansheng
So it's you
I told you
You will like him when you see him
You misunderstood
I miss you so much
I'm not your granddaughter
How is your foot?
It's better
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I knew it after you called me
By the way
Why is your phone off?
To save electricity
Why are you here?
I was in a car
It's all because of Xiaohana
She helped me with my luggage
She helped me to find you
Thank you for taking care of my grandma
You're welcome
Xiaohana
I told you
You will like him when you see my granddaughter
By the way
You are going to send shoes to that girlfriend
Go
Don't delay your big event
Sister Anshou will like it when she sees the shoes
Who said these are for her?
Feng Ning
For
For me
So you are giving them to Jian Dan
I told you
The shoes for your girlfriend
Are a pair
It means she will be with you for the rest of her life
It's so good
You didn't say that
I have something to do
I'm leaving
Bye
Grandma
Wait for me here
I will put my luggage on the table
I will take you to the canteen to eat
Ok
Grandma
This is the specialty of our canteen
Spicy fried skin
Try it
Speciality
I think
It must be delicious
You think
Grandma
This is my roommate, Mi Fen
Hello, grandma
This is my grandma
Hello
Jian Dan always says that you are his best friend
Really?
Sit down
Let's eat together
You are like my grandma
Don't steal food
Who is the one sitting next to Jian Dan?
Jian Dan's grandma
Then you have to say hello to me
Sit down
Grandma
Hello, grandma
I am Jian Dan's friend
Xia Hou Ling
You can call me monkey
Monkey
How can you call me monkey?
Then you must be like Song Wukong
Smart
Like
Xiaohan
You also come to eat
Sit down and eat together
People are more lively
Ok
I will go
Mi Fen
Jian Dan's foot is injured a while ago
You have been taking care of him
No, it's not me
He
Ok
Jian Dan's foot
Is injured because he participated in the swimming club's opening day activity
I take care of him as the president
It's a public service
So funny
It's for the sake of sacrifice
I won't pick you up on the last day
Is it because you said it yourself
Don't let me send it
I didn't say that
Then what did you say
What I said is
You said you were busy
And you went to the dessert shop
That's because I went to the computer with En Tong
I went to the dessert shop when I was waiting for the computer
How do you know I went to the dessert shop
Is it because of this
You won't let me pick you up
I didn't, Cai Busheng
Who did you go to the dessert shop with
What does it have to do with me
What's going on
Mi Fen
What's going on with them
I don't know either
He started on the first day
And then
I know this
This has to start with the forum
Don't say it
Jian Dan
Let's take a picture
You are often not at home
When grandma misses you
I'll come out and have a look
Ok
Then I'll help you
Jia Gu
You take the photo
Xiao Han
Come here
Let's take a picture together
Ok
Come
Come, Tan Zhening
One
Two
Three
One
Monkey
Did you find the button on Chen Yi's shirt
The headmaster has closed the door
I guess I can't find it
It doesn't matter
It's the first time I see my parents
I'm the first one
I like to joke
Be careful
Thank you
Your canteen is really good
Grandma, are you uncomfortable
I saw you coughing when I was eating
It's ok
The air in the city
is not as fresh as the air in our village
I'm not used to it
Grandma
Let's go back to the dorm and have a rest
I have to take a long-distance bus in the afternoon
Ok, let's go
I'm leaving
Thank you
Bye
Take care
Ok
Bye
Grandma
Take care of yourself
Call me if you need help
You should take care of yourself
Eat well
Don't be reluctant to spend money
Grandma
Monkey
This is a snack prepared by Old Huang.
Take it.
How can I be embarrassed?
This is our snack.
Please accept it.
You guys are so stingy.
This...
Can I talk to you in private?
Of course.
Easy. Easy.
Come on.
Call the director of Shenmu Village.
Ask when the bus will arrive.
Mrs. Shen.
You came to the city
not only to see Jian Dan,
but also to see a doctor.
How did you know?
I saw your medical report.
Your illness...
Since you already know,
I won't hide it from you.
I came this time
to see a doctor.
But you can't let Jian Dan know about this.
This kid is very thoughtful.
If he knows that I'm sick,
he won't be able to learn it.
Don't worry about this.
I'll keep it a secret.
But you can't delay your illness.
Remember to take your medicine on time.
Thank you, kid.
Kid.
With you taking care of Jian Dan,
I feel much more relieved.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Grandma.
The bus is here.
Let's go.
Here it is.
Jian Dan.
Slow down.
Take care of yourself.
Don't worry.
Bye, grandma.
Bye, Jian Dan.
Bye.
Han.
I have a class with Yuan San.
We're leaving now.
I have to go to the supermarket to buy something.
Bye.
Stop.
What did you say
when you pulled grandma over?
It's a secret.
I'll ask grandma later.
I'm afraid grandma will misunderstand our relationship.
I'll explain it to grandma.
What did she say to you?
She said...
What did she say?
She said she wanted me to be her grandson's son-in-law
and take care of you.
Who wants you to take care of me?
I heard that Jian Dan's grandma came yesterday.
Han Yansheng is having dinner with her.
Is it a family reunion?
Luckily, I'm with Han Yansheng and Jian Dan.
Those who are with Han Yansheng and Gu Wentong
are heartbroken.
Tong Yan's couple is in danger.
I'll be with the Christmas couple.
I have something to talk to you.
Can we meet?
Amazing!
Suddenly I am so Doctors In Lausort,
my memory is too whack.
I didn't notice, but it used to be too often.
When we first met
One look, one word
I still can't forget
My eyes are already red
Like a poem
Those young days
Are ordinary but interesting
In the gap of time
We secretly
Fly away
Those broken pasts
The vague name
Fortunately
We once had each other
Those young days
The heart does not need to be delayed
But one day
The promise becomes a luxury
Those broken pasts
It never changes
The life is just a picture
Translated by Hua Chenyu