The one you love
I love you
dialect
Tang Sheng, wait.
It's not a special day today.
I'm sorry.
They didn't mean to lie to you.
They just wanted to help me.
Don't be mad.
Can you hear me out?
But I don't want to hear it.
Why didn't you give me
a chance to explain?
I'm that kind of person.
You've known it now.
And...
Let's break up.
Say it again.
You've heard it clearly.
Suddenly, I feel like dying.
Memories are too temporary.
It hurts and it hurts, but it's not the end.
Where should I start?
When we first met.
I don't know what to do.
Wan.
I still miss you.
What's going on?
Did they not make up?
No, I have to see it.
Mi Fen.
Love is a matter of two people.
Although they're friends,
don't interfere with them too much.
Leave some space for them.
Suddenly, the wind becomes clear.
Smiling is delayed.
The weather is good.
The rain is falling.
Which address should I go?
Who will find the answer?
The passion of love, the persistence of dreams.
My future is because of you.
Like a poem.
Those young days.
They're ordinary but meaningful.
In the gap of time.
We're still beautiful.
Those broken past.
The vague name.
Fortunately, we once had each other.
Those broken past.
It's never been the same.
The life is endless.
What are you looking for?
If it's something simple,
then forget it.
I'm your aunt.
Can't I care about you?
I'm afraid you're not drunk enough.
So I brought you something.
I know you're in a bad mood.
So I came to drink with you and chat.
You need to be careful.
Don't chat and have a drink.
It's a deal.
Comp chap when you're drunk.
Just a break-up, alright?
It's no big deal.
Let's have another one.
Have it.
I prophetize.
Thank you.
There will be leaves in winter for many years.
My mouth is watering.
Two years later
Why did you break up
with Jian Dan?
Dr. Han.
I remember you used to tell me
that generations of wine 24 الإل
will pay the price.
Such a lie.
Drunk like a city.
I'm not going to ask him.
Forget it.
It's no use asking him.
Let's go and check the list.
Why did you drink so much?
Dasheng.
It hurts so much.
Can you hear me?
Dasheng.
Where are you?
Alright.
I'll send you back first.
Okay?
Here.
Be careful.
Why did you get all the way here?
Female dodgers
may have slept already.
Landing
I came back
to the pillow room.
I saw the
fan is off.
That's
a surprise to me.
I may already be
taken to my room.
Let's go, Jia제 boost his spirit.
Seeing that he Remove Jin might have land anguish.
Time must go by.
I guess I don't have to worry about his health.
I'll go find someone
to visit her again.
I made some tea.
It's good?
Sure.
I'll take care of her.
everyone May contain
information that may cause Conometimes
Master Y16
Come on
Jintai
You're finally back
Fried chicken?
I saw a new restaurant with good noodles.
It's very good.
Let's go.
I think it's good.
Come on.
Try this lamb skewer.
The grilled squid tastes good.
Come on, Jinta.
The prawn tastes good too.
Right?
I think so.
I'm telling you, the fish tofu
is very delicious.
Right.
Look at the sausage.
The potato chips.
It's really good.
The onion is too spicy.
I'm about to cry.
Right.
Boss.
Can you not
put so much chili next time?
Look at it.
It's really...
Come on.
Let's eat a little bun.
It's a little sweet.
Try it.
Bite it.
Drink some water.
Is it good?
Look at the way she's showing off.
It's really...
An.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the math competition
for Xiuchuan City.
I might not be there
for this period of time.
If you're leaving,
what about you and Jian Dan?
I've put the president's seal
in the drawer.
After I leave,
I'll go to the competition
to get the seal.
I'll walk you out.
No need.
Jian Dan.
Why did you just answer the phone?
Han is going to
the math competition.
He should be in the car now.
Hello?
Jian Dan.
Why did you leave?
Are you closely following flown?
I wish you had waited a little longer.
Pen,
the Nation's first
galaxy monoc Rare wait Chicago
Just wait for dreams
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Can you stop talking nonsense?
What's wrong with you?
Huo Zeyang is so annoying.
He always makes things up.
So annoying.
You guys eat first.
I'll leave first.
Take the bag back to him.
ş prz
tends to
you now to a coffee house
has major related things
with Lu Yubing
it sold
you to open and listen to
I'm sorry.
His illness is getting worse.
He may not be able to cure it.
I feel so confused and helpless.
Maybe I should give up.
I said I didn't love him
and broke up with him.
This...
This is my voice.
But it was edited.
Why is Ansheng so angry?
The editing of the original is not obvious.
But we can still use professional software
to identify the original sound.
I tried to fix it,
but it didn't work.
I can't find the original sound.
It's okay.
I have the original sound in my computer.
How do you do this?
Use this and add this
and edit it.
And then do this.
Easy.
That's too easy.
Let me show you the刷 Haddan used.
Ansheng is doing very well today.
Do you AmericaREACTEd?
He's doing well.
He's cooperating with me.
I'm confident
that I can help him
overcome the psychological obstacles.
He hasn't taken the exam today.
He's not in a good state.
He seems to have lost confidence in himself.
I feel bad when I see him like this.
I want to help him.
But I really don't know what to do.
I just had a nightmare.
In the dream,
Han Sheng's condition
became worse.
He may not be able to cure it again.
He lost confidence
and began to give up on himself.
Fortunately, after waking up,
I found it was just a dream.
I'm a little shaken.
I don't know if it's right or wrong
to force him to face the past.
Is it right or wrong?
Yesterday, I recommended Han Sheng
to watch a movie
called The Soul Reconciliation.
The male lead in it
is a patient with a serious injury.
He was abandoned since childhood
and abused by the beast.
It caused him to be extremely selfish and inferior.
He was afraid of being abandoned by his girlfriend
and told her that he didn't love her
and broke up with her.
Finally,
with the help of the professor,
he finally got out of the shadow of his heart
and found his girlfriend
and started a new life.
I originally wanted to encourage Han Sheng
through this movie.
But he didn't watch it.
He was very emotional.
I don't know
how to help him.
I feel so confused and helpless.
Maybe
I should give up
the treatment method now
and let Han Sheng live his life.
Actually, I don't mind at all.
Whether he can swim or not
is enough as long as he can be happy.
Even if the movie was edited,
what's the point?
I still can't cure my illness.
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed
cannot be connected for the moment.
Please redial later.
Sorry.
Your Highness,
he still doesn't answer my call.
I don't know if he saw the email.
Can you help me ask him?
Maybe it's not convenient for him to answer the phone now.
How about I send you a message?
Han,
did you see the simple email?
I thought he would ignore me after the recording.
Don't be angry.
How about you tell him in person after Han comes back?
It's easier to tell him in person.
Try this sword so hard.
Ah Xu An.
When am I done?
Give it to me.
Pick up the sword.
Does he take all the deep matters?
Fantastic.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
Jianan, why are you still awake?
My head hurts.
Headache?
Let me see.
Your body temperature is low.
You probably don't have a fever.
You are just overworking recently.
Your body is too tired.
Get up and have a meal.
Don't tell him.
Just leave him alone.
I don't believe he will ignore you.
What's up?
Jianan is sick.
He doesn't eat well.
Do you want to talk to him?
Why doesn't he tell me?
I have something to do.
I'll hang up.
Hello, Dr. Han.
Hello.
I want to order.
Jianan,
well,
Monkey told me yesterday
that there are too many things in the swimming club.
He is too busy.
I'll go help him.
Have a good rest at home.
Hello.
You got a copy of the father-of-the-pea porridge
from Nan Shan Restaurant.
It's a gift from the deliveryman.
Please check it.
I didn't take part in the lottery.
As long as you have been to our restaurant,
you will automatically participate in the lottery.
Thank you.
Perfume
fake smile
I'm afraid you want the one you love
If he answers with a smile
I'm afraid he is a simple flower
He has also asked himself
I'm afraid he is the most passionate
If he answers with a smile
I'm afraid you want the one you love
Before leaving, Han said he was in the drawer
But I sent him a little note and didn't see it
Then have you ever thought about the drawer he said
It's the drawer in the office
Is this possible
Then help me find it
Found it
Great
Wait for me, I'll go over now
Qingtan, come to the swimming pool office
I have something important to tell you
Ok, I'll be there right away
Qingtan
Qingtan, look at this
Is this possible
I'm too careless
I didn't even find his state was wrong
Xiao Miao
What are you doing
What else can I do
Find Han Yanshan
Sister
Sister, are you looking for this
Thank you
You're welcome, sister
No matter how sad you are in the future
Don't throw things away
Goodbye sister
Zishan, come in your kitchen
Come
Students, tomorrow is the official exam
Everyone goes back today
Rest early, do your best
Take the final test tomorrow
You are not a student of this school
Can't enter
Today is my boyfriend's birthday
I want to give him a surprise
Entering the school district must be approved by an emergency student
Call your boyfriend
But he came to approve it
It's not a surprise
Handsome, please be kind
I'm sorry
The school has its rules
No one can break the rules
I'm sorry
Suddenly I feel like dying
Come on, Wu Xie, where are you going?
Don't run.
Stand there.
Wu Xie,
where are you going?
There's a sign on the table.
The song is about the young days.
It's ordinary but interesting.
In the gap of time,
we secretly cry.
Those broken pasts,
the vague names.
It's okay.
We once had a...
Excuse me, could you check again?
No need.
Han Yansheng!
Subbers Alina, Sophia, Sophia
Proofreading, Translation,
Timing and Rehabilitation
The Legend of Princess Miaoshan
Suddenly we get close and miss each other.
Memories are too temporary.
It's ordinary but interesting.
Where should we start?
When we first met,
I didn't miss any of the words.
My eyes are red like a poem.
The young days are ordinary but interesting.
In the gap of time,
we secretly cry.
Those broken pasts,
the vague names.
It's okay.
We once had a...
Excuse me, could you check again?
The young days are ordinary but interesting.
When we first met,
our promise was lost.
Those broken pasts,
the vague names.
The vague names.
The Legend of Princess Miaoshan
Episode 1