♪The sun comes out♪
♪While the clouds are idle♪
♪What a beautiful day♪
♪Catching up with all my might♪
♪The wind blows away the fatigue♪
♪Telling me♪
♪To love the world♪
♪The smell of cooking♪
♪Fills the streets♪
♪Indulge myself♪
♪In the tenderness of life♪
♪The small restaurant we once went to♪
♪Is filled with my longing for you♪
♪Oh, I want to meet you♪
♪Oh, hand in hand♪
♪Stroll through the small town at night♪
♪Take our time with our sweet love♪
♪Love means to be with you♪
♪During three meals a day
for all seasons♪
♪Each meal is♪
♪A beautiful feast♪
♪Underlying♪
♪The warmth of home♪
♪Please remember♪
♪Love's about trivial matters in life♪
♪Enjoying ordinary meals with you♪
♪Your smiling face♪
♪Will always be vivid♪
♪And give me the happiness♪
♪That I expect♪
[Chef Son-in-law]
[Adapted from Yandou Laoge's novel,
The Great Nation's Master Chef]
[Episode 20]
[Singapore Huasheng International Group]
My dear,
stop crying.
Look.
They are drenched in the rain.
Let them soak if they want.
Dad,
I'm not going to cry anymore.
They are a happy couple.
I'm happy for them.
Mr. and Mrs. Qiao,
Mr. Li said he has seen your sincerity.
He will reconsider the cooperation.
Please go back now.
Please thank Mr. Li for us.
Let's go back.
This is the best available alternative
so far.
However, in terms of ingredient quality
and price,
it can't compare to the Huasheng Group.
After you and Qiao Zhi go
to see Li Hua together,
is there still no room for maneuver?
Let it be.
We've done everything we could.
Hello.
Hello, Ms. Tao.
[Huaixiang Group]
A lady named Ellie is here to see you.
Are you available?
Yes.
Please show her in now.
Miss Ellie, this way please.
Go ahead with your work.
Ms. Tao, the guest has arrived.
Please.
Miss Ellie,
please have a seat.
This is the third time we've met,
but I haven't got a chance
to get acquainted with you.
Third?
But I only remember twice.
Never mind.
What brings you here?
My daddy asked me to tell you
he'll continue to cooperate
with Huaixiang.
Really?
I have to thank him.
He said
he admires your persistence and courage.
Under your leadership,
the Huaixiang Group
is bound to grow and prosper.
He also said
he has seen the true color
of the Zhan family
and will not have any contact
with them anymore.
Please thank him on my behalf.
The Huaixiang Group
will not let him down.
One more thing.
On behalf of my father
and also myself,
I sincerely apologize to you.
Miss Ellie,
please don't be like this.
He is a good father.
To protect you,
he did nothing wrong.
Sit down.
Learning you and George had got married,
I had someone look into it and found
the Tao family made things difficult
for him at every turn,
making him do menial work
in the kitchen.
I thought
you didn't announce your marriage
because you looked down on him
and had only married him
for your mom's sake.
That's why
I disliked you.
I know very well
how outstanding George is,
and you also know I admire him,
so I was very hurt,
and my father stood up for me.
But now I know
you love him.
You love each other.
I was just being presumptuous.
I'm sorry.
Miss Ellie,
you're very kind.
Although I feel very disappointed
about not being able to marry George,
since you love each other,
I sincerely wish you both the best.
Ellie,
thank you.
What's your next step?
I heard
you came back to China for Qiao Zhi.
Without love,
I still have my career.
I'm not a child anymore.
As peers,
you and George
are more outstanding than me.
I can't fall behind you.
Alright,
let the three of us
work hard together.
Store this in the fridge
as soon as possible.
Okay?
Take it inside.
[Canteen]
Hello.
Mr. Li agreed to continue
the cooperation with us.
Really?
Ellie just came to see me.
We've cleared up the misunderstanding,
and we've become good friends.
She invited me to a facial this weekend
and gave me concert tickets for March.
But there are
only two tickets.
VIPs.
So you're ditching me already.
Fine,
go ahead.
Don't worry about me.
But she said
she regretted
that she couldn't marry you.
Well, there's nothing we can do.
Back in college,
I tried my best
to tone down my brilliance.
No way around it.
Just couldn't be hidden!
Stop being cheeky.
Alright,
I've got to go.
I have a meeting now.
Okay.
Remember to get some sleep at noon.
Come to Canteen for a meeting at 10 PM.
Got it.
Ellie.
Fine.
You two go to the concert.
Yet I have to work here alone.
We're shareholders!
Remember to complete your KPI on time.
Okay.
The little princess has grown up.
Don't worry, boss.
I'll definitely
complete the task.
Regarding what my father's done,
I apologize to you.
I do like you,
but that is not the key
to our successful cooperation.
The success comes from our efforts.
I didn't know he would set
so many strange preconditions.
It must have been
very difficult for you,
being stuck in the middle.
No need to apologize.
None of us was wrong.
Tao Ruxue is a good girl.
Please cherish her.
Don't let me down.
Of course.
I'll marry someone
ten thousand times better than you
to make you jealous.
Okay,
that's the way it has to be.
Only such a man
is worthy of you,
right?
So,
pleasure working with you.
Pleasure working with you,
Mr. Qiao.
[Canteen]
Bao,
what's going on?
Why are there so many people?
Didn't you see
Ruxue and Rushuang are here?
From my experience,
this can't be a small matter.
What is it?
How would I know?
If you don't, how am I supposed to know?
Alright,
now that everyone's here,
let's get started.
Today,
Canteen's supervisor,
Tao Ruxue,
and shareholder Tao Rushuang are here.
I'm sure
you have guessed
it's about something important.
That's right.
Thanks to your hard work
over this period,
Canteen
is about to enter
its second development stage.
Uh.
I have a question.
Are we opening a branch
or going into the delivery business?
Neither.
We're not going to follow
the beaten path
of those catering giants.
Keep things simple.
Our co-branded zone
with the Eight Great Restaurants
was a huge success.
So, next up,
the Eight Great Restaurants
will join forces
for an IPO.
That's amazing!
How amazing?
You just know even if you don't
understand it.
The Eight Great Restaurants
are going public, not Canteen.
I can't really explain it
to you clearly.
To meet the development needs
of the second stage,
I'm announcing
some new personnel appointments.
Zhou Chong
will be the CEO of Canteen.
Ding Chan will be
the manager
of the flagship restaurant.
Bao Tong
will be the head chef.
These are my decisions.
Great!
I can actually become the head chef?
Yan,
I told you I was a potential gem.
So awesome!
Right?
Wait!
Master, then what about you?
He is the boss.
What do you think?
Right.
He is the boss!
I'll fully prepare myself
and strive to win this year's
King of Chefs Championship,
bringing back the honor
that rightfully belongs
to Canteen.
Great!
That's fantastic!
So our coming here
is meaningless.
It's meaningful to me.
Then why am I here?
To watch you show off your affection?
[Spicy Chicken]
[Steamed Fish Head in Chopped Chilies]
[Canteen Official]
I'm Zhou Chong.
Today,
I will take everyone
on an immersive experience
of the co-branded zone
at Bashu Restaurant's
Yumin Road branch.
Look here, everyone.
Isn't business booming?
Please give us
plenty of likes
and come
try our delicious food.
We really appreciate your support
and hope you enjoy it!
Now,
as you can see,
our restaurant
has been doing well lately,
right?
Mr. Qiao has instructed us
to keep rolling out new dishes.
Today, I'm going to introduce
Chrysanthemum Tofu.
As the name suggests,
the main ingredient
is tofu.
The side ingredients include
winter bamboo shoots,
chicken breast,
ham, Xianggu mushrooms, lettuce
and scallions.
[Huaixiang Restaurant]
The line at Canteen is long.
I thought it might be shorter here,
but the co-branded zone
also has a queue.
Yes,
its saturation level
has quickly reached 90%.
But to expand nationwide
will take some time.
Mr. Song,
can you speed things up a bit?
Why in such a rush?
Because of the Zhan family?
Yes.
As expected,
can't escape your sharp eyes.
Here's the situation.
Back then,
when my mother-in-law was sick
and hospitalized,
the Zhan family acquired shares
of the Huaixiang Group.
Now that she is about to be discharged
from the hospital,
given her usual style,
she'll definitely take some action.
So,
as her son-in-law,
I have to put in some effort too.
Now that you've put it this way,
if I don't exert myself,
that would make me look bad.
Alright,
I promise you.
Before the finals of the championship,
all the co-branded zones nationwide
will be fully established.
This way,
everyone will
be able to taste your dishes.
Thank you.
But don't get happy just yet.
Speed up the training of chefs
outside the province.
Okay,
I will.
[Xunyang Jiangdebao BMW Dealership]
Yan,
come to Jiangdebao BMW Dealership.
I have a surprise for you!
The 4 Series.
The 6 Series.
The sports car looks better.
What are you doing?
What kind of surprise is it?
Congratulations to Ms. Guo Yan
on becoming a BMW owner
and picking up her new car!
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
Surprised? Excited?
A goddess has to be paired with a BMW.
Do you like it?
You're quite thoughtful.
Of course.
The key.
Congratulations to Ms. Guo
on becoming the distinguished owner
of a BMW.
May the vast blue sky and white clouds…
May the vast…
May…
May the vast blue sky and white clouds
embrace your beauty and aspirations.
May your journey ahead
be smooth.
Show it!
It's not a sports car.
No.
Well,
we have to go step by step.
Give me a little more time.
Okay.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Where to?
For a drive!
Yes, a drive!
Still showing off, huh?
Careful!
You're playing quite well.
Stop going easy on me
and play at your true level.
This has always been my true level.
Alright then.
Let's start.
Come on.
Start already!
Are you okay?
How are you feeling now?
I'm fine, let's go again.
No!
Let me see.
You've sprained your ankle.
How can you go again?
We're done for today.
I'll carry you.
You're quite light.
You must be under 60kg, right?
Nonsense!
I'm clearly only 45kg.
No way.
You must have set your scale
to a lower sensitivity.
You're too weak.
If you can't carry me, I'll walk.
Listen.
You won't get off easily.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Today,
I guess I was like Pigsy
carrying his wife.
Look at you!
Even uglier than Pigsy.
So be it.
Although Pigsy was ugly,
he had great luck with the ladies.
In heaven,
he was making eyes at Chang'e.
And on earth,
he fell for the beautiful Gao Cuilan.
Moreover, Pigsy,
despite his ugliness,
was exceptionally
gentle and attentive
towards women.
So you're emulating Pigsy,
knowing full well she is a female demon,
still offering yourself up.
What demon?
She might be hiding in some cave.
You're talking nonsense!
I'll get you some medicine.
Here.
Be careful.
Gently now.
Bear with it.
Gently.
Are you feeling any better?
It can't get better that quickly!
By the way,
Mom is getting discharged
the day after tomorrow.
What should we do
about what she asked us to do?
I think
we can't hide it forever.
Just do what needs to be done.
Seems you have a plan.
There's nothing wrong for us
to do that, right?
Qiao Zhi!
What are you doing?
Want to bite me?
What if I bite you?
Don't. You...
I…
I can bite, too.
Come on then.
Fine.
♪It once cured my insomnia♪
♪And healed the pain of a goodbye♪
♪The back view as you turned away♪
♪Still so vivid in my mind♪
♪I had imagined owning it♪
♪I had also imagined losing it♪
♪But I still overlooked that♪
♪The feeling of loss would be so hard
to breathe through♪
♪I want to become♪
♪Your favorite sweater♪
♪To hug you,
even if I have to stay there♪
♪We'll spend the seasons together♪
♪I want to become...♪
Square dancing, right?
Okay.
Alright, I'm on my way.
Sorry.
That was
an accident.
It was.
We've agreed
not to have a baby for now.
We agreed.
What if you can't hold it back?
Well...
Theoretically,
that possibility exists.
Because…
After all
I'm
a normal man.
Then
we need
to take precautions.
What?
Precautions!
Remember to buy some
before Mom gets back.
I, I'll buy them.
I'll buy them.
The co-branded zones again!
The Eight Great Restaurants
at the same time!
Qiao Zhi,
I underestimated you.
Dad,
it's just a co-branded zone.
Why should you get so angry?
The Eight Great Restaurants
have expanded their co-branded zones.
They have announced
their goal is to go public.
They are rebelling against me.
Don't you understand?
But we hold shares in Huaixiang.
Right now, most shareholders
among the Huaixiang board of directors
have sided with Tao Nanfang.
Once she is discharged,
she'll first
force out our shares.
Can she just do what she wants?
You are worrying too much, Dad.
Worrying too much?
I'm taking precautions!
What if Qiao Zhi's co-branded zones
are established nationwide,
and he wins a place in the championship
for the Huaixiang Group?
Have you considered the consequences?
Sit down first.
I'll make sure
he doesn't get a place.
Just make him no longer part
of the Huaixiang Group.
That would solve it.
Go on.
This is what I'm thinking.
Don't get your hands dirty.
I'll start with his team at Canteen
and completely
destroy Qiao Zhi's life's work.
First,
I'll throw him into chaos.
Second,
I'll make him touch
Tao Nanfang's sore spot
and prove that he's having an affair.
That way,
he'll be kicked out.
In the end,
he'll be nothing more than a stray dog.
By that time,
Mr. Biao, who has no children,
will be completely disappointed.
Then his assets
can only be taken over by us.
Once Huaixiang is in chaos,
the boss
of the Eight Great Restaurants
will still be you.
You have my drive from back in the day.
Tomorrow, come with me to see Mr. Biao.
Got it.
Dad,
can we agree
you won't slap me in the face?
[Canteen]
These so-called viral dishes
are disgusting!
Get your manager over here!
Sorry.
I'll get you new ones right away.
Hello,
I'm the manager.
Is there a problem?
We drove here for three hours,
and you served us these?
Try them yourself.
Yeah,
try them.
The presentation looks fine.
They may look pretty good
but taste worse
than a street vendor's food.
I'm sorry,
let me have a taste.
How is it?
What do you think?
I'm terribly sorry.
You two came all this way,
and we won't let you leave disappointed.
How about this?
First, we will refund you for the dishes
and prepare new ones for you.
We will also give you some coupons.
Would that be okay with you?
What's wrong?
Bao's dishes got a complaint.
Another complaint?
The customers said
they didn't taste as good as before.
Bao has training sessions
and needs to help Guo Yan.
Alright, I got it.
Don't worry about it.
Bao,
it's done.
You're here just in time, Zhi.
Try them while they're fresh.
Okay.
Who made this?
Mr. Zhou.
Clearly,
we can see
your knife work
is quite delicate,
but you were too forceful with it.
The meat has been diced too finely,
which disrupts its texture
and affects the mouthfeel.
You made these?
Yes.
These three
are excellent.
Tender and fresh.
They've passed.
Thank you, Mr. Qiao.
Alright,
chefs,
if there's a problem with your dish,
please optimize it
according to Mr. Qiao's requirements.
There are limited qualification
and opportunities
to be a chef
for our co-branded dishes.
If next time, you still fail to meet
Mr. Qiao's standards,
I'll have to revoke your qualification
as a chef for these special dishes.
Of course,
after you become a chef
for co-branded dishes,
Mr. Qiao will not be stingy
with your salary and benefits.
Understand?
Yes.
So you
can go back.
Okay.
Thank you.
Bye, Mr. Qiao.
Bao,
stay behind tonight.
I need to talk with you.
Madam.
You came back in advance.
Is everything at home okay?
Everything is fine.
Is Ruxue not home?
She went to work.
Is she still sleeping alone?
Then where does Qiao Zhi sleep?
The empty room downstairs.
Move his things up here.
No one is staying in that room
from now on.
Then where will he stay?
Of course, with his wife!
On the same bed!
If they sleep together,
won't they fight?
They can fight,
but fight on the same bed.
Then you'll have a grandchild soon!
Enough talk.
Pack his things.
Remember to lock that door tight!
Yes.
Oh no!
Mom,
you didn't tell anyone
you were getting discharged.
I would have picked you up!
You are a legal couple.
How long are you going to sleep
in separate beds?
I've been too busy with work lately.
I completely forgot.
He has been sleeping here
yet hasn't moved in.
Well, that's perfect.
I've packed his things here.
You're
too stubborn.
I know you have your own reasons,
but on this matter,
you must listen to me.
I managed to get through this ordeal,
but who knows
what will happen next.
I hope that in my lifetime,
I can arrange everything for you.
Then even if I'm gone,
I won't have any regrets.
Oh, Mom.
What are you talking about?
The doctor said
you've fully recovered now,
and the chance of relapse is very low.
Come on,
just grant
this dying person's wish.
Get along well with Qiao Zhi,
start a family and give birth to a baby.
You've been married for so long
and still have no kids.
People will start talking about it.
Mom!
Whether I have children or not
is none of their business!
It's my business.
Starting today,
Qiao Zhi will be staying here.
Don't push me like this.
Alright,
hand it over.
What?
Your phone.
Give it to me.
Why?
Don't think about tipping anyone off!
[Canteen]
Zhi.
What's wrong?
Why wait until everyone's gone?
Bao,
your dishes have
been complained about three times.
Rest assured.
There won't be a fourth time.
You can't help Guo Yan
with cooking your whole life.
You already know.
Well,
recently,
things have
been too busy,
and I haven't managed to handle it.
Bro,
our team will keep moving forward.
We need to improve continuously
in our own positions.
To be honest,
Guo Yan's restaurant
is under the Baiwei Group.
It's her own venture.
And right now,
you're our head chef.
Make a professional judgment.
Alright.
Don't worry.
[Good BBQ Restaurant]
Mom?
Why did you come back in advance?
We planned to pick you up tomorrow.
I came back early
for two things.
Go ahead.
The first thing,
tomorrow, go to meet Mr. Biao with me.
The Zhan family will be there too?
The second thing,
if I hadn't come back early,
how long would you have kept it from me?
No,
we've just been swamped
with work lately.
Then I'll postpone the launch
of the co-branded zones nationwide.
That should ease your workload, right?
Wait, no.
Don't do that, Mom!
What are you standing there for?
Go to sleep!
Rest early.
Yes, I'm on my way.
Get some rest too.
Come in.
Let me tell you.
You…
My things?
What's going on?
We were caught red-handed.
Mom is really decisive and efficient.
What should we do then?
What else can be done?
Let's sleep together.
Did you buy it?
What?
You know what.
No, I didn't.
Well,
I didn't have time.
Never expected Mom to come back early.
You should have called and told me!
She got my phone.
What?
Mom really is sharp-witted.
Fine then.
Just accept what happened.
I'll take a shower.
Here.
Have you
brushed yet?
Didn't have time.
Ruxue.
Can you get my clothes for me?
Where are your clothes?
Where are your pajamas?
I don't have any.
Just those floral shorts.
The floral ones?
Still can't find them?
Put this on, too.
You'll sleep here tonight.
I'm sleeping here?
That's right.
Where else would you want to sleep?
On the floor?
This air mattress is pretty decent,
so just make do with it for now.
No way! Why should it be me making do?
Aren't you a man or not?
Of course, I am a man.
What?
Check it?
Pervert!
Fine,
I'll sleep here.
Good night.
Go for it,
dear.
Dear,
I won't let you down.
♪One day♪
♪In front of me♪
♪You'll look at my face♪
♪I'll tell you♪
♪My oaths♪
♪One by one♪
♪You'll find♪
♪Oh, my heart♪
♪Has never changed♪
♪Just like the sea♪
♪That always reflects♪
♪The scene of the sky♪
♪I'll take you out
of the hustle-bustle of the world♪
♪To go wild freely♪
♪Don't worry about the journey ahead♪
♪Just keep going♪
Do you snore when you sleep?
I didn't back in college.
Not sure about recently though.
Nobody's told me lately...
Then I won't wear earplugs.
They feel weird anyway.
Alright, let's sleep.
Good night!
No.
[National Premium Tea House]
Mr. Biao asked us here.
Remember,
today is a business meeting
between two publicly listed companies.
Keep your cool, understand?
I'm here today just to learn.
Business opportunities
are negotiated into existence.
Even if there's bad blood,
keep that anger bottled up.
Got it.
Mr. Biao.
Grandpa.
Great.
You're here.
Have a seat.
Here.
I don't think
we have much to talk about.
Whatever the price
you bought the shares from Rende,
I'll buy them back at that same price.
Then you'll
withdraw from the Huaixiang Group.
But those shares are mine now.
Whether or not they get sold
isn't your decision to make.
♪One day♪
♪In front of me♪
♪You'll look at my face♪
♪I'll tell you♪
♪My oaths♪
♪One by one♪
♪You'll find♪
♪Oh, my heart♪
♪Has never changed♪
♪Just like the sea♪
♪That always reflects♪
♪The scene of the sky♪
♪I'll take you out
of the hustle-bustle of the world♪
♪To go wild freely♪
♪Don't worry about the journey ahead♪
♪Just keep going♪
♪You'll find the tears I left behind♪
♪You'll also see me
writing my own poems♪
♪And I'll always hold you tight♪
♪I'll take you out
of the hustle-bustle of the world♪
♪To go wild freely♪
♪Don't worry about the journey ahead♪
♪Just keep going♪
♪You'll find the tears I left behind♪
♪You'll also see me
writing my own poems♪
♪And I'll always hold you tight♪