♪The sun comes out♪
♪While the clouds are idle♪
♪What a beautiful day♪
♪Catching up with all my might♪
♪The wind blows away the fatigue♪
♪Telling me♪
♪To love the world♪
♪The smell of cooking♪
♪Fills the streets♪
♪Indulge myself♪
♪In the tenderness of life♪
♪The small restaurant we once went to♪
♪Is filled with my longing for you♪
♪Oh, I want to meet you♪
♪Oh, hand in hand♪
♪Stroll through the small town at night♪
♪Take our time with our sweet love♪
♪Love means to be with you♪
♪During three meals a day
for all seasons♪
♪Each meal is♪
♪A beautiful feast♪
♪Underlying♪
♪The warmth of home♪
♪Please remember♪
♪Love's about trivial matters in life♪
♪Enjoying ordinary meals with you♪
♪Your smiling face♪
♪Will always be vivid♪
♪Give me the happiness♪
♪That I expect♪
[Chef Son-in-law]
[Adapted from Yandou Laoge's novel,
The Great Nation's Master Chef]
[Episode 6]
[Inpatient Building]
You're awake.
Don't move.
Any need? I can help you.
So thoughtful of you?
Am I in heaven?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
You saved Rushuang,
so I'm taking care of you here.
Just now
during my operation,
were you hoping I wouldn't wake up?
The three fortunes in life
are getting promoted,
becoming wealthy,
and losing one's husband.
Quite the sharp tongue!
Seems your mind is fine.
I have a very sharp mind.
But
one inch further down,
I'm afraid you'll be a widow.
I don't want to chat with you anymore.
You're awake.
So you both are here.
You got hurt because of me,
so I won't leave.
Well.
Since he's awake, head back now.
No need for both of us to stay here.
I just woke up from sleep.
You should go back.
I'll stay here.
Come out.
I need to talk to you.
Just spit it out!
Why can't you say it before him?
You know he's my husband.
That was ridiculous!
He saved my life.
Shouldn't I take care of him?
I've said
I can take care of him.
I don't think you can.
Have you ever taken care of someone?
What if he needs to use the restroom?
Call a nurse!
Tao Rushuang,
you're being unreasonable.
What's wrong with me?
Wait.
You were hoping to divorce him before.
Now suddenly you act concerned.
I doubt if you can take care of him.
Good heavens!
Knock it off already!
I feel fine.
You both go home. Okay?
Nothing serious.
Stay here as you like.
But
why would you provoke her?
Can't stand how she acts.
As if being pretty
means she owns the whole world.
But she is pretty though.
Superficial!
What?
Fell for her looks?
As her husband,
if I don't love her,
should I hate her instead?
Husband?
She is plotting how to kick you
out of the door!
But she failed.
Listen.
You've met too few beauties,
so you'd be easily manipulated.
What should I do then?
Beauty is commonplace;
an interesting soul is rare.
Yet how do you know
she has no interesting soul?
Besides,
I simply go
for her appearance.
Talking to you kills my vibe completely.
What's wrong?
Alright.
I'm fine.
What did you bring today?
A sandwich.
Finish every bite.
No complaints about its taste.
Sandwich?
How does it taste?
Oh heavens!
Wait.
As the heiress
to the top
of the Eight Great Restaurants,
how could you cook like this?
If Mr. Tao ever tried your cooking,
he'd probably hit the roof!
But he sampled my dishes
and
even complimented.
He really loved you.
Eat it or throw it away.
No.
I'll eat.
How are you?
Does it still hurt?
Yeah, it hurts.
But nothing serious.
Focus on your work.
Alright, I'll head to the meeting now.
Having a board meeting today?
Go for it!
Off I go.
Keep killing it!
Didn't you bring me any food?
That hamburger on the table is for you.
By the way,
what did the police say?
The suspect was arrested at the station.
The police pressed him,
but he insisted it was solely his doing.
However,
I suspect
it might involve one of my fans.
A fan?
Who exactly?
I don't know,
but he showered me with virtual gifts,
and messaged repeatedly to meet up.
After I turned him down,
he warned me to watch my back.
I have a feeling.
He might be the one who stalked
and secretly photographed me.
You've never even met him.
I'll never meet such a madman.
He clearly has deep pockets
and a powerful backing force.
Such a pervert will be over someday
no matter how powerful he is.
Right,
what exactly did you do
with that 100,000 yuan?
Started a business!
My budget wasn't enough,
so I borrowed money from you.
Starting a business?
Nine out of ten end in losses.
I don't look down on you.
One of my friends
tried multiple times over the years,
each time losing everything.
His family had to deal  with his mess.
Pfft!
Don't talk like such a pessimist!
If you really don't believe in me,
I'll give the money back to you.
No.
The money's spent.
Alright.
Drop the whole borrow thing.
Just call it an investment.
So I'm now your shareholder!
From now on,
speak to me with more respect.
And
stop blackmailing me
with that shady incident.
Fine then.
At most, provoke you with sharp words.
No beauty would spare
a glance at your runaway mouth.
[Ellie Calling]
Ellie,
has that matter been resolved?
Resolved?
What's that?
It's about Huaixiang Group.
Can we collaborate?
My father has only agreed
to supply to Huaixiang Group
and the Canteen.
As for your customized dish proposal,
he wants to discuss it with you
via video call.
Can you come over?
Sure,
I'll head there right away.
Are you out of your mind?
Look at yourself! You can't go!
Why not?
It's crucial for our family's future,
and I promised Ruxue.
Absolutely not.
Your life was at risk!
It's nothing serious.
At worst, the wound heals more slowly.
I'm really fine.
Let's go.
Drive me there.
Slower.
Already.
How are you?
I told you not to come out!
Nothing serious.
Focus on the road.
Come in.
Ellie.
Why are you
so pale?
Ate too much since returning home
and turned all pale and gingerly!
If you feel unwell, take a rest.
I'm fine.
Let's not waste your father's time.
Begin.
Daddy.
Ellie,
my sweetie.
Mr. Li,
it's been a long time since we last met!
Qiao Zhi,
has Ellie
caused you any trouble?
Not at all.
She's helped me tremendously.
If not causing trouble,
she's excelling beyond expectations.
Daddy,
please have faith
in me.
Look at the branch company.
Operations are running smoothly now.
Absolutely!
You're the best!
Now back to business.
Qiao Zhi,
you should understand
it's our honor to partner
with an outstanding company
like Huaixiang Group.
But your pre-made food solution is new.
Can dishes turn into IP
and be sold online?
It leaves me very confused.
Yes.
After all, Huasheng Group still relies
on offline sales in other countries.
But things work differently here.
Nowadays, food delivery
and online shopping
have become indispensable parts
of daily life.
I'm fully aware of that,
but the largest food delivery platform
is Tianxiang Rankings of Baiwei Group.
It's our direct competitor.
But soon enough,
a bigger platform will take its place.
Which one?
Have you heard of short videos?
Of course,
it is blowing up worldwide!
But I recall
they lack food delivery services.
Yes.
They're a newcomer.
It's only available in China for now.
If it succeeds domestically,
they'll immediately replicate this model
in their international version.
At that point,
Huasheng Group
will seize the first-mover advantage.
If the pre-made food sales
can reach 100 million units,
I'll approve your proposal.
How long?
One year.
Two years.
Or
compromise at 50 million units?
You should know
before entering new markets…
Qiao Zhi,
I have confidence in you
and your dishes.
Ellie,
could you step outside for a moment?
I need to speak
with him privately.
Daddy,
what is it that I can't hear?
Be good.
This is a conversation between men.
Qiao Zhi,
given Huasheng Group's scale and resources,
you aren't our top choice.
I have many options available,
or I could choose none at all.
All terms and agreements
for this collaboration
must satisfy one precondition.
Please specify.
Ellie went back to China because of you.
I don't care what dynamic exists
between you two.
Ellie must
live happily.
I promised her mom
on her deathbed.
Therefore,
whether she lives happily
is the sole precondition.
Otherwise,
everything is off the table.
But I...
Speak up already!
How's the talk going?
Nothing to worry about.
Will Ruxue's matter get resolved?
Right now, all the pressure's
shifting onto my shoulders.
Why?
The next step is critical.
Even if I explain, you won't get it.
But you need to say something!
Tomorrow's the 15th.
To become King of Viral Trends,
it depends entirely on this dish!
What's this King of Viral Trends?
Who?
Please focus on driving safely.
I beg you.
I'm sorry.
My apologies.
If you really feel sorry for me,
help arrange my discharge
from the hospital.
[Huaixiang Group]
Among all current distributors,
23 have withdrawn from the bid.
Among the remaining
six groups,
Baiwei Group
offers the largest discount margin.
Meanwhile,
as the only publicly listed company,
Baiwei's product quality
should be well-guaranteed.
Everyone,
any further opinions?
No objections.
I've proposed working with them last year,
but Ms. Tao vetoed it then.
I also agree.
Calculating this way,
our profit this year will increase
by at least six percentage points.
Then it's settled!
Ms. Tao,
any opinions?
It's all about profits.
I can understand that.
Ms. Tao,
what do you mean by that?
For us investors,
if not for returns,
what are we investing for?
Exactly!
Ms. Tao,
you're too young.
Business
isn't as simple as it seems.
When you all unite against me,
what can I say?
Their ingredients are produced
with chemical fertilizers
and various technologies.
You'd stoop to anything for profit!
Tell me
if you eat the dishes from Baiwei Group.
If all the restaurants
serve identical dishes
with the same additives,
are we abandoning culinary culture
and individuality altogether?
It's inevitable, Xue.
Let me
tell you something.
As a company,
we can't single-handedly
change an entire industry.
You've just graduated.
I know
you have ideals and ambitions.
But look around.
Everyone here
was just like you
back then.
But now?
After years of being worn down by time,
we've grown numb.
Look at Mr. Jing
and Mr. Sheng.
They're from an investment firm.
focusing on ROI and output ratios.
Everything else is off the table.
You mentioned culture just now,
but what is culture?
It's merely rhetoric
used by capital to package itself.
Back then,
when your mother chose capital,
she abandoned cultural inheritance.
At such a major event today,
why isn't she presiding over it?
Wake up and face reality.
Alright.
Impressive teamwork!
To win at all costs, huh?
Fine, I'm not changing the supplier.
Our family holds veto power.
If losses occur, share them equally.
How could this work?
Unacceptable.
Massive funds involved!
Xue,
have you lost your mind?
Must you fight against money like this?
Yes,
we suffered losses due to Baiwei Group.
But now
what matters most
is making money!
Do you get it?
Smashing the rice bowls
of future generations?
You can do that, but I can't.
I'm sorry.
I don't lack money,
and what you're doing is unethical.
This meeting is over.
What kind of attitude is this?
Look at her attitude.
Well said!
I now believe
partnering with Huaixiang Group
is a wise choice for Huasheng Group.
You are...?
Head of Huasheng Group in Greater China,
Ellie.
Qiao Zhi,
we…
Look at him.
If any issues arise later,
we'll not take responsibility.
I'm terribly sorry.
If anything happens,
we'll take full responsibility.
Where did Qiao Zhi go?
All because of you.
What did I do?
He even…
Never mind.
Forget it.
Anyway, he went out for you
and felt that he was fine
and could work.
He got carried away
and went to deal with his Canteen.
For me?
He wouldn't let me tell you.
Mustn't go to him.
Pretend you don't know about this.
Hey. Your injury hasn't healed.
It's okay.
I haven't exercised for too long.
Why are you still up so late?
What do you need me for?
I've asked Ms. Chen
to prepare the room upstairs.
It has a spacious environment
and good lighting.
Move up there.
What does that mean?
After all my big help,
is this how you thank me?
I won't move.
Let me tell you.
I refuse.
I want to constantly remind myself
of the grievances I endured here,
so you'll feel guilty
for the rest of your life.
You're so childish.
So what if I'm childish?
I've put myself on the line
for this matter.
Can't I be childish?
What did you promise Huasheng Group?
You think I'm childish, right?
I won't tell you!
I won't tell you.
I'll piss you off.
After all the huge favor I did for you,
not only are you stingy with money,
you didn't even get me a gift!
There is a gift.
I just didn't expect
the custom-made would take this long.
What's this?
Tianqing Pavilion designed this,
with hand-embroidered craftsmanship.
They tailor for all past Kings of Chefs.
Based upon the design of your grandpa's,
they've made modifications:
less rustic simplicity,
more bold extravagance.
I've kept a low profile, okay?
Though I truly do love this gift.
Honestly, I adore it.
The quadrennial
King of Chefs Championship
is about to begin!
You need a proper outfit.
I never said I'll participate.
Deny it all you want,
but reclaim the honor
that rightfully belongs
to your grandpa from Zhan Jun!
It's hard for a cook like me
to become the King of Chefs.
Focus on perfecting your dishes.
Leave everything else to me.
I'll redeem the mistakes
my grandpa made years ago.
Hurry up and pack!
I'll help you move shortly.
[Kenjiro Ito, one of the Three
Japanese Gods of Cuisine]
Mr. Zhan,
who is he?
This is Kentaro Ito,
one of the three
Japanese Gods of Cuisine.
He's notoriously eccentric.
When I speak later,
just listen quietly!
I see.
Losers.
You imbeciles!
Disgraceful!
Sorry, Master.
I should have cut off your fingers!
But since we're in China now,
consider them spared for now.
Yes, Master!
Get lost!
Mr. Ito,
hello.
You must be Zhan Jun's son.
Yes, sir!
Please call me Zhan.
It's an honor
to meet you personally.
I
just prepared a gift.
It's made by Mr. Xu,
Porcelain King of Jingdezhen.
Please accept it.
Let's cut to the chase.
You're so straightforward.
I heard you came to Xunyang looking for
a new location for your restaurant,
yet haven't found one.
Yes.
Honestly,
I had secured
an ideal spot for you,
but some idiot snatched it away.
He even claimed
the Japanese people
don't deserve to open restaurants here!
Unforgivable.
So I'd like you to teach him
a lesson
to convince him.
Thus, things will fall into place.
A man's got to eat!
Let's take a break.
Are you Qiao Zhi?
To think I actually believed
you were a bodyguard at first!
What's the matter?
Baiwei Group wants your restaurant.
Name your price.
I've just got it reopened,
and you're eyeing it up.
Here is the thing.
I promised the neighbors
that I'd help boost business
for all the shops on this street.
Boost business?
You? Seriously?
Don't you know your own place at all?
Let me tell you.
The Japanese God of Cuisine
is coming.
He wants this restaurant.
His arrival
will make the entire food street thrive.
And you
go back to being a bodyguard.
As for compensation,
you won't be shortchanged.
You...
The Japanese God of Cuisine?
Alright.
I'm quite curious to meet him.
Qiao Zhi.
What are they getting at?
What Japanese God of Cuisine?
Never mind. Wait and see.
Asking for a hard time.
Seeking death!
Has Mr. Ito arrived yet?
He's here.
Mr. Ito,
this is the restaurant.
This restaurant
is quite good.
I like it very much.
That's great!
As long as you step in,
things will go smoothly for me later.
Where
is the arrogant
young man now?
Someone like him
doesn't deserve your attention.
But since you're here today,
please teach him
a lesson
and get him out of this food street.
Please.
This way.
Mr. Ito,
that's him!
Mr. Qiao,
it's really you!
I've searched for you everywhere!
Bow down!
This is the master I've been seeking.
Greetings, Master of God.
Please, get up.
We don't go by this in China.
Yes.
Mr. Qiao,
what are you doing here?
This is my restaurant.
Why wouldn't I be here?
So this is your restaurant.
Now it makes sense!
Mr. Ito,
he is the arrogant man!
Have you made a mistake?
I could mistake anyone
but not Mr. Qiao.
No way!
He's just a trainee cook
at Huaixiang Restaurant!
How could he know you?
You fool! Show respect to my master!
Without his guidance,
I'd have never been the God of Cuisine.
Although
he doesn't allow me to say it,
in my heart,
he'll always
be my master.
Never expected you would run
a restaurant here.
True masters are among the common folk.
Alright, Ito.
Let bygones be bygones.
I had no idea
you owned this place.
I came so suddenly.
My deepest apologies.
All I have
to offer now is what's at hand.
This
is a materpiece by Mr. Xu of Jingdezhen.
Please accept it.
Very well.
Thank you.
Ding Chan,
put this away safely.
Yes.
[Canteen]
Mr. Qiao,
I have so many questions to ask you.
Do you
have the time?
Of course.
Come inside and we'll talk.
Come.
Yes.
Go.
Mr. Ito!
What are you doing?
Am I not even allowed inside?
How dare he present my gift to him?
Let's go.
Ask your men
to get these Japanese out of here!
♪The sun comes out♪
♪While the clouds are idle♪
♪What a beautiful day♪
♪Catching up with all my might♪
♪The wind blows away the fatigue♪
♪Telling me♪
♪To love the world♪
♪The smell of cooking♪
♪Fills the streets♪
Everyone, listen carefully.
Stand tall and heads held high.
When a customer comes in,
put your hands right here like this.
And then say welcome.
Welcome!
♪I want to meet you♪
♪hand in hand♪
♪Stroll through the small town at night♪
♪Take our time with our sweet love♪
♪Love means to be with you♪
♪During three meals a day
for all seasons♪
♪Each meal is♪
♪A beautiful feast♪
♪Underlying♪
♪The warmth of home♪
♪Please remember♪
♪Love's about trivial matters in life♪
♪Enjoying ordinary meals with you♪
♪Your smiling face♪
♪Will always be vivid♪
♪Give me the happiness♪
♪That I expect♪
Mr. Xu,
thanks to you,
our partnership
has been such a pleasure.
By the way,
I had Zhan Jun make a reservation
at a restaurant
with a chef who's nearly impossible
to book!
Let's go.
We'll show you our appreciation.
You are visiting me
as a CEO and a top producer,
and I'm deeply thankful.
Now,
I wouldn't dare to eat carelessly.
Mr. Xu,
- it's Qiao Zhi.
- He loves to eat the most!
Qiao Zhi!
Mr. Xu,
will you be free later?
I'd like to treat you to a simple meal.
Of course, I have time!
By the way,
two of my good friends are visiting me.
May I bring them along?
Absolutely!
Welcome.
Great.
What's going on?
You said you wouldn't eat carelessly?
This isn't being careless.
Let's go!
I know a fantastic spot.
But Zhan Jun made a reservation.
Don't worry about that.
Just come with me.
You won't be disappointed!
Mr. Xu,
maybe you should change clothes?
Look at him.
I'll get changed.
Just give me a minute!
Please be careful.
Mr. Xu,
is it
really here?
The GPS says we've arrived.
Are you serious?
Wanting to recall the hard past?
It looks totally dilapidated!
Be patient!
You'll see it in a minute.
It seems really familiar.
I think I've got it.
This was Canteen
that was very popular back then?
Yeah, this looks like the spot.
That's right!
Now that you say that,
it all makes sense.
The owner here was surnamed Qiao, too.
So he…
Good day.
Are you here at Mr. Qiao's invitation?
Mr. Qiao?
You mean Qiao Zhi?
Yes.
Then we are.
He asked me to welcome you.
Please, come this way.
Okay.
Right this way, please.
Well.
Please mind the step.
Mr. Xu,
this place hides a world of wonder!
The decor is quite impressive.
Such a classic, elegant feel.
Very distinctive.
Mr. Xu.
Ding Chan, serve tea.
Allow me to introduce.
This is Mr. Huang.
Mr. Huang, how do you do?
How do you do?
And over here,
Mr. Zhong!
Mr. Zhong, hello!
Very nice to meet you!
Well.
Please wait for about 20 minutes.
We'll begin dinner right on time.
Perfect!
Alright?
Ding Chan,
look after them well.
Alright.
Have a seat.
Please sit down.
Is this soup?
This fragrance…
Wait.
I can't even tell
what this soup is by smelling it.
Is it really that mysterious,
Mr. Xu?
Yes.
You've eaten every luxury under the sun.
You are being modest.
Here comes
the soup!
What's its name?
Have any of you read
the Legend of the Condor Heroes,
the novel of Mr. Jin Yong?
Before us
is the very imperial delicacy
that haunted the memories of Hong Qigong
Mandarin Ducks Stewed
with Five Treasures.
with Five Treasures?
It's mentioned in the novel,
but does this dish
really exist in real life?
I've never heard of it.
Historically, this dish did exist.
It was made by stewing
together five different parts
from birds, wild animals,
mountain treasures,
seafood, and freshwater fish.
So, Five Treasures.
Then, mandarin ducks
refer to a male and a female pigeon.
Mr. Xu, impressive.
This broth is made with male
and female pigeon soup,
supplemented with ginseng,
Dangshen, Taizishen,
Chongcao flower, Maidong,
Tianma, Danggui, and goji berries.
It is simmered for four hours.
My goodness!
There was so much to a soup.
But
what are these Five Treasures?
As the saying goes, there may
be dragon meat up in heaven,
but on earth, nothing
is like good donkey meat!
Now "dragon meat" is the pigeon breast.
The second treasure
is the camel's paw.
Since ancient times,
it's been a staple
of imperial court banquets.
The third treasure is the deer sinew,
the fourth is the shark's lip,
and the fifth
is the pufferfish tail.
First prepare them.
Then bath them in ginger-scallion water
to remove fishiness.
Finally,
add them into the pigeon broth
and steam over high heat for 40 minutes.
Great.
Get me a bowl of it.
Sounds so incredibly complex.
I absolutely have to try it.
I can't wait!
Here, try it!
How is it?
It's absolutely exquisite.
The aroma is incredible.
Every piece of meat has
its unique texture and flavor.
The greatest delicacies in the world!
This broth is the real treasure!
I dare say
it's more fragrant
than Buddha Jumps Over the Wall.
It'd be perfect for soaking up rice.
Qiao,
any cooked rice?
It was prepared long ago.
Ding Chan.
So fragrant.
So delicious.
Mr. Huang?
This suddenly reminded me of the past.
When I was a child, my family was poor
and couldn't afford meat.
My mom would save all the meat for us,
while she ate just a bowl
of soup and rice.
Parents always love their children.
Mr. Huang,
you've now achieved great success
and can repay your parents.
But I have no such chance.
My parents
passed away a long time ago.
That's truly a shame.
So
the rumors are true.
Mr. Huang is a devoted son.
Mr. Huang,
in this case,
why not bring your family here
as my guests someday?
You've reminded me.
I haven't spent time
with my family in a very long while.
But our relationships are complicated.
I'm not even sure
if they still acknowledge me
as their brother.
How about this?
My restaurant is opening on the 30th.
On that day,
if it's convenient for you,
bring them along
to join us.
Alright, I'll give it a try
and support Mr. Qiao.
Mr. Huang, just call me Qiao.
By the way,
I'd like to reserve a table as well.
On that day,
I can bring some friends
or family over
to taste your cooking.
I'm always so full
from the wine
that I almost forget
what it feels like to be full from rice.
Right?
Admit defeat?
I'm completely convinced.
Alright, I'll handle everything
for the upcoming events.
How about that?
- Good. - Good.
Qiao, you got time? Come with us!
Join us.
I don't think I should go.
We're opening soon
and there's still a ton of stuff to do.
Okay.
Alright then.
See you on the 30th.
Okay.
[Zhan Jun Calling]
Mr. Zhan.
Mr. Zhan,
I'm so sorry.
Forgot to inform you in advance.
A last-minute matter came up today.
Well,
it's my treat next time.
I'll make the arrangements. Okay?
♪One day♪
♪In front of me♪
♪You'll look at my face♪
♪I'll tell you♪
♪My oaths♪
♪One by one♪
♪You'll find♪
♪Oh, my heart♪
♪Has never changed♪
♪Just like the sea♪
♪Which always reflects♪
♪The scene of the sky♪
♪I'll take you out
of the hustle-bustle world♪
♪To go wild freely♪
♪Don't worry about the journey ahead♪
♪Going on this way♪
♪You'll find the tears I left behind♪
♪You'll also see me writing a poem♪
♪And I'll always hold you tight♪
♪I'll take you out
of the hustle-bustle world♪
♪To go wild freely♪
♪Don't worry about the journey ahead♪
♪Going on this way♪
♪You'll find the tears I left behind♪
♪You'll also see me writing a poem♪
♪And I'll always hold you tight♪