[English subtitles are available]
Dance of the Sky Empire
Episode 23
Brother.
Brother,
I'm not going back to the State of Sha with you.
Do
you wanna go find Xiao Fengming?
I can't leave him alone with that demon.
You also know that
the demon spirit has the spiritual power of the Dragon Emperor,
which you won't be able to defeat
Don't be impulsive.
I don't intend to defeat him
but keep him company.
I'll wait for you to save him.
Nope.
It's too dangerous.
I won't agree on it.
If
the one in danger is Su Youlian,
what are you gonna do, Brother?
Go ahead.
Be careful.
Loong Wei'er,
let's take action separately. Go.
Okay.
There are criminals who are Loong Wei'er and Zheng Bainian.
They collide with the renegade, Li Xuan
to cheat His Majesty.
They released the siren of the Clan of Kunwu arbitrarily
in the name of atoning for the previous crime.
They cared nothing about the order of His Majesty as well as the safety of the people.
They won't be absolved.
According to the law of Tianqi,
they are sentenced to decapitation
and will be executed in the South City Execution Ground
on 4th, December, Renchen Year.
Time's up.
Decapitate.
You're finally coming.
Sorry to let you suffer.
Let's go.
Zheng Bainian, hurry up.
Well,
spit it out.
Who on earth are you?
A crap.
You know you're a crap.
There're plenty of you,
but you still fail to stop Li Xuan from saving them.
I have so many subordinates.
Could you help me
accomplish at least one thing?
I mean at least one thing.
Please calm your anger, Your Highness.
It will hurt you.
Do you know the punishment?
Yes.
Come on.
No wonder Xiao Fengming looked down upon you.
Reach out your hand.
Who allows you to take back your hand?
You even changed a hand.
That one.
No wonder they looked down upon you.
Since they're so different from you.
They're so different from you. They're so different from you.
Where's Xiao Fengming?
He's...he's in his room.
Go ask him to come here.
Yes. I'm going right now.
Come on.
Come back as soon as possible.
Next one.
It's your turn.
Your Highness.
What's up?
Your Highness,
Princess Yunshan of the State of Sha wants to meet you.
Who?
Princess Yunshan.
Why is she coming?
I won't meet her.
Yes.
Are you clear about what I said just now?
Your Highness.
I have something important to tell you.
It's you.
Okay.
Let me know
what important thing you wanna tell me,
which even makes you intrude into my bedroom.
Xiao Fengming has been manipulated by the demon spirit of the Dragon Emperor.
You can't be deceived by him anymore.
What are you talking about?
Yunshan.
I mean,
you're the princess of the State of Sha,
but you're slandering my subordinate
in front of me.
I mean,
what on earth do you want?
I'm not slandering him
but telling you the truth.
According to your word,
now that you're telling the truth
that he has been manipulated by the demon spirit of the Dragon Emperor,
do you have the evidence?
The evidence is ...
The evidence is...
Haven't you noticed his spiritual power is boundless
and the martial arts of him is extremely powerful these days?
I do notice it.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have recruited him
to my camp.
It's the evidence.
Xiao Fengming isn't that powerful.
What he can achieve the best is to draw formations
instead of martial and magic arts.
-Crown Prince, you... -Enough.
I get it.
Well, have you finished?
Please go back.
Guards.
Escort her out.
Crown Prince, you have to trust me.
Xiao Fengming isn't the one who he used to be.
He has been manipulated.
Hurry and take the crazy woman away.
Let me go.
I'm able to walk by myself.
What a bad temper you have!
Do you know the hierarchy and order?
I've known who you are.
You'd better stop manipulating Xiao Fengming immediately.
-Otherwise. -Otherwise what?
Otherwise...
Otherwise, I'll let the public know the truth.
I'll see whoever will believe in you.
Does it matter?
Why would Xiao Fengming have a thing for
a silly girl like you?
I get it.
One of you are pedantic and dull
while the other is impulsive and silly.
What a perfect match you are!
What are you talking...?
Xiao Feng...
Xiao Fengming.
Yunshan.
Watch her carefully.
Yes.
Xiao Fengming,
you're coming.
Come here. Come on.
Have some shots of alcohol with me.
Back off.
Xiao Fengming,
have you heard it?
Your Highness, do you mean Second Prince was saved?
Exactly.
I've never seen father so angry.
You mean, how dare
Li Xuan
come to save Loong Wei'er
since he himself is a wanted criminal?
I have no idea why Li Xuan had the courage.
The execution ground was heavily guarded,
but he still succeeded in saving them.
Your Highness,
don't you think the subordinates around you are useless?
Well,
from now on,
you'll be in charge of
my personal guards.
As for my henchmen,
you don't have to hassle them.
Besides,
go find some best talents for me immediately.
I wanna organize a best team.
I want the best one.
The team trained by me
must be the best.
Xiao Fengming,
I trust you.
Come on.
Have a full shot of alcohol.
Well,
do you know Princess Yunshan?
The princess of the State of Sha is my schoolmate.
Of course, I know her.
Then do you know
what she told me
when she came to me today?
I wouldn't know
what she told you.
She said to me that
Xiao Fengming isn't the one he used to be.
He's the demon spirit of the Dragon Emperor now.
Do you think it's ridiculous?
You don't believe her word, do you?
Of course not.
The word of her is nonsense.
I've put you in an important position,
so I'll trust you for sure.
As long as you can assist me,
I'll definitely offer you gorgeous rewards
when I succeed to the throne some other day.
I'll try my utmost to assist you.
And I wish Your Highness could succeed to the throne
and rule the neighboring states.
Don't say it now.
Loong Wei'er and Li Xuan...
Long Wei'er is a convict sentenced to death by His Majesty
while Li Xuan is a renegade.
The two of them won't have a way to make a living in Tianqi.
Well,
thanks for your hard work, Xiao Fengming.
what are you gonna do?
I intend to go to the State of Sha.
The State of Sha?
It's said that there's another Saintess Stone in the State of Sha.
I think, since Su Youlian failed to awake the Dragon Emperor this time,
and the Saintess Stone was broken,
she would go to the State of Sha
to search for the other Saintess Stone.
I have to stop her.
Besides,
do you always wanna know
the memories you lost?
If you wanna retrieve your memories,
maybe that Saintess Stone will help you.
Could that Saintess Stone help me retrieve my memories?
It's said on the historical data.
Let it go.
Even if I retrieve my memories, what else could I do?
My father has died.
It's meaningless.
Now that you have the thought,
I won't force you.
Thank you for
saving me today.
Bainian,
let's go.
Wait a sec.
I'll go with you.
There's no room for me here.
It's meaningless for me to stay here.
Xuanxuan,
I...
I also...
I also wanna go to the State of Sha with you.
So does Changqing.
Right?
Nope.
Well,
why?
I can't let you go with me this time.
We won't be able to help you, won't we?
It's I who don't wanna put you in danger again.
Nope. Xuanxuan.
You can't say anything like that.
We're close friends.
Let him go.
Young Master has already mastered the extraordinary power.
I think when he encounters something difficult later,
he can absolutely deal with it better than I.
Okay.
If I can come back safely,
we'll have a reunion.
Take care.
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
Let's go.
You’re awake.
You look
much better today.
Prince Mu, thanks for taking good care of me.
Have this, please.
I can have it by myself.
How soon will we arrive in the State of Sha?
It will take at least over ten days to
get to the border city of the State of Sha, Shiye City from here.
If we wanna catch up with the siren of Kunwu,
we'd better hurry.
This is Shiye City.
When we get into Shiye City,
it means we've arrived in the State of Sha.
Miss Su,
it's merely an unimpressive city now,
but ten years ago,
it was the busiest city on the border
of Tianqi and the State of Sha.
What has happened over these years?
It's depressed.
Old bastard.
Military Official.
It's time to pay the money.
Military Official,
could you please extend the deadline two more days?
Stop your nonsense.
If you don't pay the money today,
I'll smash your stall.
Military Official,
I do wanna pay the money,
but I have no money with me.
You have no money with you?
Don't talk with him anymore.
Smash his stall.
Smash it. Smash it. Smash it.
Military Official. Military Official, please stop.
Go away.
Military Official, I'm just running the small business.
Your Highness.
Please don't smash my stall.
Hurry and get away.
Hurry and stand up.
Thank you, Childe.
Welcome.
Please come in.
This way. This way. This way.
Please.
Sit down, please. Sit down, please.
Please wait a moment.
I'll go make a pot of tea for you.
Bring some tea.
I'm coming.
I heard that
some other trade caravans were withheld several days ago.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Now Shiye City has almost become
the territory of the State of Tianqi.
These military officials of Tianqi come to levy taxes every year.
Some businessmen like us
are blackmailed one after another.
Prince Mu,
why does Tianqi come to levy taxes in Shiye city?
Miss Su,
you have no idea about it.
Since when the Clan of Human Being
won the battle between
the Clan of Kunwu and them ten years ago,
the emperor of Tianqi has planned to
swallow up our State of Sha.
The late emperor of Sha was still alive in those years.
So,
he mapped out a strategy
while mediated with Tianqi,
which protected our state from being merged.
But
the price we had to pay
was to sign some unequal treaties.
There's one among them,
which says the border of the State of Sha should be unguarded
and the soldiers of Tianqi are allowed to get into the State of Sha without limitation.
No wonder I've seen
so many soldiers of Tianqi
walking in the streets of Shiye City.
Military Official,
what do you want?
Back off.
Scram. Scram.
Go away. Go away. Go away.
Please.
Your clothes look great.
Where are you from?
He's asking you.
Haven't you heard him?
It's fine. It's fine.
You look pretty.
Have a cup of tea with me.
Loosen your grip.
There's someone who don't dare to die.
Haven't you asked around?
Catch him.
I'm He Xiongfei. I'm sorry for coming here and saving you so late.
Your Highnes, please forgive me.
General He, stand up please.
Your Highness. Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, please help us.
Those soldiers of Tianqi have gone too far in bullying us.
They racketeer us every day.
Besides, they also hurt my guests.
What they've done is no less than the brigandage.
Yeah.
Your Highness.
Please punish those atrocious Tianqi soldiers on behalf of us.
We've been going through a hard time.
He Xiongfei,
listen to me.
Yes.
Give out my order that
from today onwards,
we should put things straight.
The border defence should be established in Shiye City.
If the soldiers of Tianqi get into the State of Sha without any reason,
kill them immediately.
Your Highness,
it's...
From today onwards,
our State of Sha won't be bullied and oppressed by Tianqi.
If any soldier dares to invade,
kill him.
Yes.
I'll obey your order.
Your Highness brings benefits to the people.
We hope Your Highness all happiness.
Your Highness,
are you worrying about what happened in daytime?
Batou,
is it baffling to you
why I announced the order
to establish the border defence today all in a sudden?
You don't want the people to suffer anymore,
so you have to give such an order.
But
not establishing the border defence is the agreement come to by the late emperor
and Tianqi.
If we breach the agreement unilaterally,
I'm afraid
the State of Tianqi won't
let us go so easily.
Exactly.
But
the cities in Tianqi are in chaos.
On the one hand, they have to prevent the Dragon Emperor from escape.
On the other hand, the competition between Loong Wei'er and the crown prince for the throne
is getting fiercer and fiercer.
Besides, Xiao Fengming who is manipulated by the demon spirit
has made such a huge mess in Qingtian City.
Even if the emperor of Tianqi wants to pick up a fight against our State of Sha,
he might not be able to do it.
Your Highness,
you've planned all of these things.
But the most important thing for me
is to give the Saintess Stone to Youlian
to awake the Dragon Emperor.
Then
the crisis of our State of Sha
will be resolved thoroughly.
Your Highness,
it's well roasted.
Thank you.
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
Are you sure?
It's I who get you into trouble.
If I didn't get you into trouble,
you wouldn't have to be here with me.
Right.
If I knew you would bring me such a big trouble,
I must have...
What a pity!
You couldn't have known it.
If I knew you would bring me such a big trouble,
I would save you anyway.
Why?
I would save my friend without any precondition.
Your Highness,
you do want the antidote, don't you?
Give it to me.
No.
Why do you want it?
You should have known it.
Why do you wanna do this?
Do you know how dangerous being a woman again will be?
I've been disguising myself as a man for too long. I'm exhausted.
Now,
I finally get rid of the control of the Tianqi Emperor.
I don't have to disguise myself anymore.
Bainian,
give it to me.
Is it because you have a thing for Li Xuan?
So you wanna...
How dare you?
Don't try to guess my thought,
even though you've been working for me for years.
I'm wrong.
Why is there a woman
having a bath here?
It's Loong Wei'er.
Seen from
his shadow,
he does look like a girl.
The birthmark?
The baby is too miserable.
Her mother gave birth to her yesterday,
while her father wanted to abandon her
because she was a girl.
Her mother found someone to escort her out.
And she was robbed on her way.
The baby is too miserable.
Is
he’s that baby?
It couldn't happen.
He's a man.
The one I saw in the place of Grandpa Elder of the Book of Heaven
was a baby girl.
Why are you looking at me?
Nothing.
If you have questions for me,
go ask me.
You're a man or a woman?
Nope.
I...I...
I mean,
since...since you're a woman,
why do you disguise yourself as a man all the time?
It's because of what happened eighteen years ago.
At that time,
my father had just succeeded to the throne.
A fortune teller told him
if a princess was born in the imperial palace,
she would bring calamity to the state and people.
So...
Your Highness.
Maid.
I...
I'm afraid...
Her Highness is about to give birth.
Someone, help.
Bring some hot water. Hot water. Hurry up.
Sure. Towel.
Come on.
Imperial Concubine Xie is about to give birth.
Send someone to watch her.
Yes.
Your Highness,
it's a princess.
A princess.
Your Highness, something is wrong.
Eunuch Zhou is coming here with some guards.
What should we do?
We should hurry.
Let me hug my baby.
Maid,
hurry and escort the princess out of the imperial palace
and to the place of her uncle.
Ask him to save her anyway.
Yes, Your Highness.
The emperor is so cautious.
How could you go back?