Dance of the sky Empire
Episode 4
In the first year of the State of Tianqi,
there was a big battle between the Clan of Kunwu and Human Being
in the Fengwei Valley.
Over a long period,
the Clan of Kunwu had ridden roughshod over our Clan of Human Being.
Besides, the Dragon Emperor of Kunwu was being cruel and violent,
which made our Clan of Human Being live in an abyss of misery.
On the battlefield in the Fengwei Valley,
facing with the cruel Dragon Emperor,
troops of our clan were courageous.
the battle remained deadlocked
due to the inherent spiritual power of the Dragon Emperor, Shi Xingyu.
Later, Lord Zi used his spiritual power to set up a formation.
In the formation,
Lord Zi attacked the Dragon Emperor
by soil, fire and thunder.
Right at the last attack of Lord Zi,
Jiu Ling'er, the Saintess of Kunwu,
transformed to an iced cocoon to protect the Dragon Emperor.
Dragon Emperor.
Sister.
This is the Dragon Emperor's Sword.
The Dragon Emperor and my sister…
Finally you wake up.
Who are you?
I am the spirit of this sword.
You're the sword spirit?
Take me to save them now!
We can't go to save them for the time being.
Then I can't see the Dragon Emperor
and my sister anymore.
Don't talk like this.
The Dragon Emperor is just confined to the icy cocoon of the Spiritual Queen.
As long as the Saintess moved the holy stone,
she can break the icy cocoon
and wake up the Dragon Emperor.
You are the last saintess of Kunwu clan
with the holy stone,
so
you're taking the responsibility of saving the Dragon Emperor
and reviving Kunwu.
Is it true that I can use this holy stone to save the Dragon Emperor?
This holy stone
was magically transformed from the first saintess's eyes
with great spiritual power.
Now
you
and this holy stone
are the only hope of our Kunwu clan.
What can I do?
From now on,
I will be your master.
You must practice Kung fu hard
until the Dragon Emperor is successfully saved.
Do you remember my words?
Master.
It's covered with ice and snow here.
Why do you take me here?
Youlian.
Come here.
Hurry!
Come on, hurry up.
Youlian.
See it?
Yes.
This is the fortune of our Kunwu clan.
If you don't work hard to save the Dragon Emperor,
the people of our clan
will be oppressed by the human clan forever.
The rise and fall
of the whole Kunwu clan
is on your shoulder.
Are you clear?
In the end,
the human clan won.
The Saintess Jiu Ling'er cursed that,
in ten years,
the Dragon Emperor would wake up
and the human clan would definitely die out.
The deadline is near.
In case that Jiu Ling'er's curse comes true,
so
everyone present here must study hard
to be a useful person of our country
to protect our human clan
kill all the rest of the Kunwu clan.
So boring!
Can't you be quiet?
Someone is sleeping.
Li Xuan.
I'm having a lesson.
How dare you sleep?
You. Li Xuan.
Stand up.
What's up?
Li Xuan.
Tell me
what I said just now.
It's not interesting.
It's all about the event
between the human clan and the Kunwu clan.
What did he do to you?
Why do you want to kill them all?
Li Xuan. Li Xuan.
As the Nation-protecting master,
how could you speak for the Kunwu clan?
Do you know
it's impossible for both the human clan and the Kunwu clan to exist together?
Many years ago,
the Kunwu clan oppressed the human clan,
making the human clan live in great misery.
Fortunately,
Lord Zi practiced the Moon-fall formation,
found the Dragon Emperor's weakness
and sealed him.
Thus we can live a peaceful and prosperous life.
You've just lived good days.
How could you talk a lot of nonsense?
Mentor.
Li Xuan just got confused,
so he talked nonsense.
Don't take it seriously.
I didn't see the Kunwu clan
oppress the human clan,
while I saw the human clan oppress the Kunwu clan,
forcing them to the extremely cold areas,
even making them puppets.
This is what I saw.
Please teach us national history lessons.
Teach us something convincing,
OK?
You.
Li Xuan. Li Xuan.
You're really stubborn!
Get out!
Mentor.
OK.
Li Xuan.
Changqing. You…
Mentor.
They are so unreasonable.
Hmm.
I will go to get them back.
I'm leaving now.
Xuanxuan.
You are so bold in the class.
Aren't you afraid that Mentor
tell your father and your master?
I can't get out if I didn't do that.
Besides,
the old man said those words every day,
I've heard enough of it.
I just worry that your father
may punish you later.
Changqing can deal with it.
Let's go back to sleep in the dormitory.
I will also show you
my carefully-designed revenge plan.
OK.
Let's go.
That's all.
Today we'll stop here.
Go back to review the lessons carefully.
Goodbye. Mentor.
Youlian.
What are you thinking of?
Let's go.
Let's go to have academic lessons.
Ten years' time is nearly up.
The Dragon Emperor is going to wake up.
The human clan will be in danger.
You're taking the responsibility of
preventing the Dragon Emperor from waking up.
So
from today,
I will teach you
how to cultivate spiritual power and use magical tricks.
The Kunwu clan are born
with ability to control the natural power..
Amazing!
While the human clan
has to cultivate constantly
to improve our ability to control the nature power
Awesome!
Yeah!
Unbelievable!
The power of your magical tricks
is up to the cultivation of your own spiritual power.
Mentor in Chief.
What about the formation?
Different from magical tricks,
formation is just used to contain and seal
as well as other functions.
It's not the same with magical tricks,
which are very aggressive.
OK.
Have you seen what I did?
Practice now.
Idiot.
I'm wondering how you were admitted to our school?
Be quiet.
Focus.
Attentive.
I have a stomachache.
Class is over.
Let's go.
Miss Su.
You are…
Ordered by His Highness,
I'm here to give you the invitation.
His Highness wants to invite you to have tea-tasting.
Time and place is on the invitation.
Please don't be late
to make His Highness wait for long.
On the bank of the Lotus lake.
Youlian.
His Highness invites you to have tea-tasting on the back of the Lotus lake.
Yanran. Come here.
She just stayed with him for a night.
Now she was invited to have tea-tasting.
Don't go with her
in case you become a bad girl.
Please go back to tell His Highness
that I'm sure to go there on time.
OK.
Yanran.
I'm leaving first.
Let's go.
This way, please. Miss Su.
Your Highness.
Miss Su comes.
Invite her in.
Yes.
Please.
Miss Su.
Your Highness.
Sit down, please.
I just made the tea for you.
Have a taste.
Thank you!
That day,
your excellent dance
really made me amazed.
Just so-so.
I just dance casually.
A casual dance is so amazing.
What if you dance by heart?
It must be very brilliant.
Miss Su.
A month later,
many states will come to visit our country.
At that time there will be a dance competition.
I want to invite you to dance in front of the palace
to show our national prestige.
Do you agree?
In front of the palace?
Need I go to the Royal Palace?
Yes.
If you can beat all the dancers
from other surrounding states
to win the first place,
at that time,
you will have high position and great wealth.
No matter what you want,
my father will present you with it.
Anything is OK, right?
Of course.
The whole country belongs to my father.
As long as my father is happy,
it will be easy for you
to have anything you want.
If so,
I can ask the Tianqi Emperor
to present me the number one token.
Ok. I can go there.
Very good.
This cup of tea is cold.
Don't drink it.
Let's change another one.
Assassinator.
Protect me.
Li Xuan. You asshole!
I know it's you who did it.
Come out!
How could you design to kill me?
I won't forgive you.
Are you OK?
What's wrong with me?
Why am I here?
It's bad.
Lord Zi.
Bad news.
There is abnormal phenomena in the city.
OK.
Immediately.
Keep a strict vigilance over the whole city.
Yes.
Wait a moment.
Check the Moyun Ancient Academy as well.
Check by yourself.
Yes.
Go
to take my clothes to get me dressed.
Your Highness.
You haven't recovered yet.
The imperial doctor told that
you should lie in bed to have a rest.
How bold you are!
I told you
to take my clothes here.
Didn't you hear me?
I must go to the Moyun Ancient Academy
to cut off Li Xuan's head
to make a ball to play with.
Quickly.
Your Highness.
You can leave now.
Mr. Li, why are you here?
Your Highness, you haven't recovered.
Why are you so angry?
It's because of Li Xuan.
He wanted to bury me alive last time
while I was not suitable dressed.
Unexpectedly, he sent some people to assassinate me this time.
Does he hate to live?
Do you think Li Xuan did it?
It must be him.
Besides him,
who is so bold?
Your Highness.
Think it over.
Li Xuan and you have been enemies since you were young.
When he bullied you,
he didn't ask others to do it.
Your Highness.
Please don't mind.
You often bully him.
Li Xuan is good for nothing.
If he wants to bully me,
of course he will ask others to do it.
It's no good for Li Xuan
to kill you.
It's unnecessary for him to do so.
I think another person was more likely to do so.
Assassinating you
is good
for him.
I see.
What?
They are all dead.
Yes.
No one is alive.
I'm wondering
when the prince has such a capable assistant
who can beat all the twenty superiors
that we sent.
I did look down upon him.
Your Highness.
What should we do the next.
Bury the corpse.
Don't make others see it.
Yes.
Li Xuan.
I'm having a bath.
What's up?
I know.
You want to watch me bathe secretly.
So you come here, right?
Tell me
why you sent people to assassinate His Highness and me.
You're so bored being like this.
You just want to watch me bath, right?
Come in.
You can come in to have a look.
Tell me
why you sent people to assassinate His Highness and me.
Enough!
You're playing cat and mouse?
Look at them by yourself.
Here is the evidence.
Don't pretend in front of me.
I did write them..
Does it have anything to do with you?
Changqing.
It's so bad.
The mark.
Childe.
The whole city is on the alert.
The killer of the Kunwu clan sneaked into the Qingtian city.
It's too bad.
Touched by water, Saintess's mark will appear.
In the academy,
master can't appear to help me.
What can I do?
All the students gather on the playground.
Overall search.
Emergency muster.
What happened?
What's wrong?
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Quickly.
What a sudden!
Who knows?
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Quickly.
Is everyone here?
It seems that Youlian isn't in the academy the whole afternoon.
What a coincidence!
Why did the event happen
when she wasn't in the academy?
In my view,
Su Youlian is a suspect.
Hey, don't talk casually.
Lord Xie.
Only Su Youlian isn't here.
What's wrong?
Eh.
I'm coming.
Youlian.
What's wrong with you?
You look so pale.
What do you wear?
Why is your head wrapped?
OK.
Everyone is here.
Let's check now.
Emergency.
There are actions of the Kunwu clan in the city.
Emergency muster.
Everyone must get out now.
Be ready to get checked.
Mentor Xie.
How did Lord Zi think?
It's natural to have a though check in the city.
Don't you know us?
Lord Zi ordered to do so.
As the important place to suppress the Dragon Emperor,
it's obvious that our Moyun ancient academy should set an example.
So much nonsense.
Xuanming.
I'm here.
Take all the people
to check all the guards and servants in the academy.
Yes.
Li Xuan.
Check all the students.
I won't do that.
Why should I do that?
You're the nation-protecting master.
You also have the number one token.
Nobody is more suitable than you.
So it is.
This is the Xuyu Mirror.
How to do with my ears?
Li Xuan.
Check carefully.
So ugly!
Su Youlian.
Why are you sweating abnormally?
Are you guilty?
Just confess it.
Don't lose our time.
Sister, what are you talking?
What? Can't I say something?
Her head is wrapped.
It must be strange.
Stand well.
Why do you check me?
Check her.
Look. She is…
Stand aside.
You haven't finished checking me.
You sister is more lovely than you.
Check what happened to her.
What's wrong with her face?
What's wrong with your head?
How could it be like this?
It's nothing.
When did you get hurt?
Was it just now…
See?
I thought there was something wrong with her head.
Li Xuan.
Use the mirror to see her.
Hurry up.
Otherwise I will do it for you.
We're all waiting here.
We have been checked.
Why don't you check Su Youlian?
Yeah.
Yes. Yes.
I can't expose myself here.
Master.
Dragon Emperor.
Who can help me?
Stop checking.
No need to check.
Eunuch Yang.
Why do you come here?
Under the command of Her Majesty,
I'm here to send Miss Su some medicine.
Eunuch Yang.
What happened?
Today His Highness
and Miss Su were having tea on the bank of the lake
when they were attacked by killers,
narrowly escaping.
Luckily, Miss Su helped
to save His Highness
to make him safe.
So
Her Majesty ordered me
to send some tonics to Miss Su.
Youlian. Youlian.
Eh. Eh.
What's wrong with her?
She faints suddenly.
Take it.
Let's go.
Get out of the way.
Why are you so hurt?
You wake up.
You’re hurt…
Don't touch me.
Rest early.
I'm leaving.
Believe it or not,
I didn't send anybody to kill you and His Highness.
If I really wanted to do that,
I wouldn't make others do it.
Don't touch it.
Master. It aches.
It's bleeding.
You gouged out the mark.
Of course it won't recover soon.
If it can't stop bleeding tomorrow,
the foxy human clan is certain to discover it.
What can I do?
It would be good if it was in Kunwu.
The spiritual herb for hemostasis In Kunwu must be useful.
In the east of Qingtian city, there is a mountain
where many of the spiritual herbs of Kunwu clan grow.
Maybe the spiritual herb for hemostasis can be found there.
Really?
I start off to go there now.
Your spiritual power has been damaged.
Be careful.
I know it, master.