Dance of the Sky Empire
Episode 8
What an annoying guy.
What did I come for?
I came to take the token.
Come on!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Why were you touching me?
I, I just
Just what?
♫Suddenly, your eyes meet mine♫
♫I have nowhere to hide♫
♫I can't express it in details♫
♫My heart beats faster♫
♫How lucky I am♫
♫to be by your side♫
♫I haven't had time to think♫
♫Extraordinary♫
♫The wild horse in my dream wakes up♫
♫Without curb♫
♫it runs wild♫
♫Like rays of♫
♫light of love,♫
♫gleaming in my eyes♫
♫Like a number of♫
♫gentle edges♫
♫afraid of nothing because of you♫
♫The first love blossoms like a flower♫
♫Its root goes deeply into the soil♫
♫You are the best medicine♫
♫to eradicate my confusion♫
Do you like him?
His Highness from State of Sha.
Yes.
I also like Yunshan,
Yanran,
Xiao Fengming,
Bian Lingcheng.
I like everyone in the Academy.
What about me?
You didn't mention me.
You are the most annoying one.
♫Like rays of♫
♫light of love,♫
♫gleaming in my eyes♫
♫Like a number of♫
♫gentle edges♫
♫afraid of nothing because of you♫
♫The first love blossoms like a flower♫
♫Its root goes deeply into the soil♫
♫You are the best medicine♫
♫to eradicate my confusion♫
What's the matter with me?
Why does my heart beat so fast?
Do I…?
Well,
since you aren't in the mood to learn,
that's all for today.
You're free to go.
Yeah! The class is over!
Wait a minute, guys.
I have something to announce.
It has been a while since you came to Moyun Ancient Academy.
There will be a history exam
a few days later.
Only students who pass it can continue to stay here.
Why?
Yes, why?
why?
History is the base of doing research.
After studying here over these days,
if you still gain nothing,
you're not qualified to be students of Moyun Ancient Academy,
let alone becoming
pillars of Tianqi's future.
Crap.
What can we do?
Oh no. Oh no. Oh no.
We are to take an exam.
If we fail it, we have to leave.
I'll be happy about that.
That's what I want.
Look at all those on the blackboard.
Oh no. Oh no.
Master only taught me swordsmanship.
I know nothing about the history of Tianqi State.
If I fail the exam,
I have to leave.
If so, it will be impossible to save Dragon Emperor.
Don't worry.
Mr. Xuanming doesn't know magic arts.
As long as we play some tiny tricks,
we will pass the exam for sure.
And
by the way,
never think of using magic arts to cheat.
Besides me,
Mento in Chief Xie will also invigilate the exam.
brother
what should I do?
Stay up to recite.
Xiao Fengming,
I depend on you this time.
What do you mean?
You are so knowledgeable.
History is just a piece of cake to you.
During the exam, you only need to give me...
You know.
No. No. No.
If Mr. Xuanming and Mr. Xie notice that, I will be punished.
Don't worry.
I won't let them know.
What do you want to eat?
You can choose whatever you like.
Choose whatever you like at the canteen.
How about that?
I can choose whatever I like?
Sure.
Youlian,
how will you cope with the exam?
No idea at all.
What are you going to do?
I have no choice
but to go over the lessons.
Me too.
If I fail the exam,
my father will be upset.
Let's go.
I can barely keep my eyes open.
Yanran, let's go back.
I'm drifting off.
Youlian, will you go with us?
I want to stay here for a while.
Don't stay up too late.
Fine. Fine. Fine.
I'll leave it for tomorrow.
It's too dark outside. I'm scared.
You take me back.
Youlian,
don't you go with us?
I want to stay here for a while
to read books.
Miss Su, see you.
Tianqi State's history is too difficult to learn.
If I knew this before,
I wouldn't come here.
The wine. The night.
It's late now. Why is the light still on?
Let's go.
Everyone,
you must get finished
before this incense burns up.
It's not allowed to talk to each other,
peek others' answers,
let alone cheat.
Mr. Xuanming invited me
to serve as invigilator here today.
I hope there won't be
magic arts during the exam.
Understand?
Yes.
Good.
Now the exam begins.
You can get to your answer sheets.
Don't look around.
Li Xuan,
why do you stand up?
I've finished.
Let me see.
No way.
Naughty boy.
I'm free to go.
Li Xuan.
Mr. Xuanming.
This character differs from that in my state.
I don't know what it means.
Give it to me.
Get out. Get out.
Yunshan,
some characters aren't familiar to you as well, right?
Mr. Xuanming, I can read them.
That's good.
Continue with your test.
Every one of you
has passed the exam.
You can stay here to learn.
Hooray!
Let's go out to drink tonight. It's my treat.
Perfect.
Be quiet. Be quiet.
Everyone,
Moyun Ancient Academy strives to train national backbone.
Hope you can study hard
and won't let the public down.
Yes.
Thank you, Mento in Chief Xie. Thank you, Mento in Chief Xie.
Well,
you are free to go.
Great!
Hooray!
Let's go.
What's wrong?
It seems that young master is playing the xun.
It's late now. Why does he do that?
Perhaps it's because I'm not with him. So he suffers from insomnia.
He wants me to be with him when he sleeps.
What?
He wants you to be with him when he sleeps?
It's not like what you think.
Do you know what I think?
Young master told me he would have nightmares at midnight.
He would see his mother's tragic death in dreams.
So he wants to talk with someone after waking up.
Lord Zi,
do you know how young master's mother died?
Changqing,
do you remember what I told you
to do by Li Xuan's side?
You told me to protect young master.
That's good.
Just do what you should do.
Don't ask
what you shouldn't ask.
Well,
it's late now.
Go back to have a rest.
Yes, Lord Zi.
Do you like him?
His Highness from State of Sha.
Yes.
I also like Yunshan,
Yanran,
Xiao Fengming,
Bian Lingcheng.
I like everyone in the Academy.
What about me?
Why do I always think of Li Xuan?
Go to sleep.
Quickly.
Ma... master.
Have you got the token?
Token...
Not yet.
It's because you are too obsessed with humans' life
and forget all about
the number one token.
No.
It's an important issue. How can I forget it?
Really?
Youlian,
are you in love with
that guy?
What?
How come, master?
I'm not.
That's good.
Remember,
you are irreconcilable with Li Xuan.
If you are in love with him,
everyone in Kunwu clan
will have grudge against you forever.
I'm wiped out.
Every day I practice dancing for
the Assembly of States. My waist aches.
What did you order?
None of your business.
I want to eat that drumstick.
Youlian, Yanran,
here, here, here.
Here, here, here.
Come and have a seat here.
Where are you going?
You are enjoying yourself here.
It's a bit cold there.
And,
here you are.
Remember,
you are irreconcilable with Li Xuan.
If you are in love with him,
everyone in Kunwu clan
will have grudge against you forever.
I don't like it. Please leave it to yourself.
No.
I can order a second one.
Have it.
No.
Soup.
Here you are.
Miss Cui,
have you smelt something?
What?
The stinky smell of love.
Xuan,
are you to abandon me?
Get off me.
Have the soup.
I'm full. See you.
Youlian.
What's the matter with her?
It's all your fault.
You should not mention the love stuff.
Where are you going?
Go to find Youlian.
Why? Do you know who is your sister?
Mr. Zhou!
Mr. Zhou comes here?
Mr. Zhou?
What brings him here?
Miss Su.
You asked to meet me?
Yes.
Nation-protecting Master.
By the order of His Majesty,
I bring Miss Cui the clothes of Assembly of States.
Hope it can add luster to your
dance performance.
Thank you.
So exquisite!
Thanks for His Majesty's care.
Please tell His Majesty,
I will dance for the honor of Moyun Ancient Academy,
no,
of our Tianqi State.
That's great!
Assembly of States will be held in 3 days.
How can I learn new dance moves in such a short time?
You are so modest, Miss Su.
His Highness said
as long as you followed what was written in this dance book,
based on your capability,
you would be sure to stand out.
If you can defeat other dancers
from small states at border areas
and take the first place,
my father will give you
whatever you want.
As long as I take the first place at Assembly of States,
I can get the token,
in which way
Li Xuan won't get hurt as well.
Miss Su.
Please tell His Highness,
I won't let him down.
Yes, Miss Su.
Who is playing the xun?
This piece of music is so familiar.
Why does it stop?
Your Majesty.
Long live Your Majesty.
Have a seat.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Sweetheart,
have a seat.
But...
It's my order.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Xuan,
do you know anything of Long Wei'er?
Why does he sit beside His Highness?
Obviously, he is His Highness the Second.
What?
He is His Highness the Second?
The person that is on an equal footing with His Highness
can only be His Highness the Second.
I didn't know.
Fortunately,
I didn't offend him
at the Academy.
Horn locked by 5-color cloud from State of Nan.
This object gathers the spiritual qualities of 5-color lucky cloud.
It is created in Tianyao Wonderland
according to interactions among 5 elements.
The red and green gems inlaid in it
can lock the spiritual qualities in the horn.
Treasure from Western States
Wine cup made of dragon scales
Nanyang eagle on peony from Nisi State.
Dried coral from Guli State.
Ruyi of His Highness from State of Xiang.
Luminous pearl
from State of Liang.
Enough. Enough.
You can get the lid on.
Did anyone see Su Youlian?
Didn't she come in with us?
I saw her outside just now.
Just a few moments passed. Where did she go?
Where did she go?
Please enjoy the dance performances.
Xuan,
I didn't expect such a small state
have such excellent dancers.
Look at your silly face. Many dancers are better than them.
Yes. They aren't good enough.
After all, Tianqi State has a person who is much better
and prettier than them.
Am I right, Xuan?
Who is that?
Su Youlian.
She dances very gracefully.
If she could take part in
the dance battle for Tianqi State,
we would win for sure.
What a pity.
Shut up.
You are the only person who keeps moaning.
Pianran,
it will be your turn soon.
It's time to make preparations.
Bian Lingcheng,
just wait and see.
Good.
Beautiful.
These dancers are flexible and lithe.
It's truly a feast for eyes.
Tianqi State has always taken the first place
over the past 10 years.
How about the preparations for
the dance battle this time?
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
Miss Cui has made perfect preparations.
and won't let Your Majesty down.
I've also heard of
Miss Cui's dancing skills.
It's not difficult for her
to defeat dancers on the stage.
Miss Cui is as excellent as her father, Minister Cui.
Your Majesty,
you can rest assured.
The first place will belong to our state for sure.
Great!
-Beautiful. -Awesome. -Well done.
It's fantastic.
Good indeed.
Wonderful.
Great!
Great.
Good.
It's great.
It's my first time to see it.
Yes.
Great.
Beautiful.
Is everything ok?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Miss Su is ready.
Dolt.
-Perfect! -Perfect! -Prefect!
Awesome.
However capable you are, there is always someone more capable.
Yes. It's marvelous.
It's my first time to see it.
It's a feast for eyes.
-Wonderful. -Awesome.
-Perfect. -Startling. - Splendid.
It's shocking.
Congratulations to you, Your Highness.
The first place
of this time must belong to Liang.
Thank you.
I'm flattered.
Is this what your perfect preparations mean?
It's...
Your Majesty,
I've heard that dancers of Tianqi State
are the best in the world.
After enjoying today's performance, I think they deserve their reputation.
But
compared with dancers of my state,
they are slightly inferior.
Your Highness, it's too early to say that.
There are so many talented people in Tianqi State.
The performance just now is just a warm-up.
It seems that
Your Highness has prepared a surprise for us?
You'll know that soon.
Well,
I'll wait and see.
This stupid His Highness indeed has something up his sleeve.
You are
truly blood brothers,
both keeping your own counsel.
It's not just us.
What do you mean?
I've heard that Su Youlian wants to get the number one token from you.
Haven't you
suspected her identity?
There is no need to do that.
Many people want the token.
That's right.
But is there
another person
as persistent as her?
What exactly do you want to say?
Kunwu.