Father. Father.
Please make sure to protect your mother and Eun Su...
I am counting on you, Han Su.
Father!
If something happens to Father, it is all your fault, Mother!
Han Su!
- Let go.
- You can't!
Let go. Let go!
Scum like me should die! Let go!
- Let go of me!
- I'll not!
If you die, what about me? How am I going to live?
What am I going to do alone?
It is all your fault, Hyeong!
Even if I refused, you should have dragged me!
You should have nagged me
hundreds and thousands of times,
saying I need to look into
where and how my only sister is doing as her family!
That is why...
I should be the one to die.
Why would you die?
I missed her.
I could not see her face properly...
because the p-prison was too dark.
I could not see at all how my Eun Su grew up...
and what kind of an adult she became, Hyeong.
But you saw, right, Hyeong?
Of course, I saw.
I looked and looked
until I could not look anymore.
She was pretty like a flower,
bright like a star,
and her smile was...
really beautiful.
- She smiled?
- Han Su.
When she smiled, our Eun Su
looked just like when she was young.
I will be able to see her once I drop dead.
Seriously...
things just had to be so twisted.
Young Master, you are different from Minister Yu.
Your goals and your path...
Princess.
The date has been set.
Will you... marry me?
If the marriage is only to weaken my father's power,
it does not serve any meaningful purpose now, does it?
I already put down my position and in the future as well—
I need a stage.
Our wedding will be a public hearing where Minister Yu gets interrogated for his sins.
All of Minister Yu's ill deeds, corruption, and illegal acts will be brought to light.
A wedding where lots of people gather is the perfect stage.
Will you be okay...
if I use you to the very end?
No.
You are not using me, Princess.
I am going to use you from now on.
Because I want revenge.
Episode 15: A Wedding Vow
Joseon Attorney: A Morality
There have been many scandalous happenings within and outside the palace,
so I am elated to deliver such good news to you all.
It is all thanks to your grace, Grand Queen Dowager.
Congratulations, Your Highness!
This wedding is specially planned to take place at an inn in Mapo so that all of our people can watch.
I will order Internal Affairs to
prepare it perfectly and completely according to royal conduct,
so please do not worry.
I wish for all of you to attend and congratulate them.
Thank you for your grace.
Young Master Ji Seon will be marrying the princess.
Thank you. Thank you!
Congratulations.
Do not forget that this is all Minister Yu's grace and mercy!
Aigoo, no doubt about that.
He gives out so much whenever there is a happy occasion for his son.
So we can only be thankful.
Here comes Minister Yu!
All hail Minister Yu!
How was your trip, Father?
Will Minister Yu willingly accept the marriage?
He has no apparent cause to oppose it.
But we do not know what he may be scheming behind our backs.
Marriage Proposal
There is no doubt you are the best calligrapher of them all, without question.
25th of December
I am aware it is not what you want,
but I truly love Princess.
There is nothing wrong with having feelings of love for her.
I am just doing my job as your father.
Look here, Mr. Gourd.
Do you have a family?
Let us orphans have a shot together.
Where is your mouth— Is it here?
I hate gourds because I once almost died because of a gourd,
but I have taken a liking to you.
It was as you said, Your Excellency.
- Bring him here.
- Yes.
Advance Payment Welcome
Hide one there and...
Wait a second. Where should I hide this?
Yes, I am sure he will never be able to find it here.
Petition to the King by Kang Eon Jik
Advance Payment Welcome
Hey!
What is this? Huh?
You little—
Just take a look. It looks like a letter.
- Gosh, I do not care.
- Just take a look—
I do not care!
Seriously!
Are you really going to keep this up?
Why did you come back if you were going to be like this?
Did you come back to stress me to death?
How long are you going to keep this up?
I am going to stop! I will stop!
I will stop when I drop dead! When I die.
All right. Sure, here you go. Drink up.
There, drink it all. There you go.
All right, go ahead.
Would that be enough to kill you today?
There. Drink these, too. All the way.
Just what the heck is alcohol to him?
Dong Chi.
Gosh, Dong Chi.
Aigoo, Hyeongnim!
I will meet you at Wishes Inn
Dong Chi!
Yes, Hyeongnim.
You are here.
Why you little...
- Wh-Whoa—
- What happened?
I asked you what happened!
Y-You are killing me.
Han Su, calm down, okay?
If I lose you, too, Hyeong...
What am I going to do if you disappear, too?
Sir!
♫  I'll always be with you  ♫
♫  On the day we held hands  ♫
♫  I always remember  ♫
♫  The moment I first saw you  ♫
Everyone, please bring the stuff piled up in the backyard.
Y-Yes.
♫  I knew  ♫
♫  That our time exists in the same space  ♫
I told him this was the only way to wake you up.
♫  Even if it hurts like crazy  ♫
It was all my idea.
♫  Stay by your side  ♫
♫  Even if the cold wind blows  ♫
I missed you.
And I was worried.
♫  Can't you come one step closer to me?  ♫
♫  I'm waiting for you here  ♫
About Eun Su...
So Won...
let us not talk about that.
How long do you plan to turn a blind eye?
Why on Earth... Why did you do it? Why?
Hit me more.
I am sure it will not be enough to calm your anger...
or bring Eun Su back to us...
but it will help me to live on.
I am sorry, Kang Han Su.
Although it is shameless of me to apologize to you...
I am sorry.
Eun Su was also...
a precious and dear person to me.
A-Aigoo, where are you headed?
I have mountains of work to do.
We left the palace using marriage as an excuse.
I should report something to prevent the Grand Queen Dowager from becoming suspicious.
Wait! So what?
What do you mean by that?
I need to go to the market to buy chestnuts, dates, and blue and red strings
to put on the table of the bride and groom.
Hey, w-wait a second.
In that case...
you will need someone to carry stuff, right?
All right, then. I will take that as a yes.
Now, let us go.
Oh, how have you been?
You are here, Innkeeper Hong?
Your business is doing well these days, right?
- Innkeeper Hong, come over here.
- Aigoo— Hey, wait—
So my dear Innkeeper Hong can go anywhere and
overcome any walls and...
What was it again?
Aigoo, excuse me. I-I will come again next time.
All right. Ta-da.
Here. Honk, honk!
Aigoo, they are pretty.
- How much are they?
- That would be three nyang.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
I am touched.
They are yours.
She is my woman.
Kang Eun Su Memorial Tablet
I will protect you.
I will ensure you can live an ordinary and happy life like others, in a safe place.
I will do that for you.
Kang Eon Jik Memorial Tablet
Lady Lee Memorial Tablet
Kang Eun Su Memorial Tablet
Eun Su knew it before she left.
Knew what?
That I am deeply in love with you.
Therefore, I am sure she was assured as she passed.
Kang Eun Su Memorial Tablet
Mother and Father, you can see, right?
Eun Su, you can see, right?
What is this?
Just stay still.
There. I am going to hold onto Kang Han Su's hand tightly like this
and will be by his side until death.
So do not worry about a thing and rest in peace.
Thank you. All right, please help yourselves.
Have some cinnamon punch with pine nuts.
Three nuts for each.
Let me come with you!
So what are you two planning to do?
I have been investigating the case of Minister Chu in secret.
If you just testify and say you saw Minister Yu killing Minister Chu at the wedding,
I will not punish you for framing Kang Han Su.
We need your help.
Since the King and all of his royal subjects will have gathered,
what better public hearing place can we ask for?
I will think about it if Kang Han Su asks me.
I have quite a debt to repay to him.
Grand Merchant Jo was being clever, knowing how I went into hiding.
Looks like he used me as an excuse to get out of this.
Just in case, Chu Sal is watching Grand Merchant Jo.
If something happens, we will be notified right away.
I will know if he is sincere or not once I meet him in person.
By the way, the two of you have got a lot of guts.
Planning to expose your father or father-in-law's ill deeds on the day of your wedding...
People might even call you immoral. Are you not afraid?
Also, our So—
Prin—
Princess So...
Well, the royal family's dignity and authority, both of which she cherishes, will be tarnished.
Do not worry about the royal family.
We need to weaken Minister Yu's power, which neither the king nor the grand queen dowager
were able to deal with,
even if it means holding a funeral instead of a wedding ceremony.
I need to be prepared for that much.
As Princess is making a decision for the royal family,
I am also making a decision for my family.
Making Father stop so he will not commit any more sins
is the best I can do.
Well...
if we have this much support, we will succeed this time.
So Won, it will be better for you to enter the palace in advance.
If you are away for too long, people will start getting suspicious.
You said you would meet Grand Merchant Jo, though.
We will be fine by ourselves.
- I will come with you.
- No.
That will only cause Minister Yu to find out.
Let us go.
Be safe.
Wait for me.
What in the world?
What in the world just happened here?
Die!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey!
You!
- What is going on?
- Where is Merchant Jo?
I have no idea what is going on!
Some men just barged in and took away Grand Merchant Jo.
What?
H-Help me...
Help me! Is anyone out there!
There is a man here!
There is something over there!
Grand Merchant, Sir!
Chu Sal...
Don't come too close.
Chu Sal!
Watch out!
Dong Chi!
Hey!
Hey! Hey, hey, Dong Chi!
Dong Chi! Hey, hey!
Hey, hey! Get up!
Wake up!
- Dong Chi, wake up! Wake up!
- Hyeongnim...
Hyeongnim.
No!
I'll have to shorten the sleeve.
It's okay. Do not waste your energy on something unnecessary.
What do you mean unnecessary?
It is your once-in-a-lifetime wedding.
Later.
- Princess.
- Come in.
Minister Yu is here to see you.
What did you say?
Do you want to save him?
Sir!
Yes?
What is going on?
I thought I would never see you again.
What has happened?
Well...
Watch out!
No!
Are you all right?
Well, for now. Dong Chi, run, run!
Wait!
Wait a minute!
Wait.
This is exhausting! I'm dying here!
I can't do it! I'm dying!
I can't go on. Too tired.
I'm dying.
This is nuts!
Who are you?
You do not expect them to answer you, do you?
Did you just speak down to me?
Our heads are about to roll. Who cares about speaking down to you, huh?
What the hell are you two doing?
Now!
Get them!
Let us go.
They're gone...
They're all gone. Gone...
Let's go!
To where?
To rescue Yu Ji Seon.
Hurry and come!
Geez, I almost peed in my pants.
Mayor Yu! Mayor Yu!
Are you all right?
Hyeongnim! Hyeong—
Mayor Yu!
I am okay.
What do you mean?
The poison has spread a lot. Let us go to the pharmacy first.
This works out.
Just use me.
In whatever way works for you.
It is an antidote.
Is it really? How did you get this?
Minister Yu had come to see me.
I think he tried to lure me away
saying you got hurt so I'd miss the wedding.
No!
Stay back.
What do we do now?
He said to use him, so be it.
- Dong Chi!
- Yes, coming!
It is the letter that my father had sent to the late King.
The one that was stolen from you.
It is the last gift that our Eun Su had left behind for us.
I, Kang Eon Jik...
write this letter to you, Your Majesty.
There are people who seem to live above the law.
They are the ministers of the Hungu Party who lead Joseon at the moment.
Please turn over a new leaf and end the politics of strife and polarization.
So this is what the letter said.
Would we be able to bring down Minister Yu with this?
Probably so.
Did you not notice anything special?
Anything special?
Yeah.
Petition to the King by Kang Eon Jik
You got it.
I intend to... use that element.
Wh-Who is there?
Princess Yeon Ju found out about Legal Officer Kang's incident.
I trust that all of you will work with me once again.
He is getting dressed.
I will bring him with me on time.
Wishes Inn
Gosh, I am looking forward to this.
By chance, did you receive the letter?
I received it, too.
I have no idea what he is thinking!
How many times have we heard this same music?
I know, right?
They should have started the ceremony already.
I could see how the bride could be delayed.
But even the groom is nowhere to be found.
Wedding Program
Minister Yu.
I'm sorry, but as for me...
Princess Yeon Ju enters!
P-Princess!
Princess!
My gosh! Princess!
Sister!
Princess! Princess!
The physician has arrived.
Let him in, and do not let anyone else in or out.
Princess needs to rest right now.
Yes.
Please enter.
P-Please...
put me to death!
Princess has been poisoned and is unconscious right now!
What?
Your Majesty, Grand Queen Dowager,
the culprit who tried to harm Princess is here in this place.
Please capture him and find out the truth and punish him harshly!
What in the world are you talking about?
The culprit is here?
Please spare us, Your Majesty!
We do not know anything about this!
Yes! We did not do this!
What do you mean you did not do this?
Then are you saying you know who has done this?
Speak up and tell the truth!
Who are you saying the culprit is?
Princess Yeon Ju found out about Legal Officer Kang's incident.
I trust that all of you will work with me once again.
The culprit is... Minister Yu!
The stage does not change. It is just that...
the charge against Minister Yu will change.
Minister Yu and the other ministers present agreed upon
and tried to assassinate the princess.
Is that true?
It is true that we did receive such a letter.
However, I did not agree to it!
It is the same with me, Sire!
What is the reason Minister Yu sent this letter to you?
W-Well...
More than a decade ago,
we were involved in a conspiracy to eliminate Legal Officer Kang, and we took out articles
that were disadvantageous to Minister Yu and us while publishing the Book of Laws.
And as the late King passed away right around that time,
he even spoke of treason and placed the blame on us.
Yes! Ever since that day, we have had no choice but to follow Minister Yu's orders!
All of that is nonsense, Your Majesty.
No!
It is all true.
I submit the letter that my father, who served as a legal officer at the time
sent to the late King as evidence of that claim.
Please take a look at the end of that letter.
Minister Yu wrote the official judgment.
Petition to the King by Kang Eon Jik
To eliminate the despair
Yi-jeol-hwa-geun?
It means to eliminate the source of trouble.
Yes.
My father wanted to prohibit special favors for personnel appointments
and limit the special benefits received by vassals of merit, among other things.
He wanted to enact policies that were disliked by the Hungu Party.
When Minister Yu found out about this, he framed my father
and caused his death.
Other than the people who are present here, people like Park Je Su, Chu Yeong Wu,
and Im Sang Ho carried out the actions according to his orders.
This is how...
Minister Yu has been eliminating people who have gone against his will.
This is entrapment, Your Majesty!
If what he is saying is true,
there is another person who is not so innocent in this place!
The last name that is written in that letter!
Si Jing...
That is Grand Queen Dowager's name that she used as a child in her parent's home!
Will you continue to go on with this kind of ridiculous interrogation
solely believing in what that man says without solid evidence?
Everything he says is true.
Royal Grandmother!
Minister Yu...
showed me Legal Officer Kang's letter and suggested that we eliminate him.
I agreed to it as well.
At the time,
I believed that doing so was for the survival of the royal family and the peace of the royal court.
I had to stop another bloodbath in the royal court!
But yet again, you dare harm Princess in this way?
How dare you try to harm my granddaughter!
Grand Queen Dowager, this is Kang Han Su's trap!
Then how would you explain that the judgment portion of this letter was written in your handwriting?
Just because it is the same handwriting, it does not guarantee that I wrote it!
If it were not you, Minister Yu...
then it is Mayor Yu.
Mayor Yu Ji Seon?
Yes.
I have read several hundred verdicts written by Mayor Yu.
When you write in Haeseo style, you use the method that is called Jangbong
where you hide the tip of the brush inward to create the brushstrokes.
However, Mayor Yu uses the calligraphic method called Nobong
which allows the brushstroke to show outward
and the trace of the tip of the brush remains on the paper.
Then...
are you saying the father and the son share the same handwriting?
February 7
The princess was aware...
That is so, Your Majesty.
Then it must be either Minister Yu or
Yu Ji Seon, who wrote this letter.
How dare you use my son to entrap me?
It is your specialty.
So what will you do?
Will you confess your crime and obey,
or will you place all the blame on your son?
How dare you!
♫  Run away  ♫
♫  We got the liar  ♫
Joseon Attorney: A Morality
We cannot fool Minister Yu by acting.
Someone must risk the danger.
You are wrong, Father.
That is why I did what I could do.
Please let me determine the punishment for Minister Yu.
Please make your decision, King!
Hear ye!
Capture Minister Yu!
♫  Run Away  ♫