You have lost, Father.
When I have not played any meaningful cards, can we really discuss who has lost or won?
At the least, there could be internal strife in the Hungu Party because of this matter.
There will be complaints about you, too.
Those who turned disloyal will be cleaned out.
Empty seats just need to be filled again.
Father.
Do not be surprised, and mark my words.
No relationship lasts forever in this world besides that of parents and children.
Do you understand?
Faithfulness and Filial Piety Throughout the Home
Young Master!
I just did not want to go home.
And I cannot go to Hanseongbu like this.
You are welcome here.
This place is your home, so please be at rest.
Do you know what?
That you are the only one who welcomes me when you see me.
You are also the only one... who greets me warmly, Young Master.
What is the matter?
Mayor Yu?
It is nothing.
Please go back inside, Young Master.
What brings you here, and for what business?
His Majesty told me that the new chief advisor incident stemmed from a saloon in Namchon.
The princess is the one who told me...
that the food in this place is really great.
But I guess she was speaking the truth.
Mayor Yu, who has a small appetite, is playing in the skirts of this place's hostess.
It is not what you think–
I do not know why I have to explain myself to you.
Because you are about to marry the princess.
I am sorry for what happened earlier.
What?
Your face is different from the one I saw earlier.
That was me.
Get out of here.
She is the one you saw.
Now, then. Please continue with your conversation.
I heard Father had saved that child's life.
Therefore, I am only looking after her, considering her as my younger sister.
Your younger sister? I see.
I knew you would not believe me, whatever I say.
Do you have anything else to say?
Why on Earth are you trying to marry her?
I mean...
whose side are you on, Mayor Yu?
Is it Minister Yu's or the princess'?
Will you reconcile the relationship between the princess and the minister with this marriage, or
are you going to take down the minister with the princess?
Before you marry her, you should first find the answer to that.
For now, I played along with your scheme.
But why did you hide earlier?
I will ask Kang Han Su directly.
I had put him in trouble before... as ordered by Minister Yu.
Therefore, I did so without realizing it.
Are you telling me you worked as Father's spy or something?
I only wanted to repay Minister Yu for his grace.
Is it not a human's moral duty to repay the grace you receive?
My father is Kang Han Su's enemy and caused his parents' death.
On top of that, he was also deeply involved in the late king's death.
Not at all. You must be mistaken, Young Master.
I would be happy if that was the case.
My son is helping your brother.
Endure just a little longer.
There will come a day you will be able to reveal the truth to your brother as well.
A scholar is only used and abandoned by politicians, just like your father!
I will also help you.
Whatever that may be, if it helps you and Young Master.
Episode 13: Nakhwa Vol. 1 - A Flower Falls
Joseon Attorney: A Morality
Gosh, a guy who is about to be married first thing in the morning...
Hey, even you think it is too much, right?
You agree it is too much, right?
Anyway, men...
What is the meaning of this? Be gone at once!
Please calm your anger, Grand Queen Dowager.
It is to take the heart of the princess that remains here.
This place needs to be gone for her to visit no longer.
Please think of the subjects who are making a living by working at the ferry dock.
Since she abandoned her status and even her name in this filthy and loud place
where everyone gathers,
no wonder she gets involved in such grotesque rumors!
An attorney?
How dare she go around with a mere middle-class attorney?
However, Grand Queen Dowager, that matter has already been—
I know.
I promised the princess to let that man live.
However, if the same issue comes to the surface again,
there will not be any mercy the second time around.
Please do not worry.
I come to this place because I must transfer the business,
but Princess has not stepped a foot here since she went back to the palace.
I promised the princess to let that man live.
Did you see a ghost or something? Why...
Are you marrying Mayor Yu... because of me?
Did Grand Queen Dowager make a hostage of me to blackmail you?
You should have told me.
How could I tell you?
You would have felt angered and betrayed already.
You know that, and yet you still do this?
If I have to marry anyway,
I wanted to marry so I could be helpful to the Royal Court, the Royal Family, and the nation.
I told you...
that is the royal family's method and the duty of a princess.
Do you know what I really hate?
Saying you will exact revenge on Minister Yu by whatever means.
Those reckless eyes telling me you can do anything and saying you will help!
Your unnecessarily tough resolve and your dangerous determination...
Do not go through with that marriage.
I will not allow it.
♫  Always be with you  ♫
♫  On the day we held hands  ♫
♫  I always remember  ♫
I did not know...
but I guess I wanted to hear that.
It is fine now since I heard it.
♫  I knew/  ♫
♫  That our time exists in the same space  ♫
So Won.
No matter what anyone says...
♫  Love you forever  ♫
you are So Won to me.
♫  Even if it hurts like crazy  ♫
♫  I will forever  ♫
And that is why I will protect you.
♫  Stay by your side  ♫
So you should... also keep your promise.
You promised me, then.
That we would become each other's cheongshimhwan.
To be together always.
♫  Can't you come one step closer to me?  ♫
♫  I am waiting for you here  ♫
♫  Hold my hand  ♫
♫  Embrace me tightly  ♫
Since I am So Won.
it is okay, right?
♫  Even if it hurts like crazy  ♫
♫  I will forever  ♫
♫  This endless road  ♫
♫  I will endure for you  ♫
♫  Can't you understand my heart?  ♫
♫  I will always be waiting for you  ♫
♫  Come back to me  ♫
♫  Embrace me tightly  ♫
You seem to be in a good mood.
R-Royal Grandmother.
Where are you coming from?
Well,
it was suffocating to stay in the palace, so...
So?
- I went to the city.
- The city?
To where and with whom?
It was...
with Mayor Yu.
Mayor Yu?
Yes.
Princess, Mayor Yu asks to see you.
Tell him to come in.
Grand Queen Dowager.
Princess.
You came at the perfect time.
Princess Yeon Ju said she was with—
You forgot to take this.
Thank you.
You will marry soon, so building your relationship by meeting often will be good.
Since you are already here, go to the garden and have a talk while gazing at the moon.
Thank you for your grace, Grand Queen Dowager.
You really helped me out just now. Thank you.
I made the right decision to come.
Yes. By the way, where did you get this?
I saw you by pure chance, Princess.
I see. I must have been running away from Royal Grandmother then, too.
Yes, that is better than her finding you with Attorney Kang.
Shall we go outside for now?
Sorry?
Our elder gave an order, so we need to pretend, at least.
It looks like Grand Queen Dowager ordered a special mission for us.
Well, it cannot be helped.
Since we are already here, let us stargaze.
Right. Did Kang Han Su tell you he met me at the saloon?
Sorry?
As I thought, he did not tell you.
He must have misunderstood the relationship between that child and me
if he did not even tell you about it.
What is your relationship with her?
I am not sure. She makes me feel as if I have a younger sister.
And that woman is in love with you, right?
How could she not love you when you treat a woman,
who was kicked out and had nowhere to go,
like a friend and a younger sister instead of saying she is lowly or unfortunate?
Is that so?
Was Kang Han Su such a being to you, Princess?
When you were So Won,
did he treat you, a broker at an inn, like a friend or a younger sister
instead of saying you are lowly or unfortunate?
I am sorry. I was only—
I know.
Love is not something one can always be returned.
I learned it thanks to that child.
It felt strange.
I have clearly lived more days, have a higher position, and own more things.
But she was always the one to console and enlighten me.
And I have always been on the receiving end.
In that case, am I mistaken to think that woman might be Minister Yu's spy?
I found out only today as well.
Looks like she told you, honestly.
It must have been hard to confess.
And I am sure she did not want me to find out that secret.
But if she was able to confess so easily...
In some way, there must be another connection between Kang Han Su and that child.
Pardon?
But she is not even a courtesan.
A woman who is connected to Kang Han Su.
I did hear he has a younger sister.
A younger sister?
Forget it. Never mind.
Look into Kang Han Su's younger sister as quickly as possible.
Yes.
Gosh, you startled me.
What now? Huh?
Where the heck did you go with the princess, huh?
Just what happened? Huh?
How did you know?
Because Hostess Hong was looking everywhere!
What is happening?
Well, we cleared up our misunderstandings, and while we were at it...
Oh, my! It is so hot. Shall we open some windows?
- It is winter right now.
- Oh, I forgot.
Huh? What is that? I have never seen it before.
- Gosh, stop changing the subject!
- Aigoo.
- O-Oh, this?
- Yes.
When you were locked up behind bars, a lady left it here.
I used all the money for your medicine, and this is what is left.
Tell me honestly. How much did you stash away?
I really spent all of it.
So Won— I mean, they are not from the princess?
No, they are definitely not.
I have never heard her voice before. It was a different woman.
Who could it be?
Well, I thought it was one of the many women who chase you.
I do have many women who like me.
There are a lot, but none of them has a lot of money.
That is true.
Is it one of my ladies then?
Sure.
- Shrimp paste Choi!
- Right.
No, no, no. She is married.
My father is Kang Han Su's enemy and caused his parents' death.
Cause internal conflict?
Yes, I heard that quite a few complaints against Minister Yu have piled up within the Hungu Party.
You must shake them up properly at times like this so that they will implode.
In order to do that,
it must be someone who has enough influence to cause significant damage to Minister Yu.
And we have a person you have been working on so far, do we not?
Your Majesty, Left State Minister Choi has arrived.
Allow him to enter.
Lately, His Majesty has sought Left State Minister's audience often.
Yes, he will pass the duties of Hall of Worthies* to the Office of Special Advisors.  (Royal Research Institute)
Therefore, he asked Left State Minister to be in charge of the Office of Special Advisors.
The Office of Special Advisors, you say?
From the lowest position to the highest position in that office,
they are all filled by Sarim Party's people.
Hence, a lot of people in the Hungu Party are also
worried Left State Minister might be allying with His Majesty and Sarim Party.
Inspector Jo Chang Wu from the Office of Inspector General
will also serve as Head of Human Resources starting today.
Dedicate your body and mind to ending the corruption regarding appointing officials.
However, Your Majesty...
for an official from the Office of Inspector General to oversee the appointment of officials
is an act of violating the exclusive rights of Human Resources.
That is true, Your Majesty.
If that happens, only those the King favors will get appointed.
There seem to exist errors in what Minister Yu and Right State Minister said.
Officials from the Office of Inspector General only audit and impeach other officials.
They are not chamberlains who are the King's ears and mouth
or messengers who deliver the King's order.
They are officials who must be the fairest and the most righteous.
For what reason are you making them out to be puppets of the King?
Could you have already forgotten the recent bribed appointment incident?
Personnel requests for border appointments
Although it was not Minister Yu's intention,
I discovered there are a lot of people who consider
bribery to be a shortcut to success, without an inch of shame in committing the act.
Therefore, I want to crack down on the corruption in Human Resources in regard to appointments.
I am not attempting to influence the appointments myself.
However, Your Majesty...
- However–
- I will dedicate my body and mind!
We will uphold your order!
I cannot believe Left State Minister clearly supported the King's order like that!
Is this not a display of his will to be standing on the King's side from now on?
I am not sure if we should just believe in Minister Yu like this.
What are you saying right now?
Frankly, we were the only ones to lose because of the land dispute.
I did feel mistreated.
It would not have been this bad if Minister Yu had been more actively engaged.
On top of that, widespread rumors say Mayor Yu is marrying Princess Yeon Ju.
If he marries into the royal family, he cannot hold a public office, either.
So Minister Yu's status is also at peril because his clever son has been his only hope.
I mean, it has been in peril for a while now.
Since Chief Advisor Park, who was his loyal servant, killed himself
and Lord Chu also passed away, we can say his limbs have been cut off.
Minister Yu's age must be coming to an end now, too.
Watch your mouth.
Have you decided to stand on the King's side?
Side, you say?
I am the King's subject, for sure.
Whose subject would I be, then?
Were we not working for Joseon in our own ways?
Therefore, I thought we had been respecting each other's will and method.
by not interfering with each other's work.
Yes, we did.
It is only right to do so.
I left something at the workshop.
There is a ledger.
It is the foundation of Minister Yu's authority and power.
Did you finish cleaning up His Excellency's room?
Yes.
Petition to the emperor: Chu Young Wu, Park Je Su received bribery...
From Legal Officer, Kang Eon Jik
Welcome home, Your Excellency.
Kang Eun Su.
Young Master.
It is you.
You were Eun Su.
Where are we going?
To Kang Han Su.
No, I cannot.
I will not ask what you were doing in Father's room and why you were carrying a dagger.
But in return, let us go to Kang Han Su.
When we get there, I will tell him to take you and leave the city
as far away and quickly as possible.
My orabeoni knows nothing.
I wish for him to continue that way.
I do not want to show myself to him in this manner.
Of course, you feel that way.
How could you, as Kang Han Su's sister...
I am sorry.
Please, just leave as you are.
So that my father cannot sin against you and your family anymore,
please...
please go somewhere far away.
It is not your fault, Young Master.
It was my fault for being foolish.
Young Master, you are different from Minister Yu.
Your goals and your path...
Thus, please do not try to bear his punishments as well, just because you are his son.
You have lost, Father.
Side, you say? I am the King's subject, for sure.
Whose subject would I be, then?
Minister Yu's age must be coming to an end now, too.
Bring someone who can die by tomorrow.
It is Minister Yu's order.
Grand Merchant, sir.
By chance...
You would not, would you?
What will a merchant not do for a profit?
Still, will you sell someone's life for profit?
There is no one in this world who deserves to die.
There are people whose deaths would be helpful.
Whether it is to their family or to the world.
Among the slaves who have committed gambling crimes,
bring one who has a debt greater than his life's worth.
And tell him I will pay him generously for his life.
I heard my name being called for the first time in over ten years.
I am so happy that person was you, Young Master.
I can see why the princess felt so much affection for Kang Han Su.
It is because she knew there was no way to repay him for how she felt.
I am like a criminal to you,
and yet, you have been so generous and kind to me.
I have received such love that I cannot repay, even with my life.
- Young Master...
- I will protect you.
I will make sure you can live an ordinary and happy life like others,
in a safe place where people call you by your name.
I will do that for you.
If that will make you feel at ease,
yes, I will do so, Young Master.
- Do you mean that?
- Yes.
However, give me some time.
I should at least say goodbye to my orabeoni.
Okay. In the meantime, I will prepare what is necessary.
Attorney for Hire
Have you come to see the attorney?
Oh, the thing is...
We do not know when he might come.
You should wait inside. It is cold outside.
You should come inside.
- You should come, it's okay!
- It is so cold outside.
You should wait inside.
Why are we stopping here?
Were we not on our way to a strategy meeting?
We were, but the weather got so cold.
If you want to go to war, you should prepare your equipment first.
What is the point of having wealth? I should use it for times like these.
- This one and this one.
- Okay.
It is silk!
- So pretty.
- What would look good on Eun Su...
Come here.
How is it? Do you like it?
If you put stripes on a pumpkin, does it turn into a watermelon?
Well, how about this?
Since your skin is fair, Eun Su,
this will look pretty on you, too.
- Do you like it?
- Yeah.
Mother, give it to me.
You should... wrap it around like this,
and if you do this a bit,
it is way prettier!
Stop it!
This is better.
What are you thinking about?
Oh, nothing.
Here you go.
What do you think of this?
I like it. It is nice.
- You like it?
- Yeah.
Excuse me, shall I show you baby clothes, too?
Sorry?
Prepare early so you do not worry later.
We are not like that!
We will come back next time to see that.
Well...
Says who?
Who says? I say so!
I mean, how is that up to you?
Is that something you can decide on your own?
Why not?
I mean, we would first have to...
- We would have to?
- M—
- M–
- M?
Are you asking because you do not know?
Well, is there a reason we would need to come together?
Pardon?
I was going to buy clothes to gift to Chu Sal's baby.
You brought your consultation fee, right?
Our attorney only works if he is paid.
Gosh, Eonni...
Feel free to look around.
Eonni!
How could you start talking about money when we just met her?
She should at least expect that much!
I mean, we heard from Han Su Orabeoni.
Law of Ming Dynasty
If someone comes for the first time, we serve them a warm cup of tea  /  Great Collection of Laws
and then proceed with the consultation!
Eonni, what are you doing right now?
I am not doing anything!
Petitions
Please just be quiet.
I am being quiet!
- Be even quieter.
- I mean, who does that?
We should give her some tea.
We need to be paid to serve her tea!
- Be quiet.
- I am being quiet.
Be even quieter.
- Eonni, this again!
- What is it!
- Be quiet.
- I am being quiet!
- Be quieter!
- Seriously...
You see! She left!
Gosh, why did she come if she did not even have money?
What! What is it?
How is this?
Well, I guess it is warm.
I did not do it so you would feel warm.
I am doing it to make you feel fluttery.
How about now?
You think this will make someone's heart flutter?
I did not do it to make your heart flutter.
I did it to make you feel warm.
Gosh, seriously!
I will personally make our baby's clothes myself.
I will change its diapers and carry it on my back.
Having tried it, it is not so bad.
So
just come to me.
It does not matter how long it takes.
If we can just be together,
it is okay even if it is not here,
and even if it is not in this lifetime.
♫  Turning back time  ♫
♫  If I see you getting farther away  ♫
♫  I'll run and call your painful name  ♫
♫  Wiping away the tears...  ♫
Me, too.
♫  ...that flow white  ♫
It does not matter if it takes a long time,
and even if it is not in this lifetime.
I would be happy, even if it were in my dreams.
♫  I missed so much I want to embrace you  ♫
I want to be with you.
♫  And convey my heart with endlessly flowing tears ♫
What is going on?
Hurry, hurry!
Move aside!
What do you mean, a murder case?
His name is Hwang Bo Geun.
He is a young official appointed as a deputy at the Office of Special Advisors.
He was found dead in the alley behind Gahaebang.
The culprit tried to cover it up as a robbery,
but after catching and interrogating him,
it was found to be a murder due to a love conflict.
Love conflict?
My apologies for having to tell you this,
but the one who died and the murderer both had relations with the same girl.
They fought over who would get the girl, and the murderer killed the other out of anger.
Not only that, but the girl was married to a nobleman.
How could such a horrible crime be committed...
But could not the Ministry of Justice take care of something like this?
The murderer who was captured says more men had relations with that girl
and is naming multiple officials who are in government positions.
Who are they?
Deputy Chief Scholar Jang Myeong Gi of the Office of Special Advisors. Deputy Jang Yoon.
Kim Yong Jae of the Office of Inspector General.
Who is this woman who had adulterous relations with these men?
We do not know her real name, but she runs a saloon in Namchon.
If it is a saloon in Namchon...
Is it that woman we know?
Minister Yu, what are you plotting?
Close the city gates!
Did something happen?
I must go to the government office to find out.
Then, I will go back and wait.
Your Excellency, will you just watch as this happens?
That child, Eun Su!
She is Legal Officer Kang's daughter.
It is about time we threw her away.
If we let that clever and bold child live any longer, she will point a knife at my neck.
By chance, did you set this up, Your Excellency?
On the off chance that His Majesty decides to dig deeper into this,
many of our people will be dragged into this!
I did this for that reason.
Those who want to live will come and kneel at my feet.
It is the criminal's house! Look for anything that might be corroborating evidence!
- Search everywhere!
- Yes, sir!
Why are you doing this?
Please let go of me.
- Ah Ri!
- Lady!
Get her!
Aigoo, Attorney Kang!
- What is going on?
- How would I know?
Supposedly, it is the owner of the saloon at the end of the street.
She is being dragged to the Royal Investigation Bureau, not the Ministry of Justice.
Maybe it had to do with the dead man in Jongro yesterday.
The dead man was a nobleman and an official of the Royal Court.
Then, it would make sense for the Royal Investigation Bureau to come!
Yeah?
His Majesty requests to meet with you urgently.
Please get in.
It appears Minister Yu has played a major hand.
He is sacrificing one of his arms for this high-level strategy.
He probably decided that it was better to use the fact that he has been caught by me.
You should not only lose your people.
Of course not. I will definitely have that girl put to death.
I should do at least that much to deal a blow to Minister Yu.
Any ideas?
Who am I?
It is the King, His Majesty. Pay your respect.
Your Majesty!
Are you really the King?
You will... surely die.
Do you have any last words?
I would like to... touch the King's face just once.
Just from looking at you, you do not seem much different from anyone else.
Your hair, eyes, skin...
You are just another person.
Why...
did so many people's blood have to be shed to establish you as king?
Why... did my parents...
have to be sacrificed so unjustly?
What a mess.
Huh?
You...
I am sorry for what happened earlier.
Huh?
That was me.
It was not you, after all.
There was no way my eyes saw wrong.
Then who was the one who was just arrested?
Is she your mistress?
Why did your mistress get arrested—
Please save us, sir.
Please save us!
My Lady.
Please save My Lady!
What is your mistress's name?
Answer me!
It is Kang Eun Su.
Why do you keep crying? Should I not go?
Gosh, do not say such a thing!
Of course, you should go. Why would you not?
They say it is the house of a nobleman.
For our household, this is a great marriage offer.
My daughter,
you cannot do anything about the family you were born into,
but you should live a different life for the remainder of your life.
Being treated well as the wife of a nobleman.
And my grandsons and granddaughters should live as nobility as well.
I am happy that I was born as the daughter of Mother and Father.
I could live forever like this if I needed to—
What is this?
How embarrassing!
- Eun Su put on makeup!
- Darn.
It is all your fault that I am getting married, Orabeoni!
I cannot stand to see your face!
Go away!
It is not makeup but a disguise!
I will always leave the door open
so that you can come home at any time.
They say that a daughter who's been married off is no longer part of the original family,
but I do not believe in that.
Eun Su, you will always be my and Father's daughter.
So if anything happens, or if your in-laws abuse you,
return home at any time, okay?
Okay, Mom.
In return, I will come when Orabeoni is not home.
Orabeoni, are you going to come and visit me?
Of course.
You really have to come.
To be honest, I am scared.
I will definitely visit you.
Promise.
I promise.
You...
Why are you...
Why are you here?
How...
Eun Su...
Eun Su!
Orabeoni.
I am sorry.
We worked with animal experts for scenes involving animals for their safety.
Joseon Attorney: A Morality
Help me save Eun Su.
I will pay a million gold if needed!
Will you really not regret it?
I am sure you have come expecting what my answer would be already.
When a person dies, supposedly, they become a star.
I will become a magnolia.
So, Orabeoni, do not cry because of me.