THIS DRAMA IS A FICTIONAL STORY
BASED ON HISTORICAL FACTS
SOME ORGANIZATIONS AND CHARACTERS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Your Highness.
You must have something important to say
considering how you came all the way here.
I'm not here for you, Your Highness.
I'm here for him.
Step aside. I am carrying a sword
from the Office of the Inspector General.
Here,
that sword is nothing special.
Let's see.
It will be
fun to watch.
I know
that you killed Jung Sa-jeong.
Who ordered you to kill him?
You will die here
if you keep your lips sealed.
But if you tell me,
I will put my position on the line
to keep you safe.
If that person is here,
point at him.
This is the only way
your life can be spared.
Say it!
Who are you to talk about killing me
or even keeping me safe?
I will figure out a way to survive myself,
so stop sticking your nose
into others' business and get lost.
Will you be able to handle
the consequences?
Your Highness will be the one
that has to deal
with the consequences later on.
If you're going to kill me,
just do it now.
If you plan to keep me alive,
get me a glass of water.
EPISODE 7
That was reckless.
Had he told us,
you would have been killed on the spot.
Things are going according to our plan.
Don't you get it?
Because of that lowly punk,
everything could have been over
for both you and me,
who's putting everything on the line.
Don't whine.
Personal feelings
make your sword dull.
What will you do about the arsenal?
We even got the Capital Patrol involved.
If things go south,
you will be held accountable
for everything.
We will stick to our plan.
He could not have done it alone.
He must have
people helping him.
Catch them all.
So you killed Jung Sa-jeong?
Eighty percent of my support squad
soldiers used to be roughnecks.
They are vicious and decisive,
but I cannot entrust them
with important tasks.
Men like you who can devise plans
and read others' moves are rare.
It sounds like
you find me suspicious.
You pique my interest.
That is another way of putting it.
Let's hear it.
Why did you approach me?
This lowborn man thought Your Highness
was a rope that will lead him
to better things.
I wanted to turn my life around,
but it turns out that the rope is rotten,
and so are all the weapons.
Everything's rotten. Damn it.
The weapons are rotten?
The swords are bent out of shape,
and all the spears
are practically useless.
Why don't you go check
if you don't believe me?
You are
trying to lure me.
But I'm just wondering...
What if those weapons are seized
by the Office of the Inspector General?
It's a trap.
Let's go to the arsenal.
Your Highness.
We'll take him.
Break it down.
What are you doing?
Having a private arsenal
is considered treason.
Anyone who refuses to give it up
must be executed on the spot
as per His Majesty's orders.
I bet you trust
someone will look after you
for you to act up like this.
I only trust myself.
Behead anyone who rebels,
regardless of their ranks.
Attention!
The moment they open the door,
we shall slaughter them all.
I will open that door.
You can all be slaughtered in fear.
I was amused
by how you dared to slay my horse
and even come to my residence
all by yourself.
I give you credit for your bravery.
However,
this was out of line.
There will be
consequences.
I won't avoid it.
Let's go.
It is pure iron, not even cast iron.
And both the hammering
and tempering were done so clumsily.
Just go exchange it
with some taffy or something.
Where did you move all the weapons?
I asked you where the weapons are.
"The treacherous ministers
are deliberately distressing His Majesty
using private armies as an excuse,
and they are even threatening me,
a prince,
which is beyond deplorable.
Hence,
I send all the weapons I own
to the Office of the Inspector General,
so do not doubt my loyalty any longer."
Said His Highness Prince Jeongan.
You offered them up
to the Inspector General?
Not exactly. I discarded them for you.
Just dump those useless pieces of junk
and get yourself
properly made swords and spears.
How dare you.
By dumping the useless weapons,
you managed to
help me regain His Majesty's trust
and made Nam Seon-ho appear guilty
of falsely accusing me?
Correct.
What should I do
with this punk?
IHWARU
This must be your second visit to Ihwaru.
Why is that important?
This might end up being your last visit.
They should all leave.
Yes, Your Highness.
Hui-jae.
Your Highness.
I know that man.
Right, the two of you
have probably met before.
This place still reeks
of Jung Sa-jeong's blood.
Will there be another bloodshed?
Today, I am just here to enjoy some wine.
Do not be concerned.
Why are you not eating?
It melts in your mouth.
Are you made of rock
or steel?
Or did your mother
feed you wild ginseng
instead of breastmilk?
I am talking about you.
I've seen people dying of starvation,
but never from eating too much.
Food helps lessen the pain
when you are getting beaten up.
They say everyone who gets beaten up
surrenders.
I suppose you are an exception.
They say you grow pitiful of the one
whom you beat up. Who knows?
We may end up becoming quite close.
You seem to live
as if there is no tomorrow.
Who can live tomorrow
when tomorrow isn't even here yet?
I asked you a silly question,
yet you gave such a wise answer.
Your Highness.
You said you are a hunter.
Then I am curious.
How do you catch a tiger?
You have to corner it.
Corner it toward a dead-end
and distract it with dogs.
Then immobilize it with an arrow
and pierce its throat with a spear.
Is that right?
I see. I should use that method as well.
How odd.
You were unfazed even when you had
a sword pointed at your neck.
They didn't do anything. Let them go.
They seem to have had a hand in it.
Your Highness!
This arrowhead and pheasant feather.
This is mine.
I shall lead this game from now on.
Lying will cost you your lives.
You will also die
if your words don't match.
Thus, if you wish to live,
you must tell the truth.
There is no other way.
Now, let me ask you.
Who sent you?
You will be beheaded if you do not answer.
I will ask you one last time.
Who sent you?
Behead them.
Cover me!
We were the advance troop
dispatched to Liaodong.
We were abandoned after being used
and trampled all over.
In my eyes,
you are no different.
We dirtied our hands with blood
for this country,
but that blood is only used to deride us.
That is your and our situation.
So?
Your Highness' country.
The country of the abandoned.
I wished to see it with you.
That is my answer. Now, it's your turn
to give me your answer.
The country of the abandoned?
You wish to see my kingdom?
That is correct.
What you just said
saved your life.
Stop by my residence.
I shall give you my answer then.
Hwi!
Take him to the room. Hurry.
They ambushed you, Your Highness.
Why spare their lives?
They devised a plan,
incapacitated my soldiers,
and even got an inspector involved
and took him down.
Not many people can do that.
That is why I spared their lives.
There seems to be a hidden story
behind all this.
Find out.
Be honest.
How many of those paralytic pills
did you take?
Ten.
Jeez, has he completely
lost his mind or what?
I wanted a painless death.
I have to say,
Bang-won scares me.
I couldn't help but take those pills
when I saw his eyes.
This won't be an easy fight.
I could almost see,
"I will become King of this country,"
engraved on his forehead.
I think he's certainly capable
of shaking things up.
Beom, it sounds like
you've taken a liking to Bang-won.
Who knows?
He may get me a family register
when he's in a good mood
after ascending the throne.
I brought you some water.
My, how dazzling.
They say that fairies have wings.
Where are your wings?
Well, I guess your tongue isn't paralyzed.
Hwa-wol, can you
get me the antidote from my chest pocket?
Goodness, what the heck?
Don't be like that.
It's inside my left chest pocket.
Take it out for me.
Goodness.
Unbelievable.
-Get a taste of this.
-Gosh, it's cold!
Jeez, I'm so embarrassed for you.
Hwa-wol, please.
Just die, you fool. Goodness.
Hwa-wol, wait.
You pig, what is your problem?
-You lunatic!
-You embarrass me so much.
By the way, the medicine you gave me
worked quite well.
Thanks to you, scabs have already formed
on my head.
How is Hwi doing?
He's asleep, so don't worry.
Hwa-wol, wait.
-You lunatic!
-You embarrass me so much.
Don't disappear like that ever again.
I do not want to lose you again.
There are so many things
that I never got to do with you.
I want to walk through
the plum blossoms with you in spring.
In autumn, we'll walk
on dry fallen leaves on the ground.
And I want to walk in the snow
with you in winter.
Is it because we met
and parted ways in summer?
I want to experience
other seasons with you as well.
I mean, we should have something
to remember each other by.
That much we can do.
I don't think
I'm being greedy.
But I remember everything.
All the colors I saw
on the day I first met you,
the pleasant breeze on that happy day,
and even the rain on the day that I left.
I kept reliving all those memories
over and over in my head
but still couldn't stop missing you.
Are you going to begin now?
I've already begun.
I am not intervening because I cannot cut
the unrelenting ties between you two,
but I will not forgive you
if Hui-jae gets hurt because of you.
You must keep your promise.
That is why I'm doing this.
Keep your distance from Hwi
and just watch him from afar.
That is why I allowed you to not
give up your feelings for him.
Hwi and I
go way back
to when General Seo Geom was alive.
I will continue to try
to get close to him,
and I will get my hands
on the information about my mother,
which General Seo made sure to protect.
It is out of my hands now.
It went to someone
who needs it more than you do.
Who is that person?
Who is more desperate than I am?
Your goal is revenge,
but that person is trying to save a life,
so he needs it more desperately.
Madame Seol.
Bring me a fresh set of clothes.
Hui-jae, you may leave.
Madame Seol.
Go on!
Go ahead and give me your excuse.
You are the one who told me
to earn Bang-won's trust.
I simply did what I had to do.
I have no reason to list excuses.
You crossed a line you shouldn't have.
Your bravado will cost me a lot.
My position, my rank,
and perhaps even my life.
Whether you can survive or not
is up to you,
just like when I was deserted in Liaodong.
You said Liaodong was like hell to you.
To me, every day was
a battleground and a living hell.
All the mockery and contempt.
I gritted my teeth and endured it all
to come this far.
So listen up now.
If you get in my way,
don't expect mercy
because even you will be slain. No...
I will have to slay you because it is you.
I regret that I tried to save you.
I truly do.
Survive.
I mean it.
I only see one name in all these petitions
that are pouring in.
"Inspector Nam Seon-ho
must be interrogated, punished,
removed from his post, and executed."
Look at this. I see your name as well.
"He is using his son
to persecute the royal relatives.
He deserves a harsh warning
and must be reprimanded.
He should be dismissed at once."
I truly apologize, Your Majesty.
Your job is to deliver my orders
and oversee all military matters.
Why can't you keep
your personal matters separate
and let your son affect your work?
I would like to execute you and your son
to set a deterrent example,
but I will decide otherwise
due to all your contributions and the fact
that you are deeply repenting.
Inspector Nam Seon-ho
will be removed from his position,
and he will be demoted to the ninth rank.
The Ministry of Law Enforcement
will continue to investigate this matter.
Your Majesty, how could you reprimand
the Director of the Privy Council?
He abused his power.
He deceived the royal family.
He must be punished severely.
Please reconsider your decision,
Your Majesty.
-Please reconsider your decision.
That is impossible.
Your Majesty, why would you
side with the Chief Secretary?
His disrespect must be punished severely
to prevent any trouble in the future.
That is impossible.
So stop pleading.
My title should have been taken as well.
Without you, who would dare
to fight against Prince Jeongan?
Sambong?
He can't.
Sambong must direct
the transfer of the capital
and establish the laws and institutions
of this country.
You saved my life at Mount Huang
and you saved my life again
from those who plotted to murder me.
That's why it's you.
You are the only one I have.
Time is on Bang-won's side now.
Disband all private armies.
Otherwise,
Bang-seok won't be the crown prince.
Because Sambong is the one
who designed a dynasty of 1,000 years.
I'm supposed to do the dogfight?
Fine.
If that is what you want so badly,
I will remove them.
The child's fault is the father's flaw.
But you are making
a pretext of your title,
let alone giving it up.
I may be the son of a concubine,
but I'm still his son.
What do you think
would have happened if the King resigned
when you beat Poeun to death?
Do you remember
what I said?
The new country isn't yours.
It's my father's.
It's my father's nation.
And...
also mine.
Of course I do.
How can I forget the arrogance?
This country is not a King's country.
So...
do not dare to call this country yours.
Then whose country is it?
It's the subjects' country.
Only then,
even a foolish king or a tyrant king
can't bring down the country.
You...
will never be King.
Why can't the fifth son be the King
when the mere eighth son tries to become
the crown prince?
You just
watch it in your grave.
Watch who will be
the King.
INSPECTOR
Go straight home and find Yeon.
Tell her I won't be home for about 15 days
because of the inspection.
She will worry. Ask for enough clothes
to change to calm her down.
But it's not the inspection period.
I got it, sir.
Go.
You're arrested for personally commanding
Office of the Inspector General,
Nam Seon-ho, and the Capital Patrol, and
threatening the royal family with a sword.
The longer you endure the whipping,
the longer the torture will be.
You had better spit out a few names
to make it easier for the both of us.
There is no name to spit out.
That's why I'm enduring it.
You do what you have to do.
Well, then...
This bag has underwear in it,
and this has outer clothing.
Actually, I think I should give them
to him myself.
Where do you think you are going?
I told you to refrain from going out.
Did you forget?
I will just deliver them
to Seon-ho, my brother.
Your brother?
You are not his sister.
Sir.
Do you know why
Seon-ho can't come back home?
It's because of you.
You are the cause.
From now on, don't do anything
in this house but breathe.
Actually,
ask for my permission when you breathe.
Lock her up in the shed.
Yes, sir.
Did something happen to my brother?
I mean, Young Master Nam?
Please tell me. Please!
What has happened?
Did he get hurt?
Just tell me he's fine!
Open the door! Open it!
Open the door.
Stop.
Do you know what you did?
It was the only and the quickest way
to support Bang-won.
Seon-ho was removed
from his position, and I...
got humiliated.
You are alive and well,
and all Bang-won's weapons are seized.
You didn't lose anything.
Bang-won
must be killed by his own soldier.
That way, I won't suffer a disadvantage
and will have a good reason
to remove his soldiers.
So hold in and hide your anger
until you get a command.
Just like now.
I will keep that in mind
and never forget it.
You can hold in your anger pretty well.
I barely manage to hide it.
About Yeon...
You said you would take good care of her
as if she was your own.
Are you keeping your word?
I told you to live and die for me.
Have you been keeping your word?
You need my confirmation
regarding the trade?
I'll be offering you Ihwaru's information.
It is why I even dare to ask.
That information you receive
is nothing but rumors said by drunks.
What information could be valuable enough
to request for my audience?
How is your atrophy?
I hear you've been barely sleeping
and that rice porridge
is all you can stomach.
Only the royal physician
of the Directorate of Medicine
is aware of my condition,
so how could you possibly know--
What else do you know?
I know what it is
you desire.
You sly old fox.
There's more to this
than the tribute and border trade.
Hui-jae, leave us.
I couldn't possibly
thank you enough for taking Hui-jae in
and looking after her.
Please use it when you need it most.
You don't know what I'll do with this.
Nam Jeon could have you killed.
Still,
it will save Hui-jae.
So what did you learn?
Know an opponent's weakness
but don't be intimidated.
You must not corner
the other party either.
Take a step back and let your opponent
think that he or she has won
before you reveal your hand.
The Queen doubted you for a second.
Did you see that too?
I did.
The fire burns all firewood in its path.
The Queen is the fire
while you are only one
of the many firewood lying around.
I now formally request
the team of private investigators.
I'll allow it.
Dig up anything you can
but without Hwi knowing.
Do not interfere.
The investigation will end
if anyone is caught.
Go.
Do not dare to call this country yours.
You...
will never be King.
Your Highness.
Those four names
were among the casualties.
They were part of the advance party.
And?
Hwi's father was killed
by the dipping in a cauldron.
I find the other three suspicious too.
Is this the tiger's mouth?
Becoming Bang-won's loyal servant might
upgrade our lives forever.
The payment is 20 seoms of rice.
I'd rather build a tower with that.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Come near the prince
while holding a weapon
and you'll be sliced open.
Even if it's the King?
Yes.
How savage.
Oh, you're finally here.
Well, it's good to see you.
You must have nine lives.
I need to live
if I'm going to rip you apart one day.
You should worry more about yourself.
I'm no match for someone
who can't see an arrow coming.
You little bastard.
Cheonga.
I'm a soldier too, you know.
Being a former palace guard
makes you high and mighty,
but I never get that respect
since I'm of lowly origins.
Take it outside if you wish to see blood.
I won't allow it indoors.
Fine.
I'll be the one to kill you,
so stay alive until then.
Here's my answer.
Be my weapon.
Before you do though,
you will dig two graves.
One for me
and one
for you.
Your life must be on the line
to be able to change the world.
I already died in Liaodong.
I do not need
another grave.
Then what about you?
You once led the subjugation up north,
didn't you, Park Chi-do?
Those memories are already long gone.
I now
serve you as my only master.
A mortician who played doctor
and a slave who killed his master.
You four sure are an interesting team.
Follow me.
I hear your father was punished
by the dipping in a cauldron.
He was an official who stole rations.
Is that so?
Yes.
This is where
I killed Poeun.
He had to be eliminated
to erect this country,
but no one would do the job.
No one
wanted to go down in history
as the evil who killed a loyal servant.
This is where
my family was saved
but also where I was abandoned.
However,
this is also where this nation began.
It hasn't even been a year
since Poeun's blood was splashed over me.
I can't allow
more blood on my hands
that'll paint me as pure evil.
From this moment on,
you will answer only to me.
You will have to die
unless you become King.
The way to become one
is for you to kill the King himself.
The blood that'll bounce off my sword
will make you a King.
If that scares you,
beg for Bang-seok's mercy
or pretend to have gone insane.
Who knows?
He might pity you enough to not kill you.
You mock me, speak about the King, and...
show hints of rebellion?
You already spoke of a new nation
and an act of rebellion.
Right here, where you killed Poeun.
No matter whose blood you shed,
always remember this.
If any of that blood splatters in my way,
I will kill you...
and every one of your friends.
I wouldn't have come to you
if that scared me.
So it's now your turn
to dig those two graves.
Your Highness.
YI BANG-WON
YI SEONG-GYE
When it comes to archery,
no one can hold a candle to you.
Is it just the archery?
I know you well.
You'd do anything to get what you want
and crush things you couldn't have.
I learned that from you.
You crushed Choi Yeong
and took this nation for yourself.
The man I wanted wasn't Choi Yeong
but Poeun.
However, you brutally murdered him.
It's an ambush!
Find the scoundrel!
Charge!
He's 400 steps away,
so what good could a search party do?
He wasn't aiming to kill me.
It's as if he has something to say.
A feather of a pheasant on a red arrow.
It's the same as yours.
The blood that'll bounce off my sword
will make you a King.
November 23, 1380.
Bring me Nam Jeon.
You, follow me.
Four assassins who tried to kill me
died in 1380.
You revealed their crimes
and had them executed.
You also said that
no one but us knew of it.
Is that true?
It is.
It seems like
another knows about it too.
It's simply just a random date.
Tear it into pieces.
Whoever it was
had the nerve to aim at my target.
It just so happens
that you were there too.
Is it really just a coincidence?
The only archer skilled enough
to hit a target from 400 steps away
is you, Your Majesty.
It seems like
someone is trying to frame me.
Then how must I handle
this mockery of an action?
You must...
kill who's responsible.
Those who lie and mock this court
will be executed.
I will never draw my sword
without contemplating,
but that sword
won't return to its scabbard
without seeing blood.
Are you here to mock me?
I'm here to get you out.
I'll see you around, Father.
Someone is after my head.
I doubt it's just one person.
That person
will kill me, you, and ruin our family.
Apart, we won't survive.
Our only chance is to fight together.
If that person is Bang-won,
then we must kill him.
Mom, let's run.
We'll live somewhere far away.
So that you can get caught
as a runaway slave
and have your face branded?
Or
would you prefer to be beaten to death?
We'll die together then.
That's what we'll do.
Stop being so stubborn!
Now, listen to me carefully.
If you pity me at all,
work hard to become someone of power.
Then make a country
that even allows
a decent life for lowlifes like me.
It must be nice to have a father high up.
What are you doing here?
Could I please talk
to Inspector Nam Seon-ho?
Please.
He was stripped of his position
and has been clubbed.
I hear that they torture
just till the brink of death.
Yeon.
Don't come near me.
Stay right there.
Come any closer and I'll scream.
Listen to me.
Don't tell anyone you came here.
Especially not Nam Jeon.
Got it?
Do you understand me?
Seon-ho...
Was it my father?
Yi Seong-gye,
General-in-Chief of the Three Provinces,
after defeating the Japanese raiders,
showed evident signs of rebellion
against the current regime
and has been conspiring
an uprising ever since.
We vow to
eliminate the traitor Yi Seong-gye
and fulfill our duties
as Goryeo's loyal servants.
We swear upon this vow at Haegeomdang
and will execute our mission
on November 23, 1380.
Kim Yeong-su, Park Seon-min,
Noh Gyeong-cheon,
and Nam Jeon.
Where's the secret letter?
Where is it?
Why?
Are you scared
that Yi Seong-gye will find out?
Are you terrified
since he might rip you into pieces?
Tell me.
You will pay for betraying our vow.
You...
will die from having your blood
drained from your body.
Twelve years ago in 1380.
Is it true that you
made a pact to assassinate General Yi?
If it is, it will destroy this family.
He's involved.
SPECIAL THANKS TO KIM YOON-SEO
Was it Hwi who received
my mother's letter?
Protect those you need to protect.
Meanwhile, I will protect you.
Prince Uian.
I hereby announce you
as the new Crown Prince.
I will not back down
until I have what I want.
I will not give up either.
I will...
not even take a step out of Gaegyeong.
Please let me serve you by your side.
I will protect your throne with my life.
I used the King
to put pressure on Nam Jeon
and had him doubt Bang-won.
Him looking for me is part of my plan.
Kill Bang-won.
I don't care
whatever it is he has anymore.
Kill him.