ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, INCIDENTS AND RELIGIONS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
Taekwondo.
Judo.
Systema?
Gosh, that's jiu-jitsu.
He's really good.
What are you doing in the dark?
Were you watching porn?
No.
-I know you were.
-No.
It's fine. You're still young.
No. I wasn't…
How are things going?
-I'm not doing much.
-Not you.
What's Joo-eun up to?
I couldn't keep pestering her
to pay me back.
So I haven't talked to her.
And she's been pretty quiet lately.
What's she doing?
I heard she's running
the detective agency.
You make it sound like you're not sure.
It's not love, right?
Right.
Even if it's love, what can I do about it?
It's none of my business.
Even so, don't fall in love.
You know that it won't work out
for you anyway, don't you?
Let's stay true to who we really are.
I'll ask again. What's she up to nowadays?
I guess you can't tell me about it.
What could it be?
To be honest, I wasn't interested,
but all of a sudden, I've gotten curious.
I'll get going.
Where's the detective agency?
SPY DETECTIVE AGENCY
Gosh, this musty smell.
EPISODE 8
A leather sofa
and a tacky receptionist
who completes the picture.
My worries always turn out to be true
for some reason.
Who is this lanky woman?
My daughter is the CEO here.
-What?
-A cup of coffee, please.
What? That's Cha Joo-eun's mom?
What's wrong with her family?
Why do they keep invading my space?
Should I request a case, too?
I heard that my grandpa was taken
by the Japanese soldiers a long time ago.
Who knows? He could have survived
and became a wealthy man in Japan.
She's not even here. I think we should go.
I'll have that coffee before I go.
Where's the CEO?
I don't know.
She might be with Sophia Chung.
She said she'd meet her this afternoon.
Sophia Chung.
-Aren't you going to drink it?
-Sure. I will.
I finally feel alive.
You should feel indebted to me
for the rest of your life.
I even fed you a delicious meal.
Kim Jae-wook.
What is he to you?
Did you love him?
"Love"? That's so childish.
You did love him.
Stop delving into what happened yesterday.
Let's focus on tomorrow.
I want to kill that bastard.
That's how I feel at this moment.
I have to do everything I can
to do some damage to that bastard.
I like the attitude.
-Don't you regret it?
-Regret what?
You were a news anchor.
That's a pretty cool job.
What about you?
Do you regret it?
Anyway, thank you.
What? What did you say?
-You heard me.
-No, I didn't.
Goodness, look at this old woman.
If you're thankful, why don't you
address me with some respect?
"Old woman"? It's unacceptable
even if you're so jealous
that you can't think and speak properly.
Jealousy?
I kind of sensed it,
but you really have no conscience.
Why would I be jealous of an old lady?
There you go again.
If people hear you, they'll criticize you
for being so mean to your friend.
That won't help you get back
those years you lost
or stop you from getting old.
Jeez. You and your attitude.
You never let anything slide
out of politeness.
You really don't know
that man from earlier?
Unfortunately, I don't.
Then, who was that knight
in shining armor?
I want to know that too.
SPY DETECTIVE AGENCY
CHIEF KO HYE-WON
This is so funny.
Drinking alone?
Don't you think about joining me
and stealing my drink.
I have my own.
Oh, right.
Were you able to get in touch
with Choi Yoon-seok?
No. He's unreachable.
Is it possible
he's dodging your calls?
Who? Yoon-seok?
He wouldn't dare dodge my calls.
Gosh, you're ridiculous.
So you obviously don't know
what he's like.
Right. I should be understanding.
Anyway, I guarantee you that
he'll never ignore any of my calls.
Oh, right. Your mother came by yesterday.
Your mother.
MOM
PORK RIBS APLENTY
It's like I'm watching The Godfather.
They might kill us
if we don't give them free food.
So what will you do?
I decided to work with her
to catch Kim Jae-wook.
Great.
Nicely done.
-What's your next step?
-What?
I'm sure you're planning a documentary
for Jeong Bok-gi.
What's the plot?
Well,
I'm still working on it.
I see.
Take your time,
and think carefully
in order to come up with a foolproof plan.
You're taking down Jeong Bok-gi after all.
Until then, you must pull off your role,
so that she fully trusts you.
Yes, I should.
And one more thing.
I want to be in it, too.
What? I can't be in it?
Mom, that's--
I know that
it's probably not the best idea.
It will be difficult for me
to work with her.
So I'll work behind the curtain.
I don't want to see
that bitch in person, either.
Fine.
Let's talk when the plot is ready.
Sure.
And most importantly,
pay me back soon.
Okay, fine. I'll pay you back.
Shall we?
Cheers.
Edward.
How will I find this bastard again?
How did it go?
Who is she? Why are you protecting her?
Jeong-hwan, are you listening?
I can't do this.
What? Can't do what?
SPY DETECTIVE AGENCY
What's this?
Didn't she turn off the lights
before going home?
This isn't a 24-hours convenience store.
Damn it. I should deduct this
from her pay.
Stop right there.
You better not try anything funny.
I already called the police.
You know that the police arrive
within five minutes in Korea, right?
What? He's…
Hey!
Isn't he
that mysterious guy?
I'm sorry, Joo-eun.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
I'm Kim Eun-ji from the Traffic Division
of Seoul Police Agency.
There was a hit-and-run accident
in front of the building yesterday.
Could I watch the security footage?
Sure. Over there. Go ahead.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
It can't be.
He's dead. It can't be.
DON'T YOU EVER SHOW UP IN FRONT OF ME
I'LL REALLY KILL YOU NEXT TIME
Kim Jae-wook?
This isn't Edward.
Right?
I agree.
Edward doesn't have the decency
to give you a warning like this.
Right.
I figured that out
when he tried to kill me.
I could tell that he's a man of action.
That's right.
Then, who do you think did this?
Not sure.
What I need to take away from this
is that someone is watching me.
In my opinion,
you have nothing to be scared of.
What do you mean?
It's a warning.
They're nicely telling you
not to do anything dangerous.
And at the same time,
they know that Kim Jae-wook is dangerous.
That reminds me.
That mysterious guy from the hospital.
What?
What I'm saying is…
I know that this doesn't make any sense.
But when you think about it,
it has to be Jeong-hwan.
What? Who?
Don't you think
-Jeong-hwan wrote that warning?
-Spy Lee?
Yes.
Let me get this straight.
Spy Lee became a ghost
and scribbled a warning?
No.
Not a ghost.
So, are you saying
that Spy Lee is alive
and he's taking care of you
while in hiding. Is that it?
It doesn't make sense, does it?
Of course not.
He's not a zombie.
You can't resurrect the dead like that.
You already had his funeral
and got the DNA result.
But then,
you became a widow overnight.
You must have been shocked.
In any case, stop imagining things.
I'll tell you something
that could actually be helpful.
I analyzed the story you told me before
in detail.
So, a question.
It means that GK's Lee Jeong-hwan put the
detective agency's Lee Jeong-hwan to work.
Don't you think
that's one too many coincidences?
Why do they always meet without me? Why?
It's upsetting.
Yes, sir.
What is Kim Myung-hyun doing?
-Pardon?
-Did he take his hands off
Lee Jeong-hwan's car accident case?
PORK RIBS APLENTY
Didn't he?
Yes, he did because he had other cases.
CHIEF OF THE CRIMINAL DIVISION
JEONG DAE-SANG
Sir, I wanted to ask you something.
What is it?
Well, why did you suddenly close
the investigation?
Right.
You're curious too, aren't you?
What should a curious detective do?
You should investigate.
Don't you dare butt in.
Butt in? Me?
I'm just trying to serve them instantly
before they even ring the bell.
Just go wipe the table over there.
It's really sticky.
We serve pork ribs. Of course it's--
Where's the dishcloth?
Here it is.
Gosh.
Go ahead.
Didn't you say
you had something to ask me?
About the person with the same name…
I mean, there's a man named
Lee Jeong-hwan at GK technology.
-You know that, right?
-A man with the same name?
Yes.
A man with the same name?
I've never heard that.
Did you investigate properly?
CHALSEONG COFFEE SHOP
NATASHA COFFEE SHOP
Where should we begin?
It looks awful,
but it even has a bathroom.
Let's start.
-Start what?
-Cleaning.
You take the bathroom.
What? Why me?
I can't believe this.
You got married?
You said you were a groomsman.
I'm sorry.
No. Sorry is not going to cut it.
How could you keep it a secret from me?
I feel so betrayed.
Our friendship is broken,
and our partnership's ruined.
Can our relationship ever be mended?
Well…
There's some premium beef in the fridge.
Are you kidding me?
Is it tenderloin?
It's working.
Is it ready?
It's delicious.
This is what I'm talking about.
Try some. Don't just stick to pork.
Here.
By the way, why did your wife
quit working for UI and start running
the detective agency? Did she get fired?
Do you think you can penetrate UI?
-Why do you ask?
-There's something I need to know.
Know what?
I need evidence that UI tried to kill me.
Cheers.
A conglomerate like UI is hard.
But,
if I get help from the inside,
-there could be a way.
-Fill your glasses!
-Bravo!
Everyone, bottoms up!
-Bottoms up!
-Drink up!
-Let's drink!
-Jeez. What are you doing?
-Be careful.
I'm sorry.
-It's fine. Just go.
-Sit down.
-Drink up.
PC GRAVEYARD
Are you in?
Yes. I'm in. I'll go up.
RESTRICTED AREA
The server room has been infiltrated.
Please check the server room.
RESTRICTED AREA
Someone tried to break in.
Check the surveillance
and close the entrance.
He's wearing a navy suit.
Wait.
Jeez.
Damn it.
I'm chasing him on the third floor.
He's heading for the second floor.
You two, go that way!
He's over there!
He's on the fourth floor!
-How's it going?
-Within ten minutes,
the system will be updated.
They'll start tracking us then,
so I need to work as fast as I can.
Three minutes left.
Did you trace him?
It's almost done.
I just need authorization.
It crashed.
I can't find him.
Korean conglomerates are terrible.
They collected
all sorts of private information.
Jeez, they have all kinds of information.
It's like a tabloid.
A STAR COUPLE IS BORN
What? Were they going out?
Unbelievable. Did she do drugs, too?
What? They have lots of ordinary people's
information, too.
These bastards are ridiculous.
Stop looking up useless information.
Find the file on Jeong Yoon-kyung.
"JEONG YOON-KYUNG," NO RESULT FOUND
SOPHIA CHUNG
Nothing.
Didn't you say you gave
Jeong Yoon-kyung's file to your wife?
Wait.
Did she get fired because of this?
What? She's still with the company.
CHA JOO-EUN
Could she
be a spy sent by UI?
-It's spicy.
-It's good.
Jeong-hwan.
Say kimchi.
-Right now?
-Yes.
Say kimchi.
Kimchi.
What? Do I look weird?
You should take another one. Let me see.
I sent them to you.
JOO-EUN
Jeez, I look--
Delete them.
Why? You look cute.
Do I?
Give me that. Please delete them.
-No.
-Give me your phone.
No.
No. She's not.
A spy doesn't laugh at red pepper
stuck between your teeth.
What are you talking about?
What matters is that
UI doesn't have Jeong Yoon-kyung's file.
It means that the ones who were after
me and Jeong Yoon-kyung
weren't UI.
Then
who killed my brother?
Could it be GK?
Yes.
TRACE THE CALL
Did you look into the thing
I asked you the other day?
What?
-UI?
-Yes.
Yes.
You were right.
It was UI.
But the problem
isn't as simple as you think.
It looks like UI hired a contractor.
It's hard to find out which department
hired what contractor.
All right.
I will
find out the rest.
Wait.
Will you be okay alone?
Yes, I'll be fine.
Tell me if you need help.
I'll send my guys over.
No. Where are you?
I can send them over now.
Where are you?
It's okay.
I shouldn't cause any misunderstanding
between companies.
Fine.
Still, we should meet up.
I'll call you again.
Is this how you work?
Well,
he's using an older model,
so we can only trace the base station.
So,
the chief of the criminal division ordered
to end the investigation.
Yes, he did.
It began as a high-profile case.
I don't know why he did that.
Coercion?
If not, they wouldn't have closed
the case so quickly.
A detective agency owner died,
and there was a coercion.
Isn't it nonsensical?
So,
Choi Yoon-seok who killed himself
went missing.
No,
it was his twin brother to be exact.
And Lee Jeong-hwan who died
was raised from the dead like Jesus.
He resurrected
and showed up without a warning.
Then he calls me whenever he wants.
Right?
This is the result
of your performance, isn't it?
I'm sorry, sir.
Is that the best you can do?
How dare you trip?
-That hurt, didn't it?
-Yes, quite a bit.
So? What's your plan?
I'll find both Lee Jeong-hwan
and Choi Yoon-seok.
Then what?
As you ordered initially,
I'll get rid of them.
HWA CHINESE RESTAURANT
Wait here.
-Yes, sir.
I decided to be audacious
and give you a warning.
Do not ask any questions from now on,
as always.
If you start asking questions,
we'll take it that you're picking a fight.
Then we'll have to clash.
Goodbye, then.
You should hear what I have to say.
You do know
that I like conglomerates, right?
So tell him not to worry.
I'm talking about Lee Jeong-hwan.
Right. One more thing.
I like to fight.
You know that.
So who was it?
Who used Lee Jeong-hwan's name?
It was GK.
Do you think you can handle them?
Who was it?
I definitely can't handle them.
So, I don't know anything like an idiot.
I just do what I'm told.
Fine.
Then let me ask one final question.
Was it the Innovative Vision Room?
My gosh.
Myung-hyun. Why are you here?
I have one question.
What's up with the Chief?
Well…
You did well. You got on his good side.
Not everyone can get
on the chief's good side.
Look confident.
You're doing well.
Damn it. We have no choice but to obey.
So? What's Woo Seok-ho up to?
Why is he at a flower shop?
Are you looking for anything
in particular?
Well,
I'm looking for some flowers to give
to a woman in her late 30s.
Oh, is it your girlfriend's birthday?
It's her wedding.
What?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
It is you. Gosh.
It's so nice to see you.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
Who are you again?
I'm from GK.
I'm Lee Jeong-hwan.
Right.
I was too harsh on you back then.
I'm sorry.
Don't be. I understand.
You were scammed after all.
He…
died.
On our wedding day.
I had no idea.
We shouldn't just stand here.
Would you like to go somewhere
and continue talking?
But don't you have something special
going on today?
Not at all.
I just like flowers,
so I buy them from time to time.
Boys Over Flowers, you know.
This is a gift for our reunion.
Are you sure I can take them?
Of course.
Then shall we go somewhere for a drink?
Well, let's go somewhere
that has tasty food.
I know of a great place.
They left.
-Start the car.
-Gosh.
We could've gotten caught.
Why didn't you hide?
Then we'll have to get down and dirty.
Let's have some hotel coffee.
Why is it so expensive?
Myung-hyun.
-Take a look.
-Okay.
-Yes, Chief.
-Where are you?
We followed Cha and Woo
into a hotel restaurant.
So why haven't you sent me the photos yet?
Well…
Are you with someone right now?
I am.
It's Kim Myung-hyun, isn't it?
What is this?
This must mean he knows
that you're receiving orders from me.
He does.
Fine.
Anyway, why do you think
he's working so hard on this case?
I'm not sure either.
Is it because of that widow?
Cha Joo-eun.
There must be a reason
that he's digging into it like that.
Word has it that the two meet alone
regularly.
Don't you think
you should look into their relationship?
Do you know me?
No.
You've been staring at me.
-Have I?
-Yes, you have.
Actually,
you look very similar to someone I know.
His name is Lee Jeong-Hwan,
and he runs a detective agency.
But up-close,
you're not alike at all.
Gosh, do I need a pair of glasses?
Anyway,
sorry about that.
He knows Lee Jeong-hwan?
KIM MYUNG-HYUN
VIOLENT CRIMES TEAM 3
That lousy cop.
You should be grateful
that today is a special day for me.
That scumbag…
What happened in the bathroom?
He could've burned holes
through your back with that glare.
I provoked him a little.
Let's see how he reacts.
He just went into the room.
Darn it. He's more careful than he looks.
You must've been bored.
Yes, I was bored to death.
That's why I made sure to be quick
in the bathroom.
What a filthy bastard.
Wait.
This is…
One minute.
Excuse me.
Do you see this?
Do your job properly, will you?
I'm sorry, sir.
The glass was dirty.
I see.
All right.
A glass for you.
-Cheers.
Why aren't you drinking?
I can't drink at all.
Come on.
Then I won't drink either.
I'm serious.
Me too.
Then I'll have a sip.
A sip?
I knew you could drink well.
By the way,
what kind of perfume do you wear?
Actually, this is
just how I naturally smell.
No wonder. Back at the flower shop,
I smelled something wonderful
among all those flowers.
When I turned my head,
you were right there.
Cheers to the most fragrant flower.
Cheers.
What? It's empty already. What a shame.
Let's have another bottle.
No.
We should go somewhere else now.
Wait.
How about
we just order room service upstairs?
What?
That was a joke.
A joke.
What's his deal? Why isn't he collapsing?
This is the tranquilizer
they use at safaris.
A few drops is enough to knock out a cow.
Give it to him when the time is right.
Got that?
What's wrong with him?
Is he stronger than a cow?
Is he a buffalo or something?
0718 is sleeping
at the Goryeo Hotel restaurant.
An emergency checkup is required.
HEART RATE, TEMPERATURE,
RESPIRATORY RATE
0411 and 0501? What the hell are these?
"0721,
investigation closed"?
"0721, gone missing
on the day of the wedding"?
Mr. Lee Jeong-hwan's case has been closed.
MY HUSBAND
It's Jeong-hwan.
Woo Seok-ho
knew Jeong-hwan.
Are you okay?
Sir.
Come out.
Who are you?
That's none of your business.
Please move aside.
Lee Jeong-hwan.
Who are you?
How did it go?
Cow, my foot.
He was finally knocked out
after three bottles of wine.
Gosh, it was agonizing.
He was despicable.
He was greasy and disgusting.
He pretty much molested me with his eyes.
Come on. You're a professional.
I'm sure you've had worse.
Exactly.
At times like this,
I have second thoughts about my job.
Here.
Have you heard of GK's
Innovative Vision Room?
Of course.
I'm sure everyone in this country
knows about it.
They created a nationwide scandal
a few years ago and were disbanded.
Disbanded?
Do you really believe that?
I beg to differ.
Anyway,
I heard they have shadow agents
just like they do at the NIS.
Simply put, they do dirty,
dark,
filthy, illegal things.
Like Spy Lee, they have different jobs
and blend in with ordinary people.
They're the Innovative Vision Room's
shadows.
Spy Lee
could have been a real GK employee.
Aren't you going to drink?
Hey.
Where have you been?
You didn't even tell me you were
going out. How suspicious.
-Min-jeong.
-Yes?
I need to speak with him in private.
Do you want me to leave?
I don't want to.
I was just kidding.
Sit down.
You know of GK Technology's
Innovative Vision Room, right?
Apparently, they have shadow agents.
-Jeong-hwan was--
-You're right.
-What?
-He was one of them.
He was one of their shadow agents.
Promise me one thing.
Just think about yourself.
Just like when you did the documentaries,
think only about yourself.
A shadow?
How could it have all been lies?
That bastard.
Jeong-hwan.
What is it?
I really thought a lot about this.
And I decided that you should know.
What is it? Tell me now.
Joo-eun
isn't an orphan.
What?
Her mother is a loan shark…
What brings you all the way to my office?
Office, my foot.
Thanks to his insurance,
your documentary barely made it.
Technically, he was your son-in-law.
Show some respect.
Fine. They say a son-in-law
is still your son.
What a good son he was.
Mom.
Yes?
Why do you think
our family ended up like this?
Because of Dad?
No.
It was because of you.
He didn't leave us.
It was you who kicked him out.
You were never grateful
and always pessimistic.
Because of your despicable personality…
Because you always put on airs,
blamed, and insulted others,
Dad ended up like that.
We'll never be able to live
under the same roof again.
You ruined everything.
Do you realize that?
I'm leaving.
She did not just say that.
Is that how she treats her mom?
And what about my personality?
She shouldn't have lied
no matter how furious she was.
You heard her, right?
I'm what?
I put on airs, am pessimistic,
and only blame others?
Am I really like that?
Someone as graceful as I am?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Why?
Joo-eun.
…and her father is serving time for fraud.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I've been very busy lately.
Married life is so much different.
I have to clean, do laundry,
and cook breakfast for him every morning.
Anyway, it's been so hectic.
I'm sorry, Dad.
What is it?
Were you that sad?
You're making me feel terrible.
Joo-eun.
Yes?
You can cry in front of me.
My daughter.
My baby.
It must have been hard for you.
I'm…
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Your mom visits from time to time.
She updates me on how you're doing.
She told me about him.
I saw his photo too.
He was handsome. No wonder you chose him.
He wasn't as good looking as I am, though.
He looked trustworthy.
I could see it in his face.
I'm sure
he had his reasons for doing such a thing.
FAMILY RELATION CERTIFICATE
FATHER, CHA HYUN-TAE
MOTHER, KIM MI-SOOK
-You--
-Also,
I really didn't want to
tell you this, but…
There's more?
What is it? Tell me.
Joo-eun
has a criminal record
for fraud.
AGGRAVATED PUNISHMENT
FOR FINANCIAL CRIME
Cheongpa Women's Correctional Institute.
We were cellmates.
We call prisons "schools."
She totally fooled you.
How could she lie
about something like that?
No. Of course, she had to. It was a fraud.
I would have done the same.
But how did she get into UI?
I'm sure she couldn't just fool them.
I should ask her myself.
What? You're going to see her right now?
Come on.
You can't just reveal yourself to her.
Jeong-hwan!
Who might be the most powerful
person here?
Do you want to work with me?
Find Cha Joo-eun and hand her over.
How dare she escape?
Did you even love me?
This is Deputy Chief Kim Jae-wook.
He's joining us as of today.
This is amusing to you, isn't it?
Can you tell?
You answer me first.
I know everything you told me
about yourself was a lie.
Let go of me, you bastard!
I'm sorry.