ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, INCIDENTS AND RELIGIONS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
TOMORROW INVESTMENT
My stomach hurts when I'm stressed out.
You bitch.
You psychotic bitch.
Don't just stand there. Go get her.
Yes, sir.
Let me go!
Come here. Come with us.
Who is this bastard?
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm okay.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
What about you?
I'm all right.
Okay.
Let's not meet for the time being.
That'd be better.
Mom.
What?
I'm sorry.
If you are, be nice to me more often.
So Lee Jeong-hwan is alive.
Let me give you a word of advice
as your mother because I'm worried.
Don't ever see him again in the future.
Okay?
It's dangerous.
And what if you have to return
the insurance payout?
Okay?
I can't see him
even if I want to.
Why is that?
He found out about my record.
He knows
everything about me.
Mom, I'll call you back
once things are settled.
Come to think of it,
I was the bait.
The bait to lure out Jeong-hwan
who faked his death.
In other words, because of me,
he's in danger again.
All of us, including you, me,
and Lee Jeong-hwan,
have crossed the line.
I wonder if she was able to escape
and is safe now.
And where is Uncle? Why isn't he here?
You know what?
That delivery guy.
I think I've seen him somewhere.
I wonder where you saw him.
So I tried really hard to recall where.
This one guy crossed my mind.
It was
the delivery boy from my favorite Chinese
restaurant. Seriously, I'm so sharp.
-But how does he know Joo-eun?
-Damn it.
No, that's not it.
Delivery boys don't ride
motorcycles like that.
You're so clueless.
Kids these days are into that stuff.
Damn it.
This is Spy Detective Agency.
We do anything for our clients.
Hi, this is Development Team 2
of the advancing GK Technology.
It's me, Ms. Ko.
Where are you now?
And how do you know this number?
I don't have my cell phone and
this is the only number I have memorized.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, how is it going?
That woman parked her car here.
She didn't even pay for parking.
So annoying.
Yoo Mi-young's car is still at the agency.
I have to go check her dashcam footage.
I have to find out who she's been seeing
and where she's been.
No. It's dangerous. I'll go alone.
I'm coming, too.
I don't even have anywhere to go.
Besides, it's my business.
Jeong-hwan.
You don't know
what your wife is up to, right?
By the way, Yoo Mi-young's car
was last seen at the agency.
Shouldn't we check the dashcam?
I mean, we might find evidence
that could clear her name.
What? Where are you going again?
What should I do with the man
who hurt you, Vivian?
Should I kill him?
Let's see if he shows up again
to save Cha Joo-eun.
He's definitely got my attention.
Just get the dashcam from the car.
Okay. I'm on it, sir.
Park Tae-joo.
Hey!
CALLING PARK TAE-JOO
The number you have dialed
is currently unavailable.
-Your call will be directed to voicemail.
-Why isn't he answering?
Please leave a message after the beep.
Is it possible
that something's happened to Tae-joo?
What? How did he know?
How did he get here before Cha Joo-eun?
Well, the order was switched,
but this will do.
It's been a while.
Aren't you glad to see me?
Yes, I am.
It's been ten years,
but this isn't the place or the time
suited for our reunion.
Right?
Yes. There are better places than here.
It makes me wonder why you've
suddenly shown up at a place like this?
Now I can finally see
if what I did ten years ago was necessary
or a waste of my time.
Unfortunately, it was a waste of my time
because of you.
Had you stayed as
the Lee Jeong-hwan I knew,
we would be working
in the same office as secretaries now.
We could've even had soju together
after work.
But
you ruined everything.
How sad.
You should have stuck with
what you were good at
and followed the company's orders.
The Lee Jeong-hwan I knew
was a loyal dog who would have
never done such a thing.
I don't follow.
I believe I'm still serving GK.
You intercepted Jeong Yoon-kyung
and stole President Choi's secret ledger.
You put on quite a show.
We all took notice of you.
That's not something
a man who serves GK would do.
So you knew everything.
This is embarrassing.
It's all right.
You don't need to feel embarrassed.
Was that it?
Was that why I had to die?
This whole thing made me
question something.
You used to be a model student.
How did you undergo such a transformation?
What suddenly made you do the things
that you did?
So I did my best
to come up with an answer.
Are you interested?
Cha Joo-eun was born
into a family of con artists
and grew up to be a promising con artist.
And I think meeting her
became a turning point in your life.
After falling for her act,
you ended up marrying her.
Just like any other men, a sense of
responsibility and greed swept over you.
Why?
You wanted to make her happy at all costs.
It would have been better
had you stopped in moderation.
But greed knows no bounds.
You couldn't be satisfied.
Your ambition grew bigger and bigger,
and that's how you ended up here.
This is the answer I came up with.
What do you think?
Is this correct?
Wrong answer.
This suddenly crossed my mind.
"If people like you
could have that ledger.
Why can't I have it?
If I had it,
I would definitely be able
to use it for a much better cause."
That's what I thought.
You bastard.
Be honest with me.
After sending Jeong Yoon-kyung abroad
and obtaining President Choi's
secret ledger,
you acted all cool,
as if you were doing me a favor.
Didn't you leave the company,
expecting me to return the favor?
I see that we had
a lot of catching up to do.
Make a choice.
Return the ledger and live your life
as if you didn't exist in this world.
Or
you can move into the cinerarium
for real this time.
If I return the ledger,
will everything I did go away?
Of course, that's what I want, too.
But
if I do that, Vivian will be so furious.
So I don't think I can do that.
How about I break one of your legs?
Go ahead.
Get back in the car.
We're meeting at the tented bar.
Get in.
Goodness.
So which one is it?
Your leg or the cinerarium?
Jeez.
Are you using only one hand?
Damn it!
What a waste of money.
Spy Lee is really alive. He didn't die.
What happened?
He's become frail.
Can you
give me some water?
Well…
Joo-eun.
Did you
ever love me?
You know the answer,
Jeong-hwan.
Where's the jewelry?
Sorry?
Where's the jewelry I gave you?
That's…
-What's this?
-A gift.
It's for your stiff neck.
Sit down.
It feels good.
You can relax like this after work.
You hid it in the massage chair?
Because the chair is big,
there are a lot of places to hide it.
Are you crazy?
Why did you put it in there?
I almost sold it.
I never knew this would happen.
By the way,
you almost sold it?
How could I pay five million won for rent?
How could you lie about such a thing?
What did you do with my money?
It's in the bank.
Wait. Did you think I used it all
for myself?
You should've used it to lower the rent.
Why did you put that in the bank?
There's hardly any interest.
All GK shadows do that.
Because if something goes wrong,
I have to go back to running
a detective agency.
That makes no sense.
Can't a detective agency owner
lease a house?
You're right.
Why didn't I think of that?
So,
because you wanted to look normal,
you borrowed money
from a friend who's a loan shark?
Right.
What's this?
Can you tell me what happened
in detail?
I don't have
much to tell you.
Is that so?
Then I'll ask those punks
who took over my bed.
If I went in there and spoiled the mood,
that'd make you happy, wouldn’t it?
What? Are you that hopelessly in love?
You're up.
Long time no see, Spy Lee.
So that's why
you've been pretending to be dead
and living in hiding?
Then why are GK's Director Kim
and Kim Jae-wook
working together again?
What are they up to?
It can't be because of Spy Lee, can it?
They're up to something big, aren't they?
Kingmaker…
The president of Korea.
So what's the plan?
Do you want some water?
Yes.
What are you going to do from now on?
LEDGER
Yoo Byung-jun…
YOO BYUNG-JUN
WOOK'S GUKBAP
UI CHAIRMAN CHOI KYUNG-HWAN
CHARGED WITH BRIBERY
PROSECUTOR YOO IS DETERMINED
TO INVESTIGATE THOROUGHLY
The first thing we need to do
is to clear your name.
If something happens to you…
Anyway, this is something
we have to do no matter what.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
I'm sorry, honey.
You hate me, don't you?
Don't ever forgive me.
Did you do it for money?
Is that it?
Actually,
I was threatened.
What?
Cha Joo-eun
said she'd kill you if I refused,
so I had no choice.
Cha Joo-eun said she'd kill me?
He's the man Cha Joo-eun hired.
I took a picture secretly just in case.
Hold on.
MESSAGE
Answer my call
if you don't want it released.
Something urgent came up. Excuse me.
Honey, where are you going?
Who are you? Who the hell are you?
Meet me at the place I tell you.
Those pictures will go online
if you're even a minute late.
Hey!
Damn it!
Yes, he just left.
Hello.
Someone's tailing you.
Come out through the back door.
Don't look around!
As soon as you come out,
turn left and walk down the hallway.
Who are they?
Take the escalator going down.
-Jump to the side.
-What? Jump?
-Jump!
-Now? Darn it.
That way! There!
Get him!
Run to the main entrance.
-What now?
-Come out.
-Where is he?
-Where did he go?
-Gosh.
-Go that way.
-Yes, sir.
-Hurry up and get in!
-Damn it.
So?
Search harder, you bastards.
What the hell are you doing?
Are you a philanthropist or something?
I'm sorry, sir.
Cha Joo-eun is acting all cute with me.
What about the Chinese spy?
We're still looking for him.
Find him as soon as you can.
Let's use him to have Cha Joo-eun
stand trial in China
for being a double agent.
That could get her a death sentence
in China, right?
Yes, sir.
How tacky.
Cigarettes in this day and age?
You son of a bitch!
Are you up?
Why are you doing this?
I don't even know you.
That's exactly why I did it.
I didn't think you'd want to talk
if I suddenly asked.
Do you feel like talking now?
Yes.
What happened?
What do you mean?
Why have I become an industrial spy?
Well, that's because…
You were coerced, weren't you?
Find Cha Joo-eun and hand her over.
That's the only way
you can clear your name.
Do you understand me?
I can arrest you
right here and now.
I know you won't.
Me? An industrial spy?
You and I both know
that's an absurd claim.
So
tell me everything you know.
Let's join hands.
Join hands?
How could a cop join hands
with a civilian?
God, I'm so frustrated.
You and your principles.
Listen carefully.
GK
is behind this case.
What do you say?
Don't you feel the urge to get
to the bottom of this as a cop?
If you can show me that you're willing
to investigate this properly,
I might consider helping you.
If you're so confident,
won't it be better to cooperate with me
and reveal the truth?
The truth?
Do you still think such a thing exists?
People only believe the things
they want to believe,
whether it's true or not.
You're a cop in Korea
but still don't know that?
So what's it going to be?
Are you in or not?
Aren't you embarrassed?
Aren't you?
To be coerced like that.
They told you to stop investigating
and turn a detective agency owner
into an industrial spy.
The police are pretty much powerless
in everything they do.
If I were you, I would have quit already
out of shame.
Don't you ever call me again.
I will arrest you the next time we meet
no matter what.
What do you think he'll do?
We'll have to make him do it.
PORK RIBS APLENTY
Dad.
Joo-eun.
Why are you…
What happened?
Well…
Could you bring the charcoal?
Okay.
One minute.
Oh, God. It's so hot!
Gosh! Are you okay?
Goodness, it's so hot.
-God, that's hot.
-Oh, no.
Let's go inside.
Gosh.
Seriously.
Gosh, you should've been more careful.
You're such a baby.
Can you make it less painful?
Like Florence Nightingale?
Why didn't you tell me?
You should've let me know
that you were released.
I did. But
you didn't answer my calls.
I didn't?
So I thought you were avoiding me.
Why would I?
Work hasn't been going well lately.
That's why I couldn't pick up.
It hasn't?
What are you doing these days?
Nothing much.
I'm working at a detective agency.
I see.
What about you?
What's your plan for the future?
Well, I…
Chief Yang has offered me a place to stay,
so I'll be working here.
Don't do that.
Where's your conscience?
Are you seriously going
to inconvenience her again?
Also,
I'd like you to find a job
that could help you grow.
Whatever it is.
Gosh.
I've finished disinfecting it.
What about Mom? Have you spoken with her?
Joo-eun.
Could you not tell her about this
for the time being?
Why?
Because…
How should I put this?
I just don't feel ready to tell her yet.
And like you said,
I should find a decent job.
Once I find one, let's meet up.
Us three.
Come here.
-Why?
-Hurry.
What is it? I already washed my face.
Gosh, what is all this?
But I already washed up.
Done.
Thanks.
So Mi-young was hired by you.
What does that mean exactly?
Are you trying to come between us
when we're deeply in love?
You're her stalker, aren't you?
In order to divorce me, my wife…
No, she's no longer my wife.
So she hired you?
No. To be exact,
that female attorney hired you.
And you hired Yoo Mi-young,
an actress, to seduce me.
Is that it?
That's correct.
You're one sly bastard, aren't you?
Do you know how much money
she took from me?
Half. She took half of my wealth.
Why did I have to divide
my father's inheritance with that bitch?
How dare you, you bastard?
Let me go! You asshole! Let go!
Hey! You son of a bitch! Let me go!
Jeez!
You son of a bitch!
This watch…
Where did you get it?
Why do you ask?
Is that important right now?
Yes, it is.
Who gave it to you?
Hey! Damn it. Well…
I got it when I became
Assemblyman Kwon's head supporter.
You know Kwon Hyuk-jang, right?
He personally gave it to me.
You've picked the wrong guy to mess with.
Now, I get it.
Get what?
Hey! Okay!
Let go of my arm! Gosh!
-Let me see.
-Yes, sir.
Okay.
Call them.
Who, sir?
The police.
Right. Yes, sir.
It's me, Deputy Chief.
Come in.
DEPUTY CHIEF'S OFFICE
Yes?
MEDICAL EXAMINER
KIM HYEON-JONG
Yes.
Lee Jeong-hwan's autopsy
was canceled when the DNA results came in.
Then you closed the case immediately,
despite my opinion.
Did we ignore your opinion?
What do you mean?
Chief Jeong called me himself,
so I told him.
Didn't you hear?
Right. You see,
I was busy investigating another case.
I'm sorry, but could you tell me about it?
Well, what I told him was…
I measured the body's legs
but not the upper body.
And it turned out
that the legs were only 70cm long
when Lee Jeong-hwan was 185cm.
Well…
He could've had short legs, right?
Come on, Detective.
Haven't you seen his photos?
I could tell at a glance
that his legs were over 100cm.
GYEONGGI ROUTE 37 ACCIDENT CASE REPORT
LEE JEONG HWAN
PERSONAL INFORMATION
Lee Jeong-hwan.
Are you still alive?
If I were you, I would have quit already
out of shame.
Birthdate…
-You punk.
-What is it this time?
Should we have soju?
What do you say to pork ribs? My treat.
Pork ribs?
Let's go.
Yes, pork ribs.
Okay. Pork ribs.
One of our former detectives
runs this place.
It tastes rather ordinary
but they give you a lot of meat.
I see. We do prefer
quantity over quality, right?
Anyway, you're paying for this.
Eat as much as you want.
All right.
Here you go.
How many servings? Two grown men
should have at least four servings.
-Right?
-No, just two will do.
And two cold buckwheat noodles.
Noodles? So soon?
Hey, the noodles are for dessert.
Exactly.
You bastard. You're trying to fill me up
with noodles.
I can see right through you.
God, you have such poor taste.
You don't know how to enjoy pork ribs.
You're supposed to wrap the meat
in the noodle.
Haven't you tried it?
Try it. It's really good.
That'll be all.
Okay.
Right, drinks.
You know, I used to drink like a fish
when I was young.
-That's right.
-Two grown men
should drink at least an entire box.
One soju and one beer.
We're not drinking much.
Okay.
Gosh, you're being so cheap.
-Sir.
-What?
You want extra meat?
In your dreams.
About Cha Joo…
Charge what?
It's nothing.
Please give us a lot of garlic.
You'll have to get it yourself.
-I see.
-Ma'am.
By the way, where's the restroom?
It's in the building to the right.
Get the key.
May I have the restroom key?
-It's 50,000 won.
-Pardon?
Just kidding.
I see.
I love your game plan.
You're emptying your bowels
before the meal.
That's the spirit!
Go flush everything down
then fill up your stomach with meat.
-Good luck.
-Right.
We don't have toilet paper.
Oh, I'm just going to pee.
I see.
You left your phone. Here.
Thank you.
Be careful.
The eye is quicker than the hand.
I'll remember that.
It's really good, isn't it?
Have some.
Eat up.
It's delicious.
DEPUTY CHIEF SEO MAN-HO
Give me a minute.
Sure.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. Goodbye.
Salute.
My God. What's wrong with you?
When did you come out?
Did you overhear the conversation?
No, I didn't.
I'm not Jaime Sommers.
Anyway, something urgent came up.
We'll have to take a rain check.
I haven't had my full share yet, okay?
I'll finish eating next time.
All right, you punk.
Tidy up your clothes, will you?
Bye.
We're going to do this again.
Just go.
Myung-hyun.
Hey.
What is it?
What are you doing here?
I was just…
-Well…
-What are you doing with a wiretap?
This is good.
Gosh, you're eating so well.
Where does all the cholesterol go?
DEPUTY CHIEF SEO MAN-HO
Give me a minute.
Sure.
Yes, sir.
A Chinese spy is going to turn himself in?
Yes?
Fine, let's join hands.
You've made the right decision.
I guess the Korean police
aren't completely hopeless.
But first, I have a question.
Who was that motorcycle guy?
I mean the accomplice
who helped you escape.
Was it Lee Jeong-hwan?
HANSANG HOT POT
-Poong-yeon.
-Yes?
Oh, sorry.
Rice soup, my foot.
Why does it smell like
the countryside in here?
Aren't you hungry?
Today,
we'll be having a special Korean dish.
Dried radish greens and rice soup.
I didn't know you could make that.
It's not like you.
Here.
It's good.
Where did you learn to make this?
My father taught me.
What?
My parents used to run
a rice soup restaurant.
I'm afraid I can't fall for your lies
anymore.
You make it so obvious.
Did you take cooking classes for me?
You don't have to be embarrassed.
Guys who can cook are popular nowadays.
HANSANG HOT POT
Rice soup…
Who might be the most powerful
person here?
YOO BYUNG-JUN
Yoo Byung-jun…
WOOK'S GUKBAP
Yoo Byung-jun.
Edward.
Kim Jae-wook.
Wook's Gukbap?
Oh, my! I'm sorry!
Oh, no! I'm so sorry!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm truly sorry. I really am.
I'll pay for the laundry.
No, I should buy you a new suit, right?
I'm so sorry. I should, right?
No, it's okay.
BAE JEONG-HONG
NATIONAL TAX SERVICE
-I'm sorry.
-It's tasty.
-Oh, dear.
-Are you okay?
-Goodness.
-What happened, ma'am?
It's okay. I'll take care of this.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, my!
What are you doing?
Mr. Cho.
Where are your manners?
Apologize politely to him.
I'm sorry, sir.
Wait outside. I'll be there soon.
What should I do?
I'm kind of in a hurry right now.
Gosh, I have no cash on me either.
How about this? I'll give you my number.
Once you wash…
No, buy a new suit and give me a call.
I'll wire you the money immediately.
Would that be all right with you?
Do you mean your cell phone number?
Yes.
Sure, that'd be great.
BAE JEONG-HONG TAX
Hello, Mr. Bae.
Hello? Hello, Ms. Chung.
Yes, it's me.
It's about your childhood friend
you mentioned today
that you wanted to find.
The rice soup restaurant.
I've found a dried radish greens rice soup
place that fits your description.
I guess I'm quite skilled.
The business license was registered
under Kim U-jik.
I'll text you the address.
KIM U-JIK
16-24 GIL, BUCHON, GYEONGGI-DO
Poong-yeon.
Yes?
We need to go somewhere else.
-I'll give you the address.
-Okay.
GIL, BUCHON
Where is this place?
A friend's house.
An old friend of mine.
Should I go inside?
No.
I will.
He's my friend after all.
Investment? You, Ms. Cha?
Is it because I run a spy agency?
I was going to invest
about ten billion won.
Thanks for believing in me, Mom.
-How's it going with Cha Joo-eun?
-I'll prepare the news about her.
It's time to repay me.
These bastards.
-Let's go.
-This case is confidential,
so a special department has been set up.
If we can't send Cha Joo-eun to China…
There's not enough evidence.
If Lee Jeong-hwan's really alive,
I can charge you for fraud.
This is Lee Jeong-hwan
from GK Innovative Vision Room.
-Have you ever stowed away on a ship?
-So?
-Should I accept?
-I don't see why you shouldn't.
-Let her do it.
-Yoon-kyung…