♪On an old stage♪
♪Light still shines♪
♪Tragedy and joy are sung♪
♪But tricks can't be dodged♪
♪Seek for purity in a chaotic world♪
♪Anger and sorrow unfold♪
♪Whether it's fate or love♪
♪Is it meant to be or just chance♪
♪In the haze, the truth emerges♪
♪Clouds above, dust below♪
♪After the embrace comes the storm♪
=Wild Fire=
=Episode 15=
Senior.
Yes?
I just got the news.
Guan Qingyang committed suicide.
What?
(I thought what he said was)
(all to exonerate himself.)
(Why would he do that?)
(Kang Shao is a key figure
in this matter.)
Yuan,
have people
watch over Kang Shao.
Make sure.
Okay.
Hurry up.
(Before it's completely confirmed,)
(I can't let Xingkai know about it.)
(If it's true,)
(I'll keep this secret hidden forever.)
Yanshu,
you know very well
I don't like that actress.
Why did you bring her home?
From now on,
don't call her 'actress.'
She is my future wife.
Will you really marry her?
Did you consider my feelings?
Soon, you'll
fulfill your wish
and marry Guan Xingkai.
Shen Muling poses no threat to you.
Fulfill my wish?
Yanshu,
all these years,
you never understood me.
Rong City has many ambitious young men.
I don't have to cling to Guan Xingkai.
I'm doing it for you.
We grew up together.
Years
on the frontline.
Scars on your body,
graves for your men.
Do you think I don't know?
Every time you return,
you lock yourself in the study.
I know you're not happy.
So I want to help you.
The Guans are a century old.
If I can marry Guan Xingkai,
their power can be used for our family.
Don't you understand?
Forget it.
You've never thought
of understanding me.
(Xin Sheng Chang Marine Goods)
Excuse me.
Ying said you want to see me.
Who are you?
Miss Xu, you need not care who I am.
You only need to know one thing.
I can rid you of your greatest threat.
Ridiculous.
I don't have the 'greatest threat.'
Shen Muling.
How could you possibly know her?
I naturally cannot.
But this woman
is fickle and unfaithful.
She flirted
with another young master before.
After gaining many benefits,
she turned and hitched up with Mr. Guan.
Our young master couldn't stand it
and swore
he wouldn't let her off easily.
An actress is ultimately lowly,
unwilling to change her ways.
However,
why should I believe you?
I heard the Commander's welcome banquet
is in a few days.
By then,
as long as you
put this drug
into Shen Muling's drink,
I will
naturally provide you
with a satisfactory result.
Sedative?
(Shen Muling,)
(prepare to die.)
Miss Xu, we hope
you will help more in the future.
Sure thing.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you
for attending my welcoming banquet.
Now the situation is turbulent.
We all need to be united
and work together.
Each of you present
is a pillar of your respective fields.
Let's all join forces to navigate
these difficult times.
Well said.
We have prepared some wine.
Enjoy yourselves.
- To Commander.
Commander Xu, you've always
kept away from women.
Now you suddenly
have a beauty by your side.
I assume something good
is about to happen.
Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations.
I'm late.
Any good news about Commander Xu
and Miss Shen?
Mr. Guan,
don't tease me.
If we are talking about good news,
it should be about you
and my sister, Qingqing.
Qingqing,
your fiancé is here.
Haven't you been expecting him?
Stop making fun of me.
Xingkai,
don't listen to his nonsense.
Actually, I am quite familiar
with Miss Shen.
If we truly become a family,
wouldn't that be even more perfect?
Mr. Guan, stop joking.
I'm acquainted with you,
but not very familiar.
Muling,
it was me being immature before.
I thought you liked Xingkai,
which is why I offended you.
Now that you've entered
the Commander's Mansion,
and my brother loves you,
we are also a family.
So we should get along well,
shouldn't we?
Muling,
if you're willing to forgive me
without holding grudges,
drink this toast.
We can let bygones be bygones
and forget our grievances.
How about it?
Okay.
It's rare
to see you two getting along well.
How about the four of us
have a drink together?
Sure.
Zhang.
Since...
Since we can't agree on it...
(Kang Shao worked for Guan Hanyang.)
(It's normal for him to contact Zhang.)
(But why are they
pulling each other here?)
Alright.
Shen Muling is really valuable.
Everyone wants her dead.
Alright.
Then let her prepare more money.
No.
Senior.
Muling,
for the opening dance,
care to dance with me?
Of course.
Xingkai,
aren't you going to invite me?
Okay.
Don't get distracted.
Are you okay?
It seems the Commander's Mansion
will soon have two weddings.
You don't know, huh?
The one who was recently paired
with Mr. Guan is none other
than Miss Shen next to the Commander.
Miss Shen is really something.
Both Mr. Guan and Commander Xu
fell for her.
People aim for higher.
If these two couples work out,
it'll be fun to watch.
Are you okay?
Miss Shen,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
It must be the wine.
I'm a bit dizzy.
Let me take you back.
No need.
On such an occasion,
you should stay.
Liusu.
Take her to her room
for a good rest.
Yes.
Ying,
help them out.
Yes.
Xingkai,
I've prepared some cold dishes
over there.
Let's go take a look.
Let's go.
I've long admired your reputation.
Miss Shen,
are you alright?
I'm fine.
I'm feeling a bit hot.
I can't breathe.
Liusu,
Miss Shen seems to be drunk.
Go to the kitchen
and make some hangover soup.
I'll take her back to her room.
Miss Shen,
you'll feel better
after drinking the soup.
I'll be right back.
Thank you.
Ying, wait a moment.
What's wrong?
Miss Xu wants you over.
Impossible.
I have to take Miss Shen
back to her room.
Can't Miss Shen go by herself?
Then I'm leaving.
I've told you.
The one punished won't be me.
Wait.
Miss Shen,
can you enter the room yourself?
I'm fine.
You can go.
Miss.
Okay.
Let's talk next time.
Is she in her room?
Miss,
did you call me here for something?
I didn't.
Didn't you send Chunsheng
to call me over?
You good-for-nothing.
How did you fail such a simple task?
Xingkai just found an excuse to leave.
And Chunsheng sent you away.
Something happened.
Get me another cup.
Excuse me.
Thanks.
Yes?
Where is Miss Shen
from the Ruyi Theater?
Miss Shen? I don't know.
Oh.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
♪Fire devours tears♪
♪Cries fade in the smoke♪
♪Storms gather♪
♪Glory falls like ashes♪
♪Sleeves flutter♪
♪You sing of love and hate
on high stage♪
♪Yearning brings only sorrow♪
♪But in your eyes, I found resolve♪
♪After one final song of parting♪
♪We'll meet again only through tears♪
♪Silently, pain blossoms♪
♪In the flames, we embrace♪
♪After one last song of joy and grief♪
♪Lovers sigh under the endless moon♪
♪Your face, like a mirage♪
♪Becomes clear again in the ruins♪