♪On an old stage♪
♪Light still shines♪
♪Tragedy and joy are sung♪
♪But tricks can't be dodged♪
♪Seek for purity in a chaotic world♪
♪Anger and sorrow unfold♪
♪Whether it's fate or love♪
♪Is it meant to be or just chance♪
♪In the haze, the truth emerges♪
♪Clouds above, dust below♪
♪After the embrace comes the storm♪
=Wild Fire=
=Episode 3=
Senior.
My junior is here.
Things have truly changed.
You're having a hard time recently.
So I should support your business.
I should be grateful, Senior.
At the previous gatherings,
I was always the one entertaining them.
Experience it today yourself.
After all,
Master never let you suffer.
Yes, Senior.
Kneel.
Call me Second Madam.
Who do you think you are
to associate yourself with me?
Yes, Second Madam.
You're much more resilient than before.
Not long ago, you were still
flourishing in Rong City.
How does it feel now?
You want to kill me?
Do you think I don't hate you?
Why is it that everyone only sees you?
Why are you so high and mighty?
You should've died together with Master,
since you had a mother-daughter bond.
You...
People in the troupe used to say
it's lowly for me to be a concubine.
Now,
even the troupe head
has become a mistress.
What do they say now?
Silly me.
I said it wrong.
At least I am official
with a proper title.
But you, Miss Shen,
are just something kept outside.
You are even lower than me.
Yes.
Wait.
Come here on your knees.
What are you doing?
Second Madam!
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean it.
Since when is there a Second Madam here?
You...
What happened?
Madam.
It's my fault.
I was clumsy
and offended Second Madam.
Second Madam?
What is that?
We only has a second concubine.
There is no Second Madam.
It seems
she misses her sisters in the troupe.
A concubine who used to be an actress
is so attached to the theater?
What are you doing here?
Zhang.
Yes.
Liang Man,
since you have married into our family,
you must follow our rules.
Now,
the master is bedridden
and Xingkai has just returned.
You should understand the importance
of harmony and prosperity.
Madam.
It's her.
How dare you!
The madam is lecturing.
How dare you interrupt!
She's new here.
Ms. Zhang,
you haven't taught her
the rules well enough.
Yes, Young Master.
Someone!
Punish her.
Yes.
Madam, I'm sorry!
Madam!
I don't mean it, Madam!
For Liang's improper behavior,
from today, she'll copy the Lotus Sutra
and stay in the Buddha hall
to reflect on herself.
(Senior,)
(hang in there.)
(The show is just beginning.)
How dare you
look for trouble with my girl!
I'll help you regain your dignity.
Mr. Guan.
She dared to bully my girl.
Give her a good scolding.
If you do it well,
each will be given 10 silver coins.
No wonder the Ruyi Theater
couldn't hold its ground back then.
She has evil intentions.
Look how she's bullied Miss Shen.
I feel sorry for her.
Vicious. Always thinking
about harming people.
And always the kind ones.
Exactly.
She has a viperous heart.
(It's ridiculous.)
(The indecency of this young master)
(is just like his father.)
(Over these years,)
(it's been hard for Madam.)
Spending all her time...
Kneel properly.
Just the antics of clowns.
She should see where she is.
No place for her little games.
She thinks no one can handle her.
You've suffered great injustice.
These few days,
you'll stay here.
I would like to see
who dares to look for trouble.
She should get lost.
Just a lowly concubine.
Thank you, Mr. Guan.
How dare she do this here!
(Shen Muling,)
Exactly.
(do you think you can avenge Lanyu)
(by relying on this prodigal?)
What filthy methods.
(Let's see where you end up in the end.)
Miss Shen.
Someone's outside.
When acting,
it has to be convincing.
The two of us
are entangled now.
Master used to
enjoy having a drink alone
in the courtyard.
Miss Shen,
tell me about my mother.
Higher.
Straight.
(Master often told me,
character is not in others' eyes.)
- The more they despise you,
(- But in one's own heart.)
the more you should respect yourself.
(Being too rigid)
Understood.
(will make you suffer.)
Thank you.
Thank you for staying with her
for all these years.
Since childhood,
Master had always protected me.
But now,
there is no one to protect me.
Don't cry.
I will protect you.
Get some sleep.
I'll guard you outside.
Master!
What's wrong, Master?
Master.
Open your eyes.
What happened?
Master.
Master!
(Lanyu)
Liang Man.
We should have killed
Shen Muling back then too.
Look how I've been tormented.
Be gentle.
Second Master.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
If you let that little wench
have her way,
I'll get ruined sooner or later.
Don't mind her.
Look at this.
I thought this bead
was lost in Lanyu's room that night.
Where did you get it?
It's almost exactly the same.
Second Master,
I know you are good to me.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have
gotten me out of the theater
and into the Guan family
to enjoy this wealth and status.
But I just can't stand
that old woman.
Will you take me away?
Wait a little longer.
The Guan family is about to change.
By then,
you can do everything
as you wish.
Change?
♪Fire devours tears♪
♪Cries fade in the smoke♪
♪Storms gather♪
♪Glory falls like ashes♪
♪Sleeves flutter♪
♪You sing of love and hate
on high stage♪
♪Yearning brings only sorrow♪
♪But in your eyes, I found resolve♪
♪After one final song of parting♪
♪We'll meet again only through tears♪
♪Silently, pain blossoms♪
♪In the flames, we embrace♪
♪After one last song of joy and grief♪
♪Lovers sigh under the endless moon♪
♪Your face, like a mirage♪
♪Becomes clear again in the ruins♪