♪On an old stage♪
♪Light still shines♪
♪Tragedy and joy are sung♪
♪But tricks can't be dodged♪
♪Seek for purity in a chaotic world♪
♪Anger and sorrow unfold♪
♪Whether it's fate or love♪
♪Is it meant to be or just chance♪
♪In the haze, the truth emerges♪
♪Clouds above, dust below♪
♪After the embrace comes the storm♪
=Wild Fire=
=Episode 2=
(France)
(Xingkai, my son,)
(after so many years,)
(the world is changed.)
(I will not be alive for long.)
(You must live on.)
(Do not inquire into the cause.)
(It's my fate.)
Mother, I don't want to
go to the Guan family.
Be good.
Xingkai.
I'm an actress.
Staying with me
will only ruin you.
No!
Let's go, Young Master.
Mother.
Mother!
You are Master's son?
See for yourself.
(Xingkai, my son. I won't be alive
for long. You must live on.)
It is Master's handwriting.
Miss Shen,
what do you plan to do now?
You don't think I killed Master?
You believe me?
Without the pendant and this letter,
do you think
you could walk out of there alive?
I will find out
the culprit who killed her.
As for you,
you are now involved with me.
They see you as my mistress.
I offer you this chance,
and will you take it?
Senior. Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Guan Xingkai
is Master's son.
What?
How could he be...
Master has many things
hidden from us.
That fire
was not just an accident.
What is it?
Senior.
Many people came here today.
You'll have to go on stage.
But now...
(I need to know
who caused my mother's death.)
(Miss Shen, you can think about)
(what to do next.)
It's okay.
I don't care about rumors at all.
But Master's death is still unclear.
It might be complicated.
The investigation will be risky.
Let's keep avoiding contact,
so I don't cause trouble for you
and our theater.
Okay.
Young master, you told Miss Shen
about your background.
Can you trust her?
What if she did kill...
Well...
If she were the murderer,
she wouldn't have visited Liang Man.
All these years,
she's been caring for my mother.
I should thank her.
But this fire
not only killed my mother,
but also ruined her.
Then...
Chunsheng,
buy the theater in the west of the city.
Go now.
Yes.
(Ruyi Theater, Miss Shen)
♪Hearing about Bianjing City,
my blood boils♪
♪A faithless Wang Kui lives
in the prime minister's house♪
Get off, a murderer performing?
♪He pairs up in curtains and drapes♪
♪Forsaking me,
the daughter of the Jiao family♪
She thinks she is pure and noble.
She's trying to latch onto Mr. Guan.
So what if she is?
The Guan family will never
let her be Mr. Guan's wife.
He'll discard her once he's bored.
Get off!
What is that?
What are you doing?
Looking for trouble?
Bravo!
Great singing!
Brilliant!
(Life is like a play.)
(How can a tragic play)
(compare to the changes of life?)
(My acting needs improvement.)
Bravo.
You sing very well.
It's Young Master Guan Xingkai.
Why is he protecting Miss Shen?
You can stir up a storm
wherever you go.
What?
Miss Shen?
Are you scared now?
I'm not afraid of anything.
As long as I'm here,
I won't let Miss Shen suffer.
I will
sing with you.
Thank you then, Mr. Guan.
So you agreed?
Miss Shen
has latched onto the Guan family.
Indeed.
(Since Miss Shen will join me,)
(we must let the whole city know)
(that your Ruyi Theater)
(is supported by me.)
(Ruyi Theater)
How is it? Do you like it?
You're truly going to sponsor me?
When acting, you have to be convincing.
My mistress
can't look shabby.
What?
You have regrets?
No.
Singing alone is tiring.
It's nice to have a partner.
Go.
♪The two sworn lovers at Caoqiao♪
♪Studied together for long years♪
♪With mutual affection and respect♪
♪I have already promised you my heart♪
(Mother, we're separated for years.)
(When I came back,)
(we are already worlds apart.)
♪Face flushed, hard to speak♪
♪Do you remember♪
♪Eighteen♪
Senior!
There's trouble!
Liang Man wants you to
perform for her tomorrow.
What should we do?
She's getting impatient.
I will be there tomorrow.
(Guan Residence)
- Senior...
- Call me Second Madam.
Who do you think you are
to associate yourself with me?
At the previous gatherings,
I was always the one entertaining them.
Experience it today yourself.
Kneel.
♪Fire devours tears♪
♪Cries fade in the smoke♪
♪Storms gather♪
♪Glory falls like ashes♪
♪Sleeves flutter♪
♪You sing of love and hate
on high stage♪
♪Yearning brings only sorrow♪
♪But in your eyes, I found resolve♪
♪After one final song of parting♪
♪We'll meet again only through tears♪
♪Silently, pain blossoms♪
♪In the flames, we embrace♪
♪After one last song of joy and grief♪
♪Lovers sigh under the endless moon♪
♪Your face, like a mirage♪
♪Becomes clear again in the ruins♪