♪Fearlessly braving all the thorns
along the way♪
♪Yearning for the dawn as it breaks
through the seams of the clouds♪
♪Facing storms despite being small♪
♪Diligently fulfilling one's mission
and leaving a strong impression♪
♪Ride the wind and embrace the dawn
that's just a step away♪
♪Keep moving forward,
for an unfinished journey awaits us♪
♪Let's go into battle and witness
the intertwining of light and darkness♪
♪Stand guard as our ideals
burn fervently like a torch♪
♪The stubborn light illuminates
the direction where dreams begin♪
♪No longer lost,
it's the belief of our lifetime♪
♪As the mist disperses, seek answers
that call from within your heart♪
♪Every moment,
set sail without hesitation♪
=Prosecution Elite=
(Key Project of the Supreme People's Procuratorate.)
=Episode 33=
If only I didn't drink.
If only I didn't wore revealing outfits.
Maybe I wouldn't be targeted
if I didn't do so.
And, you won't end up like this.
Everything is destined.
I was usually the drunk one.
I didn't drink today.
And, someone was trying to bully you.
Of course I had to intervene.
But you shouldn't suffer because of it.
That's wrong!
Ling.
I...
I feel guilty about it.
Now,
there's no way for me
to atone for my mistake!
There's no way!
I know you're nice to Siyue.
You protected him
whenever I gave him a beating.
Because of that,
I cannot afford to
let anything happen to you.
Ling!
Ling?
Siyue?
- Xin.
- Siyue?
Stop knocking.
She left.
She left together with her son.
They didn't pack their stuff.
They left the rest of their belongings to me.
They left?
How could they leave just like that?
It's been over a week since they left.
Just let her leave.
This place is literally hell on Earth.
It's best for them to leave.
That's the best choice.
Look at you.
You left just like that.
How can I return
the favor I've owed you?
Qian Tianxin.
Qian Tianxin?
I'll tell you the same thing.
There's nothing for me to tell you.
Fine.
I hope you can be as calm as you are
when the court announces your verdict.
Bring her back.
Ni,
aren't we interrogating her
to inquire about Zhao Jikai?
Why didn't you mention his name at all?
I've done my investigation.
There was no monetary transaction
between her and Zhao Jikai.
Zhao Jikai only provided her with
the users' personal details
for her to manipulate.
She intends to bear
full responsibility for it.
I wonder what kind of reaction
she'll have
if she finds out that Zhao Jikai
has turned himself in.
However, Zhao Jikai only
has limited clues.
If Qian Tianxin doesn't tell us
where the money had gone,
there's no way we can solve this case.
I know.
I know it's difficult.
However, when the criminals
get their hands on the money,
it's literally impossible
to get them back.
And, there's only so much we can do.
Prosecution and convict them of their crime.
However, if we don't get back the money,
the victims won't be able to
accept reality.
Sometimes, I wonder
why we work so hard.
We can't get back the money.
So what if they were punished
because of their crimes?
Han Xuan,
we're working hard
so that the criminals know
that the law won't
allow them to get their way.
We'll definitely bring them to justice.
The harder we work, the better the result.
If so,
Ni, do you think Zhao Jikai knows
where the money had gone?
He has a special relationship
with Qian Tianxin after all.
We'll know in a second.
Let's go.
What else do you need me to say?
You're pretty straightforward.
I've already turned myself in.
Look at the state I'm in.
I have nothing to lose.
Fine.
We'll cut to the chase.
Tell me where the money
Qian Tianxin had scammed people of
had gone to.
I don't know.
She didn't let me
participate in too much of it.
You guys know this too.
Crime syndicates like these
only contact each other in one way.
We do things independently at the same time.
She never tells me anything
that I'm not supposed to know.
Zhao Jikai,
within the crime chain,
your relationship with Qian Tianxin
was the tightest.
You're telling us that
she told you nothing?
Do you think we'll trust your words?
I know.
You're prejudiced against me.
No matter what I say or do,
you'll think
that Qian Tianxin and I
have more than just an ordinary relationship.
You will never understand
our relationship.
You didn't experience
any ordeals in your life.
Qian Tianxin and I
started from the bottom.
We got to where we were by taking
one step at a time.
We've been through so much together.
We depend on and trust each other.
None of us can be replaced.
I can even go as far as to say
that we can sacrifice ourselves
for each other.
If that's the case,
why didn't you get together
with Qian Tianxin?
Why must you go
and flirt with Li Yitang?
You see, we mustn't be
too stubborn sometimes.
I know
that once I confirm my relationship
with Qian Tianxin,
we'll restrain
and request things from each other.
That will be
the end of our relationship.
Sometimes, one's relationship
can last longer
if it isn't based on love.
And,
you said I flirted with Li Yitang.
Can you be sure
who started the flirting first?
Must I be the one
who flirted with her first?
Don't stare at me like that.
I know you two are great friends.
You don't need to hate me.
You don't need to be hostile to me
because I'm your common enemy.
My relationship with Li Yitang was over.
To me,
Li Yitang was an unexpected occurrence.
Your appearance in her life
was an unexpected occurrence too.
I can even go as far as to say
that your appearance
has tainted her life.
Tainted her life?
A relationship isn't as simple as you think.
Many people often fail due to their relationship.
You see, many things
are not within the realm of reasoning.
And, there are no solutions to them.
Love arises without reason,
and deepens with each passing moment.
Love knows no reason,
and remains unwavering until death.
After hearing that,
I feel sorry for Li Yitang.
In front of you,
she has no EQ to speak of.
She has her own ideas.
And, she isn't as stupid as you say.
Let's forget about Li Yitang for now.
She can deal with her own affairs.
According to the information we have,
Qian Tianxin isn't A.
That's right.
Does that mean you know who A is?
I only know
that Qian Tianxin isn't A.
Zhao Jikai,
since we managed to crack
this intricate crime syndicate,
which you're a part of,
we'll find out who A is eventually.
If you tell me his identity in advance,
at least you can win a chance
to obtain leniency.
I've already told you enough.
Moreover, I truly have no idea.
Li Yitang always said
that you were very capable in your job.
I believe that the truth
will be revealed one day
as long as you're around.
You didn't tell us where the money went
or who A was.
However,
your doings in Huiquan were premeditated.
You didn't do them on a whim, right?
I've told you everything
about the crimes I did.
Answering you right now
will not change the severity of my sentence.
I have nothing to say.
You're just as silly as Li Yitang.
It's no wonder you two are buddies.
However,
your taste in men is inferior to her.
What do you mean by that?
It's nothing.
I was just expressing my sentiment.
You're inexperienced
when it comes to relationships.
You still have a shallow understanding of men.
You're narrow-minded.
When it comes to this,
you should truly learn from Li Yitang.
(Payee  Grand total)
I'm running out of ideas.
My computer is dying on me.
I've analyzed and compared
all the suspicious data I have.
I couldn't find out
where the money went.
What about Zhao Jikai?
Did you not obtain any
useful clues from him?
Seems like they can't find
a breakthrough point here.
We can only depend on ourselves now.
But it's not like I didn't gain anything
out of my interrogation.
What's on your mind?
I do have something
that I'm suspicious about.
However, I cannot confirm my suspicion yet.
What about this?
Give me some time to
straighten out my thoughts.
I'll tell you guys
if I achieve any progress.
Did you find it?
Look, I already...
Why don't you try another port?
I'm sure all of you know
(Luo Jingxiao)
that Professor Luo has left the company.
Here, I will make
an official announcement.
Professor Luo has indeed resigned from his post.
(Xiao Mu'en)
Everyone, pull yourself together.
I have a piece of great news.
The investment we've attracted
will be transferred
to our bank account soon.
The foreign investment group
that we had introduced to Mr. Xiao
has signed the agreement officially.
Mu'en, brief everyone about the situation.
Yes, Chairman.
Everyone,
due to Huibo's outstanding performance,
Huiquan Group has received the acknowledgment
of new investors.
And, they've signed
the investment agreement.
Last time, I was lucky enough
to attend the shareholder cum director
meeting together with Chairman.
The shareholders and directors
were very satisfied with the result.
They agreed and acknowledged
the joining of the new investments.
The new shareholder
will become the second major shareholder
of our company.
I hope everyone can
keep up the good work
so that the company
can reach new heights.
Besides that,
I will use this opportunity
to make another announcement.
I've decided to transfer 5%
of my shares in Huiquan
to Mr. Xiao voluntarily as his reward.
But Chairman...
Don't reject my request.
This is the acknowledgment
Huiquan Group gives toward
successful people.
We must be truthful in speech
and firm in action.
- Congratulations, Mr. Xiao.
Thank you.
Mu'en,
you're my lucky star indeed.
Thank you, Chairman.
Here.
Let me offer you a toast.
You flatter me.
Chairman, I should
offer you a toast instead.
No.
I have to offer you a toast first.
I'm not offering a toast to you solely
because of Huiquan.
I'm offering a toast to you
as thanks too.
Here.
Cheers.
May you stay healthy.
May we stay healthy.
You can't hold your liquor well, huh?
Sorry about that.
I don't take baijiu often.
Mu'en,
you're a great boy indeed.
It's just that your lifestyle
is too simple.
Look at you.
Tea is the only beverage you take.
You don't smoke, drink,
or have any bad habits.
Let me tell you something.
Not only do you need to excel in work,
but you also need to enjoy life.
Don't learn from me.
You'll regret it when you grow old.
Yes, Chairman.
Chairman, I'm sure you were a workaholic
when you were young.
You see,
there's a reason
why people like me are successful.
I think you know that too.
You have to suffer the hardships
that other people cannot.
You have to endure things
You have to do things
that other people cannot.
Of course,
that doesn't mean we can
do things that are illegal, am I right?
After that, you'll be able
to enjoy the success
that other people crave.
Chairman, you're right.
If you desire something,
you should strive for it.
Chairman, I will keep it up.
Good.
Mu'en, I'm old now.
From now on,
the world will belong
to youngsters like you all.
Huiquan Company is a high-tech company.
Now,
I'm building a modern
entrepreneurial management system.
I won't let that useless son of mine
taint the reputation of my company.
However,
I'm selfish to a certain extent.
I feel like I've let him down.
Even if he's not in Huiquan,
he can still inherit my shares and my seat.
We have a deep affinity.
And, you're an outstanding employee too.
That's why I want you to teach my son.
I want my son to work beside you.
Teach him how to work.
Chairman, I'm incapable of that.
As the saying goes,
fathers know their sons best.
You're a veteran yourself.
Why don't you teach him yourself?
He has a rebellious mentality.
The more I want him to do something,
the more he'll reject it.
I have no way to teach him.
How's your relationship
with your father?
It's pretty good.
Basically, he lets me do my own thing.
Chairman, I understand.
I will make arrangements for that.
If so, when do you plan
to send him to the company?
I haven't told him about it yet.
I need to discuss it with him first.
What about next week?
Okay.
I will make arrangements for it.
Chairman, here's another toast to you.
To you.
Okay.
Here.
Cheers.
Mister, we're here.
Mister, that's too much.
Keep the change.
Thank you, mister.
Dad,
you're still awake at this hour?
Are you suffering from insomnia again?
Enunciate your words properly.
Look at you.
You go out every day.
It's either you waste your time
with all those bad influences
or you get yourself drunk.
Look at the time.
This won't do.
I know what you're going to say.
That's highly inappropriate of you.
But Dad, speaking of which,
have you fulfilled
the duties of a father?
You only have feelings for your work.
You don't feel anything for me.
What have you done for me
except for giving me money?
What gives you the right
to criticize me?
How could you speak to me
in that manner?
Are you trying to drive me to my grave?
Look at how the other youngsters
are striving to improve themselves.
You were born with a great background.
Even so, you don't cherish it.
No choice.
I was born lucky.
You have to be in charge of me
since you gave birth to me.
He's hopeless indeed.
You don't take after me at all.
Since young,
you always expected me to be number one
in everything I did.
That's too tiring.
I can never achieve that.
And,
you're asking the wrong person.
You should ask my mother
whether I take after you or not.
You scoundrel!
How could you say that?
Hold it right there!
Listen up!
From tomorrow onward,
I will suspend all of your cards.
You have to head to Huiquan
and learn from Xiao Mu'en.
Xiao Mu'en again?
You always talk about him.
Since you like him so much,
why don't you acknowledge him
as your son instead?
And, I'm Yin Tiancheng.
You want me to work under him?
He doesn't deserve it.
You!
Dad?
Dad, don't scare me.
You're so useless.
I worked hard my entire life
for your sake, you know?
You have all the resources in the world,
yet you don't want to utilize them.
You're really driving me
to my grave here.
Fine, let's make it this way.
I won't work under him
for over a month.
Look.
- Sir.
- You're busy enough.
Didn't I tell you not to come?
You still insisted on coming here.
It's fine.
I was planning to visit you
when I was sending Xiaoting home last time.
However, it was pretty late.
That's why I didn't interrupt you.
Where's Xiaoting? Isn't she at home?
She went to look for Zhang Xiaobei.
She said...
It's fine. I'll do it myself.
She wanted to learn
and improve together with him.
Sorry for the embarrassment.
Sir, don't say that.
You're being too courteous here.
Thank you for understanding me.
Right now, me and my daughter
are just like friends.
It's all thanks to you.
That's not it.
I did nothing.
It was mainly because
Xiaoting was sensible.
She has grown up too.
By the way,
I heard from Xiaoting that you resigned.
Yeah.
I resigned not long ago.
What's with the sudden decision?
After giving it some thought,
I thought it was satisfying enough
for me to experience it once.
I don't want to work all my life.
It's time for me to rest.
You're right.
Now, you can travel around the world
and take pictures of
all those beautiful places.
Why don't I hold
a class reunion for you?
Let's gather.
No need for that.
No, thanks.
I'm doing fine right now.
Alright then.
How have you been lately?
You must be doing well, huh?
I'm still in the same state.
Is Xiao Mu'en still trying to court you?
Sir, that's a sudden question.
Actually, I clarified things
with Xiao Mu'en long ago.
I told him that
we could only be friends.
That personal issue
is related to the rest of your life.
You need to take it seriously
and try to resolve it
as soon as possible.
You have to act prudently.
Do not rush things.
I think I get what you mean,
yet I think I don't.
It's nothing.
I always tell Xiaoting the same thing.
When is Xiaoting coming back?
Why don't we have a meal together?
Mr. Liu,
this place is nice indeed.
You have great taste indeed.
If I must say, Mr. Liu,
you do enjoy life to the fullest.
You're fine with having worldly desires,
yet you can abstain from them
without any trouble.
Mr. Xiao, I had a deep impression of you
during the board
of directors' meeting last time.
Although you're an R&D man at heart,
you're flexible with the way you do things.
Mr. Liu, please take care of me
in the future.
I've benefited from
the foreign investment we received too.
The other shareholders and I
had sold some of our shares
and got some cash in hand.
Mr. Xiao, thank you so much.
Please tell us if you have such
great bargains again in the future.
Not at all.
You flatter me.
I remembered that I had a feeling
when I first saw you.
I felt that we would have
a pleasant cooperation in the future.
Is that so?
Tell me about it.
You see, some words
cannot be said out loud.
They can only be implied.
However, Mr. Liu,
I believe that you'll understand it
when you see this.
No wonder you asked me out.
I thought you had
a lucrative deal for me.
Speak.
What are you up to?
Mr. Liu,
you misunderstood me.
I bought these pictures
from my friend who was working for the media.
You can treat it as if
I've solved this issue for you.
Rumor has it that
you're scared of your wife.
However, I think that's a good thing.
Men who are afraid of their wives
are good men.
They respect women.
What do you think?
As for women like them,
they're but fleeting moments.
I understand.
But Mr. Liu, this is my suggestion.
I don't think
you should let your wife see them.
If she knows about it,
she'll be heartbroken.
You'll be worried about her by then.
Now, the marriage law punishes those
who commit adultery quite seriously...
Mr. Xiao,
let's stop beating around the bush.
I never owe people any favors.
What do you want me to do?
Here,
I have an agreement.
(Agreement of persons acting in concert)
Mr. Liu, please check it for me.
Mr. Liu, in the future,
no matter if it's a major
or minor issue,
I hope you can maintain solidarity with me.
Only the two of us?
That's pointless.
You don't need to worry about that.
(Part B: Mr. Liu)
(Huaxin Villa)
Tang!
Li Yitang!
She's not around.
What should we do?
She's not at home or
at Zhao Jikai's house.
Where can she go?
What did she say
when you called her?
She said she was busy,
and she hung up on me.
I think she just wants to be alone.
I don't know.
I feel jittery.
Say, she won't do anything silly
because of this matter, right?
Dear, stop scaring yourself.
Li Yitang has a good grasp
of her abilities.
I don't think
she'll get herself in trouble.
Yeah.
You love to imagine things, don't you?
I think she went out to take a breather.
Don't overthink it.
I hope so.
Why are you rubbing your eyes?
It's nothing.
I said I wanted to
atone for my mistake, right?
I wanted to repay Mr. Xiao's favor
and make it up to you.
I've been working overtime
quite a lot lately.
That's why my eyes were dry.
Make it up to me?
You can never make it up to us
in this lifetime.
I'll buy you some eye drops later.
Mr. Xiao looks cultured
when he wears spectacles.
But he looks like a nerd
You have no idea.
Mr. Xiao wore spectacles
in order to look cool.
His eyes are fine.
Huh?
He doesn't have near-nearsightedness?
Don't you know?
No, he doesn't have it.
One time, when I was in his office,
I saw him looking for documents.
The letters on it were tiny.
I couldn't even see them.
But he wasn't affected
even though he didn't
wear his spectacles.
I thought he had bad eyesight
since he was wearing spectacles.
Me too.
Yeah.
I think only people
who worked under him
could find out things like that.
Yeah.
Two years ago,
Mr. Xiao said he wanted me
to start a business together with him.
Back then, I was just laid off.
Programmers our age were basically unwanted.
It's all thanks to Mr. Xiao.
I was also addicted
to gambling back then.
You still dare to say that?
It's all thanks to Mr. Xiao.
I had no idea what would happen to me
if he didn't help me out back then.
Enough. Stop being sentimental
in front of another person's house.
Do something practical.
Take your wife out for some good food.
Let's go.
Don't worry about it. Let's go home.
I couldn't sleep
after you left.
I remembered that I wrote down
Zhou Ling's contact number.
I searched through
all the shelves and cabinets
in order to find it.
And, I finally found it.
Here you go.
This is Zhou Ling's contact number.
I finally found it.
Hello?
Is this Ms. Zhou?
Sorry about that. I must be mistaken.
Okay. Goodbye.
Hello?
Is this Ms. Zhou?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Hello?
(Huiquan)
Aren't you guys exhausted?
Stand up and do some stretches.
Young Master Yin, you can go ahead.
We're busy with work.
We can't join you.
Please forgive us.
Don't call me that.
It's not like
I'm the remnant of feudalism.
We emphasize equality
in a network-based company like Huiquan.
From now on, call me Tiancheng.
Okay.
What about this?
I'll buy you guys coffee.
Is anyone willing to run the errand?
I'll go. What do you want?
Forget it. I'll buy them myself.
I'll buy them for you guys.
Wait for me.
What are you doing?
Sorry about that.
You thug!
How dare you molest me?
Who are you calling a thug?
You!
Explain yourself.
I didn't even touch you.
I did nothing.
You're still pretending?
Everyone, look at him.
He molested me in broad daylight.
He's shameless!
You better explain yourself.
Of course you won't admit it.
He's from Huiquan.
Stop filming me.
What a jerk.
You better mind your words.
What? You want to beat her up?
Call the cops. Stop filming him.
I'll call the cops.
Don't think that you can escape.
You can only leave
after explaining yourself.
Stop filming me!
The cops will be here soon.
You'll be humiliated.
Don't think that you can escape.
We have evidence.
Of course you won't admit it.
(Look at this man, Yin Tiancheng)
He already called the cops.
Don't think of running away.
He touched her butt.
(Yin Tiancheng, the employee of Huiquan)
We'll expose a pervert like you!
(He harassed me and didn't admit)
We already called the cops!
(Let him know the consequence of harassment)
Don't think of running away.
Mr. Xiao.
Hi.
- Mr. Xiao.
Mr. Xiao.
Where is he?
He went to buy coffee.
Buy coffee?
Don't tell me he was
buying coffee for you guys?
That's right.
You guys are something else.
How could you make the prince
buy coffee for you all?
Listen up.
You guys should assist him
with his work.
It's his first day at work after all.
Understood?
Understood.
Alright, get back to work.
Okay, please take care.
Mr. Xiao, take care.
Let go of me!
The cops will be here soon. Don't move.
So what if the cops are coming?
I did nothing wrong.
Who called the cops just now?
The cops are here.
What's the matter?
This guy molested that lady.
And, he doesn't want to admit it.
Did you guys witness it personally?
I didn't.
The lady accused him of it.
What's going on?
Sir, I did nothing.
I was carrying the drinks
with both hands.
I have no way to molest her.
Who knows what you used to touch me?
Disgusting.
Say that again?
Enough.
I'll check the surveillance camera.
The truth will be revealed by then.
What a scandal.
What the heck is this?
This is wrong.
He's fine after doing that?
What is it?
This is too much.
We're friends for many years.
You guys don't need
to talk behind my back.
Yin,
you ask for it yourself.
You better
don't get angry.
Get angry?
You think too highly of me.
I've been through
all kinds of situations.
Your son was touching a woman's butt
in broad daylight.
Nonsense!
I'm sure it was the work
of a media outlet.
Can't you guys even differentiate
between true and fake news?
This is real!
Take a look if you don't believe me.
(Yin Tiancheng, the employee of Huiquan)
(He harassed me and didn't admit)
(Let him know the consequence of harassment)
You see?
Huh?
Yin,
you're better than us in every aspect.
But look at your child.
Now, we don't compete in terms of
wealth or fame.
Now, it's our children.
I quit.
That's where true wealth lies!
What a shame.
Bad news travels fast, huh?
My goodness!
Look!
Yin Tiancheng is famous now.
I didn't expect him
to be someone like this.
Not only is he ignorant and incompetent,
but he's also a pervert.
But his profile picture
looks pretty good.
Huiquan is on the Hot Search again.
You missed the point.
A scandal like this happened
when he went out to buy coffee.
He's the harbinger of doom.
Here, I bought random drinks.
I don't know what you guys wanted.
Thank you.
Here.
Have it while it's hot.
Young Master Yin, I'm sorry.
My tummy feels uncomfortable.
I don't think I can take coffee.
Thank you so much.
Distribute them.
(You are not that kind of person.
Tiancheng, you did it wrong.)
(Someone did it on purpose.)
(You and Huiquan are famous now,
but they are all criticizing you.)
What's with the weird attitude?
I didn't do anything.
The cops already
checked the surveillance camera.
That woman already apologized to me.
If you don't trust me,
you can ask the staff in the cafe or the police.
We didn't say anything.
Please calm down.
If so, why are you guys keeping quiet?
Don't tell me you guys think
that I molested her?
We didn't.
We dare not do so.
You dare not do so?
Who do you guys take me for?
Do you think I'm that desperate?
I thought you guys were top students?
Can you use your brain for once?
We didn't say anything.
Fine.
All of you don't dare to say it, huh?
I understand now.
He's infuriated.
Yeah.
Why is he so anxious?
I'm impressed.
He can't take it already?
He left.
What's the matter?
(Hello, Mr. Xiao.)
(This is a call from Mr. Ding.)
Answer it.
Hello, Mr. Ding.
(Mr. Xiao, are you sure Yin Huiquan can still be
in charge of the company?)
I don't think he should remain
as the chairman.
Look at what his son has done.
(How can he manage Huiquan like this?)
(In the past, many things had happened.)
We thought they were just
mere coincidences.
We thought we were just unlucky.
But look at what happened.
He has no excuses now.
Hmph.
Who gave him the power
to mess around in the company?
(As the vice chairman,)
(I need to do something about it.)
And, the directors and I
want him to be removed
from his position
(as the chairman.)
Mr. Ding,
don't be angry. Actually, this matter
isn't directly related to
Chairman himself.
You guys are being unfair
to the chairman here.
♪Shimmering tears
under the flickering candlelight♪
♪No need to panic
when you're feeling lonely and sad♪
♪If you lose your way♪
♪It's best not to fantasize♪
♪Even if it's far,
it's still in the distance♪
♪Every effort and hard work
have been in vain♪
♪It's the moment
of being unappreciated♪
♪The hands were once held tightly♪
♪Even if the appearance has changed♪
♪As long as there remains
a heart beating with passion♪
♪Storms are beautiful♪
♪Free to go wild♪
♪Perhaps this is more
like a symphony of destiny♪
♪There will be clear skies someday♪
♪A breeze blowing
and clouds stretching♪
♪We can admire
after it becomes a memory♪
♪Every effort and hard work
have been in vain♪
♪It's the moment
of being unappreciated♪
♪The hands were once held tightly♪
♪Even if the appearance has changed♪
♪As long as there remains
a heart beating with passion♪
♪Storms are beautiful♪
♪Free to go wild♪
♪Perhaps this is more
like a symphony of destiny♪
♪There will be clear skies someday♪
♪A breeze blowing
and clouds stretching♪
♪We can admire
after it becomes a memory♪