♪Fearlessly braving all the thorns
along the way♪
♪Yearning for the dawn as it breaks
through the seams of the clouds♪
♪Facing storms despite being small♪
♪Diligently fulfilling one's mission
and leaving a strong impression♪
♪Ride the wind and embrace the dawn
that's just a step away♪
♪Keep moving forward,
for an unfinished journey awaits us♪
♪Let's go into battle and witness
the intertwining of light and darkness♪
♪Stand guard as our ideals
burn fervently like a torch♪
♪The stubborn light illuminates
the direction where dreams begin♪
♪No longer lost,
it's the belief of our lifetime♪
♪As the mist disperses, seek answers
that call from within your heart♪
♪Every moment,
set sail without hesitation♪
=Prosecution Elite=
(Key Project of the Supreme People's Procuratorate.)
=Episode 34=
Mr. Ding, don't be upset.
This matter has no direct connection
to the Chairman.
What you're doing is not fair to him.
(You don't have to explain for him.)
We all see what's going on.
The board of directors
has the responsibility
to protect
the interests of the shareholders
and oversee Huiquan
to ensure it runs smoothly.
I heard he put his son under you.
He's making you babysit him,
(to look after his son
and keep him under control.)
If everyone follows in his footsteps,
will Huiquan still be able to grow?
Mr. Ding, please calm down.
How about this?
I apologise on the Chairman's behalf.
Please convey my apologies
to the board as well.
Why don't we do this?
We'll ask his son
to leave the company immediately
and clarify that he has nothing to do
with our company.
He will not be allowed
to hold any position
in the company anymore.
How about that?
Let's each take a step back.
After all, without the Chairman,
Huiquan wouldn't be where it is today.
Isn't that right?
Well, give us a minute to discuss it.
Okay. Please take your time.
Well, what do you guys think about this?
It's obvious, isn't it?
He can't be the Chairman
if he hollows us out.
Yes, you're right.
That's true.
Tell you what,
we'll let it go this time.
Don't let it happen again.
It's just this once.
Zhao Jikai has been
in trouble for a long time.
The president of the company
should be a member of the board.
Plus, the partner you brought in,
the second largest shareholder,
has given his full power of
attorney in writing
(and has exercised his right
to vote for you to join the board.)
(In accordance with the relevant articles
of association and regulations of the company,)
(we, the directors,
now ask that you join the board)
(as its new member.)
Mr. Ding,
I don't think that's appropriate.
We can only be assured
if you hold a certain amount of power.
The process will be swift.
This is our wish,
as well as everyone else's.
Thank you.
I thank the board of directors
for their trust and support.
I'll treat you well
on your next visit to Huiquan.
All right.
That's all for now.
Chairman,
you asked Professor Luo
to come back and assist us.
He gave his idea.
Yin Tiancheng
was accused of sexual harassment
and blasted on the Internet.
My first response was to tell them
to delete the post and regulate the comments.
We are an Internet company.
We can't let them stir up trouble
in this industry and step on us.
But Professor Luo stopped me.
He refused to let me delete the post
or let me organise a team
to refute the claims.
Mr. Yin, Professor Luo is here.
Let him in.
Yes.
Professor Luo is here.
Let him explain himself to you.
Luo. Have a seat.
I know I shouldn't bother you
after you resigned.
But you're the only one
who can solve this problem.
In a matter of hours,
Yin Tiancheng's case
was all over the Internet,
and everyone knows about it now.
Luo, what should we do?
You've been in the Internet business
for so long.
Surely you've noticed something fishy
about this case.
You mean this is a plot against Huiquan?
Yes.
On the one hand, they chose to do this
in this particular period of time
because Hiquan urgently needed funds.
That requires
a positive corporate image.
On the other hand,
matters that concern gaming
could easily attract the attention
of the Procuratorate.
If we use means to restore
Tiancheng's reputation
and delete the post and comments
in the backend,
we will get caught by the Procuratorate
if we are not careful. Is that right?
Yes, it's entrapment.
Yin Tiancheng is your weakness.
You will act carelessly out of concern.
They're betting on you losing your calm.
If the Procuratorate catches you,
it'll be hard for you to defend yourself.
How very calculated.
Thank goodness
you see the clear picture, Luo.
Well, we can't do nothing
and stand idly by, can we?
Take the legal route.
We'll do two things.
First step. Collect evidence
and report the case.
Report the person who published the post
for online defamation.
According to the judicial interpretation
by the Supreme People's Court
and the Supreme People's Procuratorate
regarding the handling of crimes
involving the illegal use
of information networks,
if the same piece of information
has been viewed
or clicked on more than 5,000 times
or if it has been forwarded
more than 500 times,
it should be considered
as a serious circumstance
as stipulated by criminal law.
Are you confident
that a case will be filed?
We cannot be certain
if this is deliberate falsification
or a misunderstanding yet.
That's for the Public Security Organs
to investigate.
In fact, it doesn't matter
if a case is filed or not.
What matters is
we make our stance clear.
By posting that we've reported the case,
we can prove Yin Tiancheng's innocence
to a certain extent and
turn public opinion around.
What about the second step?
The second step is to go after
the website that deliberately
published this information too.
Refer the matter
to the government department.
Have the CAC intervene and
remove the offending content
and issue a warning.
It's clear that the perpetrator
is targeting Huiquan.
As the victims,
we'll promptly report this issue
to the Procuratorate.
Good.
I'll have
our corporate lawyer handle this.
No.
There's an even better candidate.
(Hello, everyone.)
(After the police pulled up
the surveillance footage,)
(I realised that
it was all a misunderstanding.)
(When the other person involved and I)
(passed each other by...)
What are you guys watching?
Hurry up and eat.
Ni, we're watching an apology video.
We're getting in on the gossip, Ni.
This is a huge one. Isn't it, Jia?
Huge?
How so? Tell me about it.
This is what happened.
Yin Tiancheng, Yin Huiquan's son,
was caught red-handed sexually harassing
a woman in public.
The woman said
Yin Tiancheng touched her behind.
Well, before even checking
the surveillance footage,
the woman took photos of his work ID
and him and posted them on the Internet.
She wanted to cancel him.
And the netizens jumped in
to criticise Yin Tiancheng.
Goodness. Look at the kids these days.
They can find one's
personal information so fast.
Here they are, all enjoying the gossip.
We've missed out on a lot,
Director Wang.
Missed out on what?
We've got our hands tied with
the cases on our hands.
We've got no time for all of this.
This is the most ridiculous bit.
There has been a huge plot twist.
That woman uploaded
a ten-second apology video on Huibo.
(Sorry.)
(I'm so sorry)
(for all the inconvenience caused.)
(We've apologised to each other.)
(Please do not spread
any form of this matter any further.)
(This will be the last time
I speak out on this matter.)
(Thank you.)
That poor Yin Tiancheng.
He got cancelled for no reason.
We're going live this week, right?
It should be Director Wang's turn.
Director Wang,
I think you can talk about this case.
This concerns the protection
and privacy of personal information.
Besides, it's actually quite similar
to the extreme Internet defamation case
that the Supreme People's Procuratorate
has just gotten involved in,
where a private prosecution
turns into a public prosecution.
Moreover, it's good
to strike the iron while it's hot
and spread legal awareness
among the public.
Yes.
The 7·7 case of the woman in Hangzhou
who picked up a parcel
and was slandered and defamed.
The Procuratorate had to issue
a Prosecution Recommendation
for it to go from a private prosecution
into a public prosecution.
Indeed. This is a pivotal landmark case
where the Supreme People's Procuratorate
demonstrates the importance
of taking a strong stance
against online defamation
from a judicial perspective.
All right.
We have the same idea.
Zhao, hurry up and finish lunch
and sort out the full story for me.
Copy that.
Are you the one looking for me?
Yin Tiancheng?
Why are you dressed like that?
I don't dare to come out
without this getup.
Why are you here?
I want to report the situation.
All right. Come with me.
I have a lot of complaints
about the Procuratorate.
What's the matter with you guys?
You guys were aggressive
when it came to investigating Huiquan.
A bunch of prosecutors kept
coming to the company repeatedly.
But where are your people now
that I've been framed?
Answer me, Prosecutor An.
What did a civilian-run enterprise
like Huiquan do to you guys?
When something happened,
you guys kept biting on us
and refused to let us go.
But now that I've been victimised,
you guys won't do anything.
First of all, I understand how you feel.
But it's neither
justified nor meaningful
for you to come at us
with your grievances.
Secondly,
you should've followed the procedure.
You should've reported the case
to the Public Security Organs first.
Even if a case is filed and the referral
is made for prosecution,
it should be handled
by the district procuratorate.
Not the Supreme People's Procuratorate.
I'll be dead by the time
you guys go through the process.
Prosecutor An, I'm not going anywhere
unless you help me.
I've been cancelled anyway.
There's nowhere I can go
once I step outside.
Give me a reason why I have to be the one
to handle this case.
Because you were in charge
of Huiquan's case.
And I'm related to Huiquan.
Take a look at this.
Someone hired a gangsterdom PR
to spread the rumour
that I sexually harassed that woman
and spread it all over the Internet.
Everything was manipulated.
I paid someone to look into it.
For the sake of my reputation.
This has nothing to do
with my father, Yin Huiquan,
and Huiquan Group.
This is all the proof I can find.
You're a prosecutor.
You should be able to find
more on the Internet.
Looking up such personal information
on the Internet
will involve personal privacy.
You'll also need to prove
that the prosecutor
is connected to the case being handled.
Everything still has to be done
in accordance with legal procedures.
You're just dismissing me.
Let me put it this way.
A dozen people can now manage
tens of thousands of accounts
on the Internet.
They are able to send
videos, pictures, and posts,
from the same IP address
at the same time,
all of which
are deliberately fabricated.
The purpose is
to inflame the public's emotions.
They will also post provocative comments,
delete comments that question them,
set the pace, and get uninformed people
to make follow-up comments
and share these things.
They are using the sense of justice
of these netizens
to manipulate public opinion
and accelerate the spread of rumours.
But in this case,
Huiquan Group has continued
to abide by the law
and did not act in retaliation.
This showed me a new perspective
of your father, Yin Huiquan,
and made us understand that many things
may not be as simple as they appear.
We also highly suspect that
there might be a third party
trying to muddy the waters.
A third party?
What do I do now, then, Prosecutor An?
Report to the public security
using the appropriate procedures.
The Procuratorate will maintain order
on the Internet using our own way.
Please have faith in the power
of the rule of law of your country.
Be it you as an individual
or Huiquan Group,
we will make the fairest judgement.
Well,
I can't just sit around and do nothing!
I know you're anxious,
but it's no use worrying.
I suggest you watch
more law popularisation videos
from the Procuratorate's channel
and spend less time
watching videos of pretty women.
Your father had Professor Luo
tell you to come and find me, didn't he?
Procuratorate Legal Awareness Day.
I'm on duty today.
Hello, everyone. I am a prosecutor
at Jiangcheng People's Procuratorate,
Wang Heyu.
(I am a prosecutor of the Public Interest
Litigation Department as well.)
Today, we will be commentating on
current events.
I want to talk about the re-appropriation
of social death and personal information.
(Innocent)
(The case we are talking about)
(took place on a certain date in 2021.)
(Mr. Yin went to get coffee
from a coffee shop.)
(The Internet
is not a land beyond the law.)
(Break the law)
(Vigilantism is not an option.)
(If everyone were to solve matters)
(that should be
within the jurisdiction of the law)
(by exposing them,
the dignity of the law)
(would be trampled on.)
(The power of the law
will be disregarded.)
(The private sphere
of Internet users will be violated.)
(The network environment
will deteriorate.)
(I would like to remind everyone)
(to use tools of the law
to defend your rights.)
This incident took less than two days
from escalation to conclusion.
But through uncontrolled and disorderly
dissemination of information,
inappropriate discussion has yet to cease
even until today.
(Law weapons)
(If the entire incident
had not been captured)
(by the surveillance cameras,)
(the consequences
would've been unfathomable.)
(It could've affected
someone for the rest of their life.)
This person might not only be
the person involved.
Tomorrow, it could be you, me, or them.
(Civil Code of the People's Republic of China)
Today, I will tell you that personality
is protected by our laws.
Article 111 of the Civil Code
of the People's Republic of China
clearly states Any organisation
or individual that needs
to access other's personal information
must do so in accordance with the law
and guarantee
the safety of such information
(and may not illegally collect, use,)
(process, or transmit
other's personal information.)
Tell prosecution stories,
conduct effective legal education,
engage in interactive discussions,
and keep up with trending issues
concerning the people.
(Thank you for watching)
(the official account
of the Jiangcheng People's Procuratorate.)
(Stay tuned every week.)
That was okay, right?
Director Wang.
Your logic is impeccable.
Protection of personal information
in the Civil Code.
Your articulation was
simple, clear, and direct,
with a perfect balance of priorities
and a seamless flow.
Don't... Don't do that.
You're a flatterer.
I was a nervous wreck.
I just made these up on
the spur of the moment.
But keep it up.
Next time, you do it.
No problem.
You sound confident.
I mean it.
Hello?
Ling?
Ling.
It's me.
Listen to me.
It's terrible!
Someone has been looking for you lately.
(Hello?)
(Did you hear me?)
What's going on?
(Madam Qi, Missing call)
(Li Yitang)
(Impartial and Responsible)
We recently received anonymous reports
from members of the public.
There are several that
are worth digging into.
The first is a report on
the alleged monopoly
and data-driven price discrimination
by Huibo, a live-streaming platform
under the Huiquan Group.
I suggest
the Public Interest Litigation Department
refer the case
to the Anti-Monopoly Bureau
of the Municipal Administration
for Market Regulation in a timely manner.
If the case is true,
suggest that they open a case
for investigation.
Yes.
Prosecutor Guo,
nowadays,
driven by the effect of the Internet
and the economy of scale,
many leading Internet companies
have begun to show trends
of monopoly or even oligopoly.
Therefore, regulating anti-monopoly
in the digital space
will be one of the future
directions of our work.
We also received a complaint
from the manufacturer
of the famous skincare product,
Maininice.
It concerns Huibo too.
They claim that a host
named Meow-Meow Cat is selling
large quantities of counterfeit products
with the brand's trademark on them,
severely infringing upon their trademark
and intellectual property rights.
An Ni, contact the Administration
for Market Regulation at once
and inform them of this matter
and have them investigate
and verify the case.
Likewise, if it is verified,
recommend they open a case.
Yes, Prosecutor Guo.
Indeed.
According to reports from the public,
there are now more and more
counterfeit products being sold
through live streaming.
I have also found that since the launch
of the live-streaming feature on Huibo,
many more hosts have joined in.
But not every one of them
meets the standard.
Many of them came from
other live-streaming platforms,
and they themselves
have a lot of problems.
Meow-Meow Cat looks very familiar.
I think she has sold goods on other
live-streaming platforms before,
and her sales did very well.
Yes. I often come across
them saying slogans such as
"direct from the manufacturer",
"authenticity guarantee", or "get ten times
money back if you receive a fake product".
I've also purchased
from live-streaming platforms,
and I've found that some of the hosts
actually fake their orders and sales
to increase their credibility.
This kind of behaviour
is false advertising, except
executed in a more discreet manner.
I wonder if Meow-Meow Cat
is doing all of this.
Let's do this.
Conduct further exchange
and communication
with our comrades
from the Administration
for Market Regulation.
This time,
not only do we need to find out
if there was any false advertising,
but we'll also need to investigate
if she infringed upon the brand's trademark
and whether she was
manufacturing counterfeit products
as she sold them.
Once verified,
we will resolutely crack down
on the entire operation,
thoroughly investigate the entire chain,
and promptly transfer
all clues of suspected crimes
to the Public Security Organs.
This includes individuals
and online platforms
who knowingly provide
customer service, copywriting,
and other forms of assistance
to the hosts engaged
in fraudulent activities.
Objectively speaking,
these people also assisted
in the commission of the crime
and are joint offenders.
Understood, Prosecutor Guo.
We must crack down
on these sales at the source
and break the chain of crime
at the root.
Indeed. Platforms are not as innocent
as they claim to be.
They turned a blind eye to the sale
of counterfeit trademarked goods
on their platform.
This time, they must be made
to suffer the consequences.
In recent years, we've witnessed
an increasing number of cases
linked to the Internet.
The new forms of cybercrime
are constantly evolving
and have infiltrated almost every aspect
of people's production and life.
Everyone, there is a long way to go
to combat the new cybercrime,
so I hope that you will do your best
to build up your legal knowledge
as soon as possible
and practice your basic skills.
- Yes.
Prosecutor Wang.
Hello.
I'm Yin Tiancheng.
Sorry for making you come all this way.
It's okay. I have a car,
so it's not a big deal.
What's this?
These are the gifts
you sent my wife, Li Jun,
on her live stream.
I calculated the cost
of these gifts
according to the platform.
I did the calculations.
You gifted a total of RMB18,600.
It's all here.
Why are you giving it back to me?
There's no way I can accept you
returning my gift.
Besides, this is just the usual gifting.
I could give any live streamer
way more than this amount in
a night on Huibo.
Yes, I know.
The gifting function
on live stream platforms
is a standard business model.
It's a form of interaction
between the live streamer
and the viewers.
But I think it's important
to spend wisely on everything.
You're young.
You shouldn't spend
all your time and energy
on things like these.
You should spend reasonably.
Practise moderation in everything.
This is nothing.
A lot of live streamers
can't thank me enough
for spending on them.
I don't care about them.
I only speak on behalf
of me and my wife.
So please take this money back.
One more thing.
I will not be delivering
the goods you ordered.
I've contacted the platform's backend
customer support.
They will be in touch.
But I suggest you cancel
the orders yourself.
That would be best.
What is the meaning of this,
Prosecutor Wang?
You stood up for me
when everyone else
refused to believe me.
I just wanted to show my appreciation.
Can't I do that?
Tiancheng,
my wife is just running a small business.
I'm just an ordinary prosecutor.
If you really are interested in
her products,
you can make a reasonable purchase.
It was your first time
joining her stream, and you placed
such a huge order.
Who would think
that this is a normal transaction?
Also, I didn't go out of my way
to help anyone.
I'm only doing my job.
I will not treat you differently
just because you are Yin Tiancheng
and your father is Yin Huiquan,
the chairman of Huiquan Group.
I only did it because I am a prosecutor
of the people,
and you are a member of the people.
You're different from the others.
Are all prosecutors like you?
To settle something without saying a word
and speak with such clarity
without an ounce of arrogance.
Thank you.
Thank you
for your recognition of my work.
Keep the money.
Goodbye.
Where are you going?
Let me give you a ride.
No need. I always to work on foot.
[*11th lines bus means on foot.]
(Huiquan Corporation)
The Municipal Supervisory Authority
of the Anti-Monopoly Bureau
wants to talk to us
after receiving a tip
from the Procuratorate.
This is a warning letter.
We have been told
to make changes and rectify ourselves
in accordance
with the anti-unfair competition law
and e-commerce law.
But if we do that,
it'll mean another crisis for us.
Chairman, I think
while this appears to be a crisis,
it could very likely be
an opportunity for the company too.
If we can react quickly
and take remedial action,
it may be the perfect time
to turn a bad thing into a good thing.
I believe that an excellent company
needs to stimulate and bring out
its comprehensive strength
and abilities all the more
in the midst of crises.
That is what makes
a mature and healthy company like ours
different from the others.
Chairman,
if this matter is handled properly,
our company's reputation
will not only be restored
but our popularity
might even be expanded.
Well said,
Mu'en. Let's do this.
Write back
to the Anti-Monopoly Bureau.
Declare our stance
and show them our corrective measures.
How should I word it, Chairman?
I think what you said was good.
You can also tell them
that Huiquan is open to suggestions
and are actively involved
in rectifying the situation.
You can add this as well.
That under the correct leadership
of the Anti-Monopoly Bureau,
we will improve
the management of the market
and promote a healthy, stable
and fair development of the market.
Perfectly said, Chairman.
It is at such critical times
that we must make a timely statement.
Jiang, be prepared
for the administrative fines as well.
If we do get a fine,
I have looked into it.
It would be around 3%
of Huibo's annual turnover.
You must be prepared for that.
We must ensure the normal flow of funds
for the company in any case.
Besides that,
the investigation will take a long time.
So let's not disclose this
to the board and shareholders yet.
Chairman, if we don't tell them
about such a serious matter
and we do receive a fine,
I worry the board will...
Oh, I'll take responsibility
if anything happens.
Just do as I say.
(Huibo, the broadcasting platform)
(under the city's leading enterprise,
Huiquan Group,)
(may become the first enterprise
in our province to be investigated)
(Huibo is investigated for anti-monopoly)
(for anti-monopoly cases.)
Mayor,
it's Mr. Yin Huiquan of Huiquan Group.
Give me the phone.
Mr. Yin.
Mayor Xu.
Good evening.
Sorry for you calling you this late.
Mr. Yin,
it must be something urgent for you
to call me at this hour.
Let's skip the pleasantries.
Please cut to the chase.
Nothing escapes you, Mayor Xu.
This is the matter.
Our city's Procuratorate provided a tip
to the Municipal Administration
for Market Regulation,
and the administration wasted no time
in conducting an investigation
on Huiquan Group's Huibo.
You know Huibo is a product
that Huiquan recently acquired.
We want to do something
for the people of Jiangcheng.
As a pillar industry,
both Huiquan Group and I have put
a lot of work and effort into it.
There is still a difference
between a live-streaming platform
and the Internet.
A live streaming platform
combines both social networking
and instant monetisation.
However, no matter how hard we try,
we are still faced with the suspicion
of monopolising the market.
We might even be served serious fines.
As the head of Huiquan, I can only ask
the officials that serve us
to help mediate wherever possible.
Mr. Yin, I'm not sure
about this matter yet.
I'll find out what's going on first.
Within the framework of the law,
and without generating
any negative impacts,
if it is indeed necessary,
I will formally bring up the issue
at the municipal government's
committee meeting
and discuss it at the assembly.
Will this satisfy you?
All right.
I'm very pleased with that.
Thank you, Mayor Xu.
That would be the greatest support
you can give us.
Thank you very much.
All right.
Let's keep in touch. Goodbye.
Here.
Mayor, I think we shouldn't get involved.
Check with the Municipal Administration
for Market Regulation.
If Huiquan has followed
all the regulations of the market,
then just let them know
that the municipal government
fully supports it.
There's no need for us to hide.
But it is important to be cautious
and prevent regulatory lag.
If the conditions
for closing the investigation are met,
then we will focus
on guiding and promoting healthy competition
and the development of enterprises.
Of course, capital must not be allowed
to expand in a disorderly manner.
Market behaviour must be regulated.
Yes.
(Jiangcheng Public Security Bureau)
Captain He.
Master. Meow-Meow Cat is Liu Yanfei.
What's our next step?
What's the update
on the Municipal Administration
for Market Regulation's end?
They had a third party
test the counterfeit products
purchased by the victims.
Maininice, the business, also provided
its own quality inspection report
and trademark registration certificate.
We have conclusive evidence.
Apply for a warrant of detention
and prepare for the arrest.
Got it.
(Ladies and gentlemen.)
(More contacts)
(Welcome to China Jiangcheng Airlines.)
(An)
(When you enter the cabin,)
(please note
the seat number on the aisle,)
(the luggage rack,
and take your seat accordingly.)
(Hand luggage can be stored)
(in the cabin luggage rack
and under the seat.)
(An Ni, blocked list)
(Please ensure that the aisle is clear.)
(Thank you for your cooperation.)
(Ladies and gentlemen.)
(Welcome to China Jiangcheng Airlines.)
(When you enter the cabin,)
(please note
the seat number on the aisle,)
(the luggage rack,
and take your seat accordingly.)
(An Ni)
(Hand luggage can be stored)
(in the cabin luggage rack
and under the seat.)
(The number
you dialled is currently unavailable.)
(Please try again later.)
(Ladies and gentlemen.)
(Our plane will be taking off soon.)
(Please make sure
you turn off your mobile phones)
(and electronic devices)
(and put on your seatbelts. Thank you.)
Hello, Miss.
Please turn off your phone
or set it to flight mode.
We will be taking off shortly.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you.
Friends!
Do you know why my skin is so nice?
That's because I use Maininice!
(Meow-Meow Cat,)
(people are asking
if our products are authentic.)
(The people who asked that)
(are definitely not our fans.)
(Listen. I have my own sources.)
Only I, Meow-Meow Cat,
have its online sales agency rights!
We don't get the goods
straight from the manufacturers,
- but our channels...
- Are legitimate!
(Meow-Meow Cat,
they're asking if they get a discount)
(if they buy more.)
That's a great question!
Only today!
Exclusively in Meow-Meow Cat's
live stream!
This discount is only for my fans!
Super low prices!
(So if you haven't done so yet,)
(be sure to follow me)
(and join my fan group!)
Follow the host, and don't get lost!
- The host will teach you... Okay!
- How to take care of your skin!
Countdown from five.
Five, four, three, two, on!
Put on the links!
Police. You are suspected of selling
and trafficking counterfeit goods.
We are now summoning you
in accordance with the law.
Please cooperate.
Stand in a line against the wall.
Come here. Get up and go over there.
- Close the live stream, Zhang.
- Come here.
Stand against the wall.
Are you the host?
Name.
Meow-Meow Cat.
Your real name.
Liu Yanfei.
Do you know why we're here?
No.
You know
what you did.
I see you've developed
a habit of counterfeiting.
(Terminal 1)
(Hello. The number you have dialled
is currently unavailable.)
Ms. Li.
Li Yitang? It is you.
It's me.
Why are you here?
I came to send my schoolmate off.
I see.
Why are you in this getup?
Well, my schoolmate came,
so I took him around for a few days.
I got myself sick.
I caught a cold, so I put on a mask.
What about you?
I just got back
from a business trip to the south.
I heard you've been
promoted to president.
Congratulations.
Actually, things are kind of awkward
for Mr. Zhao right now.
It's fine. Don't overthink it.
The military camp stays,
but the soldiers come and go.
Huiquan will continue to operate
no matter who leaves.
I still miss the time
when the three of us worked together.
I don't want these things to separate us.
In the future,
if you need my help with anything,
just let me know.
All right.
We're all in Jiangcheng.
There will be plenty
of opportunities for us to meet.
Is anyone picking you up?
No, I haven't gotten a cab yet.
Why don't I give you a lift?
My car is right there.
Sure.
- I'll take you up on your offer, then.
- Come on.
- Let me carry that for you.
- Thank you.
Liu Yanfei, you previously sold goods
on another platform.
Why did you switch to Huibo?
Well, the fees were cheaper,
they had more comprehensive
live-streaming functions,
and the service was better.
And when did you
start selling counterfeit goods?
I can't remember.
The beginning of this year, maybe.
This year?
Do you think
we won't be able to find out
if you delete the replay footage?
I started last year.
You used to be an entertainment streamer.
Why did you decide to sell
and manufacture counterfeit goods?
That's the only way
to maximise monetisation.
Relying on those gifts is unstable,
and it depends on the mood of the fans.
They're both time-consuming,
so I might as well sell goods instead.
At the start, I sold a lot of products
from different brands
just to have a try and help sell them.
I was given different percentages
of commission by the merchants.
Then I discovered
that Maininice, in particular,
was really popular
and sold very well.
But Maininice's manufacturing prices
are too tightly regulated.
I could barely make any profit.
I had no choice.
So you guys decided
to produce your own products
and sell them instead.
The quality
of their ingredients is good.
Of course, they're more expensive
than the cheaper ones.
Besides, those who watch the streams
are all greedy for a bargain.
I'm not going to pay extra
out of my own pocket.
But, Officer,
all these infringing products
were not sold at their original prices!
I don't think that's
a violation of the law.
And who was it that claimed
their products
were authenticity-guaranteed
and would give ten times money back
if any were found to be fake?
Have you considered the consequences?
I'm a public figure with a fan base
of millions of followers!
You can't do this to me.
You cheated your fans.
Do you think
they would still support you?
♪Shimmering tears
under the flickering candlelight♪
♪No need to panic
when you're feeling lonely and sad♪
♪If you lose your way♪
♪It's best not to fantasize♪
♪Even if it's far,
it's still in the distance♪
♪Every effort and hard work
have been in vain♪
♪It's the moment
of being unappreciated♪
♪The hands were once held tightly♪
♪Even if the appearance has changed♪
♪As long as there remains
a heart beating with passion♪
♪Storms are beautiful♪
♪Free to go wild♪
♪Perhaps this is more
like a symphony of destiny♪
♪There will be clear skies someday♪
♪A breeze blowing
and clouds stretching♪
♪We can admire
after it becomes a memory♪
♪Every effort and hard work
have been in vain♪
♪It's the moment
of being unappreciated♪
♪The hands were once held tightly♪
♪Even if the appearance has changed♪
♪As long as there remains
a heart beating with passion♪
♪Storms are beautiful♪
♪Free to go wild♪
♪Perhaps this is more
like a symphony of destiny♪
♪There will be clear skies someday♪
♪A breeze blowing
and clouds stretching♪
♪We can admire
after it becomes a memory♪