(All places, names, organizations, groups...)
(and religions in this drama are fictitious.)
You were a failure.
I'm creating art. It's not just murder.
Is he really the replacement for Unit 302?
Don't judge a book by its cover.
That man is scary.
How about some beer after work tonight?
I'm actually meeting my girlfriend tonight.
You have a girlfriend?
Right. Since you're so handsome.
Try it.
Why are you so startled?
Gosh, I guess he's sensitive.
It's just my taste.
You really wanted to kill the man back there, didn't you?
- What? - You got a chill of fear,
thinking that the pervert who watches weird videos alone...
broke into your room...
and touched your stuff, right?
You think you don't fit this place, right?
You think you're different.
But you're scared at the same time.
You're worried that you'll become like one of them.
You must be worried that just by living here...
would make you become just as weird.
Should I kill him?
- He laughed. - What?
He didn't look oppressed. He seemed to enjoy it.
Sir.
Can I get off here?
I don't want to go there.
Sorry, I should go to Jong Woo.
Sir,
can you make a u-turn over there?
Wake him up.
Jong Woo.
Jong Woo. Jong Woo.
Jong Woo...
Are you okay?
Eden Studio.
What's going on over there?
I am scared.
I am...
really scared.
The residents of that studio...
are all very strange.
(Jong Woo, I am at the studio. I'll go to your room.)
Ji Eun!
Can I help you?
Pardon?
Who are you?
Please don't get the wrong idea. I live here.
Are you here to meet someone?
I'm here to meet my boyfriend.
You came to see Jong Woo.
Yes.
How did you know?
We're close.
You're pretty as he described.
It sounded like he cherishes you a lot.
Did he tell you that?
What did he say?
What did he say about the people who live here?
Well...
Anyway, I think the people here aren't normal.
He just said people here were nice.
"Nice people"?
You should go up. The guys all live on the third floor.
Okay.
(Episode 6, Lost)
- Please reply. - Don't worry too much.
I'm sure she's fine.
Just reply, will you?
Ji Eun.
The number you have called is turned off.
What's wrong?
Her phone's off.
What's going on?
Darn it.
What is this? My gosh.
Who's here so late at night?
Hello.
I'm here to meet Yun Jong Woo, a resident here.
Oh, that handsome guy?
You must be his girlfriend.
Yes.
Did he come home?
I don't think so.
Thank you.
Hold on.
Gosh, your hand is dirty.
Come in and wash your hands.
No, I'm fine.
Come on. Wash your hands.
You'll hold your boyfriend's hand, won't you?
Come on in.
- I'm really fine. - Make yourself at home.
- I'm really fine. - Come on.
Ji Eun! Ji Eun!
Ji Eun!
Did you find her?
Die!
- Ji Eun. - Die!
Ji Eun. Ji Eun!
Jung Hwa.
Why won't you pick up?
- Wait. - Ji Eun.
What is this?
Why are you here with them?
Why haven't you been picking up? Why have you arrived just now?
First, let's go outside.
Hey, Jong Woo.
Do you think we did something wrong?
What's wrong? You're scaring me.
- Why are the cops here? - No.
That's not right.
Come on out.
Hurry.
Let me go.
This isn't right!
She washed her hands and was waiting... My gosh.
- I'm at a loss for words. - Darn it!
Ji Eun, are you okay?
Ji Eun.
Why would you go in there all alone?
I told you...
how dangerous these people were.
Jong Woo.
I'll take you home. Let's go.
- I can go alone. - Come on.
We can...
- drive you. - No, we can go ourselves.
Let me go.
Ji Eun.
Jong Woo.
There are so many people...
who are stranger than them although they don't appear to be.
These people are fine.
You're only saying that because you don't live here.
If you stay here for just one day,
then you'll know that...
Then leave this place!
Why are you still here?
I'm sorry.
Let's talk again tomorrow.
I'll go home alone.
We'll take her home safely.
We will.
(Police)
Your boyfriend was worried sick.
That's why we came.
Hello.
Did something happen? I saw the cops.
It was nothing.
It's the weekend tomorrow. Do you want to grab a drink?
We can talk about that novel you're writing.
I promised to meet my girlfriend.
("The Metamorphosis")
Hey, Jong Woo.
Can you open up for a second?
Hey.
- What is it? - Good. You weren't sleeping.
How's your hangover? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Drink this.
- I'm fine. - This will cure your hangover...
right away.
Drink up.
Did your girlfriend go home safely?
Yes. By the way,
only men live in this building.
So please don't allow her to enter all alone.
You're hurting my feelings.
Don't act that way.
What do you mean?
I told you last time...
that only the good people are left.
You can't have such a misunderstanding...
- while living together. - I'm just asking you...
- to be careful. - Your neighbors will be hurt too.
- Please be careful. - I'm hurt too.
I'm dizzy.
Did she spike the drink?
This won't do.
I need to move out.
Right. I shouldn't stay here.
I shouldn't fall asleep before Ji Eun gets home.
Wasn't that man strange?
Who?
The man who came to our station.
He was talking nonsense and seemed a bit strange.
Do you know why people turn strange?
What?
It's not that they're strange to begin with,
but those around them make them become that way.
If people around you keep saying that you're insane when you're not,
do you think you'll remain sane?
That's true but...
Didn't you say that...
you've lived in this neighborhood for a long time?
Well, I didn't live for that long.
I was born here.
Then do you know anything about that studio apartment?
Not much, really.
But before you joined us, there was a big fire there.
So they were going to close down.
But after her husband died, the lady ran the place by herself.
There aren't many people here since they're redeveloping the area.
I'm not sure if she makes much money.
Many friends around me live in studio apartments...
while preparing to become police officers.
Usually, the residents don't even look at each other.
It's their rule.
They're aware that others are living there,
but they do their best to respect each other's privacy and stay quiet.
But the residents back there weren't like that at all.
Jung Hwa.
Since they're so small-scale, perhaps, they're like a family.
Did they seem like a family to you?
I'm sick and tired of killing cats.
Is this what we're here for?
Don't be ridiculous.
If you keep talking like that,
you'll die like that guy...
in Unit 302.
Do you think I'm like that scumbag?
You just wait and see.
I will kill him immediately.
Don't be ridiculous.
I know you're both intimidated by him.
Don't you know the saying,
"Look before..."
"you leap"?
We have an advantage since there's more of us.
You, your brother and I.
And we can just leave out Ms. Eom.
Hilarious.
I don't think you know this,
but the scariest person in this studio...
is Ms. Eom.
He was all alone...
How's the guy in Unit 303?
There's a small bridge on one side...
You know,
- flies keep flocking around us. - The other bridge is...
Don't you think it's time for us to pack up and leave now?
Ms. Eom, I don't know what you're talking about.
You know.
I raised you, so you know.
You failed once with Unit 302.
I can do it for sure this time.
Don't worry and sit back.
I don't worry.
I can kill them all if you fail, I have no worries.
Jong Woo.
Ji Eun.
Bet your life on it.
Ji Eun!
I told you to not come here!
She's dead.
Ji Eun?
This is driving me crazy, I'm having nightmares every night.
What's this pervert doing?
Do you have something to say to me?
Darn it. So disgusting.
Hey.
Just be honest.
Ask me to kill you if you'd like.
I'd do it for you in a heartbeat.
Hey!
Kill me.
Do it.
Kill me if you can. Kill me!
You thought I'd get scared?
Kill me. Try.
What a crazy man.
Gosh. Hey!
That crazy man.
Is there something fun going on?
What are you doing?
Shut up, you lunatic.
Did you...
just call me a lunatic?
Just what are you trying to do?
What?
Should we get to it now?
Talk.
I guess you forgot again.
I don't think this is going to end by yelling at each other like this.
Do you mind if Unit 303 and I have a talk?
Let's stop now, it's not fun anymore.
Everyone is just getting frustrated now.
You keep talking weird...
and that's why Unit 303 keeps getting creeped out.
I think you're the weird man here.
I smiled and spoke to you nicely.
Do you think I'm a joke?
What? You want to fight me?
Please...
don't get mad.
Smiles bring happiness.
Let's all smile.
Apologize to him.
Sorry, I was just bored.
He was...
just bored.
- Let's go. - Okay.
It's not as hot today, is it?
What do you want to say to me?
Nothing, really.
I wanted to just break up the fight since everyone seemed upset.
Why were you arguing with them back there?
The man said he wants to kill me.
He's weird, isn't he?
According to Ms. Eom, it's all because...
he failed his business in China.
But I think the reason he was going at you like that today...
was because you got drunk and was making a scene last night.
What?
What is he talking about?
You don't remember, do you? You were too drunk.
You were screaming and cursing in the hallway, drunk.
You were knocking on everyone's doors and all.
Me? I did that?
Check the surveillance camera if you can't believe me.
It's probably all taped.
But that was better.
What?
It's better to say what you want...
and act how you'd like...
rather than bottling it all up within yourself.
That's more human, don't you think?
I'm going to head down first, you come down when you're calm.
Jong Woo, a bad article got published after yesterday's show.
We'll have to meet at night. Is that okay with you?
(Yes, I don't...)
Yes, I don't mind. Finish up well and see you later.
(Finish up well and see you later.)
Where did I put it last time?
- Ms. Eom. - Yes, come in.
Can I see the surveillance camera footage?
You want to see it again?
Yes. The guy in Unit 304 said I caused a fuss last night.
I don't remember a thing.
- You sure about that? - Yes.
What?
When...
Gosh.
Stop staring at me.
Hey.
- You. - If you're drunk,
- go and sleep it off. - Live like a decent human being.
Do you want me to kill you?
Be more like a human, you pervert.
Hey.
I know what happens to jerks like you.
Humans...
It's late.
- Why... - Be quiet!
Why are you making so much noise?
You're so noisy.
You lunatic.
You punk!
Jong Woo! He'd been asking to see the surveillance camera footage.
- Now look at him. - Go to sleep.
What a temper.
- Sleep! - My goodness.
- Gosh. - The lunatic.
What is it now?
Hey, you.
You.
Don't smile!
Don't smile.
Calm down.
You calm down.
Guess what?
Out of all the people here,
you're the creepiest.
Get out of his way.
You're very angry today.
Are you okay?
Men are like that sometimes when they get drunk.
I preferred that.
What?
It's better to say what you want...
and act how you'd like...
rather than bottling it all up within yourself.
That's more human, don't you think?
Okay, so...
If I have to move out due to personal reasons,
can you give me back half the rent I paid?
Why do you want to leave?
I want to live closer to work...
Never mind. Thanks anyway.
Hello? We sent out an official explanation this morning.
Yes.
It was sent already. Check your inbox.
Bye.
Ji Eun.
Jae Ho.
What are you doing here?
I couldn't reach you and I got worried.
About me?
What?
Yes. Both of you.
Where's Jong Woo?
I dropped him off at the studio.
I think he's having a hard time...
getting used to life in Seoul.
Oh, dear.
I thought the same too.
He's always picking a fight.
- What? - Darn it.
He almost got into huge trouble at a bar.
My gosh.
I had...
a really tough time sorting that out.
That was great of you.
Look out for him for a while.
Oh, well.
He keeps trying to fight his senior at work too.
His supervisor?
Yes.
Why does he keep doing that?
I feel bad.
I made him move here.
Don't think like that.
Let's give him some time. He'll get better.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I'm meeting Jong Woo. For a chat.
What about Sunday?
I don't have plans.
Good. Let's meet up and talk about this.
About what?
Jong Woo's in a bad place. He could get into real trouble.
Okay, I'll ask him. Let's talk.
No, don't tell him. Let's keep it between us.
- What? - He'll only get upset.
I'll ask him and call you.
Jong Woo's giving me a hard time.
Okay, I'll call you. Bye.
See you on the weekend.
I'll call you.
Ji Eun.
I'm off to a meeting.
Okay.
Why haven't you arranged a date for me and that guy?
He said he's a little busy.
Are you keeping him to yourself?
What?
You know what I mean.
See you later.
[VIU Ver] OCN E06 'Stranger from Hell'
"Lost"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Grandma. What was Grandpa like?
He was nice. He was always nice.
How can someone always be nice?
My husband was like that.
As long as you believe someone is nice and kind,
then that person will be nicer and kinder...
than you believe. That's what he told me.
He left his door open again.
He's really trash. Utter trash.
I really want to leave this place.
What are you reading?
A case my colleague's working on.
Where's the remote control?
Can't people leave it...
- where it was? - Dad.
- Listen to this. - Here it is.
People keep disappearing from this studio.
My colleague thinks there's definitely...
a correlation between the studio and the disappearances.
- It's a case? - Yes.
There's only strong suspicion.
But there is no physical evidence.
This is the problem.
- I am really concerned. - Why?
It's just a studio.
So what about a studio?
It's barely big enough for a person to lie down in.
If anything happens...
It's too heartbreaking.
You need to mind your own business.
Why would you say that? You aren't helping me.
I am sure he is not acting alone.
Right?
- Think about it. - Right.
Studios...
have a lot of surveillance cameras and people.
Right?
And if they are to move separately,
it will be hard to hide their crimes.
They will have a leader who orchestrates everything.
A leader?
Seriously? You need to use your brain.
Come on, just help me.
- I am watching TV. - Come on.
What I am saying...
is that in cases of murder committed by partners,
it is usually lead by a very strong figure.
And that dominant figure will allocate roles...
so the subordinates will move in an organized manner.
Organized?
That's why they will rarely leave any traces behind.
There must be a leader who orchestrates everything.
Is it her?
It could be someone else.
But from what you said,
this woman is somehow involved in everything.
I need to get into this right now.
Thank you, Dad!
Why do you want to do it?
Dad, I totally forgot. We should get ready.
I forgot that we got tickets for a movie.
Goodness.
Do you like it?
Yes.
This room is 350 dollars a month.
A lot of students came by to look at it.
If you like it, you should sign soon.
Or you can just give me your deposit first.
- Can I take a look inside? - Sure, take your time.
How much is it?
This room is 250 dollars.
- 250 dollars? - You have until today to decide.
Until today?
A cheap room like this will be gone by tomorrow.
Are you really going to sign the contract?
I am still looking.
I can tell you this because I am not the landlord.
- I wouldn't live here. - Why not?
This is crazy.
An old man who lived here passed away recently.
- What? - He lived here by himself.
And just died alone.
The landlord kept saying that it's not true.
But a cleaning crew came by a few days ago...
and took everything away.
Seriously...
Is it possible then...
the price may lower a little?
Do you want to live like that after I told you what happened?
Well...
If the price is lower, I can think about it.
Look at my goosebumps. I can't live here.
Right...
No one can live like a normal person here.
Thank you. I will think about it.
- Will you? - Yes.
Dad, what do you think?
I am really tired. Just get whatever and let's go home.
- How can I? Come, look. - Seriously.
You said we are going to the movies.
It all looks the same. Just pick anything.
How can you say that? They are not the same.
A legend of the District Investigation Team must help me.
- It's really hard to choose. - Whatever.
- Such an old story. - He is so mean.
What's wrong?
What is it?
I think I just saw our dentist.
- Is it a man? - Yes.
- Is he handsome? - Yes.
He is really good-looking, but it's nothing like that.
If I take a look at his face,
I will be able to tell.
You just said it's an old story.
Come on.
I can tell what kind of person my daughter's boyfriend is.
Take this. It suits you.
Go on. Hurry up.
- Go. - I will just get both.
Fine.
- Really? - Yes.
Should I ask Jae Ho to give me a pay advance?
Even if I get the advance, with taxes and everything,
it will leave me less than 1,000 dollars.
I can't live in a place with a monthly rent of 400 dollars.
Remember Soo Young, my friend?
Soo Young? Sure.
The man she is supposed to marry...
doesn't own a house but lives in a rented house.
I thought his family was rich.
He acted like he was really rich.
I know, right?
That's why Soo Young is now very confused.
How can a man of his age not even own a house?
That is so pitiful.
Isn't that funny?
If you are such a loser, how can you even dare to date?
Exactly.
Let's talk inside.
Sure.
Did you see his face?
Yes. His stare made me feel disgusted.
Let's go. I said I am hungry.
- What are you eating? - This one.
You can eat that.
This is driving me crazy.
Why do I keep seeing him?
Gosh. Hi, Ji Eun.
What's wrong?
I thought I met that man from the studio.
A man?
Did you see that man last night?
He has long hair and a very pale face.
He wears a shirt that is about this long.
- Did you... - Maybe he came to watch a movie.
Or maybe someone that looks like him.
Well,
he came to my office the other day.
- I think he is stalking me... - Jong Woo, please!
That's enough.
Why are you doing this?
Seriously.
You are not the only one who lives in a studio.
There are many strange people in society.
Why do you make such a big deal out of it?
Do you think I am a loser too?
What?
- This is too much. - What is too much?
Ji Eun.
Can't you just listen to me?
I'm going to go. I am tired.
Fine. Go.
You only listen to things that you want to hear.
Have a good weekend.
Hyun Ho. Did you figure anything out?
That woman gives off a bad vibe.
Does she? Give me a minute.
Right. Tell me.
First, she married twice.
Both husbands died in accidents and she has no children.
And even her parents died in an accident.
I see.
What creeps me out the most is that...
she was the benefactor of their life insurance policies.
It's about one million dollars.
One million dollars?
Got it.
And it seems she opened an orphanage with the life insurance money...
but she had fire insurance for it so that was compensated later too.
I see.
And that studio used to be her husband's business.
Jung Hwa.
Shouldn't we pass this over to the Criminal Division?
Right?
We should.
But all we have now is just suspicion.
Hyun Ho. Thank you, anyway. Okay.
See you tomorrow. Okay. Bye.
Welcome.
Hello.
This is strange.
Why is it so quiet in here today?
- Who is it? - Hello.
I just moved in across the hall. I was wondering...
if I could borrow your charger.
He's new?
Excuse me.
Hello.
What is this about?
Well...
I need to use my phone later, but I don't have a charger.
Can I borrow your charger?
Oh, right.
Thank you.
And the convenience store down the street sells chargers.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you. I'll give it right back. Thank you.
Hey, that's enough. Clean that up.
But why are we the only ones cleaning up this mess afterward?
Then do you want to do the cutting?
Hey, you must think my job is easy.
I always have to put on pain relief patches afterward.
Be quiet.
Why must we be quiet? Why?
Be quiet, you punk.
Did you wake up on the wrong side of the bed today?
Are you scared Unit 303 might catch us?
If he does, we can just finish him off.
You moron. You look so scared right now.
Who's scared? Me?
I wasn't scared at all.
Me?
Should I show you?
Show me.
She said no one lives on that floor.
But why do I keep hearing noises since the first day I moved here?
Show me.
Stop it, you punk.
I'll really do it.
Is anyone there?
It all worked out.
He came here on his own to be killed. We can kill him here.
That jerk. He's been behaving lately.
He's a total nut job.
Is anyone there?
Mom, hold on.
(Eden Studio)
Yes, Mom.
That jerk.
Where are you?
Me?
Where do you think?
I'm at home. What is it?
Being quiet is a must when living at a studio apartment.
He should've known better if he's lived here that long.
I love what I do.
So if anyone tries...
to interfere with my work,
I won't stand still, okay?
Do you understand?
What's wrong?
Do you want to leave as well?
That is...
ridiculous.
I love what I do.
Did Deuk Su go to paradise first?
All right.
- The sooner, the better. - Will you be able...
to listen to me?
Of course.
I...
love this job...
so much.
But what's wrong with your voice?
I had a dream about you,
and it felt ominous.
Is everything all right?
Yes, everything's fine.
Jong Woo.
Be careful of others.
Humans are the most fearful beings.
All right.
Don't worry about me and go back to bed.
You need to wake up early and go to the marketplace.
- Jong Woo. - Yes?
- Isn't it tough? - I mean...
Please stop worrying about me. I'm not a boy.
To parents, their kids will always be kids.
All right. Go to bed.
Okay. Don't keep the windows open no matter how hot it is.
All right, I'm hanging up. Goodnight.
I wonder who went in there.
Never mind. Just forget about it.
Who are you?
Run.
I said, run.
(Stranger from Hell)
If someone tries to...
break in or open the door...
while I'm away, could you take some photos?
- Unit 303. - Please spare me.
You know this is all your fault, right?
Come here. Let's eat.
Do you know of a place called Spring Orphanage?
It's similar to our hospital's name.
What's with this punk?
Excuse me.
We don't know where to go thanks to you.
Don't smile like that.