[English subtitles are available]
[Double love]
[Episode 12]
There it is.
I finally found the signal.
Now I'll log in the game.
[Enter the game]
Log in the game.
[Kaifeng]
Genius, I'm here.
Yourself?
Yes, it's me.
At your disposal.
I will let you live for now.
Later,
I'll settle the score with you.
I'm exhausted.
My Genius.
Where did she go?
Why isn't she back yet?
When did you come back?
Genius, I'll start the screen recording now.
You're a perfect match.
Ladies and gentlemen,
folks,
the good time has passed, but their marriage is still a good one.
The grand ceremony of Moonlight Blade
is about to begin.
I'm the cameraman,
Five Poisons.
Maybe you don't know me,
but it doesn't matter.
[Trumpet]
I'm honored to host today's wedding
for Genius Ink White and Chu He.
Please come to the live stream room
and witness this wonderful moment together.
Okay.
Happy wedding.
♫We didn't meet that year♫
Wish you happiness forever.
♫The sunset dyed my face red♫
♫I heard birds confess their love on the beam♫
♫They flew together across the room♫
♫We didn't meet that year♫
♫I saw stars all over the sky♫
[Sikong Xiaoxing]
[Zhu Xiaoyue]
[Sikong Xiaoxing] [Zhu Xiaoyue]
♫I didn't know who I would spend my life with♫
♫The past was like a dream♫
News from Jianghu.
Congratulations to player Between Ink White
and Chu He on getting married.
A perfect couple was born.
Wish them a long and happy marriage.
♫When we first met♫
♫first met♫
[Zhu Xiaoyue] [Sikong Xiaoxing]
♫The connection brought two hearts together♫
[Tianyi Clothing Shop]
♫We met each other in the middle of night♫
♫You had good looks and good characteristics♫
Happy wedding to Master and Madam.
♫When I looked back♫
♫We were like two birds flying past each other towards different directions♫
Happy wedding!
Wish Ink White and his wife a happy wedding
and happy forever.
Happy forever.
Happy wedding.
Three Swordsmanship.
Your dress is really nice.
You're almost as beautiful as Chu He.
Get lost. Do you want to battle?
We didn't ask you to disguise.
If you have the guts, go to Madam.
I have to say something for Three Swordsmanship.
Since Between Ink White
chose to hold such a high profile wedding,
he should've found a bestman and a bridesmaid himself.
It's unresonable
to ask one of you to disguise
after playing Rock, paper, scissors.
Miss Top Star, you're so considerate.
Cut the crap. Let's go.
Raise the sedan chair.
Music.
This is more comfortable.
[Happiness]
Let's welcome the bride and groom.
Between Ink White,
will you take Chu He as your wife,
to love her and protect her,
no matter how ugly and fat
or how unintelligent she is,
as long as you both shall live?
What kind of question is that?
I do.
Then, Chu He,
will you take Between Ink White as your husband,
to love him and protect him,
no matter
how handsome, rich
and intelligent he is,
and prevent him from being snatched by others?
You have double standards.
Before answering this question,
can I kill this emcee first?
I have no objection.
You value romance over friendship.
Alright.
This man who values romance over friendship.
Now,
you may kiss your bride.
Kiss her. Hurry up.
Kiss.
Kiss!
Kiss
♫I want to be your lover♫
♫I want to be your harbor forever♫
♫How can I♫
♫Speak out whatever it takes♫
♫Give you all my gentleness♫
♫I want to be your lover♫
Between Ink White and Chu He
got married today.
[Announcement: Between Ink White and Chu He are married today, and from now on, they will work together and follow each other]
[They will love each other and never separate]
they will work together and follow each other.
♫I want to be your harbor forever♫
They will love each other and never separate.
♫Wanting to hold your hand♫
OK.
♫to the end of time♫
The officials of the game came?
Awesome.
When Genius gets married,
♫For a moment until forever♫
the officials of the game are here.
Listen carefully. It's Five Poisons.
Darn it.
He's pretending to be an official
by live streaming.
♫I want to be your lover♫
Then, what's the next
procedure?
Every minute of the night is precious.
♫My love♫
We shall enter the nuptial chamber.
The nuptial chamber?
All right.
The wedding is over.
As for the nuptial chamber,
just use your imagination.
Dismiss.
Let's go.
Dismiss. Let's go.
Let's have a drink.
Which shop?
Did you do all this?
I thought I traveled through time.
There's something more serious.
Do you want to take a look?
Sure.
Let's go.
This is so beautiful.
And the zither.
This is indeed more serious
than what I saw just now.
[Happiness]
This bed is exactly the same as the one in my room.
It's also round.
[Happiness]
It's very big.
Come on.
OK. Bottoms up.
[Happiness]
Just the two of us.
We don't have to go through the procedures, right?
I'm recording the screen.
In this way,
you can watch our wedding
anytime you want.
Okay.
[Happiness]
Well,
what should we do next?
It's a pity
that we don't go through the process.
Can I see such a wild scene?
Please cooperate.
The system wants us to stay here for five minutes.
Let's go.
Are we just sitting
like this?
What do you want to do?
Nothing.
Let's just sit.
Anyway...
Why are you so far away from me?
We just need to finish the task.
Time's up.
Where's the title?
Put it on if you're done.
What title?
[Chu He's Husband]
This is too long.
It doesn't match my simple account.
[Title: Between Ink White's Wife]
[Between Ink White's Wife]
Are we going to keep this up?
Can I hide it?
Sure.
I'll kill you if you hide it once.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Because I want to tell the whole world
you are my wife.
My goodness.
How come
this wedding arouses my girlish heart?
No.
Calm down.
Calm down!
[Fifth Generation Mobile Communication Signal]
What a coincidence.
Do you think my performance was OK?
-Yeah. -Wanwan.
Not bad. Wanwan.
How are you?
You must be tired.
Not bad.
What did you shoot today?
You won't understand.
Here.
Take a rest.
Sit.
Thank you.
Bad news.
The video of the falling was exposed.
[Big Dunk]
Li Weiqian's persona is ruined.
God has opened his eyes.
Congratulations.
The netizens are trying to boycott Li Weiqian
and boycott this project.
The producer and the agency are here.
They're discussing changing the casting.
Poor Hanhan.
They've filmed so many scenes together.
It's all going to be retaked.
Changing casting?
No.
I have to ask our...
Well...
Mr. Lu.
If Li Weiqian dares to bully Wanwan,
she must pay the price.
How can a single video
make me feel better?
[Big Dunk]
This industry is not controlled by one.
You can't go far with your power.
The most important thing for a human being
is to be straightforward.
The biggest taboo is being indecisive.
In the end,
you can't even protect the person you love.
You think you're good to her.
Did you ask
whether she needs it or not?
What's the smell?
Hanhan...
So the video online
was released by you?
Also,
who is that bodyguard?
Mr. Lu.
I don't
like to beat about the bush.
I came here for the change
of leading female actress of Big Dunk.
Mr. Mu,
Are you here to plead for her?
Of course not.
We must replace her
and stop the loss in time.
I've heard that someone is appealling
to boycott this project.
But
I can't accept
these people.
Li Weiqian is at the top.
These three
are only second and third tier stars.
It is a disgrace to Qiaobei.
Mr. Mu.
The schedule of top artists is full.
In a short time,
it's hard to find an artist at the same tier
to take the place.
These are the artists
that we have
recently contacted
that match the image of the female lead
and
can immediately start shooting.
You're the producer.
Of course you don't care.
But this is unfair to our Lin Huang.
Mr. Mu.
How much compensation do you want?
Our Qiaobei's pay
should be raised by 50%.
What's wrong, Mr. Lu?
You're here.
You called me here in such a hurry.
As expected,
Lin Huang made excessive demands
to boost Qiao's status.
You agreed?
It's a big amount.
I have to discuss with you.
I think Gu Qiaobei is just like that.
Why don't we replace him too?
Get lost.
Haven't you thought about it?
Are you not feeling good?
Are you threatened?
50% of the pay.
What do you think?
Judging from the current situation,
the commercial value Gu Qiaobei brought to Big Dunk
has exceeded his pay.
It may increase in the future.
Do you think it's worth it?
Yes.
Then it's settled.
You are my best partner.
I respect all your decisions.
Cheers.
Mr. Mu is waiting for you.
Mr. Mu.
Mr. Lu.
How's the negotiation about the salary?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Mr. Lu, I'm sorry.
I want to talk to my boss alone.
Qiaobei,
I have something to discuss with Mr. Lu.
After we're done,
I'll find you.
No.
What I want to say is very important.
Qiaobei.
Okay.
In that case,
I'll say it here.
I
decided to quit the shoot of Big Dunk.
What did you say?
The setting of Big Dunk now
is too low.
And I heard that we have to film another month.
This
conflicts with
my next variety show.
I don't want to give up on the variety show later on.
So,
I decided to terminate the contract with Big Dunk.
Qiao.
Are you sure?
Mr. Lu,
I've made up my mind.
Please grant my wish.
Enough.
Let's talk
back at the office.
No need.
I've said everything.
Qiaobei.
Mr. Mu.
It seems that you and your artist
haven't reached a consensus.
Why don't you go back and think about it?
We will
look for new male artists.
What do you think?
Actually,
there's no big difference
in changing one role or two roles for us.
As for Gu Qiaobei's unilateral breach of contract,
the penalty...
Mr. Lu,
Li Weiqian has brought
a lot of trouble to the crew.
Mr. Lu, stop distracting yourself
for us.
Don't worry.
I will persuade Qiaobei
and bring him back.
The pay...
After all,
Qiaobei and I still need your support
in various aspects.
As for the pay,
it can be as before.
Okay.
I'll do as you say.
Here, have some coffee.
The evidence is out.
Li Weiqian's fans still came to scold me.
[Lu Wanwan]
[Li Weiqian]
I'll scold you to death with my secret account.
Wanwan. Wanwan.
Wanwan.
Are you busy shooting today?
Not really.
Wanwan.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have said that.
I shouldn't have thought about you like that either.
The leading actress is really good at acting.
I was careless.
I shouldn't have pretended to fall
and made people misunderstand you.
Now I know I was wrong.
Can you help me beg them
to not kick me out of the crew.
I really need this role.
So
you admit the video is real?
You also admit that you pretended to fall?
Yes.
I admit what I did.
You're really great.
So when you showed up,
I then had a sense of crisis.
But I know I was wrong.
I shouldn't have hurt you.
Please.
Please give me another chance.
I will change.
No.
It's useless to beg me.
It wasn't me who
forced you out of the crew.
I don't have the ability.
I really don't know.
I know you can't forgive me
for the time being.
But I know I was wrong.
Please give me another chance.
You...
Stop begging me.
Really.
It's useless to beg me.
I really don't know anything.
Right.
Then who did it?
I don't ask you for anything else.
I'm begging you
to publish a clarification
and turn the situation back?
Qian.
You've already caused damage to the reputation
of Lu Wanwan.
I'm warning you.
Please delete the false information immediately.
Otherwise Ying Ge
will hold you legally liable.
Let me tell you.
On Lu Wanwan's case,
Ying Ge will never give in.
Brother.
Thank you for helping me, Brother.
You're really my biological brother.
No matter how much I want to stand up for you,
I can't handle
such a big thing alone.
Didn't you post the video online?
Didn't you force Li Weiqian out of the crew?
I got her replaced
because the influence
is too huge and bad.
You know what?
Someone has started to boycott the crew.
Who is it?
He saved my life.
Think about it with your unintelligent brain.
Could it be
Li Weiqian's fans took photos secretly
and felt guilty afterwards?
Then who forced her out of the crew?
Yes.
Who could it be?
You're acting weird. jpg.
The way you talk to your prince charming. jpg.
Plus the look that care for an idiot. jpg.
Repeated.
I'll find him.
Hmph. gif.
Go downstairs and turn left. See you. mov.
Exclusive 4K resolution for iQIYI VIPs.
Stupid girl.
Automatic resolution adjustment.
Zhao,
you paid and worked hard as her bodyguard.
Why can't she think of you?
Well...
[Jinling]
Pass! Pass!
Don't touch my head.
I can't pet you?
Of course not.
If I ask you,
can I touch your hair?
You don't want it either, right?
Sure.
Come on, touch it.
I'll get ready.
If you want to touch my head,
come to me anytime.
[Jinling]
Be careful.
I told you long ago
men shouldn't
be too indecisive.
I'm sorry.
I almost hit you just now.
That's not how you play the ball.
This is awesome.
I...
Which department are you from?
Hello, Director.
I'm her bodyguard.
Being a bodyguard is a waste of your talent.
You have such good conditions
and are good at basketball.
Our play
is about basketball.
I'll arrange a role for you
if there's an appropriate one.
He was praised,
why are you so happy?
Of course.
Isn't him being praised the same as me being praised?
Piece of cake.
Compared to your appearance,
he's a bit inferior.
But it's not much different.
Look.
Even a strict person like Director Zheng
can compliment him like this.
He must be really good.
I was praised too.
And
many times.
Okay, you're the best.
Do you want a red flower?
I can also give you this award.
Han Jingmo, be good.
Stop looking.
No.
I really need to be a scout for Mr. Lu.
I think he's really a promising actor.
-What star scout? -Let me take a look.
Stop looking.
Let me see.
-Stop looking. -Let me see.
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
Yes, I am.
Song Chi!
Coming. Coming.
What's going on?
I'll take care
of the meal.
I wanted to use my face.
and ask the chef to give me one more portion of ribs.
We have sweet and sour ribs today.
Do you still have the consciousness to be an actress?
I want to send it to Han Jingmo.
Today, I don't know how I upset
your master today.
Why is he so childish
and angry all the time?
No way.
Why would he help you if he was angry?
Help me? For what?
The video
was uploaded online by Hanhan.
Otherwise, how could it spread so fast?
Don't you know?
I don't know. How would I know?
I overheard it too.
This is bad.
Have you heard about the story of the farmer and the snake?
Let me tell you.
I'm the snake now.
I even called the farmer crazy.
No wonder he was so angry today.
-What? -So it is not him who is crazy, it is me.
What farmer? What snake?
Who is crazy?
No.
Take a seat. I'm going to deliver the food.
Meal is here.
Why did he help me?
Could it be that
Han Jingmo likes me?
He likes me.
[The boiled dish is terrible. My sweet and sour ribs are still here. Take them all.
The boiled dish is terrible, right?
My sweet and sour ribs are still here.
Take them all.
[Cold legs]
[Hang up]
Hey, what?
Han Jingmo sent the video of the fake fall.
Does Han
have feelings for you?
What do you mean?
I have to pay him back.
It's up to you.
Also,
don't promise anything
just because you thank him.
What do you mean?
I'm just reminding
my stupid sister.
Now you remind me late, you know?
I have to apologize to him first
and then thank him, right?
Apologize?
What did you do this time?
How about
giving him a movie script
and making him the best actor?
Even if I give him a good script
and make him the best actor,
does it even relate to whether you apologize to him or not?
All right, I'm hanging up.
I have work to do.
Bye.
Where is he?
You eat so much.
It's ready.
Thank you.
Hanhan.
You look so clean and cool today.
It's just a glance that makes me fall for you.
You're definitely the next Prince Charming.
I look exactly like yesterday.
Well...
It looks the same at first glance,
but if you look closely, it's quite different.
Your appearance today
hit the depths of my soul.
You are more than handsome.
I didn't know what my birth
is for
until I met you.
I finally realized
I was born to worship you.
It's too hypocritical.
This morning,
I said you're crazy.
Lu Wanwan,
Hurry up. The director is looking for you.
It's your turn to shoot.
I said you're crazy.
I said you're crazy. I didn't mean it.
I don't think...
you're crazy.
I didn't finish.
I'll explain to you later.
Don't misunderstand me.
What is she trying to say?
She said
you're crazy.
One more round.
Cut.
Pass.
Meal time.
Food is ready.
Sir,
Let me remove the microphone for you.
Change the battery.
Okay.
I'll go get the food.
Here.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Han Jingmo.
What's up?
Didn't I say I would come back to you?
Well...
I want to apologize to you.
I spoke without thinking.
I shouldn't have said you're crazy.
I'm just...
sometimes
I speak faster than I can think.
I'm just inconsiderate.
I was not saying you're crazy.
How could I insult you like this?
That's not what I meant.
What?
Do you want to get emotional
and cry?
No, I...
How could I do?
I didn't mean that.
I... I really want to thank you.
You saved my life.
Wanwan.
A gift from someone
needs your signature.
Wait for me.
What is it? Why is it delivered to the set?
Is this a supermarket?
Other fans give roses.
Your fans send melon fruit and vegetables.
They're sincere.
Here's a card.
I wanted to send it to your house.
[I wanted to send it to your house. But I don't know where you live.
[Natural and environmental. You can share them with your friends and take the rest home.
[Your little fan Han Xixing]
But I don't know where you live.
Natural and environmental.
You can share them with your friends
and take the rest home.
Your little fan,
Han Xixing.
Look.
Who gave it to me?
It's not for you. It's for me.
I'll always be grateful to you.
Thank you for helping me in Li Weiqian's case.
If you need any help in the future,
just let me know.
I'll help you if I can.
I'll do anything.
I wouldn't say no for sure.
Yes.
You would say
you would not do anything extreme.
How do you know me so well?
No.
I really want to thank you.
Anyway, if you need any help in the future,
I will help you.
But
I can't do anything against ethics.
Against ethics?
What are you thinking? What are you thinking?
I'm thinking
what you said
is a way to repay my kindness.
How dare you!
How dare a scoundrel harm me?
You're so scared that even an outdated joke came out.
How could I be scared by you?
I've seen all kinds of things.
I see.
Then tell me
how will you repay me?
Han Jingmo.
I didn't expect you to be such a person.
You let me down, don't you know?
Why are you sighing?
Are you a spiteful woman?
Boss, give me the same one as hers.
This lady
wants only half a bowl of wonton.
No oil or salt in the soup.
Same as hers. Thank you.
Okay.
Aren't you on a diet?
Why are you here for wontons?
Don't tell me it's a coincidence.
We've been shooting night scenes.
I've been waiting for too long,
so I came out for some fresh air.
It took me a long time to find this place.
What a coincidence.
Are you sure you weren't following me?
Why should I follow you?
Let me tell you.
Don't think about things you shouldn't think about.
The sea of bitterness is boundless. It's time to turn back.
Sir, your wonton.
Thank you.
Actually,
you've helped a lot,
I should've repaid you.
You are so handsome
and have a good figure.
Actually, I won't lose anything.
But
I can't get through my conscience.
I don't want to stain you.
Stain?
Yes.
You are the pure white flower on the snow mountain.
I am the snow water with dirty
at the foot of the snow mountain.
You are the bright moon by the sky
I am the dirty ditch on the ground.
You are the fragrant swan.
I'm just an ugly frog.
I dare not even think about it.
Enough.
I was just kidding.
I want to say one last thing.
Say it.
I know.
You are trying to test
if I could be tempted by fame and fortune,
right?
No.
I just wanted to fool you.
Sit there.
If I tell Lu Guanghan,
he'll block you right away and make you
unpopular at all. Do you know that?
Really?
Are you scared?
I'm so scared.
I want to break up with you for 20 years.
Bye.
Wait.
No more joking.
I want to tell you
it's not only me
who helped you in Li Weiqian's case.
Zhao Jinghang also helped.
Li Weiqian dared to bully Wanwan.
She must pay the price.
The most important thing for being a human being
is to be straightforward.
The biggest taboo is being indecisive.
In the end,
you can't even protect the person you love.
I see.
But why didn't Lu Guanghan tell me?
Never mind. As long as the truth is revealed.
Are you going
to repay his kindness?
He's a gentleman.
Yes.
I am the only one who has a purpose.
I don't like you.
You don't like me either.
Don't be blinded by the hormone.
Be rational.
You don't like me?
Of course.
What if one day
you suddenly like me?
Impossible.
You
are so mean
and cunning.
You have good look but evil soul.
There are all shortcomings.
-You know me well. -Well…
I'm not a kid. I know.
Okay, I...
I'll send you the location.
This bodyguard is so good.
He insisted on taking me back to the set.
Then, let me walk you out.
When you get to the set, remember...