[English subtitles are available]
[Double love]
[Episode 8]
You have no idea
how self-disciplined our actors are.
I'm under a lot of pressure.
Wanwan.
You offended someone right after you joined the crew?
Look at this.
[Shocked. Li Weiqian squatted to eat on set. She's the hardest and lowest-profile person.]
[Li Weiqian worked very hard when she was shooting the Big Dunk.]
[She kept reading the script when she had her meals.]
[According to the insider, the two leading actresses of Big Dunk are totally different behind the scene.]
[One is the leading actress who plays the most important role. Another actress is arrogant and impolite.]
When did she eat like that?
She has an assistant to help her wherever she goes.
[According to the insider, the two leading actresses of Big Dunk are totally different behind the scene.]
[One is the leading actress who plays the most important role. Another actress is arrogant and impolite.]
She's as delicate as a porcelain doll.
This is too bold.
[Wagging Bear]
[Li Weiqian kept reading the script and study the play when she had her meals.]
[She has to be marked as a diligent actress.]
Let's post an announcement too.
And tell people you had a fever at 42 degrees and insisted on filming.
You also played the underwater scenes in person.
All the action scenes are done on your own too.
Well, Wanwan.
Stop reading it.
It will affect your mood.
Don't read it, please.
They're already bullying me.
Don't read it.
Don't be angry.
Anyway.
I'd like to eat. I want all of them.
-Waiter, may I take the order please? -Let's eat.
Order all of them!
Yes, let's order them all.
I'm so angry.
Take the order.
Where did you get
these photos?
Don't worry.
I got it legally.
I hope it can help.
Why do you want to help Wanwan?
Big Dunk is our company's play after all.
I don't want the negative news appear
in just a few days.
Eric.
Manage your artist.
These are...
Don't play dumb.
You know very well
how your artist is.
If she doesn't want to play the role anymore,
I'll contact the legal department
and follow the procedure as the default contract.
No, no, no.
I'm really sorry, Mr. Lu.
I apologize on behalf of Qian.
If it happens again,
I'll expose these photos online.
I'll arrange the PR department to deal with it.
I'll give you an hour.
I want all these photos to disappear.
Okay.
Connect me to the PR department.
The negative news is all gone.
That's right.
That's great.
Hello?
Brother.
I'm glad to see the result.
It seems that you still love me very much.
What are you talking about?
Didn't you withdraw the negative news?
Thank you, Cold Legs.
Han Jingmo helped too.
What's your relationship with him?
You'd better tell me the truth.
No way.
No way?
I'll go back and get even with you.
Han Jingmo.
What should we do?
What should I do?
Should I thank him?
You're right.
Well,
thank you for helping me.
You came to thank me just for this?
Why did you help me?
Don't think too much.
I just don't like Li Weiqian.
Since you want to thank me,
shouldn't you do something?
Well,
I'll
let bygones be bygones.
Alright?
Forgive me?
What is it?
You splashed water on me before.
I'll forget it.
It wasn't me.
You didn't?
Then the ghost did?
The staff upstairs was moving things
and dropped the cup.
So the water splashed on your head.
There was a coke in the basketball game yesterday...
Don't...
[Han Jingmo]
All I know is that you left without saying anything.
You didn't say anything.
Just exactly as  you are now.
I turned around to get the tissues for you.
But after I got the tissues for you,
you splashed water on me.
Believe it or not, I'll really splash water on you.
Say something.
Or I'll splash water on you.
Impossible.
Please think about it.
How could I
pour water on you for no reason?
Go ahead.
So,
that's the reason you don't like me?
Yes.
Now that the misunderstanding has been resolved,
can you
be my fan again?
Sure.
Okay.
Take out your phone.
I don't take it with me.
Do you have your brain?
Remember what I'm going to say.
Since you're my fan again,
can you exchange your wallpaper
with someone else's photo
when you get your phone later?
You mean Gu Qiaobei's?
His good looks get me through the day.
Can't I?
Unfaithful.
It has nothing to do with being unfaithful.
Not only that,
but also a bad attitude.
That's what fangirls are like.
There are thousands of idols,
I'll choose a million of them to like.
I'm asking if you'll change it.
I won't. So what?
You're too strict with your fans.
Don't follow me if you don't want to change it.
Fine.
It's done, Miss Lu.
Thank you.
Wanwan.
Wanwan?
Why are your eyes so red?
Did you not sleep well last night?
Wanwan.
My fans posted the photos on Weibo yesterday.
But I just posted a Weibo
and clarified it.
I believe the situation will be changed soon.
It won't affect you too much.
Wanwan.
You must trust me this time.
I really didn't know
what happened this time.
But I'm sorry
for the hurt it caused you.
You have to trust me.
I really like you,
and I want to be friends with you.
My fans
made a mistake.
But I will make it up to you.
I hope you can forgive me.
You don't have to do this.
I know you don't trust me now.
But I will prove it with time.
I will make it up to you.
Are you ready?
Miss Li, stand by.
Miss Lu, get ready.
Okay.
Please trust me.
I have to get back to work now.
Trust me, please.
I'll prove it with time.
Okay.
Defend! Defend!
Do your best, you know?
Why?
Fine, look how I...
[Weibo Just now]
[Li Weiqian]
Wanwan is a very hardworking
[Wanwan is a very hardworking and professional rookie actress.]
and professional rookie actress.
What did Han Jingmo do to Li Weiqian?
She's become so kind and friendly.
[She's vindicated. Wanwan did not play a big card on the set. Stay sensible, fans. I like Wanwan very much.]
Are you uncomfortable?
I slept late last night.
Don't stay up late.
You might die suddenly.
I won't die. I was just gaming for a while.
Gaming?
Moonlight Blade?
I play that game too.
How about I add you as a friend
and we play together?
Sure.
Then tell me your account username.
I'll add you when I get back tonight.
Before that,
you're not allowed to like Gu Qiaobei anymore.
Also,
change the wallpaper with my photo.
And...
-If… -Well...
I suddenly feel like...
I thought about it carefully.
I think it's too much
to add you as my friend.
You're not a real fan.
You're too strict with your fans.
I'm asking you, which idol
demands this of his fans?
Does Mr. Tao do this?
And Gu Qiaobei?
Listen.
You're a mudslide in the entertainment circle.
Say it again!
Clear stream.
Can I ask you
about Gu Qiaobei's game account?
No.
Boss, I've tried my best.
I made some changes in Shoot 3, Scene 18.
Take a look.
It's so long.
I suggested Director Zheng add it.
Why?
Because I felt like it.
Pervert.
You don't look happy.
Do you think the scene is too short or the script is too few?
How about I add more for you?
Don't bother.
I don't have anything on my schedule anyway.
I can go home and prepare for it.
Going home?
Yes, go home.
It's like preparing for the exam.
I'll do my best.
Well,
the plot was revised suddenly,
so the big plan has to be changed too, right?
Gu Qiaobei injured his wrist.
This scene happens to be a substitute
of the action scene he was going to shoot.
Qiao is injured?
What happened to him? Is it serious?
Where did he hurt? Did he go to the hospital?
I'm asking you.
If you make a mistake,
I'll teach you a lesson.
Who's here? Coming!
Okay, I got it.
Miss Wei, why are you here suddenly?
Go on Weibo and look at the trending topics.
Weibo?
Let me check.
[Han Jingmo followed Lu Wanwan]
[Lu Wanwan]
[Han Jingmo]
What's going on?
[Lu Wanwan]
This...
[New friend]
[Han Jingmo]
Miss Wei, what should I do?
Follow him and reply to his comment.
What should I reply?
I sent you the content.
[Lu Wanwan]
Leave the rest to me.
Okay.
Done.
Thank you, Miss Wei.
I didn't know this. Thank you.
I knew you couldn't handle it.
I was just passing by, so I came up.
Alright then. I have things to do.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Thank you, Miss Wei.
Thank you for coming and helping.
Bye.
Bye, Miss Wei.
Judging from Han Jingmo's fans' reaction,
I think I made it this time.
What a coincidence.
Miss Wei just left.
We met at the elevator.
Let me ask you.
What are you doing with Han Jingmo?
I also want to know what Han Jingmo is up to.
Then why did he follow you?
Of course
he's trying to play tricks on me.
He wants to make use of his fans to cyberbully me.
He's good looking, but he's devious.
No.
Ugly man.
His soul is too ugly.
He has countless ways to play tricks on you.
Does he have to sacrifice his popularity?
I know.
He wants to use me
to clarify his rumor with Li Weiqian.
He told me personally
he didn't like Li Weiqian.
What's that look?
Your eyes offended me.
It seems that you don't care about
Gu Qiaobei that much.
No, no, no.
Do you have enough pocket money?
Tell me if it's not enough.
So did you find out his game account?
Not yet.
But I have good news.
Go ahead.
Gu Qiaobei
hurt his hand.
But it's not serious.
He's been practicing basketball too hard recently.
He sprained his wrist.
So?
Here's your chance.
You're still useful.
Trauma Ointment.
Muscle Trauma Ointment.
You've never cared about me that much.
I need to prepare for this scene for the next two days.
I can't game anymore.
But I haven't seen Genius for days.
Why don't I try my luck online
and see if he's there.
I'll say hello to him if he's there.
[Moonlight Blade]
Genius works so hard.
Marriage maniac?
[Trumpet]
The Lush Peach:
I give Time Flies Flower Blooms 99 Love Flowers.
[Sword Tournament Field]
Light Rain gives Time Flies Flower Blooms
[Trumpet]
99 Love Flowers.
Whooshing Wind gives Time Flies Flower Blooms
Green Water Waves gives Time Flies Flower Blooms
99 Love Flowers.
If in the skies, may we become as birds with matching wings.
[Trumpet]
If on land, may we be as trees with entangling branches.
Really? My goddess is back.
Welcome back, Time Flies Flower Blooms.
I'm going to find my true love.
[A Thousand Faces]
Love as One Heart System is about to open.
Did she come back on purpose
to get married with Genius?
Time Flies Flower Blooms is mine.
Don't take her from me.
It turns out that Time Flies Flower Blooms is back.
[Recently] [Contact] [Group Chat]
I'm speechless.
You need to team up for fishing?
Master.
[99 Love Flowers were sent to Time Flies Flower Blooms]
The evil RMB players.
Are there any worse evildoers than the ones who caused the spam?
Who on earth is this Time Flies Flower Blooms?
Such a big scene.
I almost forgot
you're still a newbie.
Let me explain to you for free.
Time Flies Flower Blooms is good at manipulation.
She has good temperament and artistic style.
A real goddess.
She created ABCC.
What's wrong with being a newbie?
Chu He.
Have you realized the seriousness of the problem?
If she gave me a huge sum of money,
and I couldn't hold myself back, and ran away with it,
will Genius go after me all over the servers?
Master, you can't run.
Who will protect me if you run away?
Time Flies Flower Blooms always wanted to
to deepen the friendship with Ink White.
Unfortunately, Genius is not in the mood.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
It's okay, lady.
If you don't understand,
open the bulletin board,
then read all the comments, you'll understand.
[World]
My official couple is back.
Chu He, bye.
Someone is online,
but she doesn't dare to say a word.
She's obviously afraid.
If you had known this,
you shouldn't have seduced Ink White.
Why are you putting up with it?
I can't take it anymore!
[Trumpet]
The Three Swords of Tai Bai:
Love is between two people.
How come it's all Chu He's fault?
[Trumpet]
Go to pick a fight with Between Ink White if you dare.
Ceaseless Autumn Rain:
[Trumpet]
Stop the rehabilitation!
The cheap bitch knows she's wrong.
So she doesn't dare to say anything.
Cheap bitch?
Why didn't you fight back?
You must fight back now!
Show them your courage like before.
Master, go! Don't be a coward.
[Trumpet]
Che He:
Actually, I also think that Time Flies Flower Blooms
[Trumpet]
and Genius are a perfect match.
Chu He:
But Genius insisted to hold a wedding ceremony with me.
[Trumpet]
I heard he invited a popular video game streamer
to be the MC for us.
What should I do?
He is so excellent.
It's impossible for me to refuse him.
Bravo.
I have to say,
you're really a wolf in sheep's clothing.
I feel sorry for Ink White for one minute.
Now,
I really doubt Ink White's ability to pick a wife.
Although I said so,
I can't even find Genius
these days.
Will I be fooled
and be dumped at the end?
If I were you,
I would exit the game and be decent.
Right.
Being the rival in love of Time Flies Flower Blooms,
you don't deserve it.
Are you over crazy to be famous?
Ink White must have been cheated.
I've screenshot
those who just scolded my wife.
I won't do anything in the game
except hunting you down.
[Confirmed invitation Between Black and White has joined this team]
[Agree] [Cancel]
[Waiting for the player to join]
[Three Swordsmanship of Tai Bai invites you to team up]
[Agree] [Reject]
Are you okay?
No wonder so many people are crazy for you couple.
This support just now
is excellent.
Here comes Time Flies Flower Blooms.
[Time Flies Flower Blooms ]
It's just a misunderstanding.
There's no need to hurt our friendship.
I think
Ink White wouldn't mind.
Of course I do.
I'm the only one who can bully my wife.
OK.
I'll ask my people to apologize to her.
Chu He, I'm sorry.
Never mind.
Well...
Get back to what you're doing.
It's over here.
Did you hear what my wife said?
You must be Chu He, right?
Hope to see you again.
Thank you for supporting me.
It's okay.
Your business is mine.
By the way, Genius,
when did you show up?
Just now.
When you said
I forced you to marry me.
What a coincidence.
To be honest,
I've been busy working overtime recently.
I'd like to tell you this since I happened to meet you today.
I'm going offline. Bye.
Lu Wanwan.
Don't lose your mind.
Read the script.
I didn't expect this scene added to be perfect.
It's enthusiastic.
Could it be
he didn't do it to fool me?
Push.
Hit head.
This is really a big benefit for me.
No.
If I act like this
in this scene, it's will be difficult to perform.
I need to think about how to act.
Lu Wanwan, you're a professional actress.
So you must show
200% professional spirit.
You can't disappoint
Academy of Drama.
You have to act it
perfectly, right?
Yes.
Jiang Xun.
Why didn't you practice hard?
What's wrong with you?
Why didn't you...
Mr. Han, what can I do for you?
[Hang up] [Switch the camera]
If you hurt me during the shoot,
lines of this length will be added
everyday in the future.
Did you install pinhole cameras
in my home?
You're a pervert.
[Hang up] [Switch the camera]
Oh, by the way,
I forgot to ask you
why you suddenly follow me.
Don't you know that I'm very scared?
I followed you just because I wanted to.
Is there any problem?
Well,
you scared me.
According to the analysis of the enthusiastic netizens,
you are
trying to get rid of the scandal with my help,
right?
I think it's your analysis.
So,
didn't you recite the lines,
but only read gossips?
I didn't.
I'm studying the script. Look.
I was studying the script,
right before you called me.
[Hang up] [Switch cameras]
I hope so.
Don't you dare make a mistake tomorrow.
If I make a mistake...
If you fail tomorrow,
this photo will be popular all over the internet.
I knew it.
That's why you suddenly video call me.
So this is the reason.
You scheming man!
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
I don't put up a facade, okay?
But you do.
Do you remember our slogan?
Three, two, one.
We're the national champion!
Come on.
You got dunked by me, right?
I'm your basketball manager.
From now on,
you have to listen to me.
Pay attention to your movements.
Don't mess up.
Yeah, rhythm.
OK. Is this OK?
Where are you looking at?
Look ahead.
Okay, Coach.
Jiang Xun.
Do you know...
You...
Jiang Xun.
Do you know a professional basketball player...
No. Again.
Do you know
how important the basic skill is
to a professional basketball player?
If you don't train hard,
you won't be able to play in matches.
Why are you looking at me?
Listen.
I'll train you from now on.
Get down!
Why are you laughing?
Is it funny?
Stop laughing.
What's so funny?
Mr. Lu.
Why are you here?
Han and Wanwan are filming.
Go find Ye
and share the drinks in my car with everyone.
Okay.
Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu, what brings you here?
Are you here to visit Jingmo?
Long time no see.
You look better and better.
Do you need some coffee?
I'll ask my assistant to buy it for you.
No need.
[Let's run  Sports Day of Spring]
[Youth With Me College League]
Director.
Mr. Lu.
Thank you.
Hello, Qiao.
You're here too.
Mr. Lu.
You...
I'm here to visit the set.
Jingmo and Wanwan are filming outside.
I know.
I'll take a sit and wait for them.
Have a seat.
Here, have some water.
Thank you.
[Big Dunk]
You're injured.
I practiced basketball.
It's okay.
What a coincidence.
I happen to bring a sample ointment
of Jingmo's endorsement.
You can try it.
Aren't you friends?
You can help him test
the effect of this ointment.
Here you are.
No need, Mr. Lu.
It's just a minor injury.
In two days, I...
It's just ointment.
Don't worry about it.
Actors
can't get sick or hurt.
It's a big deal to delay the shooting.
Right?
Okay, I'll take it.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
You're welcome.
Yan.
Coming.
Keep it for me.
Okay.
Let's start.
Scene 18 of Episode 3, first shooting of Scene 3.
Three, two, one. Action.
Jiang Xun.
I know dribbling training is boring and tedious.
I know you can't wait
to play in matches.
I don't care.
Today, I must play in the game.
Listen carefully.
The strong basic skill
is extremely important
for a basketball player
and professional teams.
You're not qualified to play yet.
Your words are too familiar for me to hear.
I don't care. I have to play today.
Come down.
Bad luck.
If I hit it,
I might be on the trending searches again.
Are you okay?
Jingmo, what happened?
How are you? Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you okay, Jingmo? Go take a rest.
Let's go.
Be careful.
You sprained your ankle?
Hold her.
Don't move. Be careful.
Slowly.
Slow down.
Be careful.
Don't follow us.
Get back to work.
[Mind your head]
Be careful.
Are you okay? Watch the steps.
Slow down.
Sit down first.
Sit here.
Let me help you.
Be careful.
Here.
Did you get the ice pack?
[Reading Academic attitude]
I'll go.
What happened? How did it go?
She fell down just now.
Can you move your ankle?
Hurry. Give it to me.
Director, it's all my fault.
I was too reckless.
Shall we continue?
Don't delay the progress.
Your foot..
My foot is fine.
I feel much better now.
Don't let everyone wait for me.
Can you do it?
Yes.
OK.
Come on. On your marks.
Be more efficient.
Get ready to pass once.
Be careful.
I have to play today.
It's my turn. Come down.
Come on.
[Northern Seats]
Come back.
Okay. Cut.
I can walk on my own.
Hold me tight if you don't want to fall.
Are you okay?
To be safe,
I'll take her to the hospital.
I don't have scenes to shoot this afternoon.
Hurry up.
Take a comprehensive check.
How manly.
What's the relationship with them?
Have some water, please.
[Exercise infinitely Challenge yourself]
It's all my fault.
Go and wipe it.
Okay.
[Be smart. Don't talk nonsense.]
Be smart. Don't talk nonsense.
[Let's run Sports Day of Spring]
[Youth With Me College League]
Song Chi asked us to wait for her here.
Luckily, it's just a sprain.
It's a pity that I can't run and jump.
Will it affect the shooting?
It's an emergency. It's good that you're fine.
Thank you.
If it weren't for you,
I would have died on the set.
Tell me.
What do you want to eat?
I'll treat you when you're free.
I'm available on Friday.
Where do you want to go?
I'll tell you when I've made up my mind.
Are you going to
ask Gu Qiaobei to join us?
Yes.
I almost forgot if you didn't remind me.
You can ask Qiao to join us.
How dare you!
Just kidding.
I want to thank you.
Besides,
if my brother is not with us,
it's useless to call Qiao.
Your brother?
My brother admires Qiao very much.
He has little chance to see Qiao.
The car should be here soon.
I'll take you home.
No, I'm going to the set.
Since I get hurt this time,
I can take the chance to
watch others' performance
and learn from them.
You're injured but you're still talkative.
I'm disabled but determined.
I've got the medicine. We can go now.
Okay.
Be careful.
Okay, let's go.
Watch out.
Be careful.
Okay, we're home.
Are you sure you don't need me to send you in?
I'm sure.
You should've just come back from the hospital.
Why did you go to the set? It's so late.
You didn't even rest when you got hurt.
What was I doing?
It's called keep on fighting with a minor injury.
It's okay.
Go home. I am fine.
I'm leaving.
Go.
Have a good rest.
Bye.
Brother.
Isn't it that serious?
What did the doctor say?
You didn't make it clear on WeChat.
The doctor said
it's nothing serious.
I should be fine after a few days off.
A few days?
Do you know how much a few days of work
will affect the crew?
Do you know how much I need to spend on that?
I know, Mr. Lu.
I risked my life to shoot for you, didn't I?
Thank goodness.
So be careful.
Don't get hurt.
Does it hurt a lot?
It's okay.
Han Jingmo looked like
as if you were going to be paralyzed for the rest of your life.
He scared me to death.
Was he?
Yes.
He's probably trying to slack off.
If he didn't say I was seriously injured,
how could he change his schedule?
He is
always moody.
I'm not sure.
All right, I'm going back.
My leg hurts.
So be careful.
Don't get hurt again.
Let's play in the Instance Zone.
Master, you're late.
We're done.
You don't know,
he is out and about these days.
Actually, he went to play for the Pass of
Between Xing Yuan secretly.
We just finished a round.
The Pass of Between Xing Yuan?
That prop
only fell from Tianmang Instance Zones.
And the occurrence rate is very low.
So far,
only a few were exploded.
The probability is lower than the rate that you can hit Ink White to death.
Don't talk nonsense.
Don't bring back the bad memories of Genius.
The days when I got hit are
happy and memorable.
Master, Love as One Heart System is open today.
Do you know?
The whole server was talking about it.
I think
your husband is going to let you two
be the first couple eating crabs there.
I was caught off guard
to be hurt by your romance.
Ink White.
I heard you're fighting for the Pass.
Yes.
But it was all in vain.
I have the Pass of Between Xing Yuan.
If you want it, I can give it to you.
No need.
I remember it took a long time
for her to get it.
Yes.
[Add friends Private chat]
Do you sell your Pass?
For Ink White?
Name your price.
Sorry.
This is not for sale.
Ink White.
Any time,
you can come to me
if you want the Pass.
What's going on?
Hang up and chat secretly?
We are fed with the dog food the whole day.
Master, please switch back to the current channel.
Don't disturb us being your melon-eating masses, okay?
Being lovey-dovey is a torture to others.
Don't hurt me if you don't love me.
We almost meet the requirement of Friendship Level.
[Friendship Level of Chu He]
[Friendship Level of Between Ink White]
Are you in a hurry to marry me?
You're finally smart once.
Where is he?
[System Notification]
[Between Ink White and Chu He start the Love as One Heart mission. Please supervise them.]
Between Ink White and Chu He
start the Love as One Heart mission.
Please supervise them.
So soon?
All of a sudden?
So cruel.
You said you would prepare a love gift for me.
Don't let me down.
[Recently] [Contacts] [Group Chat]
Do you still want the Pass of Between Xing Yuan?
Didn't you say it's not for sale?
I changed my mind.
Let's battle.
If you win, I'll give it to you for free.
Whoever loses needs to exit the game.
Do you dare?
OK.
Deal.
Time Flies Flower Blooms
deliberately doesn't want me to get married.
I can't fulfill what she wants.
Don't worry.
I will protect you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
[3 days later]
Here, Miss Wanwan treat everyone drinks.
Well, I've wasted your time.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Please get the drinks and snacks.
Thank you.
Have some.
Come on.
Come on, everyone.
Thank you.
Let me help you.
You can talk to the producer.
Don't talk to me.
If you want to talk to me,
then let me tell you clearly.
no one can do this in my crew.
Director,
I promise I won't delay the shooting.
How?
You're the female lead?
You have more than 600 scenes.
Except the time you spend on eating,
toilet and sleeping,
you only give me five hours to shoot every day.
Tell me how can I manage it.
Director, everything can be discussed, right?
How?
You mean
you work 24 hours a day?
And we're all with you.
Don't we need to sleep?
Two choices are offered.
Either you turn the other crew down,
or
I change the leading actress today.