♪Allergic to fast-food love,
even if it's too naive♪
♪Just like a hug needs
the right body heat♪
♪Your "same here" carries
a touch of resolve♪
♪Pack my bags, we can set off right now♪
♪The future is a wondrous,
unknown adventure♪
♪The journey itself is what
truly matters before the destination♪
♪Those moments together
are what bind us strongest♪
♪Connect♪
♪Let's go!♪
♪Leave worries behind
in yesterday's sentimentality♪
♪Today, no dwelling
on negative emotions♪
♪Tomorrow holds more luck♪
♪Together we'll create moving melodies♪
♪The future begins to take shape♪
=Love In A Secret=
(I Just Want to Drown With You)
=Episode 6=
Ye Man.
Hello, Ms. Huang?
Wake up.
You're back.
Why did he drink so much?
Lu.
I will treat you
as my biological daughter.
Can you please forgive me
for what I've done wrong before this?
How are you so bad at this when you've
been learning since you were 12?
What has that got to do with you?
I suppose it was a different person.
Listen up.
You'd better mind your own business.
Alright now.
I just want to apologize to you.
I was drunk last night.
What kind of apology is that?
Is being drunk even an excuse?
How could you fall for everyone you see?
I didn't.
You're truly interesting.
I can never tell
when you're speaking the truth.
Why are you following me?
I'll do whatever you do.
Hello, Qun?
Who's back?
Where is he?
Boss, I know my fault.
I won't do it again.
Boss!
What are you doing?
Zhu?
Hi, Miss Lu.
Zhu, you're finally here.
Look, I was punched.
With a wound like that,
I suppose it'll heal up
if I come an hour later.
Long time no see. Give me a hug.
It's been so long since you came back,
yet you got yourself into
a fight right away.
Does your father know about this?
Who told him to steal from my factory?
I'm punishing the wicked
and rewarding the good.
If you do this again,
I'll chop off your arm. You hear me?
Come with me.
How long will you be staying this time?
Of course it's until the time
you no longer wish to see me.
You should leave, then.
Miss Lu,
can you please not be this cold to me?
You weren't like this before.
I was just joking.
I'll buy you a meal.
Come on. What do you want to eat?
Of course I wish to have
your home-cooked food.
Mind your words.
I heard that your father
got you a stepmother.
And, your stepmother
got you a stepbrother.
How did you know?
But of course.
As long as it's related to you,
I'll use all of my connections
to get to the bottom of it.
Why did you think I was in such a hurry
when my father told me to come back?
I just want to see you.
By the way,
how's that stepbrother of yours?
He's nothing special.
He's very ordinary.
Is that so?
If he dares to bully you,
I'll teach him a lesson.
Go on, then.
Don't tell me he's your stepbrother.
Do your friends only consist of thugs?
Who are you calling a thug?
Come with me.
She's not going with you.
Let me explain.
She's not listening to your explanation.
You're so irritating.
So, you're Ye Man,
the top student who just came back
from the US, right?
Listen up.
I'm Chen Tianze.
Hai City is my territory.
Lu Zhu is under my protection as well.
Do not bully her.
You hear me?
Come home with me right now.
Did I say I was going to leave with you?
Did she say she was
going to leave with you?
Why are you trying to drag her home?
I don't understand what you two
are talking about at all.
You can choose to stay here
if you want to see me
turn this dumb friend of yours
into a complete idiot.
Come back!
My car!
Ye Man?
What do you mean by this?
Don't worry. He can't leave.
He can't just run me over.
Are you actually doing it?
Deliver her car to our house later.
Ye Man, come back!
Boss, should we deliver her car?
Darn it.
Why should I listen to him?
Deliver the car to her, you idiot!
Where is he?
Bring him here.
Relay my message to your boss.
Tell him that I'm back.
Bring him to me.
And,
I'm the one in charge of the racetrack.
You hear me?
Can you hear me out now?
It's pointless.
Whatever you do
has nothing to do with me.
Who said so?
I don't know why either.
I was always a composed person.
But when I saw you last night,
and after I drank...
So, whatever you did doesn't count
because you got drunk last night,
right?
Lu!
Listen.
I didn't approach you on purpose.
I don't intend to use you either.
I'm not deceiving you.
And,
I...
♪Bit by bit, I'll forget you♪
♪Bit by bit, I'll erase the memories♪
♪From now on,
your image won't linger in my mind♪
♪Nor will those fragments of the past♪
♪Days will slowly drift away
like passing clouds♪
♪I'll learn to stop
longing for what's gone♪
♪The you in my memories♪
♪Will fade from clarity♪
♪How much longer must I wait to♪
♪Forget you completely♪
I don't know what to do either.
But I think I fell for
my younger sister.
I'll just take that as nonsense.
I'll head home first.
♪Days will slowly drift away
like passing clouds♪
♪I'll learn to stop
longing for what's gone♪
♪The you in my memories
will fade from clarity♪
♪Bit by bit, I'll forget you♪
♪Bit by bit, I'll erase the memories♪
♪From now on,
your image won't linger in my mind♪
♪Nor will those fragments of the past♪
♪Days will slowly drift away
like passing clouds♪
♪I'll learn to stop
longing for what's gone♪
♪The you in my memories♪
♪Will fade from clarity♪
♪How much longer must I wait to♪
♪Forget you completely♪