έβςAllergic to fast-food love,
even if it's too naiveέβς
έβςJust like a hug needs
the right body heatέβς
έβςYour έΑεsame hereέΑζ carries
a touch of resolveέβς
έβςPack my bags,
we can set off right nowέβς
έβςThe future is a wondrous,
unknown adventureέβς
έβςThe journey itself is what truly matters
before the destinationέβς
έβςThose moments together
are what bind us strongestέβς
έβςConnectέβς
έβςLet's go!έβς
έβςLeave worries behind
in yesterday's sentimentalityέβς
έβςToday, no dwelling on
negative emotionsέβς
έβςTomorrow holds more luckέβς
έβςTogether we'll create moving melodiesέβς
έβςThe future begins to take shapeέβς
=Love in A Secret=
(I Just Want to Drown With You)
=Episode 17=
I'm fine.
Do you need to take a rest, Mr. Lu?
I'll go back and rest.
Have the driver pick me up.
Alright.
Come.
Today's Li Zhou's birthday.
Let's all have a drink together.
Thank you, Zhu.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Drink up.
Stop drinking.
You're trying to get yourself drunk.
Why are you being so naggy?
What's wrong with me
having a few drinks?
Come on.
Drink up.
Cheers.
Stop drinking!
Enjoy?
Get lost!
Now!
Hey.
Who upset you
that you have to drink this much?
Ze,
if something clearly has no outcome,
would you still do it?
Of course I would.
See?
I knew someone out there
was just like me.
We don't care about the result at all.
Let's go
and find Qun.
You're drinking this much
in the middle of the day.
Let go.
Look, I can walk in a straight line.
You...
Your shoes.
(Do you think)
(we can stay together forever?)
(What if we break up one day?)
(So,)
(are you breaking up with me now?)
(Have we)
(ever really been together?)
See?
I told you I'm not drunk.
Are you really going to find
Qun and the others?
Why not?
Qun's waiting for me to start the party.
Let me tell you,
she even found
eight male models for me.
Just listen to me.
Let's not go, okay?
Stop nagging.
Wait.
Why does that guy look so familiar?
Isn't this Ye Man?
My stepmother's son.
My brother.
Why are you drunk
in the middle of the day?
What are you doing here?
Ze,
this is between us.
You don't need to get involved.
Go home first.
Are you sure?
If I leave, then he...
My sister told you to leave,
so just leave.
Why so much nonsense?
Ze,
listen.
Qun's upstairs.
Don't worry about me.
You can leave first.
Go home.
Bye-bye.
Why are you here?
Weren't you having lunch with your mom?
Oh.
You didn't eat here, did you?
Perfect. I'll go talk to your mom.
Come back.
Whatever you want to say,
wait until you're sober.
Why do you get to control me?
Who do you think you are?
Mr. Ye,
the previous order was wrong.
Could you please help process it?
Oh.
A moment.
Don't move.
Wrong shoe.
έβςSay I need your loveέβς
έβςHolding your hand, holding your handέβς
έβςThinking of nothing at allέβς
έβςTime will stopέβς
έβςMoonlight will fall across our facesέβς
έβςBy your sideέβς
έβςDon't bury everything insideέβς
έβςI've never feltέβς
έβςMy heartbeat race so fastέβς
έβςMoonlight rippling on the seaέβς
έβςHiding my love in a wooden boatέβς
Stay here and wait for me.
Don't run around.
I don't have a brother.
Is this Dr. Zhang?
Send a car to Zijin Grand Hotel.
Now.
Drunk in broad daylight?
Not your dad's
little obedient girl anymore?
Who's talking?
It's my stepmother.
You and your childish trick again.
Sarcasm,
mockery,
provocation.
You think I'll fall for it?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
I went to the private hospital
you often visit.
So? What are you trying to do?
What am I trying to do?
Maybe you should ask yourself
about that.
Someone your age
pretending to be pregnant?
Do you really think they'll believe you?
I will expose you.
Your dad won't believe you.
If I dared to claim I'm pregnant,
of course I left myself a way out.
Even if you hadn't come to me today,
I would've gone to you.
What are you saying?
Why are you pushing me so hard?
Jiaming and I didn't get to
where we are easily.
I won't allow anyone to tear us apart.
Especially you.
Let go!
Ah!
Mom.
Are you okay, Mom?
έβςBit by bit, I'll forget youέβς
έβςBit by bit, I'll erase the memoriesέβς
έβςFrom now on,
your image won't linger in my mindέβς
έβςNor will those fragments of the pastέβς
έβςDays will slowly drift away
like passing cloudsέβς
έβςI'll learn to stop longing for
what's goneέβς
έβςThe you in my memoriesέβς
έβςWill fade from clarityέβς
έβςHow much longer must I wait toέβς
έβςForget you completely?έβς