[The Vendetta of An]
[Episode 1]
[Tenth Day of the Seven Month]
[Soon, we will return to Chang'an]
In the 28th year of Qiansheng,
the founding emperor fell ill suddenly
and passed away unexpectedly.
General of Huben Army, Yan Fengshan, governed the imperial court
and threw the government into chaos.
He helped the late emperor's youngest son, Xiao Wenjing, ascend the throne
and killed the feudal lords,
causing imperial authority to decline.
In the 4th year of Wencheng,
the late emperor's eldest son, a feudal lord, Xiao Wuyang,
mobilized troops from the north
to overthrow the tyranny.
They travelled 1,300 li southward.
With strict military discipline along the way,
all sides submitted to him.
He arrived in Chang'an,
eliminated the treacherous officials,
and took control of the imperial court.
[Taiqing Palace]
[Xiao Wuyang, New Emperor]
Unable to bear the defeat, the deposed emperor, Xiao Wenjing,
burned himself inside Taiji Hall.
Your Highness,
there were five dead bodies.
None of them belonged to the deposed emperor.
[Gu Yu, Marquis of Northguard]
Have you verified all of them?
Apparently, the deposed emperor
slipped and fell
on a hanbaiyu marble staircase when he was young.
Because of that,
his upper left molar was chipped.
He also fractured his left leg.
All of these
are recorded in the palace records.
These dead bodies
might be unrecognizable,
but it is not difficult
to verify these injuries.
Your Highness,
this was just removed from a dead body's stomach.
It
still appeared in the end.
It was set up on purpose.
They are waging war against Xiao Wuyang.
All subordinates of the city-guarding general,
Li Longjing, have surrendered.
There might still be skirmishes in the city,
but it's nothing to worry about.
We've captured all 12 gates of the Capital.
We will set up camps
in the south
and southwest.
Moreover, the north side of the city
is in our army's control.
The north is secure.
What about Yan Fengshan
and his army?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
The scene at Taiji Hall
has been examined.
The deposed emperor, Xiao Wenjing,
did not die in the fire.
This was recovered from the stomach
of one of the dead bodies
in Taiji Hall.
I'm sure Your Majesty
recognizes the token.
Huben Token.
Does it mean
he has abducted
that useless brother of mine?
Yes.
Xiao Wenjing might be useless,
but one can rule the world
simply by abducting the emperor.
Perhaps
this battle is far from over.
it is just the beginning.
Yan Fengshan and the Huben Army have decided to stay hidden
because they do not want to face Your Majesty directly.
But as long as the deposed emperor is in his hands,
he will surely rise again.
A hidden battle
will soon begin.
I am old.
I was careless.
When you are facing Yan Fengshan,
no one can win
in one move.
I do recommend one particular person
if you want to deal with the Huben Army.
He understands the army the most in this world.
His father, Liu Ziwen,
is the founder of the Huben Army.
15 years ago,
Yan Fengshan led the Huben Army
and betrayed Liu Ziwen.
The Liu clan was annihilated.
He
got lucky and survived
He is an exceptional talent.
Moreover,
he carries a grudge.
After 15 years,
he is now fully prepared.
Many former retainers of the Liu clan
are also helping him secretly.
An exceptional talent?
How does he compare to you?
I am old.
I'm inferior to him.
In that case, bring him to me.
I will test him myself.
Understood.
[Huainan]
Be careful with that.
There's more over here.
Have some water.
In times of crisis,
the government is obstructive and the people suffer.
Extraordinary individuals will arise
[Huainan District Office]
like leopards and magpies.
With the momentum of soaring eagles,
they achieve remarkable feats.
Therefore, extraordinary accomplishments
require extraordinary people.
How extraordinary.
As extraordinary as I am clueless.
You don't need to understand any of that.
As long as I
[Zhou Mo, Magistrate of Huainan]
and the officials above me understand it.
Just listen to these sentences.
Divide and reclaim the land
to restore the dynasty.
With Heaven's mandate to suppress the rebels,
no rebellion can't be crushed.
With righteous actions to achieve merit,
any achievements can be accomplished.
The sentences are magnificent
and every word is exquisite.
All of you
are bumpkins.
Don't even dream of writing such an article
even in your next life.
Sir,
we specialize in
repairing the roofs and catching chickens
for the residents.
You cannot compare us to them.
Exactly, sir.
Yes.
That's right, sir.
Sir!
What is it?
The imperial envoy will arrive at the city gates soon.
All of you, pull yourselves together.
Come with me to meet the imperial envoy.
Where's Huai'an?
Where's my buddy?
Huai'an!
The imperial gazette is here!
[Xie Huai'an]
Be careful.
I just got it.
That's all you harvested after half a day?
The weather is good today.
I'm letting the paddy dry in the sun.
Sure. If you say so.
I've read
the imperial gazette.
The latest issue
is from a month ago.
It's fine even if it's late.
At least, we know
what is happening out there.
Huainan is
remote and desolate.
What happens outside
has nothing to do with this place.
The weather is changing.
Yes.
Rain is coming from behind the mountain.
Ziya.
Look at this article.
It has been a month
since Xiao Wuyang
attacked Xigu Mountain City.
After passing Xigu Mountain City,
it's only 300 li
from Chang'an.
There's no choke point
in-between to defend against any attack.
I'm sure Chang'an
won't be captured so easily.
The Imperial Guards are in charge
of Chang'an's defense.
The soldiers
are all from noble families.
They have adequate military strength,
but look at General Li.
His name is Li Longjing.
He is a coward.
Chang'an
might have been captured already.
That's impossible.
An imperial envoy has come from Chang'an.
Zhou Mo is probably waiting
at the gates to welcome him
with your proclamation condemning the rebels.
What?
[Huainan]
Sir.
They are so slow, sir.
Are you waiting for your wife?
How fast do you expect them to be?
You are useless.
[Huainan District Office]
What is it? Is the imperial envoy here?
I wrote a congratulatory article
for the new emperor's ascension.
Help me find it, quickly.
[Zhang Haoran]
There's no congratulatory article here.
Didn't you write to condemn the rebels?
Zhou Mo took it to meet the imperial envoy.
That article must not be submitted.
One and a half months ago,
Xiao Wuyang led the army
and captured Xigu Mountain City.
The city
is only 300 li away from Chang'an.
There's no choke point in between to defend against any attack.
I'm sure Chang'an won't be captured
that easily.
It has already been captured.
The imperial envoy
serves the new emperor.
If Zhou Mo submits the article,
we'll all be dead.
- That's... - Enough.
Look for it, quickly.
When did you write it?
Two years ago.
Two years ago?
Can you predict the future or something?
Found it.
They are here.
Play the music!
Quick, sound the drum.
Why does he look like a eunuch?
Look like a eunuch?
He is a eunuch.
It's my first time seeing one.
Stop talking from now on.
I, the Magistrate of Huainan District, Zhou Mo,
[Huainan]
greet the imperial envoy.
You may stand, Magistrate.
Thank you, Imperial Envoy.
Huainan District is so remote.
I think
I've travelled 70 li of mountainous roads
to arrive here from the county.
Sir,
Huainan might be remote,
but every land here belongs to the emperor.
The people of Huainan
are also blessed by His Majesty's grace.
You have a silver tongue.
Imperial Envoy,
I've prepared
the best inn
in the district town
to give you
a warm welcome.
That's right.
One more thing.
We have
prepared an article
for you to peruse
when you arrive.
Show me.
Sorry, sir.
Sir,
are you hurt?
How absurd!
Which...
He's one of our own.
Sorry, Imperial Envoy.
I am the district office's registrar.
I apologize
for my reckless action.
I'm very sorry.
Sorry.
Sir,
this is the congratulatory article you wrote.
Please show it to the imperial envoy.
Sir.
What a good article.
How impressive.
I've travelled across states and provinces
and received about 80 articles
to congratulate His Majesty's ascension to the throne.
This is the best one yet.
Mr. Zhou, your literary talent is remarkable.
You shouldn't
humble yourself in this desolate place.
When I return to the Capital,
I will put in a good word to His Majesty
for you.
Thank you, sir.
Oh.
Besides informing the world
about the new emperor's ascension to the throne,
I also travelled
to your district
for one more purpose.
Do tell, sir.
Do you have someone called Xie Huai'an
(Watch on www.kisskh.ws to support Admin)
in your district?
His Majesty has summoned
Xie Huai'an to the Capital.
I am Xie Huai'an.
The imperial envoy said
your journey to the Capital
would be paid by the district office.
We must ensure a comfortable trip for you
in terms of food and accommodation.
Thank you, sir.
He also said
that when you arrived in Chang'an,
an expectant official from the Imperial Academy called Li
will welcome you.
This man
is famous in the Capital.
He will welcome you in person.
The imperial envoy also said...
He said something else?
His Majesty
is going to meet Huai'an in person
and order him
to do something huge.
The imperial envoy wants you
to depart tomorrow
without any delay.
Huai'an,
you said
you'd be my registrar forever.
Enough. Stop pouring.
He is completely drunk.
It's fine.
I'm going to leave anyway.
Tonight,
just let him drink to his heart's content.
Zhou Mo,
I used to tell you
I'd either
be your registrar forever,
or head straight to the imperial court.
I won't choose any other paths.
Before today,
I thought
I'd stay in Huainan forever.
You are a good superior
and a good buddy of mine.
Being your registrar
isn't that bad.
Sir,
why are you crying?
He sounds so devoted.
My buddy is loyal.
What's wrong with me crying just for a while?
I believe
you will complete His Majesty's task dutifully.
Right?
Both of us
will soon reunite.
Right?
That's right.
But it might not be necessary
to return here just to reunite.
This is a farewell gift.
I don't know if your career as an official
will be smooth in the future.
But if you are
no longer an official one day,
open this letter.
It'll be easier
for us to gather in the future.
All right.
Let's make a toast to Huai'an.
- Sure! - Drink up!
Huai'an, may you soar to great heights.
♪Huainan is good♪
♪A safe haven♪
♪The mountains and rivers stretch on like our affection♪
♪An affectionate person...♪
When you were 17 years old,
you carried
a tattered pack
and came to Huainan,
a remote place,
like a homeless man.
You worked as a registrar for seven years,
and served four magistrates.
When they left,
they wanted to take you with them but you refused.
All of us knew
you were destined for great things.
We treated you well
not because we wanted you to help us out
when you achieved success one day,
but we did it out of sincerity.
However,
you are also aloof.
Yes.
But that's who I am.
Careful.
Lie here and count the stars
as your punishment.
Stars!
Stars,
why are you so far away?
You're as far as Chang'an.
Enough already.
Do you know
why I only have two paths to choose from?
Why?
I am a descendant of a condemned official.
15 years ago,
my family was wronged and annihilated.
I got lucky and survived.
Since then, I've been living in hiding.
I slept in the wilderness.
I've lived in the reed swamps.
Had I taken one wrong step
back in the days,
I'd be dead.
Did your family offend
some authoritative figures?
The most authoritative figure of the dynasty.
The leader of Huben Army,
Yan Fengshan.
Yan Fengshan?
His influence spreads across the imperial court.
But times have changed.
Xiao Wuyang
ascended to the throne as a general.
He won't have Yan Fengshan around.
I don't know what he wants me to do,
and I don't know who recommends me.
But this is my opportunity.
I must grasp it.
Huai'an.
Are you trying
to clear your family's name?
Everyone is dead.
There's no use clearing their name.
I'm going to take revenge.
All right.
Go back and rest.
You can sleep for six hours, at least.
We'll send you off at the city gates tomorrow morning.
Sure.
All of you should go back as well.
Enough.
Don't be sad.
I'm leaving.
Father!
- Go! - Father!
Go!
Move a little.
You came back late
and you're still not sleeping?
The sun is coming up.
I'm not sleeping.
Why are you taking the eggs?
Huai'an is going to the Capital tomorrow.
I want to give him some eggs.
Here,
cook the eggs
so he can take them with him on his way.
The journey to the Capital is long.
The eggs
will turn putrid a few days after they are cooked.
What should we do?
Just give him some fresh eggs.
When he feels like eating them,
he just needs to start a fire, boil some water,
and cook them.
You are right.
As expected of my wife.
Move.
What's wrong?
You have no idea, do you?
The chickens will lay eggs in a while.
We can give Huai'an more.
[Congratulations on Your Majesty's ascension]
What?
Are you sad to see me go
and want me dead instead?
Go inside.
Sit down.
You've read it?
News is hard to come by in Huainan.
I deduced what happened in Chang'an
by using old imperial gazettes.
But you had already been aware of the changes a long time ago.
And your name, Zhou Mo,
must just be a pseudonym as well.
I am a member of the Huben Army.
Huai'an, I didn't lie to you.
I also didn't lie to Haoran and the rest.
What I have been showing all of you
is my true character.
However, I was a member of the Huben Army
before I met all of you.
General Yan Fengshan saved me.
I pledged my loyalty before him.
When you were talking about your background,
I was shocked.
I didn't expect my buddy
to be a descendant of Liu Ziwen.
Is fate playing a joke on me?
Huai'an.
I might be one of the Huben Army,
but I've never
killed anyone until today.
I didn't expect the first person I would kill
to be my buddy.
This cruel fate.
There must be many shadow guards
in the imperial court.
Indeed.
They are like
a shapeless net
that hangs above the imperial court.
You will never win against them.
This is indeed a cruel joke.
I thought
I'd become a registrar here forever,
but to my surprise...
Forget it.
Here.
Drink this farewell wine.
Forget that we've ever met.
Whether we live or die, we won't have any regrets.
A cup for life
and a cup for death.
Come, Huai'an.
Life
for you.
When I was young,
my mother died in the north.
When I was ten years old,
my father died as well.
The whole Huben Army defected and killed him.
I can't die.
I must get revenge on the Huben Army.
I'll kill any Huben soldiers I see
until none of them are left.
I collected the eggs for him.
Are you sure?
I'm sure it was your wife who did that.
I did it.
Huai'an.
We are here to send you off.
What happened?
Zhou Mo.
Sir!
- Sir! - What happened?
Don't ask.
It's not his fault.
Don't tell anyone.
Don't...
Don't trouble him.
We all
have our own reasons.
Zhou Mo.
- Zhou Mo. - Sir!
Zhou Mo!
- Sir! - Sir!
Sir!
What have you done?
That's Zhou Mo!
Stay away from me
if you don't want to die.
[Autumnal Equinox: thunder begins to soften,]
[insects find space to make nests, and water begins to solidify.]
The water is chill
and the weather is cold.
Travelers, move along.
Those near the riverbank, stay away from the shore.
Color me surprised.
This place could kill you.
Why did you come back?
Only one person is buried here.
It's not a dangerous place.
The real danger is Chang'an,
70 li away from us.
It seems like you are passing by indeed.
Then, I won't be
sharing this fish with you.
I'm going back to Chang'an.
I don't know if I'll leave alive.
So, I come to see you
before I enter Chang'an.
Right.
You
are bound to return one day.
Yes.
Your younger sister
went to Chang'an as well.
She went to study.
Perhaps
she is an imperial scholar now.
I know.
Both of you are so far apart.
How did you know?
She has been writing letters to me.
I've also been replying to her letters.
Why wouldn't you reunite with her?
I dare not.
It's best not to reunite with her forever.
None of my family
ended up well.
The people of the Liu clan
suffer a harsh fate.
Her name has been changed.
Hopefully, she can live her life in peace.
You've changed your name as well.
You must be safe.
Come.
[Chang'an]
Mr. Huai'an,
both of us are here to pick you up.
It's the beginning of winter today and it's snowing.
Thank you, both of you.
Mister,
let me carry it.
Open the gates.
This way.
♪Memories are arrows flying against the wind♪
♪Piercing through what should be forever♪
♪They wake me to find our story ended♪
♪When has time ever been kind♪
♪Or shown mercy to anyone?♪
♪I ride across the mountains and return♪
♪Still cloaked head to toe in night♪
♪The bitter sea knows no shore, the wind no sleep♪
♪You remain far back in the past♪
♪I drift in a lone boat♪
♪Searching the depths of the abyss♪
♪Before old dreams scatter and fade♪
♪Why is life so short♪
♪And filled with partings?♪
♪Only now do I see fate knows only the lash♪
♪And grants no mercy♪
♪Alas♪
♪Time vanishes in an instant into dust and smoke♪
♪Ashes of regret♪
♪Burn through my remaining years♪
♪Alas♪
♪This body is trapped in destiny's cold prison♪
♪Throughout my life♪
♪I struggle between one pain and the next♪
♪Alas♪
♪Time vanishes in an instant into dust and smoke♪
♪Ashes of regret♪
♪Burn through my remaining years♪
♪Alas♪
♪This body is trapped in destiny's cold prison♪
♪Throughout my life♪
♪I struggle between one pain and the next♪