[The Storm of Roses]
[Episode 20]
How's your father's health?
He's doing well.
I'm going to Beijing next week.
I'd like to visit him.
He's not very busy lately.
I think he's just supervising a few doctoral students.
No problem. When you're planning to go,
I'll give him a call.
If I have time, I'll go with you.
Sounds good.
I'll contact you then.
No problem.
I ran into Xia Mingxuan recently.
Isn't Xia Mingxuan your father's star pupil?
Uncle Xia.
Now that you're in Puhang,
haven't you visited him?
When I first arrived,
I'd go to his place for meals every day.
I was always troubling Uncle Xia.
Later, since I took over Jade Oak Capital,
and...
Yeah, and then...
I haven't seen him much lately.
Xia Mingxuan has got some big promotion.
That's great.
With Uncle Xia's knowledge and abilities,
it was bound to happen sooner or later.
Congratulations to him.
Sir, can you
please drive as fast as possible
while ensuring our safety?
Okay, I'll do my best.
Thank you. Thank you.
No problem.
I remember when you were in college,
you seemed to have
organized some student entrepreneurship...
Entrepreneurship Week.
Yeah, Entrepreneurship Week.
It had quite an impact at the time.
Not really. I'm flattered.
Well, at the end of this year,
Puhang City is planning to host a
college student entrepreneurship festival.
There's going to be a sub-forum.
When the time comes, see if
you have time.
If it's convenient for you,
maybe you can take the lead
and organize it.
Since you're asking, Zongyu, I must make myself available.
Thanks then.
It's my pleasure.
Hello?
Yidi.
Can you hurry up?
They're about to pay and leave.
I'm almost there, almost there.
Make sure you stall them.
But I...
How am I supposed to stall them?
Should I tackle them or something?
You just...
Just do whatever you can to keep them there.
Aren't you supposed to be smart?
Right?
Use that clever brain of yours.
Thank you, thank you.
I'll treat you to a meal later.
Bye.
This year's Investment Annual Conference happens to be held in Puhang,
so I'll be staying for a bit longer.
I'll introduce you to a few of my old friends
when the time comes.
Sounds good.
Thank you, Zongyu.
Do you remember Yang Xiao?
Yes, I do.
He's now invested in a chip design company.
Pretty impressive.
That's great.
Mr. Yu.
It really is you. What a coincidence.
You are...
You must be Ms. Shen, right?
Hello, hello, Ms. Shen.
I've heard so much about you.
I finally get to meet you in person.
This is
Michael Cheng, who's in charge of project investment at our company.
Hello, Ms. Shen.
Hello.
Ms. Shen.
Ever since Puhang Capital Group
started investing in new energy,
I've thought you were truly remarkable.
I've been wanting to find an opportunity to learn from you.
I wonder if I could take up a bit of your time?
Ms. Shen's schedule is already full.
When there's a chance in the future,
I'll invite Ms. Shen to visit our company.
Not just you,
even I have many questions to ask Ms. Shen.
The elevator's here.
I'll escort you down first.
Well...
I... I'm leaving too.
I'll... I'll come along to see her off as well.
Ms. Shen, you're based in Puhang, right?
Mr. Yu, this restaurant is quite good.
The decor is nice too.
Yeah.
The food is pretty good.
Ms. Shen.
How are you leaving?
By car.
It's all arranged.
After I've made the arrangements,
I'll contact you.
Well, how about I...
How about I accompany you to see her off?
I can do it myself.
Mr. Yu!
Hello, Ms. Shen.
I'm Jiang Yidi from Jade Oak Capital.
Ms. Shen, the car is here.
Careful, the car.
Please get in.
Ms. Shen.
May I have a few minutes of your time?
Get in the car first.
I...
Take care.
Let's keep in touch.
Alright.
Goodbye, Ms. Shen.
Now, explain to me.
What exactly is going on?
What are you two doing?
I'm seizing the opportunity.
Didn't you say fair competition?
I'm competing.
Shen Zongyu is Li Weiqing's angel investor.
I... I...
Since I could meet her,
I was just seizing the opportunity, right?
What's wrong?
In what capacity
and position are you asking me this question?
Do you know what you two are doing?
Acting like fools, playing off each other!
Can't you be more professional?
Mr. Yu, can I...
Shut up!
Come with me.
Why did you bring me here?
When my mind is clouded,
I like to come to nature,
look at the greenery and the water
to calm myself down
and clear my head a bit.
I think I'm quite clear-headed.
I just don't want to give up
the Weiqing Book Club project.
You need to reflect.
I know you have a problem with me.
You may think
I'd act one way to your face and another behind your back
like your old boss did.
But let me tell you.
I'm not that kind of person.
I won't take sides,
and I certainly won't casually
introduce my resources to just anyone.
I understand you.
Recently, due to your suspension,
you've lost a lot of time.
So you want to work hard
to achieve something to prove yourself.
I can see that,
and I really admire your ambition.
But when you're focusing on your goal,
can't you also observe the environment
around your target?
Have you figured it out?
I have.
Weiqing Book Club needs funding.
I...
I don't want to give up on Weiqing Book Club.
Do you know Shen Zongyu well?
I've learned a bit about her.
What you've learned is to use Shen Zongyu
as a stepping stone,
as a shortcut,
to accomplish your Weiqing Book Club.
Is that what you mean?
Is this what you've learned about Shen Zongyu?
Alright. You say you know her.
How did you get to know her?
Apart from the text on encyclopedias,
about her background, her status,
and everything about her,
tell me, what do you know about her?
Shen Zongyu and my father are old family friends.
Even with this kind of relationship,
I have to consider my words and actions
when I'm with her carefully again and again.
What about you?
Using those cheap attention-seeking tactics
to approach her.
Do you think she can't see through it?
Yes, you might think it's not important,
because all you have in your mind is Weiqing Book Club.
Wake up, will you?
There are no sentimental "big brothers"
or sentimental big shots in this world.
Not a single big shot
would, for your little passionate sentiment,
for those dreams and ideals, do things like...
There's none.
I'm begging you,
dump all that motivational nonsense
out of your head!
This is the capital market.
It's a bloody battlefield.
If we don't fight to the death,
it's only because our opponent doesn't deserve it.
Compared to Shen Zongyu,
Li Weiqing is nothing in my eyes.
Even if we lose the Weiqing Book Club project,
we still have other projects.
But if because of your recklessness,
we offend Puhang Capital Group,
we might lose
a potential limited partner.
Do you understand?
You might think the equity market is hot right now,
but it's very likely that within a year,
it will cool down really fast.
What should we do then?
You know the domino effect, right?
When one company falls,
a whole bunch of companies will fall one by one.
So we
need to get our returns back
before the winter comes.
Do you now understand what I'm thinking about,
what I'm doing every day,
and what's most important in my heart?
Do you know it now?
I have plans for you.
I hope you can help me.
Every sentence I'm saying now,
I hope you can remember clearly.
I'm raising
one or two new funds.
This task must be completed before the end of the year.
For what?
For sufficient ammunition storage
when winter comes.
The Jade Oak Capital fund has been around for five years.
The fund matures in seven years,
which means we have two years left.
We need to either exit,
list,
merge,
or have the founders buy back
all the projects we have on hand.
But these are all very difficult.
Really difficult.
Can I trust you?
Blind efforts won't succeed.
Mr. Yu.
Well,
it's really quite cold.
Can I get back in the car?
It's about to rain.
Of course, of course.
[Front passenger airbag is activated
Check the Owner's Manual]
We're out of gas.
Song Bo. Alas, Song Bo.
Song Bo. Song Bo.
I'll
call someone in our company.
There's no signal on my phone.
Do you have any signal on your phone?
No.
I'll get out
and look for a signal.
It's raining.
You won't find gas by getting out, will you?
I want to get out and try to find a phone signal.
Don't bother.
Let's just sit for a while.
Well,
about what you just said, I...
I understood.
Well, maybe not completely.
Anyway, I got the gist of what you meant.
Regarding my behavior today,
I do think
it was a bit impulsive.
Reckless.
Yeah, reckless.
I want to apologize for my reckless behavior
today.
Apology accepted.
And also,
about what you said
regarding whether you can trust me or not,
I think it's without question
that you can trust me.
I hope so.
They're stuck on the highway.
I guess they'll be here quite late.
It's hard to say when the road will reopen.
So we'll just have to wait.
I didn't mean it.
No, listen.
It was really Song Bo who did it.
I didn't mean it.
You're talking about this?
I understand.
I wouldn't think of you that way.
This is quite funny, huh?
In a luxury car like this,
and the two of us
being hungry and cold.
It's quite like a romantic drama.
I don't watch romantic dramas.
Yeah.
I can tell.
Are you cold?
A little bit.
It's okay.
No, no, it's not necessary.
Mr. Yu.
It's okay. I'm wearing plenty.
Here.
Thank you.
This scene is also very much like a romantic drama.
I know you don't watch them.
Does it have a name?
I can look it up.
Never mind.
It's not really suitable for you.
Not suitable for me?
Are you still cold?
Not anymore.
I feel warm inside.
So what do you usually watch?
Financial news?
What else?
It's all news.
That's good.
Your life is so interesting.
I forgot the name of that movie.
Boss, has...
Has anyone ever told you that sometimes you're a bit...
How to say...
Adorkable?
Is that a derogatory term?
No, it's commendatory.
Adorable?
M-Me?
You're particularly wise.
Thank you.
You're very cute too.
I know.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're wearing cologne?
Cool Water.
Davidoff.
So classy.
Do you like watching movies?
Movies? I do watch them.
Yes.
I do.
Forrest Gump.
The Shawshank Redemption.
Are romantic dramas good?
They're good.
Really good.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
It's all right.
It's already morning.
I'll go out for some fresh air.
[Caution: Hot]
Di.
Why are you here so early today?
What happened?
You look listless
and miserable.
Yu Shi didn't scold you
later last night, did he?
Don't take it too seriously.
I've noticed that our...
Oh my.
I've noticed that our Mr. Yu
is particularly obsessed with
those useless processes.
The other day,
he said the numbers in my financial model
weren't accurate enough.
How is that possible?
You know, just like the wood club is for show,
and the putter is for making money.
The process serves the result.
Just make sure you push in
the ball with the putter, and that'll be it, right?
But I can understand.
Our Mr. Yu
hasn't been in a good mood lately.
Mr. Ding just left,
and a lot of people have left the company.
The projects aren't going smoothly,
and we're short-staffed.
I heard he's desperately trying to recruit people.
It's not that easy.
There are a bunch of newbies and rookies.
Where can he possibly find
excellent ones like us?
Hello, Mr. Yu.
[Caution: Hot]
Mr. Yu.
Sit.
Sit down.
About last night...
Last...
You're eating noodles, right?
Come see me when you're done.
"You're eating noodles, right?
Come see me when you're done."
What happened last night?
Where did you two go?
Is it any of your business?
You both didn't change your clothes,
and you both caught a cold.
Where on earth did you two go?
Go away.
As if he would be interested in you.
You think he's blind or something?
Come in.
Are you alright?
I'm fine. How about you?
I'm okay.
You've caught a cold?
No, I haven't.
I heard you sneezing earlier.
Can you manage?
It's okay. I can manage.
Take a look at this.
Uni Wine?
Right. I want to
explore the consumer market a bit.
I want you to feel out the situation.
So, regarding Li Weiqing's project,
put it on hold for now.
Why?
Tang Ruo
has made an appointment with Li Weiqing tonight.
So I'll have dinner
with her and Li Weiqing.
It's like this, Yidi,
I don't want you to focus your energy
on a battle of egos.
Since Tang Ruo has already taken the first step,
let her go ahead.
I don't want to see
the competition between you two
affect other people's judgment of
our company's professionalism.
This is very important to me.
Can you understand?
I'll try to understand.
Thank you.
Remember to take your medicine.
So much?
Send me a message each time you take it.
Thank you, Boss.
[Answer] [Decline]
[Caller: Dad]
Hello, Dad.
Hello.
Linhui.
I have a situation here.
What's going on?
You know Xiaotong left, right?
A few days ago, I helped your mom
pack up all of Xiaotong's things
from her room,
and we sent them to her by express delivery.
But just now,
I saw a young guy
carrying a lot of stuff
into her room.
Could it be a new tenant?
That's impossible.
I've asked the real estate agent,
and they said the landlord had no plan to rent it out anymore.
Besides,
I've seen that young guy before.
He seemed to be pretty close to Xiaotong.
If that's the case,
it does sound a bit abnormal.
Linhui.
Could it be that
Xiaotong wants to move back in?
Dad, well,
I'll try to find out more about this.
You help me keep an eye on things here.
Let me know if anything happens.
Okay.
Recently,
I've been watching a lot of spy movies.
Alright.
I'm counting on you then, great detective.
Okay, okay.
Okay, bye.
Classical music is the best, right?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
So beautiful.
After your sister finishes playing, why don't you go play too?
No, I'm not as good as my sister.
Sister plays wonderfully.
It's really beautiful.
Bravo.
You played so well.
Mengmeng.
You're getting better and better.
Last month,
she just took the Level 10 exam at the music conservatory.
Level 10?
Is that the highest level?
Not at all.
Level 10 is just the beginning for professionals.
Really?
So, is she planning to apply to a music conservatory?
Playing the piano
is just her hobby.
Mengmeng's aspiration is to become a lawyer.
Being a lawyer is good too.
When I first entered the workforce,
I discovered that
gender equality in the workplace
is not just a women's issue.
It's a sign of social progress.
As professional women,
pursuing equality
is not just about speaking up,
but also about taking action.
When I entered my 30s,
I got married,
became pregnant, and had my child.
It seemed like I had fully entered into family life.
But I didn't want to give up my career.
Many professional women nowadays,
to better educate the next generation,
would interrupt their careers,
or have their careers affected
due to falling behind on the required knowledge,
resulting in a decline in their own abilities.
This salon today
was proposed by Shen Zongyu and sponsored by Puhang Capital Group.
She will definitely come.
I believe we shouldn't be limited by age or gender.
Also,
the rumor that Puhang Capital Group is entering the media industry is true.
I hope I...
They're making quite a big move this time.
I heard that Oriental Commercial&Culture Group
previously talked about downsizing
and rejuvenating middle and senior management.
It's all to attract investment.
Gao Tian has had his eye on her for a long time,
but whether she'll ultimately invest in Dongfang Wenshang
is still hard to say.
That's nonsense, isn't it?
How's your relationship with her?
If she's an alpha woman,
she'll definitely be called...
Just a nodding acquaintance.
If you want to talk about specifics,
it still depends on your own persuasiveness.
A full-time housewife...
But
I believe you'll handle it well.
You don't earn money...
Thank you for having so much confidence in me.
It's like a seesaw...
To be honest, though,
why are you going through all this trouble?
So many people would love to collaborate with you.
Consider the proposal I gave you last time.
Is such a laborious thing.
You mean the startup camp, right?
Actually, I've had thoughts about it for a while,
but I don't think the time is right yet.
You...
It's my dad calling. Excuse me for a moment.
It means we will constantly endure
increasing
psychological and physical pressure...
Hello, Dad.
What's up?
I've been keeping watch at home,
and I caught this guy.
It's that young guy I just told you about.
He said
it was Xiaotong who told him to come back.
Yes.
What did Xiaotong ask you to come back for?
Come on, tell her sister yourself.
Tell the truth.
Listen to me, Sis. Sis.
Sis, I'm Zhou Zhou.
You know each other?
You're just...
Sis, it's like this.
I'm just here to get her some food and drinks
because she told me
she was coming back to stay for a couple of days.
And, uh,
she's planning to do something.
Do something?
What kind of thing?
She's coming back to cause trouble?
Dad.
Please don't interrupt. Let him speak.
Yes, yes. Let me, let me.
Come on, come on.
Sis.
It's... It's like this.
I don't know the specifics,
but anyway, these past couple of days,
she's sent me two boxes
full of her stuff.
She... She said
she didn't want to go abroad,
and she wanted to run away from home.
I... I tried to talk her out of it. I did.
I told her this wasn't a good idea,
but she wouldn't listen to me.
You know her personality,
right?
Then I had a thought.
If she lives here,
we can still find her, can't we?
This way, I can also keep you informed,
right?
Did she say anything else?
Tell the truth.
Not... Not much.
It's just...
It's just
she sent me a text message today,
saying there's a family gathering today,
and she wants to stir up some trouble.
Today? Are you sure it's today?
Okay, thank you, Zhou Zhou.
Could you please pass the phone to Uncle Xie?
So you're an insider too.
Linhui.
She...
What exactly was she talking about?
A family gathering?
Why didn't I know about this?
Dad, don't worry.
I already have a general idea of the situation.
Keep an eye
on things for me.
Let me know if anything happens.
I have an urgent meeting right now.
I've got to go.
Bye.
Linhui.
She hung up.
Is that enough, Uncle?
I've told you everything.
I've come clean.
So, can I go now?
Dream on.
What's Yifeng up to these days?
Why hasn't he been around lately?
Well, he
is in Beijing for training.
He's about to go on an aid mission to Tibet.
He said when he's done,
he'll come to visit you two specially.
Let him focus on his work.
This generation of young people
does need to gain some good experience.
Indeed.
But it's good for Yifeng
to have taken the initiative to request
to participate in the national aid program for Tibet.
Just for this alone,
when he comes back,
I'll treat him to some expensive drinks.
-The kids of our Chang family...
-Hello?
They're all outstanding,
-Good for them.
-Linhui.
And there's our Changbao.
Changbao is a child prodigy.
Come on, perform for us.
Come on.
Speak now, speak now.
There are too many people inside. I couldn't hear you.
Go ahead.
Xiaotong is next to you now, right?
Yes, she is.
It's because of her
that we're having the family gathering today, right?
I was just worried she might mess up at the crucial moment,
so I thought I'd check with you.
Nothing else.
When are you coming?
How about this?
Send me the location.
I have
a very important meeting right now.
If I can make it, I'll come.
If I can't make it,
just go on
without me, okay?
-Bye, Mom.
-Try your best.
Okay. Bye.
She's over there.
I haven't seen you since then.
Indeed.
You're looking more beautiful than ever.
Ms. Shen.
Ms. Miao.
-Hello. Hello.
-Long time no see.
Let me introduce you to a good friend of mine.
This is...
Linhui.
Hello.
Ms. Shen, we finally meet in person.
Oh, so you two know each other.
Yes, we do.
That's right.
Because of that interview about Puhang Innovation,
I've had many phone calls with Ms. Shen.
We've been wanting to meet in person,
but our schedules never seemed to align.
Yes, indeed.
These past few years,
I've been flying everywhere.
The time I could spend in one place
has really been too short.
I'd like to make some new friends,
but it's been difficult.
However, this time,
I'll be staying here a bit longer.
-That's great.
-Let's keep in touch.
Absolutely, absolutely.
Please feel free to call me anytime.
Ms. Shen.
Coming, coming.
You two chat.
Please, go ahead with your business.
We'll talk more later.
-Okay.
-Go ahead.
Hey, you.
You knew her and didn't even tell me.
Did you hear that?
She'll be staying here for a few days.
There's a chance.
I wish you success.
Would you like something to drink?
Anything is fine.
Whatever works.
I'll go check it out.
Ms. Xie.
Hello.
I'm Zheng Yi, Fu Dalin's assistant.
We've met a few times at the law firm before.
Dalin values you quite a bit,
even managed to get you here.
Yes.
Mr. Fu is professionally competent and a good person.
Although I'm just an assistant now,
getting out more to see the world,
building some connections,
and learning more is good for me.
Nowadays, employees like you
who are both clever and loyal
are hard to find.
That's why I still need
you to guide me more, Ms. Xie.
What would you like to drink, Ms. Xie? I'll pour it for you.
It seems there's no sugar-free cola here.
I'll go over there and get it for you.
Thank you, then.
Could you also get me a bottle of sparkling water?
And make sure it's room temperature.
Also, could you bring me a separate glass of ice?
Sorry for the trouble.
Thank you.
Certainly.
What's going on?
Any tasty snacks?
Not really.
I can't eat.
I'm on a diet.
Ms. Xie, your drinks.
Sugar-free cola.
Room temperature sparkling water.
Anything you'd like to drink?
You know me well.
I'll have the sparkling water.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So
she's your assistant?
Quite clever, isn't she?
Don't underestimate her.
She's a top graduate from a prestigious law school.
She's currently interning at my friend's law firm.
Is that so?
My company's headquarters is currently recruiting legal personnel.
The salary and benefits are quite good.
Are you interested?
What a great opportunity
came out of nowhere.
Come on, thank Ms. Miao.
Thank you, Ms. Miao.
A recommendation from Ms. Miao is as good as getting the job.
Oh, stop it.
Why don't you seize this opportunity
to come out and have a good chat with me?
How nice this is.
What's the matter?
Last time, our company...
Are you going to marry Fu Dalin?
You've aborted the child, right?
In order to make sure you abort the child,
Dalin must have promised you a lot of benefits, right?
What?
He got you in here today
to show you
how capable he is
and how many connections he has, right?
You also think you can
promote faster this way
at least than those who graduated the same year as you, right?
Have you noticed
his attitude changed after you had the abortion?
Did you keep the evidence?
That's a silly question for me to ask.
You studied law, after all.
How could you not have thought of the basics?
I'm not here today
to criticize you.
I'm here to solve problems.
Mao Xiaohe is my best friend.
Of course I'll protect her.