[The Storm of Roses]
[Episode 31]
I am very smart.
I am so powerful.
Although I am young,
I have a unique vision.
I will bring wealth to all of you.
I'm standing at the forefront of opportunity.
Even pigs
can fly.
Tremble,
mortals.
Does this sound funny to you?
Do you know why you find it funny?
Why?
Because you don't trust me,
and you trust yourself even less.
But I believe you have this ability.
I believe you have the power to influence this world,
even to change it.
You disappoint me so much.
I never thought
you would waste your talent like this.
What you're calculating in your mind now is
to see if this company has potential.
If it does,
you'll stick around for a while longer.
If it doesn't,
you'll cash out and leave.
You think you have some fans now,
sometimes even being
recognized when walking down the street,
and you're still young,
with plenty of opportunities ahead.
Wrong.
Wrong, wrong, wrong.
The opportunity I'm giving you now
might be the most important one in your life.
It could even change your entire destiny.
From this point on, you might
transform from an ordinary person
into a successful individual.
Do you know why?
I...
Wh...
Why?
Because I'm...
the Wonder Girl?
I wasn't wrong about you.
She can do it.
She really can do it.
This kid, Zhang Xiaoxin,
started learning computers at the age of four,
and learned about Trojan programs at 13.
He made his first fortune of 200,000 yuan.
Now he has his own company.
Do you see?
These kids
have all established their own companies now.
To put it bluntly,
they're all worth tens of millions now.
What does that have to do with me?
Behind them all is a pusher.
A pusher.
And that pusher is me.
Now I'm giving this opportunity to you.
To me?
Isn't that a bit hasty?
I'm a magician in the business world.
Right now, I'm going to transform someone like you,
an utterly ordinary girl,
into a business elite full of wisdom.
That's what I call turning stone into gold.
What does the Wonder Girl do anyway?
Just live streaming.
Anyway, the boss said,
to first establish my persona,
then expand my fan base,
and finally sell products through live streaming.
That's no different from what we're doing now.
So where's the magic in that?
The magic might be that
he said he would invest in me through another company
and make me a Gen Z startup star.
He'll invest 20 million first.
How much?
20 million.
Don't get so excited.
I haven't decided yet.
However,
this 20 million
does seem like a lot.
What's there to think about?
Isn't it like a windfall?
What do you still
have to think about?
He's not giving me 20 million in cash.
He's giving me 20 million to
start a company.
I've never run a company before, you know?
I don't know if I can do it.
Didn't you always say
you want to achieve something to show your parents?
You don't want such a good opportunity?
I'll take it if you don't.
But they wouldn't consider me anyway.
I just don't feel confident about it.
What are you afraid of?
Just give it a try.
Being an startup star would be so glamorous.
Try it.
Okay.
Let's give it a try.
How are you adjusting recently?
I think I'm doing pretty well.
That's great. Keep it up.
Chief Editor Lv, if I have any issues later,
-please let me know anytime.
-Hello, Chief Editor Lv.
Good morning, Chief Editor Lv.
Let me know if you need anything.
Alright, no problem.
If you have any questions in the future, just ask.
No problem, Chief Editor Lv.
And there are so many experienced old colleagues
in the office.
You can ask them as well.
Alright.
Feel free to ask.
Okay.
You go first.
Hello?
What?
Why are you standing here?
You didn't answer my calls.
Look how many times
I called you.
My phone's on vibrate.
Who's that girl?
A new colleague at work.
What's the matter?
Xie Linhui.
She is discussing an event with the Puhang Municipal
Finance Office.
I see.
Just send me a WeChat message if there's anything.
Don't keep standing here.
It's not good for people to see you like this.
Then keep an eye on your phone.
Alright.
I'm going to work now.
Go ahead.
I think this
[Puhang Municipal People's Government, Finance Office]
is actually a good thing.
Such a big project,
Deputy Director Yang entrusting it to us.
It shows trust in us.
Right.
But given our department's current situation,
can we handle it?
That's what I'm worried about.
Yes, indeed, right now
if we're going to do this,
manpower and venue
are all issues.
This is not an ordinary project.
You know how much the municipal government
values this venture capital and investment conference.
We can't afford to make any mistakes.
Do you want to take it on?
Yes.
I think this is an opportunity.
Then let's go with your decision, Chief Editor.
Let's give it a try.
[Puhang Municipal People's Government, Finance Office]
Let's go.
[Changqing Street Community Service Center]
Hello, everyone.
Xiaotong.
You're here.
Hello.
No livestream today?
Recently,
our company has undergone major changes.
We're not doing livestreams anymore.
Where's my sister?
Why haven't I seen her?
Ms. Xie and Mr. Wang went out.
No wonder she's not answering my calls.
She asked me to come for an internship,
but I can't even find her.
-Internship?
How about starting by getting us some coffee?
A qualified intern
starts by bringing coffee.
You're a quick learner.
Your mocha.
Thanks.
Jingjing,
your beloved flat white.
Thank you.
Here, your latte.
Thank you, Xiaotong.
It's nothing.
[Let's watch a movie tonight]
What are you writing?
Ms. Xie asked us to come up with some topic ideas
that should be relevant to daily life
and be engaging
to attract people's attention.
And better be practical.
What do you mean?
For example,
the privacy issues of mobile apps.
Isn't that something everyone's concerned about?
Yes.
Like now,
online shopping is closest to our daily lives.
Look,
what you bought,
who you bought it for,
your delivery address—
[I'm in a meeting. Call you back later. Be good.]
aren't these all privacy concerns?
But who would care about what you've bought?
[Meeting again?]
That's not necessarily true.
Let's say, for instance,
you're dating two girlfriends at the same time,
and you bought gifts for both of them.
A quick check would reveal it.
You... you're the one dating two girlfriends.
[What have you been up to?]
I'm straight, you know.
But I've really heard about it.
Nowadays, things like your phone's step count,
online shopping addresses,
even cloud synchronization of your phone's storage,
can all be used to catch cheaters and expose affairs.
You seem to know a lot about this.
Just a little.
Is it really that magical?
Jingjing,
what's wrong with you?
We're in the era of big data now.
How come you're not keeping up with the times?
You need to keep up.
You're outdated, sis.
Alright.
You're right.
So, privacy on mobile phones
must be protected.
Ye Wei,
why are you so nervous?
Are you afraid your two girlfriends
will discover something?
-Gao Xiaohui, stop talking nonsense.
-There's a story.
Xiaotong,
can you teach me?
How do I check?
Sis,
you've asked the right person.
Let me give you
a very simple example.
We all shop online, right?
-Yes.
-Okay.
When we track our packages,
there's an app for that, right?
You need to log in with your phone number.
Then the system sends you a verification code.
Once you log in,
what you've bought,
when you've bought,
for whom,
and where it's delivered—
it's all recorded clearly.
Imagine if one day,
you logged into your boyfriend's account,
you'd know exactly
what he's bought, right?
Sis,
if a man cheats,
with our women's intuition
and the help of technology,
wouldn't we catch them every single time?
That makes sense.
You women...
are terrifying.
You men...
are no simple either.
-Yeah.
-Xiaotong, you…
Let me see.
Come on.
Want to eat?
When are you going to submit this?
You've only written this much.
I don't know how to write it.
I'm talking to you.
Speak.
My parents are coming to see me next week.
Should I
arrange for us to have dinner together?
Isn't next week too rushed?
What's rushed about it?
We're planning to buy a house together, aren't we?
You haven't even met them yet.
And it's not easy for them to make this trip.
Aren't you going to meet them?
What do you mean?
I think this is too informal.
I don't know what your family's customs are.
But in my family,
we formally visit,
and bring several
big gifts,
so that when they meet me,
they'll agree
and accept me.
To make them feel that I'm a decent person.
What do you think?
My family doesn't care about all that.
Tomato handmade meatball pasta.
Foie gras sauce.
Tomato handmade...
Do you drink?
No.
Oh, right.
I ordered a shirt for you yesterday.
Can you check if it's been shipped?
What's the rush?
It'll be shipped sooner or later.
Waiter.
Coming.
We'd like to order.
You're so lazy.
For the main course, we'll have the tomato handmade meatball pasta.
There's a verification code.
Take a look.
I'll check it for you, okay?
Alright.
Slow-roasted smoked beef brisket.
Crispy fried squid and river shrimp.
Can you remember that?
You can remember, right?
Yes.
[Package on the way]
Get her a cup of hot oat milk,
or grapefruit soda.
These two are fine.
Alright, sir. Thank you.
Please wait a moment.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you unhappy?
Don't always be unhappy.
Once we get through this busy period,
we'll formally go back home
to meet the parents.
Enjoy the meal.
Okay.
I'll do as you say.
[Building the New Times First-class Media Group]
[2016 Puhang Venture Investment Conference Project: Preparation Status]
This is a good thing.
At the municipal government meeting before the New Year,
the leaders proposed
to accelerate the construction of a digital city,
an emerging city,
and an innovative city,
and to provide a better business environment.
This conference is more important than previous ones.
In addition to the awards,
it will also convey the government's
intention of promoting high-quality and healthy
development of entrepreneurship and investment in Puhang.
Entrusting such an important event
to us all at once
shows the leaders' recognition and trust in us.
Yes.
Director Yang is actually very concerned
about the future development of China Business Wave.
He has even
arranged several private meetings with me about this matter.
And this time,
he has entrusted our new media department
to undertake this task.
It's obvious that
he is also supporting us.
And our new media department is just
right for this task, as it meets the conference's demand
for a combination of online and offline formats.
Director Yang has repeatedly emphasized
that we
must take the lead in blazing a new trail.
Then go ahead and do it boldly.
The group will fully support you if you encounter any problems.
Alright.
I feel reassured with your words.
Well, there is actually a practical issue.
Go on.
I need to form
an organizing committee with leaders
from the Municipal Finance Bureau
and Finance Office in the early stage.
They will also come to our place for meetings.
So I wanted to discuss with you.
Do you think it would be appropriate
to use that unfinished office space
in the suburbs to receive them?
This does seem to be a problem.
Linhui,
it's not that the group doesn't support your work.
Your department is newly established,
and everything is in the startup phase.
Many things
have no precedent
in the group's history.
We'll have to explore and solve
these issues one by one.
During this process,
there will inevitably be some oversights.
I hope you can understand.
I understand, Mr. Gao. I really do.
I will try my best not to cause trouble
for the group.
But I feel that this time,
this matter
not only concerns China Business Wave,
but also has a significant impact
on the image of our entire Wenshang Group.
It's a very meaningful endeavor.
Also, I've heard that
the Puhang Media Group
is now actively trying to secure
the right to be the host.
They've been to Director Yang's office several times,
trying to smooth things over.
Personally, I think
at this stage,
we haven't signed and finalized
anything on paper, right?
In this situation, others might have
a chance to secure it,
so we're facing some risk.
If we can make everything
perfect at this point,
and let the leaders feel reassured
with no doubts,
don't you think our chances
of winning will be greater?
Alright,
you go all out
to push this matter forward.
As for the office issue,
I will coordinate.
You don't know,
after you left,
this office has been so quiet.
Now going to work is even boring.
How are you all doing?
We're doing pretty well.
Mr. Wang Chunlai has come to help us.
Really?
I'm so envious of you guys.
Here.
Thank you.
Thanks to Mr. Wang's help lately.
He's been running around with Hui everywhere.
After all, he's very experienced.
With him in charge, things are stable.
So, you'll need to hire more people, right?
I'm not sure.
The group is being strict with quotas, isn't it?
I heard you've hired someone new.
We hired a newcomer,
just graduated from college.
You know, someone with connections.
She's sitting in your old spot.
[Puhang Courier, China Business Wave Front Desk, Sign for Receipt]
So cute.
How about the ability?
Well, how should I put it...
She's now Lv Jian's assistant.
Anyway, she's not as diligent and capable as you were.
The girl is quite lovely though.
Just a bit pampered.
She's young, hasn't experienced hardship.
I heard she's quite pretty too.
What are you implying?
I'm just gossiping.
So gossipy of you.
But it's hard to say, really.
These two are getting quite close now.
Boss,
long time no see.
Jingjing,
you didn't even let me know you were coming today.
Chief Editor Xie sent me to get some materials.
Did you get them?
Yes, I did.
Chief Editor Lv,
you forgot your scarf.
Did you have lunch together?
No.
We were just talking about work.
It's work hours,
everyone get back to work.
Anna,
finish up what you didn't complete
this morning.
Okay.
Liu Yan,
get the minutes from the last meeting sorted out.
and follow up with the advertising clients.
Got it.
I'm leaving first.
Jingjing.
You should have told me
you were coming to the office.
I told you.
Xie Linhui sent me to pick up some materials urgently.
I can't report everything to you, can I?
Besides,
you've been on a business trip for two days and didn't answer your phone.
I had to come and check
if something happened to you.
What could have happened to me?
I was just on a two-day business trip
and in meetings every day.
I didn't have time to keep answering calls.
So busy that you couldn't even hear the phone?
I put my phone on silent during meetings,
and forgot to turn the sound back on after.
But you don't seem like
such a careless person.
Tell me honestly,
did you do
something wrong to me?
We're in the office. What are you doing?
People can see us.
Our colleagues are all around.
Feeling guilty, huh?
What do I have to feel guilty about?
If you keep making a scene like this,
I'm really going to get upset.
Chief Editor Lv.
Chief—
Are you discussing something?
Should I come back later?
It's fine, Anna.
Jingjing is here to pick up some materials.
I haven't seen her in a while,
so we're just chatting a bit.
So you're Jingjing?
I've heard Chief Editor Lv mention you before.
Glad to finally meet you in person.
What did he say about me?
He said you're exceptionally talented
and that I should learn from you.
I'm flattered.
Your name is?
Anna.
It's a beautiful name.
And you're pretty too.
Boss, you have good taste in choosing assistants.
Jingjing,
the agency is very busy today.
We have a lot of tasks.
You should quickly deliver those materials to Linhui.
Alright.
I won't hold you up any longer.
I'll be going now, Boss.
Jingjing, let me walk you out.
No need.
Anna.
Chief Editor Lv
is an excellent mentor.
You should definitely learn from him.
Okay,
I will.
I'm leaving.
Bye bye, Jingjing.
Jingjing,
we have a new office location.
Let's try a little harder
and sift through these people.
See if there's anyone we can use.
This one could be useful.
But we rarely keep in touch.
Look at this one.
I remember the last time I contacted him was half a year ago.
Do you remember this one?
Who?
Sun Jiajia.
Okay.
I've just...
taken a look,
and it seems that
only these three people can be of use to us.
It's really too bad that money is scarce when we need it.
I don't think we can blame them.
After all, they are professional investors.
If you were them,
how would you view our fund?
First, it's very new.
Second, we don't have any very successful cases.
If it were you,
you wouldn't invest in us either,
right?
So what should we do?
Maybe...
we need to
change our direction
and approach.
What should we change to?
Look at you,
can you use your brain?
Think.
So you're saying
we should look for high-net-worth individuals in China.
Rich people, right?
They're troublesome too.
They keep asking
when will the materials be submitted,
and when can we go public.
They're not interested in
the business model or field.
They don't even plan to understand it at all.
That's true.
What they're after now is that
100-meter dash feeling.
They can't wait
to invest this year,
go public next year,
and then cash out.
They want it to be faster than a child birth.
How about
those projects I showed you before?
Could you reconsider them?
Those won't work.
Those are all projects riding the hype,
not presentable.
Those are the hottest projects in the industry right now.
Whether they're hot or not,
you can't present them.
So according to you,
we should look for large wealth funds.
But these wealth funds won't even consider
a small, startup fund like ours.
If they throw that money into the stock market,
one daily limit up is 10%.
What about us?
An 8% annual return.
If it were me, I wouldn't invest either.
I...
So,
let's think carefully
about where we can actually get money.
Still thinking?
By the time we figure it out, it'll be too late.
This market trend is so hot right now.
If we miss this opportunity, will there be another one?
Don't I know that?
Of course I do.
What's the use of being anxious?
We need to put our heads together and think.
Di,
I just thought of someone.
Really?
Who?
Wu Yueting.
Wu?
Let me tell you...
Listen to me first.
Don't be hasty.
I've contacted him.
You've talked to Wu about our fund?
Did you discuss it with me?
No, I did it for the sake of the fund.
You know, besides Coroman,
he's invested in another company
called Herong Wealth.
What does it have to do with me?
I don't know,
nor do I want to know.
Mike Cheng,
let me make this clear.
Listen,
our fund has nothing to do with Wu Yueting.
The trend of a bullish market is certain.
There's so much positive news.
Registration system,
state-owned limited partners,
and lifting of foreign exchange restrictions.
I even want to throw all my money
into the stock market.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
given to us by the times.
You can't go against the times, can you?
I'm not going against the times.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I know Wu better than you do.
You...
I don't agree going to Wu Yueting.
Can you stop disagreeing with me?
I'm not disagreeing with you.
I'm just saying my opinion.
So, in your opinion,
you have the final say, huh?
We agreed at the beginning that this was a partnership,
but I don't have any say at all.
Then let's not do it anymore.
Di,
I was wrong.
I apologize.
But I'm just looking out for the fund, too.
Mike,
there are two points.
First,
about Wu,
I know him better than you do.
Please trust my judgment on this.
Second,
I think even if it's impulsive,
you have a point.
It might...
be hasty for us to start
this fund together.
Let's pause for a moment
and take it slow.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not saying this out of anger.
I'm not angry.
It's because I feel that
it seems like our
ways of thinking,
including our ideas,
are quite different.
Oh, I see someone I know. Bye.
Miss Jiang.
Auntie Zhang.
You're off work early today.
Have you been busy lately, Miss Jiang?
Not so busy.
It's been a while.
You look well.
Much better than before.
It's important to get enough rest.
Yes.
I was just looking for you.
Go ahead.
Well, here's the thing.
As you know,
the rent has gone up again this year.
For the other tenants,
since last year,
I've raised the rent by 2,000 each year.
I haven't mentioned it to you because we've known each other for so long.
Auntie Zhang, how about this?
Increase my rent by 2,000 too.
I knew it.
You're such a straightforward person.
As expected of someone in finance.
You're of a different level.
Not at all.
Let's start next month.
Later,
I'll sign a new lease agreement with you.
Alright.
[God-level Operation in Investment Circle: Jade Oak Capital's New Partner's Initial Success]
[Puhang Financial Network]
Yu Shi was able to preserve the investment
before Huake Vision collapsed.
It's truly the work of a capital master.
Shine Oriental Group can only accept
the loss this time.
Zhang Hongda's fall in this hot capital market once again
proves the cruelty of the capital market.
[Puhang Financial Network]
What is he trying to prove by sending these?
It's just to let me know
what kind of person he is.
Ignoring all the insignificant people.
Ignoring everyone and everything
in the capital interest chain.
[Resignation: Jiang Yidi]
[Resignation letter]
Impulsiveness is the devil.
Everyone's roles are clear now, right?
I have another news to share with you.
It's that...
starting from next Monday,
we'll all be working from 9 to 5.
Chief Editor,
our new office has been renovated?
That's so fast.
We won't be using that place anymore.
We have a new office location.
Where are we going then?
It's still a secret for now.
Jingjing.
Secret.
Let's see if anyone wants to treat us to dinner tonight.
Then I'll tell you the news.
I'll treat, I'll treat!
Mr. Wang is treating us!
That's great!
Sounds good!
What are you treating us to, Mr. Wang?
We should have...
Duck soup.
Okay!
Alright, alright.
Pack up and let's go!
Let's go.
Jingjing,
will we have a new chief editor from now on?
How could that be?
You're with Lv Jian.
Didn't he tell you?
Our agency has two chief editors.
Chief Editor Lv is in charge of magazine operations,
[Uphold Integrity and Prosperity Follows]
while Chief Editor Xie is responsible for new media operations.
Then why has this office
become Chief Editor Xie's office?
Have you...
heard of the cuckoo in the magpie's nest?
You mean
Chief Editor Xie took over Chief Editor Lv's office?
Anna,
you joined the agency late.
There's a lot of history you need to know.
[Uphold Integrity and Prosperity Follows]
Jingjing,
you've been with the agency for a long time.
What do you think
of Chief Editor Lv?
What do you think?
I think he's quite friendly
and very patient too.
When I first joined, I didn't know anything,
but he kept teaching me step by step.
But it seems like other people
don't really get close to him.
Is that so?
However,
Chief Editor Lv said
because he comes from a humble background
without any family connections,
everyone thinks he's trying too hard
and took someone else's position.
But he also told me that
the more so,
the harder he must work to achieve something.
Jingjing,
why are people so snobbish?
Judging him by his family background
instead of personal ability.
Don't you think it's unfair?
Why are you laughing?
I just find
this familiar.
I've heard these words before.
But hearing it from you today makes me feel...
Feel what?
Nothing.
As for this project,
I know
we need to push it forward.
President Li.
Uncle Li.
I heard Jingjing's voice from far away.
It feels like our magazine agency
has become lively again.
Yes.
That's great.
Now
the new media department and the magazine editorial department are working together,
which makes communication much more convenient.
This is the situation Mr. Gao and I hope to see.
Everyone, work hard.
Keep it up.
We'll do our best.
When Mr. Gao called to inform us,
I had all the offices cleared out.
The workstations outside have also been rearranged.
We'll make further adjustments when the new colleagues arrive.
Anna,
you've been working for a while now.
Are you getting used to it?
Yes.
Uncle Li.
Good,
that's good.
Alright,
I won't disturb you.
Please, go ahead.
This office is not only small,
but the orientation isn't great either.
It's fine, President Li.
I can work anywhere. It doesn't matter.
Lv,
sorry about this.
Given the current situation,
you'll just have to bear with it for now.
Don't worry,
I don't mind these things.
That's good.
Mr. Gao is still aiming for a promotion,
so he's particularly focused on this investment conference
to build up his credentials.
This opportunity now
has been seized by Xie Linhui.
It's okay.
You just actively cooperate with her.
As long as there are no mistakes,
there will be more opportunities.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Yes, I didn't want to be like Lv Jian at first.
I wanted to see how long he could keep it up.
But he's always there,
pulling these little tricks.
It's really annoying.
Such a petty person.
Don't stoop to his level.
You're quite well-informed, aren't you?
Who am I?
What's going on with Zhou Hang?
What happened to Zhou Hang?
Rumor has it that Zhou Hang
is leaving Yuanshen Dongfang Technology Company.
Is that true?
How could that be possible?
But he was indeed
affected by the Huake Vision incident this time.
But
it's not a big deal, is it?
How did rumors of resignation spread outside?
After all,
with such a large investment,
cooperating with an internal investigation is quite normal.
Yuanshen Dongfang is a listed company.
Any changes in senior management
must be reported to the public.
How could it be so casual?
[Hang up]
[Ms. Miao]
I have first-hand information.
It is said that Liang Wensen is
kicking Zhou Hang out.
Headhunters are on a hiring spree these days
for the position
of Yuanshen Dongfang Technology Company's president.
You really don't know about this?
You'd better remind Zhou.
It should...
all be rumors, right?
There's no smoke without fire.
I'll talk to Zhou later
and ask him about the situation.
Thanks for the heads up.
You're welcome.
Alright.
See you then
at the venture capital conference.
See you.
Bye.
The news about the Nanping land auction is out.
Coroman won the bid.
The president is very angry now.
Peng Dahai has
secretly returned to Puhang yesterday.
Our people are keeping an eye on him.
He didn't meet with Wu Yueting.
Their communication must be very secretive.
Afraid of being caught, I guess.
Also,
there's progress in Chengdu.
Several distributors who cooperated with Peng Dahai
have finally spoken up.
Is there concrete evidence?
They have videos
and transfer records.
That's great.
What about the president?
There are some movements too.
I heard that
the company is secretly contacting
several big headhunters.
It is said that the position is...
President of Yuanshen Dongfang Technology Company.
Yes.