[The Storm of Roses]
[Episode 26]
[What on earth happened?]
[Hongda, there's nothing that can't be overcome in this world]
[Huake Vision's warehouse caught fire]
Okay, got it.
Firefighters are putting out the fire there.
Everyone is saying
the fire was deliberately set.
Bo, how much longer until we arrive?
Over 20 minutes.
Has the president landed?
Soon, I guess.
I heard the flight took off an hour ago.
If we leave for the airport now, we should still make it in time.
Go investigate
when Huake Vision was reported,
which media outlet reported it first,
when they found it out,
and
when the warehouse was on fire.
I'll go now.
Where is
Peng Dahai?
He's already at the airport.
He must have known
something happened to Huake Vision
and informed the president immediately.
I'm leaving, Mr. Zhou.
Wait.
When you go there later,
there might be a lot of reporters.
Be cautious with your words and actions.
Everything you do represents only yourself,
not the company.
Aren't you going?
It's not proper.
Excuse me!
Please let me through!
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Please make way.
What are you doing?
You can't enter! Please cooperate!
We are currently
at the site of the fire at Huake Vision.
As you can see, firefighters have taken action
to put out the fire.
And the fire is now fully under control.
The cause of the fire is still unknown.
We will continue to follow up with further updates.
Huake Vision...
Jiang Yidi!
Excuse me. Please let me through.
Why are you here?
I came as soon as I got the news.
What's the situation now?
The fire has been put out,
and there are no visible casualties.
But the damage seems substantial.
Where are the people from Huake Vision?
The inventory keeper, the warehouse manager,
and the vice president are on their way.
I still can't reach Zhang Hongda.
Have you gotten in touch with your mentor?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Hello.
From now on, there might be a lot
of people contacting you.
Do not respond to any calls, messages, or WeChat.
When you arrive at the company tomorrow, come to me immediately.
Are we just going to ignore it?
This is my plan.
What's going on?
Is everything okay?
Yes.
They said
such a large fire doesn't look like an accident.
Also, I heard a rumor that Zhang Hongda
has been involved in smuggling components.
It's very possible that this fire
was caused by people from Huake Vision.
Firefighters, medical teams, and other rescue personnel
have rushed to the scene
to address the casualties and damage caused by the fire.
Alright, stop shoving.
The reporters have reached out to the factory where the fire occurred,
but the staff stated they're not sure about the details yet.
An official statement will be issued later.
The cause of the fire,
along with any casualties
and financial losses, is still uncertain.
The possibility of arson can't be ruled out.
I'm going to find my mentor!
Help me keep an eye on things here for a while!
But where are you going to find him?
It's not your concern!
[News Broadcast]
About 15 minutes later,
the fire broke out.
Upon investigation...
Who do you think told the media?
What's the purpose?
Let's talk tomorrow.
Hang up.
There are still embers that haven't been fully extinguished.
As we can see,
thick smoke continues to pour out of the warehouse.
What a pity
for Huake Vision.
From now on,
I don't want to hear your voice anymore.
Mr. Zhou.
The president has landed.
Hello, President.
You've landed?
I'm at the company.
I've been waiting for you.
There's an emergency.
I'll report to you when we meet.
Okay.
Should we inform Dongning and the others?
No.
It's too late.
Let them rest.
Because...
they've been involved with the contract from the start after all.
If the president asks about it later...
It's fine.
Okay.
By the way,
you haven't had a break in a while, have you?
Do you still have any annual leave left?
Annual leave?
I... I have never taken any annual leave.
Consider taking a short break
and think about where to go.
Mr. Zhou.
Why, Mr. Zhou?
Take a break.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Okay, Mrs. Zhang, don't worry.
I'm on my way to the old office.
I'll be there soon.
If I have any updates,
I'll tell you right away.
Let's stay in touch.
Okay. Let me know if you have
any updates. Let's stay in sync.
Okay.
Okay, bye bye.
Bye bye.
Here.
This building.
A friend of mine used to work here.
I visited his office,
and it was really nice.
They just moved out.
The renovation is not old.
You can make do with it.
No need to renovate it again.
The best part is the rent is affordable.
Don't mind the surroundings.
It may be a little further out,
but its feng shui is good.
Many companies here
are thriving.
There's even a listed company here.
Okay.
This is where my dream begins.
Do you remember that land?
The old factory site.
The road was always packed with trucks heading into the city.
I took this road every day when I went to work.
It was
all dust and dirt.
I really couldn't stand it.
But look at it now.
It's all been demolished
for a commercial center.
The whole area is developing.
Can you feel the change?
In the past, we defined stages
of development by different eras.
But now,
good God,
changes are happening constantly.
China
is developing at an unprecedented speed.
I think this is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
So I...
I'm not willing to be a bystander,
a witness, or a reporter.
I want to be part of it.
But what if you fail?
You haven't thought about it?
If we think about failure
before we even start,
no one can succeed.
In life, how many chances
do we get to take a shot?
Right now,
the chance is right in front of me.
I must seize it.
You're an idealist.
So ideals won't die.
Hongda!
Don't come here.
Hongda.
Hongda,
c-come down first.
Calm down.
Let's talk, okay?
Hongda, calm down.
Come down and let's talk.
Hongda.
Hongda! Hongda!
Hongda!
The money is still there.
With the money, Huake Vision will be fine.
Hongda.
Come down first.
We will help you.
Hongda,
we still have a chance.
Hongda.
Come down first.
We will help you.
Hongda!
Hongda! We will help you!
President.
Have a seat.
Zhou Hang,
I have a file here.
Take a look first.
[Fengshi Hong Kong Import and Export Customs]
Huake Vision is suspected of using smuggled components.
This is a serious issue.
Before we made the investment,
[Yuanshen Dongfang]
how did Yuanshen Dongfang Technology Company
handle the due diligence and risk control?
Also,
from what I know,
the agreement we signed with Huake Vision
isn't a standard equity investment agreement.
It's actually
a convertible bond agreement.
Mr. Zhou,
this is completely different from the usual
investment approval process.
It's indeed different.
Back then, for operational convenience...
You don't need to explain.
[Yuanshen Dongfang]
Of course I believe you had your reasons.
But this is against the rules.
I don't care what your reasoning was,
Zhou Hang.
The company's system
is designed to mitigate risks.
You've violated the rules.
The project didn't pass IC.
You approved 100 million yuan for Huake Vision
using Yuanshen Dongfang Technology Company's authority,
circumventing IC.
You want to play hide-and-seek with the group?
Mr. Kang,
special matters require special measures.
There are precedents within the group.
Special matters require special measures?
[Yuanshen Dongfang]
Has what Zhou Hang did
been reported to the group?
One hundred million yuan
was transferred just like that.
Who's going to take responsibility for the loss?
Mr. Kang.
Loss?
Well...
isn't it a bit too early to talk about that?
Chen.
What I'm worried about
is not just the 100 million yuan,
but also Yuanshen Dongfang's image in the industry
and the stock price of Yuanshen Dongfang Technology Company tomorrow morning.
Alright.
Stop arguing.
First,
I take responsibility for this.
The decision to invest in Huake Vision
was made by me.
[Yuanshen Dongfang]
You can't say that, President.
You set the overall direction,
and there was no issue with the direction.
Yeah.
You decided to invest in Huake Vision,
to be blunt,
because
Yuanshen Dongfang Technology Company's performance was poor
and it was dragging down the entire group.
You hoped this investment would boost
market confidence
in Yuanshen Dongfang Technology Company.
You hoped it could
help the subsidiary
and help him.
We all know that.
Your original intention was right.
It's just they messed it up themselves.
It doesn't matter what happened back then.
What matters is what happens next.
Zhou Hang,
is it possible to get the money back?
The money can be recovered.
I've sent someone to contact Zhang Hongda.
I'll inform the company as soon as there's any update.
Then tell me.
Regarding
Huake Vision's use of smuggled components,
did someone frame it
or is it true?
It still needs
to be verified.
Verified?
Why wasn't this done sooner?
The most important thing now is
what we should do if Huake Vision really collapses.
Who will take responsibility for this?
How should we explain to the board?
Let's put aside the issue of responsibility for now.
Figure out a solution first.
I'll take responsibility.
If Huake Vision's incident
causes irreversible damage to the company,
I will take full responsibility.
I, Zhou Hang,
will resign.
President,
there's an emergency.
Zhang Hongda committed suicide.
Dad,
Uncle Zhou promised
to take responsibility so easily.
Is he a little...
Why are you sleeping on the sofa again?
Look at the dypsis lutescens.
It was fine a few days ago.
How did it suddenly become like this?
I once worked on a topic.
In all the fundamental research,
biomedicine has received the most support.
Given the human race's obsession
with longevity,
why would someone
give up his life so easily?
I was right there when he jumped.
I watched him jump with my own eyes.
But...
it doesn't make sense.
Hongda was a strong and optimistic person.
Why would he do that?
When I gave my statement
at the police station,
the police told me
he had been on medication for depression.
We were good friends, but he never told me.
Why didn't I notice it?
Why didn't I...
notice anything?
It shouldn't have happened.
If I had talked
to him in the end
and if he cried in front of me,
maybe none of this would have happened.
Maybe it wouldn't have ended like this.
Linhui,
when someone has depression
and wants to commit suicide,
even if you stop him today,
he might make the same decision tomorrow.
It's not your fault.
There must be something we don't know.
There must be.
Something must have forced him to do that.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have done that.
He wouldn't have.
All right.
Let's change the subject, okay?
I need to get to the bottom of it.
A man died.
It can't just end like this.
Yes.
Someone will get to the bottom of it.
You're pregnant now.
You need to rest well
and quietly.
You can't get emotional, okay?
Now, let me take you to your bed
and get some good sleep.
Okay?
My belly hurts.
How are you feeling?
Come on.
Get up.
I'll take you to the hospital.
[Police]
[Jiannan District Branch of Puhang Public Security Bureau
Wenxin Police Station]
Arson?
It... It was Zhang Hongda?
We checked the surveillance videos.
So far, this is the information we have.
We still need to wait for further investigation results.
You were close to the victim.
And you were at the scene.
We may still need your cooperation
for further investigation.
Hello, Xiaomo.
Yidi, are you okay?
Boss said we need to be at the company by 9 a.m.
Okay, got it.
I'll be right back.
Hello.
We've arrived.
Are you Jiang Yidi from Jade Oak Capital?
Miss Jiang.
I want to ask...
if you know about
the future development.
Could you please answer the question?
-Miss Jiang!
Miss Jiang, could you please answer the question?
Was it arson?
Can you tell us the reason?
-Miss Jiang!
They still allow her to come to work after what happened.
She's so unlucky.
You know what?
Zhang Hongda jumped off the building.
And it's all over the news
that Zhang Hongda was suspected of smuggling.
Are you okay?
Come with me.
Boss,
I already went to the police station
and gave my statement.
Has anyone called you...
since yesterday?
Has anyone contacted you?
Has anyone from Yuanshen Dongfang called you?
No.
But I can call them.
No need.
Mr. Yu, I think there's still a way
to save Huake Vision.
There are a few things I want to tell you.
First,
Jade Oak Capital
is no longer a shareholder of Huake Vision.
Earlier,
I asked Zhang Hongda
to buy back all the shares we held.
We've got the principal back.
The returns are decent.
Second,
I'm no longer a director of Huake Vision.
Third,
from now on, Huake Vision
has nothing to do with us anymore.
So remember,
from now on,
you should remain silent.
I
won't help Huake Vision.
Understand?
No.
Why?
You don't need
to know everything.
You might think the equity market is hot right now,
but it's very likely that within a year,
it will cool down really fast.
What should we do?
Do you know dominoes?
When one company falls,
others will follow.
So we
need to get our returns back
before the winter comes.
The second thing is to
hand over all the documents
related to Huake Vision
to Tang Ruo.
Why?
It won't affect your performance.
I'm... I'm not talking about performance.
You know I don't care about performance.
I don't have a reason.
This is my decision. I...
If the interests of Jade Oak Capital
and Huake Vision conflict one day,
which side would you choose?
Zhang Hongda told me
besides him,
no one knows Huake Vision better than you.
I'm here to tell you something important.
The money from Yuanshen Dongfang hasn't been transferred,
but your mentor is in urgent need of money.
So...
Huake Vision operates
under a VIE structure.
It's a bit complicated.
Let's sign a loan agreement with them,
-and...
-Yes.
I think the same way.
So I want to discuss with you.
We need Yuanshen Dongfang's cooperation.
Only the names of Yuanshen Dongfang
and Huake Vision can appear on it.
Jade Oak Capital is not important.
No need to appear on it
or steal the limelight.
So...
So this is all...
your scheme?
You never intended
to help Huake Vision from the beginning.
You asked Yuanshen Dongfang
to transfer the money to Huake Vision as soon as possible
just to extract our funds in Huake Vision
in the shortest time.
Then...
Then Huake Vision's capital chain broke.
Then my mentor...
The Huake Vision project
has been under your supervision from start to finish.
You should know better than anyone
it has huge operational problems.
It came dangerously close to wiping out
all our investments over the years.
You are the investment manager
and the person in charge of this project.
You are an employee of Jade Oak Capital.
Can you think
from Jade Oak Capital's standpoint?
Can you?
What operational problems?
Come.
Look carefully.
[Huake Vision Stock Management Form]
If you tell me you really
didn't know anything about it,
it means you are guilty of negligence.
But if you knew,
you're guilty of collusion.
[Test Report]
Do you understand now?
Yu Shi.
You knew this long ago, right?
Then why are you only asking me now?
Answer me.
Why are you only asking me now?
What gives you the right to ask me now?
Why?
Have you ever trusted me?
Who are you to ask me?
We'll talk after you calm down.
No need.
I don't need to calm down.
We don't need to talk either.
We are different.
What's there to talk about?
Right?
Maybe in your...
Maybe in Mr. Yu's eyes,
a life is nothing.
It's not important
compared to your
meticulous plan.
But it's different for me.
I'm not as good as you.
What's there to talk about?
Hello?
Hello.
Are you Jiang Yidi?
I'm a reporter from Financial Weekly.
I want to ask...
You are here.
I've been looking for you.
What's up?
Yuanshen Dongfang called.
They want us to go and talk about Huake Vision.
Okay.
I'll call them back later.
No.
Eason wants
to handle this matter himself.
He wants you to stay out of it.
Okay, got it.
Anything else?
Well,
I've always been curious.
Why did you enter the venture capital field?
Then why did you?
Because in this industry,
only the truly strong can succeed.
Those who are weak, overly empathetic,
or constrained by moral scruples
simply don't belong in this industry.
You think you're strong?
I asked to speak with you privately
because I hope you can help calm her emotions.
[Save Electricity]
The child couldn't be saved.
During the first three months of pregnancy,
miscarriages are quite common.
I repeatedly cautioned her about this before.
Her current condition seems to be caused by excessive fatigue
and emotional stress.
But don't worry.
With proper rest and care,
her body should recover without any major issues.
Then...
I see.
[Save Electricity]
Thank you.
Make sure she gets plenty of nourishment when you go back.
[Doctor's Office 1]
[Diagram of the Stages of Pregnancy]
How are you feeling?
Are you feeling better?
Can we leave now?
What did the doctor say?
The doctor said
you should take a good rest
and you'll recover soon.
-Let's go.
-Really?
Yes, that's what she said.
Let's go.
I want to go in and ask Yao Lan.
I want her to explain it to me directly
so that I can understand better.
She already told me everything.
I'll... I'll tell you when we get home.
Let her explain to me,
and I can understand better, right?
The next patient has already gone in.
-You'll disrupt her work.
-It's fine.
I'll tell her I'll be waiting outside.
Linhui,
I'll tell you after we get home, okay?
We lost our baby, right?
Let's go home first.
Go home first.
[Diagram of the Stages of Pregnancy]
Let's go home.
Go home.
Have some brown sugar water.
You can drink it now.
Don't tell Mom and the others.
Of course.
I understand.
Don't think too much.
Have a good rest.
You should go to work.
I have something to address at the company,
but I can choose not to go.
Go.
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
Go.
I want to be alone.
Okay.
I'll be back early.
The Huake Vision project
has been under your supervision from start to finish.
You should know better than anyone
it has huge operational problems.
It came dangerously close to wiping out
all our investments over the years.
You are the investment manager
and the person in charge of this project.
You are an employee of Jade Oak Capital.
Because in this industry,
only the truly strong can succeed.
Those who are weak, overly empathetic,
or constrained by moral scruples
simply don't belong in this industry.