[The Storm of Roses]
[Episode 22]
Yes.
I look forward to
our future cooperation.
Yidi.
Excuse me.
It's okay.
Why pretend you didn't see me?
I didn't want to interrupt your conversation, Boss.
I do mind that you pretend you didn't see me.
Why are you here?
Li Weiqing invited me.
He gave me an invitation.
Well done.
Of course.
But I feel I must tell you,
he seems to have invited Tang Ruo as well.
I see.
You brought Tang Ruo here?
He brought me.
-Thanks.
-Eason.
Cheers.
I made a bet with Mr. Yu.
A bet? What bet?
Bet who will win between you and Tang Ruo.
Win what?
Li Weiqing?
How old are you guys?
Making such a boring bet.
Who did he bet on?
It doesn't matter.
Anyway, I'm relying on you to win back
my ten yuan.
Good luck, Jiang Yidi.
Mr. Li.
Hello.
Long time no see.
Mr. Zhou,
let's have a drink together.
Who are you looking down on?
I'll go say hello inside.
-Excuse me.
-Okay.
I'll go with you.
No need. You talk to Mr. Ma first.
I'll join you later.
Alright.
Dalin.
Linhui.
-Hello, Mr. Huo.
-Chief Editor Xie.
Long time no see.
Yes, yes, yes.
You look great.
Okay..
You two talk.
-Okay.
See you later, Mr. Huo.
Okay.
Where's Xiaohe?
She didn't come.
She has to accompany the child to piano lessons
and can't get away.
It's really not easy for Xiaohe being a mother.
So with Mao Xiaohe and Xue Lai as examples,
I have to be more cautious about having a child.
Especially Mao Xiaohe,
she has no freedom at all.
She devotes herself entirely to you and the child.
I heard from Xiaohe
that you're interested in the Chengjian Group project.
I've heard that they're having some issues with
their partner law firm and they want to change it.
I'm considering discussing and trying to compete for it.
But you know,
they usually work with big law firms.
So I'm afraid it might be difficult.
I'm quite familiar with Mr. Chen's wife.
I forget what occasion it was,
and Xiaohe was there too.
I introduced them to each other.
They got along well, seemed to have a good connection.
How about this?
I'll see when the timing is right,
and arrange a gathering.
Then I'll invite
Mr. Chen's wife and Xiaohe.
This way,
we can chat like friends.
Isn't that natural?
Then, I'll ask Xiaohe
to subtly bring up the matter for you.
Wouldn't that be nice?
That's great.
Linhui,
I must thank you properly.
More than that,
you're treating me to a year's meals.
Right.
Xiaohe is lucky to have such a good friend like you.
Fu Dalin,
you're the lucky one to have a wife like Mao Xiaohe.
You should be grateful.
Yes, yes, you're right.
Well, how about this?
Let's set a time next week,
and I'll invite you
to our company to discuss.
What do you think?
Okay.
Alright.
Cheers.
Isn't that Li Weiqing?
Ms. Jiang,
weren't you just looking for him?
Yes, I'll have to excuse myself now.
Okay, okay.
See you next week.
-Okay.
-Okay
Yidi.
Tang Ruo.
I heard we're competing again.
I heard so.
Impressive.
You managed to get an invitation here.
I guess I need to work harder.
Same here.
Yidi.
This is Mr. Xu from Smart Partner Company.
Haven't you been following
the field of enterprise services?
Why don't you chat with him?
Okay?
You two talk. I need to attend to something.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
I'm Jiang Yidi.
Hello, Ms. Jiang.
Here's the thing,
our Smart Partner Company
mainly creates cross-platform,
closed-loop efficiency solutions for
enterprise users.
Next month, we'll be launching an upgraded version.
In this version, we've integrated
our real-time communication tool,
Smart Chat.
Next, we'll put
all the necessary needs
in the team collaboration process,
like file sharing, real-time communication,
and task management,
all into the same application.
Mr. Xu, how about this?
If you have time,
I'll visit your company next week.
Sure.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
Okay.
Alright.
Here, let me scan your code.
Okay.
See you later.
I'll leave you now.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
Follow me.
Linhui.
Don't worry about it.
Here.
You'll get this dirty.
Take a look.
Better safe than sorry.
Thank you, Linhui.
Let's go.
Let's head out.
How's Tunisia? Beautiful, isn't it?
Ms. Shen.
Linhui.
Linhui's here.
Ms. Shen, thank you for inviting me.
-I'm glad you came.
-Ms. Shen.
Mr. Gao.
What a coincidence, you're here too.
Linhui is also an honored guest I invited.
Lv Jian, long time no see.
What a coincidence.
You look good.
Mr. Gao,
this is...
This is Lv Jian.
-Hello, Ms. Shen.
-He's
the acting chief editor of China Business Wave.
Welcome.
Ms. Shen.
I'll leave you.
Alright.
Mr. Gao, do you know Ms. Miao?
Mr. Gao Tian from our group.
Ms. Miao is a good friend of mine,
from Hengdu Electronics.
-We've met.
-We've met before.
We've had dinner together.
I heard Mr. Zhou Hang is here too.
Yes. He's speaking at the forum today.
No idea where he's off to prepare.
Linhui.
I might need your help.
Go ahead.
They're having some problems at work.
The host of the forum
can't get here in time.
So now I need someone
who can control the stage
and has the flexibility
and knowledge to save the day.
That's me.
You're talking about me.
I think the same way.
But the forum is about to start.
Can you make it?
No problem.
Mr. Gao knows me well.
We've worked together for years.
I'm best at unprepared wars.
That's great. I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me.
Higher standards
have been set
for the industry,
entrepreneurs, and early investors.
I remember when Secretary Xia
received the performance report,
he once told me,
[Gathering Wisdom, Winning the Future]
"You haven't let your alma mater down."
But we all know that without the government's
support and assistance for our industry,
we wouldn't be where we are today.
Thank you, thank you to the government.
That's right.
The government's support
[Gathering Wisdom, Winning the Future]
is not only the foundation of our development,
but also better protects and guides us.
Now, I'd like to
ask Mr. Zhou a question.
Many of those here today are old friends,
acquaintances.
But indeed, someone is not just an acquaintance.
So we can't let him off easy today.
So I'd like to ask Mr. Zhou,
for large enterprise groups
like Yuanshen Dongfang Group
[Gathering Wisdom, Winning the Future]
you're in,
you are now
launching aggressive acquisitions.
We'd like Mr. Zhou to share with us
what your
strategic plan behind this is?
Industrial upgrading is driven
by market consumption and users.
Under this overarching policy,
Yuanshen Dongfang
[Gathering Wisdom, Winning the Future]
utilizes strategic investments and acquisitions
to empower the real economy and industrial upgrading,
thereby generating
explosive synergistic growth effects
and bringing long-term strategic value
to the company.
That's it.
[Gathering Wisdom, Winning the Future]
Mr. Zhou answered this question
very professionally.
Because he prepared for it at home.
I knew before coming that Mr. Zhou
would be speaking at this forum today.
So this is all insider information.
Now I'd like to ask Mr. Zhou another question
he's not prepared for.
Hello, Mr. Li.
I'm Jiang Yidi from Jade Oak Capital.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Because it's rare
to have such an opportunity to seek advice from Mr. Zhou.
[Gathering Wisdom, Winning the Future]
We don't usually
talk about work or business at home.
So, I'd like to ask you, Mr. Zhou,
how do you personally understand investment?
What do you think is the essence of investment?
A question I have to answer.
In my humble opinion...
There's a saying in the industry:
"Investment is about investing in people."
I've reviewed the latest proposal
you gave me.
To be honest,
I see your determination to strive for change,
but it didn't impress me.
However, look at Xie Linhui.
In just these few minutes on stage,
she has impressed me.
So it can't just be some...
This is a reflection of personal ability.
It carries the responsibility of serving the real economy
and serving the capital market...
All the current changes in China Business Wave,
all the reforms,
are to adapt to the development of the times.
On the other hand, it connects...
If you think she's more suitable,
I can find a way
to invite her back.
What's the point of that?
Isn't that just the same as before?
There's no change.
What we need in the future is a halo,
an iconic,
charismatic leader.
I also hope to see a brand new outlook for the magazine.
A new media under the internet mindset.
I've said from the beginning,
Puhang Venture Capital is not investing in a single publication,
but supporting reform and innovation in the media industry.
Sustainable deep integration...
To achieve human...
So what exactly do you mean?
And strive for it.
[Gathering Wisdom, Winning the Future]
Who can steer the future of China Business Wave?
It seems
some more tests are needed.
Hongda is an old friend of mine.
if he hadn't called me,
I wouldn't be interested in looking at two investment proposals
from one company.
The corner of my office
is filled with proposals
from your peers.
They all say more or less the same thing:
how to make money,
how to replicate the model,
how to paint a rosy picture,
and how to make the story more exciting.
You must think
it's all about the money, right?
I'm not as high-minded as you say.
When I started the Weiqing Book Club,
I wanted to monetize knowledge.
But if it was purely for making money,
I wouldn't have started this book club.
Does that sound a bit contradictory to you?
It's not contradictory.
It's not?
Wanting to make money
while not wanting to be labeled as a businessman.
If one can't make money,
it's hard to
keep doing something persistently.
I remember you once said
that China's achievements in humanities and social sciences
have profound significance
for the future and development of the country.
Therefore,
we need to vigorously promote and encourage
to get more people to read better books.
This is how we can prevent the bad driving out the good.
So that's why you added
that support program in the cooperation proposal.
Not entirely.
I believe that
whether you choose me
or our company to cooperate with,
this support program has its value.
I hope it can be implemented.
Actually, Mr. Li,
not everyone in investment is
so obsessed with money.
There are idealists too, you know.
Instead of using fancy words
to praise women's dedication,
it's better to genuinely
focus on their professionalism.
Thank you, Ms. Shen.
[Gathering Wisdom, Winning the Future]
I think, as the writer Bing Xin said,
if there were no women,
this world would lack half of its truth,
six-tenths of its kindness,
and seven-tenths of its beauty.
I'd like to add to that,
if there were no women in this world,
it would also lack half of its market.
I remember
when I first entered the industry,
my mentor told me something.
seemed to be a quote from some famous person,
that left a deep impression on me.
The quote goes,
"We are a group of people
who work extremely hard..."
Trying to determine which
small company we invest in
can become great.
Yes.
Do you think Weiqing Book Club
will become great?
I think...
To be honest, Mr. Li, I don't know.
But
I will definitely do my best
to make it successful.
I hope our efforts
can make it great.
Then I'm counting on you.
Alright, thank you for your trust.
I will work hard.
Looking forward to our cooperation.
Likewise.
There's something I must tell you.
Huake Vision
didn't pass Yuanshen Dongfang's IC.
There will be an official announcement on Monday.
There's one more thing,
I don't know if you're aware of this.
Go on.
[Customs Declaration]
[Huake Vision]
Is there no solution?
Of course there is.
On this project,
we must
have aligned goals
and aligned interests.
What does
Ms. Shen mean?
Do I still have a chance?
There's definitely a chance.
But I'm not quite sure at the moment.
Let's work on it together.
Alright.
Actually,
I've been following your wife for a long time.
I really admire her
confidence that radiates from within.
I also admire her achievements
in the financial field over the years.
Thank you.
Thank you for your appreciation of her.
I'll definitely pass it on to her.
I... I heard that
she has resigned from China Business Wave, right?
Yes.
Speaking of which,
it has something to do with
your Puhang Venture Capital's
investment in China Business Wave.
As for Gao Tian and his team,
the more they tried to compete,
the more mistakes they made.
I believe
they've lost the most valuable part
of China Business Wave.
Yes.
Could you do me a favor?
Please go ahead.
Could you pass on what I just said
to your wife?
There should be an opportunity for cooperation
between Puhang Venture Capital and her.
Certainly.
I'll definitely relay that to her
and see what she thinks.
But she's been telling me lately
that
she wants to slow down,
take a break,
and shift her focus
to family life.
I actually think
she's not the type of person who's willing to stop.
Yidi.
Yidi?
What's wrong with her?
She must be drunk.
Drunk?
Are you okay?
Yu Shi.
Are...
you okay?
Let me tell you, Yu Shi.
Listen carefully.
I won.
What do you mean?
I feel awful.
I feel terrible.
Mr. Yu,
what should we do now?
My head hurts.
Take her home.
Why don't I take her instead?
Do you know where she lives?
I actually don't know that.
Then how can you take her?
I'll go prepare the car.
My head hurts.
No, no, no. It's too restrictive for me.
You need to fasten this.
Fasten it, fasten it.
How much did you drink?
Let me tell you,
I won.
Didn't expect that?
I
won.
What did you win?
Why do you think she would win?
Why?
What are you talking about?
You're drunk.
No, no, no.
What's wrong?
Don't drive.
I'm going to throw up.
Then slow down.
Drive slowly.
Don't throw up.
No.
Drive slowly.
No, no, no.
-It's too restricted. I feel uncomfortable.
-What?
Uncomfortable.
No, you need to fasten this.
-It's too restricted.
-No.
-I don't want it.
-Well, you...
Here, the keys.
Can you handle it?
Yes, absolutely.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm okay, handsome.
Then I'm leaving.
Go ahead.
Don't touch me.
Do you hear me?
I'm a little bit tempted by you.
Yet I'm so afraid to look into your eyes.
A little bit tempted.
A little bit hesitant.
What I fear most is loving and then losing.
It's hard to resist.
What people fear most is falling in love.
You're drunk. Come on.
Although I don't look, don't think, and don't listen,
I'm still caught in love.
You and I,
man and woman,
can't escape
love.
Come on, you...
You...
Should we continue or not?
Should we hesitate or not?
Let love approach step by step.
I'm a little bit...
tempted by you.
Yet I'm so afraid to look into your eyes.
A little bit tempted.
A little bit hesitant.
What I fear most is loving and then losing.
It's hard to resist.
Yu Shi.
I'm a little bit tempted by you.
Yet I'm so afraid to look into your eyes.
A little bit tempted.
A little bit hesitant.
What I fear most is loving and then losing.
It's hard to resist.
-You and me.
-You're drunk.
Shut up.
Is it up to you to decide if I'm drunk?
Is it up to you to decide?
Who are you?
You and I,
man and woman...
I'm going home.
can't escape love.
Fish food.
Feed the fish.
Should we continue or not?
Should we hesitate or not?
Let love approach step by step.
I...
I'm...
really a little bit tempted by you.
I'm a little bit tempted by you!
What should I do?
I really didn't expect Shen Zongyu to say
that she's actually close to you.
Did she say that?
That she's close to me?
Yes.
But we're not actually that close.
Last time,
they...
Puhang Venture Capital held a women's salon.
Ms. Miao asked me to go.
I mean Miao Yanan.
Then they set up a venue
to gather all the female entrepreneurs they've invested in
for networking and communication.
I thought it was a good idea.
Then they wanted us to
pay attention and report on it.
So I went to check it out.
Then I ran into Shen Zongyu.
I did chat with her for a bit,
but we're not that close.
I remember telling you about this before.
Yes,
I recall that.
It seems Puhang Venture Capital wants to enter the media industry.
They're in contact most frequently with your Wenshang Group.
You understand what I mean, right?
If that's the case,
I see. She's probably
interested in me.
Linhui,
I know you're very reluctant about
this resignation.
There are some troublemakers behind this.
If we let them have their way,
it's definitely not for you to accept.
But you need to trust me.
I absolutely won't let things
develop the way they imagine.
I can handle this.
My superhero husband is going to come to my rescue again.
The key is that I've been at China Business Wave
for 15 years.
15 years is
such an important period in one's life.
How do you expect me
to emotionally accept China Business Wave
becoming such a mess?
You have to accept it.
But there's
so much effort from so many people in there.
This is reality.
You have to accept it.
I don't want to accept it. I want to change reality.
Alright, alright.
To be honest, Linhui,
I'm very satisfied with my life right now,
especially since we're planning to have a child.
Our lives will change.
Of course, I know that in this matter,
your sacrifice will be the greatest.
But you have to trust me.
I will adjust my schedule
to be as involved as possible
in our family and the child's growth.
I can do it.
Here you go.
Paving the way, are you?
I just want you to rest well
and not worry too much.
Zhou Hang, I really understand how you feel.
And I'm also looking forward to
the arrival of this little one.
Really, how can I not be excited?
But I think
when it comes to my work,
you really shouldn't worry so much.
Because I don't think that after we have a child,
there will be problems with my work.
Or that if I'm working,
I won't be able to take care of the child.
So many women can do it.
Why
can't I or our family do it?
I don't think it's a problem.
It's all in your imagination.
You need to have a child first.
Right?
You asked me to handle the share buyback of Huake Vision
and sort out the company's finances.
As expected, there are some issues.
Before January of this year,
all of Huake Vision's component processing orders
were sent to this company.
I looked into it.
This company has no qualifications or equipment.
They only handle receiving orders and subcontracting.
I was curious at first.
I wondered if the person in charge of this company
might be a relative of Zhang Hongda.
But after investigating,
the result is quite interesting.
Who's it?
The person in charge of this company
is our company's former partner, Wu Yueting.
Of course,
his name is hidden behind the scenes
and doesn't appear on the list of shareholders.
So Wu Yueting used Jade Oak's money
to invest in Huake Vision,
and then had Huake Vision
issue high-priced orders to his own company.
That's right.
And I found that after January this year,
Zhang Hongda found another factory.
It seems the quality of Wu Yueting's factory's shipments
didn't meet Huake Vision's requirements,
and the defect rate was too high,
so he had to find
another factory to redo the work.
But as a result,
the costs became uncontrollable.
So now we can understand
why he later experienced a shortage of funds
and was eager to seek a new round of financing.
By the way, following this lead,
I made another discovery.
Go on.
Maybe to lower costs,
or possibly to make the financial reports look good,
he approached a Hong Kong company,
and the main business
of this Hong Kong company
is smuggling components.
I'm just curious,
apart from Wu Yueting,
do you think the investment manager in charge of this project
was involved?
Did she take any benefits?
Or does she have other motives?
Is she covering something up for Zhang Hongda?
Is this person really trustworthy?
I'm a little bit tempted by you.
Yet I'm so afraid to look into your eyes.
A little bit tempted.
A little bit hesitant.
What I fear most is loving and then losing.
It's hard to resist.
Although I don't look, don't think, and don't listen,
I'm still caught...
It's okay.
It's alright.
I'm a little bit tempted by you.
Love.
Yu Shi.
It's so hard to resist.
[Save electricity]
How do you feel?
I feel pretty good.
This cycle is for ovulation stimulation and follicle monitoring.
So
you need to relax
and rest well.
Don't worry too much about other things.
I'm actually still a bit worried about that,
you know,
about what you mentioned before,
will the ectopic pregnancy have any impact?
I'm not quite sure,
and I'm still a bit concerned.
I can't say for certain that it won't happen again,
but you don't need to be overly anxious.
The chance of an ectopic pregnancy
in IVF is quite low.
And it's usually easier to detect.
But you can't let your guard down.
I must remind you,
you've already passed the best childbearing age.
In your daily life,
you need to pay extra attention to your health condition.
Excessive fatigue and work stress
are all influencing factors.
Look at that adorable little face.
Yes, it's so cute.
Look how much the eyes and brows resemble yours.
I was actually going to ask before I came,
given the current situation,
if I continue working
at the previous work pace, will it have an impact?
I'll give you four words:
Try to avoid it.
What did you buy?
Newly purchased face masks.
[Jade Oak Capital]
Can you send me the link?
Sure.
Yidi?
Are you okay?
Yidi,
are you alright?
I'm fine, feeling great.
I drank too much.
What are you looking at?
Just looking,
looking at the company.
You don't seem right.
Are you okay?
I was really drunk.
What did you do last night?
Let me tell you,
last night was so embarrassing for me.
So embarrassing.
Tell me about it.
I'm fine.
It's nothing.
Nothing.
Come on, don't be like this.
You can't just stop halfway. Finish what you were saying.
Let me tell you,
there's a new colleague at the company.
It's said that she's back from Wall Street.
Her name is Tang Ruo.
It seems she came back for Yu Shi.
You don't know?
She said
you two had interacted before.
I mean,
if you two really know each other,
do you know anything about her?
Is there really something going on between her and Yu Shi?
If not, how about me, your buddy?
Do whatever you want, whatever.
I'm not a casual person.
She's tall and pretty,
and I'm tall and handsome too.
Alright.
Buddy.
Well, I'll get you some water.
Thank you.
Here's your water.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Di,
don't be too discouraged.
I think you've
already done your best with Huake Vision.
Some things still depend on luck.
Huake Vision?
What's up?
Well,
the Huake Vision financing plan
was rejected by Yuanshen Dongfang's IC.
You don't know?
When did it happen?
Today.
[Huake Vision didn't pass IC]
Yuanshen Dongfang didn't tell you?
Oh my god.
Drinking really messes things up.
Where's Yu?
He came,
and left with Tang Ruo.
With whom?
Tang Ruo.
Hello, the user you are calling is busy.
[Mr. Yu, Huake Vision didn't pass Yuanshen Dongfang's IC. What to do next?]
[I'm handling it.]
[Shen Zongyu, China's top 100 most popular entrepreneurs and investors]
Over the years,
I've been promoting the Female Entrepreneurs Association,
supporting and helping those female entrepreneurs.
Now it seems there have been some results.
When I went to the Puhangh Foundation's
women's salon last time, I noticed it.
What's rare here is that
you've provided
a lot of practical help to these women.
Also, there's a venue where
everyone can gather
to communicate
and share their
experiences.
I think overall this is
a very meaningful endeavor.
But I feel it's still not enough.
Women's right to speak
largely relies on
the reach and influence of the media.
Yes.
So this gave me the idea
of investing in the media industry.
In recent years, Puhang Venture Capital
has been expanding its business model.
Therefore,
investing in the media industry
is also to serve the overall industrial layout
of Puhang Venture Capital.
Compared to these,
I understand that talent is more important.
I believe you've heard,
I've been discussing the possibility of investing
with China Business Wave recently.
But what attracts me is just one thing,
and that's you.
Thank you.
I believe this isn't one-sided.
I think you must also
be very interested in collaborating with me, right?
Ms. Shen, I appreciate it
and I'm very honored.
Of course, I'm eager to have
the opportunity to work with you.
However...
However, China Business Wave might be
too small a stage for you.
Moreover,
you know the current situation of the media industry.
It's in a period of transition.
But I admire your tenacity
in staying rooted in this industry for your career ideals.
Thank you.
So when I heard you resigned,
I was very pleased.
I feel like
I see hope for our potential collaboration.
Thank you, Ms. Shen, for your appreciation.
But from what I learn from what you just said,
you're not optimistic about investing in China Business Wave, are you?