[The Storm of Roses]
[Episode 28]
The one in charge of the Huake Vision project—
what's her name again?
Jiang Yidi.
Right.
All the negative voices from outside
are now focused on her.
I think we should distance ourselves from her.
What do you think?
At least this
will show the media our zero-tolerance attitude.
It will also help restore the company's image.
The smuggling case involving Zhang Hongda
actually has nothing to do with her.
I've also asked our internal control department to investigate it.
No evidence shows that Jiang Yidi
was involved in or aware of Zhang Hongda's smuggling case.
Besides, she's one of my most capable subordinates.
She's very competent.
So,
from a professional standpoint,
I hope I can vouch for her.
You and her don't have...
You understand what I mean, right?
I understand what you mean.
Since you put it that way,
alright then.
However, before the impact of Zhang Hongda's case dissipates,
let's have her handle fewer cases for now.
Understood.
That's it for now, then.
Okay.
Come in.
Eason.
There's a small situation outside.
Could you come out and take a look?
Mr. Yu! Mr. Yu!
Mr. Yu! Thank you, Mr. Yu!
Thank you, Mr. Yu!
Thank you, Mr. Yu! Mr. Yu!
What's going on?
Didn't you tell me to throw a party
for everyone to celebrate?
Isn't this lively enough?
Try this.
Oranges.
They're very sweet.
Come on, let's eat together.
Come on. Eat up!
Try some snacks. Try some snacks.
Okay.
The snacks are delicious, too.
Alright.
Are you surprised?
-I'm okay.
-I thought we should
have an afternoon tea to liven things up.
-Give me one.
-Here.
Thank you.
Would you like to try some strawberries?
They're really sweet.
[Caution: Hot]
Where did you buy them?
I didn't. An old friend gave me these.
He's been in the imported fresh food business for quite a while.
After he heard I joined Jade Oak Capital,
he actually mentioned you.
He said he knows you've worked on
quite a few cases in the retail sector,
and he's done some in-depth research, too.
He's particularly interested.
Hasn't Yidi been looking into this area recently?
Is that so?
That's great!
I'll take a look at it with her later
and report back to you.
Right. Where's Jiang Yidi?
Mr. Yu,
Yidi went to check on a project.
[Caution: Hot]
I heard you've already got
the minimum viable product model up and running.
Yes.
The daily order volume for the front warehouse
averages around 1,000 orders.
Then, what about the average order value?
I'll have someone
send you the data later.
Alright?
No, no, there's no need for that trouble.
We can actually have these things…
By the way, I have something to ask you.
What's the situation with Huake Vision now?
I heard you were in charge of its post-investment management.
Did Zhang Hongda really smuggle?
There are rumors going around
saying he's just a scapegoat.
Who knows if it's true or not.
How much do you guys at Jade Oak Capital
actually know?
Come on, tell us.
Mr. Song…
It's unlikely that you knew nothing, right?
After all, you've been following this project for a long time.
Mr. Song, it's like this.
Well,
as for Jade Oak Capital,
we're definitely not involved in any problems.
You haven't tried the oranges yet.
Have some fruit.
You didn't see what happened that day?
No. Tell us.
I saw it.
Wasn't it that scene in the lobby?
I don't know.
Tell me quickly.
People from Yuanshen Dongfang came and caused a scene.
They pointed at Jiang Yidi and yelled at her.
They almost got into a fight.
Anyway, it was quite an ugly scene.
[Caution: Hot]
After all, it's 100 million yuan we're talking about.
I heard that
everyone responsible for this project has been fired.
Even Zhou Hang has been suspended.
Oh my, that's explosive!
[Caution: Hot]
This time,
Yuanshen Dongfang is probably going to experience a major shake-up.
It's a chain reaction, isn't it?
Really?
What's going on with Yidi?
Such a big smuggling scandal at Huake Vision—
how could she not know about it?
We can't really say for sure.
That's enough, isn't it?
Don't you know what kind of person Yidi is?
[Caution: Hot]
We're all colleagues, after all.
Don't gossip behind people's backs.
If you have the guts, say it to her face.
Just talking about this matter.
Let me say something.
Everyone listen up, I'll only say this once.
Starting today,
this matter with Huake Vision is a thing of the past.
Don't mention it again.
We only need to focus on the present
and the future.
That case you just mentioned is quite good.
Write up a proposal for me.
And one more important thing,
I want this year's annual party
to be a grand event.
Everyone
comes up with a plan for me.
The one I choose
will be generously rewarded.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Yu.
I'm looking forward to it.
Save that black cake for me, okay?
Sure thing!
[Fresh Food Warehouse 1]
Mr. Song,
I truly believe that the fresh food e-commerce sector
is a trillion-dollar opportunity.
Jiang,
no need to rush.
You see,
you've asked me to meet several times before.
I really think you're quite sincere.
So, when you asked to meet today,
I agreed to see you.
But to be honest,
in the fresh food sector,
we are absolutely the industry leader.
Of course.
So, it's not us looking for money;
it's a lot of venture capitalists
chasing after us with money, eager to invest.
Of course,
especially at times like this,
we can't let success go to our heads.
Don't you agree?
Yes, absolutely.
After all,
Huake Vision
used to be the most promising company in the industry.
But look at what happened.
It's become like this now.
To be honest,
who wouldn't be disheartened?
Who wouldn't be afraid?
So, if we don't learn
from others' experiences,
in the end, we'll be the ones to suffer.
Mr. Song,
I understand your concerns.
But I can assure you
like...
As far as cooperation is concerned,
there's no need for guarantees.
I think
we should slow things down a bit.
You should check out a few more companies.
I'll think it over as well.
Let's both be more cautious.
Don't you agree?
Alright, alright.
Yes, yes.
Mr. Wu,
Mr. Wu, what you're seeing now
is our largest warehouse.
The overall...
Let's leave it at that for today.
Okay?
I'll call you later.
I have other matters to attend to.
Although we've cleared it out now…
Mr. Wu!
Mr. Song.
Why did you come here directly?
I just came to take a look.
Come, let's go to my office for tea.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
I didn't expect
you'd target the fresh food e-commerce industry, either.
Yes.
However,
I think
their online penetration rate is still less than 5%.
There's still a lot of room for growth.
So,
the future should be a blue ocean.
Your instincts are very sharp.
I've known that for a long time.
However,
Mr. Song is not easy to negotiate with, right?
It's extremely difficult.
But didn't you also say
that easy things aren't necessarily good things?
Your memory is quite good.
That's one of the things I appreciate about you.
However,
the matter with Zhang Hongda
has had quite an impact on you, hasn't it?
Actually,
Song agreed to meet with you today
because I asked him to.
I mainly wanted to have a good talk with you.
Do you know why I haven't reached out to you all this time?
Firstly, Coroman was in preparation,
and many things were unstable.
Secondly, when I left Jade Oak Capital,
it was at a critical moment.
If you had followed me in changing jobs,
wouldn't it have confirmed many rumors?
Right.
I was also considering your interests
because no matter what,
you've always been following me since you came to Jade Oak Capital.
So,
Yidi,
come join Coroman.
You're very capable,
and now is the right time.
Let's work together again.
Work together again?
Of course,
I know you have deep feelings for Huake Vision.
Very deep.
But the situation with Zhang Hongda—
no one could have anticipated it.
If I were still at Jade Oak Capital,
none of this would have happened.
But there's no point in saying this now.
But there's one thing.
Through this incident,
you should have seen Yu Shi for who he really is, right?
Of course,
as a partner,
ensuring the safety of company funds is not wrong.
But in this matter,
he took it to the extreme.
He left Zhang Hongda no way out at all.
If you continue to follow someone like that,
what future can you have?
Can he treat you as one of his own?
You have many ideas
and ambitions,
but you've never had the chance to realize them.
Why is that?
Because you haven't followed the right person.
But I can give you such an opportunity.
I can meet all your conditions and benefits.
More importantly,
the things Huake Vision didn't finish,
Coroman can.
What Zhang Hongda couldn't accomplish,
And we can do it better.
I can also tell you
we're going to make a big move.
In future intelligent healthcare,
Coroman will definitely be in the first tier.
You will soon see
an era belonging to Coroman.
An…
era belonging to Coroman?
Yes.
Do you want to get on board?
Whether you can seize this opportunity depends on you.
Mr. Wu.
You...
There's a condition
for you to invite me, right?
Smart.
Zhang Hongda's wife, Chen Yan,
is now in charge of Huake Vision.
You have a good relationship with her.
You only need to do one thing.
What is it?
Convince her
to accept my help.
Now that your mentor Zhang Hongda is gone,
Huake Vision
will inevitably go bankrupt and be liquidated.
At that time, many people will come to you.
Some people are trying to find out the truth,
while some
just want to use you.
Use me?
The value of Huake Vision
doesn't just lie in Zhang Hongda, does it?
Jade Oak Capital and our Yuanshen Dongfang
invested in this company.
Do you think we only valued the founder?
It's because of Huake Vision's core technology.
Exactly.
His surgical robot
needs a large number of
simulated surgeries and data support
before clinical use.
Of course, you can imitate it,
copying its outer shell and hardware, etc.,
but without data support,
the stability and precision will be greatly compromised.
And at this point,
some people
might need another solution.
Do you understand what I mean?
Mr. Zhou,
you're not suggesting that
someone deliberately set
a trap for Huake Vision?
If Huake Vision falls,
bankruptcy liquidation would take a year or two.
That's enough time for another company
to copy and plagiarize Huake Vision's core technology.
This is the most crucial component of the surgical robot,
as well as the brain of the surgical robot.
This is the most valuable part of Huake Vision.
I can also tell you
we're going to make a big move.
In future intelligent healthcare,
Coroman will definitely be in the first tier.
You'll soon see
an era belonging to Coroman.
Hello, please don't hang up.
The number you're calling is busy.
This is mine. What are you grabbing?
Take it all.
You... give me a few more days,
[Huake Vision]
okay?
Look, when Hongda was here,
we never owed you money.
Take the valuable things.
I...
Should I take this or not?
Take it, take it.
In case someone else takes it.
Ms. Chen,
Mr. Zhang is gone.
But we'll still get paid, won't we?
I'll figure something out.
It's been over three months without pay.
Mr. Zhang said before
as soon as the money from Yuanshen Dongfang arrived,
he'd pay our salaries and the overdue bonuses.
Well...
Now that Mr. Zhang's gone,
will our salaries be withheld?
I'll find a way.
But now it's already...
What more do you want?
Are you trying to force me to die?
You want me to jump like Hongda did?
Would that make you happy?
I said
I'll find a way!
Okay.
Ms. Chen,
the people from Coroman called again.
Tell them to get lost!
Get lost!
Stay out of the way.
Soon there'll be nothing left.
No...
Take this, too.
Don't drop it.
Take that as well.
I bought you a cup of coffee.
Perfect. I happen to be sleepy.
Thank you.
I have a question.
Can I ask you?
Go ahead.
Is our company working with Coroman?
What do you mean?
I just happened to see this
on social media.
Isn't this Yidi with Wu Yueting?
And there's also Mr. Song, the CEO of Kuaida Fresh.
Hasn't Yidi been in contact with Kuaida Fresh recently?
[Met some top investors at the Fresh E-commerce Association—feeling confident about this year's market!]
I've heard that Coroman has been poaching people everywhere lately.
Colleagues in the company are saying
Wu Yueting used to value Yidi highly.
Hello, Mr. Yu.
Why didn't you come to the office today?
I went to meet with Mr. Song, the CEO of that fresh food company.
I went to his company.
Where are you?
I'm downstairs at the company.
Come to my office as soon as you get up here.
Close the door.
You wanted to see me, Boss?
About the fresh food e-commerce sector,
I want you to pause on that.
Hand it over to Tang Ruo.
I want you to focus on the film and television culture industry.
Then, prepare an analysis for me.
Why?
Don't even ask. This is my arrangement.
Okay.
Well,
can I ask for a reason?
Does this count?
If you're still willing to listen to an explanation,
let me explain.
I just happened to run into Wu.
We exchanged a few pleasantries.
It's nothing.
It's alright.
It's really okay. It's not important.
The doors of Jade Oak Capital are always open.
People may come at any time,
and people may leave as well.
It's very normal.
The company won't collapse
because of any employee's departure.
But I have one principle.
If one day you really decide to switch jobs,
I must be the first to know.
If I say
I'm not thinking of switching jobs,
would you believe me?
Hasn't Wu Yueting given you a job offer?
He has.
I didn't accept it.
But you didn't refuse either, did you?
So you hesitated.
You hesitated.
I hesitated; so what?
Your loyalty to me is worth so little?
Boss, did I hear that right?
You're talking to me about loyalty?
You heard it correctly.
Don't you find that particularly ridiculous?
I believe
loyalty and trust are mutual.
Right?
Have you ever trusted me?
If you had tried to trust me,
it could have very likely saved
a startup company on the verge of bankruptcy,
or even
a life.
But have you ever trusted me?
The same goes for today's matter.
If you trusted me,
you wouldn't have come to ask me.
Am I right?
You still can't let go of the Huake Vision matter, can you?
No, I can't.
This world is about the survival of the fittest.
The weak are prey to the strong.
That's natural selection.
There's no way around it.
This is the law of the jungle.
In this jungle, there are only two types of animals:
one is the wolf,
and the other is the sheep.
Wolves eat sheep.
Is that wrong?
No, it's not.
But if you insist on thinking like a sheep
while living among wolves,
then let me tell you clearly:
This isn't the place for you.
You can choose to leave.
Maybe I'm just that kind of
useless sheep.
I can't change myself.
What can I do?
Thank you for reminding me.
About leaving…
Regarding the matter of leaving,
I will consider it carefully.
Is there anything else?
No, that's all.
[Schedule reminder: Prenatal examination at the hospital]
Thank you.
I have to go on a business trip today.
Weren't you suspended?
It has nothing to do with that.
It's something else.
Does your suspension have anything to do with Huake Vision?
I feel like there's more to this matter.
Is there some inside story?
What do you want to know?
I want to know everything.
I don't think Zhang Hongda's death is as simple as it seems.
Yuanshen Dongfang must be connected to Coroman.
After I return from my business trip,
hopefully, we'll have some answers.
Zhou Hang, we're married.
So you still don't plan to tell me?
Or you can't tell me?
At this stage,
I hope you rest well,
take care of your health,
don't overthink or meddle too much.
Some things
will naturally come to light in due time.
Does Shen Zongyu know we're going together?
Yes, she does.
I told her.
How did she react?
She didn't say much.
She'll surely take action based on how things develop.
After all, she's a major shareholder.
Unless it's absolutely necessary,
she won't make a move.
So this time, we must achieve something.
Who else knows we're going together?
I suppose many people know.
Even though you've been suspended,
there are surely many eyes
secretly watching you.
At this point, my identity as your ex-girlfriend
comes in handy.
Who could guess that our real purpose
for this trip is something else?
As long as your wife doesn't misunderstand.
My wife?
Don't underestimate her.
I heard China Business Wave is building a new media platform.
If Xie Linhui is willing to do it,
let her do it.
But how are you going to allocate the staff?
You were planning layoffs before.
You're not going to hire new people now, are you?
If you do this,
everyone will be on edge.
I don't want to either,
but this is the current situation.
Should we call Xie Linhui and Lv Jian here
[Oriental Commercial&Culture Group]
[China Business Wave]
for a meeting
to hear their opinions?
Wouldn't that settle it?
Can we reach an agreement on this?
Lv,
stay calm.
[Reassignment Personnel Registration Form]
Usually, we have to have a meeting
even to change a punctuation mark.
But this time,
whether to go to the new media department
or stay here,
they let us choose for ourselves.
Can't you see?
He's forcing us to take sides,
and we have to do it openly.
President Li always likes to pull this kind of thing.
Now, it's even worse.
We can clearly see which side he's on,
but which side we're on,
whether we're on the same page as him,
he needs to see clearly.
In a few months,
he'll be retiring anyway.
Well,
he's so eager to back up that person.
What's the point?
It's just because President Li's about to retire
that he doesn't want to pretend to be nice anymore.
He's been putting up with Hui for so many years.
He's always wanted to get rid of her.
Otherwise,
how could Lv Jian rise so quickly with his limited experience?
Well…
what's your choice?
Are you choosing to work with Hui in the new media department?
What about you?
What are you all choosing?
People's hearts, you know...
No matter how idealistic you are,
how passionate,
or how much you value relationships,
in the end,
we all have to consider practical issues.
What are these practical issues?
We're all adults here.
Besides ideals,
we have to face reality, too.
You all know
about my family situation...
My parents are old,
and my child is about to start high school.
I can't afford any upheaval.
None of us can afford it.
Of course, I'd like to follow Hui,
but the new office is just too far away.
I have to drop off and pick up my child from school every day.
It would mean crossing the entire Puhang city.
The commute
would take two to three hours.
Two to three hours would be bearable,
but the key is, I heard that this new media department
will have performance evaluations
directly linked to salaries.
Even if we work our tails off,
it would still take half a year to see results, right?
And that's an optimistic scenario.
What if the operation doesn't go well?
Yeah.
From the inside information I've heard,
the layoffs
are only temporarily on hold.
I guess
they'll use this personnel transfer
to find
an excuse for poor performance and results
to cut the entire department.
If this were five years ago,
I'd really want to venture out with Hui.
But now,
with elderly parents and young children to care for,
how can I just impulsively follow along?
I've just bought a house,
with a 30-year mortgage.
[Meeting Room Usage Registration Form]
This soup is quite tasty.
You're quite bold today.
Aren't you afraid of being seen by colleagues?
You chose this place.
It's so close to the office.
Jingjing,
I have serious business to discuss with you.
Serious business?
Chief Editor Lv,
if it's serious business, let's talk back at the office.
It's lunch break now.
I need to rest.
I don't have time to listen to your nonsense here.
Can you stop fooling around?
I was wrong before.
I was too short-tempered.
I apologize to you.
Apology accepted.
Bye.
Jingjing.
Please, cut it out.
I apologize to you.
I was indeed wrong.
But I was under so much pressure lately.
Can you try to understand me?
Do you really think I'm stupid?
Don't think I don't know.
You called me here in such a hurry
because this afternoon, everyone is to choose whether to leave or to stay.
What?
Do you still want me to go to Xie Linhui's place
and act as your spy?
How could you say that about me?
Then, do you think I'm wrong?
Lv Jian, I've finally figured it out.
You
just want to use me.
All those things you said,
all those sweet words were fake.
You're quite the actor, aren't you?
How were those sweet words fake?
How was I acting with you?
How long have we been together?
Over two years.
All the good things I did for you before—
have you forgotten them all?
Fine.
[Hello, Mr. Lv, reservation for an apartment viewing at Olympic Forest Century Phase II has been successfully made]
See for yourself.
Didn't you say you wanted to see those three apartments?
I've already contacted the sales office
and scheduled a time for an apartment viewing.
The text messages are all on my phone.
The time is there, too.
See for yourself.
Really?
Those three apartments you wanted to see—
to be honest, one of them is okay.
The other two are too far out.
It's not that I'm ignoring your suggestions
or not paying attention to you.
[Hello, Mr. Lv, reservation for an apartment viewing at Olympic Forest Century Phase II has been successfully made]
I have some really good friends
who are in real estate sales.
They recommended better properties to me,
but you never let me finish talking.
You always hang up on me.
Of course, I was at fault, too.
I wanted to give you a surprise.
I didn't expect to mess things up.
You're not lying to me?
Is it really like that?
How dare I lie to you?
You'd tear the roof off my house if I did.
How can you talk like that?
Making me sound like a shrew.
Jingjing,
let's stop arguing.
Really.
Every time we argue,
I feel terrible.
I can't even sleep.
I'm left all alone,
lying in bed, lonely and cold.
Don't be so mushy here.
Let's make up.
Alright, alright.
You'd better go now.
Go on.
I know you.
You're afraid of being seen by people from the agency if you stay a minute longer.
Aren't you going back to the magazine agency?
You go back first.
I'll buy another cup of coffee.
Haven't you already had two cups?
Why are you buying more?
You should know who I'm buying it for.
Chief Editor.
It seems everyone has made up their minds.
Work hard.
[Authority and Fairness]
Hui.
A new coffee shop just opened next door.
I brought you a cup.
Try it.
Thank you, Jingjing.
You're welcome.
They…
None of them came?
Everyone has their own aspirations.
It's okay.
You have me.
Let me tell you,
if I hadn't gone to buy coffee just now,
I would have been here earlier.
Have you thought it through?
The new department
is short-staffed.
The workload will be heavy if you go.
And the new office location is far away.
The commute time will be long.
As you said,
everyone has their own aspirations.
As long as I'm with you,
to the ends of the earth,
I'll go.
But there won't be a salary increase.
No, Hui,
about this matter…
Hui,
can we discuss this a bit?
[China Business Wave]
Ms. Xie.
Why are you two here?
I heard that
there are personnel adjustments in the agency today.
So I quickly asked Ye Wei to come with me.
Didn't both of your internships end?
Well,
Xiaohui didn't get into graduate school this year.
Nonsense.
I want to learn from Ms. Xie for two more years.
What about you?
Didn't you go to some advertising company?
Oh, that.
I'm not going anymore.
I've thought about it for a long time.
I feel that
I still prefer doing news and media.
Ms. Xie,
they told me
you're going to work on new media.
Xiaohui and I also want to join.
Even if we have to intern for another six months, it's fine.
Yes.
When we interned here before,
we always felt like we couldn't exert ourselves.
We proposed many new ideas,
but they were all rejected by the teachers.
However,
in the field of new media and the internet,
I think I still have a lot to contribute.
But if you go there,
all the conditions
are far worse than here.
It's okay.
We just want to learn some real skills.
Right, we're not in a hurry to make money.
Are you two sure about this?
No need to think.
Working with the right person is never wrong.
Yes.
You have good taste.
Let's go.
So we're in?
This place is quite spacious.
There's even a second story.
It's certainly big enough.
However, with this condition,
we can't work here.
Hui,
what should we do about this?
We can do it ourselves.
Do it ourselves?
How can we do it ourselves?
I don't know anything about renovation.
I do.
Chief Editor,
when I was a junior in college,
I studied interior design.
My skills are average,
but
I can handle
simple work
like drawing some design drafts.