I know it's been a difficult journey,
but we'll be at my brother's soon.
Isak!
Brother!
Yoseb!
How did you get so tall?
You were just a runt when I left.
You stole those inches from me!
I prayed very hard for it.
Brother,
this is my wife, Sunja.
I admit, Kyunghee and I were surprised
by the news.
And already with a child.
We have been blessed.
That is how we see it.
How are you feeling?
I'm relieved to be on land again,
and grateful to be welcomed
into your home--
No need. We are family now.
But we should go.
If I don't get you home soon,
Kyunghee will be furious with me.
No.
I'll carry them.
Let's go.
Wow, look at this place!
There's our car coming.
Are you still with the factory?
Better to speak Japanese in public.
(in Japanese) I'm the foreman
at the biscuit factory now.
My boss trusts me.
Hey, look at that!
They're building a subway now.
Tokyo just opened its first line
a few years ago,
so Osaka will have the second one
in all of Asia.
It'll change everything.
But it feels like
we've already leaped into the future.
Look at that!
I was only seven, but I could catch
bigger abalones than these.
And look how expensive!
My father would come
to watch me dive for them.
I'll take two.
Not for me.
Who said I was giving you one?
I'm not even hungry
after that breakfast buffet at the hotel,
but how can I resist?
Of course I have to eat this.
Mother, I told you the buffet is included
in the room charge.
It's called sunk cost.
Only people who grew up rich
think stupid things like that.
Come now. Let's spread your aunt's ashes.
Mother!
Keep up now!
Stay right behind me!
Yoseb,
what is this place?
This is Ikaino,
our neighborhood.
Listen carefully, Isak.
There are still spies around.
Even in the church, I imagine.
You can't ever let your guard down,
understand?
Look what I'm doing,
scaring you on your first night.
You can't imagine
how dire that first year was for us here.
Look around, and you can see why.
Bellies are hungry, but there's no work.
They are desperate.
And do you know how many times
our house has been broken into?
When we go to the police,
they do nothing.
They don't care about the Koreans here.
But I suppose
when you consider everything,
we're still the fortunate ones.
Scram! Go now!
I told you not to let your pigs
run around like this!
Shit!
We're home!
Kyunghee!
Following the First Sino-Japanese
and Russo-Japanese War,
Manchuria and Mongolia
have become a lifeline for our country…
Isak!
Look at you.
But you haven't changed at all.
Not changed?
I'm an old lady now.
It's Sunja, isn't it?
You must be tired after the long journey.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
Please do not concern yourself.
But you're hungry, right?
Sit.
Today, you just eat.
I got a special treat
to mark this occasion.
You came!
I see that look.
Guess you already heard?
Just happy you're here.
Let me introduce my fiancée.
Meet Solomon, my classmate
from the international school.
Ah! The one who conquered America.
How do you find Tokyo
after all this time?
A city with too much money
but no time to spend it.
The best.
See? He always charmed the girls.
So it was a mystery
why he was always stuck on that one girl.
The intense one--
-Hana.
-Yes, Hana.
Whatever happened to her?
She disappeared.
If that's the kind of girl you want,
you know where to find them.
Kumiko's alone again.
I told you not to invite her.
She just wants your attention.
Her older sister,
she's the reason
we had to delay our engagement party.
Her parents wanted
to marry her off first, but no takers.
So, what's the situation?
Abe-san is blackballing you
from every bank in Tokyo.
Who cares?
I'm going back to New York anyway.
You sure about that?
What do you know?
No, it's nothing.
But Tom Andrews,
I wouldn't put too much faith in him.
He's busy atoning for his own sins.
Financial irregularities,
clients' assets.
No way. He's not the type.
Could be why New York shipped him
off to Tokyo.
To hush things up.
Whatever happened,
he can't afford
to damage his career any more.
So you think he'll cut me loose?
Well, wouldn't you?
I'll do my best
to defend your reputation.
But really, I don't get why
you would do such a thing.
Neither do I.
I need to greet the other guests,
but I'll see you in a bit.
Hey,
what did you mean before,
when you said
I should know where to find Hana?
Where should I look?
For that sort of thing,
I would guess the Yoshiwara area,
by the Uguisudani stop.
Hi.
What was he thinking?
Lower your voice.
How could he marry a girl like that?
She's still young.
Let her settle in.
Were we any older when we came?
We were the same age.
And we were miserable then.
Don't you remember?
I'm not just talking about that.
She's further along than I expected.
You see that as well, don't you?
And Isak,
he's susceptible to idealistic leanings.
A girl like that…
she might have planned to trap him.
Yoseb.
We've taken in someone
we know nothing about.
Doesn't that worry you?
It seems I disappoint them.
They'll come around. Don't worry.
But this place…
I feel like it wants no part of us.
I feel that as well.
For so long now,
I've wanted to leave home.
Now that I've done it…
Sunja, I worry you'll come to resent me.
Resent you?
How could I resent the one who saved me?
I don't want this debt between us.
You owe me nothing.
You said it yourself.
My prospects were bleak.
But you were not afraid to meet them.
You're wrong.
I was terrified.
You really don't see it,
do you?
You have so much fortitude.
So much that I can siphon off
my own dose of courage
and still leave you with a bounty.
And this child…
the one I will give my name to,
he will save me.
Death cannot have me.
So no matter what my brother
or sister-in-law believe, they are wrong.
I am the one
who must not be a burden to you.
You're nervous as well.
You know, I saw you that day,
dancing in the plaza.
You were there?
Where did that come from?
Who knows.
When I left that conference room,
I really wanted to sink into that ground.
But when I got outside
and I heard that music…
It's hard to describe.
I really felt I could fly away.
I was on top of the world.
But you didn't fly away.
I guess gravity won.
Perhaps there was another reason?
Perhaps Hana?
The office walls are thin.
You heard all that?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
But I must confess,
I was curious.
She must mean a lot to you.
She did,
but I haven't seen her in years.
Honestly,
I was starting to forget about her.
But then she called after all this time.
It wouldn't affect you so much
if something wasn't still there.
From the first time we met,
she's been stuck in my heart.
I was 14.
She was the daughter
of my father's girlfriend.
Strange circumstances, I know.
But maybe that was part of the appeal.
Some people just have…
that power to consume you.
Hana had that power.
Why did the two of you split?
I left for America.
Not too long after that…
she ran away from home.
You can try to find her.
I'm not sure I want to do that.
I don't think she's going to like
who I've become.
Well, Baek-san,
you like complicated women.
Like that landowner.
Why bring that up?
No amount of money
was going to make her sell.
Then do you think
that was her plan all along?
What plan?
To humiliate you.
When you think about it, it's obvious.
Naomi-san, it really is unfortunate
to be born a woman,
especially in this country.
Being married to a job
that doesn't even want you…
is that what you call winning?
Baek-san, it will be interesting
to see what your future holds.
I'm sorry.
I slept in again.
If the baby is to grow strong,
the mother needs her sleep.
Please, let me hang the wash.
Slowly.
Don't strain yourself.
I didn't even hear Isak leave
this morning.
He's getting up earlier and earlier.
The work at the church
seems to suit him.
What is it?
Are you in pain?
The smell… you washed it all away.
It's been a few weeks,
and they were smelling so terribly.
Oh, I didn't realize…
It's all I had left.
Just a little while…
I just needed it
for a little while longer.
Oh, Sunja.
When does it go away?
This ache,
when does it stop?
It doesn't.
But you'll learn to endure it.
Trust me.
You're sure this is it?
This is where your father is buried?
What are you saying?
How can I forget
where I buried my father?
This is the right place.
Then they moved his grave
when they built this parking lot.
Mother,
they would have done it right.
Don't worry. We'll find it.
I'm sorry.
I know nothing of this.
You'll have to speak to my husband.
He's not in.
We've already spoken with your husband.
But since he doesn't have the money,
it's up to his family then
to pay off the 160-yen debt.
That seal,
it's your husband's, is it not?
It is.
We don't want to be a hassle for you.
Give us a 20 if you have it.
Our boss,
he'll be satisfied with that
for the week.
The 160 yen,
that's the entire amount?
I'll handle this.
Including the interest, it's now double.
When was the loan taken out?
Two months ago.
Said his brother just got married.
Needed an extra fare over.
We'll have the money in a few hours.
-Who do we bring it to?
-You don't seem to understand--
No need to waste your breath.
Just tell me where to bring the money.
Over by the docks,
there's an office
above the net repair shop.
So you'll have the 20 yen then?
We can let our boss know?
Tell him he'll get the entire amount.
But Sunja…
Where did you get a watch like this?
My mother gave it to me.
She wanted me to have something
for emergencies.
Kyunghee, it must be paid right away.
We should trust Yoseb to handle this.
I'm sure he tried his best,
but the payments are too cumbersome now.
I've seen this happen many times.
Back home, so many farmers had to turn
to moneylenders after a bad season
to buy more seeds or equipment.
Many even lost their homes.
How could he do this?
To go to such people.
Was there any choice?
This is my debt.
I'm the one who must pay it.
Can you at least assure me
that his grave was moved properly,
that he is safe somewhere?
I understand your concerns,
but without the file,
I really don't know anything.
Let's start by processing
the request for the report.
Your name?
Kim Sunja.
My Japanese name is Bando Nobuko.
You're one of those.
When did you move over?
1931.
Do you have Japanese citizenship then?
No.
-I'm a permanent resident.
-But you carry a South Korean passport.
All we want is
to find my grandfather's grave--
Mother?
Mother,
calm yourself.
They'll find the location.
How can you say that?
So much has changed here.
It's impossible to find the living,
let alone the dead.
Excuse me!
I found a note
while looking through our files
related to relocation requests.
Perhaps you know the name
Shin Bokhee?
Do you know this person?
She's my older sister.
We've been looking for her for years.
She'd be 29 now.
Someone shows up here once a week
with the same story.
It's not a lie.
That's what they all say.
In any case,
I'm sorry, but I can't help you.
Haruki-san?
Solomon?
I'll be right there!
What is it?
What do you want to sell me today?
Have I really changed that much?
I suppose I must have.
Sunja?
Sunja, is that really you?
Sister! It's me.
Bokhee, my sister!
You came back.
It's certainly a fine piece.
But I'm sorry to say
there isn't demand for something
like this in this neighborhood.
Young men these days,
they like the ones you wear on the wrist.
I can give you 40 for it.
I'm sorry for bothering you. Good day.
I'd like to help you,
especially since you are expecting.
I'd be willing to go up to 50,
though I'm not sure I can earn it back.
It's worth at least 300.
It's from Switzerland.
They make the best watches there.
You're not in Switzerland, are you?
I understand.
Goodbye.
You're from Busan.
I can tell from your accent.
Your parents,
what do they do over there?
Just my mother.
She runs her own boardinghouse.
Must be a clever businesswoman.
Fine.
225 yen.
Three hundred.
That is my price.
Kyunghee, what is it?
We can't go there.
It wouldn't be respectable.
But the loan isn't paid
until we deliver this money.
Can't we just give it to Yoseb?
This kind of dirty work belongs to men,
not us.
Do you really think
he would take this money from me?
I'll go. Wait for me at home.
No, you can't go!
If I don't,
what happens then?
You don't realize…
before I came here,
I never even cooked
or washed my own clothes.
I never spoke to anyone
who my parents didn't know.
Never even handled my own money.
Learning how to do everything,
it was so hard, Sunja.
But then I see you.
You've only been here a few weeks.
I feel foolish.
This morning, you asked me
when the ache will go away.
The truth is,
I'm scared all the time here.
This constant fear…
how much longer
do I have to live with it?
Let's be scared together.
Perhaps some strength
can come out of it.
Do you think so?
I do.
Move out of the way.
Eat.
After you left…
it felt like
a huge hole opened in our lives.
Your mother, especially,
she felt it deeply.
It was hard for Donghee and me
to see her like that.
Then the war broke out,
and things got even harder.
We were a burden to your mother.
We knew that.
But even then,
she refused to send us away.
Then, one day,
Donghee and I were approached by a man…
who promised us decent factory jobs
in Manchuria.
We hated the thought
of leaving your mother alone here…
but how much longer
would she have been able to keep us?
Besides, your leaving,
it made us realize
just how small our lives were here.
Donghee, especially,
she really wanted to see the world.
We came back after the war,
and we found your mother gone.
The truth is,
I was glad.
I didn't want her to see
how much we had changed.
Even though there was so little
to come back to, I was glad to be back.
But for Donghee,
that happiness faded quickly…
when she realized it wasn't possible…
to fit back into the shape
of the young girl
she once was.
Remember where we used to do laundry?
That's…
where I found her.
You realize that some people
live in their dreams.
They're not made
to endure in such times.
This is where you live?
I just ran into him.
This is Solomon.
I've known him since he was a baby.
Please welcome him.
That's Noriko.
Her brother, Takashi.
Masako.
Such a handsome young man.
Is he a gift for me?
He's a little old for you,
don't you think?
You're right,
but I could make an exception
for such a good-looking guy.
And this,
this is Satoru.
This is Mozasu's son.
I still speak often of your father.
He was my greatest friend,
and he saved my life once.
But that's all a long time ago.
This is my home now.
Get me the promissory note.
I'm fine. Please serve yourselves.
You are our guest.
Thank you.
This is delicious.
What's in it?
Just eat your fill.
If it weren't for Bokhee…
my father would be just one of many
in a crowded, unmarked grave.
I don't know
how I can ever repay her kindness.
She did it for you.
In the end,
I was the lucky one.
But…
in my heart, it doesn't feel right.
It is not a shame to survive, mother.
A long time ago, someone once told me,
"For every step forward,
another person would have to fall back."
I couldn't believe that then.
But now I wonder…
perhaps he was right.
I don't know
who would've said such a thing to you,
but it doesn't sound right to me.
Hey,
let's go home.
Really?
But we still have two more days here.
I can come back.
I know that now.
When you disappeared,
my father mourned for you,
as did your wife and brother.
I know I hurt many people.
I didn't mean it like that.
It's only to say
how much you were loved.
That is true…
but…
the Haruki they loved
was a different man.
The person I am now couldn't exist then.
I may not have much here,
but I can be myself.
Please.
I'm sorry.
What am I doing?
I always felt sorry for you.
You grew up
burdened with your family's hopes
and dreams.
It must have been impossible.
But then,
to feel bad for someone who has so much,
that feels wrong somehow.
I just hope we can both be happy.
Sunja…
did we do the wrong thing?
Respectfully, may I ask
how did you know
she would come to sell the watch?
She married a dreamer.
A man weaker than her.
And for that, she'll pay dearly.
310 yen, for your troubles.
FOR SALE
BY KUROHANA ENTERPRISES
Tom, listen, I know you're pissed at me,
but I think there's something at play
with Mamoru Yoshii.
I've been hearing
he's selling off a lot of property.
Hey, I'm glad you called.
-I've been meaning to get in touch.
-Why?
Shiffley's is letting you go. Okay?
They're getting too much heat
from Colton and Abe-san.
You can't let them do this.
Believe it or not, I tried to help you.
T-Tom, my visa.
It's sponsored by Shiffley's.
That means I can't go back.
Well, you should contact a lawyer
right away, man.
I don't know if there's anything
they can do, but they--
I have to get the other line.
Don't hang up.
Hello, what is it?
Solomon, I don't want to die alone.
I don't!
Hana,
what happened?
Hana!
You need to come!
Come now…
before it's too late.