3. Transport the
Magまぁ
The first time I saw a black cat, I thought it was a black cat.
I thought it was a black cat.
It was two continue cats.
...
It wasn't a black cat.
Sw周
Good
Sweet
Season 2
Episode 22
Is this bigger or is it bigger?
No, it's bigger than this.
Yes. The first one,
This is the best.
You go to bed.
I haven't changed my clothes.
Go to sleep.
You can change your clothes.
Open it yourself.
Put your hand in.
Good.
Close your eyes.
I'm happy to be alone.
I want to be with you.
I want to teach you how to learn.
I want to practice.
Close your eyes.
I'm happy to be alone.
Where's your dress?
It's pretty.
It's a dress made of clouds.
How did you change your dress?
Teach us.
Yes.
Xiu.
You changed such a beautiful dress.
My mother bought me a tofu.
She saw your aunt buy me flowers.
No way.
Is this really your own dress?
Give it back to me.
It's bought.
My mother said that you are good at getting married.
You are a good match.
You are right.
You changed your dress.
Give it back to me.
I changed my dress for you.
Yes.
Did your mother change your dress for you?
I heard that her mother died of illness.
This flower basket must be bought by her father.
Xiu's father will pay for it.
Buy a flower basket and get it.
Don't call her father.
Xiu.
Give it back to me.
What are you laughing at?
Why are you laughing at me?
Who are you laughing at?
What is it?
It's salty.
It's salty?
How many people beat you?
Six.
Six?
You are still laughing at me?
Who beat you?
I beat you.
You beat you again?
What are the other people doing?
You didn't see it.
They are acting.
You are so stupid.
Why are you fighting?
Because of the flower basket.
They remember my flower basket.
They beat my father.
They said it's not your hand.
I'm so angry.
It's my flower basket.
I'll make another one for you.
Really?
It's my hand.
Your hand?
Remember, you can't fight.
Okay?
I'll do it.
You can't fight?
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to my mother.
You are talking to your mother?
Come on.
Mr. Li,
he is asking for your opinion.
You are in the right place.
I have something to tell you.
I know.
Li Shande's life is precious.
He is so soft and firm.
He is so stubborn.
He has to do something for himself.
It's him.
He is the one.
He is so stubborn.
It's him.
I will send news to Zhao Xinming.
Tell him Li Shande is not from Zuo Xiang.
And eliminate his concern.
Then who is the one
who told you about the life of the drug?
You can't keep your life.
You are so funny.
How could you...
How could you do this?
The new owner of the right-hand side, Li Nan,
will break your identity as soon as he sees you.
Break my identity?
It's so far away.
I'm afraid we will have time to choose.
The new owner has left Chang'an for 21 days.
He should be here soon.
Stop him.
I sent out the master.
I used to help him with the perfume.
But now the owner is so stubborn.
He has to leave the city several times.
Then he changed his route and hid your identity.
I have already sent people
to Li Nan's place of residence.
This is our last chance.
It's also your last chance.
You must seize this chance.
But don't let Wang Wuyi
get sick and die.
The future is in danger.
I don't believe he can be defeated.
Zheng Ping'an.
I'm afraid that the left-hand side, Xiang Chuiqing,
will be forced to leave the city.
You want to live?
I will take the school center tomorrow.
I will leave Li Nan.
Otherwise,
the new owner will be separated
from the family.
Where is my money?
What's wrong?
I'm busy.
Tell me.
How can I live
without money?
What should I do?
I'm afraid that I'm lost.
The wolf went out.
It burned when he came back.
Maybe it was a cold.
Nonsense.
Can this place be cold?
It's a heavy rain.
I don't know
if you're worried about me.
I'm so happy.
Stay away from me.
I can feel better.
It's hot.
Come on.
It's windy.
It's not warm.
It's cold.
It's getting warmer.
Go.
Pull the curtains.
It's so hot.
Come on.
Go.
You know everything.
I'm afraid of death.
But I'm not a timid person.
We can't be scared
because we're going to die.
We can't be scared.
Right?
Are you feeling better?
I was a little kid.
Mr. Sun Ming said
that I can't die
because of the chaos in my life.
And I have a skill.
I can turn the bad thing
into others.
What do you think?
You'll say a few words.
You won't say you're out.
It's comforting.
It's turning bad things into others.
Others want to live.
Why are you so excited?
I said that
it's turning bad things into others.
It's not my fault.
You can only say
that this person is rich.
Right?
He's a dead man.
He's a dead ghost.
Who's a dead ghost?
Get out.
Ming,
you're not a good person.
You're a good person.
You can't persuade him.
Ming,
stop persuading him.
Fine, I'll buy him medicine.
Take good care of him.
Qi Lang,
even though I'm a little bit stupid,
he's sincere to you.
Look,
he's always
making a fool of himself
in the room.
Now he's going to
go out to buy medicine for you.
I'm a good person.
Gao.
Okay, here you are.
You're here.
Qi Lang,
get out of here.
Open the door.
The snow will be here soon.
I'll go out.
The flowers are really good.
It's from Chang'an.
Do you want to buy flowers?
I heard that you also come to Chang'an.
It's hard to change.
I really came from Chang'an.
So you're here.
My husband
was a nurse.
He offended the right-hand man
and left his family behind.
I won't do anything else
after he left a few years ago.
I can only
rely on these
wall-to-walls.
I'm so tired.
How did you
get into trouble?
You're a big man.
You want to learn this?
I'll change.
I'll come to get you.
You're wrong.
You're so good.
You're faster
than my calculations.
You're not good enough.
Sir,
the jade jade is gone.
I can't get the prescription.
I forgot.
Sir,
the jade jade
was sold to Hu Sheng
a few days ago.
They're all gone.
They're all sold.
They're doing the spices business.
They're afraid of the smell.
They put jade jade jade
next to it.
They can store it
as much as they want.
They even bought the jade jade.
How about I
change it to a shirt?
The price...
The same price.
Okay.
Why are the jade jade
double-layered?
Yes.
Where did you buy it?
I haven't seen it in Ningnan.
It's only for Hu Sheng.
When I went to send jade jade jade,
I saw they used this
to store the spices.
The spices were
very small.
It's suitable
for the jade jade.
What about the jade jade?
There are many.
I don't know.
But I heard
they need to be handled.
Where to?
Boss Su,
they're inside.
there's news.
Someone's out of the store.
Out of the store?
Yes.
It's definitely ours.
It's ours.
It's our Nanshi Xiang.
Who's the one who's out of the store?
Amita.
In the beginning of next month,
we're going to launch
a new business.
At that time,
each of us will have a new business.
Who can bring the best business
will be the new one.
I hope you don't miss this opportunity.
No matter who's out of the store,
it can't be moved by Amita's status.
Amita has been a good-for-nothing
for the past years.
The scale of our business
has increased by a hundred times.
The total number of goods is also increasing.
This is all a public skill
that people know.
If we want to choose the salesman,
it must be Amita.
When Boss Su was the salesman,
we made friends with the people in the store.
We never had to see
the people's faces as businessmen.
But the way the business has changed
in the past few years.
But we're businessmen
who are running on the market in the big store.
How can we avoid the business
and make the business better?
The meaning of business is to protect the business.
This style will never change.
You're talking nonsense.
You're as beautiful as a bird singing.
Boss Su,
what style has made you come out?
It's the evil style.
The demon style.
It's the wind of stealing.
The wind of robbing.
Remember when you liked to say
that you were so talented?
Why haven't you seen it for years?
You're so strong.
If you haven't seen it for years,
you're also
so confident that you can see the whole world.
Everyone is here.
Open the store and tell me.
Why did you steal my Anxi?
You can use it in a messy way.
You can't say it in a messy way.
You said that I stole your spices.
Do you have any evidence?
Hangshou.
Boss Su has forced us to make our spices.
Not him.
Tell me.
Why?
My spices just disappeared.
Your spices appeared on the market.
Is it a coincidence?
Boss Su,
you've been away for too long.
Your spices business
has been broken down by you.
My spices are in double-layered.
In Lingnan,
my spices are in double-layered.
My Su Liang is a family.
Amitabha,
do you dare to open the box?
Is it Su Liang's goods?
We can't fool him.
We really want to make a big deal out of it.
Hangshou.
Go and get our goods.
Give me your gun.
I've put a paper in it.
I'll put it on the water.
You can't put it in double-layered.
This is a dream.
What a dream.
Who's that?
What are you doing?
I'm buying a dream.
I'm not selling it.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Li Zhishi, a saint.
I'm in charge of the transfer of the li-zhi.
Li Zhishi?
What does it have to do with me?
I don't care what you do.
I'm telling you,
I don't understand.
When you go out,
you can ask around.
Look at the background.
Be careful. You'll regret it if you lose your job.
I'm so proud of my job.
You're jealous?
No.
You think I can't thank you?
Who's disturbing me?
Yang Xiaowei, this is the one.
I'm Li Zhishi, a saint.
Shut up.
Look, the 9-point-1 is the one
with the 3-point-1.
Li Dashi.
Yang Xiaowei.
You're so lucky.
Su Lang, you've read it.
This is not your double-layered ink.
It's not my double-layered ink.
It's my Anxi incense.
The transfer of the li-zhi
has been passed down to the sea.
It can be kept for 8 minutes.
Except for my Su Liang,
in the Linan,
no one can do it.
I'm not a fan of the
Su Liang.
I'm a fan of the Su Liang.
No one can do it.
Amita, you've changed
my double-layered ink
and stole my Anxi incense.
Su Lang, I respect you for
making you smoke.
If you're shameless,
you're too disappointed.
If so,
don't blame me for not giving you the li-zhi.
What can you do to me?
I won't sell this ink.
What can you do?
I'll pay you.
Okay.
You're not worth ten yuan.
Are you a real businesswoman?
Can I buy it?
I won't sell it.
Don't be angry.
Didn't you mess it up?
Think about
how you treated me last time.
I took the paper to collect the debt.
I was about to sell it.
You jumped out and sold it.
You became a public figure.
You turned my paper
into a paper.
You didn't give me
a little face.
Didn't I tell you?
You're a fortune teller.
You're a lucky guy.
I don't want to sell it.
I'll sell this ink.
I won't sell it.
This time, Mr. Su
took the paper to collect the debt.
He asked me
where is your paper?
The paper
was given to Mr. Su
by the paper.
It was used by the paper.
It can be passed through.
Mr. Su
was enough for you to do this.
You were a merchant
who was a fortune teller.
You should know
that a fortune teller
who has broken the rules
is going to be in trouble.
You broke the rules
today.
Are you going to do it?
I won't sell it.
I'll announce it.
All the double-decked dreams
will be used as a fortune teller.
The special supply of goods
is the fortune teller.
This is the dream of fortune tellers.
You're a fortune teller.
Today,
I'm here.
You're going to break another double-decked dream.
That's going to be a lifetime.
A lifetime.
I sold half of my assets.
I'm going back to the south.
I just want to do my own business.
It's not dangerous for you.
But you
have to hold my nose
and hold my neck.
I'll be your fish
when I walk away.
You're young and beautiful.
But you're too hard-hearted.
You're in trouble.
You're a merchant.
You're a fortune teller.
The future of fortune tellers
will never have bright light.
Su Lang.
This is not a place
where you're being selfish.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
I found a double-decked dream.
It's a pre-made one.
The bottom is...
What should we do now?
Su Lang.
Listen to me.
Do you really want to do business?
Of course.
Su Lang's goods are not lost.
I'm sorry.
Su Lang.
What did you say?
Did you forget?
Your goods have been shipped
and put in the warehouse in the west.
My goods have been shipped?
Put in the warehouse in the west.
I... I forgot.
The next person told me
that looking for a warehouse
is in the west.
I forgot.
I forgot the silver and silver.
I misunderstood.
Your Majesty.
I apologize.
Su Lang.
Since the misunderstanding has been solved,
the five members of the Chamber of Commerce
are here today.
Let's welcome them back together.
Welcome.
What are you doing here?
Amida.
Don't be like Su Liang.
Even if she comes back,
she won't be able to move your place.
Amida's name is not what you should call her.
Hangshou.
I'm sorry.
Do you think I will care about Su Liang?
I'm just curious about Li Zhishi.
I had to get a Li Zhiyuan.
She turned him into a jade.
She ruined my business.
She should have lost her life
to kill fish.
Let's not be afraid of this.
Let's not block Hangshou's way.
You do it.
I... I...
I was just trying to make Hangshou happy.
When did Hangshou become so wild?
It's all my fault.
Hangshou let me be a victim.
I wonder if he can give me a chance.
Mr. Han.
Hangshou is in a bad mood today.
Please go back.
Mr. Han, please.
I'll be back in a few days.
I'll ask for your permission
when Hangshou is in a good mood.
Goodbye.
Hangshou.
He's a man.
He's not confident.
He thinks he can match you.
Okay.
It's the new year.
These old people are all so kind.
Su Liang is back today.
I need someone like him to help me.
It's so late.
I'm not back yet.
How about I go out and buy some medicine for Qin Lang?
Wait a minute.
I think he'll be back soon.
You don't have to believe me.
I was in a bad mood today.
I didn't expect that
you're a good-for-nothing.
You're a good-for-nothing.
Is there anyone in the government?
I don't know.
Amita's father is a good-for-nothing.
He was a good-for-nothing.
Now, he's a good-for-nothing.
He's a good-for-nothing.
It's hard to live a good-for-nothing.
I'm not a good-for-nothing.
Although I'm a good-for-nothing today,
I'm a good-for-nothing.
Of course.
Can you give me your double-layered questions?
I'll do it if you like it.
Thank you, Mr. Su.
I'm grateful to you.
I'm so grateful to you.
Are you polite or sincere?
Of course, I'm sincere.
If you're sincere,
can you give me some money?
Not money, but head.
Head?
What's head?
I'm a good-for-nothing with you.
Come on, let's go.
You're a good-for-nothing.
How's it going?
The old people are all so nice.
It's hard to be honest.
Thanks to your help and guidance,
I've learned so much about business.
That's why I've established the government.
Okay.
Remember, if they dare to bully you,
tell them to put their teeth down.
Who dares to bully me?
Actually, I've been getting into trouble lately.
If this matter is successful,
I can lead the people to move to Linnan.
At that time, no matter who's alive,
if they want to leave the sea,
they have to head down.
This is the garden of our family.
Then I'll stay by your side.
I'll help you clean up the garden.
Okay.
Do you want to make the sales of the company go back to Linnan?
No, that old fox.
At that time, my aunt was a businessman.
She couldn't look at me.
She didn't let me touch her business.
I didn't let her go to the port.
But you know what?
Her several sales ships were on the sea.
But then, the typhoon came.
The old man was stupid.
He was like a little fox.
He was late.
I heard that he went to the Shen family with a big family.
He went back to the old family.
Fortunately, the whole sea is ours.
You're afraid of him being the god.
Aunt, you're back.
Brother.
The medicine.
How is it?
Is it better?
I bought the medicine.
I have to take care of it.
I'll go get the medicine tomorrow morning.
You bought the medicine?
Yes.
You didn't bring it back?
You've been doing this for a long time.
I finally understand my sister's feelings now.
Why should I mention your sister?
Can't I?
Why?
You don't want to admit that you've made a mistake?
Didn't my sister change your life to a lesson?
You're sick.
Why are you angry?
Come back.
If you can really take Lv Zhi back to Chang'an,
why should I stop you?
I don't want you to live.
You're a born-in-law.
You can do anything.
But you have to take Lv Zhi back.
Will my sister die?
Can I be like this?
Let you be the one who's always the one who's good at math.
I want you to leave.
I'm afraid you'll be in trouble.
You'll be the one who's left with no money.
You're the one who's left with no money.
I want to stay.
I want to stay here.
I'm willing to take this job.
I want to eat Lv Zhi.
Is that me?
I don't want to go back to Chang'an to watch the show.
I don't want to see my child grow up every day.
Will he get married and have a good life?
He must be waiting in the yard every day
to wait for the osmanthus tree to bloom.
He doesn't know that it's a dead tree.
He doesn't know that his aunt is a dead man who can't live for six months.
I want to stay.
Yes.
I'm a life-saving man.
I only know how to make flowers and plants.
I'm not in a hurry.
I was cheated by my classmates.
I'm willing to take this job.
I'll stay.
I saw a little hope.
I want to catch this hope and go back to see the show.
You're still in a hurry with me.
Where's your hope?
Did you see it?
You're holding it.
I'm already sick and sick.
What if I die tomorrow?
What if you let go of your dead body?
What if I die?
Do you think you can live and live?
We're both dead.
What if he's a lonely and helpless man?
We'll be cursed by the gods tomorrow.
How can we go to see my sister?
Stop arguing.
Be careful.
Yes.
There's still a living one.
Tell me where I went.
Go!
Who's there?
After the storm, the waves have gone away.
Open the door.
The case is over.
The new witness is still in the forest.
I came to the Wolf King.
I've been thinking about the Wolf King.
Didn't he send a strong army?
How could he kill Chu Chongwei alone?
This man is a man of the past.
He's a man of the past.
He killed Chu Chongwei alone.
Some people feel that he's just a man of the past.
If you say that, I'll be exposed.
There's still a chance for the Wolf King.
You can tell me.
When I came back from the horse,
I didn't find his trace.
He must have gone to the mountain to hunt for the sand.
The Wolf King must still have time to finish the left.
You're not his opponent.
I'm not going to let him go.
What if I give up?
If the Wolf King leaves halfway,
Mr. Kong Lang will not let the Wolf King leave the forest.
I'll take care of you.
Calm down.
This way.
Brother.
Come on.
Why are you so early?
It's bright.
You and I are in no need to go to the forest.
What's the matter?
Of course it's about the transaction.
Don't worry.
I don't know what you're doing.
I'm staying at the same house with Li Zhi.
I'm always looking for him.
He's always looking for Li Zhi.
He's always looking for him.
He's not a leftist.
Since you've been watching me closely,
we're in trouble.
Come on.
Have some.
I can't eat.
I'm out of the house.
It's okay.
This is a special thing about Lingnan.
This is Lingnan.
It's not longer than Chang'an.
It's a big deal.
You have to finish your breakfast first.
Dorg, you come with me.
Don't give him.
Since you've lost your mind,
let's just have a talk.
I'm sorry.
No, listen to me.
He's dead.
Dead?
How can he be dead?
He's dead.
He's not dead?
No.
Where did he go?
He's dead.
Ling,
it's no use if you go to the chicken farm.
He's a chicken farm.
If you go into the chicken farm,
he'll be stuck in the field.
He won't get hurt.
How can he be dead?
Is it because of the food?
The chicken farm
is not as important as the chicken farm?
I'm right.
It's the same thing.
I'll buy him a chicken.
I'll buy you a chicken.
I usually
don't talk about the chicken.
I'm not talking about chicken.
I'm talking about money.
Of course,
this chicken farm is important.
But
if he goes into the chicken farm,
he won't be a chicken farm anymore.
Who is he?
He's a master of the chicken farm.
Run.
Chicken farm.
What do you mean?
It's father's idea.
Chicken farm?
Chicken farm.
The End
What do you think?
It's a good idea.
Come on.
Report.
The important thing is
that we don't have to deal with the emergency.
I'll ask
the one who's on the right
to wait for him.
The one who's on the right.
Look at him.
Brother Gu Yun.
We can't tell.
What's wrong?
The End