It's so noisy.
It's your straightforward attitude
that really gets me fired up.
Will beating me up really
make you feel better?
I'm just worried about you, Hayakawa...
Shaken, are you?
Konno-chan...
Do you want to have sex with me?
Have sex.
What's with the way he gets angry?
"Depth of Field"
(Episode 3)
Hayakawa, you're really late.
Huh?
What's wrong?
I get it.
Did you try to hit on a girl who already
has a boyfriend and end up getting punched?
Yeah, that's pretty much it.
I want to use it as a necktie, too.
Are you Hayakawa's
junior from middle school?
Yes.
I want to know what happened
with Hayakawa back then.
Did something happen to him?
I don't know everything either.
I think it'd be quicker if you
just ask Hayakawa directly.
Do you think he'll talk about it?
Hayakawa has a friend he's been making music
with since they were kids. That's Yamashita.
- How is it?
- Hmm... it's too hard.
- You're back.
- Yeah, I'm back.
Dad, welcome home.
Dad, help me, I can't play the chords.
Can't do it?
Alright, come over here.
Let me take a look.
Not bad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Impressive, really impressive.
All the chords came out!
You must have practiced for a long time.
- I really practiced for ages.
- Did you really practice that long?
I've probably practiced
for about a thousand hours.
That's incredible! I
could never pull that off!
- It's about time to head home, isn't it?
- Yeah, it is.
Want to practice one more time?
Well then... make sure you
practice hard when you get home.
Because there's not much
difference from before.
Okay.
Do you want to go to the
amusement park later?
How about we grab a bite to eat first?
Not bad, where should we go eat?
A new place just opened up in front of
the station recently... What was it again?
Gyudon place.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! I've been
wanting to try it for a while.
Do you want to eat there?
- That place always puts in a ton of bean sprouts.
- Really?
Alright, I'll let everyone know too.
Thanks!
Right now, only Yama-chan understands me.
Hey, you must be hungry,
right? Come over to my place for dinner,
and we can get some
practice in while we're at it.
- Yeah, sure.
- Awesome!
Even if you say that.
It's not that we don't want to practice at home.
It's just too noisy, and my
parents won't allow it.
Hayakawa must be pretty well-off, huh?
I heard his dad is a professor
at a music university, too.
It's only natural that he has a
place where he can practice.
Don't hold us to the same standards.
Seriously.
Yamashita, you really
do get along with him, huh.
You really are best buddies. I could never do that.
We're not best friends.
I... It's not like I'm with
Hayakawa because I like him.
Huh?
Haven't you two always been really close?
Because... his family has a piano.
If my family had one, I wouldn't have gone to his place.
I wouldn't have wanted to
hang out with him, either.
-For real?
Um... if Hayakawa hears that...
So what does that even mean…
What did you just say?
Ah! So you're saying you're
not with me because you like me?
That's right.
But...
Weren't you only with me
because you felt sorry for me?
Always looking down on me, the pathetic one
with a terrible relationship with my parents.
That's not it at all.
So that's why you gave up the piano
for me and started playing guitar yourself.
That's really not how it is.
I just genuinely like the way
Yama-chan plays the piano.
What does that even mean?
Learning music in such
a privileged environment.
You've actually been pitying
me all along, haven't you?
So what am I supposed to do?
What should I do?
You just don't get it.
As long as you don't
give up that environment.
I... was just thinking, no
matter what form it takes,
as long as we can keep
making music together...
Are you serious when you say “always”?
So disgusting.
He hasn't come to club practice since then.
But, I...
I thought that starting high school
and being in a new environment...
Maybe...
I see.
Thank you for being willing to tell me.
Mind if I borrow this guy for a moment?
I want to apologize for
what happened last time.
Sorry.
If there's nothing else you
want to say, I'll head back now.
About that guy named Yamashita.
You.
You gave up music just to
understand how he felt, didn't you?
But... you really haven't given up at all.
- I've already given up.
- I haven't given up.
- Gave up.
- Didn't give up.
I told you, I've already given up!
Well then...
Is it really that funny to laugh at me?
No, I'm not laughing at you. I
just think it's really interesting.
You're really something.
Doing what you love and
being understood for it.
You've never thought about
giving up photography, have you?
No.
You're really annoying.
I don't want to have anything
to do with you anymore.
Hey! Don't be mad!
- What kind of face is that? Are you about to cry?
- No way!
You know, your expressions keep changing.
It's really entertaining.
When I'm with you, I
just start acting weird.
Negative emotions just keep bubbling up.
And then I end up feeling
really miserable about myself.
Yeah.
That's nice.
You look really happy.
I wish I could be like you, too.
Even after doing something that bad.
But I still don't want to be disliked.
But...
Do what you love.
But I'll end up being disliked.
So... I have to give it up.
Stop worrying so much about
whether people will dislike you.
What you're feeling isn't
the whole picture, is it?
There are still people out there
who love your music, Hayakawa.
The most important thing is
you really like it yourself, don't you?
Alright then.
It's not about giving up for someone else.
But rather, it's about
making choices for yourself.
You belong to yourself, don't you?
I belong to myself.
Alright, alright, alright!
Easy, easy, easy!
I told you, don't do that.
Konno-chan... I'm about to get mad.
Are you going to cry?
I'm not going to cry.
Stop messing around!
Alright!
Let's take a nap.
The weather today is perfect for a nap.
About what happened before...
So fast...
I'm really sorry.
And then...
Once again... I'm really sorry.
You're back.
It's pretty rare for you
to come into this room.
Oh, is that the one I gave you before?
Yeah.
Can't break this bad habit.
That's good, then.
There's definitely someone out there who
can love even this bad habit of Shuichiro's.
That's what Mom was
thinking when she gave it to you.
Let me explain the conversion
formula and the rewriting formula for d.
The condition for a in d is that it
must be a positive number, not just 1.
For some reason
things that used to seem so
ordinary now look completely different.
Sorry, Hayakawa, can I borrow
your red pen one more time?
Hayakawa, has anything
good happened to you lately?
Huh...? No, not at all.
Do you have someone you like?
- You really have someone you like?
- Really?
No, no, no! Every girl likes this guy.
So there's no way!
I'm really sorry.
And then...
Once again... I'm really sorry.
This time... please don't hit me again.
(Next Episode)
If it's just me alone, I don't think I can
keep playing music like this anymore.
Hayakawa's been in pretty good form lately.
Is he dating a girl or something?
We're supposed to be friends,
but it doesn't really feel that way.
That's exactly how I feel.