[birds twittering]
[gentle music playing]
[keys clatter]
[phone beeps]
[woman] Hi, Luna!
I know you're supposed to be asleep
right now, so don't answer this.
But, I just wanted to remind you,
I'm gonna call you later
from the auditorium.
And no worries, though,
if the timing doesn't work out.
I can video call when
we go home for lunch.
Love you, Luna, and good night.
I mean, good morning, and sleep tight.
[gentle music swells]
[gentle music fades]
[distant roadway noise]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[woman] Hello, Luna. How are you?
Did I wake you?
No, I'm already up.
Actually, I've been working.
[woman] Good. We need you
to come to the office.
We have some questions about
the draft you sent over.
The physics textbook.
Okay, sure.
I'll be there.
[woman] Is there a problem?
No, no, no, it's fine. I'll be there.
Okay.
Then I'll send you an email
about the date and time.
-[Luna] See you.
-See you.
Thank you.
[groans]
[chill music playing]
Nope. You were crying the whole time.
I barely watched the movie because
I was just laughing at you.
Hey.
-[Kai] Belle.
-Hi.
I just missed your sister's cooking.
Gross.
Join us.
Have you eaten?
Wow. Do you even live here?
I'll eat later. I lost my appetite.
[door closes]
[Belle] Hey.
So, do you mind looking through these?
Yeah, sure. Sure.
Um, yeah. In my free time.
You know, I feel bad that I ask you
to do this all the time
when I should be paying you.
No, no, it's okay.
For the kids, right?
Why don't you just come work for us?
I like the job I have now.
Yeah, I know. But it's like…
Okay.
We already broke up so I can say this.
And I mean this
in the best way possible, okay?
I feel like you're wasting your potential.
Well, like you said, we broke up, so…
Okay, okay.
I can take a hint.
But, if you ever change your mind…
About?
About the job.
Or, you know, about us.
You know where to find me.
[gentle music playing]
[gentle music continues playing]
[music slowly fades]
[woman] We left at 10:15
when I wanted to leave at 10
so we didn't get time to get coffee again.
You know how Mom is. She moves so slowly.
But, I'm so happy!
It's such a great feeling, it's different.
It's like the universe pushed me
to graduate.
And it feels so good to achieve
something, you know?
Mm. I'm so proud of you. Congrats, Li.
I'm actually so hungry.
You know, I haven't eaten all day,
and Mom prepared a feast
with all my favorites.
Wow, sounds good.
How about you?
Don't you ever think about…
about graduating?
Yeah, but…
It's not the same for me
as it is for you, Li.
So…
But things are changing, right?
And there are other ways.
Why are we talking about me?
It's your day today so we should be,
you know, focusing on you.
So… [laughs]
[Lia] Just because you're different,
you don't have to hide yourself
from the world.
[Luna] Yeah.
I have to go, Li.
Sorry, I just have so much work to do, so.
[Lia] Wait, Luna.
Sorry. I didn't mean to.
[Luna] No, no. It's fine, it's not…
It's not about that.
I just have a lot to do.
But, yeah, I just wanted to say
congratulations, okay?
Okay. I love you.
[Lia] Bye!
[call ends]
[sighs]
[Kai grunts]
Boy problems?
-Yup.
-[Harry sighs]
How about you?
Girl problems?
Yup.
Fine, ladies first.
I met her at the station the other night.
Was she a bitch?
How did you know?
Bitchy girls are your type.
Hey, watch it!
You like guys who look like they're dumb.
Wow.
Ouch.
So, she went there to claim a prize,
but
she left before I even got her name.
Okay. So hopeless case?
Hopeless case, your ass.
Rude.
It's so hard.
I'm not sure if he likes me.
I'm sure he does.
How would you know?
I just do.
Everyone likes you.
[sighs deeply]
It's so hard to be gay
in the 21st century.
You're such a drama queen.
Help me.
Please.
Does he listen to my show?
Really? That's your question?
Not, is he a registered voter?
Is he homophobic or a misogynist?
There are a lot of
deal-breakers, you know.
I have an idea.
Join me at the station later?
No, thanks. It's so boring there.
You're so mean.
Is that a side effect
of your one-sided love?
Fine.
Make sure he's listening.
[gentle music playing]
-[Harry] Joe.
-Harry.
Where are you going?
I was laid off.
What?
Advertisers are pulling out
so they're cutting costs.
Have you heard anything?
No, I haven't.
This is my girlfriend, Jenny.
What happened to you?
Shark attack.
In Cebu.
When I was twelve.
OMG, babe! I knew it.
We should never go swimming again.
How did it happen?
I tried fighting back
since I have a green belt in taekwondo.
When it started biting my legs,
I punched it really hard
so I could escape.
You're so brave.
You know, I can't live like that.
Uh… we'll get going now. Come on.
Wait, babe. Can you take a picture of us?
-Huh?
-Just one.
You're so inspirational.
-[Joe] Harry, sorry.
-I have a lot of work to do, sorry.
Sorry, Harry.
Come on, babe.
[Joe] Bye, Harry.
Take care.
[Joe] Good luck.
[Jenny] Just one photo…
-[Joe] Stop it.
-Thanks.
[gentle music fades]
[Wendy] Luna. Hello. [laughs]
Did you get it?
[clatters]
Where's my prize?
You need to come back during office hours.
You should've claimed it earlier.
Really? Wow.
Besides, it's too early for me.
What a bitch.
[Harry] Imagine this.
You're dating someone for three months.
And then you find out
they like pineapples on their pizza.
[laughs]
Some things are really hard to accept
and you can't explain why.
I know it's shallow,
but, that's exactly what
a deal-breaker is, right?
It's like a personal preference.
[Harry, muffled] Now, we'll be reading
your own deal-breakers.
Not religious.
Doesn't support local music.
[muffled] Takes too long to reply,
a deal-breaker, I see.
Being a snob.
Okay, that's a given.
[Harry on radio]
Those are basic deal-breakers, but
here, we have something
a bit deeper from B-BOY-C.
He says this is a deal-breaker for him:
bad hygiene and lack of ambition.
Agree, agree.
You need someone
that you can grow with, right?
Bordaqueen says that
one deal-breaker for her
is public confessions.
I get it. It makes sense.
Some people are more shy
about these things.
But, you all know that
I'm a hopeless romantic.
I love grand gestures.
And, I think it's better
to let people know
who my crush is so they can back off.
[muffled] So, now, we have a guest
here in the studio.
We're going to help him out
with something.
And what he wants to know is…
Whammy, if you're listening.
[muffled] Kai has
a really big crush on you.
Does he have a chance with you?
Yes, guys! Whammy said yes!
My brother isn't a hopeless case.
[Kai] Yeah!
And since we're not a family of cowards,
well, not anymore,
it's my turn.
[normal voice] To the girl I met
at the station the other night.
Wendy's friend who is really nice.
[Harry on radio] I'll be waiting.
I hope you come.
-Oh my God!
-[Harry] Because…
Because…
I have a huge crush on you.
[Harry on radio] Even if you're a bitch.
[Wendy] Hey!
Hey, Luna!
Did you hear that?
She likes you!
What are you still doing here?
Shouldn't you be running to her?
Luna!
Maybe I won't.
Why not?
She's not your type?
Bad first impression?
No.
Actually,
I like her.
There you go!
What are you still doing here?
Don't keep her waiting!
You don't want to?
-If you're not going to, I will.
-Hey!
-Let me call her.
-Give it back!
-Hello? Harry?
-Give it to me!
-Hey, I like you.
-Stop it!
-[clatters]
-[Wendy laughing]
Don't worry, I'll take care of this, okay?
Come on, have some fun.
-You should go.
-Okay. Okay.
Believe in love!
-Here you go.
-Fine, give me back my phone.
Here. Go, go, go!
Don't forget my prize, okay?
Luna! Bye-bye! [chuckles]
I'M EXCITED
Hey. Happy?
Super.
Thank you.
It's okay.
-Maybe she fell asleep.
-[Harry scoffs]
Or worked overtime.
Or maybe her radio is broken.
[Harry laughs]
Yeah, sure.
It's okay. It's her loss.
Okay.
You're right. I'm a catch.
-Right?
-Of course.
So, when's your date with Whammy?
Maybe, after exams?
Wow, responsible.
Let's pretend I believe you.
Hi.
[gentle music playing]
Uh… Harry.
I'm a huge fan.
I forgot to tell you the other night.
Thanks.
Usually, my listeners fall asleep on me,
so
I'm glad there's someone
who listens until the end.
[Kai] Um, anyway, let's go?
Uh… um…
Have you eaten?
[bright music playing]
[music ends]