[Fangs of Fortune]
[Episode 16]
Zhu Yan.
Don't forget.
It was you who led me out of the Wilderness.
Only then did I get to see the vast world.
The mortal world is noisy and bustling.
What's so good about it?
Why must we come here?
And every time I accompany you to the mortal world,
I have to get this stamp.
It's so annoying.
Hey,
look.
What's this?
♫The trees and grass of the world sway with the wind♫
It looks really pretty.
Dear customer,
♫Beneath the bodhi tree, dust gathers♫
this is not a hairpin.
♫The good old days are gone for good like that lantern in my dream♫
♫See immortals enter Penglai♫
Let's go back.
What's so fun about this?
This is so much fun!
♫The northern wind blows from beyond the mountains♫
You can't find these in the Wilderness.
Who cares?
♫Along the icy river, it drifts into my dreams♫
Sir, this is a paper windmill.
It spins when the wind blows.
♫Drinking wine at the Tongque Terrace♫
-Humans are so smart.
-Human are so incompetent.
♫Even the stars feel close enough to touch♫
♫Life and death happen in an instant, but love and hate can endure for a long time♫
They go to all this trouble to make such things
just to play with the wind.
♫Beyond cause and effect♫
In the Wilderness,
most of us demons could do this with just a breath.
♫The heavens endure, the world remains eternal♫
That's why I say they're clever.
Without magical powers,
♫Rock and moss♫
they can still come up with such methods.
Why are you always taking their side?
♫Are watching♫
♫A lone boat drifts through the vast world, vanishing into mist♫
Why not?
♫Its sound fading away♫
♫I wish♫
♫The sorrow of parting stayed beyond the river, and that we did not share the same mountain and moon♫
♫Deep love, yet fate runs shallow♫
Heaven and Earth are divided.
Since they are two different realms,
they must follow their respective natural laws.
Humans are born ignorant,
so they need to learn principles.
Demons are naturally combative,
so they need to be restrained.
Baize Goddess.
I'm tired of your
hypocritical words.
Subject all things to freedom
and natural selection.
That's the right way.
Li Lun.
Have you ever thought that
once the Wilderness is destroyed,
the lesser demons with weak spiritual energy
won't be able to take human form at all?
Along with the Wilderness,
they will be doomed too.
The great path is hard to achieve.
Sacrifices are inevitable.
Once the Star Formation collapses,
it will be beyond repair.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
your doomsday has come.
I know.
If you don't die,
I can't possibly die before you.
Alright.
Please make sure you keep your word.
Let me die first.
Ying Lei.
I'm counting on you tomorrow.
The future of the Wilderness
is in your hands now.
I will do my best.
But
I still can't believe it.
Zhu Yin and my grandpa were close friends for so many years.
Why would he also...
When I first met Zhu Yin,
I saw that his whole body
was surrounded by an unrelenting malicious energy.
No one knows about malicious energy
better than I do.
Mr. Zhuo.
Ying Lei's safety
is in your hands now.
But remember,
don't come too early.
I still want to hear
what they're really up to.
Then how do I judge if it's early
or not?
Wait for my signal.
Ying Lei, go quickly!
Mr. Zhuo,
take care of yourself.
Grandpa!
I'm here!
Form the array.
The stars align
to stabilize the universe.
Protect!
Zhu Yin.
Who said
I could only struggle alone?
Have you forgotten that
I still have a Mountain God here?
Mr. Zhuo,
you're indeed reliable.
The Ancient Dragon God.
When it opens its eyes, it's daytime.
When it closes its eyes, it's nighttime.
It seems you've finally realized it.
Wen Xiao.
You've read thousands of books,
how did you not foresee this?
Zhu Yin can not only summon wind and rain,
and illuminate the nine dark and mysterious lands,
but also control the alternation of day and night,
making the night
arrive early.
Look,
isn't this blood moon
more beautiful than the bright moon of the mortal world?
Jiu.
How are you?
Sister Pei.
Who were those people just now?
They were from Chongwu Camp.
People from Chongwu Camp?
What do they want?
I don't know.
I was about to ask them what they were doing
when you appeared.
Jiu?
Sister Pei!
Then I was knocked unconscious.
The blood moon.
Zhao Yuanzhou...
Zhao Yuanzhou!
He's being controlled by the malicious energy!
Great Demon!
Great Demon Zhu Yan!
Zhu Yin,
take action.
Destroy the Baize Token.
Break through the shackles of two realms.
Our goal
is about to be realized.
This is bad.
Li Lun's seal has been broken.
Don't get it wrong.
Your enemy now
is not me.
Blindness.
Zhao Yuanzhou...
Snap out of it.
Zhao Yuanzhou!
Snap out of it!
Ying Lei!
Alright!
Lady Goddess,
hurry and leave!
Look.
This is his true self.
Now that the Baize Token has been destroyed,
Zhao Yuanzhou's malicious energy is out of control.
Prepare for bloodshed in the mortal world.
Why did you teach me?
Didn't I tell you?
I want you to kill me.
I, Zhuo Yichen,
swear to the heavens.
As long as Zhu Yan teaches me
the true way to use the Cloud Light Sword,
I will surely slay him with my blade.
If I break this oath,
may heaven and earth destroy me,
and my soul scatter to the winds.
Zhuo,
this isn't his true intention.
He's just controlled by malicious energy.
If I don't kill him,
everyone will die.
Interesting.
You're in a dilemma.
How will you choose?
Baize Goddess,
you're so protective of Zhao Yuanzhou.
But do you know
that he is also your enemy?
Your master, Zhao Wan'er,
was killed by Zhao Yuanzhou.
He has been deceiving you all along.
Here's a memory for you.
Do you want to see it?
Do you dare to see it?
Li Lun,
do you know your crimes?
What crimes have I committed?
You have committed three crimes.
First,
defying the authority of the Baize Token.
Second,
leaving the Wilderness without permission.
Third,
indiscriminately killing innocents in the mortal world.
Zhao Wan'er,
you are just a mortal.
Who are you to interfere in the affairs of the Wilderness?
I carry the bloodline of Baize,
so it is my duty to protect the Wilderness.
Of course I must intervene.
Then I'll kill you.
Let's see how you intervene then.
Master!
Wen Xiao!
Freeze.
What punishment will he receive?
He will be sealed at his Place of Birth,
repenting every day.
For someone who yearns for freedom like him,
that might be even worse
than having his soul scattered.
You can't bear it?
I almost forgot.
You're close friends.
Go find her.
♫A lone boat drifts through the world♫
♫The heart feels bitter, then sweet♫
♫Can't distinguish night from day♫
♫At the edge of the dreamscape♫
♫Someone is longing for♫
♫Softly calling for♫
♫A past that can't be brought back♫
♫The world echoes with a single sigh♫
♫Love and hate each fills half the heart♫
♫The years are filled with grudges and grace♫
♫The cry of summer cicadas♫
♫The slumber of winter snow♫
♫No idle wishes and no hopeless longing for eternity♫
♫The flower in my palm♫
♫Is everchanging♫
♫Sand slips through fingertips♫
♫Struggling again and again♫
♫The sea of suffering has no end♫
♫The spring breeze asks him♫
♫What troubles turned his hair white♫
But if one day,
you find out I've done something unforgivable,
what will you do?
Most unforgivable things in this world
are because we can't understand why the other person did it,
that's why it's hard to let go.
If you're willing to tell me the reason,
perhaps I might understand you.
If Zhao Yuanzhou really killed Wen Xiao's master,
why didn't you tell us before?
What's the fun in letting you know
the truth like that?
If you hold a grudge against Zhao Yuanzhou,
you'll never be able to connect with him again.
Then the Baize Token can never be merged,
and I'll never be able to destroy it.
To destroy the Baize Token,
we need the most yin malicious energy in the world.
When the blood moon appears,
it will be extremely yin and evil.
That's when we can do it.
But now the Baize Token is split in two,
attached to two different people.
What should we do?
We must make
the two people who possess the Baize Token
be of one mind.
How do you know so much about this?
I'm a person of my word.
Here you go.
You know the whereabouts of the Baize Token?
Where is it?
It's on you.
This is against principles!
Whose principles?
Heaven's, the public's, or the law's?
I only recognize the principles in my heart.
Grandpa!
I don't have time to play with you anymore.
Zhao Yuanzhou will kill all of you anyway.
Zhuo Yichen,
don't forget.
At the final moment,
your Cloud Light Sword can kill him.
I look forward to your decision.
Grandpa!
Mr. Zhuo,
don't hesitate anymore.
Do it.
Zhuo!
What are you doing?
Ying Lei!
The Baize Token has been destroyed.
I have finally succeeded.
However...
Zhao Yuanzhou.
If you really die at the hands of Zhuo Yichen,
it would be somewhat of a pity.
He's not worthy of killing you.
Please make sure you keep your word.
But I
can't kill you.
You don't need to kill me.
Just suppress me.
What should I do?
Zhuo!
What are you doing?
Mr. Zhuo,
it's up to you now!
Apply the blood of
the divine race,
the demon race,
and the Bingyi Clan
simultaneously on the Cloud Light Sword.
This will maximize
the power of the Cloud Light Sword.
Ying Lei!
You still won't let go?
Then I'll cripple both your hands.
A few minor injuries
are nothing to worry about.
This blood
will only make my sword sharper!
Dream...
Zhuo!
Mr. Zhuo!