[Fangs of Fortune]
[Episode 6]
Zhu Yan.
I still like to talk to you face to face.
Zhao Yuanzhou.
Our game
has just begun.
It really was you.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
I did it to save you two.
Did I ask you to save me?
I won't die anyway.
Taking a few hits for you is no big deal.
Who is he?
A scumbag who has to
stay hidden.
What happened to Ran Yi?
Ran Yi was controlled by Li Lun.
Weak demons
are easily controlled by powerful demons.
Zhu Yan,
you're making worse and worse friends.
At least, you used to hang out with the Baize Goddess.
Now,
even these cheap things
can order you around.
You didn't know, right?
He and Zhao Wan'er were as close as brother and sister.
Zhao Wan'er even gave him
the name of her late brother, Zhao Yuanzhou.
Zhu Yan.
Am I right?
One was the noble Baize Goddess.
One was the evil great demon, Zhu Yan.
Because he didn't want others to know
they were close,
every time
he was with Zhao Wan'er,
he would wear a mask.
It really is you.
Zhuo Yichen,
don't you want to
avenge your blood feud?
Although he had no choice,
he did kill your father and brother.
If your dead father and brother
saw you fighting alongside the enemy,
how could they
rest in peace?
I can't kill him.
You can.
With my help,
you can.
Okay.
Humans always love to lie.
I will kill Zhao Yuanzhou.
But first, I need to kill you, an even more evil thing.
If you kill me,
no one will know where the Baize Token is.
You know the whereabouts of the Baize Token?
On the night Zhao Wan'er died,
I was sealed,
but I was the only conscious person at the scene.
Naturally, I saw where the Baize Token went.
Where is it?
It's on you.
You saw it in your dream just now.
Right?
But now, you only have half of Baize Token,
so you can’t use it.
Where is the other half?
Do you want to know?
But I don't want to tell you.
You have to say it anyway.
Ran Yi's dream control magic is useless on him.
Really?
He has been running away for so long.
Today,
let him sink into it.
Zhuo!
Chen.
Today is the Double Third Festival.
Why are you still practicing?
I want to practice my swordsmanship
and help Father and Brother in the future.
The Double Third Festival
is not that fun.
I still remember when you were seven,
you came crying
to complain to me
that the others
weren't willing to play with you.
Because your father
and brother
were anomalies who hunted demons
and dealt with demons all the time.
One day,
they would turn into demons too.
Brother,
you still remember the nonsense I said
when I was a kid?
But after so many years,
you indeed haven't made many friends.
You're always alone.
Brother.
Did I
turn myself into an anomaly?
So-called anomalies
are just what narrow-minded people say
in order to team up together
and bring others down.
They use this
to show their righteousness
and hide their own inferiority complex.
Chen,
we were born with
different responsibilities,
so we are destined to bear
the pain that ordinary people don't have.
Brother.
Did you live like this too?
Do you get lonely?
Maybe one day,
you will meet someone
you see as an anomaly.
At that time, you'll need to make your own judgment.
Your eyes lie.
But your heart
will tell you the answer.
I believe you
will surely meet like-minded companions.
By then,
you won't be lonely anymore.
Will that happen?
Of course.
Remember,
one wing is hard to keep.
With two wings, you can soar.
Zhuo!
Wen Xiao!
Zhuo Yichen!
Wake up!
The Cloud Light Sword can kill demons and destroy evil
without being tainted by demons.
It can break through
all demonic hallucinations.
He can't be woken up.
Because he has never
truly faced his nightmare.
All these years,
he has never had a dream.
So he can't tell if it's a dream or not.
He won't wake up.
Zhuo!
Zhuo Yichen.
If I'm your nightmare,
then pierce me.
My nightmare
isn't you.
It's myself.
I'm afraid of dreaming
and don't have dreams,
so after my brother died,
I never saw him in my dreams again.
What I must overcome
is myself, who has always been running away
and has always been cowardly.
My nightmare
is myself!
♫Someday I'll return to my old hometown♫
♫Wearing old clothes but with eyes shining bright♫
♫Holding brilliance in the right hand♫
♫Biting down on all panic♫
♫Wiping away frost with the left hand♫
♫I finally look up♫
♫You're in front of me♫
♫Blocking the pain♫
♫Heartlessness births a dream♫
♫The dawn stings without hesitation♫
There's no way out of this vast sea
but is in the mortal world.
The galaxy is slim and we hold hands.
Travel together in the world.
Break!
You're useless.
Ran Yi.
Ran Yi!
Miss Qi.
Ran Yi.
No.
She has been parasitized for too long.
Her internal organs
have been corroded by the malicious energy of Li Lun.
Ran Yi.
Do you remember
the first time we met?
Master,
someone took down the notice of your search for famous doctors
and said he can cure the lady's illness.
But he...
He's a little strange.
When we first met,
you covered your face
with fabric
and only revealed your eyes.
But I will always remember
those eyes.
They were like
a lake under the moonlit night sky.
So beautiful.
No.
That wasn't the first time.
My Lady,
why do you always come to the lake?
The books say,
"All rivers return to the sea
and all water returns to the abyss."
But look at this lake.
It's always trapped deep in the forest.
Do you think it can return to the sea?
Who's there?
I was being chased by a demon hunter at the time.
I was severely injured
and was drifting along the water.
In a daze,
I saw you.
I mustered all my strength
to open my eyes
and see you.
You were like the legendary goddess of the Wilderness.
Your eyes were gentle
and compassionate.
Go on.
At that time,
I told myself
I must see you again.
You've swum to many places.
You must have seen a lot of beautiful sceneries.
You're so silly.
You've recovered,
but you still refuse to leave.
You can swim
freely in the world,
but you insist on
being trapped in this cage with me.
The sea is vast.
There's no way out,
but it is in the mortal world.
I remember everything you said,
the scenery you wanted to see,
and all kinds of life you wanted to experience.
So from then on,
every night,
I created a dream for you,
so that the wishes you couldn't fulfill
when trapped behind high walls
could come true.
I was willing to be with you forever like this,
even if I had to abandon my freedom
and just be a fish in your fish tank.
But dream control magic
is demonic, after all.
The longer a person stays in a dream,
the weaker one becomes.
I couldn't create dreams for you anymore.
Master.
The lady is still not getting better.
These past few days,
she's become bedridden.
That's why I became a doctor
to accompany you.
I drew,
wrote,
[Classic of Mountains and Seas]
read travel books,
and talked about the world outside with you.
My favorite phrase
is "dreams come true."
When I say it,
I feel so happy.
Whether you are a human
or a demon,
you are both my path
and destination.
Meeting you
is the happiest thing in my life.
I've never regretted it.
Thank you
for giving me the best dream.
But those dreams
hurt you.
I'm not talking about those dreams.
I mean now.
This moment.
Ran Yi committed suicide.
He destroyed his inner core.
You once said
you would take me to the Wilderness,
to your hometown.
Yes.
I'll show you the trees of heaven
and the edge of the sea.
Master said
♫The hazy dusk approaches♫
death
is when someone
♫The old days are sinking and weighing heavy on my heart♫
goes to a place far, far away
♫A great dream covers new clothes♫
♫Sleeping without waking♫
and never comes back.
♫The blue lake traps♫
♫The reflections of old friends♫
♫The ocean tides rise and fall♫
♫Thoughts are inaudible♫
♫Bitter memories♫
♫Hide in the gap of my heart♫
♫One heart chamber, one window♫
But another friend of mine told me
♫Traces of light♫
that your deceased loved ones
will become stars in the sky.
♫Murmuring breaths♫
♫Like riddles by the pillow♫
She told me
♫I only dare to look at you in dreams♫
not to be sad about the past.
♫Yet I don't utter a word♫
Don't be sad about something you can't resist.
♫Let the spring light hear♫
♫The autumn moon also hears♫
Use all your power
♫Every rainfall♫
to grasp what you can fight for.
♫Is my secret♫
Cherish it
♫Searching memories endlessly♫
♫The drenched past♫
♫Reflects you♫
♫Find you♫
Leave.
If you leave, don't come back!
In the end,
just accept what you can't change.
Like death.
Like fate.
Can't fate be changed?
Do you believe in destiny?
What I want to destroy
is what the Goddess is destined to protect.
This is not destiny.
This is my karma.
I know I can't persuade you,
but I believe
that one day,
you will meet the person who makes you want to live.
She said it's possible,
but I don't think so.
What about you?
Will you die too?
Probably.
[The Great Demon will be with Wen Xiao as long as he lives]
But don't worry.
I won't die easily.
I will always be by your side.
Demons live longer than humans.
[The Great Demon will be with Wen Xiao as long as he lives]
I won't leave you by yourself.
I'm not...
My head.
I'm going to lose my head.
What should I do about my head?
My head!
Mr. Bai Jiu.
Mr. Zhuo
and the others have successfully solved the Water Ghost bride case.
The military order is completed successfully.
Mr. Fan asked me to tell you
not to worry anymore.
Really?
That's great!
Brother Zhuo!
Watch out, Mr. Bai!
Mr. Bai,
why do you carry so many medicinal bottles with you?
The Demon Hunting Bureau has saved ourselves.
Unfortunately,
we couldn't save the fish.
At least their last moments were happy.
Is happiness important?
Of course.
Actually, happiness isn't important.
You're a demon.
You don't understand.
It's because I'm a demon
that I understand
happiness is not important.
Because every human emotion
is important.
Joy, anger, sorrow, delight,
grief, happiness, union, and separation
converge into a long river.
This long river
is called "a lifetime."
Did you know?
For us demons,
each emotion requires
hundreds or thousands of years
of cultivation
to experience.
So many demons
go a lifetime
without being able to shed a single tear.
So,
stop being obsessed with making everyone happy.
You're still so weak.
Are you worried?
Of course.
Is this worry
also
an important experience for you?
Yes.
Then was pretending you didn't know me
and watching me being confused and ignorant
also an important experience?
Zhao Yuanzhou,
you broke your promise.
Which one?
The same pace
or being colleagues?
You said
you would come to me.
Great Demon,
where are you taking me?
Tiandu.
Aren't you going to keep taking care of me?
I will definitely come to you.
Haven't I
come to you now?
Then why
didn't you tell me who you were?
Think of it as...
Getting to know each other again.
♫A lone boat drifts through the world♫
♫The heart feels bitter, then sweet♫
♫Can't distinguish night from day♫
I will definitely come to you.
♫At the edge of the dreamscape♫
♫Someone is longing for♫
♫Softly calling for♫
♫A past that can't be brought back♫
If you break the contract
you signed with demon blood,
your soul will vanish.
[Zhao Yuanzhou] [Zhu Yan]
I'm willing
to work with her willingly
like her colleague.
Keep it in mind.
It's the most important term.
Zhao Yuanzhou.
Zhao Yuanzhou!
Are you okay?
I think I'm about to die.
Mr. Zhuo's Cloud Light Sword is amazing.
Aren't you a great demon?
How can you die after being stabbed a few times?
It's improper for men and women to touch each other.
Even if you want to die,
don't die in Wen Xiao's arms.
It's okay.
I've lived too long.
I'm tired of it.
What a coincidence.
That's what my name means.
You're annoying like your name.
I bear heavy sins
and should have died long ago.
So, Wen Xiao,
don't be sad for me.
The dead demons
become the sun, moon, and stars.
I can also turn into rain.
From now on, whenever it rains,
it'll be me keeping you company.
Actually, I don't like rainy days.
And didn't you say before
you would stay with me
and you wouldn't die easily?
Zhao Yuanzhou.
You are
ridiculous!
Wen Xiao,
he's lying.
Look.
Mr. Zhuo, are you here to thank me
for saving your life?
It's nothing.
Don't get off-topic.
Why did you
kill my father and brother back then?
Although he had no choice,
he did kill your father and brother.
What did Li Lun mean when he said
you had no choice?
I saw it in my dream just now.
He was controlled by the malicious energy.
He had no choice.
That's why he lost control and killed people.
But killing
is killing.
In this world,
there are too many who have no choice.
Some people become robbers
because of poverty.
They commit evil because they are desperate.
They kill because of hatred.
Ran Yi also started killing because he was
harmed by Master Qi.
But these
can't be the excuse for them to escape punishment.
Don’t worry, Mr. Zhuo.
I’ll pay back my debts
after the Baize Token is found.
I will do
what I promised you.
Alright.
We'll talk about
your grudges another time.
Right now, we have to meet up with Ms. Pei
and go back to report.