I'm sorry, but I'm not sure if I can get a job.
Episode 19
What are you guys doing? What's going on?
It's possible that Lillun is dead.
Did you see Lillun's list when Lillun died?
No. We thought that his list was confiscated by the non-combat.
That's right. Lillun has the ability to sacrifice herself.
Before she died, she must have put her list in the body of someone.
Since then, she has been burned by the non-combat.
She has already been sacrificed by that person.
You are not dead or dead.
You will always kill her.
Kill Zhao Yanzhou.
It's Zhao Yanzhou.
It was Zhao Yanzhou who sacrificed himself at that time.
I'm now a master of the mortals.
It's you.
Go.
I will kill Zhao Yanzhou.
I brought wine here.
But it seems that you can't drink it anymore.
I once made a vow.
I must personally understand your grudges.
All the way here,
I felt that
I was too weak to say it.
I felt that I was too weak to say it.
But
this day is finally here.
It's like a book.
It's a book that has been written.
No matter how many times I look back,
the ending
is the same.
I will kill Zhao Yanzhou.
Are you okay?
The theory is over.
Let's go.
Wait.
Let's fix the white jade.
Otherwise, we will be in danger.
We can't change Zhao Yanzhou.
Right.
The key.
I will kill Zhao Yanzhou.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm afraid of you.
Get down!
Yi Qi Chang, you're still the same.
You always know how to break people.
That's fake.
So many odds now.
Master Lesh, you can fight back and avoid me.
Get me out!
Do you think Yi Bai Biao Chow Dong will win?
I'll prove it to everyone.
Don't leave me behind.
Do you think Yi Bai Biao Chow Dong will win?
Don't be mad.
Get in the house, everyone.
Don't run around freely.
Everyone's quiet.
I'm not sure if I can get through this.
It happens that way.
I'm not sure if I can get through it.
I'm not sure.
it happens that way.
I'm not sure if I can get through this.
Sure, okay?
Fine.
Alright, let's go.
Okay.
I'm going to get through this.
The
open God
Xia medic blood
Little Master, save me!
Brother! Little Master!
You...
You're not Bai Jianghou.
Bai is Li Lun.
It's time.
Until now, you've only seen it.
Damn it.
I'm fooled by you.
When will you use your hands?
I've already put the internal pill in Bai's body.
I'm going to use it with my master.
I underestimated you.
But this is a very good gift.
I just got my body.
I'm not weak yet.
I can't take care of the body at all.
So,
I can only wait for her to enter the dream at night.
Then I can make a move.
Even if that's the case,
it's not enough.
You're like a little boy.
But you're like a little boy.
I want to see if she has time to find you
under the circumstances of the whole Chen Tongji.
Yes.
So,
Ao Yin deliberately shot Xiao Zheng just now
to let you out of the control area.
That's right.
Otherwise,
how can I stop you?
You lied to Master Xiao Zhuo.
You used his sword to kill people.
What are you doing to me?
Master Xiao Zhuo,
I've been doing this for a long time.
The Soul-Demolishing String that I finally made
is a kind of fake medicine made of dead body and grass.
Why did you suddenly come out of the house?
I'm also curious.
I just hope
that I can stay in the grass and hurt you.
You don't have to suffer.
The one who did it is not you.
It's Li Lun.
What is the Soul-Demolishing String?
I've been doing this for half of my life.
I've been listening to the truth.
Don't worry.
This time,
Zhao Yanzhou is still in my hands.
As long as I can take care of Zhao Yanzhou's heart,
he can do anything for me.
He will never remember who he is.
Naturally,
he will forget you.
From now on,
he will only listen to you.
But he has a strong will.
He is no longer his curse.
He is the phoenix of the world.
The phoenix of the world.
You can't bear to let go anymore?
That's right.
If I see it more, I won't die.
But Baijiu will die.
The End
I raised this snake moth myself.
It was trapped in the 300 years of Japanese.
I'm going to play this song every day.
It will naturally be with me.
Master Shen,
this time, Zhao Yanzhou will be with us.
The End
Zhao Yanzhou,
I don't want to kill you with the Cloud Sword.
So, I must do it.
The End
This time,
it's for your own good.
The End
Stop, Xiao Zhu.
The Cloud Sword is fake.
Xiao Zhu.
What are you doing?
Baijiu is under the control of the Cloud Sword.
Go out and help them.
Leave the demon to me.
No.
This is the most dangerous.
Don't worry.
Be careful.
The End
Where is Zhao Yanzhou?
He has been in the sea for a thousand years.
Don't worry.
He is fine.
The End
If you are real,
it's good.
But,
this is my little Xia.
Do you think
I will do the same to you?
No.
But it won't hurt that much.
So,
I am not doing it?
What do you think?
Bai Ze Li.
I am done.
It's done.
You seem
different from before.
It's been so long.
It will be different.
Is it?
The End
It's been a long time.
How can I help you?
You said it's true.
It's been a long time.
The End
Little girl.
Little Chou.
Is it you?
Chao Si.
Look.
I am not your little girl.
I am Li Lun.
I want you to know the truth.
Look carefully.
Who killed you?
The End
I hated this palace so much.
I didn't expect
one day
I would take back
it and kill it.
The End
Thank you, father.
Little girl.
I will kill you, little girl.
Did you know
that Dragon King
attacked the Seven Kingdom Hades?
다른生 stood behind
squared soldiers
and attacked the Seven Kingdom Hades
After the last few hours of the dust,
his body will never be able to come out again.
The last few hours of the dust,
After the last few hours of the dust,
his body will never be able to come out again.
The last few hours of the dust,
I feel very safe.
Are you afraid of me?
Lord Xiao Zhu is here.
And Yun Guangjian, who is your best friend.
I'm not that afraid.
I'm sorry.
It's definitely not a problem.
Lord Xiao Zhu.
You can't eat the body.
My little brother is bleeding.
I can't eat the body.
Give me back the ball.
I'm sorry.
Lord Xiao Zhu.
Yu Lun.
You're really hard.
I let you get away with it.
How could I die in front of you?
Lord Xiao Zhu, wake up.
I won't talk to you again.
Okay?
Lord Xiao Zhu.
Zhao Yanzhou.
I'm really grateful to you.
If you hadn't died in front of me,
how could I have been so perfect.
So much for the body of a ghost.
You finally did something that made me happy.
You and Wen Zongyu did it
for the body of a ghost.
You know it very well.
Once you remove the phoenix from the god's eyes,
your real life will be ruined soon.
You know me well.
But it's weird.
Wen Zongyu is so cruel.
Even his disciples can sacrifice.
I've always told you.
The human body of Ru Xiao is stronger than the monster.
It's even more cruel.
You always don't believe me.
Wen Zongyu can sacrifice even his disciples.
You and him are not money, not fruit.
How could you not understand this?
Of course I understand.
I'm just going to be his partner.
Li Lun,
do you know his real purpose?
People in the world
are so easy to understand.
They are so hard to understand.
Wen Zongyu is so strong.
He wants to destroy Bai Ze Ling.
He wants to make the Red Demon into a human body.
That way, he can be reborn
in the world.
But Wen Zongyu is too naive.
You are the naive one.
Li Lun,
you've lived for tens of thousands of years.
But you're not as good as a ten-year-old child.
Wen Zongyu has been trying to make up for it.
He's been studying in the dark.
He wants to make the most powerful demon.
He wants to destroy the world with the demon.
He wants the Yellow Dragon to become the empty one.
That's his real purpose.
What did you say?
Eight years ago,
the evil that you and I saw in the world
were locked in the dungeon and tortured.
It was exactly what Wen Zongyu sent people to do.
You and I were both in the dark.
But now,
you're helping the evil.
Li Lun,
you once killed the evil.
You said you wanted to protect the Great Emperor.
You've forgotten.
You lied to me.
You lied to me again.
He didn't lie to you.
What he lied to you
has always been Wen Zongyu.
If you don't believe me,
go to the secret room of Chong Wuyang
and see where you want to go.
The Great Emperor
I too become the wind and have a song to play
When I turn and look into the rain,
I will walk by magn sinners,
I will act first,
during many fruits of the world,
I won't give up my life
I will change the future with the sky
The summer and the winter are not with the wind
The clouds and the moon are with the wind
The small and small poems are a big legend
You said that the world is full of millions
I won't give up my life
I said that the sky is full of millions
The sky is the only one
I will go on a journey with the wind
Love is not a question
Why not make a wish and dream is back