Maybe you're a zookeeper?
bnech
day 1
proverb
I'm sorry, but I'm not sure if I should be able to do that.
I'm sorry.
Let's end this.
Thank you, but I'll ask you to keep an eye out.
I won't be able to do anything.
I'm not sure if I can make it.
I'm not sure.
Of course.
Hold this.
I'm telling you.
Why are you scared?
Brother Wang Zhuo
Do you think Ying Lei will blame me?
Of course not
He is protecting you
One day
You will also want to protect someone
Why do you always hold my bell?
Because holding the bell
I dare to go to the little house
By my side
No matter how scary the front is
I dare to go forward
I will always be there for you
You want to save me?
Sorry
I have no worries
I just want to find
A place where no one can be proud of
The bell is ringing
I can take you home
Who can know the name of the grown-up?
Life is very great
The bell is ringing
I am all safe
Brother Wang Zhuo
I will protect you this time
The bell is ringing
I can take you home
Who can know the name of the grown-up?
Life is very great
The bell is ringing
I am all safe
Who has seen a short tailed bird?
In the rain, it is her dream
Her eyes are not in the way
I only think about
The bell is ringing
I am all safe
Little wine
Brother
You scared me
Father
Wake up
Little son
Father
You know me
It's good that you can wake up
I woke up like this
It's the white-collar
The white-collar
The water is not full
The gold is not in the world
Father
What's wrong?
You can't get up in the body of that young man
No, father
Little son
I will save you
I can't go back
Go save those people
They are the people in you
There is a person in you
Father
It seems that you have to watch me every day
This ungrateful daughter
Yes
I can't leave you for this life
Father
I will never leave you for this life
I can't live like this
Father
There will be someone in the future who will watch you
Take care of you
Father
I
Child
The people of the whole city are becoming the demons
Yes
My tears
Can make the demons normal
As long as the white spirit in my body comes out
Draw into a river
So that everyone can be saved
Master taught me
This is our white spirit
The final magic
The ghost
If you lose the white spirit
You will die
I was poisoned by the poison
I can't live long
Isn't this a better way to die?
I have a better way
You have to say it well
I will die
I will kill myself
But I will never die
When you turn a blind eye
I won't forgive you
Fang Yuzheng
Send her home
You know the source of the white spirit's power?
I've heard that it's not true.
The white spirit doesn't have the source,
but it's the cycle.
The reason for the white spirit is the cycle,
and it comes from the power.
The white spirit is the cycle of the world.
There is a big mess,
and the enemy is the enemy.
The enemy is the enemy,
If you're not there,
how can you get the power?
How can you get the power of the white spirit?
I...
I'm also a part of the cycle of the world.
The stronger the power,
the stronger the power of the white spirit is.
No.
In the spirit of the king of the world,
the future that the dragon has met
is the most important thing I've ever seen.
The white spirit of the soul
is the cycle of the world.
The cycle of the world is the strongest power
in the world.
No.
This is what the god woman should do.
Instead of you.
I've said that
I will make you live on.
Zhe Yuzheng.
I'm not your brother.
Let go of me.
Zhe Yuzheng.
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
Zhe Yuzheng.
Don't cry.
When you wake up,
you still have something more important to do.
Do you know why?
I'm not good at using my own words.
And then I'll throw away the sect and the sister.
Am I not good at it?
Why?
Because I'm not good at it.
Because I only give you one person
to be able to do it on my own.
That's the medicine you use for the person you love.
I think you're a theory.
So I gave birth to you.
When you give me the theory
and your own medicine,
I know you're a spy.
Look.
I've been trying to kill you.
But I finally saved you because I was wrong.
In this world,
the cause and the result are all wrong.
It's always hard to laugh.
I can't laugh.
The life of Xiaojiu is because of your death.
And your life
is because of the death of Lile and Xiaojiu.
Now,
the life of the world needs my death.
And my death
needs your lifetime of sacrifice
and the same responsibility and sacrifice.
It's time to say goodbye.
Our first meeting is your oath.
I will do my best
to protect Tianqi.
As long as Zhu Yan
can give me the real way to the Clouds,
I will definitely kill him and kill him.
I will do my best to protect Tianqi.
As long as Zhu Yan can give me the real way to the Clouds,
I will definitely kill him and kill him.
I will do my best to protect Tianqi.
Zhao Yanzhou,
there is another choice.
There is another choice.
Yinglong,
for the sake of the life,
I am a god.
But there is someone who will give him the title of the evil.
The soldier is considered a living hell.
The living hell is called a god.
But he is a mortal.
The world is so vast and vast.
Do you remember our agreement?
Yes.
Lord Zhao,
this time,
don't be a fool.
Lord Zhao,
I knew you couldn't do it.
So I decided to kill you.
You don't need to choose for me.
This is my own decision.
I will try my best to be the best killer.
You don't need to do it for me.
Zhao,
you still have to do it.
Chen Yuzheng,
Chen Yuzheng.
The poison in my body...
has been sucked away by me.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Very heavy.
Theirtail is severely injured, right?
I know you are sad, but you are crying.
Don't be sad for too long.
I can't bear to let you be sad for me.
Your tears will always be on the bed.
You shouldn't cry for me.
I can't bear to let you be sad for too long.
You won't die easily.
I will always be with you.
You lied to me.
You liar.
I will always be with you.
I met you.
It's like I had a long and sad dream.
I just need to wake up.
I should leave now.
I'm sorry.
I said I didn't mean it.
Zhang Yanzhou
I know each flower is angry with us.
but you can't
let's stand by the Lord in the dark
The long road is slowly and slowly,
it's hard to leave.
Lord Xiao Zhu,
the white goddess's eyes are painted with rain.
The road is full of tears.
Then,
everyone can be saved.
I will make you my god.
I will not let you go.
Your tears
will be buried with a spear.
You shouldn't have left them for me.
The dead demon
will become the star of the sky.
What about you?
I will become a rain too.
In the future,
as long as it rains,
I will be with you.
I will not let you go.
Who will cry for years?
I will be with you.
I will sing the song of the light.
I want you.
I am looking for you.
Let the summer spring stop.
Let the snow stop.
I will stay here.
I will go to the wind.
Finally, the wind blows.
I know where you are.
I will follow you.
I will find you.