My goodness.
Can I take some daggers
to use against barbarian thieves?
What
are you saying?
Yes.
I was sold to barbarians in Shenyang.
I suffered unbearable humiliation there.
I also met Lord Lee.
I was freed thanks to his help.
The humiliation I endured
was not my fault.
If you had asked to divorce because
of that, I would not have given in.
However…
I gave my heart to Lord Lee in Shenyang.
I am sorry.
That is why I am divorcing you.
My lady.
Thank you for everything.
Gil-chae.
No, you cannot go.
You cannot go anywhere now.
Let me go.
If I stay here,
it will get in the way
of Yeong-chae getting married
and Je-nam sitting the state exam.
It will also reflect badly
on Compiler Nam.
I will leave Father in your care for now.
But I will take care of this child.
No.
Do not go.
I will live well.
I will live well
and repay the person who saved my life.
I will contact you when I am settled.
Let's go.
Don't go, Gil-chae.
Gil-chae, don't go!
Gil-chae, don't go…
Is this the place?
Why?
I bought this house
by selling all my jewelry.
Let's eat.
It's no wonder I worry
about my retirement.
I am happy now.
Do you like it?
How should we
live now?
-Good question.
Treason?
Did you say treason?
Sim Gi-won committed treason?
According to the record of his confession,
Sim Gi-won spent thousands of yang
on brewing liquor and slaughtering cattle.
He gathered over 70 strong men
in the mountains behind his house
to practice archery
and plan for the future.
So, Sim Gi-won has been
secretly training private soldiers?
Does he intend to sit
on the throne himself?
It does not seem so.
Then?
Who does he intend to make king?
At first…
he intended to serve
the crown prince in Shenyang
but changed his mind
and decided to support Prince Hoeeun.
PRINCE HOEEUN (LEE DEOK-IN):
GREAT GRANDSON OF KING SEONGJONG
We are tracking down
all of Sim Gi-won's relatives
and those who have fled--
Summon the magistrate
of Uiju for questioning.
The magistrate of Uiju
has no connection to this treason.
-So, why…
-Did the magistrate of Uiju…
MAGISTRATE: PROVINCIAL
GOVERNMENT OFFICE HEAD
…not cover up the fact
that the crown prince
was traveling with hundreds of captives?
What does His Majesty intend?
He is suspicious of the crown prince.
Well, that goes without saying.
But why is he suddenly punishing
the magistrate of Uiju?
It seems His Majesty
is afraid of the captives
following the crown prince.
Why would he fear mere captives?
That is what I am saying.
Who ordered you to bury cursed objects
all over the palace?
Who were you trying to curse?
I do not know anything.
I know nothing about this.
The palace prison guards are trying
to find the mastermind
behind the cursed objects in the palace.
The mastermind?
If you do not believe me,
check the records on the court ladies
executed by the Office of Justice
on orders from the Palace Treasury Office.
The Office of Justice took orders
from the treasury office?
How could an order
as serious as an execution
be delivered by the treasury office
and not the Privy Council?
It seems there were reasons the justice
office could not formally interrogate.
I have nothing more to say.
Someone sent me an anonymous letter.
Far more court ladies
are being interrogated than I thought.
It says many have even died
from severe torture.
Since the nation's king
has become so cruel,
great calamity will soon
befall the country.
Our king is terrified.
Did you know that fear
can turn a person cruel?
So…
go to Joseon.
Forget all the hardships
you endured here in Shenyang…
and live a good life.
Live loudly…
and vibrantly…
like the Gil-chae I know.
I am sorry
for not living that way.
You…
Have you come to die too?
Take my hand.
If this is how it would be,
why did you not let me die back then?
I came to draw water,
but you came to die?
That's right.
I want to die.
I finally made it back alive,
but I was kicked out for being
a disgrace to the family.
It would have been better
to die back then.
Fine.
Do as you wish.
But go die somewhere else.
What are you doing at the well
everyone in the village uses?
Jong-jong.
Do you want to eat before you die?
Thief.
What?
It is you. I have caught you at last.
Let go!
-Let go!
-No.
Why touch something
so hot with bare hands?
If you want to eat, bring firewood.
I'll give you a bowl of rice.
-You are lying.
-I mean it.
But if you get caught stealing again,
I will really punish you.
Don't lie.
What is that?
I made all of these.
When I got divorced,
I took a few as my share.
I wonder how I can sell these
for a good price.
If we sell all of these, what will we eat?
Give me rice.
You said you would.
Hurry up.
Give me one bowl.
We will share it among ourselves.
I am hungry.
Where are your parents?
They are all dead.
The barbarians killed them.
Me too.
I told you that is not the case.
Your mother will surely come for you.
You are lying.
Seung-a, give them more rice.
What?
Oh, right.
Chew well,
okay?
I will give you more.
There is more rice.
Eat plenty.
I will never play baduk with you again.
You have said that 126 times already.
I mean it this time.
I enjoy playing baduk with Your Highness.
You enjoy playing with me?
Then, will you
serve me in bed this time?
Since you make me laugh like this,
how can I not enjoy it?
You said before that when you look at me,
you are sometimes reminded of someone.
Do you still think of her
when you look at me?
Or…
Let us go.
This time I will play a game I can win.
Let us do this.
If I win,
you will stay by my side forever.
You know the regent
treats me very well, don't you?
I can provide you with luxury
and riches for the rest of your life.
Then, if I win,
what reward will you give me?
That will not happen.
Soon, the Qing will conquer
the Central Plains.
Then, all Joseon people
will have to obey the Qing.
That applies
to you too.
See?
What are you doing?
I am a merchant.
I repay people.
I repay those who helped me make money
with more money.
I repay those who caused me losses
with bigger losses.
So,
I must repay the person
who shot me with an arrow.
You wicked,
selfish…
foolish woman.
Because of you…
Lee Jang-hyeon.
But it is strange.
Is it because I am so angry?
Is that why I think of you so much?
What did you mean just now?
Are you angry at me
or do you think of me a lot?
Lee Jang-hyeon.
Stop there.
Stop.
That crazy woman.
How dare a mere woman
demand the position of a prince?
She still thinks
her father is the emperor.
How long will Dorgon keep
the daughter of the former emperor
who had his mother
buried alive by his side?
With the way she is acting up,
Gakhwa will soon be sold to Mongolia.
If she is married off to Mongolia,
no one will care
whether she dies there or is neglected.
I heard her former husband abandoned her
after having fun with her once.
Such men are not worth
getting my hands dirty.
If I tell the regent,
he will have them killed for me.
What is it?
Do you also see me as an easy target
now that my power ties have weakened?
Do not underestimate me.
The regent still needs me,
and I still have
enough power to have you killed.
Your Highness,
I have not
stayed by your side all this time…
because I fear you.
Then, why?
Was it out of pity,
like how you help the captives?
No matter what they say,
you are still a princess.
I am who I am?
Wicked, foolish,
and selfish?
Yes.
That is who you are, Princess.
You are foolish…
and selfish.
But that is why…
Why what?
Your Highness.
-I…
-Enough.
I don't want to hear it.
You pushed me away before,
and you hesitated today,
but someday, you will fall into my arms.
Dorgon will soon send
the crown prince back to Joseon for good.
You will stay, right?
No.
You must stay.
Is that true?
Yes, Your Highness.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
You are returning to Joseon.
Your Highness.
Congratulations, Your Highness!
Your Majesty.
Enter.
Your Majesty, the Qing emperor is
sending the crown prince back to Joseon.
They must be experienced farmers.
That old man
spent his life savings to buy seven fields
but was captured
before he could even sow seeds.
He says his only wish is to farm
those fields just once before he dies.
Looking at him now, it seems hopeless.
It is not hopeless. He can go to Joseon.
Yang-cheon.
The crown prince is returning to Joseon.
He will take
all of us with him.
What?
Hey!
The crown prince is going back to Joseon.
-What?
-Now, we can all go back to Joseon too!
We can go to Joseon?
We are all going back?
-Yes.
-We are going!
Let us go back!
The food tastes good.
I DO NOT HAVE LONG TO SEE
MY FATHER - I WILL WORK HARD
Jang-hyeon.
We are going to Joseon?
Yes.
I finally feel at ease.
These people…
are all going to Joseon, thanks to you.
What did I do?
It is because of you.
Jang-hyeon did not
use to care much about others.
He only helped the captives
because you kept whining about it.
This has delayed the opening
of the Usimjeong Namwon branch.
So, if you think about it,
the reason I am not rich yet is
also because of your meddling, you punk.
If I had become rich earlier,
Jong-jong would not have left so quickly.
But once the Namwon branch opens,
all the Joseon women will…
Right. Put all this away.
You do not care about me at all.
We cannot take
the captives back to Joseon?
Do you know that His Majesty in Joseon
recently punished the magistrate of Uiju?
It was for failing to report in time
that Your Highness
would travel with hundreds
of officially redeemed captives
when you visited Joseon.
The magistrate was punished
because I took captives back?
Yes, Your Highness.
Therefore,
apart from the 150 farmers
who have already been reported,
the hundreds of captives
you privately paid for and hired…
cannot be brought to Joseon.
No.
I promised them.
I promised that when I went to Joseon
I would surely take them with me.
Your Highness.
You must not take the captives with you.
His Majesty in Joseon does not wish it.
Your Highness.
Leave the captives behind?
What are you saying?
We are not leaving them forever.
We will bring them later.
Later?
His Highness is returning
to Joseon for good.
If they do not come with us now,
who knows when the captives will ever
be able to enter Joseon again.
His Majesty…
dislikes the idea
of the captives that have been
under His Highness's care
in Shenyang entering Joseon.
He must be under some misunderstanding.
Trust the crown prince and wait.
Once we return to Joseon,
he will surely clear up
the misunderstanding with His Majesty.
What? He is abandoning us?
He is not abandoning us.
The crown prince
is not that kind of person.
Lee Jang-hyeon.
Since when do you side with the royalty?
I am not taking sides.
Just sit down first.
Okay?
Yang-cheon.
Without the cooperation of the
Joseon court, even if we cross the river,
we will be dragged back to Qing.
Many of the people we have with us
have not been officially ransomed,
and some are escaped prisoners, right?
So, Yang-cheon…
let's go to Joseon first together.
And then later,
once the crown prince gets permission,
I will take responsibility
and bring over all the other captives.
I shall stay here too.
-Yang-cheon.
-Think about it.
They kidnap even normal people
and claim they are prisoners.
Do you think the Joseon people
will be safe in Shenyang
after the crown prince has left?
If people are arrested again
as escaped captives,
how will we stop it?
What if their ears are threaded
or have their ankles cut
and are even killed?
Then I will stay.
So, Yang-cheon--
That will not work.
You must go
and make sure to get
a promise from the crown prince.
I will stay here
and take care of the captives.
You go to Joseon
and get a promise from the crown prince.
You won't abandon me, right?
If everyone leaves,
what will happen to us?
Are they leaving us all behind?
-I knew this would happen.
-When will we ever be able to go?
You said they would take us all!
-Quiet down.
-Yes, be quiet.
It is just doubtful.
Hey!
You may not trust the crown prince,
but do you trust Lee Jang-hyeon?
I trust Lee Jang-hyeon.
So, I shall stay behind too.
I will stay here
and return with all of you.
I promise to take you,
your children,
your siblings,
and your parents…
back to Joseon.
If you stay, then it is fine.
That's right.
We should trust him.
If you stay, it will be all right.
Right.
We'll be able to go eventually.
If we just endure a little longer,
we'll be able to go back.
That is right.
-Your Highness.
-You have decided to stay, right?
Are you leaving?
That woman has already
gone back to her husband.
Yes.
I have no intention of causing trouble
by hanging around a married woman.
So…
if you wish,
I will stay by Your Highness's side.
But
I have a request.
I hear you were kicked out
by your husband?
The truth is I left on my own,
but no one believes me,
so I have given up trying to explain.
You are like me.
Whenever something
bad happens in the palace,
they all blame me,
but I just let them
because I also cannot be bothered.
So, how much
will you sell this dagger for?
That dagger
was engraved after our master blacksmith
dreamed of receiving a peach
from Grandmother Samsin.
They say any woman
who owns this mystical dagger
will give birth to 12 sons
as healthy and strong--
You are making strenuous effort
to make a living.
I guess you have to.
Who would buy a dagger sold by a woman
who was humiliated by the barbarians?
Fine.
I will buy it at a high price.
But there is something you must do for me.
Soon, the crown prince
will return to Joseon for good.
So…
The crown prince
is coming to Joseon?
Lady Jo is giving you work?
What kind of work?
He told me to live loudly and vibrantly.
I will never let him
see me living like this.
Pardon?
The crown prince is coming.
That means
Interpreter Lee and Gu-jam will also…
-He has come.
-The crown prince has come.
See?
He is not coming.
The Qing princess has claimed him,
so why would he come here
when he can live well there?
Just wait and see.
Someday, Lee Jang-hyeon
will be mine.
I guess you are right.
It seems he is not coming after all.
Gu-jam.
You came back.
Your Highness.
Crown Princess.
Father.
Mother.
Come here.
His Highness is smiling.
Are you glad to be back in Joseon?
Do you need to ask?
I grew up here.
This palace is my hometown.
Everyone was happy
to hear they would be going home.
I thought I had no hometown,
so I had nowhere to go.
But I found I too had a place
that I longed to return to.
Sleep well.
It seems you will be
drawing water all night.
So, are you happy after leaving me?
-Gu-jam.
-You did not come, so I came to you.
Why are you crying?
And if you are going to cry,
why did you leave?
You do not know.
You do not know my heart.
Fine, hit me.
Hit me as much as you missed me.
I met Jong-jong.
Lady Gil-chae does not even
work at the smithy anymore.
Even so, is she not out and about?
I do not have much time, so hurry.
You just came here.
What do you mean you do not have time?
I have to go back to Qing.
Anyway.
I need to quickly check
if Lady Gil-chae is doing well.
So, try to arrange a meeting
through Jong-jong.
I am telling you, it is difficult.
Since the barbarians invaded,
they have been strict
about women going out,
especially noblewomen.
Then, I will have to check for myself.
Jeez.
How did you know I live here?
You know Lord Lee
has returned to Joseon, right?
Do you want to meet with him?
You want me to meet with Lord Lee?
I do not want it.
But
Lord Lee wants to meet with you.
So,
you should seek him out first.
I do not want to.
You probably do not want him
to see you living like this, right?
It is only a matter of time
before he finds out about your situation.
So, go to him first.
You need to show him you are living well.
Only then, can Lord Lee
completely give up on you.
There is not a single
noblewoman to be found.
Jong-jong? Jong-jong!
Gu-jam.
-What are you doing?
-Just looking.
What are you doing?
So, did you meet other women in Shenyang?
There were many women who liked me.
You know I am the Batter of Joseon.
But, you know,
I am a very upright person.
Hey.
I had my fortune told.
I will make big money soon.
Hold on to me tight.
Hold on very tightly.
I am so bored being served
in my room all the time.
Officer Gu fusses too much over me,
not letting me walk or stand freely.
So, I came out today
by pretending to visit my father.
My sweet baby,
your mother told a little lie today.
Pretend you did not hear anything.
How have you been, my lord?
I did not think you would come to Joseon
since the Qing princess is so possessive.
I will be going back to Qing soon.
I came back briefly
because I wanted to visit my hometown.
I did not realize,
but it turns out I have a hometown too.
Are you okay?
This will not do.
-I will call a palanquin bearer--
-No.
I told you I wanted to walk.
Besides, I am really craving
steamed bean rice cakes.
Steamed bean rice cakes?
Yes.
No matter how much I make them at home,
they do not taste like the ones sold here.
Why is Jong-jong taking so long
to buy rice cakes?
Where did Jong-jong go?
Please wait here for a moment.
I will go look for Gu-jam and Jong-jong.
-Jong-jong!
-Lord Lee.
Jong-jong!
Please buy this.
Take a look.
Come and buy some.
Come and try some.
This tastes great.
That Gu-jam must be off
somewhere with Jong-jong
cooking beans or something…
I cannot find them anywhere.
Oh, this is…
On the way back,
I met an old lady selling rice cakes.
You can try one if you like.
Yes.
This hits the spot.
Have some sikhye too.
It is refreshing.
You should try some.
I am fine. You eat it all.
Put the bowl here.
I will have some more.
Why did you quit working at the smithy?
You know why.
Since being captured and taken to Qing,
I have been very careful
about going outside.
What else can I do?
Anyway, Lord Gu said he would
send ahead a palanquin.
There it is.
Okay.
I guess it is time to go then.
I would like to look around
the market more, but what can I do?
My lord cannot even eat dinner without me.
Well, then…
Let me make one request.
Soon, Ryang-eum
will host a gathering
to celebrate returning to Joseon,
at which he will perform a song.
Will you
be able to join us?
Please.
It is my last request.
Stop.
My lady.
Your clothes are pretty.
Who knew Gil-chae could look pretty?
There you go, speaking rudely again.
Which house is it? Is it here?
This is the right place.
This one or that one? Which woman is it?
That one there.
What are you doing?
Do women who have slept with barbarians
have no shame?
How dare you flirt with my husband?
All I did
was answer when he asked for directions.
How dare a wench
stained by barbarians talk back?
-Are you done talking?
-Not yet. Move!
-"Stained by barbarians"?
-Move!
-Get out!
-Get out of here!
-Go away.
Let us wash.
Look how dirty you are.
You little rascal.
Blow.
Harder. One, two, three.
A little more. One, two, three.
Look at that gunk.
Goodness.
Hey, you!
You come here.
You too.
Come here, all of you.
What?
-Come here.
-Gil-chae!
Come here.
She got divorced?
Yes.
Please stop.
Look.
Lady Yoo is smiling.
Gil-chae!
Get over here.
If you go over there now…
she will want to cry.
USIMJEONG
I gaze into the distance
At your dear face
Carried on
A distant wind
The memory of a face
I came because you said
it was your last request.
But I will never again--
Thank you.
It has already started. Let us go in.
Waiting with your head in your hands
I wait
For you
To come down
That path
At the slightest rustle
Of a bamboo leaf
In the twinkling moonlight
I see
You standing with your back to me
But then you turn
And smile at me
I put what remains of my longing
-Into the memories
-You were once enamored…
Of back then
-One drop at a time
-…by Ryang-eum's singing.
-I pour in
-So…
I cannot…
Every last drop
I love you
-What is going on?
-Why did the singing stop?
-What is he doing?
-Why did he suddenly stop?
-What happened?
-Why is there no sound?
What is going on?
I am sorry.
My morning sickness is still severe.
Do you think such a world could exist?
A world cast in moonlight,
filled with the sound of Ryang-eum singing
and the sound of flowers blooming.
A world like that.
What sound do flowers make?
Have you not heard it?
I have heard it.
It was truly a precious sound.
I should
get in the palanquin now.
Do you remember
what I said before?
I said I would never again
cause you any trouble.
I am so glad…
that I can keep that promise.
So…
Please…
be at peace.
How long do you plan to deceive me?
How long…
do you think you can keep this up?
I was so foolish to think
that I could deceive you, of all people.
My lady.
I am living well in my own way.
So, do not pity me.
Do not feel sorry for me.
That is
what I want.
No.
I cannot do that.
You must.
I left Shenyang…
because it was what you wanted.
Now, it is your turn.
Please pretend you did not see me.
Things did not work out.
But do not worry about Lord Lee.
I explained it to him
so he would understand.
"Understand"?
You are
truly impressive.
You really are.
-What?
-Why?
Will beat me for speaking informally
to a noblewoman?
Once again,
you only care about
your own pride and feelings, right?
You do not care at all
about Lee Jang-hyeon's pain, do you?
I hate seeing Lee Jang-hyeon sad
because of a woman like you.
It drives me crazy to watch Lee Jang-hyeon
get hurt because of a woman like you.
If I were you…
If I had even a fraction
of Lee Jang-hyeon's heart…
Then…
Why on earth are you…
You have no right.
You have no right
to be loved by Lee Jang-hyeon
or even to be ignored by him.
You…
have no right to take
anything from Lee Jang-hyeon.
What do you know?
So,
now that Lady Yoo is divorced,
will she run to you?
She does not want that, right?
I knew it.
That woman
thinks she is the most
important person in the world.
So, she can play with your feelings--
Watch your words.
I shall be going to Uiju soon.
It is only right…
that I go and bring back Big Brother.
Then, are we going back
to Uiju like before--
And then, I will cross over to Qing.
I shall finish things
with the princess and come back.
What promise did you make to the princess?
What did you say to get her
to take care of the captives in Shenyang
and let you go so easily?
I told her I would go to her side.
However…
Things have changed now.
I did not know then…
that Lady Yoo was divorced.
So?
Can we…
go back to before we met that woman?
You and me
with Gu-jam and Big Brother…
Things were good, right?
Do we…
mean nothing to you?
Of course not.
Ryang-eum.
I would…
die for you.
But…
I want to live for her now.
And…
if anyone gets in my way,
whoever they are…
I will never see them again.
Then, I will go with you too.
Fine.
You live for that woman.
As your younger brother…
I will follow you…
wherever you go, Brother.
I have been waiting.
Do you know
what I wanted to do most
when I saw you again?
I wanted to serve you a meal I cooked…
with my own hands.
It feels like…
we have become newlyweds.
Now,
we can spend
the rest of our lives like this.
My Lord.
Yoo Gil-chae.
Now, there is nothing standing…
between you and me.
So, no one can stop me either.
That was a great meal.
I am so full.
I have fulfilled my wish.
This is enough for me.
I wish for nothing more from you.
So…
Why did you get divorced?
You never asked me.
And I never told you.
But in Shenyang…
Yes?
You can say it if you want to.
It does not matter to me.
Do you still not know me?
Do you still not…
know my heart?
I just…
want you.
Poor Gil-chae,
rich Gil-chae…
impertinent Gil-chae,
obedient Gil-chae…
Gil-chae, who does not love me.
Gil-chae, who loves me.
Any version of Gil-chae…
is fine with me.
All right.
Then…
What about a Gil-chae who was
violated by barbarians?
I should hold you
because you must have suffered.
You must have been in anguish.
It must have been hard.
It is all over now.
Do not worry about anything anymore.
I will be
by your side now.
Even if you push me away, I will be here.
Even if you get tired of me…
I will be here.
The moment…
I first saw you, I knew.
I have never…
wanted anyone…
but you.
Can I…
hold you today?
I will make for him a pillowcase
embroidered by my own hands.
Please grant the captives
safe passage across the river.
Once Interpreter Lee comes back,
we will all live happily together.
Lee Jang-hyeon.
Let us not think of anything else.
Things are moving quickly, so hurry.
Lee Jang-hyeon.
Where is he?
If he were alive, why would he
not have come back by now?
It has disappeared.
Do you think we would fear a woman
who lost her virtue to barbarians?
Then, you and Interpreter Lee…
If only you had slept with him sooner…
You know, he says he will stay with me.
Subtitle translation by: Jay Lee