Your Majesty!
The barbarians…
The barbarians have invaded!
They have
imprisoned the king!
Barbarians?
That is preposterous. Are they back?
-My goodness.
-Oh, no.
Is it true, Soon-yak?
His Majesty…
Does this mean we are at war?
Goodness.
Since they are saying we are at war,
I am not sure we should be doing this.
The barbarians have His Majesty confined,
and it will be a while
before trouble reaches here.
Today is a special day for you,
so enjoy this sweet persimmon and rest.
Goodness.
You could consummate
as if this were your wedding night.
How could we when a war is waging?
Young Master Jang-hyun.
Why are you being so nice to me?
Because you deserve it.
Now that the barbarians
have invaded our land,
the nation will fall.
The foundation of the state will collapse.
Close your doors.
Ladies, cover your faces and hide.
Men, take up arms.
Ladies, cover your faces and hide!
Father.
Father!
Please.
Father, please.
Father! Father!
Father!
What is wrong?
What did you see
that made you so startled?
So, a war finally broke out.
What will you do?
What can I do but run?
Lee Jang-hyun will choose to run?
I am not made out of steel.
But do you not think the barbarians
will retreat after just a few days
like the last time they invaded?
I do not know.
Unlike before, they are holding
His Majesty captive.
Their leader declared himself an emperor.
How can you smile when we are at war?
Goodness.
It is not like the war will end if I cry.
No one can carry a tune like you.
Ryang-eum, the world's greatest vocalist.
A once-in-a-century master talent.
Is it true that the barbarians
have surrounded Namhansanseong Fortress?
If the barbarians
have truly invaded our land,
His Majesty should have gone
to Ganghwa Island.
Why is he at Namhansanseong Fortress?
I have news from the government office.
The enemy passed Pyongyang
three days ago
and passed Songdo a day after that.
So, His Majesty was pressed for time
and could only make it
to Namhansanseong Fortress.
The barbarians may be fast,
but how could they have made it
to Hanyang in three days?
Is it not just a rumor spread
by those trying to incite public unrest?
It is not.
The Amnok River is likely frozen.
The time line makes sense
if the barbarians
headed straight to Hanyang
without striking other fortresses.
A direct invasion?
Why would they
penetrate the heart of Joseon
without first trying to eliminate
the Joseon soldiers?
Something must have
made it worth the risk.
The king of Joseon.
They have His Majesty surrounded
at Namhansanseong Fortress.
That must have been their main objective.
Receive His Majesty's order!
His Majesty has issued a new decree.
Receive His Majesty's order.
"The men of Jin have
crossed the border and invaded."
"Those who are loyal
will propose strategies,
and courageous scholars will
volunteer their services in battle
to repay the benevolence of our king."
If we are respectful,
I doubt they will treat you with cruelty.
However,
I am not a high-ranking official.
And Lord Neungbong
is not your younger brother.
I am worried they might find out and--
How could they know
who our royalty and high officials are?
Besides, we cannot send
a real prince as they demand.
You were held captive
by the barbarians in 1619.
The Jin people were
so impressed by your spirit
that they treated you with respect.
I trust you will do well once again.
Of course.
It has been a while.
Yes.
Are you
the younger brother of the king of Joseon?
He is asking if you are
His Majesty's brother.
High official?
He is asking if you are a high official.
I am.
I will only ask once.
Do not deceive me.
Are they really
the king's brother and a high official?
Yes.
I assure you, they are
the king's brother and a high official--
You two will head back
and tell the king…
that this time around…
This time,
they have demanded
the crown prince as their hostage.
Such insolence!
How dare you speak of His Royal Highness?
Your Majesty, you cannot.
You cannot, Your Majesty!
Who exactly are you, Young Master?
Since you seem to want it so,
would you like
to lock lips with me today?
Why on earth is everyone gathering?
His Majesty is being held captive.
The mighty leader of Joseon
is asking for the assistance
of righteous men.
People of Joseon,
it is time for you to prove your worth.
Let us rescue our king.
Let the world witness your loyalty!
His voice carries well.
He would have been a talented singer.
When have you seen nobles
learn how to sing?
It is only for the lowly.
Then, you should try your hand at it.
I will teach you as a fellow lowlife.
What did you say?
Lady Eun-ae, why will you not stop crying?
Seeing you cry makes me cry.
Do not mind me.
What is she up to this time?
Why are you crying?
What is it to you?
I am curious why you are crying.
Let the world witness your loyalty!
He must be shouting
at the top of his lungs to rally soldiers.
Of course.
Unlike someone I know,
he is not a wimp who will run and hide.
Goodness.
How did you know I was planning to flee?
It is written on that ugly face of yours
that you could not care less
about the nation
as long as you can live comfortably.
I am a great judge of character.
I knew you were shrewd enough
to deserve to be my woman--
Those with burning hearts, step forward.
Those who are fiercely loyal,
step forward.
I will go.
Anyone else?
I shall go too!
Same here.
-Me too.
-I shall also go.
-Same here.
-Me too.
No, do not dare.
Why not?
I shall go as well!
Hold your horses, little one.
What about you?
I will…
I…
I have no intention
of joining the righteous army.
He has no morals!
Listen here.
It is an army for the righteous.
One must volunteer out of righteousness
and cannot be forced.
Some may not be
healthy enough to fight a war.
My body and spirit are perfectly healthy.
However, I am curious.
The king fled and left his people behind.
So, why
should the people save him?
It is to protect
the foundation of our nation.
Did the king do that by fleeing first
-at the sight of danger?
-You…
-What would you know?
-How dare you?
That pathetic fool
does not know any better.
He is truly pathetic.
One must fulfill his duty.
I simply cannot understand it.
But go ahead
and try your best to save His Majesty.
Why, that little…
Even that little boy
raised his hand and volunteered…
I commend your audacity.
I am worried about what they will wear
for battle in the winter.
What if we donate 600 grams
of cotton to make padded clothes?
That sounds like a great idea.
I will make thick padded clothes
for Young Master Jun-jeol
and embroider my name on the collar.
I will sew a talisman wrapped in a towel
onto the inside
of Young Master Dae-oh's shirt.
-One that will prevent death?
-No.
-One that prevents infidelity.
-Goodness.
-Is there such a talisman?
-Of course.
I should also embroider my name
on Young Master Yeon-jun's…
Are you really going to flee
while all the others fight?
That is what I said.
They are my favorite clothes,
so wrap them with care.
Unbelievable.
As a man, one should ride a horse
into battle and wield a sword.
You fool.
Do you think fighting in a battle is fun?
You will be teaching
evil bastards a lesson.
Do you think the barbarians invaded us
because they are evil?
Are they not?
They invade foreign lands
and harm the people.
Can you call that honorable?
I guess not.
However,
who will be left in the villages
if all the men join the war?
Well,
the elderly, the young, and the women.
This will not do.
Wait for me here.
Where the heck are you going?
-Young-chae, I am off.
-Sure.
-Write to me.
-I will.
Gosh, it is freezing.
See you.
Take care.
My lady.
We meet again.
I thought you would have fled by now.
I will set out soon.
Do not be like that…
and flee with me.
What?
If we hide down south
further away from the fortress--
I do not intend to flee,
so flee all you want by yourself.
One could die.
I mean the righteous army men.
You are the one who should be careful.
You could break your nose while fleeing.
My righteous Young Master Yeon-jun
will defeat the barbarians and--
Have you ever seen a barbarian before?
-Well…
-You have not.
The barbarians have never
come this far south before.
So, what could you know
about barbarians?
Did you hear they were uncivilized people
who ate the flesh
and drank the blood of live animals
without any rules regarding men and women?
Is that not true?
They do eat the flesh
and drink the blood of live animals.
However,
did you also know
they are such well-trained warriors
that they can eat and sleep on horseback?
They are poor at farming
and cannot even tell pen from paper.
But even though
they cannot read or write…
they know how to kill people.
That smart Young Master Yeon-jun of yours…
The same young master
who spends all his time
reading at his desk
and worrying about the nation.
His loyalty is admirable, but do you think
he could harm even a hair
on a barbarian's head?
No, wait.
Do you really think
he could survive a fight…
against an army of trained assassins?
Though they cannot read or write,
they know how to kill people.
Do you really think
he could survive a fight
against an army of trained assassins?
Lady Gil-chae.
What brings you here?
Are the preparations going well?
They are.
Our weapons are rusty,
and we are not well-trained,
so we decided to set out
after a few days of training.
But most importantly,
we need armor and horses.
Please do not join the volunteer army.
Pardon?
The warriors of Qing
are said to be trained killers.
With just one brandish of a spear,
they leave five to six bodies
in their wake.
You have spent more time
reading than shooting arrows.
You are a tender soul
who cannot even kill a bird.
If you go to battle against those
brutal barbarians, you might…
I might die.
However, His Majesty is being held captive
at Namhansanseong Fortress.
The people of Joseon
only have two choices.
We can either live as cowards
or die doing the right thing.
But…
We must stop him.
The Qing warriors are so nimble
and ruthless that our scholars--
They will not be a match for them.
Wait.
Are you saying you knew
Young Master Yeon-jun could die
but still did not stop him?
Power is not the only way to win a battle.
He is fiercely loyal and resourceful, so--
The barbarians are also resourceful
and loyal to their leader.
Young Master Yeon-jun
studied his whole life
to fulfill his duties as a man of honor.
He would never
turn his back on this nation.
Sure, it is great to be a man of honor
who serves the people
and is loyal to his king.
But I could care less about His Majesty.
Gil-chae!
However,
when I think of the barbarians
shooting arrows into our men's hearts
and breaking their bones with spears…
Will you let Young Master Yeon-jun die?
You are right.
Everything you said is true.
Young Master Yeon-jun could die.
I might never get to see him again.
That is it. You are doing great.
Keep it up.
What are they talking about?
Good. She got through to him.
Eun-ae.
Gil-chae.
How did it go?
Then, he will not join the troops--
Before he departs for battle,
he will marry me.
What?
Marry you?
You were right.
Young Master Yeon-jun could die.
I could not let him leave me
without first tying the knot.
I owe it all to you.
What now?
Please stop crying.
Crying will only make your eyes ugly.
They will not go through
with the wedding, will they?
Young Master Yeon-jun
never goes back on his word.
No, wait.
It is Lady Eun-ae who does
what she sets her mind to.
What do I do?
It is your fault for urging her.
Be quiet!
I urged her to stop him
from going to battle,
not to secure a proposal.
Why does it have to be Eun-ae?
Why is it Eun-ae and not me?
That is because you are too--
Too what?
You know better than anyone
that men lose interest in a woman
once they win her over
and get easily tired of women
who chase after them.
Yes, you are right.
Right? It is about time
you forgot about him--
Young Master Yeon-jun
has not considered
that I could marry someone else.
If he hears that I plan
to marry someone else,
he will realize how much he loves me.
He will end up kneeling before me
and confessing that I am
the only one he loves.
I will pretend to give in reluctantly,
help him to his feet,
and tell him that I feel the same way…
My lady!
What?
Lady Gil-chae.
Why did you ask to see me?
Are the preparations
for battle going well?
Yes.
I will snap off the head
of a barbarian with this hand
and bring it to you.
Please stop.
I do not wish to talk
of such scary things.
Gosh, I apologize.
But I feel reassured to know
that you will be fighting the barbarians.
Thank you.
I am the one who is grateful.
But I must say I am upset.
Pardon? Why is that?
Did not the elders of our families
once speak of a marriage between us?
The elders got ahead of themselves.
You could not possibly love
a talentless scholar like me.
Young Master Yeon-jun
will show his devotion to Eun-ae
by marrying her before leaving for battle.
How can you be this cruel?
My lady.
-Goodness.
-Hold on.
-Gosh, thank you.
-Thank you.
Dig in.
Eat up.
Oh, heavens!
In a few days, this humble man
will depart for battle
to save His Majesty.
Before I go,
I only ask for one thing.
Stop it.
Do not worry about me and your mom.
Yes, sit down.
What is this?
Lady Gil-chae,
marry me.
-Goodness.
-What?
Goodness me.
How could you ask that
in front of all these people?
That is because I am not ashamed
to confess what is in my heart.
If someone asks me what I am proudest of,
it is being brave enough to do this.
Soon-yak, you fool!
Why are you making a fool of yourself
in front of everyone?
-Father!
-What…
This is the only thing I want.
Will you deny
the final request of your son,
who could die out on the battlefield?
-My gosh.
-Honey!
-Wait.
-Oh, dear.
Marry me.
A marriage?
You will marry out of spite?
What is it to you?
That clueless Soon-yak
would not have proposed
so dramatically for no reason.
Do you think this will change
Young Master Yeon-jun's mind?
Young Master Yeon-jun
is a calculating man.
He may have acted interested in you,
but he has no intention of marrying you.
Do you know why?
Because he does not have the guts
to handle a woman of bad repute like you.
He is too weak-hearted
to handle a woman like you.
What?
Young Master Yeon-jun
is calculating and weak-hearted?
That is rich coming from a man
who is fleeing to save his skin.
How dare you speak ill of a man
who is risking his life
to save His Majesty and the people.
If you ever
speak of him again
with that detestable mouth of yours,
I will grind that ugly face of yours
into powder.
Is that not a little harsh?
What? Young Master Yeon-jun
is calculating and weak-hearted?
I have a bad reputation?
You do not have the best reputation.
Whatever.
You are behaving oddly if you ask me.
Whenever Young Master Jang-hyun
says something,
you always respond more than necessary.
You do not let the other young masters
even get near you.
When did I ever do that?
I have never behaved like that.
Unbelievable.
Gil-chae.
Are you going to marry
Young Master Soon-yak?
I am not sure.
The truth is,
I thought you harbored feelings
for another man.
Me? Which man?
At the wedding anniversary banquet,
we were all shocked to hear
a war had broken out.
Yes, we were.
Do you know who you looked
at as soon as you heard?
I am not sure I recall.
I believed he was the one
you had feelings for.
I actually asked you here
on behalf of Young Master Soon-yak.
He will be here soon.
Normally,
one must be picky
about choosing a wedding date.
But our options are limited
due to the war.
That being said, Gil-chae,
do you intend to marry Young Master
Soon-yak before he heads for battle?
Young Master Soon-yak is the man
my parents wanted me to marry, so…
My lady!
Then,
why do we not have a joint wedding?
What do you think, Young Master?
It is a fine idea.
My lady.
He is heartless.
He is truly heartless.
Wipe those tears.
Cold wind on a damp face
will ruin your skin.
Are you that upset
Young Master Yeon-jun is marrying?
Our country falls and the king is captive,
but this is what saddens you?
That is right. This saddens me more
than our nation being ruined.
I am not even afraid of dying in the war.
You do not fear death?
I see it is hopeless.
Then stop him from getting married.
I am in this mess
because I cannot do that.
Do you want my help?
My lady, if I help you,
what will you do for me in return?
How could you possibly stop the wedding?
Stop teasing me, and be on your way.
Get lost.
I heard you were having trouble
gathering armor and weapons.
The weapons we procured
during the first Jin invasion
ten years ago are rusty and old.
We have been repairing them, but…
I could help.
I bought some armor and weapons
a few months ago.
You purchased weapons?
I had a hunch as a merchant.
Since I do business with the barbarians,
I had a hunch that something big
would soon go down.
I knew that if a war broke out,
the people would have to obtain
weapons and armor on their own,
which meant I could make a big profit.
You are supposedly a nobleman,
but you have devoted your life
to making money.
You knew the nation was at risk,
and all you thought about
was making a profit?
There is nothing noble about you.
We have shamelessly
failed to repay you for the rice
you donated to our academy.
Is there a condition this time, too?
In exchange for the rice,
the academy took you in.
I am sure you will not
give us the weapons for free.
Finally,
we understand each other.
I hear that many
are rushing to get married
before the righteous army departs.
What do you say to delaying the weddings?
If the men die on the battlefield…
How dare you?
You are going to fight a war.
Should you not be prepared to die?
If a man's wife dies,
he can take on a new wife
without his children suffering
any consequences.
However, if a widow remarries,
her children are prohibited
from taking the state exam,
so they can never hold office.
In other words,
a husband's life continues
after his wife dies,
but the life of a woman
ends with the death of her husband.
Please consider the future
of the young ladies of this village.
They are beloved daughters
who were raised preciously.
Are you really willing
to put their futures at risk?
Lady Gil-chae.
I will soon be leaving.
Before I leave,
there is something I have decided
because of how much you mean to me.
What would that decision be?
We will not marry.
Pardon?
A husband's life continues
after his wife dies,
but the life of a woman
ends with the death of her husband.
That is why no man in this village
will marry anyone
before leaving to fight the war.
"No man"? That means…
So, Lady Gil-chae…
My lady?
Lady Gil-chae!
But Young Master, I…
I was wrong about Lee Jang-hyun.
He is more thoughtful than he seems.
But…
Instead,
I will keep you in my heart.
It is all right.
At least they are not getting married.
That is more than enough.
Tell Young Master Soon-yak
I wish to see him.
Again? For what reason?
My lady.
Jong-jong is watching.
You are the best archer in Neunggun-ri
and a skilled swordsman, are you not?
No one here is as valiant as you.
I guess…
Eun-ae
is deeply concerned
about Young Master Yeon-jun's safety.
That is why I ask
that you stay by his side,
for Eun-ae's sake.
If you were to protect him
with these broad shoulders…
Lady Gil-chae.
My friend, Eun-ae,
would deeply appreciate it,
and so would I.
Then…
Then?
Once you are back, the two of us alone…
The two of us alone?
-Without Jong-jong.
-Without Jong-jong?
It shall happen. I will make sure of it.
My lady.
Farewells should be kept short.
Jong-jong.
He will not wed, right?
Do you only follow me around?
Do you not have something for me?
Maybe a token of your gratitude.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Do you still see me
as a vulgar, narrow-minded,
and ugly piece of rock?
A rock cannot turn into gold,
no matter how many times you ask me.
Will I seem less ugly to you
if I help save the people?
You promised Soon-yak something
in return for protecting Yeon-jun
out on the battlefield.
Something about meeting in private
without Jong-jong.
Were you eavesdropping?
How about this, then?
If I am lucky enough to return alive
after helping the people,
kiss me once…
with those precious lips.
Good.
That is how you should react.
If you meet a barbarian
after we depart…
refuse them as harshly
as you did just now.
I shall get going.
Today,
I stand here to make a vow
with the people.
I will
defeat the barbarians
who have invaded our land.
Hurrah for Joseon!
Hurrah for the land of Joseon!
Did I eat too much
red ginseng candy this morning?
My heart is pounding.
You too?
Me too.
Men are all the same.
Yesterday, he asked if I would love him
if he helped to save the people.
He must be joining the battle
to win me over.
As if I would bat an eye.
Unbelievable.
Will you be joining the fight?
No.
I am fleeing to safety.
Are you wondering about my armor?
I wore it in case I came across barbarians
while I am on the run.
I shall return.
Look after yourself out there.
We will wait for you.
Please leave before I change my mind.
Gosh, no one is bidding us farewell
even though we are also leaving.
Who would cry for us
when we are fleeing to safety?
They say an item from a woman
will protect you from death.
But we are just fleeing to safety.
Even that can be dangerous.
Goodness.
I am afraid I ran out.
Let me see. Who could give you one?
Soon-yak! Soon-yak!
Please give me a moment.
Do not forget our promise.
Don't worry.
I'll protect Young Master Yeon-jun--
You, I mean.
Stay safe. Do you hear me?
Me?
Don't worry. I won't even lose
a strand of my hair.
Soon-yak.
Father, please.
Gil-chae.
Don't you have something
for Young Master Jang-hyun?
I shall be off now.
I have nothing to give
to a rock that is fleeing.
I have something for you.
Take it.
As if I would fall
for something like this.
Do you give daggers to ladies
in every village you visit?
Forget it.
Keep it on you.
Anyway, I have a favor to ask.
Look over there.
If you see smoke on that hill,
promise to flee the village
and head to safety.
Why would we flee
when the men will protect us?
Besides, it will not be an easy task
for this many people to flee.
-Bang-doo's baby is due soon, and--
-Then flee by yourself.
I do not care about the others anyway.
You must keep this promise.
What did you receive from her?
She did not have anything for me.
But I appreciate how kind you are being,
even though I am
just someone passing through.
You saved our village.
Besides, we might have
a closer relationship in the future.
What do you mean by that?
You are fond of Gil-chae.
Fond of her? Gosh, no.
Gil-chae and I grew up together.
I know her well.
I might even know her
better than she knows herself.
I also know who she harbors feelings for.
Do you know how I know?
Women…
Actually, it is the same for all people.
Like children seeking their moms,
when we are terrified or scared,
we turn to those we rely on.
When I heard about the war on the day
of the wedding anniversary banquet,
I immediately looked
to Young Master Yeon-jun.
I also happened to see
who Gil-chae was looking at.
Stay safe.
And return safely.
Gil-chae and I will both
be waiting for you.
-Goodbye.
-Good luck.
Stay safe!
Take care.
How can Young Master Yeon-jun
look that good in armor?
-Young Master Jang-hyun provided it.
-What?
But in return, he asked
for something peculiar.
What was it?
He requested the men
not to marry before leaving for battle.
Are you saying
he is the reason
they all decided not to marry?
That is what I said.
I bet
it was to make sure
others stayed single like himself.
Stop him from getting married.
Do you want my help?
Do you know who you looked
at as soon as you heard?
I looked
at that rock?
What is on your mind?
At Song-chu's wedding anniversary banquet,
did you see who Lady Gil-chae looked
at when we heard about the war?
They have
imprisoned the king!
She looked at Young Master Yeon-jun.
I knew it.
Look over there.
I hear you are from Neunggun-ri.
Yes, we received His Majesty's order.
I apologize for the delay.
We had trouble procuring armor.
Do not apologize.
I have been waiting
for circumstances to change.
Look.
That is where His Majesty is.
We are close,
but His Majesty does not know we are here.
It is time we told him.
Of course.
Your Majesty. It is the Royal Guard.
Enter.
Your Majesty, a flaming arrow
was shot from Heomcheon.
The loyalist forces must be here.
Currently, at Namhansanseong Fortress,
His Majesty is desperately
waiting to be rescued.
Those who die for His Majesty
will be remembered
for generations to come.
So, do not be afraid. Do not fear.
We will risk our lives
to rescue His Majesty,
protect Joseon, and preserve the state.
As soon as the day breaks tomorrow,
we will strike
the Qing soldiers from behind
and escort His Majesty to Ganghwa Island.
With your hands
and with your swords,
will you rescue His Majesty?
It is an ambush.
An ambush!
Yeon-jun, stay behind me.
Yeon-jun!
When you took out the blade,
I thought you had finally
decided to kill some barbarians.
But here we are, peeling persimmons.
You are back. How did it go?
Why ask? It is as expected.
Goodness.
The loyalist forces of General Jung Se-gyu
encountered barbarians
on their way to Namhansanseong Fortress
and suffered a crushing defeat.
Didn't the men of Neunggun-ri
go to that general?
Either way, the battle
should be settled up there.
I hope it does not reach the south.
This time around,
the Jin soldiers are being helped
by Mongolian soldiers.
Mongolian soldiers are different.
Different? How?
The Manchus and the Han will be
following their leaders' strict orders.
But the Mongolians must be here
with an ulterior motive in mind.
What motive is that?
To plunder riches and prey on women.
I hear horses galloping. They are coming.
I will go get him. Go up the hill
and raise the smoke signal.
We cannot take the boat.
We must go another way.
The Mongolians must have already left
to loot Joseon villages.
We just have to cross that mountain.
Take the baby and run!
Where are you right now?
I am scared and exhausted.
Nothing happened to us at all today.
I will have to hunt them down.
Subtitle translation by:
Hyelim Park