Nothing is better than being honest.
[Ba Wool]
So I've decided on a way to get past this crisis.
Hello,
students of Hwayang High.
This is Lee Seungmin.
I have something to tell you about the rumors concerning Oh Jina lately.
First of all,
as you all know, Jina and I are in a contract relationship.
- Contract relationship?
And I...  didn't want to go through with this contract.
What?
Because with Jina,  I didn't want a fake contract. I wanted to date her for real.
And it's also true that Jina had the upper hand in our relationship.
But only because I liked her a lot more than she liked me.
In all relationships, the person who likes the other more is at a disadvantage.
Really? He locked the door?
Open up. Open up before there's trouble.
Hey! Open up!
She did call me out all the time, and she did kiss me out of the blue.
I was so bewildered.
I was so nervous that my legs almost gave out.
If it weren't for this contract, I would have just had a crush on her.
In that sense,
the contract that you've all read around the school was the best opportunity I've had.
So, if it's okay with you,
please stop criticizing Jina and support my love for her instead.
So that we can start a real relationship after our contract is terminated.
He's such a romantic.
- He's awesome.
- Yeah.
So cool.
- A round of applause!
- A round of applause.
A round of applause.
That idiot.
Even if everyone else hates me,
if I have that one person who sincerely loves me, I'll be okay.
Just like now.
So do whatever you want.
I won't cave in.
Lastly,
I apologize for using the school's equipment like this for my own personal use.
And thank you for listening.
Come here, come here.
Is the school broadcasting system yours?
Do you want some balloons to go with it?
- Come here, you.
- I'm so sorry. Huh?
Lee Seungmin.
I'll go to your classroom later.
Where do you think you're going to go? You're headed to the teachers' office now.
Come here, you.
[It might be a contract, but for me, it's a real relationship.]
He's got it all wrong.
Does he think that he's the only one who wishes this were real...
[A Few Days Later]
After that, the rumors concerning us quieted down
and people started to root for our contract relationship.
Wow. Jina,
are you two glued to each other now that you're really going to date?
We're rooting for you.
I hope you two will be a couple for a long time.
Oh, my gosh! We're rooting for you!
I'm hungry. What should we eat?
And...
Hanna stopped coming to school.
How many laps do you have left?
Eighty laps.
You didn't play by the rules, so you deserve this.
I know.
Did you take care of what you wanted to do that day?
That was the first day ever
picking Jina over baseball.
The whole time I was running,
I realized that my heart was always Jina's.
[It might be a contract, but for me, it's a real relationship.]
Please stop criticizing Jina and support my love for her instead.
So that we can start a real relationship.
But I was late once again.
And Jina's heart was already someone else's.
As long as you tried your best.
Why aren't you coming to school?
Why do you care?
I'm still really mad at you,
but I forgot to say this to you. So here I am.
If you had a hard time because of me all that time, I'm sorry.
So please come back to school.
Let's go back to how things used to be.
Don't play it all cool.
You're right. I am playing it cool.
But we're still friends. What choice do I have?
I'm going to believe what everyone says about friends fighting
and give making up a chance.
[Relationship Contract]
[Ends December 22nd (Started on November 3rd)]
[December 22nd (D-DAY)]
"Jina! Let's really date, starting today."
No, no.
"Oh Jina,"
"let's date, starting today."
Oh. No, no.
"Are you my girlfriend?"
What?
Where have I heard this before?
"I love you."
No, no, no.
This is really hard.
What do I do?
I don't know.
What is this? A video?
- Didn't you know?
- Come on!
You dummy.
I have one condition.
"Condition"?
After the contract is terminated, don't date Lee Seungmin.
Why is that the condition?
Because I like him.
You should give up at least one thing.
Then I'll try to forget all the bad thoughts I had about you
and go back to being good friends.
[Lee Seungmin]
Good night.
[D-DAY for confessing]
You scared me.
Let's play hooky from school today.
I didn't see Jina today.
[Next Episode]
She's not answering my calls.
They must be together.
This date is really nice.
Let's do this once a week from now on.
What happens to the main characters?
They break up.
Isn't it fun?
I don't like those endings.
Are they really breaking up?
I told her to.
Are you sure you asked?
And didn't threaten her?
How did you like it all?
[Be My Boyfriend]