I tried to assassinate the president.
Mr. Prime Minister!
With these hands,
I wanted to stop his heart from beating.
Do not forget
that Park Dong-ho's time
is connected to Jang Il-jun's time.
What is your plan?
I've already told you
that if you cannot remove enemies,
you should control them.
I am the only one
who can control me.
Daejin Group Chairman Kang Yeong-ik
was released
from Anyang Correctional Institute
this morning.
He was sentenced to 12 years
in prison for charges
that included aggravated punishment
for specific economic crimes.
But he was released yesterday afternoon
after two years in prison
on President Park's special pardon.
He was checked into
the Daejin Medical Center upon his release
for a health check-up
and treatment for a chronic disease
that had worsened
during his time in prison.
I hate the bastards
who remove the smell from cheonggukjang.
The smell is what defines cheonggukjang.
Give me the reins to control Park Dong-ho.
Park Dong-ho is a hound
that even President Jang couldn't tame.
I will hold onto the reins.
We don't have time.
My brother is on trial
for something he didn't--
If you disclose what he didn't do,
then what he did do will be disclosed.
He embezzled company funds,
set up a private equity fund,
and made large profits
by stealing national business information.
He used that as bait
to lure in Jang Hyeon-su
to get to President Jang Il-jun,
then falsely accused Assemblyman Seo,
who found out--
Goodness.
It looks like my son has been quite busy.
I will give it to you
if you want to save your son
and abandon Daejin Group.
That's your business.
It doesn't concern me.
I will bring you a list of people suitable
for the minister, vice minister,
and key positions in the government.
That's my business.
It doesn't concern you, does it?
They are a helpful bunch. Use them.
PRIME MINISTER, DEPUTY PRIME MINISTER,
MINISTER OF EDUCATION
Filling the Cabinet with your people--
You grab onto those reins,
but I have to hold the whip.
PRIME MINISTER JEONG SU-JIN
THE WHIRLWIND
EPISODE 6
There are 3,000 key positions
that the president fills.
And another 25,000 under your authority.
We will fill those.
We'll leave a few positions
for you to fill,
like the chief of staff
and personal secretary.
That's about it.
Lee Ji-hun was involved in a sex scandal,
and Baek Jong-su is morally flawed--
I never thought
someone who helped
the president's assassin
would be this moral.
Turn a blind eye to their flaws…
and I will do the same for you.
Jeong Su-jin!
In politics, power is superior to morals.
You will have a list of appointees
within the week--
I'd like to see the list today.
They must have worked for Daejin
in politics, law, and academia
while the government paid their salary.
It won't take long
to compile a list of their own people.
Isn't it humiliating for you
to appoint those people
as the heads of government institutions?
The shorter the humiliation, the better.
Don't we owe each other
that much consideration?
29 DAYS EARLIER
THE FIRST DAY OF THE CAMPAIGN
ON THE SAME NIGHT
Our campaign strategy and conversations
are being leaked to Jeong Su-jin.
-We need to destroy the watch.
-No.
If we destroy it,
she will stop supporting us.
We undoubtedly need her help
to win the election.
Sir, we should trust the public for--
Seo Gi-tae also
trusted the public.
I once did too.
I will tell the public
the lie they want to believe,
that Park Dong-ho is Jang Il-jun's heir.
Ask Assemblywoman Jeong
to join me for a visit
to President Jang's birthplace tomorrow.
Park Dong-ho!
She will stand next to me
on the campaign podium in major regions.
We must win
this election at all costs.
Assemblywoman Jeong sent over
a list of names for heads of institutions.
The list has about
200 heads of major institutions,
including the National Tax Service
and the Financial Supervisory Service.
Kang Yeong-ik's long-hidden dogs
have finally surfaced.
It is now their turn to feel remorse.
Jang Il-jun's watch
made all this possible.
I am grateful to him
for the first time in a while.
Su-jin.
I told Cheol-min
that you have sensitive tonsils,
so he sent bellflower root juice.
He has loved horses since he was a child…
What?
My husband's recommending
a friend addicted to horse racing
for an executive position
at the Racing Authority.
What do you think?
You know
he hid me in his house
when I was on the run.
Friendship has a price tag?
Listen, Su-jin.
He went to prison for hiding me.
I have to repay--
Did we expect to be repaid
for what we sacrificed in our twenties?
Su-jin.
Ma'am!
I will announce the list of nominees
for President Park's first Cabinet.
BLUE HOUSE - CHUNCHUGWAN
For Prime Minister,
Assemblyman Park Chang-sik
of the Korean Liberal Party.
PRIME MINISTER JEONG SU-JIN(X)
For Deputy Prime Minister
of Economic Affairs,
Lee Jun-il, President of the KDI.
For Deputy Prime Minister of Education,
Ahn Il-sang,
President of Wonil University.
For Minister of Unification,
Min Hyo-seong,
former Vice Minister of Unification.
For Minister of Justice,
Kang Jun-seong, former assemblyman.
For Minister of National Defense,
Song Tae-min,
Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff.
For Minister of Interior and Safety,
Choi Young-man,
former Commissioner General of the KNPA.
Out of the 200 heads of institutions
in 19 ministries,
not a single person we recommended
was appointed.
He is waiting for you.
BLUE HOUSE - SANGCHUNJAE
I won the by-election ten years ago
thanks to you.
At the dinner that night,
I remember you enjoying raw anchovies, so…
Enjoy.
You go ahead
because this will be
your last meal in the Blue House.
I am thinking about
sending this recording to YTV.
The National Assembly will begin
discussing your impeachment today.
It won't take long.
I will at least
see you off to prison.
I finished Jang Il-jun off.
I did it with the handkerchief
he had given me.
I forced him
to stop breathing
with my own hands.
That's why, Man-gil,
I have to pick up
where he left off.
I think I finally understand why
Jesus sat with Judas at the Last Supper.
He must have seen Judas' devastated face
and thought, "I was right."
Sit down and eat.
It looks like Jeong Su-jin
has lost control of the reins.
How should I handle
the coachman who let go of the reins?
I wrote a novel when I was young.
Copying other writers' work
helps you become a writer.
You should imitate those
you want to defeat.
I will give everything back to you.
It won't take long.
Here is my ring
from our broken engagement.
I will see
if I have anything else to return.
Let's head towards Jeongbal IC.
That way takes longer.
You don't want to go by the AFC Hospital?
How did you feel
as you watched him take his last breath?
I am sure you remember how he looked.
I bet you still hear him scream
even when you cover your ears.
That you see his pain
even when you close your eyes.
You must think to yourself,
"I can't change what I did,
so I need to at least make sure
that it was worthwhile."
I swear to you…
that I will protect
your honor
and your family.
I understand.
What's inside me is also inside of you.
I finished Jang Il-jun off.
I did it with the handkerchief
he had given me.
I forced him…
to stop breathing
with my own hands.
That's why, Man-gil…
I have to pick up
where he left off.
None of this would've happened
if they'd disposed of the rotten apples
when Seo Gi-tae was investigating.
The administration would have collapsed
since the president's son was involved.
You don't cut down a tree
because there are a few rotten apples.
A single bug can cause
even a big tree to rot.
Even a pot of well-cooked rice
contains some burnt parts.
Rotting pus doesn't turn into flesh.
We must live by the same standard
we judged Jo Sang-cheon by.
I am sure
you felt unappreciated
that the president and Kang Sang-un met
behind your back.
Were you upset
that someone you served for ten years
was going to send you to prison?
I sometimes wonder
what would've happened
if Jang Il-jun had discussed
his son's issues with you first.
You led the smear campaign
to get Jang Il-jun elected.
You even fabricated documents
to cover up his election fund issue.
I wonder…
if it could've been you…
sitting in this chair, not me.
I am curious…
as to what made you so upset.
Is it a sense of justice, or…
is it your desire to punish
the colleagues who abandoned you?
How about both?
We are all multifaceted.
Prepare for the impeachment process.
The prime minister hasn't been confirmed.
Also, conduct the legal review
on the acting president in case
the incumbent can't perform his duty.
Park Dong-ho, Jeong Su-jin,
Kang Sang-un, and Jang Hyeon-su
will all be under investigation soon.
Have you not heard?
The recordings of
President Park and Jeong Su-jin
will be released to the media today.
President Park
has already prepared himself for this.
He instructed me to organize
a trip to the US next month
and prepare a draft of his UN speech
by the end of the week.
Those orders came this morning.
I hold your reins,
and you have the whip that can tame me.
I put the president into a coma,
and you killed the president.
If you can forget
how I got to the Blue House,
I will forget
how you finished off the president.
I sincerely thought…
you would sacrifice yourself
and jump off the cliff with all of us.
But you are planning on…
pushing everyone else off
and standing alone on the cliff.
The reason I visited Jang Il-jun
that rainy night
was to clean up the world.
If I were to leave now,
Jo Sang-cheon would still be around
after I was gone.
Chairman Kang would also be around
in the world I left behind.
How could the cleaner leave
when there is still some trash?
I am determined to stay in the Blue House
until I've cleaned every speck of dust.
Ma'am.
Please resign as chief of staff
as soon as
the secretary's office is set up.
Sir!
Thank you for the nomination.
I will make sure
that the new administration's tasks--
Park Chang-sik,
the nine-tailed fox of Yeouido,
switched party membership 15 times,
left the party eight times,
and founded six new parties.
An old and diligent migratory bird
from Yeouido
who sometimes gets confused
about which party he belongs to.
We conducted a survey and found
that 70% of the people perceived you
to be an obsolete politician.
This joke seems inappropriate
for an awards ceremony.
I will wash away the stains
from your 30-year political career
and give your image a makeover.
This is a list of public officials
who work for Chairman Kang.
I would like these people removed
from politics,
the legal professions, and academia.
Using a blacklist to target certain people
is legally problematic.
"Leader of reform
and the eradication of corruption."
Wouldn't that makeover be great
for your presidential campaign?
Ma'am.
Once he is officially appointed
as prime minister,
take over his vacant seat in Yeouido.
We must secure the nomination rights
for the next general election.
We will revolutionize our party
with new people.
While Park Chang-sik
reforms the government
and you try to innovate Yeouido,
can we agree
to delay the fulfillment of my promise?
I am determined to stay in the Blue House
until I've cleaned every speck of dust.
As you wish, sir.
Prepare for your confirmation hearing.
-Especially--
-Excuse me.
Thank you.
-Hello.
-Dad.
MACAU (CASINO HOTEL CELLAR)
Dad, please help me.
These guys are gonna kill me
if you don't send the money right away.
To pass the hearing,
there shouldn't be anything
that would upset the public,
including any issues
related to your children.
Can I count on you?
Of course, sir.
DAEJIN MEDICAL CENTER
I have told you
that half of the world's problems
come from trusting people.
I can no longer be useful to you.
You will not see me again.
I wish you good health.
Are you threatening a sick old man?
I want to take responsibility
for my incompetence and resign.
Park Dong-ho has a list of people
who look after my business.
Now, my guys can't even cough
for fear of being noticed.
My goodness.
I am short-staffed. What do I do?
I have no choice but to use
the incompetent coachman for now.
Does that mean
you are giving me another chance?
I hired the ladies
who clean my company buildings
as full-time employees.
They wanted to clean up
their husbands' shit,
so I couldn't let them work as just temps.
Park Dong-ho plans to use Park Chang-sik
to eradicate our people in the government.
We need to get
Park Chang-sik disqualified.
We invested in a casino in Macau.
Come in.
I have a fresh tip-off.
Contact with personnel under inspection
is prohibited by internal regulations.
Forward related information in writing
to the deputy chief prosecutor.
A high-ranking ruling party member's son
has been involved in overseas gambling.
I heard his gambling debt
is 500 million won.
He couldn't pay the debt,
so they are holding him
in the basement of the casino.
I'd be all over this case
if I weren't under investigation.
As you are an honorable chief prosecutor
well-trained in special investigation,
I'll leave this
in your capable hands, sir.
Nice!
-What the hell?
-Hey, yeah.
I gave him the file.
Listen, Su-jin.
My wife signed the lease
for a place near the Blue House,
thinking I'd be
the Senior Secretary for Civil Affairs.
She keeps asking me when we are moving.
I see. Okay, I understand. Yep.
God, this is so bitter.
Chief of Staff Choi is said to be
returning to Yeouido.
She has been contacting senior members
and other lawmakers within the party.
Let's take it one step at a time.
We've got to get rid of
Park Dong-ho's left-hand man first.
PRESIDENT PARK DONG-HO NOMINATES
PARK CHANG-SIK FOR PRIME MINISTER
THE BLUE HOUSE OFFICIAL RESIDENCE
Those bastards sent this.
My wife collapsed yesterday.
She has been hospitalized.
She never lost her smile,
even when I lost elections,
but she couldn't take this.
You can't wire the money.
Overseas gambling is your son's problem.
You will take a hit from it,
but you will pass
the confirmation hearing.
As soon as you wire the money,
you will be charged for violating
the Foreign Exchange Transactions Act
by providing illegal gambling funds.
How can I abandon my son to save myself?
The prosecution is probably
monitoring your account.
They will be checking
your account, your family's,
and even your relative's accounts
for illegal activities.
We will get help from the local police
in accordance with the law
and its principles.
Principles take time.
My wife is at her limit.
Can you fend off the prosecution?
Lee Jang-seok is in charge.
You are the only person
who can stop him.
RESULTS OF GAMBLING INVESTIGATION
I'll be your go-to guy
for as long as I am the prime minister.
The dozens of lawmakers supporting me
will be your shield.
Please help me save my son.
I am asking as a father.
GRAVE OF ASSEMBLYMAN SEO GI-TAE
The prosecutor general wants to resign.
Asking for the new president's trust
is just a formality.
I plan to accept his resignation.
So many issues have been amassed
over the last 70 years,
such as the power to issue indictments,
investigative authority,
and privileges of the former post.
Jang-seok, I want you
to take over the prosecution.
Please create a prosecution
that fights injustice
without becoming one itself.
Get yourself off all your current cases.
Don't make enemies for now.
Assemblyman Park reached out to me.
He told me to slow the investigation
and said I should hear from you.
I wondered on the way here…
whether you would threaten me
or ask me for a favor.
Wow, anyway…
what a good friend you are.
You're even getting me a good job.
Come on, Jang-seok.
Drop it
just this once.
You know it won't be just once.
He has a job to do as the prime minister.
Is that why…
you are preventing me from doing my job?
Do you remember the Jang Hyeon-su case?
Why didn't you drop it?
You should have ordered an investigation
into your son's illegal activity.
President Jang Il-jun
also had a lot to do as the president.
Please resign from your position
because the future you create
shouldn't be a part of history.
Don't ask me to do
what you failed to do.
I intend to do my job.
Transfer me anywhere you want.
If you want a hunting dog
for your administration,
there are plenty in the prosecution.
I can even recommend one.
RESIGNATION LETTER
"I, Park Chang-sik, solemnly swear
that I will speak honestly
without attempting to conceal
or embellish anything
at the confirmation hearing
held by the National Assembly."
He will acknowledge his son's gambling
but plans to deny
his illegal overseas money transfer.
Everyone has a plan.
We will now begin the hearing
for the nominee, Mr. Park Chang-sik.
Please proceed, Assemblyman Min
of the Korean Liberal Party.
TWO DAYS BEFORE THE CONFIRMATION HEARING
The extinction
of local communities is serious.
I heard your constituency
will soon be merged.
MIN BYEONG-IL
KOREAN LIBERAL PARTY ASSEMBLYMAN
I can keep that from happening.
Your political career will be over
if your constituency disappears.
A casino manager testified
that he released your son
after receiving 500 million won.
Is it true that you transferred
the money illegally?
Words also carry weight.
The words of an employee of a casino
and the words of
a prime minister candidate
cannot carry the same weight.
Show me the evidence.
Do not rely on hearsay.
Submit the evidence if you have any.
When making inquiries,
you must
accurately confirm the facts
and have a legal basis.
I gave Assemblyman Min
the investigative information
from the Macau Police Agency.
I asked you to submit the evidence
if you have any.
ONE DAY BEFORE THE CONFIRMATION HEARING
You got the Political Funds Act passed,
but the money you took…
Sure, every politician does politics
on someone else's dime.
I understand.
However, the CIO doesn't agree
with me on this.
Would you rather protect
your constituency or your future?
No more inquiries.
Mr. Min appears to have sided
with Park Chang-sik.
RESIGNATION LETTER
Are you going to continue lying
in this hallowed hall?
Don't ask me to do
what you failed to do.
Do you think you can defeat me?
Do not forget
that Park Dong-ho's time
is connected to Jang Il-jun's time.
Hello.
Jang-seok.
Don't change who you are.
How about you?
I am going to change
the world.
Breaking news.
The Seoul Central DPO
has just arrested a suspect
for illegally transferring money
to a casino operator in Macau.
The suspect is
the brother-in-law of Mr. Kim,
secretary to Mr. Park Chang-sik,
prime minister candidate.
The prosecution believes
that he illegally sent the money
to the casino
at his brother-in-law's request
and is tracking
Secretary Kim's whereabouts,
but he is currently out of contact.
The prosecution is focusing on
finding Secretary Kim
and said they will further investigate
Mr. Park Chang-sik's involvement.
Lee Jae-cheon, former chairman of the BAI,
and Yoo Hong-man,
former chairman of the KITA,
both turned down a nomination
to be the prime minister.
The administration could look weak
without a prime minister.
Jeong Su-jin will foster
a lame-duck session.
If that happens,
you could be a lame-duck president.
You can run the government
under the deputy prime--
No.
I'll appoint a new prime minister.
Even senior members of the party
are refusing to be nominated.
Elders from all the organizations
are rejecting our offer…
There is one!
Someone who agreed to be nominated
and already submitted a consent form.
DAEJIN MEDICAL CENTER
My sincere apologies
for having worried you.
We old people have nothing to do
but worry.
I will now remove
Park Dong-ho's right-hand man.
It's Choi Yeon-sook's Achilles heel--
Father!
The Park administration
has decided to nominate
Assemblywoman Jeong Su-jin
as the next prime minister.
She will faithfully carry out
the current administration's tasks
as the deputy prime minister
in the previous administration
and will be an asset
to the Park administration…
I sent documents to Park Chang-sik
as to who made the report
about his son's overseas gambling.
JEONG PIL-GYU
I explained to him how Jeong Su-jin used
the media and the prosecution
to slaughter Park Chang-sik and his son.
I sent documents to Jo Sang-cheon
as to who tipped me off
about his half-brother.
Jo Sang-cheon now knows
who reopened his old wounds
to bring him to his knees
during the last presidential election.
Park Chang-sik and Jo Sang-cheon
are the leaders of two major parties.
The anger of the two giants
is directed at Jeong Su-jin.
Park Chang-sik will hack her to pieces,
and Jo Sang-cheon will chew her up.
Her family will be destroyed,
and her husband will be exposed.
So the question is,
can she survive the hearing?
This hearing will be…
the execution ground for Jeong Su-jin.
THE WHIRLWIND