FIVE MONTHS AGO
The Nobel Committee in Oslo, Norway,
announced today
that President Jang has been selected
as the Nobel Peace Prize laureate.
He is the second person
in the Republic of Korea's history…
Take responsibility and resign.
I'll keep you from being arrested.
…to be honored with the Peace Prize,
the most prestigious Nobel category.
We will now hear
from our Norwegian correspondent, Gong.
The Nobel Committee emphasizes
that President Jang is a leader
who protects the human rights of workers,
ordinary people, and the poor in Asia
and highly praises his efforts
to narrow the wealth gap
and provide welfare to ordinary people.
The presidential election is next year.
I will help you to sit
where I am sitting right now.
I have no intention
of cleaning up the seat you soiled.
Do you think you can defeat me?
I must!
Because the future you create
shouldn't be a part of history.
I'll get you an invitation
to the Harvard University Asia Center.
Since you are interested in welfare,
the Royal Swedish Academy might be good.
Take a break.
We've had the same dream
for the last ten years--
But we've lived in different realities.
While I investigated
Kang Sang-un's slush funds, you--
We reformed the economy
and kept peace in the peninsula.
If the administration wavered,
everything would have collapsed.
-If it hadn't been for us--
-Why did you oppose the dictatorship?
They also achieved industrialization.
-Mr. Prime Minister!
-Why did you resist the coup?
They also championed the cause
of lifting the country out of poverty.
Was their cause
any different
from yours?
What's the difference?
They thought
this nation would collapse without them.
You share their arrogance.
You may hold a different shield,
but you wear the same armor.
The prosecution will come after you.
It looks like the police, the NTS,
and the NIS will all get busier.
You will be completely crushed.
I thought we were on the same path.
You are the ones who strayed from it.
Just wait.
Park Chang-sik will hack her to pieces,
and Jo Sang-cheon will chew her up.
Her family will be destroyed,
and her husband will be exposed,
so the question is,
can she survive the hearing?
This hearing will be
the execution ground for Jeong Su-jin.
THE WHIRLWIND
EPISODE 7
Ahead of Nominee Jeong Su-jin's hearing
for prime minister,
suspicions about Namsan C&C,
an equity firm headed by her husband,
are growing.
THE NATIONAL ASSEMBLY BUILDING
Five billion won,
ten billion won,
and another ten billion won.
SOLAR CELL BUSINESS PLAN
Your husband took
so much from Kang Sang-un.
What would a man's little lady be doing
at her husband's business meeting?
Did you get this from the Blue House?
Your confirmation hearing
will cause quite a commotion.
Oh my, it's so bloody hot today.
If you were to turn a fan on for me,
I might consider
turning the expensive AC on for you.
What I mean by that is
that if you save me first,
I will save you too.
You forgot
that I never cooperated with you
despite being waterboarded for six days.
People say
politics is the art of possibility.
Only humans create art.
Look, lady!
Do you remember what I said back then?
What did you say?
I will
protect
our chairman.
I will protect
President Jang's honor and his family.
If I die,
I'll create a wall with my bones
and a river with my blood
so your filthy hands
can't reach President Jang and his family.
It's me.
Add another witness
to the list for the hearing.
Jang Il-jun's son, Jang Hyeon-su!
Please, sir!
Put Jang Hyeon-su on the stand
and badger the shit out of him.
If Park Chang-sik chews you up
and I sink my claws into you,
you'll wish you were back
in that torture room.
When news broke that Jang Hyeon-su
had been asked to appear
as a witness at the hearing,
President Jang's supporters
began protesting at the National Assembly,
demanding an end
to political manipulation.
Some protesters clashed with the police
while attempting
to enter the Assembly Building.
This hearing is not about Jeong Su-jin.
It is an all-out war between those
who wish to tarnish Jang Il-jun's honor
and those trying to protect it.
About the charge against your husband--
It's a rumor, conspiracy,
and manipulation!
I am prepared to get hit
by the stones they throw.
If I fall, mark the spot with a flag
and a plaque that reads,
"In the Jang Il-jun era,
justice prevailed."
Jeong Su-jin!
Thank you for accepting
my invitation.
I was told you left these in the annex.
Do you recognize them?
Seven years ago,
you bought these during your trip
to Spain.
Caesar's wife was
once suspected of infidelity.
When Caesar chose to divorce her, he said,
"Caesar's wife must be above suspicion."
The same applies to Jang Il-jun's wife.
Ma'am.
You shouldn't worry.
Your secret is safe with him.
People only become true friends
when they share their secrets.
I will keep yours.
Will you keep mine?
WE SUPPORT JEONG SU-JIN
PLEASE PROTECT PRESIDENT JANG
There's going to be a rally
to support you this weekend.
We are expecting more than 10,000 people.
I never expected it to go that far.
This, however, I did expect.
PARK DONG-HO
I gave him that
after his first year in office.
President Jang cherished it.
He used to cut off the rotten leaves
whenever he had time.
He probably never thought
he would become rotten.
A public opinion poll was conducted.
More than 60% of people think
the private equity fund case
is political manipulation.
Your ability to turn personal corruption
into political conflict…
I thought I knew you well,
but I was wrong.
I still have much to learn.
Stop giving Park Chang-sik
private equity fund-related information
and leaking Namsan C&C accounting files
to Jo Sang-cheon.
If you do, I will stop too.
I might invite the former first lady
to our weekend rally.
Her tears will trigger
a political explosion.
She can't go.
She is about to board a plane.
Why did you suddenly decide
to leave the country?
I have been interested
in the World Food Conference
for quite a long time.
Some say you are trying
to avoid getting caught up
in political conflicts before the hearing.
Isn’t the hearing a private matter
for Assemblywoman Jeong?
There is a verse in the Bible.
"Thou shalt not take
the name of the Lord thy God in vain."
I am asking you, Assemblywoman Jeong,
to refrain from mentioning
the late President Jang Il-jun's name.
If Jang Il-jun were Jesus,
that would make her Mary.
Is this a fight between Mary and Peter
or Mary and Judas Iscariot?
Why won't you back down?
If you had taken just one step back,
none of this would've happened!
Because you people
are behind me.
In front of me,
I have a friend who died.
He
keeps approaching me.
So I step back…
out of shame
for not having lived as he did.
And because
there is something I must do…
before I grab onto his hand.
So you think I am advancing,
but in reality, I am backing away.
You are also…
going to perish.
I have made my peace with that.
I just hope I survive long enough
to lay you to rest.
Send the gift I prepared
to Chief Prosecutor Lee.
BLUE HOUSE - SANGCHUNJAE
Abalone, sea urchin,
octopus, and even octopus minor.
I heard Gi-tae's mother
still dives for these in her seventies.
Gi-tae really liked them.
Since he's no longer with us,
she sent us some.
You go ahead.
You know
that prosecutors don't eat
with suspects during interrogations.
On November 18th,
when Jang Il-jun collapsed
from a heart attack…
were you at the Blue House?
That night at 1:26 a.m.,
you left
the Gwanghwamun Government Complex.
Five minutes later,
at 1:31 a.m.,
you turned right on Samcheong-dong.
Two minutes later, at 1:33 a.m.,
you drove into the alley.
That alley only leads
to the Blue House.
I got a tip-off.
I have to look into it.
If you can't answer…
I'll have to investigate.
Kang Sang-un assassinated the president.
I believe he is already on trial.
At 1:20 a.m.,
40 minutes before the president collapsed,
Kang left the Blue House.
I believe
Kang is not denying the murder charges.
Remaining silent doesn't mean
he's admitting to a crime.
Dong-ho.
Is your silence an admission to a crime?
As a prosecutor, I want to hear
why you came here that night.
As a friend, I want to know
why you've been hiding it.
JEONG SU-JIN
Yes.
The gift you bestowed upon me
was so generous
that I sent a few photos to thank you.
If that's not enough,
I can send more to your friend.
If you stop here, sir,
I will do the same.
Let's eat, okay?
-These are from Gi-tae's mother.
-Dong-ho!
Just be my friend today, not a prosecutor.
Does that mean
that you will face me
as a suspect one day?
Not today though.
Get Park Chang-sik
and Lee Jung-gwon right now.
We have three days left
until Jeong Su-jin's hearing.
It is irrational to replace
the hearing committee members now.
It's irrational, indeed.
Let me be irrational too.
Is your son's habeas corpus review today?
Three former prosecutors have replaced
three of the hearing committee members.
They are planning
to turn the hearing into an interrogation.
The CIO,
"Completely Idiotic Office."
You have been ridiculed enough,
so it's about time
you got some applause.
The CIO is said to be
investigating Namsan C&C.
The prosecution
has strengthened their team.
Jeong Su-jin convened a meeting
of senior leaders at noon today.
She will ask for
their support in the hearing.
I will also have a luncheon at noon
with senior leaders at the Blue House.
I will keep your afternoon open.
-You need to rest--
-Tell the governor of the FSS.
-Namsan C&C…
-Sir, please.
My friend Jang-seok
is getting close.
I need to at least
clear his way to Jeong Su-jin.
And if possible,
I just want to…
delay him from coming my way.
LEE JANG-SEOK
It's me.
It's Gi-tae's birthday today.
I will bring the cake.
GRAVE OF ASSEMBLYMAN SEO GI-TAE
He said he would survive
until there was no room…
on the cake for all the candles.
Dong-ho.
Kim Eung-chan and Oh Yoo-jin
are both highly skilled.
We put together a team.
They will be requesting a visit.
I got another tip-off.
TO: THE CHIEF PROSECUTOR
SEOUL CENTRAL DPO
At 1:36 a.m.,
you went to the Blue House.
At 2:00 a.m.,
the time at which
Jang Il-jun collapsed from a heart attack,
you left the Blue House.
A coincidence.
Too many coincidences
is not a coincidence.
I asked to see
the visitor log for that day,
but it has been deleted.
Someone who had the authority to delete it
must have done so for a reason.
I just hope it isn't
the reason I am thinking of.
Dong-ho.
I'm launching an investigation.
If there is an unfair personnel order--
I promised you.
If you need my blood
to bring Kang Sang-un
and Jeong Su-jin to justice,
don't hesitate to slash me.
I want you to keep your promise.
If I meet my end
and you are
the only one left sitting here,
I want you to create the world
I wish to see.
Jang-seok, do what you have to do.
I ought to try harder at my job.
I have a lot to do.
Let's go.
I am Seo Jeong-yeon,
secretary of the Blue House.
Everything I say from now on
comes from President Park.
The Daejin Group's vice chairman,
Kang Sang-un, who's currently imprisoned,
will appear as a witness
at nominee Jeong Su-jin's hearing
and address all suspicions
related to Namsan C&C.
Namsan C&C is an investment firm headed
by the husband of the nominee, Ms. Jeong,
and is accused of making
tens of billions of won in profits
using information
on government-funded businesses.
Daejin Group is said to have invested
in Namsan C&C's…
Only if you are prepared
to expose your own truth also.
Come on, Su-jin.
I…
I want to survive.
JO SANG-CHEON,
NEW CONSERVATIVE PARTY
This is Jeong Su-jin.
Oh my, it has been 30 years
since we shared a meal.
I suppose you didn't have
much of an appetite in the torture room.
You barely finished
half of your yukgaejang.
Vice Chairman Kang Sang-un
is planning to testify at the hearing.
You can't sell when there is no buyer.
Why don't you hitch a ride on my wagon
all the way
to the prime minister's office?
Aren't your supporters abandoning you
for sending money to North Korea?
Some say your political career is over.
The 30 years I spent
knocking the commies down
taught me something.
For the South to live,
the North must die.
Did I startle you?
Jeong Su-jin, director of
the NCSR Cultural Propaganda Division,
and Jo Sang-cheon,
chief of the Public Security Department…
could do something great together.
Sang-un is appearing at the hearing?
Oh my.
The older kids get,
the less they listen to their parents.
He may break laws,
but he never dares to disobey his father.
I guess you gave him
permission to attend the hearing.
I am too old to stay awake for long.
I need to take a nap.
Many things will happen while you sleep.
Assemblyman Jo Sang-cheon will
raise suspicions that you were behind…
-Ma'am!
-…the private equity fund-related scandal.
I've spent my whole life
avoiding true accusations.
You think lies can take me down?
There is a first time for everything.
NOMINEE JEONG MEETS
WITH CHAIRMAN KANG IN PRIVATE
Reporters will swarm here in ten minutes,
wondering why you secretly met
with a nominee whose political career
is about to end in a scandal.
Twenty years ago…
Which presidential election was it?
…you contacted a North Korean official
and asked them to fire bullets
at the Military Demarcation Line.
That official is now a big shot,
ranking fifth in the Workers' Party,
and you remain in contact.
Ask him for a favor.
He will demand a lot of money.
Double the asking price. It is urgent.
If someone finds out,
it's a violation of sanctions,
and it could jeopardize--
I doubt you'll mind the sanctions.
It means Daejin will survive until then.
I will leave you to it.
I hope to hear from you
before I face the reporters.
Give us a statement.
What did you discuss?
Tell us what you talked to him about.
What brought you here?
How do you know the chairman?
I WILL DO TO YOU
THE VERY THING I HEARD YOU SAY
"I will do to you
the very thing I heard you say."
Vice Chairman Kang and I
went to the same college.
I came to see my friend's sick father.
-What did you talk about?
-Give us a comment.
I wish him a swift recovery.
He has a lot on his plate.
RYANGGANG PROVINCE, NORTH KOREA
Here is the sentencing from
the Democratic People's Republic of Korea
and the Korean People's Army.
For the South to live…
You have become
a tool of propaganda by the South,
and you have soiled
the dignity of our country.
Therefore, you will be executed
in the name of the party and the people.
…the North must die.
The father of Assemblyman Jo Sang-cheon
and four of his family members
living in North Korea
are said to have been executed en masse.
The Korean Central Broadcasting Committee
delivered the news today,
criticizing Mr. Jo Sang-cheon,
former New Conservative Party leader,
labeling him "an enemy of the Republic."
A poor older brother
bought some food
for his starving younger brother.
And for that, the North Koreans killed
his father using anti-aircraft guns!
Look! Does it make sense
to call a witness now?
Shame on you!
How old are you?
JEONG SU-JIN'S
PRIME MINISTER CONFIRMATION HEARING
Jeong Su-jin, director of
the NCSR Cultural Propaganda Division…
I, Jo Sang-cheon,
will take the lead in eradicating
pro-North Korea forces!
Jo Sang-cheon!
…and Jo Sang-cheon,
chief of the Public Security Department…
could do something great together.
The hearing started two hours ago,
and they haven't asked a--
Jo Sang-cheon's men
are requesting a new witness.
Whoever it is, just accept it!
It's you, sir.
They requested you
as a witness for the hearing.
They want to question you
about the equity fund case
since you were the prime minister--
-I'm going to the National Assembly.
-It's a political assault.
A sitting president
appearing as a witness at--
It is only once I am there
that the hearing will start,
and Kang Sang-un will testify.
Sir.
-How can I help you?
-We are from the Central DPO.
Hold on, please.
Jo Sang-cheon's men have requested
a new witness,
the former first lady.
She is not even in the country.
Jo Sang-cheon is trying
to dissolve the hearing.
How could Jo Sang-cheon possibly
conspire with Jeong Su-jin
to have his own father executed?
I did it.
Jang Il-jun was like a father to me,
and I stopped his heart.
To Jeong Su-jin,
Jang Il-jun was like a father,
and she killed him.
And now Jo Sang-cheon…
I had forgotten…
that they could do
the same thing I did.
LEE JANG-SEOK
Mr. President,
please let the Internal Affairs Team in
to conduct an investigation.
Jang-seok, your request is denied.
-Dong-ho.
-Chief Prosecutor Lee Jang-seok!
Dissolve the team instantly.
I will no longer tolerate
any investigation
based on groundless intelligence
related to a sitting president.
This is an executive order!
Transfer Prosecutor Kim Eung-chan
to the US
and Prosecutor Oh Yoo-jin to Germany.
Prosecutor Lee will not give up
even if you cut off his limbs.
He will come crawling.
That's who he is.
It will merely delay him…
but I need the extra time.
Come on!
We have now concluded
voting on the appointment
of Prime Minister nominee Jeong Su-jin.
Of 296 registered members,
257 are in attendance,
and 142 voted in favor.
Therefore, the appointment motion
has been passed.
"I present this certificate of appointment
to Jeong Su-jin."
"You are hereby appointed
as prime minister."
"President Park Dong-ho."
It is my honor, sir.
I will serve you as prime minister,
just like you served President Jang.
I will do what I must do
as prime minister.
I also intend to do
what I must do as prime minister,
just like you did.
Please resign from your position.
But do not make me repeat
your last decision.
How dare you!
After all, you are the one
who made me come this far.
THE WHIRLWIND