[power cord rustling]
[reporter] Controversy is brewing
over a deceased man in his twenties
who was writing the autobiography
of a famous serial killer.
Mr. Kim hanged himself
in his small studio apartment in Seoul.
He posted on an online message board
before his death,
saying that he was
ghostwriting an autobiography
of the murderer Ji Hyang-cheol.
Ji Hyang-cheol is
a notorious serial killer
who was sentenced to death
for murdering eight women
in the early 2000s.
Police stated
that they did not find any evidence
linking Ji, who is currently incarcerated,
to the alleged autobiography
and dismissed rumors
that Mr. Kim's death was a homicide.
[vacuum powers down]
[dramatic music playing]
[Yeong-ha] If a tree falls in a forest…
and no one is around to hear it…
does it make a sound?
Or is there nothing…
but silence?
THE FROG
SEOUL CENTRAL POLICE AGENCY
-Hello.
-[man] Hello.
Ah, okay.
[chair rattles]
So I heard you were the one
who found the body in the water tank.
Not true.
Detective Cho said that.
Seriously, how'd you know?
You're good at catching criminals
and finding clues.
When I see the faces of violent criminals,
I just say to myself,
"Really? That's who did it?"
But how do you know?
Is it the way they talk? Their behaviors?
Does it have to do with
the nickname they gave you?
[intriguing music playing]
What are you asking me?
"It," right?
Let's talk about the case.
-Are you doing an article?
-I won't tell a soul.
[young Bo-min sighs]
The water bill.
[tires squealing]
[mysterious music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[unsettling music playing]
[officer] We have a two-car accident
that just happened. Please come quick.
Yeah, it happened
right in front of the station.
Okay, yes. Please hurry. Thank you.
[coughs]
[clattering]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[groans]
-[curtain rustles]
-[nurse yelps]
[breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
[tense music swells]
[yelps]
[nurse] Are you… are you okay?
[music fades]
[woman] Welcome back.
Did you get a ride?
I should've picked you up.
Ugh, I get it. I'm sore everywhere too.
And yet
my painting is going really well. Hm.
Do you have my bag with you?
Don't be stressed.
[paintbrush rattles]
You worried about that footage?
[sighs] If only it didn't exist,
you'd be living your life carefree.
Well, I threw it all out.
You're able to live carefree now.
[Yeong-ha] Get out.
There's nothing I can do
at this point anyway.
I couldn't care less anymore.
I promise you
I'll keep my mouth shut about it.
Now get out.
[woman] I don't wanna.
[mysterious music playing]
[water sloshes]
You get so angry.
All you do is try to get me out.
Why are you trying to pull away from me?
Can't we just pretend to be friends?
[exhales sharply]
[woman sighs]
-I'll leave if you can convince me.
-Convince you?
Selling this place won't happen.
But, honestly, what I don't understand is
how you could possibly need this house
more than I do.
Tell me.
There has to be a reason
that you need this entire place
just for you.
[scoffs]
You want me to tell you
why I own my house?
[woman] Mister…
take a look around.
Doesn't this look like my house?
You just lived here before I did.
That doesn't necessarily mean
it should be yours forever, does it?
[music fades]
[stirring music playing]
[eerie music stab]
[Yeong-ha] It was
a whole different game now.
And now
what started as a battle
for evidence and the truth
became a turf war
led by that psycho woman.
[pharmacist] You're experiencing pain
due to the accident.
So we'll prescribe you
muscle relaxers and painkillers.
[machinery whirring]
[Yeong-ha] And this was a fight
I was less likely to win.
[sighs]
[microphone feedback]
Attention!
[gunshots]
[gun clicks]
[gunshots continue]
[bullet casings clatter]
-Great work, Captain.
-[officer 1] Welcome back.
How'd it go?
Captain Yoon scored… perfect.
-Oh!
-[officer 2] Ah, just wow.
Officer Kim did too.
The chief complimented
his shooting at lunch today.
-[officer 2] Wow!
-[Choi] Don't you get all cocky now.
[officer 2] We're gonna kill it this year.
[officer 3] Oh, I know.
This year is flying by, isn't it?
[officer 2] That's how things are
when you're doing fieldwork.
I'll be done soon, I think.
My workflow is improving.
[woman] What should I do with
the poster and invitations?
I don't really wanna advertise it.
Ah. I wasn't thinking. Sorry.
Mm, actually, forget it.
Let me give you a call back
as soon as I've finished.
Talk later.
[disconnect tone]
[pensive music playing]
[sighs]
[spoon clatters]
MISTER
[phone line ringing]
[vehicle approaching]
[man 1] Are you the rental owner?
[dog growls]
[dog grunts]
Oh! Jae-hwan.
-[woman 1] Give, give. Give it to me.
-[dog barking]
[girl] Oppa, give it to me.
-Give it! Give it to me!
-[laughing]
[Choi] So the owner hasn't been
picking up your calls,
and you arrived
to find that woman staying here.
[man 1] Exactly. I was obviously shocked.
-Could you show me your booking details?
-Sure.
[Jae-hwan] Learn to run faster.
[girl] Give it! Give it!
Excuse me, were you in that accident
in front of the police station?
[automated voice] The person
you are trying to reach is unavailable.
Ma'am. Excuse me,
but I need to see your booking details.
[phone line ringing]
[sighs]
[pensive music playing]
[music fades]
[both sigh]
[automated voice]
Your call has been sent to voicemail.
-Shit.
-Please leave a--
He wouldn't go far,
not after accepting a booking.
I imagine you have to get going.
Must be busy here.
Do you
really have nothing
to show your, um, booking,
like a deposit or something?
There's no website, so when I got here,
he told me I could pay in cash.
I told the, ah…
I forgot the name of the other guy.
[woman sighs]
Their website's right here.
FOREST VACATION RENTAL
Any texts?
When you book, don't you exchange texts?
Uh, you'd need to communicate somehow, no?
My texts get deleted.
[scoffs]
Why are you asking me all these questions?
Do you think I'm trespassing right now?
You know, it must be tricky for you 'cause
you're by yourself.
[chuckles]
You can't talk to me like that.
[footsteps approaching]
We're leaving.
[moans] My God.
MISTER
-[bubble toy whirring]
-[phone line ringing]
[pensive music playing]
[automated voice] The person you are
trying to reach is currently unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
[man 1] Ah, hello, sir.
I'm so glad I finally got through to you.
Yeah, I was a bit shocked at first, but…
Oh, she's a live-in employee?
[pants]
Hey, mister,
why are you not picking the phone up?
[disconnect tone]
Oh shit! Shit!
[door closes]
[exhales]
-[man 1] It's hot.
-[woman 1] Thank you.
[man 1] Mmm! It's good.
-[man 1] Mmm!
-[woman 1] It's really good.
[man 1] How come Daddy only gets tomatoes?
[children laugh]
[man 1] Give me some meat too.
[woman 1] Give him one of those.
[music swells]
[light switch clicking]
[sighs]
[clatter]
[monitor beeping]
[woman moans]
Hello, ma'am.
How have you been?
My grandma, do you know where she is?
[labored breathing]
[mysterious music playing]
The flowers your son sent have wilted.
May I throw them out?
[grunts]
[Gi-ho] Go back to sleep.
[Jong-du] Oh, hey.
[music fades]
[exclaiming yawn]
[vehicle approaching]
[man 1] Oh, hi!
Are you the one I spoke with?
-[man 2] Ah, yes. Hello.
-[man 1] Here you go.
-[man 2] Did you enjoy your stay?
-Yes, it was brilliant.
[man 2] Great!
I hope you didn't have any issues.
-It was perfect.
-Oh! What are you doing?
-Who are you to be taking the keys?
-What?
[man 1] Oh, don't worry about her.
She apparently works here.
-I'm sorry?
-Who are you?
I'm here because the owner asked me
to handle all the cleaning
and laundry here.
[gasps]
-The laundry?
-Huh?
[laughs] My God! Oh my God!
You forgot, didn't you? [laughs]
[man 1] Do you know this woman?
[man 2] I don't.
I would remember her.
[man 1] She's a strange woman.
Just ignore her.
[man 2] Oh.
I'll just take that.
Seriously, stop it. Jeez.
-Take care. Have a safe trip home.
-[man 1] Thank you.
-This is bullshit.
-[man 2] Come back soon!
-[man 1] Thanks!
-[man 2] Wonderful!
Leave me alone.
What are you doing? [grunts]
You're crazy! Stop it!
[Yong-chae] An obnoxious guest?
Well, just tell them off
if they break your rules.
If they don't stop,
you must call the police.
Hmm.
You think so?
[Yong-chae] Having a guest like that
could cause huge problems for any job.
You can never let 'em win.
[sighs]
Gambling, drinking, or drugs.
I'd report them
if they're doing anything illegal.
What if the police can't help?
[Yong-chae] Well, sometimes,
the problem may be irritating,
but legally, it's not worth reporting.
In that case, the only thing you can do
is wait for them to leave.
-And if they won't?
-[Yong-chae] Won't leave?
[Yong-chae laughs]
Why wouldn't they?
Everyone has to go home eventually.
They all need to leave
once it's checkout time
so that the next booking is able to enjoy.
[sighs]
The next booking?
[pensive music playing]
[Yong-chae] Hurry, it's your turn.
Uh… Ah, darn it.
[music fades]
[vehicle approaching]
-Fuck me! This rental's insane!
-Yo, this place looks dope!
-[man 1] This is it?
-[man 2] Holy shit!
-[all cheer]
-[man 2] So sick, bro.
[pop music playing on radio]
[indistinct chattering by pool]
[girls shouting, laughing]
Those noisy bitches.
-[girl 1] What are you doing? Come on!
-[man 1] For real?
[girl 1] Dude, I'm serious. What the hell?
[sighs]
[man 2] All together now!
[guests shouting by pool]
[sighs] God-fucking-dammit!
-[sighs]
-[tray clatters]
[guests shouting by pool]
-[girl 1] Come on! Let's do a shot!
-[man 1] Yeah!
[indistinct chattering by pool]
Ugh! Shit!
[sighs]
[man 2] Come on!
-[knocking at door]
-[door opens]
-I need a toothbrush.
-What?
Ooh!
[pop music on radio continues]
Well, he said there were
spare toothbrushes in the bathroom
and that the auntie here could help me.
Who said?
-Who said?
-The guy who owns the place.
Who are you calling "auntie"?
[laughs] Well, you're old.
I can't say unni.
[both laughing]
[sighs]
[girl 2] Unni.
Can I get two toothbrushes?
Ugh, two of the same color? Man!
-Keep it down out there.
-What?
Are you able to drink?
[girl 1] Fuck yeah!
-Bring me all your IDs, please.
-We're all mature adults.
Then prove it.
Or should I call the police?
Ugh, goddamn, bruh.
Clean up all of your mess, or else.
And what happens when you call them, huh?
Huh? They'll shut
the whole place down, won't they?
Shut this place down?
That's exactly what I want.
[toothbrush wrapper rustles]
-Get out.
-[girl 2] What the hell?
-[girl 2] Fucking bullshit.
-Go.
-Ow!
You're an absolute psycho.
[sighs]
[noise cancellation tone]
[loud clatter]
[gasps]
[exhales]
-[loud clatter]
-[tense music playing]
[pants]
The hell?
-Hey!
-[man 1] What?
-Goodbye, old lady!
-Yo, have fun with the window, old lady!
[phone ringing]
[girl 2] Let's go!
[sighs]
-Where are you?
-[Yeong-ha] You still haven't left?
You're pulling tricks
and hiding out, are you?
[Yeong-ha sighs]
What tricks?
What's strange about having guests?
It's a vacation rental.
And anyways,
you're being the strange one here.
[stirring music playing]
[sighs] Come back,
and let's talk this out.
[Yeong-ha] More guests are coming.
A lot of large groups have booked.
It is vacation season.
You're not helping yourself, you know?
And can you clean the place up for me?
The cleaner won't go because of you.
[sighs] Fucking piece of shit.
Hey, sir.
I could kill your daughter if you'd like.
SLIDE TO POWER OFF
[automated voice]
The person you have dialed is--
Damn it!
[grunts]
[sighs]
[groans]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[music fades]
[mysterious music playing]
[knocking at door]
[door opens]
[sighs]
What happened to the window?
[music fades]
[door closes]
[machine beeps]
[unsettling music playing]
[detective] He was working on
Ji Hyang-cheol's autobiography
moments before he died.
Only one unidentified individual
was captured on CCTV
at the presumed time of his death,
but we don't know if he has anything to do
with that ghostwriter.
That was a month ago.
[Bo-min] And the autopsy?
He hanged himself,
so they ruled it as a suicide
and cremated him.
Detective Cho investigated everyone
who knew him but found no viable suspects.
He even investigated people
related to the victims
but found nothing of note.
Are you sure he was really writing it?
Hyang-cheol said he didn't know anything
about an autobiography,
and the victim
never contacted any publishers.
He could've made it up.
That's what everyone's saying
since the news broke.
Do you think Ji Hyang-cheol is involved?
[detective laughs]
I called to ask you the same thing.
I don't know either.
You doing all right?
Yeah.
You aren't bored yet?
No.
-[mosquitoes buzzing]
-[smacking]
[smacking]
[tent unzipping]
[Yeong-ha sighs]
[door closes]
-[Choi sighs]
-[grunts]
Going on vacation, huh?
-What are your plans?
-Don't you even think of calling.
[Choi] You better not call me
when you're gone.
Your uniform. You're not changing?
There's one thing I have to do.
[phone buzzing]
-Hello?
-[man] Hi, are you the rental owner?
We got here a little early,
but the lady here
won't hand over the keys.
I'll head right over.
[dramatic music playing]
[vehicle approaching]
Give me the keys.
Uh, sir?
What if she gets in?
She'd be trespassing.
Call the police right away.
-Let me clean up quickly.
-[man] Thanks.
[music fades]
[officer] Good to finally see you here.
You can leave that right here.
Kim Seon-tae, Hosu Police Station.
Why are you here?
I have a reservation.
Those guys are with me.
Turns out you were close by,
so why did you make
that poor woman's life so hard?
Are you harassing her and messing with her
because she's a woman
staying at your property all by herself?
"All by herself."
Are you talking about that woman?
[Seon-tae] That's unacceptable behavior.
You'll get yourself in trouble.
Let's head in, guys.
[stirring music playing]
You called the police?
The guy volunteered.
By the way,
you're not looking too good.
What have you been doing?
[door closes]
[sighs]
[guests] One, two, three!
[woman] Woo-hoo!
[men laughing]
[woman] Wow!
-[man 1] Whoo!
-[man 2 moans]
-[laughs]
-Oh!
[all exclaim]
[laughs] Take it.
[woman exclaims, laughs]
-Join us in the pool.
-Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
-[man 2] Yeah, yeah, yeah!
-[woman screaming]
[men laughing]
-[man 3] Yeah!
-Hey!
-[man 2] Oh my God.
-[woman exclaims]
[man 1] Ah, hey, hey. You drive, okay?
-[man 3] Are you kidding me? You drive.
-[man 1] Then you pay.
[man 3] Okay.
-We're off.
-[man 2] Good night.
-See ya!
-[man 3] Have a great night.
Thanks, guys. Get home safe.
[Seon-tae sighs]
-[Seon-tae] You sure you'll be okay?
-[clears throat] Sure.
Jeez! I don't know
if you're brave or naive.
[laughs]
Leave the bags. I'll grab them tomorrow.
-Don't you have work?
-I'm on vacation.
-[engine starting]
-See ya.
[creatures chittering]
[mysterious music playing]
[sizzling]
[chuckles]
Food good?
It's not bad.
You owe her an apology,
don't you think, sir?
As a police officer,
I've met way too many men
who act more entitled as they get older.
Guess they only have
their pride remaining.
They all think they're in their prime.
It's truly pathetic.
Sounds rough.
So you're a people person?
I think so.
-You're good at reading people.
-[laughs]
[music fades]
Wine, anyone?
Let's all forget about it
over a nice glass of wine.
[Yeong-ha] Why'd you become an officer?
[footsteps approaching]
[Yeong-ha] Have you drank anything
that woman's poured you?
I wouldn't if I were you.
[groans]
[breathes deeply]
[belching]
[groans]
That little son of a--
I need a toothbrush.
[sighs] Thanks to you, mister,
that bastard won't go home.
-He insists on staying.
-So?
[sighs] He's painfully annoying.
Ugh, he's honestly so stupid
and talks way too much.
Can't you just work with me
on this, mister?
We'll tell him we're good again
and get him out of here.
Well, he actually did
book this place, unlike you.
He's a police officer.
You really want him here?
Having him here puts me at ease.
[chuckles] My God.
How about we…
go halves on this place?
[commentator 1]
Cho Hyun-oo catches the ball!
[commentator 2] After scoring one,
they come up with another delicate play.
-[commentator 1] They sure do.
-A long ball into the head.
A simple yet effective play.
-Split it?
-Mm.
We can meet in the middle.
I don't need this room anyways,
if I'm honest.
So I'll live in here,
and you'll live over there?
-That's what you wanna do?
-Mm.
[both laughing]
You bitch.
[unsettling music playing]
Don't call me that, okay?
Live together with a murderer?
With you?
Do you wanna know how I killed him?
I can tell you in great detail
what I did to Si-hyeon.
Do you really think you can live here
after hearing what I did to that poor boy?
Just face it.
It belongs to me already.
I'm letting you keep this room
because I pity you.
[dramatic music playing]
[gasping]
This isn't your house.
I don't need another reason.
I have no intention
of giving anything to you.
[gasping]
[gasping, coughing]
-[breathing heavily]
-[door opens]
[tense music playing]
Shit!
[panting]
What happened?
That bastard.
[woman] Hold on.
[music fades]
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
[car engine starting]
[music subsides]
[exhales]
[tense music resumes]
[music swells]
[animal growls]
[mysterious music playing]
[engine shuts off]
[animal growls]
[unsettling music playing]
[growls]
[music intensifies]
[loud clatter]
[vehicle stops]
[unsettling music playing]
POLICE
[door opens]
[loud banging]
[tense music playing]
All of this is my property.
And that's my bed.
Get out.
-Aren't you going?
-[grunts]
[Seon-tae groans]
You might be a paying guest,
but this is still trespassing.
The two of you are…
[Yeong-ha grunts]
You son of a bitch!
-Have you lost your mind?
-Whoa! I dropped my weapon.
Let go. Let go of me right now.
You're the… the police.
You're a police officer.
Wake the hell up, you dumb bastard.
[Seon-tae] Give me a fucking break!
[both grunting]
You'll break my arm! Hey. Let go.
You're gonna break it. Okay, okay.
Wake the hell up, you asshole!
[both grunt]
[music swells]
[Seon-tae] Are you crazy?
[panting]
[siren wailing]
[siren stops]
[car doors open, close]
I heard Officer Kim responded
to a call at your rental recently.
-Was there some kind of problem?
-No.
How about when you came to the station?
[mysterious music playing]
You came in
and just walked right out the door.
What brought you here that day?
Guests are only allowed
to use the main house,
the yard, and the swimming pool.
Those two tonight
were in my personal quarters.
They were in there without my permission.
Have you ever hit someone out of anger?
I'm not trying to imply anything,
but it takes a lot for the anger you feel
to lead to physically harming somebody.
Getting into street fights,
practicing martial arts,
gambling, drinking, drugs,
or even experiencing physical assault.
Something needs to happen in one's life
for them to get violent like that.
[chuckles]
So you're telling me
that someone who's lived like me…
has no choice but to be helpless.
Sounds to me like there's something
you wanna fight against.
[sighs]
I wanted to file a report.
For what reason?
It's all over.
There's nothing anymore.
I can still listen to your story.
[phone buzzing]
OFFICER KIM SEON-TAE
Excuse me for a second.
[music fades]
[disconnect tone]
Can I go home, please?
-I can give you a ride.
-That's okay.
What happened today with Officer Kim…
Can we just let it go?
I just… never want him
coming back to my rental again.
I'll give him a full refund.
I will let him know.
[rain pattering]
[sighs]
[Choi] Causing trouble on your vacation?
[Seon-tae] Man, you know,
you didn't have to come.
I was patrolling the area.
Captain Yoon already smoothed things over
with that owner.
And what about the woman?
Seon-tae.
I know you want bigger
and greater things from your career.
You'll get promoted soon.
Don't put yourself in a bind.
You know what I'm saying, right?
Yeah.
Let's go. I'll give you a ride.
I'll… take a cab. Thanks.
All right.
See you later.
Have a good night.
[mysterious music playing]
[music fades]
[sighs]
[mysterious music playing]
[bag unzips]
[unsettling music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[breathing heavily]
SERGEANT CHOI JEONG-HO
[phone line ringing]
[engine revving]
[music fades]
[phone ringing]
THAT CRAZY WOMAN
[phone line ringing]
[phone ringing]
[woman] Why did you have to
take things this far?
I'll sell you my house.
[mysterious music playing]
Are you serious?
That's incredible.
That's exactly what I needed to hear.
Just wait a few days.
[young Bo-min] Moisture… to be precise.
There wasn't a single bit of moisture
in that house.
The property hadn't been charged for water
for the past two months.
I thought, "Why didn't they use any water?
The pipes are working just fine."
[rumbling]
[water sloshing]
I checked the water tank on the rooftop,
and there was nothing inside.
[sighs]
But that water tank on the hill
was visible from that rooftop.
The killer couldn't use any water.
It reminded him of the body in that tank.
Whoa!
How do you figure that out
from seeing that?
It's not what you see.
It's the opposite.
Not what's there, but what's missing.
Looking for what should be there,
but for some reason, it isn't.
-That's what I look for.
-What should be there.
So something like
their environment or everyday life?
And in themselves as well.
What emotions or behaviors
are missing in someone.
What words or time frames seem
to be slightly off in their testimony,
or eye contact they're avoiding.
Oh!
Surely that's…
that's only with certain
work-related cases, right?
You can't analyze everyone like that.
[pensive music playing]
But I do.
I doubt everyone.
Victims, their neighbors,
their family, or anyone.
My coworkers too.
Even my loved ones, my neighbors.
Team Leader Kang, Detective Cho.
Everyone in this building.
Especially everyone in this building.
And you. As you sit beside me, Mr. Yeom.
I see and evaluate everyone equally.
I don't make an exception for anybody.
You're thorough.
I know I'm not some heroic cop
who's catching criminals
in the hunt for justice.
I'm just…
[unsettling music playing]
[music fades]
[dramatic music playing]
[Bo-min] We're all just
playing a game of tag, and I'm "It."
[dramatic music playing]
[music fades]