[Start-Up]
[Previously]
I'm looking for Korn.
I don't want Alice to think poorly of me.
- Are you coming to my birthday party?
- No.
But Dream is coming.
Can you help me locate him?
Korn isn't even real.
We want to join Sandbox.
And where's this boyfriend you were bragging about?
Or there isn't one.
Dream, have you been waiting for long?
Mom, Dream is here.
Dream!
Dream! I've missed you so much!
You say you missed me, but why haven't you contacted me at all?
I'm sorry.
And where's this boyfriend you were bragging about?
Still waiting to make an appearance?
- Hi, Ji.
- Hi, Maco.
Or there isn't one.
Dream…
♫ And suddenly everything is out of sight ♫
♫ It's like the sky lost all the light ♫
Have you been waiting for me?
♫ I tried to run, but I fell back down ♫
♫ Looking for the door but there's no way out ♫
Korn?
♫ I tried to hide but I don't know how ♫
♫ I can't get you off my mind ♫
Sorry, I told my sister you were my boyfriend.
But let's just roll with it, okay?
Sure.
We haven't had much time to hang out lately,
so we kind of miss each other, you know?
Yeah, I've missed her a lot, too.
I forgot to properly introduce him. This is Korn. He's my boyfriend.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
You two seem close.
- Hi, I'm Alice, Dream's elder sister.
- Nice to meet you!
Dream talks about you a lot.
I heard you're doing business together now, right?
Business? Of course!
Yeah, I mean, but the business…
So, what do you do exactly?
Just in case there's any opportunity for a collaboration.
By the way, I'm the CEO of Nature Morning.
I'm Korn. CEO of Samkorn Thai Tech.
CEO?
Yeah, it's pretty impressive. I feel so proud that he's a CEO.
- Sorry, what series of funding are you in?
- Series?
- Yeah, which round?
- The first round.
- First round?
- Yeah.
I'm about to invest in his company.
Even if Mr. Korn's company is in the initial stages,
it's still considered seed funding.
- Mr. Ji, you know Mr. Korn, too?
- Yes.
Hello. I'm Jiraphat from SH Venture Capital. Are you Ms. Dream?
Yes.
Finally, we meet. I heard a lot about you from Korn.
I see. Nice to meet you, Mr. Jiraphat.
I'd like a moment to talk to Mr. Korn about the investment.
As you please.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Pretend to be laughing and talk business with me.
Yes.
[Episode 3: Angel]
Your boyfriend must be special, for him to catch Mr. Ji's attention.
Smart and good-looking. Dream is really lucky.
Right. He's so cool.
Why are you so amazed? Still not used to it?
I'm crazy in love.
Every time we meet, I feel excited like it's the first time every time.
Like I'm falling in love with him all over again.
- That much?
- Yeah.
Why are you here?
Didn't I tell you that I couldn't help with Sandbox?
I didn't come here for your help getting into the Sandbox.
I came because I wanted to come. I'm here for Dream.
Why? Do you think this is charity work?
I just thought I might be of some help to her.
You are because now you are a hotshot CEO,
catching the attention of a well-known investor like me.
Was that a compliment or a boast?
I'm just being honest.
Just keep talking and laughing, so it looks real.
- Yes.
- What should we talk about?
I was wondering if you were strong in calculus?
I'm more of a marketing guy.
How about multiplication tables?
Up to twelve?
Shall we start?
Twelve times one is twelve. Twelve times two is twenty-four!
Twelve times three thirty-six.
Twelve times five is sixty. Twelve times six is seventy-two.
Twelve times seven is eighty-four.
Twelve times eight is ninety-six.
Twelve times eleven is one hundred thirty-two.
Twelve times twelve is one hundred forty-four!
Your boyfriend has a good connection.
But this industry is not easy.
Miss Alice, Mr. Witoon has arrived.
Thank you.
- Mom, will you come too?
- No.
- Good evening.
I thought you weren't coming.
Why wouldn't I? It's my daughter's birthday.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- Happy Birthday.
Come on, let's sing together.
Everybody, please join in and sing along.
♪ Happy Birthday to you ♪
- Alice.
- Korn, let's go.
Mom, Korn and I need to excuse ourselves.
- Oh, Dream.
- See you.
Dream…
- Dream…
- May I excuse myself?
Dream…
Are you leaving so soon? Stay a little longer. I wish you would stay.
I'd better not. I'll let you guys spend quality time together.
A happy and complete family.
What's the rush?
Then I'll get a car for you.
Didn't you bring a car?
Mr. Korn, you had valet park your car, didn't you?
I did.
- Then, let's get the car.
- Yes.
Wait here.
Are you going to drive me? Thank you.
No. I'll let you drive Dream home.
Then, why won't you drive her home yourself?
Well, Dream thinks you're her friend, so you have to drive her home.
Be nice.
It's better not to talk, not to say anything at all.
Keep cool. If she asks, say as little as possible.
After that, give an excuse to cut her off.
What kind of excuse?
Well, you can say that you already have a girlfriend.
But I'm still single.
Do you know how to lie? Hurry up and send her off.
And return the car to me.
Yes.
- Here is what you left.
- Thank you.
Can you drive?
I can.
Dream, can I give you a hug?
I'm sorry I left you.
I'm really sorry.
I miss you so much.
I'm all right, Mom. Don't worry about me.
I've been doing well. I've got a job, money, a boyfriend,
and I feel good and happy with the path I chose.
So, you don't need to feel guilty,
or to say sorry anymore.
Dream.
At the moment, I am not as successful as Alice,
but from now on, I'll outdo her.
Look at you, bluffing. I wonder if you can actually do it.
Do you want to bet? You are three years older than me.
If within 3 years I am as successful as you,
you have to pay me a hundred baht.
Only one hundred?
Yes, one hundred is enough.
Grandma says anything more than that is gambling,
not a bet.
Yes.
Just wait and see. My business will be bigger than Mark Zuckerberg
and Steve Jobs level, so big that you can't even compete.
Let's wait and see.
Dream.
Bluffing without a real plan makes you a fraud.
Going in blind hoping for success, you will end up like your dad.
You know that?
I'm heading out.
Why?
Are you leaving when Dream leaves?
I just can't stand being around your dad.
He annoys me, and it only gets worse.
I don't want to talk to him.
Just be careful with your future.
Do you really think your father will let you run his empire?
What do you mean by that?
Well, I'm tired of real estate. I want to explore new markets.
And I'll have my son handle them.
Anyway, please support him.
Is it hot in here?
I'll turn on the AC.
What?
I'm sorry. I haven't driven this car in a while.
Can he make it?
Where do you want to go?
I'll take you there.
I'm not sure.
Anywhere to take my mind off things.
Why did you bring me here?
In the letter, you mentioned you love to sit and look at the river when you're stressed.
Do you remember that?
Over here.
Don't you want to know why I suddenly wanted you to come to me?
And why I pretended in front of my sister and mother?
I'm curious.
But I figure if you wanted to tell me, you eventually would.
I'm going to tell you. You know I've never kept secrets from you…
What are they talking about?
What are you doing? Hurry and take Dream home and end the conversation.
Did your girlfriend send you a message?
You can just leave.
I'll take you home.
It's okay. You can go. I can stay here.
- But you…
- No problem. Thank you very much.
Then, I'll go home.
See you.
Korn, you are like that book.
I don't need to open and read it.
Just having you by my side makes me happy.
Doing something you've never done does feel good.
And sometimes, sailing without a map is really wonderful.
Dream.
What?
That book? Have you opened and read it yet?
Yes, I have.
How was it?
It's…
incredibly good.
I now understand the phrase "sailing without a map."
From now on, no matter where life takes me.
Having Dream by my side is enough.
This is my business card.
You can always call me.
Okay.
So, don't you have to hurry back?
How about your girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Really?
This is for you.
♫ And come away with me ♫
"Follow your dream."
♫ While the world is still sleeping ♫
♫ Wuh-uh-oh, stay close to me ♫
♫ Even if we all fall down tonight ♫
Right here.
That's enough.
Hey.
Why didn't you hurry back and cut her off?
Why didn't you do as I told you?
Well, I want to try sailing without a map.
Are you serious? Sailing without a map?
We're going to get ourselves killed!
Waves, wind, storms, sharks, the whole package!
But the Thai seas aren't crawling with sharks.
Damn…
Even you agree with this in the letter.
That's just a metaphor.
Metaphor?
Whatever. From now on, absolutely no contact with Dream. You understand?
Yes.
I'm so glad we could meet. Thanks so much for helping me.
If there's anything I can do to show my appreciation, just tell me.
Tell me what you want to eat and have.
What if Dream was the one who contacted me?
Did Dream text you?
Yes.
What's up? Why are you grinning like that?
I'm thrilled. She is the first girl, other than my mom, to text me.
I'm happy for you.
So, what did she text?
- Okay.
- Can I reply?
Just go ahead.
My favorite food is BBQ.
Now I want a 2-terabyte hard drive.
No! You can't send that. Delete it all.
Why? I…
I told you to delete it. Just delete it.
I just answered all her questions.
She wanted to know what I want to eat and what I want now.
If I tell you to delete it, delete it, and type what I tell you. Okay?
No need to repay me.
"No need to repay me" means that Dream doesn't have to return you the favor.
But it doesn't mean you don't have to repay me.
I see.
"No need to repay me."
- Simply seeing you is more than enough.
- "Simply seeing you is more than enough."
I'm always happy to help you.
"I'm always happy to help you."
If there's anything I can help with, just tell me.
"If there's anything I can help with, just tell me."
- Sweet dreams.
- "Sweet dreams."
XOXO.
No "XOXO".
Why not?
No "XOXO." Are you a child?
See.
That's okay.
May I send it?
- Or should I end with XOXO?
- No need for XOXO.
Emoji?
Or…
Mr. Jiraphat?
No need to repay me. Simply seeing you is more than enough.
I'm always happy to help you.
If there's anything I can help with, just tell me. Sweet dreams. XOXO.
- Are you home?
- Grandma, look at here!
Grandma, do you know who I met today?
I met Korn and got his number, too.
Which Korn?
Korn, my first love, do you remember?
But you told me he stood you up.
Finally, he came. And he came at the perfect time.
He looked so handsome like a hero riding on a white horse to me.
One more thing. He runs his own company and is really skilled in IT.
Grandma, feel it. My heart is still racing.
[Grandma's Pancake Rolls]
So how was your meeting with Korn?
Dream said he looked so good like a runway model.
Grandma, any man looks good in a suit.
No man looks good without one.
Except me.
I can tell you that he is a total nerd. Extremely emotionless.
When I talked to him, it was like talking to a wall.
He must talk to a robot the whole day. So nerdy.
- Nerd?
- Yes.
Is there anything else for me to carry?
Why is it not like what Dream said?
But anyway, I have to thank you for your help.
Dream was very happy yesterday.
I haven't seen her so happy for a long time.
It's okay. But I'm more worried after this.
I think Dream will find out the truth.
Now, Dream is having a sweet dream
without knowing what the truth is.
It's time to wake up her from that dream.
I have to tell her I wrote those letters.
If so,
Dream will be so disappointed.
It's bound to happen, sooner or later.
Better now than later.
Thank you, Good boy, for helping me.
Have you sent the files?
- It's done.
- Okay.
- If this file is on time, just send it.
- Yes.
Even though I am in the US, you must report to me if something happens here.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, madam.
You said you didn't like to come here.
Do you miss Dad?
If it's not necessary, I wouldn't have come.
So, have you contacted your sister?
How is she?
I haven't contacted her. I don't have her number.
Why don't you contact her? After all, you are still sisters.
Mom, is this your necessity?
I don't have that much time.
Will you really go back to the subsidiary company in the US?
Well, Father ordered it. Do I have a choice?
And here?
You didn't think about choosing for yourself at all, did you?
Can I choose?
You must try talking to your father.
Start to fight. Don't just give in.
Is that all you want to say? I have work to do.
See you.
It's been a while since you've been back, but you haven't had any time at all. You must be very tired.
- I'm not tired, Dad. I can handle this.
- That's not true.
I saw you working hard without resting until your face got this haggard.
Thank you for your concern.
I'm a terrible father. Really selfish.
I should've cared about my daughter's health.
How about this?
- This company.
- Yes?
Why don't you have your brother handle things here?
And you just focus on the US branch.
Are you going to kick me out of the CEO position?
Not exactly.
Do you really think your father will let you run his empire?
But before you leave, I might need you to train me.
I'm still not that skilled.
Otherwise, I would be managing the US branch.
But, Father, would the shareholders and investors approve of this?
Suddenly changing the CEO like this could damage the company's credibility.
You don't have to worry about credibility.
As for the shares…
what's my ownership percentage?
It's 72 percent, plus mine's 14 percent. It's exactly 86.
Just Witoon and I make the decisions.
Who else do you need to care about?
Think of this as my gift.
I'm really worried about you. I don't want you to work too hard.
You should have a work-life balance.
Yes.
So, what's your plan now?
Now the manager and Jack's FC are putting a lot of pressure on the boss.
I'm just a small webpage reporter. No influence, no wealth.
What chance do I have against a famous star?
Go to the 32nd floor using the elevator in the High Zone over there.
Thank you very much.
Is it true?
So, what's your next move, Dream?
If you get let go, what's your plan?
You look so unfazed.
[HIGH ZONE]
[135789 23-24]
Probably a full-time employee with just a few Baht for salary.
Just wait and see. My business will be bigger than Mark Zuckerberg
and Steve Jobs level, so big that you can't even compete.
I've made up my mind. I'd like to take the elevator to the High Zone.
Are you really going to resign?
Yes, I've made up my mind.
I have a new goal in life.
I want to take the High-Zone elevator.
Yes, Mom.
Are you really leaving?
Are you going to see me off?
I might be gone for a long time.
If you're just leaving to live abroad, I'd see you off.
But if you're giving up everything you've built, just go.
Today, your father is calling a shareholders' meeting.
Make up your mind.
So, if nobody objects, from now on, I will be the CEO in place of Ms. Alice.
Please support me.
Haven't you left for the US yet?
I thought you were leaving today.
I just wanted to come and congratulate my brother first
for getting his position by stealing someone else's job.
And I also came to thank my father for teaching me a valuable lesson
that what is easily obtained can easily be taken away.
CEOs like me, who don't have shares, are probably like chewing gum
that Dad chews and then spits out. Right?
Another thing,
I'm not going to the US.
I'm handing over all the tasks in this company to this loser.
You mean me?
What do you mean?
From today, I am no longer involved with this company.
I quit!
Alice! I told you to reclaim your position, not to quit.
- Are you crazy?
- Yes, I'm crazy.
But I don't want anyone to tell me again that I'm successful because my dad is rich.
Most importantly,
I don't want to be anyone's puppet again.
What will you get from this?
I'm relieved, Mom. I'm free now. Maybe you should try it.
You made this company grow. Aren't you sorry for leaving it like this?
I'm sorry, Mom.
But this position wasn't mine from the beginning.
From now on, I will build everything myself.
[San Francisco]
Looks like the MFP 43.2 is winning, right?
[/Coda-Committee]
It actually has the fastest FPS, too! That's unbelievable.
Yes, they are Samkorn Thai Tech from Thailand.
Thailand! That's unbelievable. What is the name of the developer?
- Their head developer's name is Korn.
- Korn?
Please make sure I meet this guy when he gets here.
Sure! But I think there're going to be a lot of people wanting to meet him after this.
Yes. They have the highest score and break the record as well.
Korn, I'm really looking forward to meeting you.
- Hello, Grandma .
- Where are you?
I'm going to see Korn.
Hey! You guys, Dream is coming!
Hey, Grandma, what's up?
Dream is going to Korn's company,
and I haven't told her the truth yet.
What? When is she going?
Right now. What should we do?
Don't worry. I'll handle this.
Pack up anything you don't need. Got it.
Shouldn't you tell Mr. Jiraphat that Dream is coming?
I totally forgot. I was too caught up in the moment. It's him.
- Hello.
- Dream is heading to your company, right?
Grab your essentials from the office
and head to my place. I'll send you the location.
Computer! Take only the computer.
- Hurry up!
- Where's my bag?
You're not helping me carry it. Here it is. I'm coming.
- Come on in!
- Hi, Mr. Jiraphat.
Put everything on the table.
Which table?
There is only one table!
- Not that table.
- Mr. Jiraphat, where is the electric socket?
- The socket should be in the back.
- There's only one?
Can you handle it more gently?
Do we have to sweat this much?
Stop complaining. Just organize things first.
Give it to me.
Quick!
- There's another socket.
- Go use that one.
Mr. Jiraphat, where should we put this?
Bank, what about the sign?
Right there?
Watch out for the walls.
­[Taxi Meter]
Get up quickly and change.
Change clothes?
Do you have to wear a suit at home?
Why not? It's stylish.
Come on, just put it on. You'll look good.
Take off the watch.
But no one can see it anyway.
Take it off.
Thank you.
Is that her?
- Go get it. Open the door quickly.
- Yes.
Key, come here!
Let me put away the hangers first.
Have you packed everything?
You arrived so quickly. Just come in.
­[Thai Tech]
Is this your office or your house? It's very beautiful.
We rented this place as an office.
This is Thanakorn
and Kirakorn. The three of us co-founded Samkorn Thai Tech.
- Hello, you can call me Bank.
- Bank.
Hello, I'm Kirakorn.
But hey, here's the real deal.
I'm actually the president of Samkorn Thai Tech Company.
Just pulling your leg. You can just call me Key.
Sure thing, Key.
So it's like Korn, Thanakorn, Kirakorn.
That's why it's called Samkorn* Thai Tech, right?
(*Sam means 3, three Korns
Exactly. We've got three of us, you know.
And "Korn" means hands. So technically, it's six korns. Right?
Six korns, right?
- Just take a seat.
- Okay.
- I'm so smart.
- Whatever.
Mr. Ji!
What brings you here?
I'm interested in investing in Samkorn Thai Tech.
So, what brings you here?
I wanted to stop by to see Korn for a moment.
Please, feel free.
I wanted to bring this to you.
Goldfish are believed to bring good fortune and wealth.
Just find a jar for it.
How can a goldfish make a person rich?
(Thank you).
Ah... Thank you.
And… I have good news to share.
Good news?
Today, I decided to quit my job.
And I'm going to start a company like you did.
Like me?
I got inspiration from you.
I was really hopeless before. I felt like I was no match with my sister.
And I keep finding excuses that I'm younger than her.
But when I met you. You're even younger than my sister.
But you own a company.
So I decided I wanted to be like you.
Like me?
Yes.
I will also be more successful than my sister.
Please support me.
Keep fighting.
Bank, why don't you return the suit?
- It's cold.
- You said you didn't want to wear it.
My computer?
Where is it?
Korn.
Here it is.
What's this for?
It's the compensation as we agreed.
How much longer do we have to keep up this act?
Just for today, Dream's grandmother decided to tell her the truth.
About the letters and what happened at the party.
Then, what did we even come here for today?
Good question.
Sorry for wasting your time.
Anyway, thank you so much.
When you're done, don't forget to tidy up.
I cannot accept this.
Korn.
That day, I decided to see Dream myself. Not because you hired me.
And about the lie to Dream, can we hold off on telling her the truth for now?
No, today is already a mess.
Seriously, we told her two lies.
First, you wrote the letters 15 years ago and we told her it was me.
Second, we told her I'm a hotshot CEO.
As for the first lie, all will be fine if you don't tell and I don't tell.
And how about the second one?
As for the second one, if we can get into the Sandbox
and become successful, it becomes true.
Get into Sandbox?
Don't even dream about it. It's impossible.
Why do you keep saying it's impossible?
You haven't even seen our work yet.
Because it's impossible.
Even if your technology is good, your business plan can't entice investors.
How do you plan to sustain long-term profitability?
More importantly, you guys have no guarantees for your abilities at all.
Isn't that just a pipe dream?
- Bank .
- What?
- Look at this.
- What's this?
Is it what I think?
Yes! Look at this, Korn.
Korn! Look, we won first place in CODA!
Samkorn Thai Tech won the top prize!
Hooray! We did it!
You did it!
Take a look at this. It's proof of our capabilities.
Now you can stop looking down on us.
CODA!
Got the lighting? Here it is. Hold the reflector.
Okay. Bank, you might want to put on a hat.
- What about the reflector?
- Tilt it up a bit.
- Higher!
- Yeah. A little more!
- This?
- Okay.
Okay then. Wear it well. Turn your hat up a little.
Nice. Are you ready?
Do we really have to film this?
Of course, we do.
We don't have time to apply for a visa, so we need to send this clip.
The world must know about Samkorn Thai Tech.
- Ready?
- Hold on! So, what do we have to say?
Yeah, what's the script?
Leo Burnett, the advertising genius, once said:
"Ads should be simple, memorable, fun and catchy."
- Hey, you know Leo Burnett?
- Of course!
That's my motto, too.
- Do you know Leo Burnett?
- Yeah!
Then, let's come up with three impactful sentences.
We are the future. We need a partner.
And we make a lot of money.
- That's it. Good. Let's go. Ready?
- Okay.
Ready, three, two, one. Action!
"Hi. I'm Korn, CEO of the Samkorn Thai Tech.
And…
we are the future, we need a partner, and we need a lot of money."
Okay, cut. Great. Very good. We're done.
Is that all?
That's it, just like the script. The rest will be edited.
Just one take?
Well, believe me. I am Leo Burnett of Thailand.
As for your pay?
No worry about that. We're cousins.
But I didn't pay you for the business cards.
Never mind it. Just call me when you need help.
Video production, editing, PR, marketing. I get you covered,
but I want 1% of your shares. kay?
Right?
Can I have another take?
It's already good. Trust me. Great!
- Are we done?
- We are.
- Come on.
- Do you think we got it?
Why don't you want to tell Dream the truth?
I came to think about it. Keeping this secret shouldn't be any harm.
I won't tell. You won't tell. No one will know.
And what about Korn?
I will make Korn the perfect man. Just like in the letter.
I don't think it's easy.
Grandma, trust me. I'm so talented.
Guys.
- Do we really have to send a video?
- Yes, of course.
Our message should reach the world.
Some major global companies will definitely take notice of us.
We're talking about dealing with giants like Google or Apple.
Small players like Mr.Ji's company just aren't on our level.
Really?
But I think Mr. Ji is the best partner for us.
- Why?
- How?
I think we and Mr. Ji have the same objective function.
Objective function?
Why go through such difficulty? I don't get it.
I want to do something for you.
And...
I'm so worried that I can't sleep.
You've been fine all along. Why can't you sleep all of a sudden?
Well, you wouldn't want to disappoint your granddaughter, would you?
Don't worry, Grandma.
Korn, the man of her dreams, I'll make it happen.
Your guys look at this.
What?
We and the investors have two types of networks.
Let's say two networks were to find the Nash Equilibrium.
That means the investors and us, Mr. Ji and Samkorn Thai Tech…
have two networks.
- We're listening.
- Go on.
But if we are too different, it will be hard to calculate the loss function
and learning won't be easy.
But what if…
we have the same objective function?
Then you will only need one loss function.
- And the learning process will be easier.
- Exactly.
Why are you bullshitting?
This is why people talk shit about engineering majors.
You could've just said that Mr. Ji shares the same goal with us.
So, we can expect a good result. That's it.
- No need to be convoluted.
- Right.
Yes, our company's goal is success.
And Mr. Ji wants our company to be successful as well.
Because Mr. Ji doesn't want to disappoint Dream, just like me.
- Like you?
- Yeah.
I can understand the thing about Mr. Ji and Dream.
They have a history, so it's natural for him to want to help her.
But what I don't get is why you would pretend to be Korn in the letter.
Yes! She's just a stranger.
And if she's disappointed, what does that have to do with you? Why do you care?
I don't want Dream to be disappointed.
Do you have feelings for Dream?
You're making such an effort to spare Dream from disappointment,
because you have feelings for her. Right?
♫ Still I found you there in my dreams ♫
♫ Still I'm lost in our memories ♫
♫ Don't know how long it's gonna be ♫
- No.
- Yes, I like Dream.
♫ I'm begging for the star to shine me back the light ♫
[Welcome to Sandbox Next Gen]­
[Why do you want to start a startup?]
[I want to use an executive's elevator.]
[I deserve better.]
[To turn a misunderstanding into reality.]
[To return a favor.]
[Follow your dream.]
Why do you want to join Sandbox?
[Next Episode]
Nobody, including you, will truly see what I'm capable of.
Are you stupid?
How could you give away the whole algorithm like that?
Dream said she'd take me to the beach to celebrate her birthday.
What wish did you write down?
My wish?
You don't have the DNA of being an executive.
If you get into Sandbox, you should find a new CEO.
Welcome everyone to the 9th generation of Sandbox.
Why are you here?
And why is your CEO boyfriend here?
♫ It’s like the stars have been snuffed out ♫
♫ It’s not the same, they’re not shining enough for me to see the way ♫
♫ The fading sky ends up in darkness ♫
♫ There’s no hand for me to hold from someone who was once beside me ♫
♫ I’m going in circles in the same place ♫
♫ Where we used to be before you abandoned me ♫
♫ However much I run, whatever I do ♫
♫ I find only exhaustion ♫
♫ When I close my eyes, I still see your image ♫
♫ Whichever way I look, I still see you ♫