Working as a BA makes
the passing of seasons feel so fast.
After summer,
we've already moved on to
the holiday collection
after the Christmas season for winter,
and as soon as the new year arrives,
we start preparing for
the spring collection.
If you blend them together like this,
it will look very beautiful.
You're right.
And...
our cohabitation life has already
passed six months.
Huh?
You've been promoted to makeup artist?
I applied just to try,
without any expectations,
but Nanjo-san supported me.
(Makeup artist Sahashi Toma)
That's amazing! So awesome!
You did it, Toma!
Wow!
Come on, be more excited!
I am glad,
but it looks like you're more thrilled.
Of course I'm thrilled!
And...
there's our collaboration stage
at the TSS event, right?
I've been assigned to work there.
So, you'll be doing makeup
for the models backstage?
Yes.
Wow, that's amazing!
I wonder what it'll feel like to see
the models you've done makeup
for walking the stage.
Let me know how it feels.
Feels?
Mmm.
Oh, Tenma is coming too.
Tenma-san is?
It seems my family's brand
is exhibiting.
I hope we don't run into each other.
If you run into him, make sure to
greet him properly.
He'll get lonely otherwise.
Hmm?
Anyway,
congratulations!
I'll definitely come to see it!
Alright,
I'll do my best too!
Wow, amazing.
Makeup artist...
(Romy Feerique Lounge)
The Tokyo Style Stage,
or TSS,
is a fashion show-centric event,
- but every year,
- Alright.
- there are collaborative stages
- Here.
- featuring cosmetic brands.
- All good.
- Yes.
- This year, Romy
is participating for the first time.
Good work today.
Oh, Mamiya-kun, what brings you here?
I got a ticket from Tanouchi-san,
so I came to see Romy's stage.
As expected from a workaholic.
You never missed anything.
Hey, Toma.
Toma, huh?
Sahashi.
Even if you correct it,
this brother still heard it.
Toma, Toma, Toma, To...
Toma!
What a relief.
- Tenma-san.
- What's with you?
Long time no see, Mamiya Natsume.
More importantly, Toma,
I beg you,
please be our brand's model.
No way.
Huh?
Hey, who's this?
- Why not?
- He's Toma's older brother.
Hey!
- Sahashi's older brother?
- Why not?
Hear me out first.
My model...
The model scheduled to appear on
Tenma-san's brand stage was injured,
I can only count on you.
- A replacement couldn't come in time.
- They're a bit similar.
Please, I'm begging you!
You owe me one,
Toma.
Are you going to do it?
Yeah.
I changed my mind.
In that case, I'll do my best.
Sit down here.
- Absolutely not.
- Huh?
Natsume-san.
Huh?
No, but I'm...
Then I won't do it.
- Huh?
But I don't know how to
do runway makeup.
You won't mind if I give some advice
from the side, right?
That's fine.
Natsume-san,
I'll be in your care.
Alright then!
Leave it to me!
Alright.
So let's start with the base.
Mmm.
My hands are shaking.
Even though I've touched this guy's face
so many times,
this feeling,
is different from any of them.
I will do everything I can to make Toma
the coolest
with all I've got.
It's done.
Thanks.
Okay, then,
fitting.
I'll show you, let's go.
Toma.
Do your best.
Yes.
Huh?
Hey, I'm standing here, you know?
Toma's back had already become
that of a model
and was shining very brightly.
Everyone will see Tomoya,
the one I did makeup for.
Still looking at those photos?
They're just so cool.
So, how was it?
Seeing the model you did makeup
for walk the runway?
Well...
Mmm...
It was…
amazing.
Even days later,
I still get excited
just thinking about it.
Seeing the audience in front
captivated by you,
feeling their excitement…
Isn't it cool?
Yeah, I did the makeup.
It made me feel proud.
Mmm.
Makeup is all about
making people shine
and smile.
That's how it is.
But since I'm in BA,
I want to continue
standing at the counter
and make even more customers smile.
You're truly a dedicated workaholic,
Natsume-san.
But it was worth modeling.
Hmm?
You
didn't do it just for that, did you?
Is there any other reason to do it?
Toma.
Thank you.
You looked so cool!
Thanks to Tenma-san keeping
Toma's media exposure to a minimum.
It seems like Toma was successfully
kept out of sight of the customers,
but there's no doubt
that the model industry noticed.
Work?
A contact from my modeling days.
I see.
He constantly gets
messages from former colleagues.
Yes.
No. It's been a while.
Ah...
It was a coincidence,
I was working for Romy.
Yes.
Thanks for your hard work.
Are you free now?
Yes, I'm free.
The TSS stage the other day is being
talked about in the PR department.
There's a discussion about hiring
Sahashi-kun as a PR model
for our men's cosmetics.
Huh?
He should be talking with
the PR department at the HQ right now.
He…
went on stage for me and now...
What? Is it about the model role?
Yeah.
I heard from Tanouchi-san.
I'm really sorry.
It must have been tough to refuse.
No, I accepted it.
Huh?
Why?
Hmm, because the conditions were right?
Conditions?
Ah, hello.
It's been a while.
Yes.
Could it be that he's seriously
considering returning to modeling?
He just became a makeup artist.
It was just starting…
Is this really okay, Toma?
Are you sure about this?
If it's come to this, I...
will keep Toma tied down!
Natsume-san, is something wrong?
You've been acting weird since earlier.
Toma,
the next event you're assigned
to is at our store, right?
Yes, that's right.
Then...
let's have a personal sales competition!
A competition?
If I lose,
you can return to modeling
or do whatever you want.
But
if I win...
you must listen to my request.
Got it.
Alright.
I'll make you do as I request.
Huh?
Watch me.
Alright.
From now on,
we're not lovers
but rivals!
You say that,
but you'll still cling
to me tonight, right?
No,
until the result is out,
I'm going to sleep in the living room.
Strictly no flirting allowed!
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
Understood.
I'll watch ‘senpai's' seriousness.
This is my personal color,
but I prefer this color.
What do you think, Mamiya-san?
I bought some eyeshadows and other items
that aren't available in Japan,
but I can't seem to use them properly.
Personal color is important,
but you can to try the colors you like
without being constrained by it.
I might be able to offer
some makeup suggestions.
Please consider it for
the next opportunity.
- We look forward to seeing you again.
Hey, don't stick so close.
This is part of the job.
By the way,
are you aware of the quickly diminishing
stock of the freebies?
Don't do anything careless like
running out early in the event,
Chief.
What's with that attitude?
Welcome.
Toma!
It's been a while.
Risako told me.
I didn't know you were with Romy.
You haven't changed at all.
You could've returned to being a model.
- What are you laughing for?
- Hey, make a come back, yeah?
- No, no.
- Do makeup for me please.
- Refuse now!
- Right?
- Please recommend products for me.
- Tell them...
I won't let him return!
Then oil products then.
Sales are looking good.
At this rate, we might reach
a pretty high position
compared to other stores.
Really?
Ah, sit down.
Especially since Sahashi-kun's
model-related customers
have been spreading
the word on social media,
it's been quite effective.
The average spend per customer
is also high.
Yes.
As for you,
your customer age range is
broader than Sahashi-kun's,
and your turnover rate is good,
so it's really well-balanced.
The overall atmosphere
at the counter is good,
and morale is high.
Keep up the good work!
Yes.
Thank you!
I won't give up.
I'll do my best.
And yet...
Ah...
Good night…
Good night.
I'm tired…
and lonely.
Sorry for the wait.
Here to pick up the items, yes?
Yes.
- Sasaki-san.
- Yes?
- Please take care of this customer.
- After that,
- Sorry for the wait.
- we're still rivals,
- There are customers waiting in line now.
- and the event reached its final day.
This is the queue card.
This day coincided with the weekend,
leading to customers waiting in line.
Aizawa-san, sorry.
Hmm?
Since it looks like it'll get crowded
in the afternoon,
I was thinking of shortening the day-of
reservations to 45-minute intervals.
I think that's fine.
Alright, I'll do that.
- Looking good, Mamiya.
- Sorry for the wait.
Yes, it is.
In the end,
I didn't reach the top spot
in individual sales.
But my stable sales
and high customer satisfaction
were recognized,
and I was awarded.
Chief Mamiya,
congratulations on the Rookie award.
- Congratulations!
Thank you, everyone!
Well then, let's hear a few words
from Mamiya-kun.
Huh?
Come on, stand up.
Oh, okay.
Alright.
Umm...
I believe this award
is not just mine
but something we all achieved together.
I aspired to be in BA since
I was in elementary school.
I wanted to make people shine like that.
That was my inspiration.
I knew it would be tough with
so few men in the field,
but when I achieved my dream,
there were many challenges.
But
making customers smile with my own hands
and earning their trust
is incredibly rewarding.
I've faced my work
with the determination
to never forget that feeling.
I'm...
still inexperienced as a chief,
but the positive feedback from customers
is thanks to everyone's efforts.
I'm truly grateful to you all.
I...
I love this job as a beauty advisor.
A lot.
Has Harada-san received the item yet?
And Aizawa-san...
(Sahashi Toma: Meet me at
the fountain plaza later)
Mamiya-san
is so cool.
Harukawa, try to follow him.
Yes.
Do your best.
Toma!
I wanted to see it with Natsume-san.
Yeah.
It's beautiful.
Congratulations on the award.
You too, right?
You won the Rookie Artist Award.
Congrats!
Are you happy?
Of course!
It's my first time being awarded.
But...
I didn't reach the top in
individual sales like you did.
Are you frustrated?
Of course I am!
Besides,
that promise...
If I lose,
you can return to modeling
or do whatever you want.
As promised, I'll do what I like.
I didn't mean ‘do what you like'
like this.
I...
If you want to return to modeling, then…
I won't.
Huh?
I'm suited for behind-the-scenes work,
and I actually like my current job.
Then...
why did you do modeling for our brand?
Oh.
Even though it was called modeling,
I turned down opportunities
to show off fancy outfits.
As a makeup artist,
wearing a uniform would be too flashy.
Then...
why the competition with me?
That is...
When I talked to the PR team at HQ,
I told them that if they wanted to
focus on male staff,
Natsume-san would be better.
Why did you say that?
Because Natsume-san
loves his job
and takes pride in it,
and BA is more accessible to customers.
However,
the PR person said that
my job is more glamorous
and I have a better future.
That's to be expected.
I was really annoyed that Natsume-san
was being underestimated.
So I wanted to
prove myself in the event
and show that PR person.
Was that all?
Yes.
That's trivial.
What's that all about?
Even if it seems trivial to you,
I was frustrated seeing you
being underestimated.
I thought you must have misunderstood
about the modeling,
if I could stir up
your competitive spirit,
you would work harder.
I was…
desperately afraid you
might quit makeup.
I won't quit.
I really like this job.
But...
I...
like you as a model too.
Huh?
But more than that,
I think you look even more dazzling and
cool when you're doing makeup.
Ah...
Sure, there are things
about you that annoy me.
But
working together and doing
many things is enjoyable,
and I'm glad you're here.
I'm sorry. I lied.
The reason I accepted
the challenge with you…
I said it was because
I was annoyed with PR,
but it wasn't just that.
It's because I couldn't
stay away from you,
hoping you wouldn't be
able to stay away from me either.
If there's anything I can do
for what Natsume-san wants
or aims for,
I will do everything I can
to make you believe that
you can achieve it with me
and that you can't live without me.
I...
am desperate to become someone
essential to your life.
You think about a lot of things.
It must be tough,
you got caught by someone like me.
Is it tough?
I...
I love Natsume-san so much
that even I am surprised myself,
so it's very hard
because it's heavy and annoying.
So...
I'll tell you something good.
I also...
love you a lot, too, you know.
You don't have to think so much.
When I
wake up in the morning
and when I go to sleep at night,
if you're there…
I'm incredibly happy.
"Cosmetic Playlover"
(Episode 8)
The competition is over,
so we can finally be affectionate.
No,
I haven't given up yet!
I'm going to become a better BA
and definitely surpass you!
Watch me!
Alright.
I'm serious!
I'm really serious!
Yes, yes.
I understand, Natsume-san.