[English subtitles are available]
[Forever and Ever]
[Episode 19]
I am so not used to
his sudden missing.
You are drinking alone?
Want some?
No, thanks.
What's up?
Nothing.
Then why are you constantly staring at your phone?
I sent Shi Yi a text,
yet she hasn't responded.
Why don't you just call her?
She's in sleep,
I am afraid I will disturb her.
You two
are too polite to be a couple.
Shi Yi went to the hospital.
Give me the car key.
Why do you want the key?
I am a faster driver.
You just drank, didn't you?
[Family of Books and Ritual]
I forgot that, then you drive.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Why did you bring Wang Yingdong here?
We were at the same party just now.
I was drunk, so I was unable to drive.
He knew that I was coming for you
and never gave me a chance to say no.
Well, put this under your wrist.
Where did you get this?
I bought it downstairs.
No, thanks. I am good, I am not feeling cold.
Well, then you take care of her.
Okay, I got it.
The drip is done.
I'll go get the nurse.
Just take it as a normal concern
from your colleague.
And that's it.
I am afraid he would misunderstand that
I had feelings for him if I used it.
You are very good at keeping the right distance, huh?
Of course.
Excuse me.
May I ask where the transfusion room is?
Hi.
Patient Shi Yi in the transfusion room needs to change her IV bottle.
Shi Yi, right?
Follow me, please.
Let's go.
Shi Yi, right?
When did you arrive?
One minute ago.
Come on, have a seat.
How are you?
You are still a bit feverish.
Not that fast.
This is Mei Xing, he's a lawyer.
Nice to meet you.
Did you come here together?
I was afraid he might get distracted
due to his worry about you,
so I came along.
And I happen to have an old friend
that I'll go visit in Shanghai tomorrow.
We gotta go.
Can you accompany her throughout the night?
Is that even a question?
I am her husband.
If I don't keep her company, who else will?
Here's the thing.
We know that you are usually very busy.
As her friends,
we will definitely come here for her, right?
Thank you.
We are now leaving.
Bye.
Then I am leaving too.
Where are you going?
You two have made it to see each other,
which means my job is done.
I am going somewhere for fun.
Bye.
Why is your hand so cold?
The hospital Wenxing often goes to
is near here.
Do I need to take you there?
The doctors there will be better.
I am too tired to move.
I didn't know
Wang Yingdong would come here today.
Are you jealous?
No.
Get closer to me.
Closer.
Come on.
I will do it when we go home.
Wait a minute for me.
I will be right back.
Stay here.
Hi, I'm wondering
how long it will take
before she can go home?
Your wife is Shi Yi, right?
That's right.
At least three hours.
Are there any wards available here?
They've already been occupied.
Thank you.
Hello.
This is Zhousheng Chen.
Help me book a ward
near the Central Hospital.
Thanks.
I am only here
to get some tea today.
I never expected to see you coming for me.
This is a very remote area
where it's difficult to get a cab.
How are you gonna go back
if you get drunk?
Let's drink first
and not talk about future for now
Right.
If you overdrink,
there's a staff dormitory here.
Great alcohol.
Take it slowly.
The heated alcohol
is easy to make people drunk.
What's the matter? You have something in mind?
Grown-ups
all have something in mind
that they find it hard to talk about.
That's right.
Here.
I don't have a lot of friends here
and I am afraid that I would say something wrong if I get drunk.
So I couldn't come to those I am familiar with either.
That's why you are here for me?
Okay, okay.
Isn't it good that I could go home to sleep
after getting 3 to 4 hours of infusion
over there?
Your husband cares about you.
Isn't it better to have a ward?
So that you can sleep whenever you want.
Take a good rest.
Thank you.
Go have a rest now, it's over 10 pm now.
Sit down.
Sit here.
You are not sleepy?
No.
I have to chat with you.
All right, go ahead.
I am a patient, you want me to talk?
Okay, then I will be the one to speak.
What do you want to hear?
Describe what was on your mind when you felt jealous just now.
Just tell me about it.
Not feeling well.
And?
It's just not feeling well.
Don't put me off.
Did you fail your Chinese tests when you were young?
I was not bad at Chinese,
although I never got a full mark.
Who could get a full mark in Chinese tests?
Do you actually know
what it means to be modest?
For those I am not good at,
I am always very modest.
What about those you specialize in?
In the fields where I specialize,
modesty leads to fear.
It will stop people from making progress.
That's way off the point.
You brought it up first.
All right, my fault.
Go on.
Talk about how you feel about jealousy.
Where are you going?
Your question is pretty tough to answer.
I need more time
to think about it.
How's the water temperature?
The water you fetched must be warm.
You see, you are such a grown-up,
yet you still want me to take care of you.
How about me helping you
wash your feet later?
No need for that.
Lin Fei.
It's late at night, what's going on?
Why are you not sleeping?
Me Xing overdrank
in the tea plant on the outskirt.
Would you mind
helping me pick him up?
No, not at all.
It's just overdrinking.
Lin Fei, hurry up and go pick him up.
Okay, no problem.
Needless to say,
I won't feel easy if this was handed to others.
Hurry up.
Slowly, slowly.
I am sorry to bother you today.
Mr. Zhao.
Don't mention it.
It was my fault as well.
I shouldn't have given him so much to drink.
Uncle Zhao.
I am not drunk.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you are not, you are not.
Let's keep drinking.
-Go on.
-Let's keep drinking after getting in the car.
Be careful.
Let's go.
Slowly.
Watch out, watch out.
Yeah, okay.
Sorry to trouble you, Mr. Zhao.
Now go.
Okay, we are leaving, Mr. Zhao.
Drive slowly.
Be careful.
Get off the car.
Don't dilly-dally.
Get all of your
valuable stuff out.
Bro.
I didn't take anything
valuable with me today.
Cut the crap.
Now, take it out.
I only have this watch
with me.
You can have it.
Anything else?
I, I
have nothing else to give you.
Nothing else?
What are you doing?
Mind your own business.
-Go.
Go.
Mr. Mei.
Uncle Lin.
What's going on here?
They are robbers.
Do we need to call the police?
No.
My father doesn't want me
to get involved in the business here.
It would be more of a trouble if he knew this.
Don't tell anybody what happened today.
Including my father.
But...
But if we don't call the police.
What if it was not a robbery?
Didn't you get beaten for no reason?
I know whom to blame
for this.
All right, let's go home first.
No, I'm not going home.
How about hospital?
Just to tell our family about it.
Wenxing is mousy,
she would be more worried
if she sees what I look like right now.
Let's go dress the wounds.
All right.
Slowly.
You drive that car home.
I will take him to the hospital.
Okay.
Slowly.
Here.
You are back.
Where is Mei Xing?
He drank too much
and let nobody touch him,
so he went to sleep there.
Uncle Lin went to find you, did you see him?
Yeah, we did.
He is with him there.
Thank you for tonight.
I have to go now.
Zhousheng Chen.
Are you sleep walking?
You haven't fallen asleep yet?
I did, and now I am awake.
I walked around
your bed
and I noticed the central air-conditioner
is blowing right towards your legs and feet.
I am afraid you might catch a cold,
so I went to turn up
the heat.
I have the quilt on me, the cold air won't get me.
You like to kick the quilt.
Nonsense.
I never do.
I just realized marriage is pretty good.
You just realized
how good it is to get married?
I have been to hospital alone
ever since I started to work.
I would feel sorry
if I had to bother my friends
as they needed to work the next morning.
If I asked my parents to come with me,
I would be afraid they would get too worried.
What about you?
Who would go to a doctor with you?
I have always been alone.
Only when I had a minor surgery
that I asked my classmate to go with me.
Didn't your family accompany you?
They didn't know.
Well, why didn't you ask someone from the corporate
to come along?
I didn't know them at that time.
No wonder
the driver in Bremen said
he had never seen you in the company.
I didn't have to.
I was not interested anyway.
Then who would drive for you?
You were not good at driving, were you?
It only takes ten minutes
from my institute to the apartment on foot.
I didn't need to drive.
Well, there were definitely occasions
when you need them, right?
When you need to go to the supermarket
and buy some food or daily essentials,
a car is handy for carrying stuff.
Whether they are food
or daily essentials,
my institute has got them all.
You are the one
with the least requirements for your life
among all the people I know.
What a couple,
you guys have been talking since the moment you moved in
and you are still talking once she woke up in the middle of night.
What a great relationship you have.
You don't feel uncomfortable, right?
No.
The lady's husband.
Our patient needs to rest.
Time to sleep.
Then I'll go to bed.
Good night.
I can't fall asleep.
Zhousheng Chen.
Can you talk with me a little bit longer?
Professor Zhousheng?
Mr. Zhousheng?
Zhousheng Chen.
Fell asleep so soon?
Why did you come down here?
I can't fall asleep if you are not holding me in your arms.
Go sleep on the bed.
I want to sleep here.
All right.
Good night.
Why is your face black and blue?
I accidentally fell down.
You alcoholic.
Why can't you drink at home?
Why did you have to go out?
Your family has got too many rules, I dare not.
I gotta go.
You guys continue.
Thank you, Uncle Lin.
Come over here, I will apply some medicine for you.
I have been applied.
What's the matter?
Lean against here.
Here, come on.
Did you feel better?
Afraid, are you?
This is the result of you hiding things from me.
The reason why I didn't tell you
is exactly because I was afraid that you would get too worried.
How many times have you taken this medicine these days?
There was much more
last time I checked it last week.
I dropped some yesterday
and I forgot to refill it.
You need to check it every day from now on.
Why did you drink?
Are you bored at staying at my home?
To release the pressure, obviously.
There is too much pressure from work.
You have a big household with a large fortune
and your family is investing on manufacturing
which has the most powerful growth momentum.
I can't sleep, not even a single night.
Bring me along when you go for a drink next time.
Bring you along?
Well, the next day,
I will get kicked out by your mother.
I will be just watching without drinking.
At best, it's like when I was a kid
and I wanted to have liquor filled chocolate,
you could let me have a lick of that on the sly.
I remember when we were kids
and you were having a chocolate,
you would lick it first
and then put it in my mouth.
And you would start to cry if I didn't take it.
As a result, when my father came in,
he thought I was the one who secretly
let you eat the liquor filled chocolate
and gave me a good kick.
He almost
wasted his own son.
If you want to drink next time,
drink at home.
Anyhow, you have Uncle Lin
and Uncle Chen to take care of you.
Okay.
[Family of Books and Ritual]
Uncle Lin.
Look at the water on the ground.
Stay away, far away.
What a pity
if such a pair of beautiful shoes got stained.
Uncle Lin, I was gonna ask...
You want to ask about what happened last night, right?
They bumped into some robbers for money.
He didn't hold his temper after overdrinking
and took a few hits.
Where did the robbers come from?
He's a man,
it doesn't matter for him to take a few hits.
Meanwhile,
isn't it a good thing
for him to remember
not to overdrink in the future?
Yesterday,
Mei Xing got beaten by others.
Oh, yeah?
How's he?
Do you really have no idea
or are you pretending that you don't know?
My account is now being checked by my own family
while I am being watched by Mr. Mei and his son.
I don't even dare to go to the company,
yet I have to be treated unfairly by my own sister.
Am I not the poorest man here?
My life is way harder than you thought.
The moment Chen was back,
all my plans I'd made these years
were ruined.
I am not only losing my own money.
The ones who co-invested with me
are now trying to get even with me.
We are twins from the same mother
and we share the same blood.
The one you should take most care of
is me.
I just hope you are all safe and sound.
Who doesn't?
Here.
It still feels a bit hot.
Not really.
Our body temperatures are pretty much the same.
I will buy you
a thermometer.
We have one at home.
It's in the right drawer of the desk.
Here.
You see, 36.9 degrees,
pretty normal.
This is tasteless.
You are still recovering.
You should eat something bland.
Add some sugar, can I?
How much?
Half a spoon.
A quarter of a spoon.
Who is it?
Zhousheng Chen's wife?
It's mine.
It's the vegetables I bought, take them in.
Give it to me, please.
Here.
Thank you, thank you.
You bought vegetables.
We agreed, a quarter of a spoon.
You're stingy.
So that marks us
officially living our lives together.
So what do you
want to talk about?
House chores.
Okay.
I have hired a
cleaning lady to do the cleaning job
and she has been working for almost four years.
She will come over to have three times of thorough cleaning every week.
So, we don't have to
worry about cleaning.
She is from a financially embarrassed family
and she works really hard.
If there's no problem,
I don't want to fire her.
No need to fire her.
You have the final say in this house.
I can cook.
So, no need to
hire another one to cook for us.
Bad news is we need to wash to dishes
and clean up the kitchen ourselves.
Along with doing the laundry, hang the clothes out,
bring the clothes in and fold the clothes.
The fact that you can split one thing
into four
tells me that
you are really not a big fan of doing the laundry.
Washing and hanging them out in particular.
Bringing in and folding clothes are fine.
I'll do it.
I like cooking,
but dislike washing the dishes.
I'll do it.
What about cleaning up the kitchen?
That's my boy.
Here's your reward.
Now, do you think
getting married is actually not bad?
I used to think
that it would be worth getting married
if someone could share the duty of
doing what I hate.
You don't ask for too much
and are easily satisfied.
If you can put up with
having noodles every single day
in the future,
I can also take the job
of cooking.
Cooking is where my happiness is from.
Well, now.
Do you think marrying me
is actually a good thing?
The dishes I make taste like home
and are better than what aunties make.
I'd say I was lucky.
And washing the fruits.
I'll take it.
I am pretty sure
you are born
to marry me.
Everything I hate to do,
you can do them all.
I have always
been into washing things.
Dealing with all kinds of dirty
utensils or cabinets.
What about things in the sink?
I'll do it.
It seems like
you have never gone into this place.
No, I haven't.
Aren't you interested in
my workplace?
Of course, I am.
When I first knew you,
I searched it on the internet
and found some pictures of its interior.
So I have, more or less,
some knowledge about it.
This is my recording studio.
If you want to go in,
just walk in there.
Yours?
Yeah, my workshop rented it.
Let's go.
I will show you my property.
Hey, it's you guys.
Your feet are okay?
Yeah, yeah.
When it comes to this,
I gotta thank you
and your boyfriend.
Sorry, I've got a phone call.
Hello?
Yeah, yeah, I am sorry.
I will be right there.
Okay, okay, okay, will do.
I am sorry.
I've got too many orders.
I gotta go.
Bye.
How did you know him?
Well, by chance.
Let's go.
Miss Shi.
Miss Lin.
This is our sound engineer, Lin Yao.
This is my husband.
Nice to meet you.
It's the first time our beauty
brings her family member here, huh.
You just go on with what you're doing and I'll show him around.
This is the control room.
In there you have the recording studio.
That's the monitor
and the TV in there.
They have the same display signal.
That way, people on both sides
can see the same picture.
Let's get in there and have a look.
Let's go.
When doing the recording, there will be two mics positioned,
one close to you, one far away.
Can you guess why?
To record two sounds.
If you want to use the sound recorded near you,
use the one recorded by the mic that's closer to you.
Otherwise,
use the one recorded by the farther mic.
Almost there.
We read once,
and he will have two soundtracks.
When doing the sound mixing,
depending on the scenario,
he can choose either the closer one or the farther one.
So when you were playing the heroine,
you would sit here and dub
with a male voice actor?
Sometimes I would do dubbing together with another actor.
But it's quite rare
as two people dubbing together
is highly demanding
for their skills.
That's why we would usually do solo recording.
For example, I could,
from this afternoon all the way till tonight,
finish dubbing
about two to three episodes for my own part.
I would usually be the first one to dub.
Because it's always the hardest.
Let's go out and have a look.
With the size of such a recording studio,
how many voice actors
would you recruit?
That depends.
As long as we have voices
of all different ages,
from junior to senior.
We could have a whole package project working.
My workshop
has signed up with dozens of voice actors.
Miss Shi can stand on top of the pyramid
of her industry
at her twenties.
That's pretty impressive.
More impressive than I am.
No, not really.
You are flattering me.
Every time you stood down there waiting for me,
I would be standing here watching you.
Here you are.
[Debit card]
What is it?
My salary card which I just got.
It feels fantastic
to have someone hand to me his salary.
It's like I have the power in my grip
and I have you in my hand.
Miss Shi.
You have a very strong desire for control, do you know that?
Shi Yi,
you are here.
Me and Wang Yingdong
are simply workmates.
He often comes here.
I know.
I have no feelings about him.
Not even a single bit.
I can see that.
Do you really not mind?
Yes, I do.
But I can manage to digest it myself.
Nevertheless, hearing that you said you do
makes me feel a bit proud.
Proud?
I love to see you getting jealous.
Mother,
if you are tired,
I can help you get upstairs to take a rest.
No, I am good.
You don't have to go.
Here, we've got more people to look after each other.
And the grandsons and granddaughters can make you happy.
How wonderful is that?
East or West,
home is the best.
I have been used to living at my own home
and I feel like a guest wherever I go.
I am not going there.
How about we wait till they come back?
Meet each other
and then leave after having a reunion dinner?
Sounds good, good.
So, Chen and his newly married wife.
When are they coming back?
This weekend.
This time after they return.
You gotta treat them better.
It reminds me of
how I treated you
when I saw how you treat them.
I was so stubborn and so subjective,
trying so hard to separate you and the second eldest son of the Zhou family.
It's already too late for me to regret now.
Too late.
Wan.
I hope you won't make the same mistake as I did,
okay?
Mother.
It's been 20 years.
Stop thinking about that.
How regretful I am.