[English subtitles are available]
[Forever and Ever]
[Episode 9]
Do you have any books you like?
I quite like the books here.
Wenxing said that you went to settle something.
It's settled.
As for the rest,
I don't think they'll need me anymore.
Let's go.
I want to take you somewhere.
Where?
Let's go.
You can have a full view of
the old manor from here.
You can even watch the sunset now.
What's up?
I have a fear of heights.
But it's not serious.
Sometimes, I'm fine.
But I think it's pretty bad today.
Come.
♫Spring flowers and autumn moon♫
♫Hidden in my heart♫
♫Write words for you♫
♫Tenderly and carefully♫
♫Rewrite the end of the past♫
♫Let the story continue♫
♫You're in my dreams♫
♫It's getting clearer and clearer♫
Do you feel better like this?
♫When the heart beats, one, two, three, four♫
♫It starts to tremble♫
♫The rhythm of love is composed for you♫
♫Go to the end of the world with you♫
You are right.
♫And be your companion for a lifetime♫
The view here is amazing.
♫When every second of time♫
Do you come here often?
♫Becomes precious♫
I often come up here alone
♫Because of you♫
to enjoy the view
♫I know what heartache feels like♫
and do some thinking.
What are you thinking about right now?
♫Forever and ever is like a dream♫
♫I'll still be with you♫
Chen.
Sorry for
disturbing you.
What's up?
J-Just an allergic reaction to dust.
Let's go then.
Let's go.
Chen.
Why didn't I realize before that
you are so good at acting pitiful?
Are you okay?
I'm fine now.
Don't worry.
I told you just now, right?
His allergy is not severe.
Although he is fine now,
you have to pay attention to him.
Usually, after his allergic reaction,
he feels weak at night.
Make sure
to stay by his side
and take care of him.
I forgot to tell you about the important matter.
Uncle Lin said that the car
is ready.
You can depart at any time.
Where are we going?
We are going to meet my elder.
Again?
How many elders do you have?
This is the most important one.
Are you afraid?
No.
I'm just a little bit nervous since I don't have the experience.
Don't be nervous.
Have you been to Chen's house?
Yes.
But it's different from here.
And they are different from you.
Where are you going?
Let's go into the house.
Okay.
Let's go in.
Let me help.
Be careful.
Be careful of the step.
Over there.
Let's sit over there.
Chen didn't tell me that you'd be coming.
So, I didn't prepare anything for you.
Have some sweets.
[Chocolate]
-Eat this.
-Thank you, Grandmother.
No need to thank me.
Go ahead and eat it.
I just eat it like this?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Is it not good?
No.
It's good.
Eat more then.
Eat more.
Your grandmother gave me this.
You liked it when you were young?
Yes.
You don't like it?
The flavor is very surprising.
But from today onwards,
I'll try to like it.
What are you doing?
This is
her favourite radio.
She listens to it every day.
Just now, I found that
its volume got softer.
So, I want to
fix it for her.
So, besides studying about Venus,
you know how to do this too.
You've been working ever since you came in.
Every time, after raining,
the moss on the floor will become very slippery.
She's old now.
I don't want her to fall.
You do this all by yourself?
I like to
do everything myself.
No matter
how many people you hire,
there's always something that they fail to take care of.
It feels better
to do it yourself.
Indeed.
My mother and uncles
hired a care provider for my grandmother before.
But later they found out that
the care provider didn't like to talk to her
and didn't give her enough time
under the sun.
After some discussions,
they decided to take turns
to take care of her themselves.
Some things may seem trivial,
but those are the things that
only family will pay attention to.
Are you thirsty?
Let me get you some water.
It's okay.
Shi Yi.
Come.
What is it, grandmother?
Give me your hand.
Good.
I kept this
for Chen's wife.
Thank you, grandmother.
Well.
You...
You should go out and chat with him.
Go on.
I want to take a rest.
I need a nap.
Let me hold you.
I just have a daughter.
I've disappointed
the Zhousheng family in this life of mine.
The eldest young master
shouldn't have married her.
If he knew about the second young master's story,
he wouldn't have married her.
Your grandmother has fallen asleep.
Just like my grandfather and grandmother.
No one can stop them from taking an afternoon nap.
Is there anything
special about this?
It has the circumference of 28cm.
It has 18 jadeite beads,
pink tourmaline flower carving,
coral beads and pearls.
It's a bracelet from the late Ming and early Qing.
Looks like I need to buy a safe
to keep them.
This is a rosary.
It has been used for chanting and praying
for generations.
Wear it.
I know.
This is the smallest one.
There are the 27-bead,
the 54-bead
and the 108-bead rosaries.
They are all rosaries for prayers.
This
belonged to my mother.
It belonged to your mother?
My birth mother.
The one you saw
is not my birth mother.
She is Wenxing and Wenchuan's birth mother.
They are your half-siblings?
Your grandmother is your birth mother's mother?
She is Wenxing and Wenchuan's
birth mother's mother.
Are you confused?
Because you are
quite close with your grandmother.
I never thought that you are not related by blood.
My birth mother and my grandmother
are distant relatives.
She was brought up here since young.
But my grandmother treated my birth mother
like her own daughter.
So, your mother
married your father first.
After she passed away,
Wenxing's mother
married your father.
In order to
marry my mother,
my father left the Zhou family.
After my mother passed away,
in order to let me
take after the Zhousheng surname,
he gave in and married Wenxing's mother
to appease the family.
He brought me back to the Zhou residence.
Before I went back to the Zhou residence,
I lived here.
So, he has lost all of his closest ones
in this family.
Uncle Lin.
You are eating stinky tofu again.
Give me the car key.
You want to go out?
I'm worried about your driving skills.
What about me?
I have my driving license with me.
Any other drivers
will be more reliable than him.
You can't be sure about that.
No one is perfect.
You are used to being at the top since young.
It's time for you to learn
how to accept your weaknesses.
Last time, in order to pick you up,
he drove around the lake
for an entire afternoon.
Well,
I don't need to drive
to work.
I can just walk.
So...
He has me when he comes home.
So, he doesn't even have
the chance to touch the steering wheel.
Let's go, Professor Zhousheng.
I'll let you experience my driving skills.
Go.
Drive carefully.
[Gather Fortune]
There's a mountain road nearby.
It's quite steep.
The year when I graduated from the university,
I once drove down from that road.
It felt dangerous
even driving at only 20 miles per hour.
Where is it?
If you like car rides,
I'll take you out for a ride next time.
I know a few mountain roads.
They have great views.
Mister.
Your fruits are quite fresh.
Of course.
I plucked them
from my fruit farm this morning.
And they are cheap.
Are the oranges sweet?
Yes. Try one.
Thank you.
I'll take some oranges
and some pears.
Okay.
Mister.
Hello, Sir.
I'll take them all.
I'm sorry.
I was here first.
Yes.
I'm buying them for you.
It's okay.
My boyfriend will buy them for me.
You don't have a good taste in men.
What is it? What's wrong?
Nothing.
Have a taste.
Beautiful girls
always attract attention.
Chen's mother
was very beautiful.
When she was still in school,
she was the campus belle.
No, grandmother.
I'm not talking about me.
He said something bad
to Zhousheng Chen.
I don't like it when others criticize him.
Not even a word.
Because of that?
Newly-weds
are so loving.
You don't get bored of
looking at your wife.
Let me take this to them.
Grandmother.
Have some fruits.
You are so good.
You still think about us.
Mother.
Mrs. Zhou.
What are you chatting about? You look happy.
We are
very happy every day.
Why are you here?
I'm here to visit you.
I only have one daughter,
Qin Wenjin.
Tonight,
I'm going to eat dinner
with my eldest grandson and his wife.
I don't have time for you, Madam Zhou.
Then, I won't disturb you further.
This is for you.
I don't need it.
My eldest grandson
has been providing for me all these years.
Grandmother.
Let me peel an orange for you.
[Lotus Fragrance Pavilion]
They said that you didn't eat.
I went home.
My mother
is still the same.
And Chen was there,
she was even more unwilling to talk to me.
One may become more stubborn
with age.
Don't mind her.
When I was young,
I was so adamant about right and wrong.
I thought that
everyone had done me wrong.
I was forced to become Chen's stepmother.
Because of this, I had a fall-out with my mother.
Now,
I'm old.
There are a lot of things
that I feel I should let go.
Family is the most important.
Especially Wenxing. Look at her.
She's young.
But she can only stay in her room, battling with her illness.
No matter how wonderful our life is,
we can't cure her.
Qin Wan.
You need to learn how to put your mind at ease.
Wenxing will be fine.
Trust me.
We've been on the road for half an hour.
And you haven't said anything at all.
I'm sorry.
Are there any specific formalities
for the engagement ceremony
in your family?
No.
I've asked them
to get rid of all the redundant formalities.
Do I need to wear a ring?
Of course.
After putting on the ring,
do you need to
kiss your fiancee?
I've never thought about
this question.
Come closer.
Is it awkward for me to ask
such a specific question?
I think so.
Close your eyes.
Close my eyes?
Close them now.
♫In the memory♫
♫The snow-covered city tower♫
♫When your name rings out♫
♫Finally blooming again♫
♫Like a flower of the soul♫
♫The dreams that have accompanied me through the light years♫
♫I know that with just one look♫
♫I can be sure it's my destination♫
♫Not afraid of falling♫
♫Running to the world with you♫
♫The poem I'll continue to write♫
♫With your name in each line♫
♫If it started all over again♫
♫I'd still remember our love♫
♫It took♫
♫Hundreds of centuries♫
♫For our love to begin♫
I'm sorry. I pressed the wrong button.
We are almost there.
[Introduction]
Your book is upside down.
♫The day we met♫
♫Time froze♫
♫It's your smiling eyes♫
♫That made the hustle and bustle of the world gone♫
I'll go up first then.
♫Every moment♫
Go ahead.
I still have things
♫Drives away the weariness of the past♫
to deal with.
Goodnight.
♫Love spreads♫
♫I'm glad you're here♫
♫One more day with you♫
♫Love gets deeper♫
♫Making it a poem♫
♫Kissing through the long years♫
♫Wrapping love around my fingertips♫
♫Make a vow in silence♫
♫Embrace again♫
♫A few forever♫
♫Nothing will change♫
♫With the same warm sunny day♫
♫Give you my true love♫
♫Thank you for being there♫
♫The day we met♫
♫Time froze♫
♫It's your smiling eyes♫
♫That made the hustle and bustle of the world gone♫
♫Every moment♫
♫Drives away the weariness of the past♫
♫Love spreads♫
Based on her usual habit,
♫I'm glad you're here♫
after she enters her room,
she'll head into the shower
♫One more day with you♫
in around 10 minutes.
♫Love gets deeper♫
♫Making it a poem♫
♫Kissing through the long years♫
♫Wrapping love around my fingertips♫
♫Make a vow in silence♫
♫Embrace again♫
♫A few forever♫
♫Nothing will change♫
♫With the same warm sunny day♫
[Zhousheng Chen]
[I want]
♫Give you my true love♫
♫Thank you for being there♫
[Zhousheng Chen]
[I want]
Uncle.
What is he looking at?
He's waiting for her to get into the shower.
He has this fetish?
You don't understand.
What do you mean I don't understand?
Hush.
Let's go.
♫Give you my plain and simple♫
♫Wait and protection♫
♫Give you my intense♫
♫Longing and tenderness♫
♫Give you my complicated♫
♫Joy and sorrow♫
♫Give you my insignificance♫
♫All that I have♫
♫Give me your smiling♫
♫Corners of mouth and eyes♫
♫Give me your bright and shining♫
♫Early spring and late autumn♫
♫Give me your untouched♫
♫Innocence and freedom♫
♫Give me your most precious♫
♫All that I have♫
♫Give you my undying love♫
♫Long and lasting♫
♫Give me your hands♫
♫In the years to come♫
♫Give you maturity and you give me accommodation♫
♫Will we age like this♫
♫Give you my undying love♫
♫Long and lasting♫
♫Give me your hands♫
♫In the years to come♫
♫Give you maturity and you give me accommodation♫
♫Will we age like this♫
Do you think he's asleep?
♫Give me your smiling♫
♫Corners of mouth and eyes♫
Yes?
♫Give you my intense♫
♫Longing and tenderness♫
You are lying.
♫Give me your untouched♫
Goodnight.
♫Innocence and freedom♫
♫Give you my insignificance♫
♫All that I have♫
Chen.
You are up so early.
Where are you going?
I'm going for a run.
Why is he doing that in the morning?
He's not familiar with this place.
Go with him.
Uncle, you know me.
I don't run.
Go.
Let's take a break.
Let's take a break, Chen.
What's wrong?
They have been
talking
about you
since I was young.
Finally, I get to meet you today.
Whenever I came back before,
you were always not here.
Yes.
I was still in school back then.
Chen.
Are you a natural bookworm
or are you a self-made bookworm?
I think I'm born like that.
I knew it.
It must be an inborn talent
to be such a serious case of bookworm.
I told my uncle about it.
But he wouldn't believe me.
He always sets you
as my example.
Okay. Let's continue.
Uncle Lin.
You are back.
You are so sweaty.
Why aren't you heading to the shower?
I have to take a rest.
You should
learn from Chen.
You
lack training.
Is there water?
Good morning.
You just woke up?
Yes.
Do you want to join me for a morning run?
Sure.
Let me get changed first.
Good morning, Lin Fei.
Good morning.
Where are you going?
We are going for a morning run.
Lin Fei.
Eat properly.
What is it?
Do you want to go for a run too?
No. Go ahead without me.
Okay. We'll go for a run then.
Let's go.
Bye.
He's not spending time with his girlfriend.
He's risking his life for her.
No.
I can't
stay here anymore tonight.
This is too scary.
Let's take a rest.
Okay.
Wait for a while.
Sit on top of this.
I didn't sleep well last night.
Why?
Because of me?
No.
That's not true.
Did you have a good sleep last night?
I had quite a good sleep.
I slept all the way until morning.
Yeah, all the way until morning.
Great-grandpa, thank you
for coming with me.
This is such a coincidence.
If it wasn't because of this engagement banquet,
he might not be at home.
Behave yourself when you see him.
Of course.
Great-grandpa, be careful.
Be careful.
Okay.
When you change the sand,
put one or two tablespoons of salt into it.
Will it be depressing for them
to stay inside here?
We can't do it here.
But when we go back to Shanghai,
I plan to move them
into a bigger aquarium
and add some containers that they can climb on.
He's here.
He's your great-uncle.
Chen.
To be exact,
he's my distant relative.
Based on the seniority,
he has to call me great-grandpa.
We heard that
you are back from abroad.
So, he came here to greet you.
Greet him.
Who?
Greet him. He's your great-uncle.
Greet him now.
Uncle, take a seat first.
Why are you suddenly acting so shy?
Greet him.
Great-uncle.
She is my fiancee.
Great-aunt.
Go and
tell your great-uncle about
what you did after you came back.
I came back from abroad after I graduated two years ago.
Now, I have my own company.
My throat has been a little bit itchy lately.
I have allergies from pollen.
You take your time chatting.
I'll go to the library.
Come.
Tell me more about your company.
It's just a small company. It's not worth the mention.
Chen, Mrs. Zhou is looking for you.
What is it?
The Tong family and the Tang family are all here.
The Tong and the Tang family
are in a fierce battle.
How pitiful
of their unconscious daughter.