LINK
Did you have a nightmare again?
It's okay.
It means you're growing.
Other kids dream
about falling from high places.
But I always have the same dream, Grandma.
Where on earth is that place?
Whenever that happened, my grandma
told me all sorts of fairy tales.
…and the nice girl
married into a wealthy family.
-All stories had one thing in common.
-One day, a monk was passing by.
The monk said to the nice daughter-in-law,
"Don't ever turn around.
If you do…"
You either turn into stone…
God said to Lot,
"Don't ever turn around.
If you do…"
…or a pillar of salt in those stories.
Why in the world
do I keep dreaming of the same thing?
Every time I got scared or curious
about the meaning of this dream,
my grandma said to me…
Don't turn around, my child.
Don't turn around, Dahyun.
Having too much on your mind
will make you ill.
Dahyun, do you know why
people can walk well facing forward,
but not backward? Do you?
And why do you think you have eyes
in the front and not in the back?
Jeez, Grandma. You've said that
ten million times already.
-Have I?
-Yes.
"Don't let useless regrets
or worries get to you
and just keep moving forward.
Live for today."
But…
That's me.
Do you want to play with us?
Hi, I'm Eun Gyeyoung.
What should I do, Grandma?
My past…
is haunting me.
DON'T TURN AROUND
Are you still talking about that?
Once you're willing
to kneel before me and beg,
-we can talk again.
-Let me go!
-Hey, where do you think you're going?
-I said that's enough!
Are you going to fight to the death?
Hey, this really is a reunion.
Do you finally remember me?
No.
I don't.
Lee Jingeun.
I'm going, you punk.
Call me.
Wait here.
Han Sejin.
Sorry for not recognizing you.
No thanks.
I no longer want to be involved
in your affairs, so just keep ignoring me.
You just wait.
You guys will end up looking for me.
Desperately.
Did you really think
your dad was a murderer?
That's not true. Do you know why?
Because I was there that day.
JUNKYARD
Darn it. Why did I come here?
You were too busy having fun
that you had no idea
your injured sister
was being dragged somewhere.
I know who took your sister.
What are you thinking about?
Lee Jingeun said some strange things.
He said that on the day she disappeared,
Gyeyoung was hurt
and that he knew who took her.
She was hurt?
No.
Lee Jingeun likes the attention.
You're right.
He enjoys drawing attention to himself
by rubbing salt into others' wounds.
If I react to this,
it'd just make him more excited.
But do you feel uneasy?
By the way, what did he say to you?
Nothing much. I won't let
what that lunatic said get to me.
-What's wrong?
-Jerk!
-Me?
-No, Lee Jingeun.
He completely messed up your face.
Did he?
I said I'd kill that scumbag
if he touched you.
By the way, did you just say, "me?"
Sorry?
When I said, "jerk,"
-you asked, "me?"
-That's because…
I guess you do feel quite guilty.
You have a conscience at least.
-That's…
-Come on. Let me treat you.
Why did you stop midway?
I'm already done.
Let me see it.
-It's okay.
-What if it leaves a scar?
Were you close to Mr. Ji Wontak?
We were best friends at one point.
Oh, I see.
But he changed his name,
and I forgot all the kids
from elementary school.
But once I realized that I knew them,
the memories flooded back.
I remember Han Sejin,
I mean, Ji Wontak, Lee Jingeun,
and everyone else too.
What about me?
You don't remember me?
I guess not.
But I don't have
a good memory to begin with.
I can't remember
people's faces in particular--
But didn't you say a minute ago
that you started remembering everyone?
It's fine. I don't remember you either.
Jeez. You're no different…
We're even then.
Good for you.
-Can you be more gentle?
-You're a crybaby, aren't you?
I'm not a crybaby.
Why does it hurt now? It didn't hurt
when I actually got hit earlier.
That's why you're a crybaby.
I can handle pain.
I'm just not good with these minor ones.
My first love used to be cool,
not like this.
Your first… What?
I remembered my first love
looking through the album.
Who was it?
Eun Gyehoon.
It's you.
But you were just a snotty little kid
in elementary school. First love, my foot.
-I wasn't snotty.
-You were still a little kid.
He was a real cool heartthrob.
-I'm sure he's changed for the worse.
-I doubt it.
People tend to romanticize their past.
-Are you jealous?
-Jealous? No way.
-That's enough now.
-Just a little more.
How dare he mess up this face
I cherish so much, that jerk…
What am I spewing?
Don't laugh.
Okay.
How is the preparation coming along?
What do I do?
-What are you doing?
-What do I do…
-Hello.
-Hi.
-What are you doing?
-Can you hang out with me?
-Doing what?
-I feel dizzy.
I don't know,
but I really want to hang out.
But we need to go home.
All done.
Does Lee Jingeun bother you?
Kind of.
I shouldn't be talking.
If what he said bothers you,
why don't you just ask?
Ask that prime suspect or witness
or whatever he was.
He did say this to me once.
I was supposed to take Gyeyoung with me…
Why was he supposed to take her?
In what situation
are you supposed to take someone with you?
My gosh. Is she still here
watching the CCTV footage
around Geumdo Villa?
Why is she doing
the detectives' jobs for them?
Leave her alone, Chief.
It wouldn't hurt
to have another pair of eyes.
You're right.
Hello?
What? Eun Gyehoon?
Eun Gyehoon?
Yes.
What?
Over here.
Sorry.
I left my phone inside,
but I thought it'd complicate matters
if I go in looking like this.
What happened?
Nothing serious.
Are you okay?
Thanks.
What's going on?
Hey, Officer Ji! Come over here.
You shouldn't have come.
Why not?
He's our patrol unit's rookie.
Since he lives in Jihwa-dong too,
he's qualified to be one of us, right?
"Rookie" is so old-school.
What?
Hey.
My bad.
That rude punk.
Let's see if he spills
my drink by accident too, okay?
If he does, he's a rude punk indeed.
-I'll pour it properly, sir.
-Okay.
I'm sorry, sir.
-That punk.
-What a silly fellow.
Ma'am, I left money on the table.
Enjoy the food.
Who was that? Your friend?
No, sir.
What's wrong with your faces?
What happened?
Did you two get into a fight?
He's not a policeman. He's a thug.
It's not like that.
Besides, he's a stalker.
Stalker? Who is stalking whom?
His name is Lee Jingeun. He's stalking
the girl from the stew place.
-Dahyun?
-Yes.
That scumbag…
Don't be like that, man.
Just drink, okay?
We're off duty right now.
By the way,
why did Eun Gyehoon call you earlier?
He asked me something
about Mr. Han Euichan.
That man who urinates in public? Why?
Maybe he wants to get his revenge.
Men shouldn't forget any grudges.
-I'll get going first.
-Sure.
-Where are you going?
-I need to use the restroom.
I came to ask you something.
Would you like some warm barley tea?
No thank you.
It's okay.
Come on in.
Last time,
you said to me
that you were supposed
to take Gyeyoung with you.
Why? Why were you supposed to
take Gyeyoung with you?
Gyeyoung definitely knew her way home
and she was more than capable
of going home alone. So why?
Because she was hurt.
At the time, Gyeyoung…
injured her leg.
Gyeyoung, are you hurt?
That's why she wasn't able to go home.
She was hurt and I was her teacher.
But I just left her there
even though she could barely walk.
If I had taken her with me…
It's my fault.
I'm sorry, Gyehoon.
I'm really sorry.
Gyeyoung injured her leg…
You were too busy having fun
that you had no idea
your injured sister
was being dragged somewhere.
I KNOW WHO TOOK YOUR SISTER
That man…
Why are you looking for him?
I needed to ask him something.
It's important
to both you and me.
It's important to me too?
What is it? Tell me.
There is a chance that Mr. Han Euichan,
your father,
might have been falsely accused.
You too?
Lee Jingeun said to me
that he isn't the culprit.
But…
so what?
-What do you mean, so what?
-You heard me right. So what?
What difference would it make?
I have something to confess.
He became a suspect
because I wrote a letter.
If he had been accused of murder,
my heart would've been at peace at least.
But he was released immediately
due to a lack of evidence.
But the ridiculous thing is
that the police kept insisting
he was the murderer
even though they had no evidence.
Seriously.
What do you want?
What do you want from me?
-People have called me
-Say it!
-the son of a murderer my entire life.
-I said, say it!
-So what now?
What difference would it make now…
if he's not a murderer?
-Sejin--
-Shut your mouth.
Don't you ever call me that again.
I know it's a messed-up thing to say
and I feel sorry for you,
but you should've
looked after her to begin with.
You should've taken care
of your little sister.
Don't you dare
linger around me or him ever again.
I'll really kill you.
You still live here?
I'm impressed.
But do you remember who I am?
It's okay. I don't have to take this call.
EUN GYEHOON
Lee Jingeun.
Hello? Lee Jingeun.
-Hello?
-Where are you now?
I'm a bit busy at the moment.
What?
Can we talk later?
No way.
What did you mean by that?
What did you mean by
Gyeyoung was hurt
and that you knew who took her?
Me?
I never said that.
Nonsense!
No. Wait.
Answer me straight.
I'm with someone right now.
I coincidently ran into this person
after such a long time.
This person has a question for you.
-What?
-Eun Gyehoon,
how is your father?
What?
What did you just say?
Lee Jingeun.
The call can't be connected.
Transferring to voicemail.
You will be charged after the tone.
RESTROOM
Isn't that the stalker?
What's he doing?
What's wrong?
You know everything too.
What did he mean by that?
What am I supposed to know?
Don't turn around, Dahyun.
Why do you look like that?
What did he say?
What Lee Jingeun said was true.
And Lee Jingeun asked me about my father.
He asked me how he was doing.
What does that mean?
He asked you about your father?
What in the world could it mean?
I totally spilled it everywhere.
What? They aren't back yet?
Where did they all go
in the middle of drinking? Jeez.
-How would I know?
-You startled me.
Just drink up.
Okay.
When did he get so drunk?
Jungho.
What are you thinking so hard about?
It's just that
it explains why they carried around
the tools all the time.
So I feel bad.
What are you talking about?
He's talking about the stew place.
You mean Bokhee.
It's freezing.
Where have you been going around?
I went to see someone.
Did you get yourself a girlfriend? Jeez.
Where's Mr. Cho?
He left a while back. Something came up.
Is that right?
How much did you drink?
Goodness.
Gyehoon.
Did you do this with Dahyun?
What happened to your face?
Did Dahyun punch you?
In any case, I deserve a metal
for being a loyal friend.
I suppose, you mean a medal.
Do you even know
what I've been doing because of you?
Why in the world…
am I dancing here?
How did I end up here?
-Where do you think you're going?
-Sorry?
Hey, young man.
You can't leave yet.
Shall we go have some more fun?
-Let's go!
-Yes!
Well, the thing is
that since I don't
get to see him much at all,
-I get confused sometimes.
-Right.
"Is that man my husband
or the next-door neighbor?" You know?
What do you mean, what should you do?
Just go for it.
Should I just go for it?
Look at him. He looks shocked.
Open your mouth. Here you go.
Are you having fun?
Do we seem funny to you?
I'm sorry.
Why aren't you eating that?
If you're sorry, chow down now.
-Chew well.
-It's okay.
It's still scary just thinking about it.
By the way, Gyehoon.
Yes?
I think the ladies really want to know.
By the way,
why did Eun Gyehoon
return to this neighborhood?
What Lee Jingeun said was true.
When did I first come into your life?
We didn't meet for the first time at work.
We met right in this alley
a very long time ago.
Right here in this neighborhood.
Don't you remember?
What's wrong? You know everything too.
What are you doing?
What are you doing at this hour
with all the dishes from the restaurant?
That's a good question.
If it is, you should answer me.
What are you doing?
Questions are more important than answers.
Einstein said that.
Your forehead feels hot as I had expected.
You have a high fever.
If the Earth's temperature
rises by two degrees,
it'll bring mass extinction.
What?
It's a tragedy.
Forget it. In any case,
you're going to be very sick today.
When someone has a fever,
they end up saying nonsense and collapse.
Thus, we'll close shop for the day.
Wake up and eat!
You said, you can't be even a minute late!
You're as loud as a train.
-That little…
-Okay. Leave it to me. I'll go get her.
Dahyun.
You were awake?
-Yes, Grandma.
-Why are you just sitting around?
Can you tell me that again?
That one saying.
-Did you have a nightmare again?
-Yes.
Get rid of useless thoughts
and don't turn around.
Let it all go
and just keep going forward,
okay, my child?
Okay.
Lee Jingeun and I were alumni.
-We went to the same elementary school.
-What?
Maybe that's why I had
that nightmare from the past.
But it's fascinating.
I haven't had that dream in a while,
but it felt so fresh and vivid.
Hey, how vivid could it be?
It's still just a dream.
Exactly.
As luck would have it, that lunatic
went to the same school as you.
Are you sure he didn't have a crush on you
from your elementary school days?
He has high standards as a stalker.
If he ever shows his face again,
I'll gouge out his eyeballs
and turn them into lollipops.
-My goodness.
-Jeez.
What? I still wouldn't be satisfied.
ONE UNREAD MESSAGE
We're closed today.
Are you okay?
I hope you aren't terribly ill--
The detective in charge
of Dajung's case called me.
Lee Jingeun has become
a suspect in another case.
The detective said, it might be possible
to reinvestigate Dajung's case too.
That's great to hear.
You reported him, didn't you?
Yes.
I'm glad you did. Thank you.
I hope they catch him soon.
I feel so anxious.
If I could, I'd just catch him myself.
Eunjung, why don't we leave this
to the police for now
and go have some fun?
-Isn't that pretty?
-Yes, it is.
I like this one. The color is pretty.
Do you like it?
-Yes.
-Please give me the whole set on display.
I can't believe you bought
everything for me.
Thank you. I'll really enjoy them.
Oh, no.
Hey, man. Watch where you're going!
Eunjung, we're both at fault.
-Are you okay?
-I'm sorry.
-He needs to watch where he is going.
-I'm fine. Let's go.
The color is so beautiful.
I think it'd look good on you.
Eunjung, this is so pretty.
-It's so cute.
-The white one.
-Eunjung, what do you think?
-It looks so radiant and beautiful.
This one's nice too, right?
-Could you ring us up?
-I got these, Eunjung.
-I got it.
-Please use this one.
-No, I got it.
-Please use mine.
Oh, that one's so cute--
Do you like that one?
It's so cute. How much is it?
Do you want to get matching pairs?
Aren't they so cute?
There are so many cute ones here.
People who live
looking backward, not forward.
A long time ago,
I owed a friend five packs of ramyeon.
But…
now I'll never be able to do it for her,
and perhaps I'm doing it for you instead.
Unresolved feelings,
regrets,
and longing. They live with such feelings.
Who they see before them is not me…
-Splash!
-Stop it!
…but the people they left in their past.
How does this look?
Isn't the color so pretty?
Everyone needs one of these.
Eunjung.
I'm not your little sis.
But I'll be a new little sis to you.
Okay.
Thanks.
And I'm sorry.
You should get going.
As I was thinking about my sister,
you were thinking about someone else too.
I'll let you go.
What's wrong?
I was really determined
to stop liking Eun Gyehoon.
But it won't last one day,
let alone three.
I have to tell myself once a day,
"Let's not like him."
"You've got to let him go."
"Don't you have any self-esteem?"
Ridiculous, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Is it?
Eun Gyehoon, what a lucky man.
You think so too, right? He's so annoying.
He is annoying.
He has a terrible personality.
But he isn't that annoying, you know?
Shall I handle him?
Sorry?
I'm your big sis now.
How dare that snob make my little sis cry.
Strictly speaking, he didn't make me cry.
I just cried on my own.
Come on, Eunjung.
It's because we've lost someone.
We've lost someone precious to us.
That's why he and I
can't hold on to someone.
We're afraid of losing them again.
Dahyun.
What? What are you doing here?
It's not even late.
Why are you out here? It's so cold.
What's that?
Well, I ended up getting them.
You got clothes?
Don't tell me you only bought yours.
I'll let you borrow them.
How can I borrow them?
Your clothes don't fit me.
They aren't elastic.
Grandma, aren't you cold?
Come home before it gets dark.
I'm not a high school student.
-Before it gets dark.
-You're in no position to say that.
-Come on, Grandma.
-Your mom's right.
-"Your mom's right."
-Why do you always call out to Grandma?
By the way, I heard
the chef's face got all beaten up.
How did you know?
This neighborhood is tiny.
Word spreads quickly.
Was it Lee Jingeun?
Yes.
-What?
-Mom, don't tell me…
-What's this?
What? This?
I'm just carrying it around.
Seriously.
Ta-da.
-What's that?
-Those are horrendous.
-You can't even use them.
-Grandma, you poke their eyes with this.
-How scary.
-Oh, really?
You're the scariest one here.
-Gosh, seriously.
-Put that away now.
-What are you doing? Put that away.
-Come on, Grandma.
Oh, right. I almost forgot.
A soft opening is around the corner,
so there is a lot to do. Let me stop by.
What would you do there
with only men around at this hour?
What else? I'll work.
But you said you're off today.
Your daughter is the troublemaker.
Those nerdy men couldn't harm her.
Come on in.
That's my point. I don't trust her, Mom.
Don't worry.
What brings you here now?
Weren't you sick?
What are you doing down here?
I took a fever reducer
and feel much better now.
And I really hate just lying around.
You're so odd.
I love just lying around.
You're so pale. You don't look fine.
Let me get you some warm tea.
Stop trying to do things for me
and allow me to take care of you too.
Thank you.
Aren't you dying to know?
You've been waiting
to ask me since yesterday.
Actually,
I came here to look for my father.
After Gyeyoung disappeared, my father
literally spent his entire life wandering
looking for Gyeyoung.
I'll be back.
Have a safe trip.
Hello?
REGISTRATION CARD
EUN CHULHO
Father's wallet.
This was found in Jihwa-dong?
There are no credit card,
banking, or phone call records.
There are no traces of his existence.
I would like to report him missing.
Perhaps my father…
Maybe
he just isn't able to contact you.
He might be okay
looking for your sister somewhere.
The family of a missing person
would never just vanish into thin air
without contacting the family.
Because they know more than anyone
how painful it is
for those who are left behind.
But I completely lost touch with him
and there are no traces of him whatsoever.
So I believe my father…
passed away.
That's why I came back to Jihwa-dong
to look for his final traces.
But the only worry I have…
is my mother.
Is Dad… doing well?
Yes, he is.
I ended up lying to her.
But if she were to find out
that my father had passed away,
I doubt she'd be able to endure.
What about Eun Gyehoon?
Sorry?
Not your sister,
not your father,
and not your mother either.
Eun Gyehoon.
Is Eun Gyehoon all right?
I'm curious about Eun Gyehoon.
Sometimes, questions are…
more important than answers.
How was it
for Eun Gyehoon?
How was it for me?
Isn't it pretty?
I thought it would work
if I made the effort.
Three orders of today's recommended dish.
Two ravioli. One salmon.
-Yes, chef!
If I worked harder than anyone else,
I thought I could fill the gap.
FATHER, IS EVERYTHING WELL WITH YOU?
I'M DOING WELL
But…
GONE EARLY TO THE MARKET. PLEASE EAT.
LOVE, YOUR SON GYEHOON
FATHER, IS EVERYTHING WELL WITH YOU?
I'M DOING WELL
AUNT
Hello, Aunt?
Mom!
But no matter how hard I tried…
the crack kept getting wider
with no signs of closing at all
and became a big void in the end.
I guess I'm sick after all
to tell you all this.
I wish you had stayed here
and not have moved away.
Then my grandma would've told you,
not to turn around,
and regardless of what
you might've left behind,
just keep moving forward.
If so, you would've grown up
to be a carefree person like me.
You could've been a little happier.
I…
have no intention of being that way.
I don't have the courage to become happy.
REGISTRATION CARD
EUN CHULHO
TICKET BOOTH
How have you been?
How is your health?
You're not skipping meals, are you?
Of course not.
Is everything well with you?
You've become a bit pallid
while I've been away.
I can't get it out of my head
not even for a moment.
Day after day,
I think about that day
over and over again.
I regret it over and over again! I…
No…
I'm not blaming you. No.
It's not your fault.
But all the work
I've been doing did pay off a little.
If I try a little harder,
we'll be able to find her.
So don't you worry.
-So--
-Enough, Father.
Enough already. Please.
I came to ask you to come home.
You've done so much already, so please
come home now.
Father, Mom is very ill.
Her mind and body
are deteriorating rapidly each day.
Mom…
I mean, we
need you, Father.
I'm sorry.
If that's what you came here to say,
I'll get going.
Please, it's enough already!
How much longer…
How much longer must we wait?
After you left,
Mom and I have been waiting for so long.
For how long will you
just look for Gyeyoung? For how long?
Your little sister Gyeyoung
is left all alone.
I'm her father.
If I don't look for her, who will?
If I give up, who will look for her?
Dad.
I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
It's all because of me. I apologize.
So please… Please stop now.
Let's let go of Gyeyoung now.
I know it might sound shameless
for me to ask this,
but can't we just live like other people?
Can't we just live an ordinary,
happy life like others? Please?
Like others?
Dad.
Dad…
If you leave like this, it's really over!
I swear, I'll never look for you again.
Until the day I die. Never!
I won't look for you
or see you ever again.
I can't
go back like this.
Be happy, Gyehoon.
Like others.
Dad…
How could I be happy, Father?
I learned that happiness ends
and anything precious vanishes in the end.
Father, I…
no longer have the courage
to become happy.
So,
I, who was cowardly and foolish,
made a decision.
The only way to keep those you love safe
is by not letting them
come into your life.
But…
I've never been concerned about you.
But I definitely felt your concern.
What was that then?
Back then…
Why did you look for me so hard?
And then again…
I like you.
I kept acting like a coward.
Why do you keep
coming into my life?
I came back because…
for some reason…
I had this strange feeling.
LINK
As you know, I had no intention
of becoming close to anyone.
However, something unpredictable happened.
You came into my life.
You and Eun Gyehoon can never be together.
There's a reason for that.
The nightmare. I'm going to dig into it.
Letting my imagination run wild
makes me want to run away
in fear even more.
Do you finally remember? The red gate.
In what may have been
the happiest moment of my life,
the scariest memory resurfaced.
Translated by [Ji-young Hwang]