I want to bring a dog home.
Just for a few days.
No way.
My friend asked me
to watch his dog for two days.
Can you help me persuade Ling Yizhou?
If I hadn't gone abroad two years ago,
I'd be married to you right now,
wouldn't I?
An Ran.
Some things in this world
are destined to be.
No matter how many times you reset it,
the results will still be the same.
A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
EPISODE 6
I'm writing a story based on
Ling Yizhou and Chu Yan.
A gripping romance between
a business mogul and a movie star.
What do you think?
Feifei, could you talk
about something else?
Stop bringing up Ling Yizhou all the time.
What's wrong now?
You two still aren't getting along?
When it comes to Ling Yizhou,
I need to re-evaluate the way I...
The way you what?
The way I...
Did the boss man plant a tracker on you?
What do you mean?
What a coincidence. Have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
I just happen to be free.
Let's go eat.
Sounds good.
Come on. He can afford to pay for a meal.
Were you really just driving by?
I came to pick you up.
He came to pick you up.
You're very considerate, Mr. Ling.
Don't be so stubborn.
-Get in.
-What are you doing?
Hurry up. Get in.
Let's go.
You're not getting in, Mr. Ling? Come on.
Miss Jia, you can order whatever you want.
I already ordered some.
We'd love to have
whatever Mr. Ling is having.
My taste buds aligned with Linlin's
a long time ago.
But I'd like to order something spicy.
He doesn't eat spicy food.
I ate it at Grandma's place.
I thought you were all talk.
Actions speak louder than words.
Sorry to be rude,
but my mind is jumping all over the place.
I'm just putting two and two together.
Feifei...
isn't our house rental contract
ending soon?
Don't bring that up.
The landlord wants me to move out early
in order to sell the place.
I was busy writing so I haven't
started looking for a new place yet.
Move in with me then.
Would that be OK?
I'll let you decide.
Miss Jia, if it suits you,
you could move in with me first.
Wow, I'm impressed.
He's sacrificing himself for love.
Yes, Wen Li takes good care of people.
She doesn't need to live with a man.
That's alright. I need someone
to take care of me anyway.
Mr. Wen, I hope we'll get along
as roommates.
Hello, Lisa.
I got you a role in Frosty Moon.
It's a small supporting role,
but I think you'll like it.
I mailed you the script.
Thanks, Lisa. I'll do my best.
When does filming start?
The main actors start in two days.
They'll contact you about it.
Could I start in two days as well?
I want to get used
to the environment there before filming.
I'll ask the producers then.
You got some work?
I just got the call.
I go on set in two days.
I heard that.
Are you trying to avoid me?
I think we should be separated
from each other for a while.
Why?
Our contract stipulates
that both parties shall not infringe upon
the other's work or private life.
Didn't you declare that
the dog would go wherever you go?
Now you're leaving.
His owner just happens to be coming
to pick it up tonight.
Just in time.
Do whatever you want.
It's getting late. Where is he?
I hope he didn't forget about you.
Hello, this is Xia Lin.
When are you coming to get Eleven?
I'm sorry. I can't pick him up today.
Is tomorrow OK?
I'm going somewhere tomorrow.
How about this?
Give me your address.
I'll drop him off for you.
If it's not too much trouble.
No problem.
Let's go.
Come on.
-You?
-The tie lady?
That's right. I didn't know we lived
in the same neighborhood.
And you found my dog.
What a huge coincidence.
-Want to come in?
-No, thanks.
I'm glad Eleven is home now.
You did me such a big favor,
I'd feel rude if I didn't offer you
a glass of water.
Thank you then.
Have a seat.
Your house is beautiful.
Thank you so much for everything.
I must have caused you trouble.
Not at all.
It's just that someone
in my house doesn't like pets.
Are you fighting?
It's fine. He agreed to it.
I understand.
I didn't want a dog at first.
Why?
Because dogs don't live as long as humans,
so they'll always leave us first.
But later on, I realized that
in the whole world, the animal
that's best at desertion is mankind.
They abandon their lovers...
their family, and even their own children.
Maybe sometimes they have no other option.
Perhaps.
So, if you don't want to be abandoned,
you have to take your fate
into your own hands.
That way, everything in life
will happen according to plan.
What's wrong?
It seems like you have
a lot of stories to tell.
I've been through more than most.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
I have a slight fever.
I slept all day.
That's why I forgot to pick up Eleven.
Did you eat anything?
I'm too weak to cook.
What about your friends and family?
There's no one to take care of you?
They're all abroad.
You could have something delivered.
You really should eat when you're sick.
I don't like restaurant food.
Where's your kitchen?
Over there.
Why are you asking?
I have to take care of you.
After all, you let me
have that tie last time.
I still don't know your name though.
You can call me Nan.
Alright, then. You get some rest.
I'll call you when it's ready.
-Go and rest.
-Thank you.
Nan, I'm heading home.
Make sure you finish the congee.
Heat it up if it's cold.
What's up? You want some, too?
-I thought you'd already left.
-I was late.
We're not going the same way.
It's fine. I'm already late anyway.
Get in.
If you're going to miss me,
we can just head back now.
You're not mad anymore?
Do I seem that petty?
You don't seem petty. You are petty.
If that's what you think,
then I need to live up to my reputation.
What do you mean?
When you get there,
don't talk to men you don't know.
No sex scenes or kissing scenes.
No revealing clothing.
How do you define "revealing"?
No showing your collarbones.
No showing your belly button.
Skirts must be at least knee-length.
You have a lot of rules.
Mr. Ling, this isn't even a real marriage.
I take my marriage very seriously.
Fine. That's enough.
I'll do what you said.
Where's your ring?
I always have it on me.
What are you doing?
Rings are supposed to be worn.
But I can't wear it when I'm filming.
Try taking it off then.
We'll be so far apart.
You won't be able to see me anyway.
Try and see what happens.
Stop. I can get off right here.
I've got to go. Bye.
That's how you say goodbye
to your husband?
Call me once you arrive.
OK.
I really need to get going.
I've got to go. Bye.
Mr. Ling, the show she's doing
is produced by Xing An Entertainment.
If you're worried,
you can have Miss An look after her.
No need for that.
Isn't Chu Yan filming there, too?
That's right.
-Head back to the office.
-OK.
Linlin, what brings you here?
I'm acting in a show.
Why are you here?
Let me introduce you.
This is Lu Di.
He's one of Xing An's actors.
This is Xia Lin.
She's my best female friend in China.
Is Ms. Xia also acting in Frosty Moon?
I'm one of the supporting roles.
I've always wanted you
to act in one of our company's films.
I'm so glad it happened so soon.
If you ever need anything
when we're filming,
come to him. He'll do whatever you ask.
It would be my honor to help you.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
An Ran, I'm going to head upstairs.
-Bye.
Miss An.
If you two are friends, why do you want
the media to spread rumors about us?
Just do whatever I tell you to do.
Everything else is none of your business.
Anything else?
Over the past two months,
a lot of important R&amp;D employees have quit
to go and work somewhere else.
Carry out an internal investigation first.
If there aren't any issues,
I remember that our contract includes
a non-compete clause, right?
That's right.
Look into the companies they switch to.
If they're our competitors,
press charges for breach of contract.
Got it.
People might start making assumptions
about why our employees are leaving.
Notify everyone that we start
employee evaluations today.
Those not up to par will be fired.
Old and new employees
will be treated the same.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
Women...
What do they like?
Mr. Ling, are you thinking
about what to get your wife?
I don't really have female friends, so...
You seem to know Jia Fei well.
Just what do they like?
Why are you here?
It's not time to move yet.
Sorry. I couldn't reach you on your phone,
so I had to come here.
Is Linlin in trouble?
No. Mr. Ling wants to know what she likes.
Mr. Ling really does spare no effort
when it comes to maintaining peace
in the relationship.
He's always been very attentive.
Don't worry, Miss Jia.
Mrs. Ling won't hear
about our conversation today.
I'm not worried about that.
Mr. Wen, you're an elite assistant.
Don't you think helping Mr. Ling
with this matter is below you?
It's my honor to help my boss.
I can help you and Mr. Ling,
but one thing you should know about me
-is that I don't help people out for free.
-Don't worry.
If you provide information,
you'll get a DVD signed by Director Cai.
Deal.
Diamonds are a woman's best friend,
but your wife is no ordinary woman.
To break this emotional gridlock,
it's imperative that both parties
start to connect emotionally.
Just tell me the plan.
For example, you could get a pet.
Your wife seems to like dogs very much.
I think that...
you can go home now.
Mr. Ling, are you going
to work late every day
while your wife is filming?
Yes.
I must earn money to support Mumu.
Single men like you
could never understand.
Why are you here?
Mr. Lu, can I help you?
Are you ready
for our scene together tomorrow?
I'll be ready for it.
I don't want to cause you trouble.
I just happen to have some time.
Let's practice.
There are mosquitos out here.
How about we go back inside?
It's quieter out here.
-I don't like crowded places.
-Mr. Lu.
It's almost time for lunch.
I don't want to take up your time.
I promised Miss An
that I'd look after you.
I have to keep my word.
What are you two doing out here?
Mr. Chu.
Why are you here?
Just happened to stop by?
No, I came to see someone.
You two know each other?
We don't just know each other.
We actually often read scripts together.
I'll get going now, Mr. Lu.
See you in a bit.
-Bye.
-Alright, then.
But...
Miss An.
I didn't get a photo.
Chu Yan showed up and took her away.
Chu Yan? Why would he show up?
Keep an eye on them for me.
Who on earth is this Xia Lin girl?
I have to know who I'll be offending.
All you need to know is that
if you don't do your job,
you'll be offending everyone
at Xing An Entertainment.
Got it. Alright.
OK. Goodbye.
When have we ever read a script together?
Why are you here?
Someone asked me
to deliver a bunch of medicine
and nutrition supplements to your hotel.
How's life as Mrs. Ling going?
Great.
Everyone has been very nice to me.
Perhaps too nice.
Why was he trying to hug you?
I don't know why
he thought he could do that.
Thanks for getting me out of there.
I wasn't helping you.
I was saving Ling from embarrassment.
Nobody knows about Yizhou and I.
If they knew you were Mrs. Ling,
they'd never do that.
Don't you dare tell anyone
about our marriage.
Why?
We agreed to keep it secret.
Just act like you didn't see anything.
Don't tell him, OK?
I'll take that as a "yes."
Those people are all from our set.
You should get going.
I'm warning you,
stay away from that Lu Di.
Or else I'll tell Yizhou.
Fine, you snitch.
I know that the Chu family
has given me everything I have.
But that doesn't mean you can
have me marry someone to benefit yourself.
I know.
I'm just an orphan you adopted.
You don't need to remind me of that.
When did you get here?
Before you hung up the phone.
Do you enjoy eavesdropping?
You love finding out
other people's secrets, don't you?
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to give you an umbrella.
Don't worry.
-I won't say a word.
-Just stop.
I don't need to be pitied
by someone like you.
Who's pitying you?
You don't deserve pity at all.
You're handsome. You have a great body.
You won Best Actor at such a young age.
You have over 50 million fans.
When you post,
you get thousands of comments.
You have a sports car and a mansion.
There's always gossip about another girl.
You have what most people
will never achieve in a lifetime.
What more could you possibly want?
You can't go this far
just because you know my secret.
I just hate seeing you whine all the time.
It's not like the entire world owes you.
You have the right to despise me?
Who do you think you are?
You're like those girls
who sleep around to move up.
Ling helped you deal
with the dress problem.
You won't even admit that
you approached Yizhou just to use him.
My relationship with Ling Yizhou
is none of your business.
I didn't want to find out
about his secret. He's so mean.
I shouldn't have given him that umbrella.
I should have let him get rained on
and have an asthma attack.
-You're here.
-Mr. Lu.
I thought this was a cast and crew event.
Where's everyone else?
I only said that so you'd come.
So, only the two of us
are going to be here?
That's right.
I think the two of us
should have a nice long chat.
I need to go to the restroom.
No, stay here.
A meal for forgiveness?
So unoriginal.
Here.
To our first time working together.
Cheers.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lu. I don't drink alcohol.
Everyone drinks alcohol.
Some people are better at it than others.
I really don't drink.
-Here you go.
-No, I really can't.
-I never drink.
-Just try a sip.
-I don't drink, Mr. Lu.
-Just one sip.
Are you stupid?
He told you to stay, so you stayed?
We're filming a moving together.
I don't want to make things awkward.
What if I hadn't shown up?
How dare you not come
after all the nasty things you said?
Fine. I was in a bad mood this afternoon.
But I just rescued you. So we're even now.
Was that an apology?
I wouldn't say that. I'd say...
it's reconciling.
Why would I want to reconcile with you?
Fine. I'll apologize then.
We started arguing because of Ling.
Think of it as forgiving me for him.
It has nothing to do with him.
It's because I'm generous.
Stop treating me like a three-year-old.
You'd be a two-year-old.
Alright. We're good now.
Ling, I saw your wife today.
Is she doing OK?
Not really. I think someone's trying
to make a move on her.
Who left you here?
Pick a name for it.
You bought me a dog?
You're not going to invite me in?
Hurry up. Quick.
Come in. Hurry up.
Why are you acting all mysterious?
We're legally married,
not having an affair.
Let's call it Pidan.
Whatever you want.
So, why are you here?
I wanted to help you relax.
I'm really busy though.
We're filming my main scenes.
I don't have any free time.
"Due to the set
suddenly being unavailable,
cast and crew get two days off."
All cast and crew must return
by tomorrow night.
You came at the right time.
Some coincidences are planned.
Let's go in.
If something's bothering you, tell me.
Don't hold it inside.
Secrets make you ugly.
Didn't we agree not to interfere
with each other's work?
Don't you know how big of a hit
production will take because
you made our set unavailable?
We could wait for my break
to come on this trip.
That would be true
if nobody was trying to harass you.
Chu Yan, you snitch.
Mumu, we have a crisis of trust right now.
You didn't tell me about
what happened right away.
And you didn't tell me later.
Is it because you think
it has nothing to do with me?
Nothing really happened.
It would be too late if it had.
That's enough for now.
Let's go inside.
Come a little closer.
Welcome, Director Ling.
How does he know you?
I thought you're always low-key?
The owner is a Lingshi Group shareholder.
It's fine.
Hello, Miss Xia.
I'm in charge of this guesthouse.
My name is Mr. Wang.
I'm glad to be of your service.
This is a personal visit.
-Treat us as normal guests.
-OK.
Mr. Ling, you requested
a luxury room with a king-size bed.
The room is ready for you now.
Only one room?
When I called,
there was only one room left.
That's right.
Are there any other
vacant rooms right now?
-Let me take a look.
-Excuse me...
Yang has only been
working here for two days.
She's still learning.
It's peak travel season now.
All our rooms are reserved.
What about other room types?
Everything's booked.
Mumu, if you insist,
we can see if any other guest
is willing to give up their room.
No need for that.
That's too much trouble.
Yang, get me the room key. Hurry.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go.
Mumu, did you turn off the light?
Is the power out?
Sorry, I hit the wrong switch.
Not tired yet?
Waiting for me?
I'm not tired yet.
You can go to bed first.
Go take a shower.
I took one before we came out.
OK, then.
I don't care if you shower or not.
Hotel beds are really gross.
You should put on a shirt.
But I'm hot.
I don't know why I feel so hot.
I'll turn on the AC for you.
It's already on.
Then I'll turn on the TV.
We don't need the TV.
It's late. We should go to sleep.
As long as I hold
the last line of defense,
I guess sleeping in the same bed
is pretty much the same
as staying in the same room.
But with a pretty young lady
lying next to him,
what if he can't stop himself from...
doing something?
Can you stop moving around?
You're not asleep yet?
How can I fall asleep
when you keep moving around?
I'm sorry.
Relax. I won't do anything to you.
Ling Yizhou...
what do you think is
most important in a relationship?
What do you think?
I used to think that
loving each other was enough.
Now, I think it's being
completely honest...
and respecting every decision
the other person makes.
That's what it takes
to have a relationship.
What if someone lied to you?
It depends on the situation.
Actually...
I lied to you...
about your illness.
Good morning.
Morning.
I caught you in the act.
-You can't run away now.
-I haven't brushed my teeth.
I don't care.
You'd better pay up.
You understand me?
You need to pay us back today.
Stop!
Get over here!
Pay up!
I'll call the police!
You're causing trouble!
Go away. I don't have any money.
You took everything in our house.
Where's your father?
How dare he owe me money?
He must be trying to get himself killed.
I haven't seen him for a long time.
I'm begging you.
Please don't come back here.
He's your father. If he can't pay up,
we'll take you away instead. Come on.
No! Let go of me!
What are you doing?
Director Ling,
I'm sorry you had to see this.
Who the hell are you?
Watch your language.
He's not someone you can afford to cross.
What do you want?
You want to pay off
the Yang family's debt?
If not, go mind your own business.
-How much do they owe?
-Including interest,130,000RMB.
Take this to Gangdong Tower.
They'll give you the money.
But I'm warning you,
don't you ever come back here...
or I'll make sure you pay for it.
We'll see about that
after we get the money.
Come on.
Let's interview today's hero.
He paid off 130,000RMB of debt
just like that.
It's not them I care about.
I paid for my own peace of mind.
Come on. Let's go.
Shouldn't we wait for them to get
the money? What if they come back?
We'll be in danger once they have it.
-Why?
-Who are they?
Local gangsters? The mafia?
If you were them,
and you saw a rich man
with a beautiful young woman,
what would you do?
Kidnap the lady
and kill her once I get the ransom.
You're right. Let's go.
You...
I just got fired.
It's OK. I'm used to it.
Those loan sharks always come after me
wherever I work.
I never last more than a few days.
I want to pay you back for your kindness.
I'll give you the money someday.
Where do you live? We'll drive you home.
Thanks.
This is your home?
It looks pretty nice.
It's not the house.
It's the small shack in the back.
The shack?
Alright, Tongtong.
Why isn't there anyone around?
They're all out working right now.
You look pretty young.
Do you have any other family members?
My mom died when I was young.
I'm the only one left in my family.
I'll let you decide.
Tongtong, would you like to come with me?
What do you mean, miss?
I travel a lot for my job.
I just happen to need an assistant.
Would you like that?
I'd really like that.
Thank you so much.
Mumu, I need to tell you something
when I get home.
What is it? It sounds important.
I'll tell you when we meet.
OK.
Mr. Lu.
-Why haven't you left yet?
-I just got back.
Where are you going?
Production has been cancelled.
Why would I stay here?
How could it be cancelled?
Hello, Mr. Wen.
Mrs. Ling, Mr. Ling had a car accident.
A car accident?
Yizhou...
I thought you were ignoring me.
About last time--
I asked you here
to talk about Frosty Moon.
Is this about Linlin?
-Don't worry. I'll take good care of her.
-No need.
I'll buy one percent of Xing An shares
to own this show.
You're doing this to help Linlin's career?
No.
I want production
to be cancelled immediately.
One more thing.
That actor in your company, Lu Di.
I don't want to hear
another word about him.
That's all.
Subtitle translation by Luke Deming
You.
Fire her for me.
Right now.
His amnesia might just be
a reaction to shock.
Perhaps he'll be normal by tomorrow.
Before I get my memory back,
I hope we can live independently
and not interfere with each other.
Mr. Ling lost his memory, right?