Come bike with me. You'll get paid
handsomely at the end of the day.
Am I glowing to you right now?
I'm absolutely perfect.
Ling?
How's the investigation into Chu?
Everything is pretty much in place.
Set things in action.
You rotten child.
If Ling Yizhou finds out,
the Chu family's prosperity
will be ruined!
My last name is not Chu. I don't want
to be a part of this family either.
A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
EPISODE 13
Xia Lin!
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine, but something
has happened to Chu Yan!
Chu Yan? What happened?
Look.
FIRE AT HOSPITAL
STATUS OF CHU YAN UNKNOWN
-I have to go!
-I'll come!
No.
-Take care of yourself. Bye.
-Please be careful!
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
I'll be off then.
Come tomorrow to assist the investigation.
OK.
MORGUE
What happened to Chu Yan?
The news said his room caught on fire.
Did he get hurt?
Why are you here? Where is Chu Yan?
Mumu...
Chu Yan is gone.
You... Since when are you
the type to joke?
This isn't funny at all.
I'm going to find him.
It's true.
The police are already investigating it.
I don't believe it.
There's no way!
You're lying to me!
I wish it wasn't true, too.
Mumu...
Why are you still here?
I can't be alone today.
I want to be closer to you.
Then why didn't you say so?
I didn't want it to be awkward.
And I didn't want you to say no.
Mumu, you're all I have now.
I won't leave your side.
Don't move. I want to say something.
I've realized... life is so short.
If I keep chasing after the past
and hesitating, I'm just wasting my time.
Since I still love you...
there's nothing more important
than being with you.
Because you never know what might happen.
I don't want to regret anything.
Thank you, Xia Lin.
Thank you for coming back to me.
WEN LI CALLING
Hello?
Mr. Ling, I apologize
for bothering you at this hour.
It's fine.
Mr. Wang, any new developments?
Yes. The reason I'm here so late
is because I'd like to ask you
whether you know of any women
close to the deceased?
Did you find new evidence?
I can't reveal any details
of an ongoing investigation.
Mr. Wang, I need to know
the specifics of the situation
to give you any useful information.
Don't worry, I'll keep the details
of the case absolutely secret.
The coroner's autopsy was released.
Chu Yan was holding an earring
in his right hand.
It's the most significant piece
of evidence from the scene so far.
An earring? Can I see it?
As per the law,
only immediate relatives of the deceased
have the right to see relevant evidence.
Chu Yan's father has asked Mr. Ling
to work with you on his behalf.
From now on, Mr. Ling will answer
any questions you may have.
Mr. Chu is currently hospitalized
due to a heart attack.
Mr. Wang, you can go see him
if you have the time.
Just don't excite or agitate him.
Since Mr. Chu has authorized you, it's OK.
This is the earring.
Does it look familiar, Mr. Ling?
I'll get you a glass of water.
I don't normally pay much attention
to women's accessories.
So I'm afraid I might not be of any help.
But I can provide you a list
of women close to Chu Yan.
Thank you for your assistance.
We'll get going now.
Of course.
I was hardly any help, Mr. Wang.
Please do let me know
of any further developments.
I'll see if I can help you
with any additional information.
Sure. You'll be the first to know
when we find the owner of the earring.
Thank you.
-Boss, you...
-Don't worry about it.
I'll get going then.
I just saw the police.
Has something happened?
It's nothing.
Mumu, did you lose an earring recently?
I did lose one.
How do you know about that?
Do you still have the other one?
Let me see it.
It's this one. What's the matter?
Mumu, were you wearing those
when you met Chu Yan before the fire?
Yes, the day before he was hospitalized.
That was the day I lost it.
What does this have to do
with the incident?
The cameras in the hospital
were disabled before the fire.
That fire was not an accident.
Someone caused it on purpose.
Are you saying
someone killed him on purpose?
The police already have clues
pointing to an arsonist.
What kind of clues?
This earring.
Me? How could that be?
Your earring was in Chu Yan's hand.
With no other evidence besides this...
you are the main suspect.
This has to be a joke.
Why would I hurt Chu Yan?
I know. This has nothing to do with you.
Don't worry, Xia Lin.
I'll make sure you're OK.
But why was my earring in Chu Yan's hand?
If I ventured to guess,
the person who plotted all this
was not targeting Chu Yan...
but you instead.
UNKNOWN NUMBER:
DO YOU LIKE THE GIFT?
Gift?
Could it be the earring?
I need you to track a number.
This was where I met Chu Yan.
Someone is leading us here.
Mr. Ling, ten minutes of footage was wiped
from the surveillance cameras here.
That was the exact same time
we got the text messages.
How meticulous of them.
We must have been led here for a reason.
What is it?
A photo.
I was just holding him back!
How did they get it like this?
Xia Lin, who else was here
with you that day?
Yang Tong and the driver
were waiting for me.
With this picture,
they will think
that I killed Chu Yan, right?
I know it wasn't you.
Let's get going.
Mr. Wang, any news?
Regarding Mr. Chu Yan's death,
we'd like to ask
for Miss Xia's cooperation.
Based on a single photo, Mr. Wang?
It doesn't prove anything.
We're just doing our duty.
As a friend of Chu Yan,
you should also cooperate
and avoid interfering
with our investigation.
Investigating Xia Lin is a waste of time.
You could use this time
to look for new leads.
I'm willing to cooperate.
Mr. Wang, we hope the police
can solve this case quickly.
My innocence will be proved
when the real perpetrator is found.
People close to him will also get closure.
Thank you for your help.
I'll be waiting outside.
Xia Lin, do you know
what you're stepping into?
I do. I'll just think of it as field work.
Maybe someday I'll be cast
in a detective series.
Don't worry.
Mr. Ling, when we were out there,
the photo was posted online.
We're already checking the IP address.
Let's go then.
I put the notes on your desk.
-Xia Lin.
-Tongtong.
What are you doing here?
They asked me about you.
I don't know what's going on.
I just told them what happened.
It's standard procedure.
Miss Yang, you may go now.
You'll be OK, right?
Don't worry. You should go now.
Based on surveillance footage
outside Yang Tong's apartment,
you left the apartment between
seven and eight o'clock last night.
I went to buy some food.
Can anyone verify that?
The lady who sold me the food
gave me 20RMB in change.
She probably remembers me.
Who else?
I chatted with the girl
who sells brown sugar water.
A girl? How old was she?
She was about this tall,
probably seven or eight years old.
Is there anyone else old enough
to give us a testimony?
I also ran into a man walking his dog
outside the market.
But I don't know if he'll be back there.
Ms. Xia, the entirety of this conversation
will be on the record.
I do hope you act accordingly.
Sir, I'm more concerned
about this case than anyone else.
I want to know who hurt Chu Yan.
I don't understand why you're so hung up
on me buying groceries.
What's that have to do with it?
You were away from the apartment
when the fire started at the hospital.
You think I went to the hospital,
not the store?
Your whereabouts fit the case perfectly.
Mr. Wang, Mr. Ling has arrived
with new evidence.
Got it.
Mr. Wang.
Mr. Ling has come to provide evidence.
Mr. Wang, don't you think that
there's something odd
about that picture online?
We've already examined the photo
and confirmed it is genuine.
Yes, it's genuine.
But choosing to shoot from that angle?
What do you mean?
Mr. Wang,
this is the IP address
of whoever posted that photo.
IP ADDRESS REPORT
Someone abroad?
They deliberately used an untraceable IP.
It's clear someone was prepared
and waiting for a chance to strike.
This IP address alone
cannot prove that Miss Xia was framed.
We found the location
through this cell phone.
The picture was taken with this phone.
All the security footage
from that day was wiped.
Do you find that suspicious, Mr. Wang?
Mr. Ling, what are you implying?
I'd like to post Xia Lin's bail.
Miss Xia, could you explain this photo?
-Are you here as a suspect?
-Please, excuse us.
-Ling Yizhou?
-Let's head home, Mumu.
Please talk to us.
-Don't worry.
-Miss Xia, explain.
-A few words.
-Miss Xia, please explain.
-Anything you'd like to say?
-I'm Ling Yizhou.
Miss Xia and I were very close to Chu Yan.
There's no way we would have harmed him.
The case is still under investigation.
Please be careful
with your words and actions.
If anything slanderous or libelous
is said about Miss Xia,
I will not hesitate
to pursue full legal remedy.
Let's go.
Please step back.
-Anything else, please?
-Mr. Ling!
I'm sorry.
The first public appearance
of the CEO of Lingshi Group
is at a police station.
No problem.
I love being in public with my wife.
Let's go.
You killed my son.
How dare you come here? Get out!
Mr. Chu.
I understand you are in pain
because you lost your son.
But please watch your words.
Ling Yizhou, you connived
your way to my signature
just to cover for her!
Mr. Chu, we are so sorry for your loss.
I know that you won't believe
anything we say right now.
I won't try to explain.
I just hope that
whoever killed Chu Yan
will be found as soon as possible...
and handled according to the law.
Ever since Chu Yan chose you over me...
I knew you'd hurt him sooner or later.
You're the reason all this happened!
I...
Our condolences, Mr. Chu.
We'll get going.
Why did he say that I'd hurt Chu Yan?
The anger of an elderly man.
Don't take it personally.
Mr. Ling, Mrs. Ling.
I'll wait for you in the car.
-What is it?
-After we left the scene of the crime,
I had a private investigator
look into Yang Tong's background.
There are some major discrepancies.
We'll pay her a visit shortly.
Yes, sir.
An Ran?
Are you surprised to see me here?
If the main suspect is allowed to attend,
is it so surprising
that his good friend does, too?
Whether you come or not
has nothing to do with me.
Nothing to do with you?
The spirit of Chu Yan would feel
very hurt about that.
What do you mean?
He had a fallout with his father
all because of you.
What could that mean
other than that he loved you?
That's impossible. Watch yourself.
You pretended to be unaware of it
while he was alive.
Now that he's gone,
can you live with a clear conscience?
I don't care what you say.
Chu Yan was our friend.
That will always be true.
The death of Chu Yan
is an immeasurable loss to me
and everyone who loved and supported him.
We are all grieving him.
All I can do now
is live with the memories of him.
I'm positive that's what
Chu Yan would want to see.
-You're--
-Mumu.
Something came up,
so I can't drive you home.
I've arranged your driver.
Is it about the case?
No, it's just work.
OK, go do your thing.
Don't worry about me.
-Go home and wait for me.
-Alright.
Miss, are you following
your boyfriend or husband?
Husband.
Is he having an affair?
An affair? Is this how you talk?
When wives act like this,
nine out of ten times it's an affair.
You're quite experienced
in this matter, aren't you?
My husband isn't having an affair.
Miss!
I'm sure he's my husband.
The taxi fare.
Mr. Ling, Xia Lin isn't here with you?
She's busy.
What is this all about?
You took that photo.
No, I didn't.
-Why would I do that to hurt Xia Lin?
-You can drop the act.
I know you're not capable
of doing something like this on your own.
Tell me who you're working for,
and I'll let it slide.
Mr. Ling,
I really didn't take that picture.
I was in the car the whole time.
The driver can attest to that.
You know that the driver
has already disappeared.
That's why you're saying that.
Mr. Ling, I really don't know
anything about it.
I'll give you a chance to prove yourself.
From 2015 to 2017,
where did you live
and what were you doing?
Sir, I'm just a girl from the countryside.
You know from that day
what my family is like.
You know everything already.
If you're still suspicious,
I'll have to explain everything
to Xia Lin.
I encourage you
to make things a little clearer.
I'm not Xia Lin.
I have no sympathy towards you.
Mumu.
Xia Lin, please talk
some sense into Mr. Ling.
He thinks I helped someone frame you.
You're interrogating her?
I deserve to be consulted
for something like this.
You wouldn't have the heart to do it.
I might not be as cunning as you,
but I'm not an idiot.
Xia Lin.
Yang Tong, tell me the truth.
Did you have anything to do with this?
No.
When I first saw you...
I thought,
"This girl is really something."
Living all by herself
out in the middle of nowhere...
chopping wood,
starting fires, and cooking food.
Even cultivating fruit trees
on the mountain.
But I gradually realized...
that your hands
are not hands
that have done real country labor.
Even writers get callouses...
not to say someone who chops wood
with an axe every day.
What do you think?
Xia Lin, I'm so sorry.
I lied to you.
I just wanted
to find a good job in the city.
I didn't want to live a life
like that anymore.
That's what I told myself at first.
I saw nothing else suspicious,
so I let my guard down around you.
But I have no choice now.
Please!
Believe me just this once!
Just once!
I beg you...
After this incident,
regardless of whether
you were involved or not,
I can't keep you by my side anymore.
Moreover...
I trust Ling Yizhou.
He would not suspect you without reason.
You can't blame all this on me
just because I told one lie.
Think about it, Xia Lin.
I've been with you for so long.
I've never done anything to hurt you!
You were waiting for an opportunity.
You've never had cramps like that before.
But you suddenly did after we went
to see Chu Yan at the hospital.
And we ran out of brown sugar water,
so I had to go get some.
It all seems like quite the coincidence.
You pushed me into a trap step by step.
Isn't that right?
If you still cherish the bond
we've created over all this time,
you'll tell me who's behind all this.
I promise I won't hold
you responsible for any of it.
If you don't tell me...
I'll have to hand you over to them.
OK. I'll talk.
It... It was An Ran.
An Ran paid me
to keep an eye on you and Chu Yan.
I sent the picture to her that day.
Then I found your earring
in the hospital room.
When she found out about it,
she told me to stall you.
What is it?
Do you believe Yang Tong?
As soon as this happened,
An Ran was the first person I looked into,
but I didn't find anything.
If she's lying...
why would she put it all on An Ran?
That's what I can't figure out, either.
Didn't you say that
the person behind this was after me,
not Chu Yan?
An Ran does hate me.
She had the means and the motive, but...
I still don't get it.
How could she be so cruel to Chu Yan?
Go get some rest.
I still need to take care of some things.
He never lets me see him sad.
Hello.
I need to find out where someone is.
Be discrete about it.
Hello?
Hey, Linlin. I don't have internet here.
I just saw the news. Where are you?
I'm at Ling Yizhou's.
Wait for me. I'll be back soon.
I'm fine, you don't need to...
She's so hotheaded.
Right, the news.
-LING YIZHOU ABANDONED BRO FOR A GIRL
-BOYCOTT LINGSHI!
You people know nothing about him,
how dare you say that?
No, defending him like this
will only make things worse.
WEIBO USERNAME: THERE'S ONLY ONE TRUTH
BIO: DETECTIVE JIMMY KUDO
Ling Yizhou has been possessed!
Ling has an IQ of 146. Even possessed,
he would be smarter than a normal person.
Ling Yizhou is giving up on himself.
Giving up on himself?
Giving up on the old me
brings out a new and better me!
You guys should read more.
Boss, as of eleven o'clock this morning,
all shopping centers, supermarkets,
and stores in the Lingshi Group
have seen a minor drop in revenue.
A further decline is anticipated.
Give me a revenue analysis
at the end of each day.
Push forward scheduled renovations
for our all stores.
We can take this opportunity
to get rid of some brands in those stores.
Yes, sir.
Alright, thank you.
Notify me immediately of any news.
Anything else?
Boss, people online are talking
about how you bailed out your wife.
It's all very negative coverage.
Don't bother telling me this.
Let PR handle it.
Someone has acted faster than PR.
I'll get going then.
Hello.
What are you up to?
I'm... I'm reading.
Is that so?
I was worried you'd seen
the comments online and felt bad.
You've see them, too?
Yep.
I guess this is what
Internet outrage is like. Now I know.
A bunch of strangers running their mouths,
it's not worth reading.
It's very smart of you
to never use social media.
I do keep seeing a certain user called
There's Only One Truth speaking up for me.
Don't waste your time on all that garbage.
Get your work done. I've got to go, bye.
Are there cameras in here?
I'm working hard on the script.
I thought Chu Yan could play
the main male character.
And now... now he's gone, just like that.
I still can't believe
what happened to Chu Yan.
It doesn't feel real.
You just can't get rid of that An Ran.
With a pretty princess face like hers,
how can she be so heartless?
Right now, I suspect that
she also arranged for me
to go to that interview at the bar.
That's possible.
Last time it was you and Chu Yan,
and she failed.
This time she upped her game,
smearing you,
and bringing Mr. Ling into it, too.
That's like killing three birds
with one stone.
I've already destroyed
Ling Yizhou's reputation as it is.
I can't even bring myself
to see his grandma.
He's quite the homme fatal.
An Ran's love was unrequited,
so you and Chu Yan had to suffer for it.
Why did it have to be so tragic
for my dear Chu Yan?
Miss Jia, you're here.
Why are you back so early?
I wanted to be with you.
I'm going to use the restroom.
What is it?
Nothing.
Are you avoiding me?
Why would I do that?
I've been working myself to death.
I haven't had the time to avoid you.
-Get over yourself.
-We need to talk.
-I'm busy.
-You had time to kiss me!
I mistook you for my idol.
I kissed the wrong guy, OK?
You can't just kiss people like that.
Fine, we kissed.
Why are you upset about it?
Are you my parent or my boyfriend?
Jia Fei.
Wen Li, come with me.
Yes, sir.
What's up with you two?
Don't ask about it.
Wen Li is a ticking time bomb.
I need to move out.
You need to take me in, OK?
Save me, or I'm done for.
What's going on at the company?
Chu Yan's fans have blocked
the main entrance.
They say you're using your influence
to break the law
and cover up the fact
that your wife killed Chu Yan.
I haven't even dealt with the slander
and they go and start a riot,
coming right to our front door.
Notify the Ministry of Justice.
Make sure they hear from our lawyers.
Understood. Oh, yes...
The board has taken great interest
in rumors about you and your wife lately.
If we can't keep it under control,
they might be alarmed.
Prepare a press conference for me.
It's time... for some things to go public.
Yes, sir.
LINGSHI GROUP PRESS CONFERENCE
Good afternoon
to all our friends in the media.
Welcome to
the Lingshi Group press conference.
What is the main purpose
of this conference?
Is it related to Miss Xia?
Please be patient.
You were invited here
for two main announcements.
Two announcements?
Why did Ling Yizhou
not even tell me one of them?
Just keep listening.
First announcement.
Mr. Ling Yizhou, Director of
Lingshi Group, and Miss Xia Lin
were legally married on February 25, 2018.
Is he insane? How could he go public
with our relationship right now?
Mr. Ling is too slick.
No wonder I've been a fan for so long.
Why wait so long to reveal the marriage?
Why is Mr. Ling not present?
Is it because of the Chu Yan case?
Could you explain?
Please explain.
Please elaborate. Just a word or two!
Please explain everything.
I am just as curious as you all are.
We'll wait for my husband to arrive.
He'll explain everything.
I can give everyone an answer.
Isn't that An Ran
of Xing An Entertainment?
Didn't she disappear a while ago?
What is she doing here?
Yang Tong, you traitor!
Hello, everyone.
I'm here today to reveal the truth
about this Mrs. Ling
so that my dear friend Chu Yan
may finally rest in peace.
What is the truth?
Hello, everyone.
I'm Mrs. Ling's assistant.
I am here to identify...
Mrs. Ling as Chu Yan's murderer.
Yang Tong, I was so lenient towards you.
Why would you backstab me like this?
What proof do you have?
I was there the day
she went to see Chu Yan.
I saw her argue with Chu Yan.
She almost pushed him into the water.
I felt it was unfair to Chu Yan,
so I took the photo and posted it online.
But this only makes Mrs. Ling a suspect.
That doesn't mean she's the murderer.
Yeah. That's right.
You can't prove anything.
I prepared a video clip.
You'll understand after you watch it.
What? How could this be?
Are you filming? Quick, run the camera.
That is certainly evidence.
So you're the one who framed me.
Xia Lin feared her illicit relations
with Chu Yan would come to light,
affecting her status as Mrs. Ling.
So, she took the chance
when she went shopping
to go to the hospital and kill Chu Yan.
Then she returned home to cook for me
in order to establish her own alibi.
Yang Tong, when did you
get so good at storytelling?
I almost believed you there.
Xia Lin, you can fool Ling Yizhou
and use your status as his wife
to obscure the fact that you're a suspect,
but you can't cover up this evidence.
You're the one who killed Chu Yan.
Even when Ling Yizhou gets here,
he won't be able to change that fact.
Please explain everything.
What if I show up?
Isn't that Chu Yan?
-Mr. Ling.
-Wen Li.
Don't worry too much
about the comments online.
But you hate being discussed.
That's something I'm willing to endure
to see my wife show her love for me.
Why am I telling you this?
You don't get it, you don't have a wife.
Boss, was that a workplace injury?
Subtitle translation by Jake Eberts
Even if there was only a 0.01% chance
of seeing you fall from grace,
I'd still do everything I could.
The only person who fell from grace
and lost everything...
is you.
An Ran, according to our investigation,
you're accused of arson and kidnapping.
You're now under arrest.
Regardless of whether
it was An Ran or Yang Tong,
they were just pawns being sacrificed.
This matter isn't over yet.
Who are you? Why are you following me?