Hey.
What's your next goal?
To reach that goal,
how much pain do you have to go through?
Have you calculated that?
So...
Is it possible that we misunderstood ourselves?
We think we're chasing happiness.
But actually,
what we really love might be the pain.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Schrödinger.
Is it a person?
(Schrodinger's Cat)
A scientist.
Is his cat famous?
It was an experiment.
What kind of experiment?
I've read about it, but I can't remember.
I think it's an experiment on quantum mechanics.
Didn't I say...
if you want to know something...
Look it up yourself.
Yes.
In another universe,
cats are alive.
But what determines the universe we exist in?
Someone suggested it could be our consciousness.
Do you get it now?
So is Schrödinger's cat dead or not?
Why did they experiment on cats?
Don't worry.
This is just a hypothetical experiment.
So none of the cats died.
You can go brush your teeth, wash your face, and go to bed.
Okay?
All right.
What are you doing?
Look it up yourself if you want to know.
(Schrodinger's Cat)
Look it up myself?
Jian Qing Fen.
You're really sick.
Is it broken?
- I don't know. - Let me.
Thank you.
Restructuring?
Yes.
I heard that after the US company comes in,
there would be personnel cuts.
There will be big changes in management too.
The vice president might have to retire.
Really?
So just in case,
it's best to spread the word online.
Sure.
No problem.
Yes.
Hey, have you noticed...
that Christine has been acting like she's got it in the bag lately?
It's on me.
How annoying.
Yes, that place is hard to book.
Ed was so upset.
He went to talk to the general manager...
and Christine found out about it.
I think if Christine really were to become the new vice president,
Ed wouldn't be able to stay.
Midlife career change can't be easy.
Especially in this economic downturn.
Did you go to work or shopping?
Don't you work to make money?
We make money so we can spend it.
Hey, what do you think?
Don't I look like someone?
Who?
Grandma Xu.
It's slippery here.
Dad, wait.
I saw a cool bug.
You can't smoke here.
Dad.
Do you have something on your mind?
Me?
No.
I see.
Why do you ask like that?
Because Mom said she only smokes when she has something on her mind.
Dad, I found it.
Dad, come and look at this.
It's so cool.
Siva stag beetle.
It's a common insect in low-altitude Taiwan.
We're home.
There's fried chicken.
Bu Bu, wash your hands first.
Okay.
I've washed my hands.
I'm going to eat fried chicken.
Okay.
Is this how you slice scallions?
How long have you been a mom?
You can't even slice scallions nicely.
Didn't you say they all taste the same?
When did I say that?
Appearance, aroma, and taste.
Appearance comes first.
Familiarity breeds contempt.
You'll always find fault with what you have.
What? What do you mean by that?
I don't understand.
I mean...
I'd better get out.
I don't want to cause you trouble.
You're right.
It's better to be dumb.
Me? I'm too smart.
Are you itching to pick a fight lately?
Mom.
What are you making?
Tomato scrambled eggs.
It's Bu Bu's favorite.
Go for it.
If you win 10 million, I'll take you on a world tour.
Do I need 10 million to go?
Traveling around the world is expensive, okay?
And you need to save up for your tuition.
I'll take you for five million.
Be more ambitious, okay?
Let me tell you.
Our consciousness determines our universe.
At 400 meters,
turn right.
Gosh. It has been 10 days.
Nothing.
(Rebecca. Zhang)
Your sister-in-law is so knowledgeable.
She even knows about such an out-of-this-world restaurant.
That way, her taste will stand out.
Turn right.
Bu Bu, stop playing the games.
You'll ruin your eyes.
- I have 11 left. - It's your turn.
It looks like it will continue to drop.
How much did you lose?
How could I lose?
I have your sister-in-law.
How could I lose money?
I've already sold it.
It's a small profit.
It's a small profit this time.
But there are lots of delisted stocks at home.
I'm going to the restroom.
Mom, I'll go with you.
It's okay.
I'll go with Mom and take a smoke break.
Your new hairstyle is really nice.
Hey, this restaurant is really nice.
I only get to enjoy good food...
when you treat us to lunch.
It must be expensive, right?
We're a family.
What's wrong with a good meal?
I read all the texts you sent to your brother.
He was going to call you back.
But I think it's better...
to talk about this in person.
We don't want to take the blame again.
Come on. Don't say that.
You make it sound so serious.
Because I feel really hurt.
Attie records...
Mother's blood pressure twice in the mornings and evenings.
Your brother and I...
followed the doctor's instructions to take care of Mother.
We watched her take her medicine and meals.
As long as it doesn't rain,
Attie would take Mother for a walk in the park.
Mother's blood pressure has never exceeded 170.
I thought your brother and I could discuss it ourselves.
But you misunderstood.
What's abnormal is Mother's memory.
What do you mean?
Last week,
she looked at your brother and called your dad's name.
And the week before that,
she said, Attie stole her bracelet.
That bracelet,
didn't she give it to you a long time ago?
I just felt something was wrong.
I forced your brother to take Mother to the doctor on Monday.
The doctor said...
she has early-stage dementia.
Shouldn't she see a few more doctors?
We can't rely on one diagnosis.
I will.
If you're worried,
you can take Mother to the doctor yourself.
What I'm trying to say is,
what if she really has dementia?
I've discussed it with your brother.
We think the best way...
is to send Mother...
to a professional nursing home.
How can we send her to a place like that?
I knew you'd react this way.
But you know your brother.
Your brother may be unambitious,
but he's not an unfilial son.
I'm so busy with work.
But I'm married into your family,
so I regard Mother as my responsibility.
However, being filial...
isn't enough to handle a dementia patient.
She needs someone to watch her and take care of her 24 hours a day.
We do have a helper,
but you can't force her to work 24 hours a day.
If something goes wrong,
I can't handle the consequences.
The best solution...
is to send Mother...
to a professional care facility.
- I... - I can pay for that.
I disagree.
Or I'll leave Mother with you.
- No, this... - Qing Fen.
Qing Fen.
Look.
The rooms are all the same.
How can I find you?
Jian Qing Hui went for a smoke again.
I don't see the servers either.
Mom.
What's my phone number?
Look.
It's really beautiful here.
Do you hear me?
My cell phone. What's the number?
Your...
Your cell phone number?
Yes.
Cell phone number...
I...
I saved it on my phone.
What about my landline?
Your...
landline?
It's saved on my phone too.
My birthday.
- Your birthday? - Mom.
Is Mother okay?
Your birthday...
Don't be so negative.
Just get a checkup first.
If her condition is confirmed,
she can take medicine to slow down the deterioration.
If your mom's condition is still bad by then,
we'll talk, okay?
What's wrong with Grandma?
I won't let my mom go to a nursing home.
Okay then.
We'll bring your mom back.
Who will take care of her?
Me.
And you.
Why don't we get a helper?
Do you think our home can fit a helper and my mom?
I think...
What's wrong with Grandma?
Don't interrupt when adults are talking.
Hey.
How about...
you quit your job?
Well, your insurance sales job doesn't make much anyway.
And you don't really like that job.
My salary should be enough.
I don't want to discuss it now.
Can I talk now?
Grandma is unwell.
What should we do?
We're not sure yet.
It should be fine.
Don't worry.
(Personnel Announcement)
(1. VP Guan Yi Xiong has applied to retire.)
(His last day will be on Feb 13, 2023.)
(2. Sales Manager He Rui Zhi will take over as the VP.)
(Please be informed of this. Sorry for any inconvenience.)
Why are you working overtime again?
Do you want me to turn off the lights?
Zhang Yi Jing.
Should I turn it off for you?
Sure.
Rebecca
My embrace is waiting for you
Rebe...
Thank you.
It's not worth wrecking your health for work.
You know what it means to take responsibility, right?
You should strive to be a manager in marketing.
I'll make an effort next time.
Why do you always want to be the good guy?
You don't fight for what you should.
If Christine ends up becoming a vice president,
I'll despise you.
I'm really a vice president now.
I really did it.
I've been to that restaurant before.
- Nice. - Let's go.
It's my treat, okay?
No.
I have to pick up my son later.
- Come on. - Join us.
Vice President.
Ed said it's his treat.
Don't be such a killjoy, okay?
Yes. Okay, fine.
Let me ask my wife.
- Okay. - Hurry up and ask.
Actually, I don't keep an eye on him.
Luckily, he studies hard enough.
So he's always in the top 10.
- Honey. - Yes?
They're going for another round.
Okay.
I'll drive to your mom's house to pick up Bu Bu.
Don't get too drunk.
- Don't worry. - Okay.
Look.
I don't even keep an eye on my husband.
You're good.
Gosh.
Thank you.
Why are you smoking here alone?
Just like you.
I came out for some air.
I thought it was me.
Me too.
I asked him just now.
Why?
He said because I'm a woman.
Bullshit.
I even got divorced for the sake of the company.
A few years ago, I got an offer from a headhunter.
An American company.
They offered me three million dollars a year.
I wanted to quit.
He told me to put up with it.
Just put up with it for two years until Guan Yi Xiong retires.
He even gave me a 10,000-dollar raise.
But I'm already over 50 years old.
There aren't any other opportunities.
But I'm still better off than Guan Yi Xiong.
He must be gutted...
to be forced into retiring.
That's why...
loyalty is worthless.
If there's a good opportunity,
you should seize it.
Okay?
Just a word of advice for your reference.
By the way,
do you know Rebecca had an affair with the general manager?
Yes.
I've asked around.
Okay, I got it.
Didn't I tell you not to get endorsements?
- Good morning. - Didn't I say no endorsements?
Okay, no problem.
Didn't I tell you not to get endorsements?
Video ads.
- Radio ads. Print ads. - I'll start the meeting.
I've already told the agency to withdraw the manuscript.
But it'll be too late for the ones scheduled today.
I'll reply to the reporters first.
We'll explain it to the public after the emergency meeting.
Where's our press release?
- I'll rush it. - Okay.
What did the lawyer say?
Right.
I've double-checked with Mr. Zhao.
He's drafting the statement now.
We're terminating the contract in the spirit of the contract.
As for the compensation for breach of contract,
it was stated to be double the amount.
Defamation is not included.
I'm sorry I'm a bit late today.
Hey, did you know Huo Yi Jian is in trouble?
- What? - Really?
What happened?
He was caught doing drugs last night.
I heard that his ex-girlfriend got back at him.
- That's harsh. - So unlucky.
What should we do now?
I don't know either.
We can only wait for the meeting.
I see.
I'm not Rebecca. She is busy.
Rebecca.
How much longer for the press release?
Five minutes.
She said five minutes.
(Zhang Zhi Hao Calling)
When the press release is out,
we'll explain it to the public.
It has been five minutes.
It's just a press release.
Where's Daniel?
The manager is flying to Shenzhen today.
I'm reporting on his behalf.
As for the sales department,
I've contacted all the counters and selling points.
They'll help us remove the cut-outs,
the posters, the flyers,
and all promotional items.
After the meeting,
I'll also patrol the Taipei area.
If necessary,
we can also go down to the central and southern cities.
Reactions at the selling points.
Okay, I'll ask.
- Boss. - Yes?
Do you think we should give the consumers some offers?
- Offers again? - Come in for a second.
We can discuss this when the general manager arrives.
Wait, what does this say?
Strong work ethic during his endorsement?
He's highly cooperative?
Why are you still defending him?
I'm just stating the facts.
Besides, he's really...
Rebecca, why do you keep missing the point?
Here's what's important.
We need to protect the company and the product's image.
By kicking him when he's down?
What do you mean?
Can I really tell you what I mean?
- Hold on. - You think...
Actually, young people's opinions...
are worth listening to at times.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Every time something happens,
everyone wants to distance themselves.
But to the consumers,
distancing ourselves...
means nothing to them.
People might even think...
that we're taking advantage of the artists' negative perceptions.
So I think...
instead of terminating the contract,
we should turn this crisis into an opportunity.
This way, we can get more exposure for our products...
and have a positive image.
Turning a crisis into an opportunity.
That's not a bad idea.
What do you think?
Everyone makes mistakes.
Celebrities are human too.
That's why I think we shouldn't terminate his contract.
Instead, we should tell people...
People who make mistakes...
should be given a chance to take the right path.
We'll never give up on him until he gets back on his feet.
That's good.
Let's have a meeting in that direction.
Eric, let's put it on hold for now.
You can go.
What's your name?
Zhang Yi Jing.
She's in my department.
Stay for the meeting then.
Come here.
Come in, Rebecca.
Sir.
- This is today's press release. - Let's start the meeting.
Take a look at our draft.
I'm actually protecting you.
You know?
So if you have any ideas, discuss them with me first.
Otherwise, these inexperienced ideas will expose your weaknesses.
At the same time,
I hope you can support me.
The vice president, Mr. Guan was parachuted in.
He has been tampering with HR.
So we have to be more united and cherish each other.
What is it?
The general manager is looking for you.
He's looking for Rebecca.
Is there anything you want to eat?
I'm fine with anything.
So everyone was wrong about you.
They told me you're very creative.
Can I have Subway then?
I've already contacted them.
That fast?
Call me Handy Helper.
Okay. Let's go.
I'll treat you to a meal.
That's nice.
Let's celebrate R defeating C.
Rebecca is really cool.
She is.
She just doesn't know it.
What do you mean?
Look.
She'll get scolded if things go wrong.
And Christine keeps rejecting her proposals.
So she's bound to doubt herself.
You're right.
But it's good that she has so many ideas.
It was such a pity.
But things will get better now.
Is that what you like about her?
That's what bothers me too.
It's a double-edged sword.
How so?
We don't seem...
to be in a relationship.
It's all about work.
What about you?
Are you passionate about work too?
Me?
I'm doing just fine.
To me,
it's just a way to make a living.
And I get to make more friends...
to liven up my life.
It's just a way to prevent social withdrawal.
So, I'll just do what I can.
No wonder.
No wonder what?
I mean,
you're a hard worker.
You're doing okay at what you're asked to do.
But it's a bit...
How should I put it?
You lack...
A bit of passion?
I see.
Why are you sitting there?
It's nothing.
I was just thinking.
Maybe one day,
I'll end up like Mr. Guan.
Actually, Mr. Guan is at the age where he should retire.
Voluntary retirement and forced retirement...
are very different, okay?
Self-esteem, get it?
The point is,
how much more are you getting paid?
I don't think it's a lot.
You still don't get it?
Mr. Guan's salary is too high.
They promoted me to take his place...
to save money.
These bosses.
Why do we slave away like dogs?
To make a living.
So,
I'll just be a dog.
As for you,
don't torture yourself over a bit of money.
We clock in every day just to clock out.
If your mom is really ill,
I mean it,
just quit your job.
Hey, why do you always look down on my job?
Look down?
You complain every day that you're tired and frustrated.
Didn't you say you work just to make friends...
and to prevent social withdrawal?
Technology is so advanced now.
With a laptop, you can have access to anything.
But I don't want to be trapped in this house day after day.
I also want to gossip with my colleagues.
I want to dress up to meet clients.
I also look forward...
to that joyful feeling of leaving the office on Fridays.
I also need to prove that I'm not just...
He Rui Zhi's wife,
He Yong Li's mom,
and Jian Qiu Mei Lan's daughter, okay?
I need me.
But you don't want your mom to go to a nursing home.
So what should we do?
Even if I quit,
it should be because I want to.
Do you understand?
Self-esteem.
Hey.
Why is it always so hard to communicate with you?
So do you think...
it's good or bad to be less passionate?
What?
Didn't you say...
I'm less passionate about work?
So is it good or bad?
Tell me as a friend.
There's nothing good or bad about it.
To each their own.
(Zhang Yi Jing: Zhang Zhi Hao keeps calling me.)
Excuse me.
I need to make a call.
The last time I had a sandwich was about 10 years ago.
In Los Angeles.
What about you?
Two weeks ago.
Is it okay working under Christine?
Yes.
Come on.
She has been doing...
what she thought you'd like.
You mean, she's very loyal?
Then why did you pay for a marketing manager?
Answer it. It's okay.
It's okay. Someone will take care of it for me.
He Rui Zhi?
Tell me it's not him.
Before I fire him.
He...
He's really capable.
You're a terrible liar.
It's true.
I like it.
Zero.
Nine.
Seven.
Hello?
We're not meant to be.
Who is it?
Hi, how are you?
Is Zhang Yi Jing here?
You've got the wrong house.
But Zhang Yi Jing gave me this address.
- Look. - Zhang Yi Jing?
Hello.
Zhang Zhi Hao.
(Changhua Prison)
Hey!
Get out of here or I'll call the police.
This is really addressed to me.
You've got the wrong house!
How could she give our address to that kind of person?
What do you mean by that kind of person?
Can you not talk like that all the time?
That's her brother.
You need to write a return address.
Then write the company's address.
It'll be awkward if she gets a reply in the office.
I see.
She doesn't want it to be awkward.
Aren't you afraid something might happen to your mom?
What if he barges in?
I'm just an old lady at home.
Not all ex-convicts are bad people.
Okay?
With that face,
you can tell he's up to no good.
I don't care. Tell her to move out.
If you don't want your mom to die,
tell her to move out.
That's not what my mom meant.
Don't think too much.
She's just shocked.
It'll be fine.
(Homes and apartments for rent)
Ms. Zhang.
Excuse me, Ms. Zhang.
The general manager wants to talk to you.
Hey.
How are you?
I'm doing pretty well.
I'm not okay.
Just now,
I drank too much at the farewell party.
Everyone came to raise a toast to me.
I really want them to shut up.
Mr. Guan is retiring.
Guess who I promoted?
Why should I care?
Do you not care about me or do you not care about He Rui Zhi?
Anyway,
I'm tired.
So I sold some shares.
I'd like to ask for your opinion.
It's not like I have anything nice to say.
That's right.
So you know.
That time you called me...
a mediocre boss.
What did you say?
That I only like listening to sweet talking.
I can't tell...
slander from remonstration.
There's more.
The reason the company has come this far...
is through sheer luck, not my ability.
You're not a good mistress.
You're my confidante.
Life is so lonely without a confidante.
Do you know that?
Everyone is lonely.
Maybe it's because loneliness is necessary.
It allows you to face yourself.
I hope you can still find him.
Your consciousness called me here, didn't it?
I can go up now.
What for?
So are you here...
for a confidante or a friend with benefits?
What about you?
What do you take me for?
Who have you been waiting for? He Rui Zhi?
He Rui Zhi loves his wife.
He won't divorce her!
You're free now.
Without Mrs. He's nagging and He Rui Zhi's watchful eyes,
it feels great, right?
Yes.
You can't escape from me.
Hurry up and go home.
Give me a smile.
Hurry up and go.
Hurry up.
I miss you already.
There's no answer to this.
It's too hard.
So let's not make it hard for ourselves.
That's right.
It's time to move.
Mom.
You're so late.
- I'm... - Why are you so late again?
Are we having takeaway again?
Is it from the place with the good drumsticks?
Yes.
I'll be mad if we have takeaway again tomorrow.
Then I'll get off work early tomorrow.
How about five dishes and a soup?
I'll be so happy tomorrow.
You still look better with straight hair.