How are you?
Fine.
How is your mom?
Fortunately, you were there.
It's just...
that when I saw those keys,
I didn't know what to do.
So...
Are you okay?
It is how it is.
I'm trying to satisfy...
all the people who love me.
That's good.
Those who are capable do more work.
You did the right thing by breaking up with me.
That was ages ago.
Are you still holding a grudge?
I mean,
by doing that, you'll always be the smile in my heart.
Hey, have you thought about it?
Where does consciousness come from?
Why is it always awake?
Buddhists say,
"Everything comes from the heart."
It's our hearts...
that remember everything.
And from that, everything is created.
Then,
what does Jian Qing Fen's heart...
remember?
It's Qing Fen,
she insisted on taking me to the movies.
That's so nice.
You even went to the movies.
What?
I couldn't understand the plot.
I even wore 3D glasses.
And the snow would fall down like this.
It looks so real.
Mrs. He, can you ask him if he got the estimate?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Hey, did you get the estimate?
I got it.
Thank you.
Sure, you're welcome.
By the way,
do you know Daniel was headhunted?
Yes.
Kun told me.
Everyone says you'll definitely take over his position.
It looks like...
you'll be transferred back soon.
Really?
Or...
do you want to stay in Shanghai?
No.
I have to go back sooner or later.
If not, how will my mom cope?
Anyway, Kun has a girlfriend in Shanghai.
He wants to stay in Shanghai.
Really?
Then...
What about you?
Me?
No, I...
He Rui Zhi!
Did you learn to drive?
Yes. It's easier to get around if I drive.
I can take Mrs. He to the market...
or pick up medicine at the hospital.
Let me do it.
Hey, I was so nervous during the driving test.
Gosh, my hands were shaking when I held the steering wheel.
Do you want me to drive?
Thank you.
Thank you...
for everything.
Why don't you drive then?
Like those two...
in the merchandising department,
they were fired when they were caught dating.
But you and He Rui Zhi are fine.
That was Xiao Xiang.
- I'm not his girlfriend! - Xiao Xiang was caught...
dating that guy.
You're not his girlfriend, but you're staying at his house?
I'm really not.
I'm just there to keep Mrs. He company.
So you're...
A domestic helper.
So are you or are you not?
Do you want another one?
(Resignation Application Form)
To avoid unnecessary misunderstandings.
I remember all the painstaking efforts.
I remember the humiliation.
And from that, it created my consciousness.
My consciousness told me...
that I'm not his smile.
(That smile in his heart... I really love this role.)
I'm just his...
Thank you.
Good morning.
You're not staying with my mom?
Are you going to Shanghai again?
No.
Then you can stay with your mom.
If I continue to stay here,
even if you're not afraid of being misunderstood,
what if I can't get married?
Marry me then.
But we haven't even...
started dating yet.
Is it too soon?
Hey.
The box.
Right.
I don't think I need...
to do that awkward one-knee proposal, right?
I'm sorry. This is the right finger.
I think it's too small.
Hey.
Be careful.
It's too small.
You'll hurt your hand.
I can do it.
I'll exchange it for a bigger one.
I can really fit it in.
Be careful.
But I know...
I didn't win.
It's all because my enemy...
Forfeited.
(Rebecca. Zhang)
(He Rui Zhi)
(Permanently Delete Account)
(Confirm)
(We're sorry that you've deleted your account.)
(We hope to see you again very soon.)
(Block Contact, Cancel)
(Cancel)
(Zhang Yi Jing)
(The Forgotten)
(Save)
The current contestant is...
Rebecca Zhang from Taiwan.
She's almost 40 years old,
but she claims to have the physique of a 25-year-old.
Goodness. Not bad.
Hey.
(Thank you, the Rebecca from 12 years ago.)
Should I thank Jian Qing Fen from 12 years ago?
(Head of Family: Is everything okay?)
(Something came up.)
(I'll be home a bit late.)
(Sorry.)
Mom.
Can we not have fast food again tomorrow?
I thought you liked it?
But I don't like having fast food every day.
Do you think I like bathing your grandma every day?
I want to eat scrambled eggs with tomatoes.
Bu Bu.
Grandma, do you want some chicken nuggets?
But I don't want to be trapped in this house day after day.
I also want to gossip with my colleagues.
I want to dress up to meet clients.
I also look forward...
to that joyful feeling of leaving the office on Fridays.
Qing Fen.
Put your hand down.
I'm asking you to put your movable hand right here, okay?
I will fall...
That's all I'm asking.
Can you put your hand here?
You can use this hand.
You can still move this hand, right?
Just hold on to it.
Don't pull me!
- I'll fall... - You're making a mess.
How am I supposed to wipe you?
I'm sorry...
Don't apologize to me.
Mom, don't scold Grandma.
Please, I'm begging you, okay?
Just hold on tight.
Don't move.
There's a mess on the wall.
Mom, what should I do?
- I think I stepped on poop. - I'm sorry.
Why are you crying?
I should be the one crying.
- I'm sorry... - Me!
Mom, I think I stepped on poop.
Don't pull me!
How can I...
I'm sorry.
In my utterly terrible...
and mundane life,
my enemy hasn't revealed...
a word about her life for some time.
So I can only look at her smile over and over again.
And her victory.
The current contestant is...
Rebecca Zhang from Taiwan.
She's almost 40 years old.
The current contestant is...
Rebecca Zhang from Taiwan.
She's almost 40 years old,
but she claims to have the physique of a 25-year-old.
Take one.
I'm not...
Suddenly,
I understood a language I didn't know at all.
She said,
"How are you?"
"Can I give you a hug?"
Thank you.
(9:30am, follow-up checkup)
I'm going to the office for a meeting.
I should be able to pick you up in time.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Mrs. He.
What's your name?
He Wei Shui Mei.
Okay.
Let's see.
Her lungs sound fine.
Okay.
Come on.
Raise your arms.
Okay, put it down.
Hold my hand.
Squeeze harder.
Okay.
Switch to your left hand.
Here.
Hold my hand.
Come on.
Harder.
Very good. You've improved.
Continue with the rehabilitation.
You've taken good care of Mrs. He.
She smells good whenever she's here.
You're really awesome.
To my beloved enemy.
Congratulate me.
I finally found a new goal...
for my trapped life.
Castella cake.
It's good.
It's really delicious.
Taste this.
Okay.
Is it good?
Yes.
It's good.
It's like the likes you collect on social media.
Even if it's just a passing compliment...
from a passerby,
that little bit of strength...
is enough for me to face tomorrow with courage.
Let's take a photo.
When I was bathing her yesterday,
I vaguely felt that her left hand touched me.
It was as if she was consciously trying to touch me.
Then I thought,
"Am I too tired? Am I seeing things?"
But as I continued to observe,
after giving her a bath...
- Mrs. He, here. - She really did touch me.
Come on, hold my hand.
Come on.
Harder.
Squeeze hard.
You can do it, Mother.
Come on, harder.
Yes.
- Do you see it? - Yes.
Yes, it's good. Look.
Helping Mrs. He with physical therapy every day...
Is Dr. Lu still busy?
He's just next door.
I see.
Hi, Dr. Lu.
Hi, how are you?
Sorry, I was just changing the dressing.
I see.
You look handsome today.
Do I?
How are you, Mrs. He?
Are you getting better?
Dr. Lu.
- Did you hear her? - Hello.
She's greeting you.
Hello, Mrs. He.
You're talking more energetically now.
Yes.
But...
You abandoned me.
(Rebecca. Zhang)
(This account no longer exists or you could have been blocked.)
That's so cruel.
Because having no enemies...
is lonelier...
than having no friends.
(164 days later)
After you disappeared for 164 days...
I'm free.
He Rui Zhi.
Mother.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Everything's fine.
By the way,
Mom's death registration...
I'll handle that tomorrow.
Thank you.
(9:30am, follow-up checkup)
Number 68.
He Wei Shui Mei.
Please come in.
Mrs. He, long time no see.
Number 67, Zhang Xiu Lan.
Are you working hard on your rehabilitation?
I thought...
I should come and tell you.
My mother-in-law passed away peacefully.
Thank you for taking care of her.
Don't mention it.
It's what I should do.
Thank you.
Mrs. He's family!
Mrs. He's...
Well...
After my wife...
survived a traffic accident,
I took care of her for eight years.
So...
If you think there are some things...
that no one understands...
I might understand.
(New Contact: One Like)
My conscious tells me,
she said,
"How are you?"
"Can I give you a hug?"
I said, "Thank you."
"I'm fine."
But you know what?
I recently found a good way to bathe them.
It's to find a big platform like this.
Then, remove the board on top and replace it with a net.
That way, it's convenient to give them a bath...
or wash their bottoms when they have diarrhea.
The water will drip down.
The point is,
the platform has to be about 40cm high.
Like this.
When they move from the wheelchair,
it'll be just the right height.
Wait.
It'll slide?
I forgot.
I forgot to add lever lock brakes.
Why am I so dumb?
I...
It's okay.
It's all right.
You've done enough.
Stop blaming yourself.
Really?
But I had wanted to strangle her every day.
I get it.
I understand.
I ask myself hundreds of times every day.
"Why aren't you dead yet?"
I know.
I get it.
I ask myself every day.
"What if it's Rebecca?"
"Would it have been different?"
(Another 85 days later)
He Bu Bu.
Wake up.
Last time,
I saw Zhang Rui Di and his mom...
holding hands on his way to school.
And he was acting cute.
Our class president,
Zhou Yu Xin saw that and he said,
"Zhang Rui Di, are you a mama's boy?"
And Zhang Rui Di cried.
No wonder you only let me walk you to the traffic lights lately.
You're afraid of being called a mama's boy too, right?
That's right.
Hey.
Your dad is here.
Hurry up.
I'm not done yet.
Mom.
Who are you spending the weekend with?
Don't worry, I have a lot of friends.
I'll be happy without you.
Come on, hurry up.
Dad.
Where should we go first?
Have you eaten?
I did. I ate a lot.
Where do you want to go?
Let's go catch some bugs first.
Hey, He Rui Zhi.
What's up?
My sister-in-law is treating us to lunch this Sunday.
Can you join us?
Maybe not yet.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I was just asking.
Bye, Bu Bu.
Bye, Mom.
Hurry up, Dad.
I'm sorry.
Let me sit down for a while.
Don't mind me.
Thank you.
I slept with someone else.
Was it good?
I feel better now.
Dad.
What's wrong?
I have a question.
Is it math?
No.
Did you move to Grandma's house...
because Mom did something wrong?
Who said that?
Mom.
Maybe I...
was at fault too.
We all make mistakes.
But didn't you tell me...
that we can be forgiven if we admit our mistakes?
So will you forgive Mom?
Go play video games.
Hold a tall-kneeling posture.
Tall-kneeling.
Tall-kneeling posture.
And look forward.
Look forward.
Lift your right foot.
Right foot.
When you're stable,
put your hands on your right knee.
Then pull yourself up.
Thank you.
Yu Xiang Li?
I am...
He Yong Li's mom.
Your brother,
he's my son's coach.
Don't you come here often to fill in for him?
It's this place, right?
I think I've seen you before.
How's your girlfriend?
She's...
She's fine.
Do you know each other?
Yes.
Yes, she's a friend from a long time ago.
But we don't keep in touch much lately.
She's fine, right?
Very well.
What a coincidence.
Then...
Be careful.
Sure, okay.
I'll get going.
Einstein said...
Bye.
"Coincidence is God's way of staying anonymous."
The New Age Movement says,
"Coincidence is the law of attraction."
And the Buddhists say,
"It's all in the mind."
I say,
"This is great."
"My enemy..."
"She is well."
It seems that Rui Zhi hasn't been to the gatherings for a long time.
There's an event at Bu Bu's school.
He has to attend it.
I asked Rui Zhi to take him there.
Otherwise, he'll want to come here.
When are we having cake?
Go to your dad for cake.
You're turning 15 years old.
Honey, go get the cake.
Okay.
I'll get the cake.
Why can't he take the day off?
I could have rescheduled it for yesterday if you told me.
Gosh.
It's my fault.
I got the dates wrong.
Rui Zhi scolded me for that.
Hey, is his old house still for sale?
Don't sell the old house.
They should sell their apartment.
There's more space in the old house.
- Yes, we've been discussing it. - Sir, the cake.
The cake is here.
Hooray! Let's eat the cake.
Happy birthday, my dear sister.
Why isn't it a Mille Crepe cake?
Hey, Mom. Give it to me.
Jian Bao, the candles.
Because Grandma said that your aunt likes this cake.
Yes.
I don't.
You really like cream cakes.
Don't you know?
One time, it was Jian Qing Hui's birthday.
His dad got him a cream cake and put it in the fridge.
When he came home from school and opened the fridge...
There was only an empty box.
It was such a big cream cake.
Your aunt ate it all.
That's right. I cried the whole night.
Dad, you cried too?
- Yes. - That's right.
Your dad was a crybaby when he was little.
Hey, Jian Qing Fen.
He Rui Zhi is a good husband.
After your brother told him about that story,
he kept laughing and laughing.
Then he told me that in the future,
whenever it's your birthday,
he'll prepare a cream cake for you.
That's right. He Rui Zhi treats you really well.
Here.
Hey.
Light the candles.
I need to record this. Wait a second.
Are you ready?
How do I press it?
Over here.
I'm lighting them.
Are you ready?
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing.
Happy birthday, Qing Fen.
My consciousness...
made me gaze at my enemy on the other side...
while I focused on looking ahead on the runway.
That's why...
I tripped over myself.
I caught all the balls...
- that Dad threw at me. - Really?
Even a bouncing ball.
That's amazing.
Are you that excited to go out with your dad?
You're all sweaty. Go take a shower.
Can I bring my baseball mitt to school tomorrow?
Sure.
Hooray!
Gosh.
Can we talk?
If you want a divorce,
I'm fine with it.
But for Bu Bu's sake,
I hope...
If so, how could you do that?
If you ever thought about Bu Bu for a moment,
how could you possibly...
So you want a divorce?
You love him?
How is that love?
If that's not love, then what is it?
If you want a divorce,
then do it.
He Rui Zhi.
I just want an answer.
At that time,
was it because she gave up?
Who?
This.
Whose ring size was it?
My mom took the ring you left in the bathroom.
She said it was too big.
It always slipped out when you washed your hands.
Well, at that time,
I suddenly wanted to take a break.
Yes, I've been looking for a job lately.
Do you want to come back to work?
My performance was so bad.
So are we, okay?
Hi, I'm Sunny.
I get nagged all the time.
- Okay. - Anyway, I just think...
that I'll still get paid even though I'm nagged at.
- Yes. - That's right.
Just be thick-skinned.
How much bonus did you get last year?
Sunny got more.
She got six months' worth.
As for me...
Three months?
Yes. Only three months for me too.
Be content, ladies.
A lot of us don't even get a month's worth of bonus.
I'm very grateful.
Otherwise, why would I still be here?
My poor client.
She's only 40 years old.
She wanted to buy a pension plan from me.
But in the end,
after she got a health checkup...
Breast cancer.
What?
- Forty years old? - Yes.
Luckily, she bought medical insurance.
There are many people in this world named Zhang Yi Jing.
There must be plenty...
of 40-year-old Zhang Yi Jings.
Rebecca!
So she would never...
And she can't be...
My enemy on the other side.
Rebecca!