[Happy Ending Romance]
[Episode 8 - Happy Ending Romance]
Timing and Subtitles are brought to you by the 💙 Happy Ending 💙 Team @Viki.com
[Last Story]
Writer Cha. Writer Cha!
Where did he go?
Writer Cha.
Writer Cha!
Where is he?
Not here.
♫ If I close my eyes ♫
♫ All our moments together are like a dream ♫
♫ I'll approach you slowly ♫
♫ So you can lean on me and rest ♫
♫ Even when winter comes after the season passes ♫
♫ I'll at least protect you ♫
♫ Our past days that are full of wounds ♫
Hello?
♫ Until they're forgotten ♫
♫ I still, I still remain in your heart ♫
♫ I'll always be someone who embraces you warmly like a ray of sun ♫
What do you have to tell me in regard to Jung Woo?
By any chance, have you seen this before?
[Happy Ending Romance]
♫ Like an unchanging tree, I'll still be with you ♫
It's Writer Cha Jung Woo's work.
Something he's been writing recently.
I'm sorry, Sunbae.
I'm really sorry, Sunbae.
Am I supposed to hate you...
or hate Jung Hyun?
What in the world were you thinking?
Let me hear your reason.
Or you should've kept it hidden until the end!
So what will you do going forward?
If it becomes known you were voluntarily ghostwriting,
then Jang Soo Cheol, who you reported, and all those people
will attack you while bringing up the past.
I came here since you asked to meet me.
But let's stop here.
I just wanted to write!
Sunbae, I'm sorry the situation turned out like this,
but then or now, all I want is to write under my name.
And?
Jang Soo Cheol can't, but Kim Jung Hyun can?
Are you the Cha Jung Woo that I know?
I trusted and loved Hyung!
He was someone who did his best to shield me from misfortune!
He said I was Hyung and Hyung was me.
The more Jung Hyun shined, I thought it would be okay if I just hid deeper in the dark.
I thought that was the right thing to do!
But Sunbae, I realized it now.
That I was simply afraid that I just didn't want to get hurt again. That's why...
That's why I cowardly hid and ran away.
♫ I still, I still remain in your heart ♫
♫ Like an unchanging tree, I'll still be with you ♫
How is it?
It's good.
As always.
Jung Woo's doing well, right?
Would you be able to...
help him?
I want Writer Cha Jung Woo
to come out into the world.
Do you like Jung Woo?
Yes.
I like him.
Do you love him?
I love him.
What if the person you like gets hurt and has a hard time, the moment
he goes back out into the world?
If the person you love gets hurt and has a hard time,
will you still tell him to go back out into the world?
Yes.
The result is obvious,
but there are many things you have to try to know.
The same result doesn't come out every time.
♫ The days I look up at the sky are getting rarer ♫
Let's go somewhere with me.
Sorry?
You'll know once we get there.
♫ When the days my frozen heart locked up ♫
Let's face it head-on.
[Literature Square]
Sunbae!
Why are we...
He's the only person within Literature Square who can lend you his strength.
Why? You don't want to?
Are you scared?
Shall we go?
Writer Cha!
How are you two here?
Then what are you two doing here?
How refreshing.
Refreshing?
You're not really a suitable combination.
He said he'd help Writer Cha.
Help Jung Woo?
♫ I want to forget and erase my regrets ♫
♫ Your heart embraced me until they were erased ♫
Okay, then shall we head inside?
♫ I want to be your angel, become your stars embedded in the night ♫
Wait, what are you saying?
Wait, you're not that close with Jung Hyun?
Why would he introduce you here when you're not even close?
Well, you see, Professor.
I mean...
Director, yes.
That's a mystery to me as well...
I don't really know.
Yes.
I guess we'll know once Jung Hyun arrives.
He must be here.
Yes?
It's okay. Don't feel awkward.
What do you mean? What have I done?
You're being like this because you feel bad toward me.
Well... that's true.
I was upset at first,
but I thought about it in your shoes,
and you must have been more upset.
The company could go under at any moment,
so I can imagine how resentful you must've felt toward your Cha Jung Woo-obsessed friend.
I wasn't that resentful.
Anyway, I'm sorry, Woo Joo.
We're still friends, though.
Tae Young!
It's okay.
Kim Young Seon and even Cha Jung Woo...
What brought you all together like this?
Everyone here, including me,
has something to tell you.
Okay, go ahead.
All novels released under my name until now,
Yeah?
are actually all... novels written by Jung Woo.
Okay.
What a ridiculous thing to...
Is it April fools? What's with all of you?
Wait, is he serious?
Hey, Cha Jung Woo, you tell me.
Is what Jung Hyun said true?
Yes, it's all true.
You crazy-
Let's talk alone.
Hyung!
It's okay.
This is what I expected.
Jung Woo, you just think about the future.
Let's not avoid anything now.
Hyung...
It's okay, man.
Let's go in.
What's the reason you're telling me this after all this time?
Did you plan to screw me over as soon as I joined Literature Square?
I was miserable all this time.
What nonsense are you spewing?
Are three consecutive bestsellers an easy feat?
Happiness made by someone else is still happiness.
But can't you see you're ruining that with your own hands?
A life where I wear someone else's words like a mask...
I want to remove that mask now, Professor.
I want to be recognized for my own words now.
Jung Hyun,
a writer of three-consecutive bestsellers was actually a ghostwriter.
On top of that, it was Cha Jung Woo who was kicked out of Literature Square.
When this is revealed, you think anyone here will benefit at least 1% from this?
- Let's bury it.
- Professor.
Doing this won't improve the situation that's enveloping us.
Let's just cover it up.
Everyone can become happy if we just cover it up.
I think that's how we ended up at this point.
Even if it hurt... even if we were miserable,
even if we felt like dying, if we had just endured a bit,
things would've been different than they are now.
Please help Jung Woo make a comeback, Professor.
Then convince Cha Jung Woo to publish his book here.
From Literature Square.
- That's-
- I know.
That Jung Woo hates this place for whatever reason.
But is there any reason for me to help when it doesn't benefit me in any way?
I believe he has already entered a contract with another publishing company.
Tell him to break it.
Tell him we'll pay for the breach of contract fee.
How about it?
Will I not suffice?
You're the one who confessed that you're just an empty shell.
Do you expect me to be convinced after hearing that?
Asking Jung Woo to become editor in the first place was
because I didn't want Jung Woo's talent to go to waste.
And when the opportunity came, I was going to publish a book for him.
That was my original plan.
We can just think it's happening a bit earlier. What's the problem?
It's good for Jung Woo if a big-scale publishing company has his back.
Jung Woo probably won't budge.
- If you could convince the literary world-
- What do you think...
will happen to you two if I report this?
Before you make a confession.
I'm sorry!
I ended up eavesdropping inadvertently, Director.
And I'm going to stick my nose in inadvertently.
I'm the CEO of Yi Rang Publishing Company, Han Tae Young.
I'm sorry, but I have something to discuss with Writer Kim.
Would you be willing to listen to me if I speak as the CEO of the publishing company
in contract with Writer Cha Jung Woo?
What are you so deep in thought about?
I'm just wondering why we're going to such lengths over something insignificant.
Huh?
In the end, it was nothing.
I should've just lived the way I wanted to.
It's nothing significant,
so I think living each day to the fullest is the best we can do.
What I want to do,
who I want to see,
what I want to eat and drink,
and living a life doing what I want to do.
"I'll just do my best to play with you for today."
Living with that kind of resolution isn't that bad.
Sunbae, you're really different from me.
I lived in anxiety and worry over what tomorrow would bring.
I was like that, too.
Sorry?
Before I met you and went under.
But once I went under, that's when I realized.
If things were going to end up like this, all my worries were in vain.
So Jung Woo, you'll end up doing great.
Thanks, Sunbae.
Well.
Cha Jung Woo,
even if I have to beg,
I'll try to convince the literary world.
Let's work well together going forward.
Come on, what are you waiting for?
- Cheers!
I had no idea you'd move Yoon Chi Hyung.
As expected, Kim Jung Hyun is Kim Jung Hyun.
Thanks, Hyung.
Kang Woo Joo.
Yes, Sunbaenim.
What's with this atmosphere?
We should be overjoyed,
but why does the joy feel forced?
Well... it's not my place to tell you.
Jung Woo,
let's talk for a moment.
I'll tell him, Writer Kim.
Please let me tell him.
Shall we step out?
What ridiculous nonsense is that?
What do you mean go to Literature Square instead of working with you?
Please do me this favor and do as I ask.
You said you wanted to publish a book with me.
But telling me to go to Literature Square instead of Yi Rang Publishing Company?
Well...
Well, that was Professor Yoon Chi Hyung's condition,
but I want you to go somewhere bigger
and shake off all your sorrows.
Am I a beggar?
Am I a charity case?
Did you think that would help me?
Actually, why would you decide what's good for me in the first place?
So what you want is for me to publish a book at a bigger company?
Fine, let's say I join them.
Then what about you?
If I go elsewhere and write and publish a book, would you be happy?
Is that it?
Writer Cha...
By chance...
are you afraid I'll drag you under...
Is that why you sent me to Literature Square?
Is it like that?
I only now realized...
Now...
Because of you, Tae Young...
Because of you...
Han Tae Young, because of you!
♫ If I close my eyes ♫
♫ All our moments together are like a dream ♫
♫ I'll approach you slowly ♫
♫ So you can lean on me and rest ♫
♫ Even when winter comes after the season passes ♫
That's what I thought.
Yoon Chi Hyung would never do something out of the goodness of his heart.
That's why you two arranged this gathering to convince Jung Woo, huh?
Just help him since you're already helping.
Help him with what?
Is he a child?
Jung Woo will make his own decisions.
Gosh... this was a farewell party, not a congratulatory party.
You're right. It's a farewell party.
♫ Embraces you warmly like a ray of sun ♫
♫ I still, I still remain in your heart ♫
♫ Like an unchanging tree, I'll still be with you ♫
♫ Even when winter comes after the season passes ♫
♫ I'll at least protect you ♫
♫ Our past days that are full of wounds ♫
♫ I hope they're forgotten ♫
♫ Until they're all erased ♫
Writer Kim.
We called a taxi.
Should we call one for you, too?
I want to walk a bit.
Okay.
♫ I still, I still remain in your heart ♫
♫ Like an unchanging tree, I'll still be with you ♫
♫ A day that was the same every day looks different now ♫
♫ Even on painful days if I'm with you ♫
♫ I'm not afraid ♫
♫ I still will always be the one  ♫
♫ Who hugs you warmly like a ray of sunlight ♫
♫ I still, I still remain in your heart ♫
♫ Like an unchanging tree, I'll still be with you ♫
Come on.
Final credits
I'm sorry, Professor.
It's good, Kim Jung Hyun.
Let's work together.
Don't flatter me.
Why would I need to flatter you?
Don't go elsewhere and just work with me.
Did you happen to be nervous?
Let's publish the best book...
my friend.
Where are you going?
Huh?
Timing and Subtitles are brought to you by the 💙 Happy Ending 💙 Team @Viki.com
Why did you come?
This won't do.
I came to propose.
I want to publish a book... with someone who feels happiness from my writing.
You might go under.
But if you're okay with that,
then please publish a book with me.
♫ Always on your side ♫
♫ The comfort I found through your many words ♫
♫ I'll always be by your side ♫
♫ Won't you light my day? ♫
♫ I'm always by your side ♫
♫ I can't carry the weight of your baggage in your place ♫
♫ I'll always be by your side ♫
♫ For however long, as long as it's you ♫
♫ It's okay ♫
♫ There are days that are hard to handle ♫
♫ Hard to forget even after days pass by ♫
[Happy Ending Romance]
[Best Seller]
♫ Your obvious words saying it's okay ♫
[10: Happy Ending Romance, Cha Jung Woo]
♫ Sincerity must not reach your heart any longer ♫
♫ Your closed-off heart ♫
Don't bother me. Things are going smoothly for me right now.
You look happy.
Oh, Hyung!
Wow, your office is amazing.
Bestselling authors sure are on another level.
Are you teasing me? I'm still trying to catch up to you.
But I'll challenge you with the book I'm writing right now.
- What about Tae Young?
- I'm coming up!
♫ Won't you light up my day? ♫
It's Han Tae Young over me, huh?
Of course. It's the CEO of my publishing company over my rival.
You two are both precious to me.
Writer Kim Jung Hyun has agreed to work with us this time.
Really? H-How?
How did you manage to recruit Jung Hyun hyung?
I used my good looks.
You're not my style, though.
Your looks became dirt cheap.
I know. It must only work on you, Writer Cha.
♫ I'm always on your side ♫
Within my fence, there was stability and comfort.
And it was dark as night outside my fence,
so I believed things would be safe this way.
That's when he suddenly appeared...
A happy journey full of adventure had begun.
Happy Ending Romance.
♫ I'll stay by your side ♫
♫ For however long, as long as it's you ♫
♫ Always on your side ♫
♫ The comfort I found through your many words ♫
♫ I'll always be by your side ♫
♫ Won't you light my day? ♫
♫ I'm always by your side ♫
♫ I can't carry the weight of your baggage in your place ♫
♫ But I'll always be by your side ♫
♫ For however long, as long as it's you ♫
[Happy Ending Romance]
♫ It's okay ♫