JICHEONG MIDDLE SCHOOL
Today, we'll be learning about
the Trolley Dilemma.
Who knows what a "trolley" is?
-What is that?
-Trolley?
-Beats me.
-What is it?
It's a streetcar. Do you recognize it now?
-I've seen that on TV.
-I see.
I saw it in a movie.
This trolley's brakes are broken,
and there are five workers
working on the track.
If you do nothing about it,
all five of them will die.
But if you pull a lever,
you can change the trolley's course
to a different track.
However,
there's another worker working
on that track as well.
Let's think about this.
If you don't do anything,
the trolley will kill five people.
If you pull the lever
to change its direction,
the five workers will survive
but that one worker will die.
What will be your decision?
I'll definitely pull the lever.
I'm not sure.
Yes?
I would definitely switch the tracks.
It's five to one.
But those five were fated to die.
If I pull the lever, that one worker
would suddenly meet their death.
That would haunt me forever.
This is giving me a headache.
Do we have to decide?
Then who will?
Not me.
Hey, you can decide.
No. Why should I?
There's no right answer to this dilemma.
We each have an opinion.
All right. Write a paper
about what you would do and why.
Then submit it in two weeks.
Seung-kyu.
Seung…
-Seung…
-Seung-kyu.
Seung-kyu!
-Seung-kyu!
-Seung-kyu.
Please come this way. It's all right.
Help!
Please help.
-Help!
-It's all right.
MURDERER
NAM JOONG-DO
THE BLAME
Good work.
-Good work.
This is Nam Joong-do.
Of course, I remember you.
Ms. Na Mun-suk, the head
of Taeyang Apartment's resident committee.
Didn't we meet
at the district office last time?
Yes, it really is my personal number.
NEW MESSAGE FROM
SENIOR SECRETARY LEE SANG-HUN
Ji, a medical student and the assailant
of a case in Sinyang-gu
that led to the suicide
of Namgoong, the victim,
committed suicide by jumping
out of his apartment today
after his arrest warrant was issued.
-Goodness.
-Assemblyman Nam Joong-do
-of the Daehan Party…
-No way.
-…had mentioned him to the media recently.
As a result, he was put in the spotlight
-as the assailant of a sexual abuse case.
-Shit.
The police, as they deemed the assailant…
I see.
But like I told you before,
I have no say in that.
Yes, that would be an issue
with the procedure.
Is that so?
What is it?
All right.
I will relay your message
to our district office
and get back to you.
Goodbye.
What's the matter?
Sir.
What is she doing?
I don't know. She's in her room.
What could she be doing in there all day?
She even lost her phone.
Just let her be. Yes.
Call me if anything happens, okay?
All right. See you tonight. Bye.
It's illegal to have a paternity test
for an unborn baby, sir.
It's not impossible,
but it's too big of a risk
with the general election coming up.
Let her stay here.
That lowers the risk,
and she may be helpful to us.
Not only did you lose Ji-hoon,
but you took in his pregnant girlfriend
who had nowhere to stay.
They'll feel your sincerity.
Woo-jae, that wasn't what I meant.
I know, ma'am.
I understand.
What I'm saying is that the girl
may seem like a ticking bomb,
but she could actually be
a double-edged sword for us.
It was only a couple of days ago
that the Nation and People's Party
were on our case
about Ji-hoon's meth possession
and the favor from the police.
The election is in seven months.
If you kick her out now,
things could get out of control.
You should be glad that she came to you.
Imagine if she had gone
to the opposing party instead.
We don't know
her true intentions just yet,
but you should keep her here
and humor her for the time being.
Sir.
You have to focus on the general election.
JICHEONG MIDDLE SCHOOL GRADUATION CEREMONY
Who was it that you had to
take the call outside?
-Was it a guy?
-Don't be ridiculous.
You still have a lot to do.
Are you dizzy again?
Sit down. Goodness.
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm okay.
You were doing better
after taking herbal medicine.
I'll finish up making the dumplings.
Just go home and rest.
I've already been clocking out early
despite being the owner.
-Now you want me to leave earlier?
-Yes.
-Gosh.
-Do you want some water?
Come in.
What were you up to?
Nothing.
I need to go to work. This is your lunch.
Okay. Goodbye.
Also, I thought you'd be bored
since you lost your phone.
Yoon-seo and I enjoyed reading them,
but I'm not sure if you'll like them.
Okay. I'll give them a try.
Okay. I'll be back.
Okay.
Take that girl to a hospital
and get her tested for drugs.
Tomorrow, are you--
Right. I'm going to the hospital later.
I'm going to get that drug test.
I gave it some thought.
I think it makes sense
that you and your husband
have trouble trusting me.
After all, Ji-hoon had bought drugs.
Although he didn't use them.
I swear that I'm clean as well.
I'll prove it to you.
Okay. Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Then I'll be out later today.
I'll go to work then.
I'll be back before dinnertime.
Okay. Goodbye.
You know, that lid…
BOOK CONSERVATION
Come in.
Everything looks so interesting here.
I heard you fix books.
Ji-hoon told me.
-He told you that?
-Yes.
How do you fix books?
Well…
I tend to say "conserve"
rather than "fix."
What's the difference?
Take a seat and have a look.
ASSEMBLYMAN'S OFFICE
I'm sorry. Just a second.
I reported it to him.
Let's get to work.
-Yes, sir.
Hello, this is Ko Min-seok.
We'll contact you right away
once we're ready.
If it isn't Mr. Park Yeong-su.
When are we going out for drinks?
Are we strangers
just because I quit eight years ago?
I know, why did he have to fall
in front of the kindergarten bus
and traumatize the kids?
Assemblyman Nam's statement?
We're still working on it.
Yes.
I'll send it over as soon as we're done.
Okay.
Goodbye.
We'll need a draft of his statement.
Sure.
I'll be back in a bit.
-Okay.
Assemblyman Nam Joong-do
of the Daehan Party
had mentioned him to the media recently.
As a result, he was put in the spotlight
as the assailant of a sexual abuse case.
Hello, ma'am.
Thank you so much for your time.
Don't mention it.
I should be the one
thanking you for inviting me.
She's put so much effort
into preparing for your visit
over the past three months.
And I've been losing sleep
for the past three months
because I was so eager
to participate in this seminar.
-Shall we go inside?
-Sure.
This way.
What's the matter?
Ji Seung-kyu jumped off a building.
He jumped off a building?
Ma'am, are you serious?
That medical student committed suicide
by jumping off a building?
Yes, the articles
are being posted as we speak.
Come to think of it,
Assemblyman Nam was often referred to
as Daehan Party's sharpshooter.
But publicly attacking a mere civilian
and driving him to suicide?
I'd say this is a terrible case of…
improper handling of a firearm.
You're absolutely right.
Goodness.
JI SEUNG-KYU'S SUICIDE
SHARPSHOOTER NAM'S IMPROPER HANDLING
Mr. Shin.
Yes, sir.
Although there's nothing
we could possibly do to comfort
the parents who lost
their child so tragically,
find out where his wake is being held
and send them some flowers under my name.
Yes, sir.
Goodness.
I can't fathom
how Assemblyman Nam must feel.
Anyway, we'll get going.
-Please call me if anything happens.
-I will.
-Goodbye.
Let's go.
FUNERAL HALL
No way.
How is this possible?
This is so fascinating.
It's a totally different book.
Do you think
this could be done with people too?
What?
I was just asking.
So…
why did you bring me here?
Right. Can you give me
that thing from earlier?
Right.
There.
No way.
Here you go.
This must be a new lipstick.
Someone gave it to me.
And it's a lip balm, not lipstick.
It's for moisturizing your lips.
I see.
They make such great products these days.
It's a pretty color too. It suits you.
By the way, what's that?
It's a dehumidifier.
Since I work with paper,
maintaining the right amount
of humidity is crucial.
It can't be too humid or dry here.
What if the weather
was fine during the day,
but it starts to rain at night
when you're home?
In that case…
I can control it remotely
through the app on my phone.
That's cool.
But if it suddenly
starts pouring at night,
I come by to check at times.
Why? I thought you could do it
on your phone.
Because I'd rather check in person.
Come take a look.
These are all my clients' books.
I can't have these books
getting more damaged.
After all, they entrusted me
with their precious books
that they've cherished for years.
So when there's heavy rain,
I can't just rely on my phone.
I have to come and see for myself
that these books are safe.
Seeing them for myself
is much more reassuring.
Yes. I guess you're right.
Where did you learn to do this?
BOOK REPAIR
I used to go to the library often
when I worked at the welfare center.
Then one day,
I saw that the library
was looking for volunteers
in the book repair department.
You're here again.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
-Ms. Kim.
-Yes?
Do you want to give this a try?
I do.
All right.
Make sure to remove all the adhesives.
That's it. You're doing great.
The more I conserved damaged books,
the more fascinating it got.
It became fun and I wanted to know more.
Then I taught myself
through books and online research,
and I opened up this studio
after quitting my job there.
Hello, I'm afraid Assemblyman Nam
can't do any interviews for now.
-Yes. We're still looking into it.
-I see.
-I'll call after we release a statement.
-A statement?
-He's…
-Thank you.
We're still working on it.
I'm sorry.
We'll email it to you
as soon as it's ready.
Thank you.
All the reporters are waiting
for his statement, aren't they?
Yes.
This is Assemblyman Nam's office.
-We're still looking into it.
-Hello. Yes.
Right.
We're sorry.
Please be patient,
and we'll send out his statement soon.
-Thank you.
-Goodbye.
WANNA PHONE
THIS MONTH'S CELL PHONE
Right. Thank you.
I appreciate it.
No problem.
Did you cancel your old phone?
You don't want a stranger using it.
I did.
There's nothing important in there anyway.
Are we going home now?
SONMAT NOODLES
Can we have lunch elsewhere?
Like I said before,
this is Yeo-jin's restaurant
and I'm a regular here.
If you want to live with us,
you should get to know the staff here.
Who will you tell them I am?
Just tell them I'm some kid you know.
Okay. I'll say that.
Let's go inside.
-Did you enjoy your meal?
-Yes.
-Please throw away the receipt.
-Sure.
-Have a good day.
-You too.
Have a good one.
She sure has a great appetite.
You were so skinny when you were pregnant
because you couldn't eat anything.
It's different for everyone.
And I had it rough back then.
I was pregnant with Yoon-seo not long
after my mother-in-law passed away,
and Ji-hoon was starting school soon.
And my husband was too busy with his work.
I felt so helpless.
When you moved in with us,
you didn't just move in.
You practically saved my life.
That's why you're my savior.
One who came to ruin your life?
Yes.
That's why you should always
be there for me.
Yes, ma'am.
Can I have some more kimchi?
Soo-bin.
You can get home by yourself, right?
DEOKSUNG MILL
A new form of fraud targeting young adults
is becoming more and more elaborate.
Many fell victim to the allure…
-Ma'am.
-…of a high-paying part-time job
only to enter into the world
of voice phishing…
It's barley tea.
You could get sick from overeating.
It's the most I can do for you.
Drink it slowly
and let the food be digested.
By the way,
I'm just asking out of curiosity.
What's your relationship
with Ji-hoon's family?
You're not family.
What do you think a family is?
I consider myself a part of their family.
I can do anything for them.
That's what a family is.
That bastard.
Served him right!
MED STUDENT COMMITS SUICIDE
BY JUMPING OFF APARTMENT
The police do not suspect foul play…
He killed himself
because he was facing prison time!
INVESTIGATION EXPEDITED
FOLLOWING ASSEMBLYMAN'S PUBLIC COMMENTS
…to investigate his case thoroughly.
I've never seen
such a competent assemblyman before.
…caused a nationwide uproar,
triggering a hashtag movement and more.
Meanwhile, the residents
who witnessed his death
-were severely traumatized
-Thank you.
-and are receiving treatment.
They said he would have
gotten out in no time
even if he was sent to prison.
But it's not like I could have gone
and killed him myself.
I was worried
that I couldn't look my granddaughter
in the eye after I died.
But look at that.
Now that he's dead and gone,
I have nothing more to wish for.
Thank you, God. Thank you, Buddha.
Thank you, Assemblyman Nam.
I am truly thankful.
Thank you so much.
I was already grateful
that both of you came
to my granddaughter's wake.
How could I ever repay you?
Thank you so much.
Hold on.
Wait here for a second.
Ma'am, take these.
Here are your two bottles of perilla oil,
and try some of the sesame oil as well.
No, that's okay.
-Gosh.
-No, really.
I used domestic sesame seeds.
It's really good.
Take them.
-No, it's okay.
-Just take them.
Youngsan.
-You know where that is, right?
-How dare you come here?
-In North Chungcheong-do.
-Get out!
Their sesame seeds are the best.
Just take them.
I don't have much to give you
on such a happy day.
Take them. Please?
Okay?
Okay. Thank you.
DEOKSUNG MILL
NAM JOONG-DO IS A HERO OF JUSTICE
HE DESERVES A NOBEL PRIZE
People are calling Mr. Nam
a hero of justice.
It must be so nice
to have such a righteous family.
Right?
It looks good,
but instead of
"flustered by the shocking news,"
could we use "heartbroken"?
"Heartbroken by the shocking news."
That's better.
You haven't lost your touch.
Assemblyman Nam replied to my email.
Mine too.
Supplementary material?
COMPARE WITH OTHER BILLS AND REVISE
ADD EXAMPLES
Right, this part.
How meticulous.
I'll be off to a debate now.
-Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
-Goodbye.
Send it to his phone when you're done.
Okay.
Release it as it is.
Yes, sir.
Confirmed.
The online opinion
seems to be mostly in your favor.
There won't be any more articles either.
The wake is taking place
at Kwangsun University Hospital.
You're not going, are you?
The public sentiment
is currently in our favor.
If you attend,
it might seem like you're mourning
the death of a sex offender.
-Hello.
I thought I'd mention it, just in case.
ASSEMBLYMEN DROP-OFF AND PICK-UP AREA
Hello, Assemblyman Kang Soon-hong.
Goodness. Hello, Chairwoman Woo Jin-seok.
Please.
By the way, Chairwoman Woo.
All the controversies surrounding
Assemblyman Nam these days
must be causing you some headaches.
Controversies are made
day and night here in Yeouido.
I doubt there's a single politician
who hasn't had one.
Even still, there should be a limit
to such controversies.
He called him out publicly
and he committed suicide?
I'm truly concerned about whether or not
Assemblyman Nam can overcome this.
This is a surprise.
Your in-laws' real estate speculation
which Assemblyman Nam mentioned
seemed to be getting swept
under the rug due to this current matter.
So I thought you'd be glad.
I was actually worried
about whether or not
you'd be able to overcome it.
What are you…
Goodbye, then.
Why that…
I see.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Was it another call
complimenting Assemblyman Nam?
Yes.
They thanked him
for taking out the garbage
and said they'll keep rooting for him.
Right. It was the caller who used
the word "garbage," not me.
You know, it would be more helpful
if they thanked us by making a donation.
Exactly.
I was worried sick earlier.
I'm just glad things are working out.
Agreed.
I'm exhausted right now
from being so tense all day.
All right. Who's down for a drink
after work today?
-I am.
-Should I book a place?
Sure.
Why? I thought it was good.
You liked the eggplants?
Yes. It wasn't bad.
Yoon-seo, did you watch the news?
I can't believe it.
What do you mean?
You haven't heard?
You know that medical student
your dad called out on the news?
He committed suicide today.
Your dad is so amazing.
Justice was served.
Seriously. He's the best.
I can't believe it either.
Seriously. It'd be a waste of tax money
to send him to prison.
I wish all murderers and robbers
would commit suicide too.
-That's intense.
-I wish…
adulterers would also die.
This is the key point
of the real estate speculation
surrounding Assembly Kang
of the Nation and People's Party.
Lee, his sister-in-law, had purchased
a 10,000 square meter farmland
in Youngsan,
North Chungcheong-do a year ago.
Recently, that land was chosen
to be redeveloped by the MOLIT.
Suspicions of insider--
Hello, ma'am.
Where are you headed?
-To Youngsan.
-Sure thing.
Wait. Youngsan?
As in South Chungcheong-do?
It's North.
I see.
That's really out of the way for me.
I'll pay you for the round trip.
Yes, ma'am. Hop in.
Seung-hee.
Hey, Ki-young.
I didn't think you'd come.
Is Mom home?
Your mother? Yes, she's there.
I guess she's not out
shopping for land today.
Of course not.
She's waiting for you at home.
You don't need to lie.
Why would she wait for me
when I ran off for three years
saying that I couldn't stand her?
MED STUDENT COMMITS SUICIDE
ASSEMBLYMAN NAM'S PLEA
FOR A REINVESTIGATION DROVE HIM TO SUICIDE
LEE SEUL-GI MEDICAL CLINIC
-I'd like to take a drug test.
-Pardon?
A drug test.
The medical student's wake?
Why would you go there?
It's bothering me too much.
Hye-joo, I understand
that this was unexpected
and that you're feeling troubled.
But no one is criticizing
Joong-do right now.
I'm not saying they're right,
but people are saying
that the kid deserved it.
I doubt Joong-do will go there.
If he does, it may seem like
he's taking responsibility
for that kid's death.
But that's not the case.
So you shouldn't go there either. Okay?
Think of what the bereaved family
might say to you.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
Get out!
How dare you come here?
How dare you set foot in here?
How brazen could you be?
YOUNGSAN SESAME OIL
Youngsan.
You know where that is, right?
In North Chungcheong-do.
Take them.
-No, it's okay.
-Just take them.
Take this. Okay?
We've arrived, sir.
Thank you.
Let's go.
-Hello.
Nam Joong-do, you bastard!
You killed my child
and won't even come to his wake.
How can you call yourself human?
-Nam Joong-do! Do you know who I am?
-Stop him.
I'm Ji Seung-kyu's father!
The father of the boy you killed!
-Stop it!
-Get inside, sir!
-Let me go!
-You murderer!
You killed our son!
Nam Joong-do, you murderer!
Murderer!
Where are you going, you bastard?
Are you okay?
I can't believe this.
Use this.
I'd like to thank you
for your interest in paternity leave
and for attending this debate
held in support of this policy.
Paternity leave is a right
for all infants and their parents.
Frankly, I never took paternity leave.
If my wife finds out
that I'm giving a speech here,
she'll give me an earful.
So please keep this a secret from her.
Okay.
PML is an abbreviation
for "pregnancy and maternity leave."
Hey.
-Hey.
-Sorry for being late.
That's okay. Did you eat?
Of course not.
MS. KIM
Ms. Kim.
It's me, Soo-bin.
Why didn't you go home?
I was bored.
Can I come in and watch you work?
Thank you, sir.
My pleasure.
I loved your speech.
Thank you.
-Goodbye.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
-Thanks for the jacket.
-Don't mention it.
The rest of your schedule
is at the National Assembly.
You can wear the spare suit in your--
Wait.
I'm sorry, but could you cancel
my schedule for the day?
Mr. Park, you can go home
after dropping me off here.
Yes, sir.
Are you going somewhere?
We can drive you there.
That's okay. Could you take
my suit to a dry cleaner?
I'm sorry. See you tomorrow.
By the way,
do you have to graduate from university
to become a book conservator?
I didn't go to university.
-Really?
-Yes.
I see.
Right.
I think Ji-hoon mentioned that.
He told you that?
Yes.
I don't have any parents. Just like you.
Ji-hoon told me.
Did he tell you anything else?
Did Ji-hoon tell you
anything else about me?
He did.
That you're not his birth mother.
Anything else?
No.
That's all.
I'm sorry, Soo-bin,
but could you go
and buy me a bottle of water?
Water?
Do you remember seeing
a convenience store nearby?
Can you get me one from there?
I forgot to buy it.
Sure.
My purse is in my handbag. Take it.
I have enough money for water.
I'll be back.
That you're not his birth mother.
That's all.
What did you expect?
Mom, I'm home.
You came together.
Yes, I picked her up from the airport.
Why didn't you just leave
while you were at the airport?
Why did you come back?
Come on, Mom.
Don't be like that.
Didn't you miss me? It's been three years.
Why would I miss the daughter
who abandoned me?
Honey.
Hye-joo.
This is just too hard.
Someone died…
because of me.
No.
It wasn't your fault.
You didn't do anything wrong.
You're not to blame, honey.
You didn't know this would happen.
But…
But they lost their son
because of me.
Ever since I fell in love with him,
I…
I know exactly how that feels.
…have never once doubted…
It's all my fault.
…the kind heart he has…
They lost their son.
…toward this world
-that we lived in.
-I'm here.
-Have some of this.
-Not once.
Hey.
Come sit.
Come on.
Stay a bit longer.
-We can eat together.
-That's okay.
You should save it for tomorrow.
Don't worry about tomorrow.
I'll be back.
Enjoy your meal. Goodbye.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
-Come by again.
-I will.
-Goodbye.
-Go home safely.
-Okay.
-Go on.
Goodbye. Go home safely.
-Okay.
-Bye.
HAJEONG-DONG, SINYANG-GU
She must work at the community center.
No.
I asked her and she said she didn't.
Then where?
I'm not sure. I don't even know her name.
She won't tell me.
But you haven't told me
where you're from either, young man.
I'm not that young.
Goodness. Are you married?
You look so young.
I have a child.
-A child?
-Ma'am, the stew is getting cold.
-Let's eat.
-Okay.
It's been three years now.
Who could it be?
They sent us a hefty sum.
Exactly.
-And it's anonymous, so they'll be taxed.
-Did the Anonymous Angel come by again?
Yes. Along with a million won,
just like the other times.
Let me help.
-Let's put it on the cart.
-Okay.
-One, two…
I fixed it,
so it should last you a bit longer.
Goodness, thank you.
You're better than my own kids.
-I'll get going.
-Hold on.
Here.
-Thank you.
-Go on.
Goodbye.
Goodness. You're here.
Hello. Have you been well?
Have some apples.
Okay.
SINYANG-GU SENIOR WELFARE CENTER
Ma'am.
Ma'am, the meat--
You're here.
-Hello.
-Goodness.
-Eat up.
-Okay.
Thank you.
I'll get you some rice tea.
Let me.
It's okay. You two stay and eat.
I'll go get it.
Sit down.
Come on.
About that rice…
I didn't tell anyone, so don't worry.
Thank you.
My name is Nam Joong-do.
What's your name?
I'm Hye-joo.
Kim Hye-joo.
Ms. Kim Hye-joo.
How pretty.
I meant your name. You have a pretty name.
My child died
because of you.
Get out!
How dare you come here?
Get out of here this instant!
Get out!
How dare you set foot in here?
Mom, I'm hungry. Let's eat.
-I don't want to.
-We haven't eaten together in a while.
Why are you being so friendly? Let me go.
-Mom.
-Did you forget that you left me?
Will you have the baby?
I'm not sure. Would you prefer that?
I guess that depends on who the father is.
Ji-hoon might not be the father.
You're right.
He might not be.
I LOVE YOU, MOM AND DAD.
SINCERELY, NAM JI-HOON
TROLLEY
You know that I gave you up
to share with the world, right?
I just want to be here with you.
I came by to see you,
so I'll just be doing that.
Are you going to stay in that house?
Then lay low, as if you're dead.
Don't get too attached to her.
I'm afraid you'll get hurt.
I got tested for drugs.
I don't know what to feel
whenever I see her.
Frankly, I'm very disappointed
in your wife.
Youngsan? Why all of a sudden?
It's your hometown,
so I was wondering if you knew anyone.
If you had to choose
between the world you dream of
and your wife,
which one would you choose?
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim