Hello.
I am Kim Hye-joo,
the wife of Assemblyman Nam Joong-do
of the Daehan Party.
Tell me everything
that you've lied to me about.
Don't leave anything out.
And I mean anything.
And I'm not forgiving you for any of it.
There's nothing else.
Are you sure?
Twenty years ago,
I was molested
by a boy I went to school with.
I reported it to the police,
but the assailant
immediately took his own life,
and the case was closed
without further investigation
as there was no one to indict.
"Molested"? This is ridiculous.
As a result, I lost my chance
to reveal the truth of the incident.
I ended up having to leave my hometown
as I was falsely accused of lying…
and driving the boy to his death.
She came to our house
and demanded settlement money
for her alleged molestation.
The claim that I lied about being molested
for money is completely untrue.
I see. I would like to ask
Assemblyman Nam a question.
You proposed an amendment
to the Criminal Act
that you named "Namgoong Sol's Law".
But ironically enough,
your son was an assailant of a sex crime
who died shortly after his offense,
bringing his investigation
to an end.
Am I right?
Yes, that's correct.
Yes.
It's true.
The anchor will bring up Ji-hoon.
She'll point out
that I proposed Namgoong Sol's Law
when my own son is a sex offender.
But Ji-hoon is innocent.
And do you have to
mention that bill today?
Talking about Ji-hoon
will be the most effective way
to appeal my sincerity
to the public.
I'll make sure the bill gets passed
so that no one will suffer like you did.
Isn't that what you want as well?
Even though
he put me through much emotional pain,
I can swear that I never wished
for him to take his own life.
Not even for a moment.
When he took his own life,
it turned my life completely upside down.
Even if Namgoong Sol's Law gets passed,
my case will not be revisited.
However,
I mustered up all the courage I had
to come out here today
in hopes that there won't be
any more victims like me.
For a very long time, I thought
that I shouldn't have reported him
to the police back then.
I was filled with regret.
But thanks to my husband,
I am now convinced
that I would do the same thing
even if I were to go back in time.
I will…
never…
run away again.
THE TRUTH
I'm going to see a lawyer tomorrow.
We can sort out our divorce through them.
Don't take off your ring.
You and Namgoong Sol's Law
have just become
the center of attention.
So not just yet.
How can you be so shameless?
The bill needs to pass
before the election.
If it doesn't,
it'll be discarded when my term is over.
We can't get divorced until then.
Shall we go, sir?
One minute.
We need a moment to talk.
THIS IS OCY REPORTER LEE JEONG-JI.
ARE YOU AVAILABLE FOR AN INTERVIEW?
REPORTER KWON IL-RYUL, QTBC
REPORTER LEE YONG-I, YTE
YEO-JIN
What is it?
Yes, that's me.
Jeongsun Medical Center?
What?
Suicide?
Yeo-jin.
Are you Ms. Hyeon Yeo-jin's guardians?
-Yes.
How is she?
She was brought here in time,
so her life's not in danger.
What happened?
She overdosed on sleeping pills
and fainted at her restaurant.
A regular was passing by
when they found her unconscious.
So what now?
She needs to be hospitalized
until she wakes up.
But we only have
private wards available now,
so she'll stay in the emergency room.
Take her to a private ward.
Pardon?
Please do that.
Okay. One minute, please.
I'll be going now.
Thank you.
I'll stay here. You can go.
-What?
-Honey.
Isn't that our district's assemblyman?
You're right.
It's Nam Joong-do.
-Right?
-Yes.
I just saw him on the news.
-You did?
-Yes.
Do you want to shack up with her?
Do it after we're divorced.
For now, just leave.
Okay.
I'll call you.
Don't let Yoon-seo know.
About any of this.
Ever.
Okay.
But ironically enough,
your son was an assailant of a sex crime
who died shortly after his offense,
bringing his investigation to an end.
Am I right?
Yes, that's correct.
INTERVIEW WITH ASSEMBLYMAN
NAM JOONG-DO'S WIFE
Yes.
It's true.
You're going on the news with him today?
How can you do that
after finding out about his affair?
This is the only way right now
to reveal the truth to the world.
But still.
I watched it.
The dashcam footage of Ji-hoon.
I don't blame you.
I'm sorry for doubting you.
And I'm sorry for letting you down.
It's fine, sir.
JICHEONG MIDDLE SCHOOL GRADUATION CEREMONY
Congratulations, Ji-hoon.
I didn't think you'd make it.
I can't miss this.
Guess what, Dad?
Mom is taking us out for jjajangmyeon.
It's your lucky day.
What happened?
I thought you couldn't come.
Can you have lunch with us?
No, I have to get back. I just dropped by.
YOON-SEO
Hey, Yoon-seo.
Are you back from your classes?
Yes, I just got home.
Mom, I saw the news.
Everyone's rooting for you now.
I'm so relieved.
By the way, where's Auntie Yeo-jin?
She isn't home.
She's out of town?
Yes.
So make sure to lock up, okay?
I'm sorry
for thinking you were lying the other day.
Mom.
Stay strong.
I love you.
Thanks, Yoon-seo.
You know I love you very much, right?
Good night.
POWER OFF
Kim Jae-eun is lying.
I want you to interview
her and me together.
-The National Assembly is observing
-Signatures are being gathered
-the public's response to the bill.
-throughout Seoul in support of the bill.
-Daehan Sex Crime Victim Support Center…
-Heated debates are going on…
Thank you for supporting
Namgoong Sol's Law.
I will relay your message
to Assemblyman Nam.
Thank you.
Bit-na.
This was Gangnam Station this morning.
Petitions are being signed
all over the city.
-Oh, my.
-Hey.
The donations for Assemblyman Nam
just reached the annual limit.
-We got 60 million won just today.
-What?
No way.
I can't believe it.
Thank you for interviewing with us, sir.
Thank you. Take care.
See you another time.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. Goodbye.
Hello, sir.
Reporter Shin Jae-hui
from Daeho Daily, right?
-Yes, that's me.
-Nice to meet you.
Please come on in.
This way, please.
The public sentiment is
in support of Namgoong Sol's Law.
Shouldn't we show support as well?
No. It was an arbitrary decision
by Assemblyman Nam
made without any discussion
with the party at all.
We don't even know if the bill
will pass the committee's review
with the juridical issues it entails.
We need a cause if we're going to
support it as a party.
Public sentiment is
the only cause we need.
He completely excluded the party
from his decision.
That's just a lack of discipline.
You left these clothes
in the car yesterday.
Thank you.
You must feel uncomfortable
being with her.
I'll stay with her.
You can talk when she wakes up.
You should go home for now.
Were you aware of their relationship?
Yes.
I had forgotten.
For you, Woo-jae…
I mean, Mr. Jang,
my husband always comes first.
How long have you known?
Was I the only one in the dark?
I'll stay here.
Nam Joong-do is
our district's assemblyman.
Hey, I saw him
in the emergency room yesterday.
-Really?
-Yes.
This is the only big hospital in the
neighborhood after all.
I wonder why he was here though.
No idea.
Your dad was amazing on TV yesterday.
Your mom has cleared her name too.
This is so great.
But her brother is still a sex offender.
I'd be too humiliated to come to school.
Hey, shouldn't you drop out?
Hey, that's enough.
It's not like she did anything wrong.
Do you want to be called
to the disciplinary committee?
Why are you always bringing up
the committee? You snitch.
That's right.
Nam Joong-do's son molested me
dozens of times.
But Nam Joong-do made it
sound like it was just once.
Jeez. He deserved to die.
Right. I heard his son was a meth addict.
Did he force it on you too, by any chance?
Of course he did.
He tried to make me use it too.
You're lying.
Ms. Kim, this isn't right.
MS. KIM
The phone is turned off.
You will be redirected to voicemail.
JICHEONG JEIL REAL ESTATE
The lady from the other day
wants to buy your restaurant.
Please give me a call.
I'll call the doctor.
No, Hye-joo.
I'm okay.
The realtor called.
Were you going to sell
the restaurant and flee
before I found out about you two?
Did you take the pills
because you got caught?
You know how much I suffered
because of what happened in the past.
How could you do this?
Did you hate me that much?
Did you want to make me suffer
even after you died?
I am
really mad at you,
but I never wanted you to die.
Don't you feel bad about it at all?
You couldn't do this if you do!
I'm sorry, Hye-joo.
I lied.
What else have you not told me?
I thought I was saving you
from bigger pain.
Cut the crap.
Just cut to the chase.
Nam Joong-do…
He…
raped me.
You're out of your mind.
JI-HOON'S GRADUATION
Don't come any closer.
I'm going to call the police.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
Please forgive me.
"A mistake"?
You call that a mistake?
How can you call yourself human?
How could you…
How could you do that to me?
Please forgive me this once.
It will never happen again. I promise.
So…
please forget about…
what happened last night.
I truly regret it.
I will become a better assemblyman
and make up for what I've done.
Do you even hear yourself?
If Hye-joo finds out,
she won't be able to handle it.
Please, Yeo-jin.
How could you use Hye-joo as an excuse?
Yeo-jin.
Are you still feeling unwell?
I'll leave your medicine outside the door.
Take it and get better soon, okay?
COLD MEDICINE
Yeo-jin, are you sleeping?
I'm about to go to bed.
You've been sick for so long.
I made a doctor's appointment
for tomorrow. Let's go together.
Okay.
And I made some seaweed soup.
Tomorrow is Chae-eun's birthday.
Please give this to Chae-eun.
From Ji-hoon's mom.
Let's go together tomorrow.
Okay.
Good night.
Rest up.
That's the day I decided
to forget everything
and move on.
Yeo-jin, you're up.
Give me a second, honey. I'm almost done.
Take your time.
Are you going to work?
Yes.
Honey.
But…
-Don't forget this.
-Thanks.
-it wasn't easy.
-Won't you be cold, dressed like that?
You've been coming in
for five years already.
But if you don't tell me anything,
I can't help you.
I'm sorry.
I just need some sleeping pills.
Then why did you say
that it was an affair?
I thought the truth would
hurt you even more.
That's why I lied.
You wouldn't look any further
if you thought it was an affair.
What about that conversation
that Ji-hoon and Soo-bin
overheard that day?
It's a misunderstanding.
-A misunderstanding?
-I tried my best to forget about it
for the past five years.
But…
I still couldn't set foot into his study.
Just seeing the door ajar
suffocated me.
But that afternoon…
-Yeo-jin.
-Yes?
Have you seen any envelopes in my study?
I don't know. I never go in there.
You don't?
I thought you cleaned the study.
How can you…
How can you even think
I could go in there?
-Why are you suddenly so upset?
-"Suddenly"?
Does this seem sudden to you?
I've never forgotten it for a moment.
Right. I'm sorry.
But I apologized for that.
I made a mistake.
Don't call it a mistake.
It wasn't a mistake.
Will you keep it down?
Why?
Are you afraid that Hye-joo will find out?
Fine.
It may have been a mistake to you.
But I've been confused
and tormented ever since.
I can barely look Hye-joo in the eye.
Everything will be fine if you keep quiet.
-So--
-That's enough.
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
When he mentioned the study
so nonchalantly,
I couldn't hold back my anger.
And Ji-hoon must've gotten the wrong idea.
I still couldn't set foot into his study.
Just seeing the door ajar
suffocated me.
The study?
I don't want to misplace anything
in there by mistake.
I see.
Sure, I'll clean it.
Thanks.
Yeo-jin.
What's wrong?
Can you close the door?
Right.
Okay.
There's a cold breeze coming in, right?
Gosh.
Come in.
Let's talk inside. Yoon-seo is upstairs.
I thought
you were just coming down with the flu.
I thought you'd feel better…
after a good night's sleep.
But
you've been in pain…
all this time.
And I had no idea.
I'm sorry, Yeo-jin.
Yeo-jin.
I'm so sorry, Yeo-jin.
I'm sorry.
I'm…
I had no idea. I'm sorry, Yeo-jin.
I'm so sorry.
You are probably the one person
in the National Assembly
who cares the most about
the less privileged.
As I've been following
your activities over the years,
I wasn't surprised at all
to find out that you're the one
who proposed Namgoong Sol's Law.
Thank you.
Was her name Chae-eun?
The girl who was murdered by her father.
I covered your story
when you filed that appeal
to punish filicide as an aggravated crime.
I see.
You proposed the same bill
during your last term as well, right?
Although it didn't go through.
He proposed it this term too.
It's pending at the committee.
I see.
I knew it.
Chae-eun's mother and the other victims
must feel reassured to have you.
Thank you.
I don't think
I can report him.
Why not?
Let's go to the police together.
It's already been five years.
There's no evidence.
I'm sure we can find a way.
I know how hard it is to be called a liar.
I've seen it.
I was right by your side.
I…
just don't want to do that.
Plus…
he did help me with Chae-eun's case.
I'll just
keep living like I have so far.
Assemblyman Nam stated
that he had evidence
of Assemblyman Kang providing
his in-laws with sensitive information
about the MOLIT's land development plans.
He plans to report it to the police.
As soon as Lee,
Kang's sister-in-law, purchased the land,
-the development plans were announced,
-Seung-hee.
-causing the price to skyrocket.
-Seung-hee. Where did she go?
Seung-hee!
Seung-hee.
I heard everything about your husband.
Do another interview.
Say that you lied yesterday
and that you framed Seung-ho.
If you don't,
I'll go public with
what your husband did to that woman.
Hold on.
The owner of this place
is related to that case.
-No way. Are you serious?
-Yes.
The kid who killed himself
after molesting that assemblyman's wife
when she was young?
That was the owner's son.
And that man, Nam Joong-do,
is the victim's husband.
He seems determined to take revenge.
It was a mistake.
It was an accident.
It was one mistake.
How could you call that a mistake?
You can't do something
like that by mistake.
Wake up! You didn't just have an affair.
How?
I mean…
Why did you do it?
That day, I--
No.
Don't say anything.
I don't want to hear your excuses
and I have no reason to.
Just stop talking.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
How could you do something so heinous…
and preach Namgoong Sol's Law?
Did you never feel guilty about it?
Did you completely erase the incident
from your memory?
No.
That was the reason
I was so obsessed with the bill.
It was the guilt driving me at first,
but after hearing your story,
I became determined to push it.
I thought passing this law
would be my atonement.
I've truly repented
and tried my best to live righteously.
You know how I lived
for the past few years.
Don't ever say that you lived righteously.
You betrayed Yeo-jin, me,
and the trust of all the people
who voted for you.
And you're sitting there
telling me you lived righteously?
Turn yourself in.
If you don't, I'll disclose everything.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
What did you say?
Namgoong Sol's Law is gaining support.
It might really get passed.
I'm the one who proposed it.
If I turn myself in right now,
that'll be the end of the law--
Enough already!
I'm so sick and tired
of hearing about that!
What about Yoon-seo?
What will happen to her if this gets out?
Will she be able to go to school?
Will you be okay with that?
How dare you even say her name?
Do you know what I asked Soo-bin
when she first came to our house
and said she was carrying Ji-hoon's baby?
By any chance,
did Ji-hoon force you in any way
without your consent?
Did he force himself on me?
No, it wasn't like that.
I felt terrible afterward.
I'm his mom,
and I had suspected him
of doing such a thing.
But I've never doubted you.
Because never in my wildest dreams
did I think you'd do something like this.
That's how much I trusted you.
Do you know why Ji-hoon made the mistake
of believing you were having an affair?
It's because
he also trusted you.
He never imagined
that you would do something like this!
That's why he thought
it was just an affair!
SONMAT NOODLES
The owner of this restaurant
tried to kill herself? Why?
I don't know.
But there were ambulances
and everything here last night.
-Excuse me.
-Goodness.
-Gosh, you scared me.
-The owner lady…
Yes?
Did she really try to kill herself?
Yes, but I don't know
what happened
after she was taken to the hospital.
Why?
Do you know which hospital?
Probably Jeongsun Medical Center.
It's the closest hospital.
Wait, so who are you?
CLEAN, HONEST, AND COMPETENT WORKER
NAM JOONG-DO
You knew?
-Yes, sir.
-When did you find out?
Never mind that.
How much did you know?
Everything, sir.
At first, I thought you were
just having an affair.
You're cheating on Mom with Aunt Yeo-jin!
I'm going to tell Mom.
That's not true!
Why won't you let your mom live in peace?
Plus, do you really think
she'd believe you?
Back then, I thought it would be fine
as long as I kept my mouth shut.
Because Ji-hoon was
no longer around to disclose it.
But that was a miscalculation on my part.
I'll be going now.
Assemblyman Nam…
sexually assaulted me.
Sorry?
What did you just say?
Five years ago,
I was raped…
by Assemblyman Nam Joong-do.
But if I knew anything about you,
it was that you never make
the same mistake twice.
Don't…
do anything.
If people find out about this,
you won't be able
to handle the consequences.
The media will dig into it persistently,
and it'll be the talk of the town.
But most of all,
Ms. Kim will be utterly shocked.
In the end, you'll be left alone.
I'm saying this for your own good.
I advise you…
to forget about this.
I thought everything would be fine
if I quietly handled it myself.
I believed it would be better
if you stayed in politics.
For me…
and for this world.
After what happened,
I worked like a dog…
to make this world a better place.
I believed that was my way of atonement.
Do you think Ms. Kim will
stay quiet about this?
I'll just have to believe that she will.
No.
Please don't get up.
Hello.
This is the first time we meet formally.
So what brings you here at this hour?
Five years ago,
my husband, Assemblyman Nam,
sexually assaulted a woman.
Yes.
Okay.
Ms. Kim is speaking in private
with Chairwoman Woo at the moment.
I would go to the police,
but I'm worried that
it won't be properly investigated,
or that I'll end up
getting even more hurt.
Most importantly, the victim is scared.
She's afraid of the consequences
of this going public.
I don't know what to do.
That's why I'm here.
After all, you're the one who chose him.
If I were you…
I'd keep quiet about it.
I didn't think
Namgoong Sol's Law would pass
due to many juridical issues.
But with such enthusiastic
support from the public,
even if it doesn't pass,
I believe it could bring about
some meaningful changes.
However,
if people find out
that the very person who proposed the bill
is guilty of sexual assault,
isn't it obvious
what would become of the bill?
Ms. Kim.
Didn't you want the bill to pass as well?
He tells me
that he has repented
and worked hard for the good of the world.
And he asks me to put the bill first.
But I'm very confused.
To think that his efforts
really have been genuine and sincere,
it feels wrong and disgusting.
But to think that he's been
putting on an act all along…
I'd be so disheartened and miserable.
I'm so lost.
At this point,
I'm starting to doubt
whether it even matters
if his intention
for pushing this bill is sincere.
You see,
I have no intention
of defending his crime.
However,
let me tell you this
as someone who's in politics
for the people and the society.
If Assemblyman Nam remains in politics,
the world will change for the better
with Namgoong Sol's law and more.
It will probably
put this world closer
to your image of an ideal world.
But some may believe
that we must sacrifice
Namgoong Sol's Law among others
and shed light on
what Assemblyman Nam has done
for this world to become a better place.
So…
as for which option will
change this world for the better,
it's up to you to decide.
So please,
Yeo-jin.
Please keep quiet about this.
I'll
retire from politics as soon
as the bill passes.
So please.
I beg of you.
Your silence will
change the world for the better.
I promise.
So please help me.
I beg of you.
Piece of shit.
1 ITEM SELECTED
DELETE VIDEO
It's not synced to a cloud drive.
So that's it.
It doesn't matter.
I heard everything.
Who will believe you
when you have no proof?
I guess we'll find out
whether they'll believe me or not.
Here.
This is your last warning.
Excuse me.
Aren't you Assemblyman Nam's wife?
Ms. Hyeon.
I heard everything.
About what Mr. Nam did to you.
Call the police right now.
Why won't you answer me?
If you don't do it, I will.
Soo-bin.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't do this to her.
She won't take it to the police.
You can't force her to do that.
I'm not.
I'm telling her to reveal the truth.
Soo-bin.
No one's suffering more than her.
I was devastated when my incident
became public against my will
and I still am.
So please.
Don't do this to her.
Also,
don't tell anyone about this.
Please.
When you appeared on the news yesterday,
you lied that Ji-hoon was a sex offender.
Because of you,
people are now spreading rumors
saying he was a serial sex offender.
You turned him into a sex offender.
Why are you turning a blind eye
to the real sex offender?
If this comes to light,
that'll be the end of Namgoong Sol's Law.
I went through something similar
when I was young.
I don't feel bad that he's dead.
I actually think he deserved it.
However,
people criticized me
for telling a lie
and causing a person to die.
I hope
that bill will be passed
so that there won't be any more victims
like us.
Countless people are desperately waiting
for Namgoong Sol's Law,
and I don't want
there to be any more victims.
So…
I believe keeping this a secret
will ultimately be
the better decision for this world.
You know what it's like
to be falsely branded as a liar
and to suffer because of it.
And now…
you say you want to reveal the truth,
but you're turning a blind eye
to another truth.
Are you really okay with that?
Yoon-seo.
Yes?
I'm…
I AM KIM HYE-JOO,
THE WIFE OF ASSEMBLYMAN NAM JOONG-DO…
I am Kim Hye-joo.
My son…
did not sexually assault anyone.
I…
NAM'S WIFE KIM HYE-JOO'S PRESS CONFERENCE
lied despite knowing the truth.
And…
my husband…
sexually assaulted a woman five years ago.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim