=Royal Upstart 2=
(Based on "Zhenguan Foolish Son-in-Law")
=Episode 26=
(The Fall of Cui Xiongkai and Wang Chen)
Who was sent to
secretly protect Wei Hao?
Two teams of Iron Guards
were dispatched.
Good.
You could also choose to kill me.
But I have already
prepared several copies of those things.
If anything happens to me,
those things will immediately appear
on His Majesty's desk.
At that time, His Majesty
will know exactly what to do.
Your influence is far too great.
Every time trouble arises,
the great clans have
people in court to back you up.
They impeach me whenever they please.
I need to have my own influence as well.
(Since I cannot bring out)
(printing technology openly,)
(I will nurture talent
for this world instead.)
(Perhaps)
(future generations
will think of movable type.)
(By then, it will have
nothing to do with me.)
About this first condition,
ten thousand guan per year
is too much.
Look,
we are seven different clans here.
That would be
70,000 guan a year for you.
Can't you just...
I've realized you all
are terrible at arithmetic.
With my movable type,
if I don't earn
10,000 guan a month, I lose.
That's 120,000 guan a year.
And that is the bare minimum.
We could
earn 300,000 guan a year.
The people of the Great Yong,
including your great clans,
who wouldn't want to collect more books?
Besides, are the great clans
really that poor?
Ten thousand guan.
It's pocket change.
It's hardly any money at all.
This...
You brat.
Our clan only makes
20,000 guan a year in revenue,
and you want to take half of it?
Why...
Why don't you just be the clan leader?
I won't do it.
You can't just become
a clan leader whenever you want.
Training 500 people is too many.
And every year, too?
How about this?
One hundred people every year.
Is that okay?
One hundred people?
Don't even think about it.
If I only have a hundred a year,
how many of them can
actually enter the court as officials?
They wouldn't even
have a chance to serve
before being bullied
to death by you lot.
You have those things in your hands,
so who will dare bully you now?
Exactly.
Who knows what will happen later?
Wei Hao,
rest assured.
From now on, we from the great clans
will avoid you whenever we see you.
Yes, yes.
Exactly.
But
five hundred people are just too many.
What about
two hundred?
No way.
Three hundred people?
That's the final number.
Three hundred?
Three hundred people,
and each clan will make
a one-time payment
of 10,000 guan.
Then,
can you sell the glazeware to us?
If you make
a one-time payment of 20,000 guan,
I will let you sell it
in your clans' territories.
The glazeware...
Then...
Father.
It's a deal.
It's a deal, right?
Yes.
Good.
Twenty thousand it is.
On the 22nd,
deliver it to my engagement banquet.
It's just
that this deadline is a bit too tight.
We...
We don't have that much ready cash.
That's your own problem.
Figure it out yourselves.
You can't expect me
to keep backing down, right?
Fine.
We'll find a way.
Does that mean
the deal is done?
Let's eat.
Give it a try.
I told you that we'd talk after eating.
But you didn't listen.
See? You've lost your appetite.
(Wei Hao)
(is a talent,)
(so we must win him over.)
Wei Hao,
you are a son
of the great clans, after all.
Don't lean too much
toward His Majesty's side.
Keep us in your heart as well.
Indeed.
I'm done eating.
I
don't care about your nonsense,
so don't worry about mine either.
Let's not interfere with each other.
If you provoke me again,
don't say I didn't warn you.
We won't.
I
am not a patient man.
Just remember to come
to the engagement banquet.
Don't forget.
I'm off.
Don't let it go to waste.
Finish it up!
(Ganlu Palace)
Your Majesty,
we couldn't find out anything.
We saw Wei Hao go in with a chest
and come out with the same chest.
He looked very relaxed.
Couldn't hear a thing?
That brat even cleared out all
the surrounding private rooms?
That brat
is definitely hiding something from me.
Could it be that he really has
a trump card in his hand?
I have an idea.
From among our great clans,
we should choose
a woman to give to Wei Hao.
I wonder if that would work.
You mean...
To win Wei Hao over, of course.
We can't let him side
entirely with His Majesty.
He must lean toward our side.
Gentlemen,
don't even think about it.
Wei Hao is currently obsessed
and completely infatuated
with the Eldest Princess.
If you try to win him
over by sending women,
it
won't just fail,
but it'll also ruin everything.
Right now,
the most important thing
is to keep him steady.
Don't let him reveal
whatever is inside that chest.
Don't worry
about anything else.
It's not necessary.
What a blunder.
It's all because of these fools.
Knowing Wei Hao had such abilities,
you still went and provoked him.
Who could have known the fool
was capable of this?
Indeed. How could a human
even invent those things?
You ignorant fools.
With what capability
did you dare provoke Wei Hao?
Father...
Clan Leader,
I didn't realize
it would lead to such a disaster.
A mistake is a mistake.
Stop looking for excuses!
In the centuries
of the great clans' history,
when have we ever been so humiliated?
Wei Hao is a man of immense talent.
The great clans should have
approached him actively.
But look at you lot,
you've blocked our path.
If we don't punish you severely,
how can we show
our sincerity to Wei Hao?
Without severe punishment,
how can I face all our clansmen?
Clan Leader,
I am willing to make amends.
I'll give up all my family property
to cover the deficit.
And what about the 300 scholars
to be trained each year?
I have decided.
Cui Xiongkai,
from this moment on,
you are no longer the Cui clan's
representative in the capital.
Hand over your
official seal immediately.
Also, according to clan rules,
your clan membership is revoked.
You may never enter
the Cui clan ancestral hall again.
Clan Leader!
Father,
I can't survive without the clan.
I really know I was wrong!
And you!
Get out of the Wang residence right now.
From now on,
regarding the Wang clan's assets,
don't you dare touch a single fen!
Father.
Father,
I really know I was wrong.
Please put in a good word
for me with Wei Hao.
I'll never provoke him ever again.
Father!
Clan Leader,
from now on,
we will treat Wei Hao with respect.
We will follow his every lead.
Please don't kick me
out of the Wang clan.
Clan Leader Wei,
please plead with Wei Hao for me.
I'll never provoke him again.
I told you all a long time ago,
but did you listen?
Back then,
you certainly didn't show
any respect to me.
If you had known this day would come,
why act so arrogantly
in the first place?
Back then, it was...
Enough talk.
The clan rules must be obeyed.
No one can change
today's punishment.
Someone,
come drag these two away.
Send them out of
the capital immediately.
Clan Leader,
don't drive me away.
I can't leave the Wang clan.
- Clan Leader.
- Father.
- No.
- Clan Leader.
- Father.
Clan Leader.
Clan Leader!
Hao,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
Aunt,
are you ready for
the banquet on the 22nd?
The renovations on the new
Marquis Mansion are finishing up,
so I have to go supervise.
I still need to send out invitations.
Right,
we still have to hold
the banquet on the 22nd.
Are we still doing it?
Of course.
I've already made
arrangements with my parents-in-law.
Prepare well.
We might need more tables.
Those great clan
leaders will be coming too.
What?
The clan leaders are all coming?
You've settled it?
Of course.
Is there anything
I can't handle once I step in?
How did you settle it?
You wouldn't
understand even if I told you.
Well, you know,
confidentiality is key.
If word gets leaked out,
those clan leaders might feel offended,
and that would be troublesome.
Just focus on the preparations.
By the way,
don't tell anyone yet
about my parents-in-law coming.
You have to keep
an eye on the kitchen yourself.
Don't let any untrustworthy people in.
Don't worry.
I have plenty of people I can trust,
and they are
completely loyal to our family.
Good.
Today,
were any new petitions
for impeachment delivered?
Your Majesty,
there were no new ones.
It seems
the fool must have
settled the negotiations.
Well?
Is the brat here yet?
The Marquis has entered the palace,
but
he went to see Her Highness.
What's with this brat?
Instead of reporting to me,
he goes to see the girl?
Cheng Chuchi.
I am here, Your Majesty.
Go tell the brat to come
to Ganlu Palace now.
This brat...
It's like I don't even
exist to him anymore.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Fool!
Girl.
How did it go?
What did they say?
Did they do anything to you?
Girl,
didn't you sleep well?
Your eyes are all bloodshot.
I just couldn't sleep.
Tell me.
How did the talks go?
You're just worrying for nothing.
I told you it was fine,
but you still didn't believe me.
Don't worry.
It's all settled.
Right,
remember to come on the 22nd.
I'm hosting an engagement banquet.
I can't pull it off without you.
Really?
It's really all settled?
♪Colors and darkness♪
You fool.
I knew you could do it.
I had to.
Anyway,
I have to go to the lords' houses later
to deliver the invitations.
The 22nd is coming up fast,
and I haven't even paid them a visit.
You should go.
Go quickly while you have time.
♪See me differently.
Who dares to challenge me?♪
♪The world mistakes me♪
♪For an ignorant and stubborn fool♪
♪As the storm approaches♪
♪I just shrug and watch with a smile♪
Well, Marquis Wei...
Come on.
Cheng Chuchi...
His Majesty wants to see you.
I'm busy.
I have to go deliver invitations later.
Does my father-in-law have a problem?
That, I wouldn't know.
You'd better just go.
Go...
Go ahead.
Since Father is looking for you,
it must be something important.
My father-in-law is really something,
always making trouble for people.
♪We are free and happy♪
♪Everyone says I'm a big silly fool♪
♪When things happen,
I only know how to count on my fingers♪
♪They shake their heads
and say I'm pitiful♪
♪Sigh and walk away♪
♪Little do they know,
I am sharp and bright♪
♪With a heart like a mirror,
I understand the world's♪
♪Colors and darkness♪
♪But I keep my edge hidden♪
♪The day I become famous
is just around the corner♪
♪In the hotpot restaurant,
skewers boil in the broth♪
♪People come and go,
with few worries or troubles♪
♪The clacking of the abacus rings out♪
♪See me differently.
Who dares to challenge me?♪
♪The world mistakes me♪
♪For an ignorant and stubborn fool♪
♪As the storm approaches♪
♪I just shrug and watch with a smile♪
♪This foolish image is convenient♪
♪I use it as a protective shield♪
♪Navigating with ease, I attract♪
♪A lucky star to accompany me♪
♪In a peaceful golden age♪
♪I hold my lady's hand
to watch the world♪
♪Pouring youth and fireworks♪
♪Into a precious glazed cup♪
♪Having experienced life's changes♪
♪And tasted its highs and lows♪
♪My wish has finally come true♪
♪To stay by your side♪
♪In this fleeting world♪
♪We are free and happy♪
♪From a nobody♪
♪To someone now famous♪
♪Ordinary people laugh at me♪
♪But I laugh at how
they cannot see through it all♪
♪Let others plot and scheme♪
♪I will keep my heart unchanged♪
♪In this vast world♪
♪I find my own leisurely freedom♪
♪The world is bustling,
and things constantly change♪
♪Everything ends eventually♪
♪All that remains before my eyes♪
♪Is this street wandering,
still tinged with pity♪
♪No matter how time flies♪
♪Even if the falling snow♪
♪Dyes the hair at our temples white♪
♪All I want now♪
♪Is to pray for
my lady's peace and safety♪
♪Year after year♪