=Royal Upstart 2=
(Based on "Zhenguan Foolish Son-in-Law")
=Episode 2=
(Subduing Princess, Startling Aunt)
(Juxian Restaurant)
I wonder which run-down
(Xiu, Lin Luo's personal maid)
restaurant the Young Master bought.
How are we supposed to find it?
That guy knows nothing about business.
Just look for the place
with the worst business.
We'll surely find him.
No need to look at this one.
Let's split up.
Go.
How come it's been this long,
and I'm still not up?
That's nothing.
I've been waiting for two hours.
(Could it be that all these people)
(are here to challenge Wei the Fool?)
Please don't push, everyone.
Take a number first.
One at a time.
The line starts back there, ma'am.
We're looking for someone.
Don't crowd! One by one!
(Since when did Great Yong
have such a popular restaurant?)
How did this guy come up with this?
Minister Duan?
And you are...
It's me.
Didn't you come here
to challenge Wei Hao in arithmetic?
Why are you eating?
Also,
what is all of this about?
Your Highness,
after I lost to Wei Hao last time,
the more I thought about it,
the angrier I got.
So I brought my colleagues
to challenge him.
As a result,
we've been losing
for three consecutive days.
Three...
Fortunately, he lets those of us who lost
eat hotpot for free.
He also gave us a so-called
three-day VIP membership.
It's amazing.
Once you start, you can't stop.
I come to eat every day.
Anything else
tastes like sawdust now.
I feel
like I've been set up.
You've already lost for three days?
I am ashamed.
Even my secret savings
are all gone.
Next.
Let me try one more time.
I don't believe I can't win it back.
It's you again?
Are you going to give me
another child's problem?
This is a problem
I spent all night thinking of.
You've already lost
ten guan to me, you know?
You solved it just like that?
This...
You're now a VIP.
Go to a private room.
Private room?
Dear,
you're here.
You recognized me so easily?
Insolent.
Call me that again, and I'll...
Don't be angry.
Anger causes wrinkles.
It's not pretty.
(Why should I argue with a fool?)
Did you win all of this?
One guan per problem.
Those people you found are no good.
They're ill-tempered
and stubborn.
They keep coming back after losing.
I've made almost a thousand
guan these past few days.
I'm exhausted.
A thousand guan?
So, how about it?
We had a deal.
If you can't beat me, you'll marry me.
If you say that again,
I'll seal your mouth shut.
Have you eaten yet?
No.
Do you like hotpot?
Eat slowly.
You're a princess, after all.
Take your time.
From now on,
this private room
will be reserved just for you.
Wei the Fool,
how dare you use me!
Don't think I don't know
what you're up to.
You provoked
the civil and military officials
to compete in arithmetic with you here
just to hype up
Juxian Restaurant, right?
Since that's the case,
you must give me an explanation.
What explanation?
One thousand guan.
I'm buying half of
your shares in Juxian Restaurant.
Why do you want my restaurant so badly?
Can't I just be short on money?
You're a princess.
How could you be short on money?
You...
You're an unloved princess.
(This fool is indeed easy to deceive.)
My mother and I...
We
have been marginalized
since I was a child.
We couldn't even scrape together
enough money for my brother's wedding.
My mother's health is also poor.
What a miserable princess.
This
is the down payment.
Go and prepare the contract.
Wait.
What is this?
You're using this as a down payment?
What do you mean by "what is this"?
This is a precious gemstone
brought as tribute from abroad.
Even the smallest one is worth 15 guan.
I don't blame you
for not knowing their value.
Isn't this just glass?
Can you have some dignity?
You've been swindled by glass,
and you call them gemstones?
They're just picked up from a volcano.
They aren't worth much.
If you want them, I'll give you a few
carts in a couple of days.
I won't waste any more words
on someone so ignorant.
I...
I'm ignorant?
You...
Wait.
Are you saying
that even the smallest piece of glass
is worth 15 guan?
Of course.
(If I just make some glass,)
(won't I make a fortune?)
How about this?
You give me one thousand guan,
and we'll partner up.
You provide the venue
and have the Ministry of Works
build me some machines.
Stuff like this?
We can have as much as we want.
Who brags like you do?
If you don't want to sell
your restaurant, just say so.
Why make up nonsense to deceive me?
I'm not so bored that I'd lie to you.
Believe it or not.
I'll earn
the money myself.
Fine.
One thousand guan it is.
But let's be clear.
If this stuff doesn't make money,
half the shares of Juxian Restaurant
will belong to me.
Eat.
This restaurant's business is too good.
We've been waiting for over an hour.
Look, Young Madam.
Done?
It's on the house.
As I said before,
it's free as long as you come to eat.
It's our own family's restaurant.
You little rascal.
No, wait, Aunt.
I had to wait forever
for a meal, didn't I?
Aunt, it hurts.
It hurts, let go.
It's falling off.
If it falls off,
I won't be able to get a wife.
Wait...
How can you not know
your own family's restaurant?
You insisted on waiting in line,
and yet you blame me?
Couldn't you just come straight in?
How...
How was I supposed to know
this restaurant belongs to us?
You're the head of the house,
yet you don't even know
if this place is ours.
And you think you're in the right?
You even...
You even pulled my ear.
Young Madam,
you're here.
Go, go.
Clear out a private room
upstairs for Young Madam.
Yes, sir.
Young Madam, please this way.
You've really made something
of yourself.
You're quite capable now.
Please.
(How could a place this booming)
(be run by this fool?)
Mother,
these gemstones
are products of nature.
Can Wei the Fool really create them?
(Empress of the Great Yong Dynasty)
Running a restaurant is actually hard.
Most aren't profitable.
Many who open restaurants in the capital
struggle to find their footing.
But not only did Wei Hao
open one,
but it's also very successful.
So, Mother, you mean...
If those gemstones he mentioned
can be manufactured,
we should give it a try.
The deficit in the imperial treasury
is estimated to reach
40,000 guan this year.
Great Yong was just established,
and the national treasury is empty.
Your father is also facing
many difficulties.
Besides,
if your workshop doesn't succeed,
Wei Hao has to give you
half the shares of Juxian Restaurant.
We won't suffer any loss.
(Wei Mansion)
Aunt,
why did you come in?
To scrub your back.
Hao,
based on Juxian Restaurant's
current revenue,
can we return to
the Wei ancestral home soon?
Is there no distinction
between men and women?
I've bathed you since you were little.
Lean forward a bit.
I'll help you with the bath beans.
Lean forward?
Perhaps
we could even buy a new mansion.
That tickles, it tickles.
It tickles.
How about I do it myself?
You never wash properly on your own.
I always have to re-wash you anyway.
Am I really that silly?
(Poor Hao.)
(You don't even
know how foolish you are.)
You can stand up now.
No...
I'll do the bottom part myself.
You
have grown up.
That scared me.
What's this?
A massage?
Lie down.
Well, I do like massages.
You've been exhausted lately, right?
Let me help you relax.
Ouch.
Ouch...
Why are you walking on my back?
Is it because I've gained weight lately?
Then, I'll use more strength.
This is quite comfortable.
(She might not be my biological aunt,)
(but she treats a fool like me
with such genuine kindness.)
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
(Ganlu Palace)
Envoy, what is the meaning of this?
We request that Your Majesty,
the Emperor of the Great Yong,
provide 60 million kg worth of grain.
Our empire does not
have that much grain.
The Northwest
suffered a drought this year.
(The Emperor of the Great Yong)
Great Yong is also facing a grain shortage.
We don't have that much grain
to give to your Beicang.
(Beicang Envoy)
However,
you could certainly
buy it from the common people.
If there is nothing else,
you may all withdraw.
The Court of Diplomatic Affairs
will see to you.
Please wait, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
I am Duo Xiang,
a Hu merchant traveling
between the grasslands and the West.
Entrusted by Beicang,
I am here to coordinate trade.
(Duo Xiang, Hu Merchant)
While we lack the wealth of Great Yong,
we
have gemstones.
I ask Your Majesty
to allow us to use
the money from these gemstones
to purchase grain.
Such beautiful gemstones.
This time,
we have brought
two carts full of these gems.
Two carts of gemstones?
That many?
(Zhangsun Ying, Left Chancellor of the Great Yong)
They must be worth a fortune.
(Cheng Sanfu, Duke of the Great Yong)
Look, it is indeed as said.
Isn't this just glass?
Can you have some dignity?
You're being fooled by glass.
"Gemstones", really?
Weren't these just
picked up from a volcano?
They're dirt cheap.
If you want them,
I'll give you a few
carts in a couple of days.
Your Majesty,
these gemstones are dazzling tokens
offered to all living beings
after Han'er Volcano spews lava.
They are a blessing from heaven.
In our grasslands,
each one is worth 15 guan.
Now, we are willing to sell
them to Your Majesty
for only ten guan each.
We have a total of
ten thousand such gems.
We wish to use the hundred thousand guan
to purchase grain in Great Yong.
We wonder what Your Majesty thinks?
(Ten guan)
(for such fine gemstones)
(is really not expensive.)
(If what Wei the Fool says is true,)
(the Great Yong)
(will be giving up hundreds
of thousands of kg of grain)
(in exchange for these cheap stones.)
(No.)
What gemstones?
They are nothing but cheap goods.
You
must be the Princess.
As expected of
the Eldest Princess of Great Yong.
Your beauty is as delicate and fragile
as the Central Plains peony.
A peony may be delicate,
but it has character.
Unlike some common items
that are insistently claimed
to be rare treasures.
Your Highness,
please do not insult
our precious and noble gemstones.
Ning'an,
what do you mean by that?
Father, please see clearly.
In our vast and
resource-rich Great Yong,
these things can be found anywhere.
I can produce these items
as many as I want.
Then, we shall
wait for the Your Highness's gemstones.
♪Everyone says I'm a big silly fool♪
♪When things happen,
I only know how to count on my fingers♪
♪They shake their heads
and say I'm pitiful♪
♪Sigh and walk away♪
♪Little do they know,
I am sharp and bright♪
♪With a heart like a mirror,
I understand the world's♪
♪Colors and darkness♪
♪But I keep my edge hidden♪
♪The day I become famous
is just around the corner♪
♪In the hotpot restaurant,
skewers boil in the broth♪
♪People come and go,
with few worries or troubles♪
♪The clacking of the abacus rings out♪
♪See me differently.
Who dares to challenge me?♪
♪The world mistakes me♪
♪For an ignorant and stubborn fool♪
♪As the storm approaches♪
♪I just shrug and watch with a smile♪
♪This foolish image is convenient♪
♪I use it as a protective shield♪
♪Navigating with ease, I attract♪
♪A lucky star to accompany me♪
♪In a peaceful golden age♪
♪I hold my lady's hand
to watch the world♪
♪Pouring youth and fireworks♪
♪Into a precious glazed cup♪
♪Having experienced life's changes♪
♪And tasted its highs and lows♪
♪My wish has finally come true♪
♪To stay by your side♪
♪In this fleeting world♪
♪We are free and happy♪
♪From a nobody♪
♪To someone now famous♪
♪Ordinary people laugh at me♪
♪But I laugh at how they
cannot see through it all♪
♪Let others plot and scheme♪
♪I will keep my heart unchanged♪
♪In this vast world♪
♪I find my own leisurely freedom♪
♪The world is bustling,
and things constantly change♪
♪Everything ends eventually♪
♪All that remains before my eyes♪
♪Is this street wandering,
still tinged with pity♪
♪No matter how time flies♪
♪Even if the falling snow♪
♪Dyes the hair at our temples white♪
♪All I want now♪
♪Is to pray for
my lady's peace and safety♪
♪Year after year♪