=Royal Upstart 2=
(Based on "Zhenguan Foolish Son-in-Law")
=Episode 8=
(Imperial Edict Arrives)
I said I'm going
to be granted a count title.
Aunt, what are you doing?
You've been acting strange
ever since you came out of prison.
Aunt,
I'm not acting strange.
think about it.
Why would the Princess let me out?
So the Princess saw you were unwell
and let you out because of that.
Mister Wang,
quick, call a physician.
No need.
No,
before, even though you got into fights,
even though you were foolish,
you weren't out of your mind.
But now you've lost your senses.
What hope does this family have left?
What's the use of all that money then?
Aunt, calm down.
I'm really fine.
What will it take for you to believe me?
Alright.
I'll tell the truth.
I got into a fight.
They're coming
first thing tomorrow morning.
Really.
I beat up an official's son.
Injured him.
They know who I am,
so they'll be here early tomorrow.
Is that enough?
You brat!
Now you even dare lie to me?
Let's see if I don't
beat you to death today.
It wasn't that serious.
You beat an official's son
and still say it wasn't serious?
No,
today I must beat you.
Young Madam,
I said before,
someone like him will never change.
Just as expected,
he's still the same as before,
never giving anyone peace of mind.
Young Madam, you should have
taught him a proper lesson earlier.
He beat an official's son.
When their family comes tomorrow,
and they see he
doesn't even have a scratch,
they'll be even more furious.
But if he were injured as well,
perhaps the matter could be eased.
Today the Imperial Guards delivered
eight thousand guan.
I'm quite startled at first.
This is the money earned in a single day
by Wei the Fool's glaze workshop.
In a single day?
Your Majesty,
this is a good thing.
I didn't expect Wei the Fool
to have such ability.
Your Majesty should
reward Wei Hao generously.
I intend to grant him a count title.
What do you think?
Isn't a count title a bit too light?
He didn't just produce
beautiful glazed gemstones.
More importantly,
he has helped the royal family greatly.
Originally,
I could have granted
him a marquis title.
But that mouth of his,
when he speaks,
he can infuriate people to death.
Granting him a count title
is already me holding back.
Otherwise, I wouldn't even want
to grant him anything.
What does this mean?
This man,
he speaks without thinking,
and can't keep his hands to himself.
Today he even got into
a fight with Commander Cheng.
So foolish.
Exactly.
Ning'an,
from now on,
see him less.
This boy is full of schemes,
and he even dares set his sights on you.
What?
He's even set his sights on you?
What's going on here?
Mother,
that's just Wei the Fool
talking nonsense.
I don't think so.
I think this boy is ready to go all out.
Father,
I'm hungry.
Please go dine with Mother.
Alright.
Go on. Hurry.
Young Master,
Young Master.
This...
You must be freezing.
Come.
I told you not to fight,
told you not to fight,
but you wouldn't listen.
You just had to fight.
Look.
Aunt has gone mad.
I told her the truth,
and she says I'm mad.
I said I got into a fight,
and she still wants to beat me.
What am I supposed to do?
Young Master,
just like when you were little,
then you must have gotten into a fight.
Forget it.
Young Madam must be asleep by now.
You should rest early too.
You don't believe me either,
do you?
(Who doesn't know
you're a fool, Young Master?)
(You said you'd be granted a title.)
(Who would believe that?)
I believe.
Young Master,
rest early.
if you can't sleep,
then
I can warm you.
You should go.
I want some quiet alone.
Then rest early.
(Hao.)
(You're actually quite handsome.)
(If people didn't know you're a fool,)
(they'd probably think)
(you're quite
the refined young gentleman.)
You're the only family I have.
If you really
get taken away by officials,
what will I do?
Hao,
don't blame me for being harsh today.
If I hit him while he's asleep,
it must hurt a lot, right?
What if he gets startled?
Stop it.
Are you asking for a beating?
Who dares disturb my sleep?
Who do you think you are?
Aunt?
You beat an official's son,
and you're still
acting like some big shot?
Father, Mother, save me!
You still dare call for your parents?
Today I'll discipline you
on their behalf.
Wait,
don't hit me!
Are you going to keep fighting?
Say one more word!
Aunt, don't lose your senses!
Stop hitting me!
Help!
Are you done yet?
(Wei Mansion)
I've decided.
I'm splitting the household.
I...
I'll go buy a house later.
I'm moving out.
What kind of aunt are you?
Beating me is one thing,
but hitting me while I'm asleep?
Don't touch me.
What kind of aunt does that?
Wasn't I doing it for your own good?
As long as you don't end up
in the Ministry of Justice Prison again.
You beat an official's son.
When his family comes
do you think they'll spare you?
But if they see you like this,
they might take pity on you.
We'll just compensate them
with some money.
Right?
I...
I didn't fight.
No.
They're here!
Young Madam,
they've arrived.
Looks like quite a large group,
seems like people from the palace.
From the palace?
Let's go.
Slow down, Young Madam.
Mister Wang!
Do something!
(Heavens.)
(This fool hit someone from the palace.)
(Then...)
(Is there any hope left?)
Is this Wei Hao's residence?
Yes...
Eunuch, please.
Where is Wei Hao?
And who are you?
I am Wei Hao's aunt.
Hao.
Quick.
Call Hao here.
Young Master.
Move aside.
Slow down.
Greetings, Eunuch.
You...
This...
I fell.
No, he didn't fall.
I beat him.
Eunuch,
this is Hao's fault.
He...
He's not right in the head.
You see, I've already
beaten him like this.
He'll surely learn his lesson.
Please be magnanimous
and spare him.
(This...)
(What are they even talking about?)
(Wei Hao hasn't offended me at all.)
Eunuch,
let's handle official business first.
Then set up the incense altar.
We should first carry out
His Majesty's instructions.
What?
Set up the incense altar?
His Majesty?
(This fool must have beaten a prince.)
You all,
go set up the altar.
Hurry.
(Qichi)
Quickly, get it done.
We can't stay in this courtyard anymore.
(This family is finished.)
(It's the end of everything.)
Eunuch, please.
The imperial edict arrives.
Wei Hao, receive the edict.
Young Master.
Step aside.
(This may be the last time I see Hao.)
(He'll probably be taken away soon.)
By the Mandate of Heaven,
the Emperor decrees,
Wei Hao, for assisting the Princess
in crafting treasures, has rendered merit.
He is hereby granted
one thousand five hundred mu of land,
a fief of seven hundred households,
with three hundred
households under direct grant,
and is conferred the title
Dynasty-Founding County Count of Pingyang.
Respect this.
Thank you, Your Majesty!
What?
Dynasty-Founding
County Count of Pingyang?
♪Everyone says I'm a big silly fool♪
♪When things happen,
I only know how to count on my fingers♪
♪They shake their heads
and say I'm pitiful♪
♪Sigh and walk away♪
♪Little do they know,
I am sharp and bright♪
♪With a heart like a mirror,
I understand the world's♪
♪Colors and darkness♪
♪But I keep my edge hidden♪
♪The day I become famous
is just around the corner♪
♪In the hotpot restaurant,
skewers boil in the broth♪
♪People come and go,
with few worries or troubles♪
♪The clacking of the abacus rings out♪
♪See me differently.
Who dares to challenge me?♪
♪The world mistakes me♪
♪For an ignorant and stubborn fool♪
♪As the storm approaches♪
♪I just shrug and watch with a smile♪
♪This foolish image is convenient♪
♪I use it as a protective shield♪
♪Navigating with ease, I attract♪
♪A lucky star to accompany me♪
♪In a peaceful golden age♪
♪I hold my lady's hand
to watch the world♪
♪Pouring youth and fireworks♪
♪Into a precious glazed cup♪
♪Having experienced life's changes♪
♪And tasted its highs and lows♪
♪My wish has finally come true♪
♪To stay by your side♪
♪In this fleeting world♪
♪We are free and happy♪
♪From a nobody♪
♪To someone now famous♪
♪Ordinary people laugh at me♪
♪But I laugh at how
they cannot see through it all♪
♪Let others plot and scheme♪
♪I will keep my heart unchanged♪
♪In this vast world♪
♪I find my own leisurely freedom♪
♪The world is bustling,
and things constantly change♪
♪Everything ends eventually♪
♪All that remains before my eyes♪
♪Is this street wandering,
still tinged with pity♪
♪No matter how time flies♪
♪Even if the falling snow♪
♪Dyes the hair at our temples white♪
♪All I want now♪
♪Is to pray for
my lady's peace and safety♪
♪Year after year♪