Subtitles and Timing provided to you by the 👔 How to Tame a CEO Team💓 @viki.com
♫  A tidal wave of tears is like falling stars
after encountering the cold  ♫
♫  Dreams in winter are too fragile  ♫
♫  The chirping cicadas wake me from my deep sleep  ♫
♫  Intoxicated under the sunset  ♫
♫  The light fades through my fingertips  ♫
♫  The ripples bloom in my heart like the tide  ♫
♫  Let time no longer be boring  ♫
♫  The evening breeze blows gently  ♫
♫  I want to have a glass of lemon soda  ♫
♫  A sip of summer intoxication  ♫
♫  The sun is shining brightly and I match you perfectly  ♫
♫  Add some ice for a slightly tipsy flavor  ♫
♫  Stop frowning  ♫
♫  Oh you are like soda, spreading the flavor of my heart  ♫
♫  My hair blows in the wind,
how many times have I fallen for you?  ♫
♫  Waiting for the wind to get drunk, drink a few glasses,
love is like water  ♫
♫  Tenderness is too fragmentary and cannot be taken back  ♫
Ms. Yuling, do you need any help?
No, thanks.
Please let me help you.
That way, I will participate in a big interview.
I heard the editor-in-chief highly recommended you for the interview.
You are the trump of our magazine.
You are the perfect person for this kind of interview.
Ms. Yuling, the sales of this interview will be outstanding.
The editor-in-chief entrusted me with such an important task, I will try my best to do it well.
You've lost the chance to interview Shi Yan.
Zheng Shuyi, why are you still working on the interview outline?
I think Shi Yan is unconventional.
I just read my outline.
Some of the questions are conservative.
I could have done better.
I want to work on it.
Are you insane?
Are you out of your mind because you lost your chance?
No matter how well you revise the outline, you can't get the chance to interview Shi Yan.
I heard that the lead editor called Mingyu Cloud Innovation and recommended her.
So, means are more important than strength.
We have a lot of interview opportunities. I can't interview Shi Yan.
But there will be Li Yan or Wang Yan.
You can use the means to get an interview.
But it takes strength to write a good interview.
Since I don't have the means, I can only continue to improve my strength.
What a pity.
You can't meet Shi Yan, and tell me if he is handsome.
Mr. Shi, the Financial Introduce's interview is at 7:00 after dinner.
Reporter Xu Yuling will come to the company to interview you.
I don't think the reporter I chose this Reporter Xu.
The Financial Introduce's lead editor highly recommended Reporter Xu.
He said that she had a lot of experience.
And her interviews have always been excellent.
I don't have to be present for a question-answer interview.
You can give them my answers.
Interviews should be enlightening conversations and reflections.
I like Reporter Zheng's interview outline.
Sorry, I didn't think about it deeply. I will have it rearranged.
Ms. Yi, are you looking for me?
Okay, see you.
You don't have to comfort me.
I can understand that. I am okay.
What do you understand?
I know you want to talk to me about Shi Yan's interview.
I can understand it.
Ms. Yuling hasmore seniority than I do.
I didn't take it so well, but there is room for improvement in my outline.
Anyway, I will take it.
I'll be more prepared next time.
I like your clothes.
Today is my boyfriend's birthday.
I dressed up for him.
Think of it another way. If I interview Shi Yan,
I won't be able to celebrate my boyfriend's birthday.
I think it's a good thing.
I see.
What's wrong, Ms. Yi?
I just received a call from Cloud Innovation,
they said Shi Yan wanted...
you to interview him.
What a pity. You have to celebrate your boyfriend's birthday.
I am afraid you will not be available.
Shi Yan wanted me to interview him?
Yes, Shi Yan wanted you to interview him tonight.
Are you free tonight?
I am free.
Are you sure?
Okay, the interview is tonight at 7:00.
Shi Yan's general assistant will communicate with you for details.
Okay, I will go and get ready.
Wait.
What about your boyfriend?
He has a birthday every year.
But there's only one chance to interview Shi Yan.
I will finish the interview as soon as I can. Maybe I will be able to celebrate his birthday before midnight.
Good for you, Zheng Shuyi.
Mr. Shi, the interview is scheduled.
What about arranging the interview in the large meeting room?
Isn’t Le’an Technology coming over for an interview this afternoon?
Department One booked the large meeting room for this afternoon, but they canceled it.
They scheduled the interviews with Lieying and Le'an in the morning.
- In the morning?
- Yes.
The system shows that. Director Feng of Department One rescheduled it.
Old Fan, drop me off.
I need to go back to the office.
Got it, Mr. Shi.
What about Ms. Qin?
You pick her up and take her to the old house.
Got it.
Good job.
You've written nine front-page articles this year.
You have set a record for our magazine.
The lead editor's record is eight front-page articles in a year.
Don't drink coffee. Don't you want to get better?
Drink this.
I wonder why Mingyu Cloud Innovation changed the interviewer.
It shows that their boss has good taste.
Are you talking about Shi Yan?
I think Shi Yan has good taste.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have made the company so strong in just a few years.
But he is a weirdo.
In Mingyu’s most difficult time, he left his family’s company alone
and insisted on going out to start a new company.
What do you think he was thinking?
A lot of people out there are saying bad things about him.
That he's the runaway successor of Mingyu.
That he's a coward.
And his girlfriend, the actress Bei Lin broke up with him immediately.
I think he's quite brave.
Although he was questioned, he still chose this path.
How much courage does it take?
It will be a pleasure to work with Lieying.
We are honored, Director Feng.
- We are partners.
- Yes.
That's right. We've been partners for years.
Right.
Mr. Shi.
Please grab me two cold cokes.
Okay.
I'm writing an interview for Lieying.
I heard that Mingyu Cloud Innovation was going to invest in Lieying.
You must know Lieying, right?
It has been strong in recent years.
Many companies want to invest in it.
There are no clear photos of Shi Yan on the internet.
After he started his business, he kept a low profile.
He has never met the press.
If I could record an exclusive video or audio for him,
it would attract many subscribers.
You are still thinking about upgrading the e-journal?
Financial information is relevant to everyone.
If we don't upgrade it, and keep publishing the same content as the paper magazine,
we can't interact with the subscribers and we will lose them.
It makes sense.
But we don't have the people or the money to upgrade it.
Even if you convince the lead editor, he will ask you questions, like,
"What about the people? What do we do?"
"Where do we get the money?"
I will do it.
I want to show the leaders that I can lead the upgrade of the e-journal.
Then through content monetization, meet the human and financial resources
required for the new e-journal.
Good for you. Go for it.
I fully support you.
Come to visit us when you are free.
No problem.
- Mr. Shi.
It's cold coke.
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
Well, I read your updated information and data on my way here.
It's going great.
Yes. We finished that last night.
Lili, take Mr. Chen to the meeting room and take care of him.
Okay, Mr. Shi. Mr. Chen, this way, please.
Mr. Shi.
Shi, if you have any requirements, just ask.
We've been partners with Mingyu Group for years.
And we had business with your father before.
However, the situation was special.
Anyway, we will help you.
I'm sure we'll have a good cooperation.
Mr. Shi, do you have any questions?
Thank you.
I've learned about Lieying.
I am interested in where the company is headed.
Our company ranks among the top in the industry.
Le'an Technology is just a supplier of our company.
It has nothing to do with the rank.
According to the information,
the purpose of your company is to serve a wider public.
You have to further improve your technology.
So far, there's no solutions for that.
Mr. Shi, look.
Lieying is an established company.
Investing in it will help us enter the industry quickly.
And Lieying and Mingyu Group are partners.
We've been through adversity together.
Yes.
I totally understand.
My father values Lieying.
But this is business.
The essence of investing is to buy future value.
If Lieying wants to cooperate with Mingyu Cloud Innovation,
you should come up with solutions to improve core technologies.
We are an investment company, not a charity.
Am I right?
Thank you for your time.
Director Feng, please see Mr. Li out.
Mr. Li.
- Mr. Li.
- Mr. Chen, please.
It takes time to solve technical challenges.
Once solved, it will revolutionize the domestic chip.
You should work hard, to create our own patent.
I believe in you.
Mingyu Cloud Innovation will do its best to support you.
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
If we can get the R&amp;D funding,
I'm sure we will achieve a phased breakthrough.
I will visit Le'an Technology tomorrow. We will talk about it.
Okay, then I'll take my leave.
Mr. Shi, let me get this straight.
Lieying's Mr. Li is a friend of Mr. Shi and Mr. Tian.
If you insist on investing in Le'an,
I'm afraid you won't be able to convince the board.
Interviews are the most basic part of investing.
If you can't schedule an interview well,
I can't trust your judgment on investments.
Mingyu Cloud Innovation wants to invest in the future, not relationships.
Mr. Tian, Mr. Shi showed up during the interview.
Mr. Shi.
Uncle, you said you were going to pick me up.
Something has come up.
Uncle, you don't love me.
Mr. Shi.
I have to go.
I sent Ms. Qin there.
She's been complaining that you didn't pick her up yourself.
She wanted me to pass that.
Anything else?
Yes. Mr. Guan said he couldn't reach you.
What does he want?
He's hosting a banquet at Warner Manor.
He wanted you to attend it.
I am not available.
Mr. Guan knew you would say that.
He wanted to introduce you to someone important.
Okay. Tell him that I will attend it.
What about the Financial Introduce interview?
Explain the situation, and reschedule it.
Okay, I will go.
Dear, you're not going to work overtime. Right?
Xingzhou,
remember I told you about Shi Yan's interview?
The editor-in-chief just informed me
that he wanted me to do the interview.
But I only have one birthday a year.
I am sorry, Xingzhou.
I've been preparing for Shi Yan's interview for two months.
The opportunity is rare.
Shi Yan asked me to interview him.
If I don't go, the front page of the next issue will be blank.
You know, he has lots of stories.
He has not been interviewed since he founded Mingyu Cloud Innovation.
This is the first exclusive interview.
Okay. Let's celebrate it later.
I will wait for you after work.
I am sorry, Xingzhou.
It's too sudden.
It's fine. I can understand it.
You've been working hard for this interview.
Hold on to it.
Thank you, Xingzhou.
You are the best.
The interview starts at 7:00.
I will try to finish it in two hours.
We'll still have time to blow out the candles, make wishes, and eat birthday cake.
I will pick you up after the interview.
I'll text you the address later.
It's so nice of you.
Is your boyfriend cool with it?
Yes. He said he understood it.
And he wanted to pick me up.
Your boyfriend is really too reasonable.
Not like the clingy one in my family.
Whatever reason I ditch him, he gets mad.
See you.
Hello, Ms. Zheng, I am Chen Sheng from Mingyu Cloud Innovation.
Hello, Mr. Chen.
Ms. Zheng, for some reason, Mr. Shi needs to cancel the interview.
We will reschedule it.
I am sorry.
When is the interview rescheduled?
A week later at the same time. Is that okay?
Or when you have time in a week?
If the interview is rescheduled for next week,
we won't have anything to cover in the next issue.
Can Mr. Shi spare me a few minutes?
No matter what time of day.
We can split it into two interviews.
I am afraid it won't work.
Mr. Shi's schedule is full these days.
Then…
Could he spare me two hours tonight?
Or one hour.
He has plans tonight. He has no time for you.
I am sorry.
No.
Dear Shanshan, could you find out where Shi Yan is going tonight?
Hello.
Shi Yan?
I don't know him.
But you're a lucky dog.
Guan Ji, Shi Yan's friend,
is going to host a banquet at Warner Manor.
I think half of the Guan friends in Jiangcheng will attend it.
I don't know if Shi Yan is going.
I will take a shot.
Wait.
Aren't you going to celebrate Yue Xingzhou's birthday?
Are you going to ditch him?
My boyfriend and Shi Yan, I choose Shi Yan.
Good.
Enterprising women are the most attractive.
Thank you.
Warner Manor.
Enjoy.
Come to me.
Mr. Chen, good evening.
I arrived at Warner Manor.
Ms. Zheng, why…
Sorry to just come over here.
I don't have much time.
Please tell Mr. Shi that I will wait for him.
I hope he can feel my sincerity and spare me some minutes for the interview.
Well. Please find a place to wait.
I'm going to talk to Mr. Shi.
I can't promise you anything.
You may have come for nothing.
Okay. Thank you anyway.
I think Guan Ji is throwing the banquet to get everyone together for dinner.
I don't think so.
I heard that Yu You was specially invited by the Guans from abroad.
He is a professor at the University of Finance and Economics.
Only the Guans can hire him as a consultant.
Mr. Shi was also invited.
Shi Wenguang's son is no good.
Mingyu Group was in trouble, but he started his own company.
So Shi Wenguang handed over the company to his son-in-law. What a shame.
In my opinion, Guan's son and Shi's son are ambitious.
They hired a professor from abroad.
I think they'll accomplish something.
One is timid, the other is playful.
What can they accomplish?
Funny. Let's go.
Is Guan Ji going to be late again?
Mr. Guan said there was a traffic jam.
He will be here in 10 minutes.
Anything else?
Ms. Zheng from Financial Introduce is here.
She is waiting for you.
She wanted you to space some time for the interview.
Zheng Shuyi?
I told you to ask her to reschedule it.
I did. But she said if she rescheduled the interview,
they won't have anything to cover in the next issue.
I don't know how she knew about your plans.
I have a meeting with Le'an Technology tomorrow.
I don't have time for the interview tonight.
It's remote. I don't think she ate.
Grab her some food and get a car for her. There's no taxi here.
Okay.
Graduated with a full scholarship from Harvard.
Double Ph.D. in Economics and Finance, University of Cambridge.
The youngest professor to be at the University of Finance and Economics.
Nice resume.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
Are you Professor Yu You?
Do you know me?
I am reading your research.
Fintech. Technology-driven financial innovation
isn't just macroeconomic,
it can also bring profound changes to each of our lives.
I feel close to the field.
It is closely related to our lives.
You are right. That's why I chose this research direction.
In the past, "Capital" and "Finance" were out of reach.
But now I study them
to see how much they can transform our lives.
If I had the chance, I would like to return to my alma mater and listen to your lectures.
You graduated from the University of Finance and Economics?
Yes. I am a reporter at Financial Introduce.
Professor Yu, can I add you on WeChat?
- Mr. Shi.
- Of course.
- I'll scan your QR code.
- Okay.
That is Zheng Shuyi from Financial Introduce.
Okay.
Zheng Shuyi. I'll remark you as Reporter Zheng.
Thank you.
Zheng Shuyi.
The winner of the Interviewer of the Year,
writer of Zhu Xingguo on Currency Wars, Zheng Shuyi.
I am sorry. I am late.
Guan Ji. It's been a long time since you came to ride horses with me.
My bad.
I heard you went to Qionghai. I was waiting for you to come back.
I am back.
I'll wait for you at the racecourse tomorrow.
As far as I know, tonight's banquet is closed to the press.
I know. I'm here to wait for an interviewee.
Work is important, and so is health.
You don't look well.
I am fine. I'll be fine with my medicine.
See you in there.
- I will see you later.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Mr. Shi.
Sorry, Ms. Zheng. Mr. Shi is not available tonight.
I'll find the closest time to finish the interview.
You didn't eat, right?
You should eat something first. Then I will get a car to send you back.
It's okay. My friend will pick me up.
So close.
At least let me see your face.
- Long time.
- Mr. Zhang, long time no see.
Long time no see.
- Nice to meet you.
- Long time no see.
Mr. Wang, how are you doing?
Hello, Professor Yu. Welcome back.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Shi. Thank you.
I've read your article.
Research on the Impact of Financial Constraints on the Investment and Financing Behavior of Listed Companies.
Your opinion is different from that at home.
The article was written last year.
It's a little long.
I have some new ideas this year.
It's good to embrace changes.
I'm glad that Guan Ji brought you back.
There should be plenty of opportunities to consult you with in the future.
I am flattered.
Mingyu Cloud Innovation has a bright future.
We will learn from each other.
Well, I read an article called Zhu Xingguo on Currency Wars.
Its view is sharp, and its content is sensitive.
It's very stimulating to me.
You should read it when you are free.
I have an impression of this article.
It's not bad.
Cheers.
Guys, let me say few words.
All of you here today are friends of Guan Capital.
The new year's coming,  I am hosting this banquet
to thank you all for your cooperation.
And I want to introduce you to a new friend.
The strategy consultant of Guan Group, Professor of Finance, Mr. Yu You.
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
Enjoy yourselves.
- Let me introduce…
- No need.
Yu You, he's wanted to see you for a long time.
You're not even so interested in a girl.
I am flattered, Mr. Shi.
Okay, I've finished my mission.
Here's the man you wanted to meet.
My old man supports us.
Now we have to convince the fogies of Mingyu Cloud Innovation.
About your father, do you…
Don't rush. One step at a time.
Right.
We are three lame…
You are the lamest.
Fine. We are three musketeers in Jiangcheng.
All for one and one for all.
Cheers.
Xingzhou, where are you?
The traffic is heavy. Wait for me for a while.
I'll be there as soon as possible.
Okay. I'll wait for you on the side of the road in case you can't see me.
Ms. Zheng, long time no see.
What are you doing here?
Long time, Mr. Zhang.
I'm here for an interview.
The interview you wrote for me was great.
I haven't had time to thank you.
Get in the car. I'll give you a ride.
I am flattered.
You are a veteran in the industry, so I have room to play.
My boyfriend will be here in a minute.
Thank you.
Okay, see you.
Miss, are you alone?
Do you need a ride?
It's raining hard.
No, thank you. My boyfriend will be here in a minute.
Then, why are you standing here?
It has nothing to do with you.
Why is Ms. Zheng still here?
Didn't I tell you to get a car for her?
She said her boyfriend would pick her up.
Xingzhou, when will you get here?
I am so cold.
Did her boyfriend ditch her?
This time, this road, and it's raining.
I don't think she can get a taxi.
Drive the car over.
I know it's raining, but I am waiting for my boyfriend.
Right, I have a boyfriend. Take care. Thank you.
No way.
Let's go.
She is waiting for her boyfriend.
I didn't know she really had a boyfriend.
I talked to her a few times today.
I think she is nice.
She didn't get to interview you.
And people were hitting on her.
And it's cold.
I think that's why she was acting so impatient.
You seem to care if she has a boyfriend.
No.
She's pretty and capable.
It's normal for her to have a boyfriend.
You think she's pretty and capable?
Yes. Her colleagues think highly of her.
They thought she could be a deputy editor.
- Chen Sheng, I noticed one thing.
- What thing?
You're better suited to be a gossip reporter than my assistant.
I am sorry, Shuyi. It's hard to drive in the heavy rain.
There was another traffic jam before I got there. You must be freezing.
I am fine.
How was your birthday? Were you happy?
How could I be happy without my girlfriend?
I am sorry.
Who spent your birthday with you?
Who else?
Xu Feng?
He started wearing perfume?
The perfume is light and special.
His taste is good.
Next time you meet him, ask him what perfume he wears.
I think it will smell great on you, too.
How was your interview?
It's a long story.
Never mind. Let's change the subject.
Okay. Don't be upset, dear.
Why don't you answer that?
I am off work. I want to focus on you.
I don't answer calls for work.
Let's go to my place.
I will make longevity noodles for you.
No, thanks. It's late. And you don't feel good.
Rest early. You will have plenty of chances to make it up to me.
You are so nice.
That's because I love you. My little fool.
Your birthday isn't over yet.
Happy birthday, Xingzhou.
Thank you, baby.
I will leave.
Hello, what's up?
What?
I will tell the chief editor about it.
Where is my phone?
Hospital?
Why is it in the hospital?
Was it stolen?
I got in the car with it in my hand.
Why did Xingzhou go to the hospital?
Is he sick?
Did he get into a car accident?
He is here.
Plate with same numbers.
It must belong to a big shot.
It must be his friend.
It's not unusual to visit a friend in the hospital at night.
♫  Being emotional is accidental. I acted in the wrong role  ♫
♫  Can a happy ending be fixed?  ♫
♫  Meeting you, approaching you  ♫
♫  Falling in love with you, losing you  ♫
♫  You left by yourself and left me where I was standing  ♫
♫  Let the tears struggle and fall  ♫
♫  Are you just a passerby from now on?  ♫
♫  My heart feels like it has fallen off a cliff  ♫
♫  Does it hurt  ♫
♫  Love always makes people sink like quicksand  ♫
♫  The closer I get, the more I can't extricate myself  ♫
♫  Don't say you can let go  ♫
♫  Don't go far, okay?  ♫
Subtitles and Timing provided to you by the 👔 How to Tame a CEO Team💓 @viki.com
"Passerby" - Zhou Shen
♫  Being emotional is accidental. I acted in the wrong role  ♫
♫  Can a happy ending be fixed?  ♫
♫  Meeting you, approaching you  ♫
♫  Falling in love with you, losing you  ♫
♫  You left by yourself and left me where I was standing  ♫
♫  Let the tears struggle and fall  ♫
♫  Are you just a passerby from now on?  ♫
♫  My heart feels like it has fallen off a cliff  ♫
♫  Does it hurt  ♫
♫  Love always makes people sink like quicksand  ♫
♫  The closer I get, the more I can't extricate myself  ♫
♫  The more I pretend to be cool, the harder it is to let go  ♫
♫  Do you want to let go like this?  ♫
♫  Does it hurt  ♫
♫  We're clearly already trapped in quicksand  ♫
♫  Don't say you were never afraid  ♫
♫  Don't say you can let go  ♫
♫  Don't go far, okay?  ♫