Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
👔 How to Tame a CEO Team💓 @Viki.com
♫  A tidal wave of tears is like falling stars
after encountering the cold  ♫
♫  Dreams in winter are too fragile  ♫
♫  The chirping cicadas wake me from my deep sleep  ♫
♫  Intoxicated under the sunset  ♫
♫  The light fades through my fingertips  ♫
♫  The ripples bloom in my heart like the tide  ♫
♫  Let time no longer be boring  ♫
♫  The evening breeze blows gently  ♫
♫  I want to have a glass of lemon soda  ♫
♫  A sip of summer intoxication  ♫
♫  The sun is shining brightly and I match you perfectly  ♫
♫  Add some ice for a slightly tipsy flavor  ♫
♫  Stop frowning  ♫
♫  Oh, you are like soda, spreading the flavor of my heart  ♫
♫  My hair blows in the wind,
how many times have I fallen for you?  ♫
♫  Waiting for the wind to get drunk, drink a few glasses,
love is like water  ♫
♫  Tenderness is too fragmentary and cannot be taken back  ♫
And now let's give a big welcome to our distinguished guests.
We're honored to have you here.
In the future, Guan Group will remain committed to innovation and talent.
This year, we also hired new blood.
Now, let's give a big welcome to our new partner.
Professor Yu You, the Strategic Adviser of the Group.
Hello, I'm Yu You.
It's an honor to join Guan Capital
and witness its breakthrough.
Similar people hang out together.
Excellent men come in packs.
Yu You looks handsome and young.
He's pretty good.
Is he better than Guan Ji?
Well, I can't compare them.
What about you? Is Shi Yan better than both of them?
Shi Yan is… like an unreasonable and annoying little goblin.
In that sense no one can compare to him.
Why do I suddenly feel so cold?
The Guans are taking bigger strides.
Yeah, they are.
He's also from our Planning Department.
Nice meet you.
We'll be counting on you.
Excuse me for a moment.
Hello, Ms. Zheng. It's good to see you again.
Hello.
I almost missed this occasion.
Why? Pray tell.
I'm a little embarrassed to say this.
There was a slight hiccup. I lost the invitation you gave me.
My coworker then found me another one.
I see. You could've contacted me.
By the way, do you want a separate interview?
Maybe I can help when he's done.
Thank you. My coworkers did an interview last week.
Shuyi.
This is my friend.
Sanjiang Entertainment Buzz's on-camera reporter, Bi Ruoshan.
- Hello.
- Hello, Professor Yu. I've heard a lot about you.
I'm flattered.
I'd like to introduce you to two friends of mine.
Unfortunately, one of them just left.
Is the one who just left…
Guan Ji?
My apologies.
This is the journalist I told you about. Ms. Zheng from Financial Introduce.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Zheng.
And this charming lady is?
Bi Ruoshan, Sanjiang Entertainment Buzz.
Journalists nowadays are indeed all very charming.
Mr. Guan, are you available for an exclusive interview?
Sure.
That's Guan Ji for you.
He gets talkative around charming ladies.
Shanshan is similar, getting talkative when handsome men are around.
Excuse me, I have to take this.
Hey, Mom.
Didn't I tell you I just got back and I'm trying to get settled.
Okay, I'll do as you asked. Don't worry.
Okay, I'll get back to work.
I feel you.
When I visited you, my mom said she wanted to introduce me to her colleague's son.
My mom wants to introduce me to her old friend's daughter.
Professor Yu, we need you to go early and prepare for the dinner tonight.
Okay. Thank you.
Well, if you'll excuse me.
Go ahead. Let's schedule the interview later.
Sure.
Staying for the dinner?
I have an article to write. I won’t accompany you anymore.
It's an honor to join Guan Capital
and witness its breakthrough.
Yu You's voice is pretty nice.
Gentle and charming.
I just wonder if he's good looking.
It wouldn't be a coincident that he heard me mocking him?
Since he never replies to my serious messages.
Then I have to resort to fun stuff.
I got a letter today.
It's an honor to meet you.
I read a book today.
It's called "I'm lost since I met you".
That's not going to work.
Come on, let's drink.
Congratulations.
This way, please.
Thanks a lot.
I can't claim the credit.
It's because you and Bruce got along well.
You impressed him with your plans and challenges.
That's why he's joining Le'an.
I got a letter today.
It's an honor to meet you.
I read a book today.
It's called "I'm lost since I met you".
What are you laughing at?
You've been acting really weird lately.
I'm curious. Why did you suddenly disappear this afternoon
in the middle of the press conference?
Maybe because I'm unreasonable.
Since you won't read it anyway, I'll text whatever I want.
Why don't you text me back?
Your phone's out of order, or you're working on some billions worth project?
I won't blame you for not replying.
Because you're an illiterate who can't type.
Illiterates can't read messages, either.
I haven't had a chance to ask you yet.
Is your friend from the media here?
Yes. I just introduced her to you.
The journalist, Ms. Zheng Shuyi.
Are you two seeing each other?
We are just good friends and we get along well.
Professor Yu.
Come on, a toast.
That's what unreasonable little goblins do.
I'm doomed. He definitely heard everything.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at…
I'm looking at you who's different today.
You're different at work.
You were different today, too.
There was a different kind of beauty.
You're such a sweet talker.
These heartfelt words are only for the most dazzling reporter in the city.
We haven't had enough fun today.
Let's have another round of drinks.
Sure.
This is the place.
You still remember.
Of course.
It's easy to tell we're the same.
Hi, Gorgeous. Are you alone?
Let's have a drink together. It's on me.
You want to buy me a drink?
I don't drink normal wine.
This is my precious collection.
It's one of a kind in the world.
Ordinary people can never dream of having it.
Hello.
Get me a bottle of that wine.
A moment please.
Excuse me.
I'd like to ask how much this wine costs.
Since it's one of a kind in the world, I fear I may not be able to afford it.
580 yuan.
What a relief.
I don't need others to buy me the drinksince it costs only 580yuan.
So, I'm worth only 580 yuan divided by 10.
That's 58 yuan.
The memories we share are so beautiful and intoxicating.
Maybe you're really drunk.
- Good morning!
Shuyi, the schedule for Cloud Innovation's annual conference is out.
They sent you an invitation, didn't they?
There really is a leak in the house and it rained all night.
The schedule just came out today.
Invitations won't come so fast.
Besides, the interview with Shi Yan was well received.
I'm sure he'll send you an invitation.
Shi Yan must still be mad now.
Our magazine has two more issues this year.
Going over each company's year-end conference
is definitely a great choice for the headlines.
I have to go, whether he's mad or not.
We've added a session for Le'an and invited Mr. Chen.
Is there anything else you want to change?
Looks fine. Go ahead with it.
Got it.
Mr. Shi, see you next week.
Wait a minute!
What about the press?
Mr. Shi, as usual, we included everyone.
We also added new agencies.
I've confirmed the list. Financial Introduce is there.
I'll go over the arrangement again.
Express delivery from Cloud Innovation.
The invitation's have arrived.
Shi Yan isn't so mean after all. He just likes to act.
Then I'll forgive him.
I will thank him properly at the press conference.
And invite him for a dinner.
Yuling, this delivery's for you.
For me?
Thank you.
Beier, hurry up and gather Cloud Innovation's material.
Send it to me as soon as you can.
Yes, Yuling.
We're going to be very busy.
What's going on?
It’s not the lead editor, right?
My uncle does care for me.
But it's a bit too much, isn't it?
Why haven't you spoken yet?
Before, I was still worried about the lead editor.
Now, you and Yu Ling will each cover one of the Guan Group and Cloud Innovation's conferences.
Somehow we no longer have to worry.
It's my problem. I didn't handle it well.
It's over for me now.
What is over?
It's just a press conference.
You have done so many front pages this year and you have already done well.
Take advantage of this time to unwind.
Prepare the next plan of attack and fight again next year.
I want to do a feature on Cloud Innovation.
I have to go to this conference.
I want to publish it on our e-version and make it a special series.
Even if you went to the conference and convinced Shi Yan,
it's still a long way to go for the e-version's upgrade.
I know.
I can't persuade the lead editor right now.
So I have to take every opportunity.
And shorten my time spent on that "long way to go."
Then go for it.
By the way, bring Shiyue along if you go.
Bring her along?
I'm not sure if I'll be allowed in.
How can I bring her along?
You can always charm your way in.
Please ask someone else to bring her along?
I'm afraid I can't help.
I don't get why a rich kid like her wants to toil in a news agency.
Why doesn't she stay home to enjoy something she likes?
Don't you think Shiyue's very pure-minded?
Not only is she simple-minded, she also has an empty head.
Ms. Yi, I can't be her mentor.
Don't you like pure-minded people? Or do you prefer sly ones?
Virtues come before competences.
Shiyue does have many shortcomings.
But I believe she can be taught well.
You have to trust me.
Take care of her well and be a patient mentor.
Consider it as if I owe you a favor.
Shiyue, Cloud Innovation's press conference is around the corner.
Do some research and come to the conference with me.
Shuyi, I thought you didn't receive the invite.
You don't have to worry about that.
But Shuyi I haven't gone over the recording you gave me…
That's for you to familiarize yourself with the workflow
and deepen your understanding of the industry.
This year, Cloud Innovation is the hot topic of the industry.
Financial journalists are dying to be invited to the press conference.
Shi Yan's sharp-minded and his understanding of the market is spot on.
Previously, you just listened to his interview recording.
This time you can meet him in person.
The chief editor is partial.
She's probably comforting her.
But the invite from the chief editor is different from Shi Yan's invite.
Go back to work.
Yu You, someone texted you.
Shi Yan, do you have a spare invite for news agencies?
What is it? Is it for Ms. Zheng again?
Yes. How do you know?
I've just returned home and she's the only journalist I know.
It's so nice of you to get her an invite.
Be honest.
Are you pursuing her? Or is it the other way round?
No, we're just friends.
We're from the same city and school and we get along.
Besides, isn't it normal for a senior to help his former schoolmate out?
Not everyone's like you going after ladies and trying to impress them.
I remember that she interviewed you a while ago.
You didn't give her an invite?
Anyway, do you have a spare invite?
No, I don't.
If you beat me, you might get one.
We've worked all day.
I thought we were here to relax.
But I'm actually here to be your sandbag.
I say. Why are you so eager to win after getting off work?
Another round.
Shi Yan wouldn't deliberately withdraw my invite.
He's too important to go over trivialities like media invitations.
There must be some misunderstanding.
It's no use thinking on my own.
Why don't I just call and ask him?
If it's a misunderstanding, I'll ask him for an invite.
If he's still mad at me, I'll apologize and calm him.
I'm sorry I lost to Shi Yan.
I can't help you with the invite.
So he's deliberate!
Shanshan,
I'm done for.
Cloud Innovation's conference's drawing is near.
Shi Yan himself gave Xu Yuling an invite.
Shi Yan himself, on purpose?
And he left me out.
He heard my mockery.
He's mad at me now.
Is that what you're talking about?
You're deliberately making me jealous, aren't you?
I envy you.
Take it easy.
I'll check with my friend. Let's see if I can get one for you.
That's great, Shanshan! Thank you, you're my benefactor.
I can't help. I can't defeat him.
Defeat him?
My friend can't help.
Shi Yan is so mean, isn't he?
You're right.
Forget it. I'll sneak in after you.
Were he more generous, I wouldn't have to act like a thief.
I told you that he cares about you.
And that's why he gives you a hard time.
The more he doesn't want me to go, the more I'll try to get in.
I lost the bet.
I think it's a pity, though.
Ms. Zheng is a very good journalist.
Her articles are also very insightful.
I can't help out this time.
I hope she won't blame me. She will blame you.
Hello.
Have you sent out all the invites for the press conference?
Yes, sir. They were all delivered this morning.
Hello, Mr. Shi?
We received attendance confirmations from Financial Introduce and Jiang TV Station.
It's not a misunderstanding, is it?
It is all the more reason to ask him in person.
Why scream like a ghost late at night?
Screaming like a ghost?
You're sitting here in the middle of the night with no lights on.
You're more like a ghost.
You almost gave your niece a heart attack.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Everything's fine. You're not freaked out.
Go back to bed.
Uncle, what's wrong with you?
Did you get dumped?
Or is it an outright refusal?
Is it about the lady from last time?
Don't tell me you fell for her while she's not into you.
Qin Shiyue, I'll say it again. Go back to bed.
Okay, Uncle. Good night, Uncle.
Sign here.
- Ms. Xu, right?
- Yes.
Hello. I'll take you there.
- Okay. Thank you.
- This way, please.
Take your seat, please.
So close to the stage.
Financial Introduce is our important partner.
Our boss himself asked us to sit you here.
- Please, sit.
- Thank you.
This is a nice spot.
Mr. Shi, would you like to take a break in the lounge?
No need.
Mr. Shi, you're here.
We've sat important agencies in the front.
You should put more effort in improving your skill set.
Ugh…
Mr. Chen,
didn't you instruct us to get a proper seat for the lady from Financial Introduce?
Come with me.
- Ms. Xu. My apologies.
- Hello.
A colleague in my department made a mistake with your seat.
Please come with me.
This way.
Mr. Shi, it's all properly set.
Shiyue, you don't have to dress up like this for a press conference.
Oops, I thought I could go unnoticed in black.
Shuyi.
- It's you.
You two know each other?
The conference's about to start. Let's get inside first.
Let's go.
Hello, please sign here.
My apologies.
We can only admit two persons per invite.
- I… I…
- Sister Shuyi.
The press conference is about to start why don't you leave me here and go in first?
Shanshan, you take her inside first. I'll think of something.
Shuyi, I don't have to go.
You go inside. I've got an idea.
Don't be too late, then. Let's go.
Shuyi, why don't I wait for you outside?
He's walking toward me.
He came out specifically to find me, right?
Oh, no, my uncle has seen me.
What's with that strange stare?
He won't have me give him a conference recap tonight, will he?
Shuyi, I'm heading in.
Mr. Shi, what a coincidence.
It's been a long time. Have you been busy lately?
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
Mr. Shi, is Xu Yuling a better interviewer or a better writer?
It's not my job to confirm the press list or issue invitations.
Mr. Shi.
Find her a seat.
Ms. Zheng, please follow me.
His language skills are so poor that he can't even explain properly.
Let’s see what you can say when you take the stage.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
You're welcome, Ms. Zheng.
This seat was specially arranged for you by Mr. Shi.
It's our PR team's fault that you didn't receive the invite.
Please don't take it personally.
Mr. Chen, I have a small favor to ask.
Please, say.
I have two other coworkers.
I was wondering if you could arrange for us to sit together.
No problem.
How did you get in?
And we've got such a good spot.
He arranged it.
Then you should thank him properly.
Are you coming to the conference today?
I'm here.
Okay. I'll see you later.
Are you here?
Yes.
See you in a while.
Sure.
The setup's too bland.
It's his style.
I hate press conferences and stuff.
They're boring.
I have to sit through a couple hours of gibberish.
Heaven, who can come and save me?
Is it about to start?
Mr. Shi, everyone's already downstairs.
Mr. Shi, Mr. Shi. Straight A Boss.
Today is not a press conference for Mingyu, but a press conference for your personal charms.
Although I can't speak at the moment,
I am already screaming for you in my heart.
♫  Everyone is looking forward to  ♫
♫  the wonderful things arranged by fate  ♫
♫  Don't know if it exists or not  ♫
Mr. Shi
♫  You came to me, unexpectedly  ♫
♫  But it's also the future I imagined  ♫
♫  No time for showing off  ♫
♫  Maybe sincerity is the best image  ♫
Distinguished guests, sorry for keeping you waiting.
I'm Shi Yan.
♫  You are like the moon in a deep night  ♫
♫  You are like the sun in the blue sky  ♫
Shi Yan's business has been prosperous in recent years.
The father and son are really good.
By leaving the family corporation, Shi Yan got rid of a burden.
Welcome to Cloud Innovation's press conference.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
👔 How to Tame a CEO Team💓 @Viki.com
"Passerby" - Zhou Shen
♫  Being emotional is accidental. I acted in the wrong role  ♫
♫  Can a happy ending be fixed?  ♫
♫  Meeting you, approaching you  ♫
♫  Falling in love with you, losing you  ♫
♫  You left by yourself and left me where I was standing  ♫
♫  Let the tears struggle and fall  ♫
♫  Are you just a passerby from now on?  ♫
♫  My heart feels like it has fallen off a cliff  ♫
♫  Does it hurt  ♫
♫  Love always makes people sink like quicksand  ♫
♫  The closer I get, the more I can't extricate myself  ♫
♫  The more I pretend to be cool, the harder it is to let go  ♫
♫  Do you want to let go like this?  ♫
♫  Does it hurt  ♫
♫  We're clearly already trapped in quicksand  ♫
♫  Don't say you were never afraid  ♫
♫  Don't say you can let go  ♫
♫  Don't go far, okay?  ♫