Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
👔 How to Tame a CEO Team💓 @Viki.com
"Lemon Soda" - Lai Meiyun
♫  A tidal wave of tears is like falling stars
after encountering the cold  ♫
♫  Dreams in winter are too fragile  ♫
♫  The chirping cicadas wake me from my deep sleep  ♫
♫  Intoxicated under the sunset  ♫
♫  The light fades through my fingertips  ♫
♫  The ripples bloom in my heart like the tide  ♫
♫  Let time no longer be boring  ♫
♫  The evening breeze blows gently  ♫
♫  I want to have a glass of lemon soda  ♫
♫  A sip of summer intoxication  ♫
♫  The sun is shining brightly and I match you perfectly  ♫
♫  Add some ice for a slightly tipsy flavor  ♫
♫  Stop frowning  ♫
♫  Oh you are like soda, spreading the flavor of my heart  ♫
♫  My hair blows in the wind,
how many times have I fallen for you?  ♫
♫  Waiting for the wind to get drunk, drink a few glasses,
love is like water  ♫
♫  Tenderness is too fragmentary and cannot be taken back  ♫
If I had known, I wouldn't have driven today.
This way Yu You could've taken me home.
We could've spent time together for a little while longer.
Next time I see him, I definitely won't drive.
I can't believe I still have to work overtime on the weekend.
But with you, it's a date anywhere.
Are you cold? Do you want to get in the car?
No.
You won't be able to hold me in the car.
Your arms are the warmest place in the world.
How long have you been waiting for me today?
Tell me! Why are you here all of a sudden?
Zheng Shuyi.
Why are you asking so many questions at this point?
Can't I know?
I thought as a girlfriend I could learn everything about you.
Isn't that the privilege of being in love?
Yes, it is.
I…
It's my mom.
It's cold outside. Go home and answer it.
Okay.
Shuyi, what took you so long?
How are you today?
It's been a great day.
Shuyi,
I know what girls your age are thinking.
You only fix your eyes on handsome internet celebrities.
You spend money and time for them.
In the end, you get so caught up and can't stand the boys around you.
How many dating opportunities have been missed for nothing?
It's a shame, isn't it?
Yu You is great.
You've got to get to know each other better, you hear me?
I didn't say he's bad. What's your hurry?
I'm not in a hurry.
I'm just trying to talk to you.
So that you don't get any of those fanciful ideas.
Mom, I'm done talking to you. I'm going to take a shower.
Wait.
I've just spoken to Dr. Chen.
She's very supportive of you two, too.
You two have to go to that exhibition this weekend.
We'll see.
I'm going to take off my makeup.
My makeup today is bland.
Professor Yu, I've already booked the tickets for the exhibition.
Thank you. How much are the tickets? I'll transfer it to you.
Even his punctuation seems polite.
- Uncle.
- Shiyue, you're back.
Uncle, did you have a good day?
Tell me all about it.
Kids should mind their own business.
Uncle, you have lipstick on your mouth.
It's late. Go to bed early or you'll turn into a panda with dark circles.
I teased him, and he joked with me.
Uncle, what's going on here?
Good morning, Shiyue.
Did anything good happen yesterday?
Why is everyone so happy?
Hello. This is your blanket.
- Good morning.
Nannan, what's wrong with you?
Ugh, I had a leak at home last night. I was up all night.
So, is it fixed now?
It's been inspected. It needs to be redecorated.
I don't have a place to stay in now.
I have to look for one after work.
Didn't you read my post last night?
Last night?
N… No.
You're wearing eyeliner.
I refreshed it a bit today on a whim.
My eyeliner will expire if I don't use it soon.
That's not it.
What's "not it"?
It's more than just eyeliner.
And this rouge and your lips.
Hello, Mr. Chen.
The average age of Juhe's team members is way too young.
And its size isn't impressive.
Yu You, do you need to revise your report?
Otherwise the old menwill say we're just fooling around.
Shi Yan, what do you think?
Take a look for me.
Is he smiling?
That's a little creepy.
He seems to be in a good mood today.
What are you looking at me for?
Have you read the report? Anything to add?
Playing cool, huh?
Shouldn't you be the one to share with us your happy experience?
Yeah, something good happened.
Juhe is young and energetic.
They want to upgrade their technology.
They have a clear division of labor among the management team.
I think highly of them.
And judging from this report, its valuation is very reasonable.
We're getting a great deal if we invest in them now.
Shouldn't I be happy about it?
That's it?
How can that be?
You believe him?
Have you eaten?
I'm eating a luxurious meal.
My girlfriend isn't enjoying a fancy meal.
What about my boyfriend? Can he bring me a fancy meal?
Sure.
Shuyi, I'm a little busy tonight. I'll make it up to you this weekend.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Shuyi.
Are you messaging Professor Yu?
What are you talking about?
Shiyue, I need to talk to you for the record.
I only admire Yu You as a friend but I have no other feelings for him.
Shuyi, I have something to tell you.
Go on.
I think I gave you some bad advice last time.
- You and Professor Yu are the same.
- The same?
Yeah, that's right.
Have you ever heard that "Likes repel and opposites attract?"
You two are too much alike.
You don't complement each other and can't be a match.
What kind of person do you think I'd be good with?
That "Uncle."
You really think so, too?
Of course, you two have complementary personalities, ages, and careers.
It all adds up!
According to you, Yu You and you would be a good match.
Yeah, we would!
Shuyi, you think so too?
Want some?
No. No need.
I'm meeting someone.
Let's have dinner, shall we?
I need to talk to you.
Shanshan.
We'll be going now.
Bye.
Let's get in the car first.
They're for you.
Thank you.
Ms. Kong, I went to college with a local who just happened to have a flat for rent.
It's also close to your agency.
I saw your post.
So I thought I could help out.
That's great. You're doing me a big favor.
Don't call me "Ms. Kong." It's too formal. I told you to call me Sister Nan.
Nan…
If you can't, you can call me "Kong Nan."
Kong Nan.
This is a new neighborhood, isn't it? Will it be expensive?
I asked him before we came.
The rent's about the same as your old one.
If you're interested, I can check with my classmate again.
Oh, sure.
How do you like it? Is it good?
I can't be more satisfied.
But the rent…
Don't worry about that.
Chen Sheng has been nagging me all day.
I definitely have to help him out…
Thank you for today.
No problem.
Well, if there's nothing else.
I'm going home now.
- Bye.
Chen Sheng!
Today…
Ms. Kong, don't take what my classmate just said to heart.
He used to make fun of me when we were in college.
So you're saying you're not interested in me?
That's not what I mean.
I mean, I'm… you…
You're a grown-up. Can't you just be a little bit straightforward?
Yes or no?
Yes, a little.
How much is a little?
I just think you're nice.
I want to see if there's a chance.
A chance for what?
A chance to develop a relationship with you.
I was just thinking about it.
If you don't want to…
Then you should really think about it carefully.
You know, I'm five years older than you.
By July of this year, I'll be 30 years old.
My mom's been pushing me to get married, too.
So, I don't even have time to play with a little kid.
I got it.
So…
if you want to pursue me, you have to be serious.
and think about the future and get ready to get married.
Don't waste your time.
And don't waste my time.
Do you understand me?
Yes, I do.
I give you my word.
So, do you have plans later today?
Why don't we eat together?
Have you eaten?
Shi Yan, you're so clingy.
I'm eating. It's my turn to ask you.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
Mr. Shi, your takeout.
Did you get the takeout?
Why haven't you eaten yet?
I'm just waiting for you to join me.
See if you like it.
Shuyi,
thank you.
Don't be so polite.
If you want to thank me,
don't leave a single grain of rice.
Forget it. You don't have to stuff yourself.
Anyway, I'm hanging up. Eat up. Bye.
Don't sit down to work right after you eat. Get up and move a bit. Okay?
What do you want to tell me?
I want to ask… if you have time to ride this week?
No, I don't.
If you don't have time this week, what about next week?
I'm busy next week.
What about the week after next week?
What are you trying to say?
I actually wanted to ask…
Can we do more things like, you know... dinner, horseback riding,
movies, and things like that?
And then?
Guan Ji,
actually, you can enjoy dinner, horseback riding, and movies with many different people.
Have you thought about how we should define our roles in doing these things together?
I'm done.
Thanks for dinner.
I'll go home first.
No need to send me home.
I can call my own cab.
If you have time, you should think about what you want.
I'm home. Get some rest.
Good night.
Uncle, you're back.
What are you doing?
Doing my homework.
Your leader taught you well.
Do your homework and go to bed early.
What did my leader teach me?
Shuyi, you have a visitor today.
I've got him waiting for you in the conference room.
Is that the boy from earlier?
Who is it?
It's him?
Hi. I'm Yi Yang.
Mr. Yi, hello. I'm Zheng Shuyi.
You asked for me?
Ms. Zheng, I'd like to ask you to do an interview like this.
We can settle this today.
Then schedule a time when you give me the outline for the interview,
I'll make preparations.
By the way, I have one more request.
I'm going to put this interview in the Financial Introduce's e-version.
Mr. Yi, look, my time is probably next week.
I can wait.
I don't know what you do, or where you work.
Good. You're starting to want to get to know me.
In order for you to know me better, how about this?
There's a live launch on Friday at 3:00 p.m.
I'm inviting you to be the only media party.
Mr. Yi, you've just seen my schedule.
I'm still hoping you'll make some time to attend.
This will help you get to know your prospective interviewee faster and better.
What's your WeChat number?
I'll send you the address later.
Why did he ask for you?
He said his name was Yi Yang and wanted me to write an article for him.
He seems delusional.
It could be a scam. You need to be careful.
Yeah, it could be.
Why don't you tell Youran not to let him in next time?
But when we were alone, he didn't do anything weird.
What if he's a well-disguised psychopath?
You didn't give him your personal information, did you?
Shuyi, I'm going to class.
Did you graduate from college?
I don't think any of them are the Yi Yang I met.
What's this live launch? There's no news at all.
Is he really a…?
Hi, there's no one here. Come sit here.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Professor Yu's class is crowded.
I always see you in class.
So I thought I'd find a seat for you.
By the way, I'm a sophomore finance major.
My name is Qian Yucheng.
Hello.
I notice that you come to this class every week.
But I haven't seen you in any of other classes.
You are…?
I'm not a student at the University of Finance and Economics.
I'm interning at Financial Introduce.
I've come to listen to Professor Yu's class. I want to enrich my mind.
I see.
You're a reporter?
We…
- Hello, students.
- Hello, professor.
Let's start today's lesson.
Today, I'm going to teach you about market risk measurement.
Please open your textbooks.
We focus on what risk measurement is.
The we look into the methods of measuring market risks.
Yucheng which page should I go to?
Not this page. This is the one.
So the partial valuation method is the simplest one in the whole V2 calculation.
Of course, except for the partial valuation method
historical simulation is also a very important method.
Thank you so much for today.
You've thanked me many times.
It's hard to find a seat when you're off-campus.
How about this?
I'll get a seat for you next time.
Really?
Thank you so much.
I'll invite you for a meal sometime.
Sounds good.
Where is he?
He left so fast.
Shuyi, you're not working late today, are you?
I'm going to work late a bit.
Nannan, I can't believe you're wearing full makeup today.
Tell me what's going on?
There's nothing going on.
I have to sign the contract later.
Contract?
You've found a flat?
Yeah, my friend found it for me.
Then I'm leaving.
See you tomorrow. Bye.
See you tomorrow.
Will you be working overtime today?
Yeah.
Then go for it.
I'm working overtime, too.
Let's work together across space and get things down quickly.
I'll see you on the weekend when we're done these few days.
I look forward to it.
Okay, I'll see you this weekend.
I'm starving. What should I eat?
- Hello.
- Hello, is this Zheng Shuyi?
Your meal is here.
Ms. Zheng, your takeout.
The food is still hot, and there's no spillage.
Your boyfriend placed the order, didn't he?
Your boyfriend is very attentive.
He talked over the phone for ten minutes.
He showed me where to buy a thermos and how to get the noodles out of the store.
Running this errand is like being a thief. It's quite a hassle.
Eat it while it's hot.
By the way, please tell him to give me a good review.
Thank you.
There's no green onion. You're so careful.
Thanks for the special love delivery.
I like it.
But I still want to eat with you.
No. 18, Wanxing Road?
What? No. 18, Wanxing Road?
Isn't it near the science park?
Yi Yang?
You're not really going, are you?
It's a little remote.
Ms. Zheng!
- Mr. Yi.
- You're here.
The broadcast hasn't started yet. I'll give you a tour.
Then I'll have to trouble you.
That's about it for the company.
We just set things up here. It's still new.
So, you're just starting out? But last time…
It's about time.
Ms. Zheng, your questions will be answered soon.
You're doing live-streaming here?
Yeah, that's right.
When I was abroad, I had my own video channel. I often live-streamed on it.
I shared my research and some of the fun things in my life.
The opening ceremony at home is a bit over the top.
That's why I'd like to do this broadcast as my opening ceremony.
This way, more people can see it.
I'll continue to share my life and work on the air.
Did you really invite only me?
Yep.
Please be seated.
Hello, everyone. I'm Yi Yang, Jackson Yi.
I'm so happy to be able to share the opening of my company on live TV.
Jackson Yi? Why does this name sound so familiar?
JY, chip genius.
He became interested in semiconductors at the age of 14.
After obtaining his Bachelor's Degree, he went on to pursue a Doctorate Degree.
He started a business with his classmates when he was in college.
He earned his first bucket of gold with a few researches of his own.
I've always had a passionate relationship with challenges.
Challenging and being challenged have always been a source of joy in my life.
And they motivate me to improve.
I'm lucky. I've got a lot of like-minded friends on my way to challenges.
Our challenge this time is Black Horse Technology.
And joining me in this challenge is my good partner, Bruce.
Next, let's give the floor to my partner, Bruce.
Shi Yan.
Don't look at me. Look at your cell phone.
…give the floor to my partner, Bruce.
JY is a very good friend of mine.
We're confident that we can lead our technical team
to develop a chip with better performance.
And take the industry to the next level.
What does Bruce mean? And this one. Who's Jackson Yi?
Can someone please explain to me what's going on?
You don't know, do you?
I don't.
Shi Yan, take a look. What's your plan?
I'll talk to Bruce.
Let's go to Le'an Tech and talk to Chen Kang.
Mr. Shi, Bruce left Le'an Tech.
He joined a chip company called Black Horse Technology.
I already know.
If he leaves now, Le'an Tech will be in trouble.
Uncle Tian and the others won't let you go.
Mr. Shi, Mr. Tian wants to meet with you in half an hour.
Thanks, guys.
Bruce.
This is Ms. Zheng Shuyi from Financial Introduce.
She's my special guest today.
How are you? Very nice to meet you, Ms. Zheng.
I have to take this, sorry.
Hello, Yu.
Bruce, I think we should talk.
I'm really sorry. I've made my decision.
I hope you're okay with that.
Bruce, Cloud Innovation and Shi Yan have shown you 100% sincerity.
Le'an Tech needs you, too.
You have been doing so well.
Shi Yan is actually very good. Le'an Tech is also very professional.
But I've known JY for years.
We share a common vision.
Besides, he's a genius in his field.
With him, I have more possibilities.
I hope you understand. I'm sorry.
Thank you for coming all the way to witness our opening ceremony.
Congratulations, Mr. Yi.
I'll wait for you to schedule an interview.
Mr. Yi.
I may have to go back and think about it before getting back to you.
Okay.
Just call me Yi Yang.
If there's nothing else, I'll go.
Do you need a ride?
No, I called a cab.
Did you see Black Horse Technology's live broadcast?
What happened to Le'an Tech?
Shi Yan, how are you doing over there?
Let's go to Mingyu Cloud Innovation instead. I'm sorry.
Ms. Zheng, what are you doing here?
Mr. Chen, I'm sorry. Could you please take me to Mr. Shi? It's urgent.
Don't you have an appointment with Mr. Shi?
He just left ten minutes ago.
Uncle, I'll be at the mansion tonight doing some research, so I won't be coming back.
Shi Yan, I'm coming for you.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Shi Yan.
Why did you come?
It's nothing. I just missed you.
You've been drinking.
Why didn't you call me over when you drink?
The Shi family's Yan is stingy!
I haven’t forgotten it since I tasted it at your house last time.
I drank it all up.
I'm drooling over the one you're drinking right now.
Why don't you pour me a drink? I'll drink with you.
Sure.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
👔 How to Tame a CEO Team💓 @Viki.com
"Passerby" - Zhou Shen
♫  Being emotional is accidental. I acted in the wrong role  ♫
♫  Can a happy ending be fixed?  ♫
♫  Meeting you, approaching you  ♫
♫  Falling in love with you, losing you  ♫
♫  You left by yourself and left me where I was standing  ♫
♫  Let the tears struggle and fall  ♫
♫  Are you just a passerby from now on?  ♫
♫  My heart feels like it has fallen off a cliff  ♫
♫  Does it hurt?  ♫
♫  Love always makes people sink like quicksand  ♫
♫  The closer I get, the more I can't extricate myself  ♫
♫  The more I pretend to be cool, the harder it is to let go  ♫
♫  Do you want to let go like this?  ♫
♫  Does it hurt  ♫
♫  We're clearly already trapped in quicksand  ♫
♫  Don't say you were never afraid  ♫
♫  Don't say you can let go  ♫
♫  Don't go far, okay?  ♫