=Thousands of Years of Love=
=Episode 9=
My master's Qionghua Residence
is in front.
She is proficient in the secret magic
of the Five Elements.
You'll know when you get there.
This forest is arranged according to
the Five Elements and Eight Trigrams.
The terrain is complicated.
Be careful when you walk.
The forest is arranged according to
the Five Elements and Eight Trigrams.
The terrain is complicated.
Be careful when you walk.
How do you know?
Master.
Where are you, Master?
Master, we're here.
Master.
Hmph.
You finally came.
I've missed my Xuanming
Snow Mountain Wine.
Give it to me quickly.
Be patient.
This time,
I've brought a new flavor,
Qingxu Mist Wine.
You know me well.
This is the husband
I've found for myself,
Mo Chenyuan.
Our story is too long.
You might as well
read the story book.
This is my autographed book,
a public display of our affection.
Neither the old nor the young
will be cheated.
Greetings.
Yeah.
Come in.
So
you recognized her a long time ago?
Why don't you tell her?
She hasn't recognized me.
You're really petty.
No, I'm not.
She has tried to beat me
since we were young.
If I told her that the little boy
is now an Immortal Lord,
how could she agree to marry me?
No need to explain.
You are petty indeed.
Ruoyao has a hot temper.
If you let the cat out of the bag,
she won't let you off easily.
I have my way to please her.
As for my Heaven-overturning Mark,
please help me to deal with it.
I warned you so many times,
but you still used your magic
to break through the Spirit Shield.
It's a waste of my efforts.
How do you have the nerve
to come to me?
Ruoyao brought me here.
She has no idea about this.
Then you should wait
another 10,000 years.
You'll be saved when the new
Eternal Ice Silk grows.
Here, our fresh fruits. They're sweet.
Try it.
The sweet apricot blooms every 300 years
and bears fruits every 300 years.
Try it.
So sour!
You've been tricked, you fool!
I don't like sour food.
Who told you it's sour?
Where
were you just now?
I went to the Snow Pond.
It's deep in the mountain.
Do you know the way?
It's not hard to find.
That mountain path twists and turns.
Isn't it hard for you to find?
Mo Chenyuan, you must have been here.
No.
No?
Do you know?
When you lie,
your eyes never blink.
Do you really believe my lie?
I saw you talking to Master today.
There's something wrong with you.
You must have known each other
for a long time.
If you don't tell me,
I'll go ask Master.
If I find out about it,
you're finished.
OK.
I'll tell you.
Feather.
My master said
when I meet the man who's destined for me,
the feather would fall off,
and then, I'd marry him
and cultivate together with him as a couple.
My feather is amazing, isn't it?
You don't have one.
You...
Are you Ice Block?
Yes.
But over 100 years ago,
you were recuperating
in the Xuanming Realm at ease
because you knew I couldn't beat you.
No.
Because I knew
you would be good to me.
You liar.
You ate my food and drank my water.
And now you're making a fool out of me.
I really want to be
your immortal spouse
and engage in dual cultivation
with you.
I was
talking nonsense when I was a child.
You're not the only one for me.
♪The wind in the courtyard
blows out the candlelight♪
(Mo Chenyuan,)
(you big rogue.)
♪The night is bleak at the pavilion♪
♪I ask the red begonias♪
♪If there was a lovesick man♪
Are you still mad?
♪The red begonia stands out
against the flowers♪
♪Sadness ripples in my heart♪
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
But once I've missed my first chance,
I don't know how to bring it up.
If you don't know,
you can ask me directly.
I can teach you.
First, you kowtow to me 180 times.
Then you offer me a humble apology,
anyway...
♪The red begonia stands out♪
♪Against the flowers♪
♪Tears run down endlessly♪
♪Tender feelings
arise in the worldly light♪
♪Don't miss out on the national beauty♪
♪And heavenly fragrance♪
♪The wind in the courtyard
blows out the candlelight♪
♪The stars and moon
shine through the western window♪
♪The night is bleak at the pavilion♪
♪I ask the red begonias♪
♪If there was a lovesick man
telling his pain of separation♪
♪The red begonia stands out
against the flowers♪
♪Sadness ripples in my heart♪
♪Tears run down endlessly♪
♪Tender feelings
arise in the worldly light♪
♪Don't miss out on the national beauty♪
♪And heavenly fragrance♪
♪The red begonia stands out♪
♪Against the flowers♪
♪Tears run down endlessly♪
♪Tender feelings
arise in the worldly lights♪
♪Don't miss out on the national beauty♪
♪And heavenly fragrance♪
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)