(Yume) Um...
The beer is freezing cold
Ah... then do you want a photo?
Huh? During the day, that... the one I took with that one.
I only took pictures of mine...
(Misato) Free?
Huh?
Ah...of course
So, um... would you like to come over here for a little while?
It's definitely different...
I don't know... I don't know anymore...
Um... can I ask you to talk to me for a moment?
I don't like something about myself
I mean, it irritates people...
In my life, I am always doing important things wrong at important times.
I can't forgive myself for being like that.
for me…
Could you please stay a little longer?
(Misato) What is it that you can't forgive so much?
Huh? (Misato) About myself
I don't like it because I make so many mistakes
At the ramen shop at work...
When I throw away the juice that smells like muddy water
That's a 58 year old sauce.
And many other things...I've been fired many times already.
Eh, but...
If it was that much of a mistake
That's within the permissible range, right?
Actually when I was a child...
(Misato) Huh?
Maybe I can try to forgive
I wonder...
(Misato) Because you gave me beer.
Huh?
(sigh)
Even if I make a lot of mistakes, I'm not a bad person.
me too…
Maybe I should try to forgive you
Huh?
My kind of...
Where I made a mistake
(sound of opening a can)
(sound of drinking beer)
good
Are you going home?
(Klaxon)
good morning
(Mio) Why are you... Ah! it hurts…
Why is it better not to move?
Don't you remember?
I remember, but...
What do you mean "good morning"? I'm not angry.
(Yume/Mio) Huh?
Ouch... I don't say "good morning" in such a stupid way!
What do you mean "I'm not angry"? it was yesterday
Mio-chan suddenly... "suddenly"?
Huh? What do you mean suddenly?
You say something suddenly, suddenly, without any cause or effect.
Suddenly, BOOM! Ah... that wasn't sudden.
How many months has it been? With a face like that dog
What you did and the lies you told
The dust piled up and became a mountain! What is it?
I know! I know, but...
I understand, so don't say you're not angry.
And you pulled it in the end, right?
I'm not pulling it!
I'm here because you pulled me, right?
I pulled it, but...
But I had no choice but to come out.
It's not out. What does "out" mean?
You were helpless
"I feel sorry for you, I can't help it.
Yume-chan, that's how I lived my life.
That's why I said "good morning"
Huh? (knock)
(Nurse) Good morning, do you have any pain?
Um, I'm sorry, I can't. If you still move like that.
We were both lucky and escaped with only minor injuries.
I'm sorry it's taking a long time to heal.
Can I have a separate room with this person?
(Nurse) Huh? No, it's already
It's fine if it's small, like that bench in the hallway...
(Nurse) Sorry, I'm busy right now.
I don't mind if I go outside (Nurse) Huh?
It doesn't matter if it's a toilet, a storage room, etc.
(Nurse) They're not children.
I can be discharged from the hospital tomorrow, so no, no, no, no!
I can't stay with you all day, so I'm fine with using the toilet.
Please wait a moment
please
(Endo) What happened?
Can you tell me more about the situation at that time?
I pressed it (Endo) Huh?
I tried to push her down the stairs.
Is that true? Huh?
So what? Am I being arrested?
She supported her mother and was not charged with any crime.
No one said that, right?
Huh? You...
(Endo) Please calm down! I will ask you for details personally.
I mean, why are you here? (Sakuma) Huh?
(Endo) Well... Mr. Sakuma... I can't leave him alone after all.
Huh? With Taro
I feel like I need to talk to you properly, so I'm worried...
I went there with Mr. Osako, but he wasn't there...
How many times have I come home? I have a bad feeling...
I contacted Mr. Endo to see if something strange was going on...
So why did you come?
It's partly my fault that the two of us turned out like this...
No, I know, but I shouldn't say things like this now.
But I also wanted to do the right thing just once...
Are you saying that's a mistake? (Endo) Anyway
I'll talk to you privately, so it's not her fault.
(Endo) Huh?
all…
It's really all my fault
(Ambulance siren)
It hurts...
it hurts…
Sigh... just a moment...
Why did you help me?
That's... right away...
The day I first met you, not your mom, but me.
That too...
After that? Huh?
Go bungying, eat crab, go to a club, drink alcohol.
Why did you act like we were friends?
It's not pretend
I really thought about it
I want to forgive you
But... you were next to me the whole time.
I wonder what that felt like
forever…
sorry…
Did you really know? Huh?
The reason my mother wanted to die
I really don't know that
why? Because we were together in the last moment, right?
We drank beer and talked.
We talked, but...
I feel like my story was heard.
I feel bad for myself because I keep making mistakes...
Did you also talk about your childhood? Huh?
about your father
Oh, by the way, you told another lie, right?
Huh? Name About your mother
I wish your birth was just a dream.
You said that's where the name came from, but what is that? A lie to gain sympathy?
That's not really a lie...
Well, whatever is fine.
I'm really sorry
Which part are you apologizing for?
it is…
Everything... Everything I...
"It's all my fault" is an escape, isn't it?
Huh? Because that's it
The other day I was thinking and thinking
That I said I wanted to forgive you
I mean, I haven't heard anything like that at all.
That doesn't mean I'm ignoring you.
For now, let's just say it's all my fault.
Somehow, I felt guilty and felt better.
What are you really angry about?
It doesn't mean I don't think about that at all.
No... no difference
Well, it's okay because it's different now.
I don't think that's what you should do as a friend.
You said something like you wanted to make amends.
Simply say that everything is bad and stop thinking.
What was really the biggest mistake?
As long as I'm running away from that kind of thing
I don't think there can be true redemption.
♬〜
(breathing heavily)
(Takeshi)《Quickly...》
《I wish it was all a dream...》
《That you were born》
(conflict sound)
(breathing heavily)
(Nurse) Mr. Nakata? Yume Nakata!
Have you woken up? Huh?
(Nurse) Even if I woke you up, you wouldn't wake up, so I finished eating.
Ah...
(Nurse) Ah, your friend just got discharged from the hospital.
Huh?
Mr. Nakata also had another check-up with the doctor after this.
If there are no problems, you can go home.
♬〜
(Taro) Sister!
thank you
Does that look like a dog?
Ah... Yeah, just a little bit.
(Taro) I got a call from Kenken.
When did you come here?
As soon as I got a call from my sister yesterday.
After all, that house was at its limit.
I'm glad you're doing well
Well then... Thank you for the tea.
Good job
(Taro) My sister...
(Taro) I wonder if he's a really bad guy...
Huh?
I thought about everything about this time
What my sister did and what she was lied to about.
I also remember my father.
I wonder if he's seriously a really bad guy.
And the conclusion...
Ah, I just feel like I'm an irredeemable idiot.
Huh?
No, if that's all there is to it, it won't be enough.
It's all about things that can't be undone...
But for me either is fine
Whether you're there or not, it doesn't matter
Something like trauma, family, toxic parents, etc.
I'm a little bored
(Taro) I just want to go on to the next one.
I see.
That girl, that girl... Who is Sakura?
It seems like he can't think of kissing, huh?
So are you just friends?
Ah, we became friends.
(Taro) Do you want to eat? Hehe, did you make it? that
But I'm definitely making a mistake somehow, it's so bad
Hehehe
Good job
let's see…
♬〜
Hehehehe
Huh? Hehehehe
That's fucking bad hehehehe
My mom wanted to eat it, haha.
(Chime) Yes! Ah... yes
(cell phone vibration sound)
Oh, Sakura?
I mean... I always feel like I have free time like this.
Even if I get a call, it's a problem...
Huh?
(Taro) Sister...
what?
(Sutra reading)
(Shigehiko) Ah, um...
Did Mio-chan call you?
(Sutra reading)
Sorry, I didn't contact you...
(Chihiro) I really just wanted to raise some incense today.
(Sutra reading)
(clicks tongue)
(Sae) Dad, be careful there.
♬〜
Eh, just some incense is fine, right?
(Shigehiko) Ah, the sushi here is quite delicious.
Hahahahaha
Excuse me for a moment...
(Shigehiko) I forgot to get the receipt from the sushi restaurant.
That's why I still can't drink alcohol.
The teacher said it was fine too.
Because it's no good
that…
Um... (Sae) What is an insane person?
I don't want you to think that, huh?
But I thought that if I didn't come today, I might be able to escape.
I wanted to settle it, or rather, be satisfied with it in my own way.
You said you wanted to end it all.
If so, at least what are you thinking now?
I wanted to ask you
who is the worst
Who do you think is to blame for this?
I want to hear it from your mouth too
That's why I asked you today. I'm sorry.
But today, I want to see my mother off properly.
(Chihiro) It's my daughter who's at fault.
I'm not asking you right now.
Everything... it's all my daughter's fault that this happened.
No, it's me... it's all me...
(Chihiro) That's why I don't have the right to say things like this.
I think I fully understand Kondo-san's feelings.
But today is Mr. Osako's funeral.
Shouldn't we quietly remember the deceased?
(Sakura) Are you lying?
Is that really it? I wanted to pay the settlement fee and get things settled.
Otherwise it's work
Because it would cause trouble for my current family other than Taro.
So to wrap up that person
You just came here to get in a good mood, right?
(Chihiro) That can't be true, right?
(Sae) Which one is the worst?
That's what happened at my house all of a sudden.
Bring me that settlement letter.
My mom is also the worst, right?
So I apologized for that, but...
(Sae) Why is mom the worst? (Chihiro) Now
Money can only be the solution, right?
It's normal to look for the culprit at a funeral.
(Chihiro) As the young lady says, who is the worst?
Even if we look for the culprit... there's a different culprit, my daughter.
That's not true!
At that time, I was scared... I was scared that my affair would be found out.
That's why I told you to run away...
That's not what I'm saying now.
What do you mean by covering?
This person senior
Huh? Huh?
So that day, I said I wanted a divorce, but I said no.
Why don't you always listen to me?
(Hiroshi) What's the difference? That's why I want a divorce...
(Sae) A story from the past! The reason I wanted a divorce
I've heard many times that it's not like that... (Sakura) I wonder if it used to be that way.
♬〜
Well, at least... what's the reason?
Huh? (Sae) Reason
Hey! Because write a will
Isn't it worth it to go up to the roof with that?
So what is it? Did you have debt?
Were you mentally ill? Were you sick?
Yes, there is usually a reason.
Or, after all, my daughter canceled my order suddenly.
I was so shocked...
Otherwise, will the mother die and leave her child behind?
(Endo) That's... I don't think that's true.
I can't generalize...
(Sae) Why did anyone do it in the first place?
Aren't you going to get arrested?
This can only be described as an unexpected accident.
(Sae) Who was the worst police officer?
Because you can't decide properly!
Even I don't want to do something so insane.
But the person who is important to me...what is important to me?
(Sae) Actually, you are the one who regrets it the most, right?
Then, not me, but these people...
Me!
♬〜
(Chihiro) I'm going home
I'm really sorry for everything.
(Sakura) Hehehehehe something?
Taro: I'm glad I don't look like my aunt.
Huh? that! It's really me...
It was all me... I'm sorry!
(Sae) Please don't disturb me now. I'm really... I'm really sorry!
(Sae) Please be careful, no, it's me.
(Sae) Please come back! Please come back!
(Taro) Sister?
It's good after all
go home let's go home
No, because my mother too...
Sakura and her parents all gathered at the funeral...
It's definitely a shambles
About that person... When I tried to help...
Because I can't help you
(Misato)《I guess it's possible to try to forgive.》
《Even if I make a lot of mistakes, I'm not a bad person》
⚟♬「Small sunset glow」
⚟♬〜
(Chihiro) Dad? Dad!
Everything... I wish it was a dream...
Huh?
I wish everything about my birth had been a dream.
(Chihiro) Ambulance please.
Yes, when I came back, my husband had collapsed...
If it weren't for me... I'd be all wrong...
I just wanted to help...
♬〜
There's nothing wrong with that feeling
Sister?
♬〜
(sob)
(Sae) After all, it will be settled in court... (Chihiro) That's why...
For some reason... for some reason...
(Sae) Yes?
I think I might have been your mother... now.
What is it?
Because of this, I wonder if my mother wanted to die.
(Sae) Huh? I understand
I shouldn't say that...
Now, I guess that's not the case...
but…
I thought my mother wanted to die.
I don't think it's a mistake
what? Huh? What do you want to say?
Would I be able to say the same thing if I were dead?
(footsteps)
I'm really... sorry.
What I did exactly...
So... Mom, I'm sorry.
But I have to pay money and stop going to court.
Can you please stop doing that?
(Chihiro) That's because... I can't pretend it didn't happen.
It's all wrong...
Just run away like that because you can't take it back anyway...
I tried to pretend it never happened, but that was my biggest mistake.
(Chihiro) When you make a mistake, solve it with money or ignore it...
Even if mom ignores me or doesn't want to see me...
No...actually, I don't want to see it either.
But still... I'm here, right?
(Sae) Hey, Dad, we're not done talking yet.
It's already over
Huh?
Endo-san yes
I have a small request...
Huh?
Let's go!
Huh? Wait... what?
(Endo) Ah...wait!
♬〜
(Taro) Kenken?
Go home, where's your mom? Huh?
(Sakura) Lock the door, then this is here.
Put it in the mailbox at the end
(Chihiro) Where are you going back?
ourselves
Ah so
♬〜
"I'm glad we don't look alike"... haha...
(sigh)
Please... it's okay.
♬〜
(sigh)
Sorry last time?
push me down the stairs
Is your neck okay?
Ah... it still hurts a little when I turn this way.
I'm not facing you.
Can I be honest? Huh?
I don't think I'll ever be able to completely forgive you.
Yeah…
But... thank you
Huh?
Thank you for being by my mother's side at the very end.
Yeah
(Chihiro) Would you like to eat this? It's a waste
♬〜
(Chihiro) Unexpectedly, when we met normally,
It seems so nice that we might become mom friends or something.
Haha... At this age, you can call me a mom friend.
Ordinary friends? What do you think?
He seems to be talking a bit noisy, so I might not get along well with him.
So, are you on the other side? good friends
I... am I saying something that wrong?
♬〜
that!
(breathing heavily)
this…
♬〜
Ah!
(breathing heavily)
♬〜
What should we do? You from now on
What about that?
I... aren't we the same?
Even though I'm as irritated as ever
Don't make a mistake
Careful and jumpy
And then I put up with it again and got irritated... It goes back and forth.
But I guess that's not bad either.
Huh?
No, no, it's bad, I didn't do anything bad at all.
I haven't done it, but I guess that's the way it is.
Yeah…
Because the world is full of landmines
Things that I don't understand happen.
No matter how seriously I live my life
Huh? Something like this usually happens
Huh? People like that are common too.
I get irritated by that kind of thing
But sometimes I'm happy...
But I made a mistake again...
Even if I try to be courageous, it's a mistake in itself
I'm scared of making a mistake and I'm nervous
I thought it was me who wasn't impressed.
No, that's actually normal.
If you can't feel anything, is that an error?
Frustrated, scared, angry...
I can't forgive it, I hate it...
Cry, laugh...
I was scared and ran away...
Sometimes I want to die because I can't do it
That's because I live a normal life.
♬〜
I wish we could have met in a different way.
good morning
♬〜