Hello.
Hello. Is this Li Xuebo's house?
Yes. Are you my son's friend?
Come in.
The things my son asked me to prepare,
I have already prepared them.
Please give them to him.
The things your son asked you to prepare?
What is this?
Look.
So much money.
How much is it?
Three hundred thousand.
Did your son contact you
and ask you to prepare this much money?
Right. When did he contact you?
Yesterday.
Yesterday. Did he say anything else?
He said after I get it ready,
his friend would come to pick it up.
Aren't you his friend?
Then do you know where my son is now?
What exactly happened?
Who are you?
There's no time to explain.
Can I use this phone?
Yes.
Don't panic.
Is this Dongwan Criminal Investigation Detachment?
I'm Ma Guodong from Guangnan Criminal Investigation Detachment.
Please contact Comrade Lin Wei
and ask him to come to Room 303, Building 2, City Garden.
Yes, requesting backup.
Hurry, as soon as possible.
Officer,
what should I do?
He didn't answer my call...
Coming, coming, coming.
Are you Li Xuebo's family?
I'm Xuebo's father.
Are the things ready?
Xuebo told me.
They are ready.
We were just waiting for you.
Come on, come in, come in.
That brat Xuebo called me yesterday
and asked me to prepare money.
Where was I supposed to get that much money?
I just got it ready
and waited for you to pick it up.
You look a bit familiar.
I just have a common face.
The streets are full of old men like me.
Here, take a look at the stuff.
I'll pour you a glass of water.
Do you smoke?
I used to.
Got a light, buddy?
A Zippo.
It's fake.
Actually, a real Zippo isn't expensive either.
Ask your girlfriend to buy you a real one.
Later, my health got worse,
and Xuebo wouldn't let me smoke,
so I quit.
My girlfriend replaced it with a real Zippo for me.
I want to lend it to you again.
What is a Zippo?
Where is the money?
I don't have any money.
But you can have my life.
Are you Li Xuebo's father?
Where's the money?
Take it out.
Hurry up.
Ma, Ma, speak to me.
I'm alive.
What are you yelling about?
Well, I...
I don't have much time left anyway.
Careful, he's got a gun.
Should we shoot?
Hua Weihong, don't do anything stupid.
You can't get away anyway.
Throw the gun out.
If I told you to throw your gun, would you?
Let me tell you,
I'm here to put my life on the line today.
You can't afford to play this game.
We can't afford to play.
So we won't play.
Life is very precious.
Life is precious.
How much do you earn a month?
And you're talking to me about preciousness?
All right, all right.
You are all precious, okay?
Let's not talk about preciousness.
Let's talk.
Cao Aiyuan.
I don't know.
Why didn't you hit my head?
I feel like he won't come back.
Meijuan,
let me go.
I'm sorry, Xuebo.
I lied to you,
but I was forced.
It's fine.
I don't care if you're Cao Aiyuan or Liu Meijuan,
I love you.
We even have a child now.
The three of us
will live a good life,
okay?
But I'm not sure if the child is yours.
I don't care.
I don't care what kind of person you are,
or whose child it is,
I accept it all.
Can I trust you?
Of course.
You said you'd take me to many places,
was that true?
Of course it's true.
Let's leave here
and turn ourselves in.
When you get out,
I'll take you
and our child
wherever you want.
But
if I turn myself in, I won't get out.
How could that be, Meijuan?
It's just a kidnapping case.
I'll tell the police
that you were forced too,
there won't be a big problem.
Even if you're sentenced
to one, three, or even five years,
I'll wait for you.
I've also killed someone.
Are you scared?
No.
How could I be scared of you,
Meijuan?
Let me go.
I won't say anything to the police.
You lied to me.
I didn't lie to you, Meijuan,
really.
Let me go.
I can pretend I don't know you,
like we never met.
I can give up the child too,
just let me go.
Okay.
Can you do me a favor then?
Yes.
You need money to leave here, right?
Let me leave,
I'll give you as much as you need.
Lin Wei.
No way. Was Hua Weihong's punch that heavy?
Stomachache.
Is it serious?
Let me go to the hospital with you.
It's an old problem.
Stomach cancer.
Are you serious?
Of course.
Then why didn't you go see a doctor earlier?
I told you.
But you didn't believe me.
I took sick leave last time to get a checkup at the hospital.
Alright.
Hua Weihong has been caught.
I'll leave the interrogation to you.
I'll hurry to the hospital
and get checked again.
Go get checked at the hospital early.
Come back and get your cigarettes after the checkup.
Kid.
You are quite nosy.
Lao Ma.
I'm sorry.
Come back early to get your cigarettes.
Wait for me.