[English subtitles are available]
[Taste of Love]
[Episode 19]
[Freedom for You]
How was your rest yesterday?
If you're not used to staying in a hotel,
you can come home.
I'm fine staying in the hotel.
Do you think Tang Su...
By the way,
what do you think about
the Blue Sky Project of our group?
The concept of environmental real estate
was first brought up many years ago.
But the fact of the matter is
that they construct apartment buildings
in the name of environmental protection.
That's also the main reason
why this kind of project has been criticized
these years.
If our group wants to do things for the environment,
we must do something concrete and practical.
I want to leave this project in your hands.
But there are a lot of things in Time.
Some things are just for fun.
A hobby is a hobby,
but business is business.
Don't forget
you are the heir of the group.
Don't let your grandpa down.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I know the Blue Sky Project.
Why do you have this photo?
I wanted to ask you.
Do you know who he is?
He is Mike,
a big client of Leo Culture.
Mr. Luo is very polite to him.
He must be somebody.
And?
And...
Mr. Luo invited me to dinner.
He said it was an important business event.
But there were only three of us.
I didn't wear a coat.
It was so cold with the air conditioner on.
You don't know how awkward it was.
A business event?
Didn't wear a coat? Awkward?
Is Luo Shi crazy?
No.
Mr. Luo went to
talk serious business.
Serious business
takes place in an office.
There must be something fishy
about the business after dark.
You were smeared before
because you went to the director's room
in the middle of the night, right?
What do you mean?
Why do you bring up
something in the past?
Besides,
the director
has clarified it.
We were simply discussing
the script.
I'm just kindly reminding you
not to forget the pain after you recover.
Thank you for reminding me.
I haven't finished yet.
Where are you going?
You can finish it tomorrow.
No need for innuendoes.
That's not what I meant.
But don't attend
such activities anymore.
Especially when I'm not around.
What a bad temper she has!
She knew she was wrong,
but she didn't come to comfort me.
[Curious]
What are you doing with all the noise?
Come.
You'll find out soon.
Royal cuisine.
Miss Tang, please accept it.
Instant noodles?
Of course.
Why are the fried eggs in this color?
They are the best-looking ones
among all six of them.
If there were more eggs,
I believe they could look better.
What's wrong?
I...
Just now I...
Just now I had a bad attitude.
I'm sorry.
Do I look like
I'm angry?
But what I want to tell you is
no matter what happens in the future,
don't just walk out.
But I just
went upstairs.
But don't go
out of my sight.
You can cry to me, squabble with me,
or even fight with me.
But don't just take off.
Don't leave our problem unsolved overnight,
okay?
Okay.
Now I'm calmly
talking to you.
I don't want you
to attend
those unnecessary social activities.
Because your boss
is not a good boss.
He doesn't know
how to protect his artists.
What about you?
Are you a good boss?
Maybe not.
But I will be
a good boyfriend.
I believe you.
I have to take this call.
Eat the noodles.
Hello, Mr. Jin.
I have a few problems to solve.
Will he come?
I'm leaving if he doesn't.
Wu!
Mike specially mentioned
he wanted to meet
all the members of SURAGR GIRL.
Now Tang Su
is sick.
Mengmeng
can't leave from the crew.
You know that.
If you leave too, then we'd...
we'd break the appointment.
Mr. Luo.
He's here.
Mike.
You're late.
It's hard to find this place.
This is...
Tong Yiwu,
an artist of my company,
and a member of SURAGR GIRL.
Miss Tong.
I've heard so much about you.
Wu.
All right.
Now that you've met me,
I'll get going.
Wu.
Miss Tong, you don't care about my feelings at all.
You're leaving when I just arrived.
It's not that she doesn't care about your feelings.
She's young
and a bit inhibited.
She doesn't know what to say.
She's just a little young.
She's too inhibited.
How about this?
Cheers.
Mr. Luo.
Miss Tang Su
I met last time...
Didn't you say she'd come today?
She's not feeling well. She can't come.
Call her.
Tell her
I'll wait for her.
Okay. Okay.
I'll try to
call her then.
Why are you calling her?
I've already told you
she's not feeling well and she can't come.
All you want is to drink, isn't it?
I'll drink with you.
Okay.
I have to take this.
Yeah, solid waste treatment...
Hello.
Su!
What did you say, Wu?
Why did you call me,
Su?
Where are you?
Listen.
I drank
a lot of wine today.
Don't move.
I'll pick you up now.
Okay?
She's here.
Hello?
Where did you go?
Why did you go out alone?
I came to pick up Wu.
She's drunk.
I was afraid I'd disturb you,
so I didn't tell you.
Stay where you are.
Send me your location.
I'm on my way.
All right.
Wu!
How is it?
Wu, wake up!
Wake up!
Let's go home.
Let's go.
Are you in such a hurry to go?
What do you want?
I want to chat with you.
What are you doing?
Can't I chat with you?
Let go.
Chubby Su.
Don't touch me! Let go!
So what if I touch you?
Let go!
So what?
Luo Shi, open the door.
Let go of me, Luo Shi.
What?
Let go! Don't touch me!
Let go!
Let go of me!
You scumbag!
Stop!
Chubby Su, are you okay?
Aunt.
Good morning.
Where's my cousin?
He's almost here.
There's a traffic jam at this hour.
Hope cousin wouldn't be late.
Let's go.
Do you want to leave after hitting me?
If you dare to go out,
I'll call the police.
Do you believe me?
You were up to no good.
The police will arrest you first.
-I'll beat you... -Huangfu Jue!
Don't be impulsive.
If I didn't save him,
he would have drowned.
Can you be blameless if I drown?
You arranged your artists
for drinking and entertaining.
And you got thrown into the sea.
Will you look good
if the word gets out?
Who threw me into the sea?
Wasn't it him?
And my motto
is
what I'm afraid of is not trouble,
but that there is no news.
Of course I know.
I also know
that you love money more.
Back then,
you asked Yu Mengmeng to force herself
to beg for my forgiveness,
you just wanted to reunite SURAGR GIRL
to make money for you, didn't you?
Yes.
Since you want to
make a big deal out of it,
let's just go our separate ways.
From now on, there's
no more SURAGR GIRL in Leo.
Are you still aware that
you work for Leo?
Then do you know
which side
you should take?
The side I should take
has always been the same.
That's all I have to say.
Think about it.
No need.
I think that is a great idea.
Just terminate the contract.
You...
What are you two doing here?
Are you doing cross-talk?
You're singing the same tune.
I'm the victim.
Understand?
What do you want then?
I don't know what I want.
I have to think about it.
Don't worry.
I won't let you drink the water in vain.
I want more.
Luo,
don't be too greedy.
In terms of greed,
I'm no match for you.
Your goal is the Blue Sky Project.
Mind your own business.
I'll think about it.
He has no sense of time at all.
That's right.
Everyone is here.
We're all waiting for him.
Look at the time now.
So many people are waiting for him alone.
I called.
I can't reach him for now.
Aunt.
Have you reached my cousin?
It's been more than 20 minutes.
The meetings of our group
have never been delayed
for anyone before.
Directors,
I'm sorry.
Jue suddenly
feels unwell today.
So he can't attend
our meeting.
Aunt,
don't cover it up for him.
Everyone,
why don't you
look at your phone
and read the news.
Huangfu Jue, CEO of Time,
pushed his rival in love, Luo Shi,
into the sea
because of jealousness.
I didn't expect
my cousin
to be such a man of character.
It was for Tang Su again.
The gossip is not believable.
I hope our board
won't be disturbed
by these boring things.
Yes.
Aunt is right.
Let's not take such boring gossip
too seriously.
Aunt,
about our meeting...
The meeting begins.
About our Blue Sky Project...
About the Blue Sky Project,
I've made
a very detailed proposal.
I'll hand them out to you now.
Then
I'll introduce them in details.
Luo Shi is so despicable.
Su, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have drunk so much.
It's okay.
Do be careful next time.
Don't come to this kind of party again.
Well,
I have to go.
The meeting of the group directors
is about to begin.
Now?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You don't even change your clothes
and haven't prepared anything.
It's okay.
I sent Chi Ye a message.
-He'll be here soon. -Boss.
I've brought everything for you.
Get in.
Let's go together.
Cousin, why are you so late?
Are you here
to congratulate me?
I've taken over
the Blue Sky Project.
I knew it.
Love makes people confused.
Miss Tang,
I look forward to working with you.
Sorry.
This time,
you've gone too far.
Ma'am,
please don't blame Huangfu Jue.
-It was all my fault. -No need to explain.
I told you before
it's not that simple.