[English subtitles are available]
[Taste of Love]
[Episode 10]
[Come Back to the First Stage]
Mr. Huang Yousu.
I want to ask you for a favor.
Can you get me a basin of hot water?
I want to soak my feet.
The water needs
to be hotter and more.
Then it's comfortable to soak my feet.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Thank you.
Play dumb?
Let's see when you will show your real identity.
I didn't expect you to end up like this.
Now,
if there's a hot cup of black tea,
it would be perfect.
I just said
that I was bored in the ward
and wanted to take a walk.
Then you have prepared so much for me.
You're so sweet.
♫The Hall of Memories♫
It's not a big deal.
♫The bell is ringing♫
Get some more fresh air.
♫The appearance of the latecomer♫
Maybe it'll help you heal faster.
♫When I'm lonely♫
♫I raise my head and look up♫
♫Waiting for the rain to fall♫
♫I love to stay with a cat all day♫
Go!
Let's have some fun!
♫Seeing the wandering cloud♫
Wait.
What now?
♫A star falls on my hand when I open a window♫
I'm tired.
You are tired!
It seems
that no matter how many awful things I have done to her,
♫When I close my eyes, I feel at ease♫
she would smile
like this.
Sometimes
♫Everyone has gone through some hardships♫
I couldn't tell
whether she was kind
or she never cared about me.
♫Only then can you face disappointments♫
Would you like
to hear my story?
♫Don't be afraid of these annoying things♫
Okay.
♫They are gone with the wind♫
Have you ever experienced
that you couldn't show others
your real identity?
♫When I got close to my previous dream♫
♫I tamed my youthful indiscretion♫
It seems
that you can understand what I used to think.
Back then,
♫Looking back at the silent rainy seasons♫
I was at a low point in my life.
I've gotten myself into so much trouble.
♫Like daisies bloom secretly by the road♫
No one would believe me
and I had no place to stay.
But at that time,
I met someone
who hated me very much.
And I became his maid
somehow.
In the beginning,
I was worried every day.
I was afraid that he would find out
my real identity.
♫I love to stay with a cat all day♫
But later I found
that he seemed cold.
But deep down,
♫Seeing the wandering cloud♫
he is a kind,
warm and proud Husky.
♫A star falls on my hand when I open a window♫
More importantly,
when I was a superstar,
he hated me.
♫When I close my eyes, I feel at ease♫
But when I was at my lowest point,
he gave me
a place to stay.
♫Everyone has gone through some hardships♫
He protected me and comforted me.
♫Only then can you face disappointments♫
Tell me.
Is he my angel?
♫Don't be afraid of these annoying things♫
♫They are gone with the wind♫
♫When I got close to my previous dream♫
Since
♫I tamed my youthful indiscretion♫
you take him as your angel,
♫Looking back at the silent rainy seasons♫
then why did you hide it from him?
♫Like daisies bloom secretly by the road♫
I didn't know how to say it.
I was afraid that if I had said
the name he hated,
he would have stayed away from me.
♫The Hall of Memories♫
♫The bell is ringing♫
♫The appearance of the latecomer♫
♫When I'm lonely♫
♫I raise my head and look up♫
If
♫Waiting for the rain to fall♫
you had been the one I lied to,
would you forgive me?
Actually.
I've already forgiven him.
Has he forgiven me?
Didn't he go home?
Lu...
She fell asleep.
Why is he Lu Yanzhi?
No one told him.
Thank you.
You came here in person
for such a trivial thing.
I saw you in the hospital every day,
but I was embarrassed to say hello to you.
Miss Tang is so lucky.
there are so many people who care about her.
When will she be discharged?
Tomorrow.
Okay.
Is there anything
that she needs to know about?
Recently...
Huang Yousu is Lu Yanzhi.
But why did he change his name?
Did I mistake him for someone else?
Right.
How could Huangfu Jue
take good care of me
so gently?
It's just my wishful thinking.
You have to be prepared
before peeling apples.
Wash the paring knife.
Wash the apple and dry it off.
And then,
peel a small piece
of the apple.
You need to pay attention to
the thickness of the peel,
it must be the same.
Next,
use your thumb to move the paring knife.
Why is it so hard?
Peel slowly
with the round surface of the apple.
You're still so cute.
Chubby Su.
I've made my decision
about the question you mentioned last night.
When we meet again,
we'll start over.
OK!
Chubby Su.
About the question you mentioned last night...
I know you like apples.
Do you prefer a hard one
or a soft one?
Anything is fine.
Actually,
I knew
you are Huang Yousu.
Whatever the Huang Yousu is,
the most important thing for you now
is to get well soon.
Nothing else matters.
Thank you
for taking care of me these days.
Don't be so polite.
But there's something
that I want to tell you.
We are just friends.
I have no right
or reason
to accept your help.
So I will
repay the favor.
Alright.
Let's not talk about this.
Eat the apple.
Thank you.
♫Do you believe it?♫
♫We spend our whole life just for our meeting♫
No matter how much I've done for you,
is  Lu Yanzhi
♫No matter how many scenes change♫
the first person that comes to mind?
♫No matter we are sad or happy♫
Do you like her?
♫No matter we have quarrels or peace♫
Yes.
Does she like you?
♫The simplest plots♫
♫The most memorable experience♫
Of course.
♫Don't be childish♫
♫It's time to make peace with the past♫
♫Even if we end up breaking up♫
How do you feel?
Have a try.
Can you see clearly?
I knew he wouldn't come.
Okay.
Don't get your eyes wet.
Get some rest.
Thank you, doctor.
You're welcome.
Why are you still here?
You'll be discharged today,
someone needs to be here.
They removed my gauze,
so I can handle it myself,
and take care of myself.
Okay.
Let's just get through today.
I'll take you home.
Let's go.
How do you feel? Are you feeling better?
Why should I
do as you say?
It's very simple.
First,
you need to win back
your reputation and popularity.
Second,
it's safer to keep your enemy close
than away.
Finally,
do you want to keep Lu Yanzhi?
Tell me.
What do you want me to do?
Chi Ye.
Can you drive faster?
It's too late.
We have to follow the traffic rules,
even if we're in a rush.
What time is it now?
You are telling me to obey the traffic rules.
Forget it.
You are unreliable.
I'm not counting on you, I'll do it myself.
Hello, madam.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm Miss Tang's friend.
What! Lu...
What?
What's going on?
Just leave me here.
Thank you for taking care of me these days.
I'll walk you home.
It's okay.
I can do it myself.
You just got out of the hospital.
Let me walk you home.
No need, I can do it.
Su.
I've recovered, and I'm really fine.
Let me walk you home.
I can do it myself.
Let me do it.
I will take care of her,
so there's no need to bother you.
Well...
Su, I'm sorry.
I'm late for picking you up.
It's okay.
Then...take care.
I'm leaving.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
Lu Yanzhi
has been taking care of you for a couple of days.
Is he up to something?
Is he
up to no good?
I think
you need to ignore him
even if he has good intentions.
He's breaking up
with his girlfriend
while he's eager
to please you.
He is a scumbag.
Can you stop nagging me about him?
At least he took care of me.
Unlike someone.
Someone
went to the hospital today.
No wonder
he was so angry today.
Did he meet Lu Yanzhi
in the hospital?
Impossible.
I haven't seen him for many days.
If he had met him,
he would have punched him
based on his personality.
Then what?
Are you not going to see him?
[Chi Ye]
Hello?
Are you interested
in Yu Mengmeng?
Spit it out!
Mengmeng announced that
she will call a press conference about apology.
What?
Someone is making trouble again.
She wants to call a press conference
and make a public apology to you.
And she wants you to be there.
The longest day has an end.
Do you think
that she will truly apologize to you?
Will she clarify the rumors
she spread about you?
Do you believe it?
Su.
What do you think?
I think...
If we're here, we will know
what she wants to do.
Good idea, Su.
You're indeed our captain.
Let's see
what Yu Mengmeng is up to.
I won't
be her cannon fodder this time.
I want to apologize
for my suicide.
I'm sorry for taking up your time.
From the allergy incident
to now,
I have suffered a lot of
malicious speculations and criticism.
But these
are not the reasons
for hurting myself.
Her acting skills have improved a lot.
If I didn't know
what happened,
I would trust her.
She is now
a perfect victim.
But she didn't mention a word
about the one
who was really hurt by this matter.
I'm waiting for her to mention me.
If she dares to
start another rumor about me,
I will confront her in person.
Tang Su has disappeared for so long.
But she stole your boyfriend as soon as she showed up.
Does it
hit you hard?
It has nothing to do with them.
Yanzhi is a very devoted person.
We
have the perfect relationship.
Then why do you
want Tang Su to be here today?
Please answer.
Because I want
to tell her that I'm sorry
in person.
Unfortunately,
she didn't come.
Su.
Although you didn't come,
I still want to say
that I'm sorry.
I've always
taken you as my closest friend.
I hope we can
keep the most precious
teammate relationship.
I can't stand it anymore.
So disgusting.
Let's leave.
Su.
You came.
I'm so happy
to see you here.
It is Su!
Su.
Did you hear
what I just said?
Can you forgive me?
Take the picture! take it! take it!
[After flirting with the CEO of Time Entertainment at a cocktail party, now Tang Su is back]
[Huangfu Jue and her former teammate Yu Mengmeng]
Do you remember this place?
Of course we do.
Yes.
This is our starting point.
Unfortunately,
we split up
right after we started.
Stop reminiscing.
Just tell us what you want.
Do you want to regroup Sweet Girls?
Do you think
I need you to regroup
with my current status and popularity?
I want to tell you,
it's the end of
your acting career.
Let's see where we started.
Do you still want to come back?
Wait.
Yu Mengmeng, what do you mean?
Yu Mengmeng.
I've never thought about
competing with you
from the very beginning.
Back then, everything I had
was made by myself,
step by step.
I have never wanted
your position.
But this time,
I'm afraid I'll let you down.
Since you are so afraid of me.
Let me tell you.
This time,
I won't back down again.
So, Yu Mengmeng.
You stand here
and see
how we take back
everything we lost?
Yu Mengmeng
has reacted so quickly.
Take Tang Su down with her,
and face this together.
Even if she can't clear herself,
Tang Su will be getting lambasted with her.
Yu Mengmeng couldn't be
the one who came up with this idea.
If I'm not mistaken,
it should be Luo Shi who is behind her.
Whether the two artists
are innocent or vilified,
Leo Culture will gain
all the data and clout.
It's his style.
Boss,  are you...
Are you really going to give up on Tang Su?
If
Tang Su comes back to find Luo Shi again,
can you just ignore it?
How could
someone be so stupid?
Mr Luo.
Mr Luo!
Please give me another chance.
I can let you come back,
but you have to understand that
our company won't give you the job opportunities
like before.
I understand.
I'm willing to start over.