[English subtitles are available]
[Taste of Love]
[Episode 16]
[Different Us]
Are you done reading?
What do you think about it?
The story is not bad.
So, you've decided to invest in it?
You can discuss the details
with my assistant
later.
I myself
have a few questions.
Please feel free to ask.
Regarding the guest actress
of this drama series,
does she
have any kissing scenes?
I don't think so.
Then, how about scenes like
jumping out of a car, falling off a cliff,
or falling into the water?
Don't worry.
We won't let actors
without specialized training take a risk.
Good. You are very professional.
You flatter us.
Okay.
Do you
have any other questions?
Not yet.
I'll let you know if I do.
Okay.
By the way,
can she ask for leave of absence
during the filming process?
Of course.
When would you like it to be?
I'll tell you when I've made up my mind.
Okay.
[Add more scenes for Miss Tang. No kissing scenes]
[No diving, jumping out of a car, or jumping off a cliff]
[I'll tell you when I've made up my mind]
He will tell me when he has made up his mind.
What?
No.
I'm not doing it.
Absolutely impossible.
What do you mean?
Listen.
You girls were in tune with each other
even when you rejected the idea.
So, I think it's very appropriate
to reassemble SURAGR GIRL.
What?
Have you forgotten about
your current
work performance?
Tang Su.
You are merely playing a role
who gets some extra scenes.
Do you think you can make a comeback
with this role?
Also, think carefully about
whether or not
you have any good opportunities
on hand?
Do you think you can rely on this role
for the rest of your life?
Yu Mengmeng.
Yes.
You're very popular now.
But I can tell you,
Tang Su's scenes
have outnumbered yours.
I also need to remind you
that the advertisers
have already removed your endorsements
because of the incident before.
What does that mean?
Why do you stop when it comes to me?
What can I talk about you?
You're a rich young lady.
You've never had any job opportunities.
What do you want me to say?
Let me reiterate.
It's not that I am forcing you
to reassemble SURAGR GIRL
but that reassembling is the only thing
we can do now.
The conflict between you girls is not important.
What's the most important is your personal career development.
Do you understand, ladies?
You didn't say such nice words
when we disbanded back then.
What prospect?
What conflict?
Go play on your own.
Su, let's go.
Why are you still here?
I'll go then?
Lu Yanzhi made a statement.
But he didn't do it
through the official channel.
He posted it using his own account.
I know that you have many questions
that you want to ask.
I'll take this opportunity
to explain to you.
First,
Tang Su and I never started a relationship before,
so there wouldn't be an end either.
We will be friends
forever.
Also,
I announce
that my love relationship with Yu Mengmeng
is completely over.
We didn't confess to the public before
because we wanted to maintain our respective privacy.
I would like to apologize to all those
who care about us.
Sorry.
He's usually dispirited
but he's unequivocal at the critical moment.
Should we do anything
in response to this statement?
Not yet.
Let's see how Leo would react.
Is the clarification conference all set?
Yes.
The live stream will start at three o'clock on time.
Su, what do you think about this?
Not bad.
Right?
What are you looking at?
Huangfu Jue asked me to watch a live stream
at three o'clock.
What live stream?
He didn't make it clear.
So secretive.
Let him be secretive on his own.
We will just focus on our shopping.
Look.
Those two people over there
seem to be celebrities.
Yes.
They seem to be SURAGR GIRL?
Yes…
Su.
Did you hear that?
Celebrities.
After all,
we are quite popular.
That one is Tang Su.
There seems to be quite a few trending topics related to her recently.
The other one…
I can't remember the other one.
What's her name?
She must be a has-been for too long.
I can't call to mind her name.
Wu.
This bag…
I have a black one at home.
I think I can buy another one that is white.
This one is okay too.
I'll take it.
Let's go, Su.
I'll take all of these.
Okay.
It's quite expensive.
Excuse me.
Do you have another card?
What's going on?
It doesn't work either.
She's really an unpopular celebrity.
She can't even afford the new clothes.
Hello. Please try this one.
Okay.
Sorry.
Use mine.
Okay.
Wu!
Wu.
Wu, are you okay?
Mrs. Tong intentionally
froze my card
just to force me to go back.
Su,
I'm sorry.
I'll pay you back later.
How am I going to pay you back?
I have no money to pay you back now.
What are you talking about?
You helped me so much.
Don't treat me as an outsider now.
Alright. Don't think so much about it.
She is your mother,
not your enemy.
Auntie froze your cards
only because she wants you
to go back to her.
She forced you to go on blind dates
but she is not
as snobbish as we thought.
Maybe she just wants to find someone
who is reliable
and able to take care of you
so that you can continue your life
as a rich young lady
and don't need to worry about anything.
After all, she loves you,
and she's doing it for your own good.
What you said
seems to make sense.
Let me think about it then.
By the way, what time is it?
I forgot all about the live stream at three.
Hurry up.
Follow me.
Tang Su
could have had a promising future,
but because of me,
she has been misunderstood by everyone for so long.
Today,
I will recount to everyone thoroughly
how the incident
happened on that day.
On the day of the incident,
Tang Su did go to the room of the hotel
where my crew stayed.
But we were only
talking about the script in the room.
After that, she left.
Our talk
didn't last longer than 30 minutes at most.
But someone captured
that you and Tang Su
left the hotel together on the next day.
It wasn't Tang Su who was captured in the photo.
It was her, my wife.
So, this is the live stream
that Huangfu Jue
asked me to watch.
Great!
Here it is finally.
Why didn't you
clarify the situation back then?
At that time,
the photo provoked much discussion
after being exposed
and were taken out of context.
For some reason,
we couldn't make our relationship public either.
So,
I'm sorry that I had to be unfair
to Miss Tang Su then.
Wu is immature.
Jue, are you immature too?
Even if it's like what you said,
it was your girlfriend who took her in,
that is not okay either.
Do you know what impact it will make if this gets out?
Auntie,
I understand
what you mean.
Then, you are here today…
I'm here today
to take Wu home.
Mrs. Tong,
whether Wu leaves or stays,
she should follow her own will, right?
This is the affair of the Tong family.
We don't need outsiders to interfere in it.
We are home.
Su, stop watching.
You've been watching it all day.
Stop watching.
I'm excited.
It's been a long time
since I've encountered something so refreshing.
I can finally get my own back.
Do you really think
that you are her boyfriend?
My mom?
You froze my cards, I can let it go.
But you even come here today
to humiliate Chi Ye.
Mrs. Tong, you've gone too far.
Wu.
Mrs. Tong?
You are really
getting more and more unruly.
You didn't even call me "Mother"
but you sided with him as soon as you came in.
I am unruly?
You are making a scene in someone's house.
Are you behaving yourself?
Go home.
I'm not going back.
-I'm not going back. -Auntie.
Wu!
Wu.
Stop being so willful.
You think you've grown up.
But don't forget,
you are still
under my protection.
Without me…
How are you going to live without me?
Can you make money?
Can you sustain yourself?
Our bossy CEO
is cooking personally today?
There's a happy thing happening
for our superstar today.
Of course I have to help her
with the celebration.
I want to ask you a question.
How did you
find the director?
Don't ask about this.
Just tell me.
The CEO has his own way.
How do I wash this?
Do I need to peel it before washing it?
Or can I just directly wash it?
Come home with me.
Stop being willful.
You are
a little flower
in the greenhouse.
You simply can't live on
without others' support.
So, I'm such a good-for-nothing
in your heart.
I'm telling you.
Even if I can't live on,
I won't go home with you.
Wu!
Wu! Wu!
Calm down, Wu.
Sorry.
Leave me alone.
Wu!
Look at this one.
Fried eggs with persimmons. What do you think?
I can't guarantee anything else,
but at least it's fully cooked for sure.
What's wrong?
I'm grateful
for everything you did for me.
But
why did you make everything easier for me
even when it was about my work?
What are you talking about?
You invested in Love and Espionage, right?
It was the producer
who called just now.
Your phone is ringing.
Answer it for me.
Hello?
Isn't it normal for me
to invest in a drama series?
So, if I'm suddenly asked
to go back for filming,
or whether I can take leave of absence,
it's all up to you.
If you want to add more scenes for me,
you can just add them.
If you want to change my scenes, you can just change them.
I didn’t.
By the way,
can she ask for leave of absence
during the filming process?
Of course.
When would you like it to be?
I'll tell you when I've made up my mind.
Okay.
The producer
misunderstood me.
Huangfu Jue, you know about me.
I would rather be a benchwarmer
than be considered an eye candy
or a person relying on connections.
All right.
I know.
Let me explain.
Don't explain.
I need to draw up a three-point covenant with you.
First,
don't shadow me.
It was the producer who wanted to…
Second,
don't practice jobbery.
He misunderstood me.
Third,
don't interfere in my work.
I won't agree then.
Why not?
Because I still have your contract.
I'm speechless.
Did I do anything wrong?
Wu.
Why are you here?
Su.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying here?
What happened?
Don't cry.
Did you quarrel
with your mom again?
She…
She often disregards others' feelings,
but…
but I think she was right.
I'm just a parasite.
I became an artist.
I ran away from home.
It was all because
I wanted to prove myself.
But in the end,
I proved
that I'm a good-for-nothing.
No.
Wu.
Do you still remember
what we used to be like
on stage?
At that time,
we were charming
and shining.
We were
never afraid of anything.
Stop it. Let's go back.
Come. Hurry up.
They are already off duty.
Let's go.
Wait for me.
Wu.
This is the most exciting moment
of our award ceremony today.
Next,
let me announce for you
the Best Female Artist—
the visual center of SURAGR GIRL,
Miss Tang Su.
Thank you, Father, Mother,
and my friends,
for supporting and accompanying me.
I made every effort
offstage
to give my best performance onstage.
I know
I'm really not perfect.
I also know
that there might be a lot of regrets.
But I believe,
as long as I stand on tiptoes,
I will definitely
be able to touch the brightest star.
Well said.
That's already in the past.
It's
as ephemeral
as a meteor.
No one will
remember us from the past.
If that's the case,
I would really be the one who is a good-for-nothing.
Su,
how can you say that about yourself?
You are the best
in my heart.
What's wrong?
I have always thought
that I earned everything I have now
through my own efforts.
But actually, I found that every step I took
wouldn't have been possible
without the help of Huangfu Jue.
So I tried my best
to prove myself.
But I still found
that I can't do anything well
without him.
Can we still go back?
I want to give it a try.
You mean
you want to accept Luo Shi's suggestion?
Maybe
reassembling is the best choice
for us.
Wu, look.
We once fell over there.
Then we need to get up from there.
There shouldn't be only sweat
under the spotlight,
but also our glory.
Wu.
Let's say goodbye to the past together.
Next,
let's welcome the award winners.
They will perform their award-winning song,
"Girls' Declaration."
Please.
♫No matter how many fairy tales and fables we read, it's not as good as an adventure♫
♫Start a new chapter, it's time to say goodbye to yesterday♫
♫We clearly know the jungle is too beautiful yet too dangerous♫
We are the most beautiful.
The most beautiful.
♫But who can live in a paradise forever?♫
Let's do a body wave.
♫If you want to touch the starry sky, you have to stand on tiptoes♫
A body wave.
♫Youth is about being crazy and burning energy for our dreams♫
Here comes the chorus.
♫Even for only a moment♫
Okay.
Chorus, chorus, chorus.
Wait, wait, wait.
♫Be like the sunflowers and embrace fervor♫
♫Be like the thorn birds and forget about fatigue♫
[SURAGR GIRL]
♫Be like the clownfish and explore the new world♫
[SURAGR GIRL officially reassembled]
♫Be like the swallowtails and wait to break out of the cocoon♫
Hello, Chubby Su.
The company has arranged an ad hoc event.
So I won't be able to have a meal with you.
Remember our three-point covenant?
Okay.
I need to go and get ready.
Thank you everyone
for coming to our launch event today!
First,
please greet the enthusiastic fans
and the press and media present here.
Friends from the press and media,
hello.
Although you might
have already known us,
I still
have to reintroduce our group members.
I'm Sunny, Yu Mengmeng.
This is Sugar, Tong Yiwu.
This is Tang Su.
We are SURAGR GIRL.
First of all,
we would like to thank SURAGR GIRL
for coming to today's launch event
for our brand's
latest skin whitening product series.
How about starting
with the three of you sharing with us
if you have learned anything
from your experience of skin whitening?
My usual beauty tips
-are that… -You have that many dark pasts.
Do you think it's appropriate
for you to be here now?
How could you say that?
Tang Su, you can go on. Leave her alone.
This friend from the media,
you are right.
I, Tang Su,
do have many dark spots.
The reason why
I'm qualified to be here today
is that I'm dark enough.
That's how we can prove
that this brand new
skin whitening product
is remarkably effective.
Great.
That's why
I can be so confident
about my dazzling white skin.
Well said!
Great!