[English subtitles are available]
[Taste of Love]
[Episode 6]
[The truth is out]
Don't
take things too seriously.
I always get myself in trouble.
How could I be protected by someone?
Here
is today's entertainment news.
Idol singer Yu Mengmeng
has been rushed to the hospital,
because of an accident during a variety show.
As you can see,
Huangfu Jue, the CEO of Time Entertainment,
escorted Yu Mengmeng to the hospital.
He has been with her
all the way.
According to reliable information,
this accident
may be related to a food allergy.
The whole incident is a mystery.
-An allergy? -It's said that
this is related to the maid
of Huangfu Jue, the CEO of Time Entertainment.
An allergy again?
Mengmeng,
I recommended you to the director.
So you gotta impress him later.
In this way,
we can act together.
Allergy medicine!
Let's go to the hospital.
Su.
I might not be able to
see the director.
Why don't you go first?
No, I'll take you to the hospital first.
You just go.
I don't want to waste your time.
Then...
Go.
Are you really okay by yourself?
Yes.
You stay here.
I'll be down soon.
Be careful.
Was Mengmeng behind all this?
But why did she
do this to me?
I've always treated her
as my close friend.
Have a good rest.
Thank you, nurse.
We will pay
for all the treatment fees.
Miss Yu.
Rest assured to recuperate here.
Rest assured?
Before we came to do the variety show,
we had told you many times
that Mengmeng is allergic to peanuts.
There should not be any products with peanuts.
How did you arrange it?
Now...
Mr. Huangfu.
We're not being unreasonable.
It has already
had a serious effect on Miss Mengmeng.
You must
give us an explanation.
After we find out the truth,
we will give you
a reasonable explanation.
Why do you investigate?
All the dishes
were made by the chubby assistant.
It must be her.
I don't think she did it on purpose.
How about apologizing?
Miss Mengmeng,
you are kind,
but it doesn't mean others are kind too.
Besides,
this has affected
your health and work.
They must apologize
in front of the media.
Calm down.
I believe Mr. Huangfu
will handle it impartially.
We haven't found out the truth yet.
It's still too early
to say this.
Mengmeng,
have a good rest,
we're leaving.
Mr. Huangfu.
If I put you in a difficult position,
it's totally okay.
This will go no further.
Don't worry.
I will give you an explanation.
Please,
please ask your assistant
to help us cook this.
Why do you investigate?
All the dishes
were made by the chubby assistant.
It must be her.
You must be hungry.
How is she?
Sit down.
Did you do it
today?
No.
You don't trust me?
I trust you.
You're hurt.
I'm fine.
Why?
Stop.
Zoom in.
Before we came to do the variety show,
we had told you many times
that Mengmeng is allergic to peanuts.
There should not be any products with peanuts.
Thank you.
It's ok.
Chubby Su.
I knew that I could ask you out
in the name of Lu Yanzhi.
Tang Su, it's been a long time.
Sorry, you have confused me with someone else.
Stop it.
I recognized you long ago.
Chubby Su.
[Tangsu, I knew you were innocent and who did this to you]
[I'll wait for you at Jiaoye Park, Lu Yanzhi.]
Since
you recognized me,
why didn't you tell them?
It wouldn't have come to this
if I had told them earlier.
Mengmeng, we love you.
Mengmeng.
I found it.
The person whom Lu Yanzhi has been looking for
is the maid of Huangfu Jue.
And this maid
is Tang Su.
I see.
So,
from the script scandal
to the food allergy,
you planned all of these things.
So what?
Mengmeng,
did I do something wrong
to you?
Why did you do these things?
I've always treated you
as my close friend.
Close friend?
We
have always only been competitors.
You thought you were kind,
conscientious and hard-working.
Have you ever thought
that I was the same as you?
But as long as you were here,
there was no place for me.
No matter how hard I tried,
I was always your green leaves.
You got all the job opportunities
and applause.
Now I want to show you,
in this world,
not everyone
lives the same life as you.
I didn't know
you hate me so much.
I don't hate you.
Only when you are out,
I can have my place.
You have always been so arrogant.
You thought you were helping me.
In fact,
you were reminding me
that I was not as good as you.
Mengmeng,
I recommended you to the director.
So you gotta impress him later.
In this way,
we can act together.
Allergy medicine!
You just go.
I don't want to waste your time.
Go.
Are you really okay by yourself?
Yes.
Be careful.
You always feel wronged.
Others should understand you.
But you never
care about others' feelings.
Sweet Girls came out
as a dark horse this year.
And you
are the most competitive girl group
among the popular groups.
How do you feel?
Thank our company
for the training and cultivation.
Thank
our fans and audiences very much
for your support and love.
I've tried
as hard as you,
or even harder than you.
But you have always gotten
more than me.
Seeing you give up yourself
like an underdog.
It
is so exciting.
Mr Luo, it's not like that.
I can explain it to the media.
The more you explain, the darker it gets.
What you need to do now
is to wait quietly.
The company will
help you solve the problem.
But I never
did such things.
-Why should I? -Su.
Let's calm down first.
Mr Luo,
please give me a chance.
I can explain it.
-That night, it wasn't… -Su.
-I didn't do that. -Calm down.
Su.
I have a reporter friend
who is very influential in the industry.
I'll ask her out
and you can do an interview to clarify the whole thing.
It might work.
Great!
But you have to promise
not to tell anyone
before the interview is released.
Okay, I promise you.
Thank you, Mengmeng.
Let's go.
I went to the director's room
to do the interview.
But Mengmeng and I
went together.
When
we arrived at the hotel,
-she suddenly felt uncomfortable. -Mr Luo.
I have some ideas about
the event this afternoon.
I think...
Why is Su here?
Mr Luo.
Why don't they trust me?
What the hell is this?
Stop looking at it.
Su, I'm sorry.
I've told Mr Luo
all the good words.
But he still decided
to stop all your work.
Just take it as a vacation.
Take a good rest.
Let's eat something
to distract your attention.
Mengmeng.
It's okay.
I'll always be with you.
I didn't expect
the former superstar
to become
so ugly.
But I didn't figure
that you came back.
You even found a sugar daddy,
Huangfu Jue.
Instead of saying that I'm cruel,
it's better to say you're smart.
Do you think everyone
is like you?
I did all these things for the life I wanted.
So what?
Listen.
No matter how much
Huangfu Jue protects you now.
As long as I
crook my finger,
-He will do whatever I say. -Stop it.
The past
doesn't matter.
From now on,
get out of my life!
You're so amazing.
Should I applaud you?
You won't be laughing
in five minutes.
What...what do you mean?
Soon,
your ugly appearance
will be exposed in public.
Let everyone see
the glorious superstar
has become
an ugly girl.
Stop!
She hit me first.
Apologize.
Why should I apologize?
Do you hear him?
Apologize!
I want you to apologize to her.
Me?
Before we find out the truth,
you framed her publicly.
Please apologize to her.
But she is the most suspicious.
Was she the only one who touched the dishes?
You were there too.
You know
who is the victim.
That's it.
Otherwise,
you'll be the only one to be destroyed.
Let's go.
Stop!
What?
Do you want me to ask these reporters
back?
I'm afraid you got slapped for nothing.
I don't care
about what happened between you two.
Please remember.
Stop pestering her.
She's mine.
Let's go.
Why are you here?
To save a fatty.
I didn't expect
him to come to save me.
To save a fatty?
Maybe Mengmeng
is right about one thing.
No one cares
about the disappearance of the star, Tang Su.
But they will care
that she becomes
an ugly fatty.
Maybe I can go back to the way I used to be.
For myself,
and...
Was I
childish before?
Not just you.
Tell me.
Why did people change so much?
I used to think she was so wonderful.
But now...
So you don't like her anymore?
Don't think too much.
Look.
That star
is Cygnus,
which only appears in summer.
It's
two hundred and thirty light years away from earth..
It's shining in the dark.
You can imagine
all its brilliance and beauty.
But that's not true.
Yes.
It takes ten thousand years
for the light's image
to be seen.
So what we see now
is just the past image.
To be exact,
just like
the beauty with your love.
To you,
Yu Mengmeng is like the Cygnus in the sky.
She is far way,
beautiful,
but not real.
Maybe
you don't like the person,
but the beautiful feelings
that she gave you.
Once you close the distance
and know the truth,
the beautiful feelings
will vanish.
You're right.
Saying goodbye to my past.
To our past.
Actually,
everyone
doesn't know themselves clearly sometimes,
whether in life
or in love.
Love?
But I haven't
known what love is.
What love is.
The love
is
that there's someone
who can make you worry.
Your happiness
comes from her.
You sadness
is caused by her.
You saw her
with other men,
you get jealous and angry.
You'll become very selfish,
ang you don't want anyone to bully her.
You want to protect her wholeheartedly,
and treat her
as your private property.
Chubby Su,
I'm curious
about what kind of person you are.
I don't know why,
when you're with me,
I feel at ease.
If you are happy,
I'm happy too.
If someone wants to bully you,
I want to rush up to protect you.
Maybe
I have someone in my heart.
Everything has changed.
Look.
The moon is so beautiful tonight.
Let's move a little bit.
♫Can we depict ourselves in the story♫
I'll teach you how to dance.
Come on.
Come.
♫With the tone of our first encounter?♫
One, two,
three, four,
♫Interesting souls with the equally sincere gaze♫
five, six,
seven, eight.
♫Let time freeze and be made a negative for us to keep♫
Stretch.
Close.
♫You tolerate my willfulness, I understand your annoyance♫
♫Nobody's love can be perfect♫
♫Two hearts are enriched because of each other♫
♫Is it tacit understanding or trust?♫
♫The most beloved, the dearly beloved♫
♫For whom do you keep your naïvety♫
♫Learn to be grateful in laughter and tears♫
♫The happiest person, the lucky person♫
♫Is also a brave person♫
♫Bravely chase and seize the fate that is slipping away♫
Chubby Su,
It's good to have you.
Actually,
♫You tolerate my willfulness, I understand your annoyance♫
I have something
to tell you.
♫Nobody's love can be perfect♫
I really made up my mind
to tell you.
♫Two hearts are enriched because of each other♫
Actually I'm not Chubby Su.
♫Is it tacit understanding or trust?♫
I'm the Tang Su whom you hated the most.
♫The most beloved, the dearly beloved♫
♫For whom do you keep your naïvety♫
I know you don't want to talk now,
♫Learn to be grateful in laughter and tears♫
because you are shocked and angry.
♫The happiest person, the lucky person♫
But
I didn't mean
to hide it from you.
♫Is also a brave person♫
I want to
♫Bravely chase and seize the fate that is slipping away♫
find a proper time.
I don't want to keep lying to you
♫Even if our love is not as deep as the sea♫
I really...
♫It takes root in every inch of my heart♫
♫To my beloved♫
♫Who has accompanied me through my youth♫