(The first full meeting)
We're back.
The new guest is here.
What do you think
about the new guy?
Not telling you.
Feels like it's almost over.
They could all be your type.
I value how we get along.
If it's one-sided, you'd let it go.
It'll be exhausted.
I've never felt
such tension before.
=Live and Love S2=
=We're on Balance Island=
(Day 2 of the secret date)
Did you sleep well last night?
Not bad.
I passed out instantly.
You had to wake up early.
Maybe we can go back earlier at night.
Yeah.
Let me see your hand.
Not bad.
What about this side?
Much better now.
Yeah, it's better.
Let's eat.
Go ahead. Let's go.
(Happy)
(A hearty breakfast)
Foodies again.
How nice.
So nutritious.
Look at all this fruit.
(Eats enthusiastically)
What kind of bun is this?
This one is...
Savory.
Is it BBQ pork?
BBQ pork bun.
So lucky.
Is the food on the island so good?
(Silent)
Just okay?
Well.
I haven't been on the island much.
(Barely stayed)
I asked the wrong person.
Yeah.
I'll ask someone else later.
I got "banished".
Looking forward to anything?
First thing you wanna do?
No idea.
I think once we get there,
they'll have
another task for us.
There might be a game at once.
Yeah.
A game.
I wanna play a game.
But I'm a little nervous.
It might be...
Intense?
Yeah, intense.
I don't think so.
When girls play games,
it's usually pretty chill.
Love and peace.
Exactly.
It's just you guys.
Yeah, tense for guys.
What's your favorite food?
I love hot pot.
Hot pot?
What kind of hot pot?
Sichuan hot pot.
Spicy?
What about numbing?
I can eat it, just not my favorite.
It's a normal extent.
Thanks.
This sunshine feels great.
Yeah.
It's so bright.
Let's sit here.
Thanks.
(Facing the sun)
Too bright for you?
It's dazzling, right?
I can barely open my eyes.
You should wear shades later.
Yeah.
It's dazzling.
Seriously.
Well.
Last night,
did you sleep well?
Honestly, not really.
How about you?
Pretty well.
I fell asleep once I got back.
You said you've been here before.
Did you ever eat here?
Nope.
Not even once?
No.
But it's gorgeous here.
Did you notice?
Yeah.
That sea over there.
As I told you, it's stunning.
That round spot.
It's a check-in spot at the hotel.
Have you checked in there?
No.
I sat on one of the lounge chairs
and took some photos.
Here they come.
I'm seriously starving.
Me too.
Thanks.
Do you eat a lot in the morning?
Yeah, I eat a lot
for breakfast.
Since you work out,
I guess you like eggs.
I love eggs.
Ten a day.
(That many!)
What?
Ten a day.
Ten eggs a day?
Seriously?
Yep.
Boiled or fried?
Or sunny-side up?
Mostly sunny-side up.
I don't eat that many in one meal.
Well.
Yeah.
Three meals in total.
Have you tried salted duck eggs?
Yeah, the kind you have with congee,
right?
Exactly.
Do you like it?
I actually like it.
I'm from Yangzhou.
If we have congee in the morning,
we pair it with salted duck eggs.
What about century egg?
Century egg?
I like it too.
Me too.
During the Chinese New Year holiday,
we usually serve cold dishes,
including century eggs.
Century egg with tofu.
We serve the century egg straight.
With a slightly dry texture.
Have you been to Yangzhou?
I don't think so.
Nope.
I should go sometime.
Any special snacks?
Have you heard of Yangzhou fried rice?
Yeah.
What else?
Any other specialties?
Local snacks.
Crab roe soup dumplings.
That kind.
(Gestures)
So big.
Is that for one person or...?
Yep, single serving.
It's kind of flat in shape.
You mean like a pancake?
It's not upright.
Aren't you scared of butterflies?
It's really pretty.
That butterfly.
When you eat that,
they'll give you a straw.
You poke a little hole
and then sip out
the crab roe soup inside.
Drink it before you eat it.
Right.
You like quite a lot of foods.
Yeah.
You're such a foodie.
You think I'm like a foodie?
Sounds like it.
So much bread.
Do you like carbs?
I love carbs so much.
(Loves carbs)
You love carbs?
Carb hero.
Rice is my favorite.
Rice.
We're meeting them in a bit.
(Feeling uneasy)
Are you nervous?
A little.
Don't be.
You'll have to introduce me.
Of course.
Maybe we'll have games today.
There will surely be.
What are you good at?
How about running?
You'll need to sprint.
I can do that.
When you were kids,
did they time your 50-m sprint
in seconds?
What was your time?
Do you still remember?
Ours was 100.
Both 50 and 100 for us.
In primary school, I was slow.
14 s, if I remember right.
14 s?
I don't remember my time exactly.
Not sure if it was
the 50-m sprint
or some other distance.
I ran it in just over 8 s.
It must've been the 50-m sprint.
That's pretty fast.
Are there any games you're scared of,
if we have to play later?
I'm scared of water.
Anything else? Balance?
A little bit.
I'm not great
at pulling things.
I'm not that strong.
If you work out,
your arm strength must be solid.
Not bad.
Can you do that?
Pull-up.
With assistance.
I can if it's assisted.
If you ask me to just grab it,
I can't do it on my own.
You can totally do it.
Yeah, I can.
The sky is so blue today.
Seriously?
These days,
the sky was all gray.
The sun seemed to have dipped a little.
Do you feel that?
(Feeling it)
Just a little.
Not so dazzling.
Do you like daytime or nighttime better?
Nighttime.
Because the sun's not strong at night?
Do you like going on island vacations?
Do you enjoy traveling in general?
Yeah, I love traveling.
Me too.
I've always wanted to come to Sanya.
Perfect.
You're here now.
I think it's nice.
So, we've got to take a walk
along the sea.
We're leaving here
in just a bit.
True.
Are you done?
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Seriously.
So cozy.
Yeah, I think so.
This is their famous white sand beach.
It looks different in the daytime.
Pretty, right?
Yeah.
Do you feel like touching the water?
I do.
Wanna give it a try?
Let me see if it's cold.
Let me see.
Just a light touch.
Wait.
It won't get me wet, right?
I don't think so.
Wait for it.
I'm touching it.
Not cold.
Wow, it's not cold.
Right?
It's warm; the sun's blazing.
That sound is so calming.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
That's awesome.
Look at them.
I wanna lie down here too.
Me too.
Very chill, right?
Wanna check it out?
What's this?
Let's watch it.
I wanna see.
Anything cute for you?
This one's adorable.
It's wearing a hat.
I think you like white.
Like your...
Like our family dog.
With hats, they look alike.
Ultraman.
Did you like Ultraman as a kid?
Not really.
Not really?
What did you like?
I loved Crayon Shin-chan.
Me too.
Let me tell you something.
I'm gonna do
a Crayon Shin-chan impression.
Can you do that?
Do you want to hear it?
Sure.
Don't laugh.
(Focused and waiting)
Hang on a sec.
Let me get into character.
Misae, you're back!
Let's go.
That was hilarious.
I've started doing
Shin-chan's voice now.
Sounds about right.
Doesn't it?
Yeah.
Don't do that again.
Don't do that again?
Did it work?
What?
I haven't tried it.
Not yet?
It got too late last night.
(Day 2 night, a foot bath basin)
You fell into water today.
You'll need this.
Thanks.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
More oil.
This is our guys' territory.
I'll handle the fire and cooking.
Sure.
This pot's got a name.
What name?
Look, it says here:
75869752.
Nice name.
(Big applause)
Later,
I'll have name like that.
What if you forget me?
Think about what it's called.
It's called...
75869752.
Sorry.
It's fine.
I seemed to have touched you.
Do it a few more times.
I don't know how to respond to that.
It's fine, no need to respond.
That's awkward.
(So sweet)
75869752.
I've memorized it now.
Good.
Will you remember me?
Yeah.
Your name is...
Feels like that pancake.
Not bad.
Why did they all head out?
Let's step outside.
Is that high enough?
A bit higher.
Alright, I'll push harder.
Okay, perfect.
Thanks.
What game will it be today?
Will we team up today?
No idea.
We didn't team up the past two days.
I've been thinking about it.
There's definitely
gonna be newcomers.
I think so.
What are you talking about?
(Request to join)
Someone new.
Our talk?
It's about little secrets.
You went all in, right?
(Center of attention)
You went all in?
Yeah.
(Firmly)
You've made a choice so early.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Listen.
Before yesterday's date,
he didn't really show much.
You'll notice
that before yesterday's date,
he barely talked to her.
Yeah.
When the date happened,
I felt it was a chance
for him to express himself.
Once he says it out loud,
he'll start getting closer.
Well.
I'm not exactly afraid
of a crowd.
Most of the time,
I prefer
one-on-one chats.
How did that conversation go?
Pretty good.
We talked a lot.
Got a lot out of it?
Yeah.
(So sweet)
A question for you.
Are you feeling unsure now?
Today?
Yeah.
Not at all.
Still not?
Let's wait until after today.
I'll always have your back.
Just go for it.
Is this real?
(Whether the branch is real)
I think it's fake.
Do you think it just fell there,
or is it a prop?
A prop.
It was made
just for you.
For me?
Yeah.
Only you would play
with this thing.
Do you think I'm childish?
I think you're cute.
You're cute.
(Cheered up)
Right?
Such a fancy life.
I'm not used to this.
(Fancy, cute)
Too fancy.
You should be fancy too.
Do you have any fancy clothes?
(I do)
Yeah.
I have them.
(I think...)
On your fancy day,
I'll be ordinary.
I'll "shoot" them all.
Indifferent.
This spot is perfect
for...
Paintball.
(Paintball?)
Doesn't it splash color?
Paintball guns are high-end.
They have laser sights.
You'll have a laser point on you.
Once you're hit, you're out.
I need to hide, right?
I need to hide.
Listen.
If we team up for this game,
we won't lose.
(Mark my words)
I'll be in front of you.
No one's getting past me.
(Winning by size advantage)
True.
I'll stay behind you.
Exactly.
We'd be perfect at playing
eagle and chicks.
What?
Yeah, true.
We'd still be tough to beat.
Then you'll be the eagle.
(Rivals now?)
Me? The eagle?
Yeah.
(Is this the eagle?)
The eagle's supposed to catch.
Then what will you be?
I'll be the lead chick.
(The one looking out for you)
Mother hen.
Are you afraid of elimination?
Of course.
But I also think it's okay.
Ideally, it should be mutual affection.
If not, we shouldn't settle.
Why did you get the most votes?
Well, maybe
I talk a lot.
They see me as cheerful,
so they give me some weights.
It's a casual choice.
After they picked a guy they liked,
they'd wonder
where the last weight could go.
They couldn't go all in,
so they gave it to me.
That's how I see it.
Not necessarily.
Really?
I don't care about the weights
of the other girls.
I'm pretty curious about yours.
How did you guys guess?
Not telling you that.
Let's wait for the final reveal.
Alright.
(Homely boyfriend)
Why are you always here?
Is that right?
A fixed position for you.
Seriously?
Yeah.
I don't think so.
You were here yesterday.
The same.
The sink was also clogged.
(The previous night)
Do you need help?
No, we can handle it ourselves.
It's clogged.
(Same spot, same people)
Same thing today.
Exactly.
Felt like déjà vu.
Déjà vu.
You're honestly so good
at housework, right?
Just look at the way he does it.
Yeah.
I like things neat and tidy.
Bonus points.
(Points, points)
See?
(Clean and tidy)
You're so considerate.
We haven't cleaned this up.
I meant to tell you something yesterday.
But I went to do an interview.
What is it?
Go ahead.
Based on my first impression
of you,
plus your Beijing accent,
I figured you might be hard
to get along with.
You can call me Michael.
My Chinese name is Zhang Zizheng.
I made two dishes.
That was my thought back then.
Seeing some
of the things you did yesterday
made me realize
first impressions aren't that accurate.
We need more time together
and go through a few things
to get to know each other.
Yeah.
Like what?
I don't know.
For example,
you took care of Huang.
He had a leg cramp yesterday.
A cramp?
Here, take this.
You helped him stretch it out.
When Yijia
fell in,
you rushed to save her.
That's when I felt
that your actions
show you're thoughtful
deep down,
not just pretending to be nice.
I can tell everything you did
came from the heart
and wasn't just for show.
Right.
I think that's what wins over the girls.
Not just me.
Really?
(Sincerity is the best move)
Yeah.
What you did
(Extra points!)
is so nice.
You changed my impression.
Thanks.
Yesterday, I also realized
you are
a sharp observer.
Really.
You're observant too.
That's why you know
what people need.
You bet on me yesterday.
I was touched.
Really.
Really?
As a girl who barely knows me,
you chose to trust me.
I think that is
pretty touching.
I made the right call.
You're amazing.
My hands are dirty.
Fist bump?
Okay.
Elbow bump.
(Looking)
Come and talk with me.
Sure.
Go ahead.
Let's go.
Where are they going?
She asked me to chat with her.
You two?
Zhao Enda had no clue.
Today,
I asked him
whether he'd feel awkward
if I could ask him out
on a date.
He said
a little.
He was worried about Yang.
Right.
He feared that putting him
in that position
would make him unable
to handle the situation.
But his perspective
is limited.
Still, he went all in.
It made me wonder
whether I've rushed into things.
Maybe I didn't handle it well.
I'll adjust a little.
Nice.
Looks good.
The flowers?
You're stunning.
Thank you.
It's just that feeling.
I don't want
to pressure him.
I'm regretting it.
If I stay quiet,
he might feel a bit lighter
and not overthink it.
Come on.
Help.
Do what you want
to do first.
Help.
I want to hear it.
Why not join us?
You've been talking a lot today.
I'm just curious.
Yeah, I have.
I just started getting to know everyone.
It happened so fast.
By the second day,
everyone seemed to have made
their final choice.
It seems to be coming to an end.
It's not final.
If someone went all in for another girl,
would you still hang out with him?
It depends on whether I like them.
If you like them, you'll reach out.
Of course.
I might think about it.
Seriously...
Is it good? It's burnt.
Honestly.
(Funny girl)
You're forcing it down.
I spotted the girls.
Hello.
We're back.
The new guest is here.
Back so soon?
Our new islander.
Welcome!
Let's take
a walk.
Come on.
Alright, tourists.
Follow me.
(Tour guide)
Let's go.
Showtime starts.
(Village chief on duty)
Where's our first stop?
The first stop...
The dorms.
The most important place.
Here.
Alright.
Okay.
Introduce yourself.
Guess where he's from.
Hi, I'm Zhang Zizheng.
From Beijing, right?
Northeast China.
Right, from Beijing.
You can call me Micheal.
Michael.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'll put it here.
Sure.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
(5 minutes earlier)
You have a little flower.
Yeah.
Do you want one?
Pascal.
Sure.
Where did you get that flower?
Stop picking.
We've picked two.
Just one last one.
Over there.
There?
Let me tell you.
You might not find it.
Someone wants it; she must have it.
Here.
The purple one.
Listen.
Let me pick
the most vibrant one.
Easy to wear.
It's got thorns.
It might prick her.
How about two?
Thanks.
What do you think of this island now?
It's like a village.
You image...
A village.
That's why he's the village chief.
(Village chief calling)
Come on.
We've gotta keep up.
We're going to check out the dorms.
Let's go over there.
She's probably sharing with Jiayi.
Alright, let's go.
Why are your eyes red?
Yeah, kinda dry.
You didn't sleep well?
No.
I've got eye drops.
I need them.
Super dry.
Why are you picking on me all day?
When did I pick on you?
(Playful tease)
How vulnerable.
You were harsh just now.
I was harsh?
What did I say?
You slammed the cup.
You said I was boring.
So harsh?
Yeah.
Really?
Sorry.
No need to apologize.
I could get hurt.
Then you got hurt.
Just a little hurt.
A guy taking a little hit is nothing.
Let me ask you.
What do you think of the new male guest?
Not telling you.
You like him?
Walk faster.
Hurry.
Alright.
Good.
Okay.
This should be your dorm.
You can take a look.
What's the code?
5185168.
Same for everyone.
Those numbers seem
to have stuck in my head.
5185168.
Who told you that on the first night?
He told me.
I was upstairs; you were downstairs.
You forgot the code.
I told you.
(First night)
Why is your door still locked?
I was trying to remember the code.
5185168.
518.
5168.
5185168.
Okay, I'm going in.
Good night.
You told me that day?
Our first day back.
Did you forget?
I didn't forget.
Okay.
(Fine)
I'm gonna change my shoes.
Do you need me?
Sure.
(This morning)
You're so tall today.
Oh, my gosh.
Can you not wear such high platforms?
You're making it hard for me.
We're not even
in the same frame.
They'll get you and my head.
Yesterday, you said you didn't have
any particular type you're into.
You just get along
and see how it goes.
After spending time together,
you start to catch feelings.
Yeah.
I feel like everyone could...
They can all become your ideal type.
Not exactly.
I value the vibe
when we're together.
When it comes to girls,
do you like gentle ones
or cool ones?
Cool girls are definitely not my pick.
I wanna get out.
Jump right in.
I said I wanna leave the island.
You have to be eliminated then.
There's a chance to leave in the game.
Do you work out regularly?
Of course.
(Clear muscles)
Definitely.
That's obvious.
I think your muscles are bigger than his.
Eight-pack abs.
Unfortunately,
we had a water activity yesterday.
If you had been there,
I could've seen it.
Come on, everyone.
Follow me.
A new tour guide.
I've never felt
such tension.
I didn't feel that at all.
I've been living
in my own world.
I'm not involved in that heated part.
My vote was pretty simple,
as you know.
So, I didn't feel any tension.
I'm talking
about a few specific people.
Yeah, certain individuals.
That stuff doesn't exist
in my world.
Same for mine.
What a coincidence.
Coincidence.
We're on the same page again.
Are my eyes still red?
Still red?
They're okay.
Don't wear those contact lenses.
Should I wear glasses?
Yeah, you look great in glasses.
Business style.
I saw you wearing glasses.
I thought you were new.
Your look leans more sporty.
So good.
You could go for a business vibe.
Sure, go change.
Alright, I'll go change.
You should look forward to this.
He'll be completely different.
Did you forget to button this?
That's just how it's meant to be.
You don't get it.
(I don't get it again)
Okay.
I don't get it again.
I don't get it.
Today, seriously.
Please,
stop picking on me.
Maybe I've always been like this.
I'm into it.
Falling for you.
Here comes the finance guy.
(Finance gentleman)
Not bad.
Totally different, right?
Once I put on a suit,
I'll look like an insurance salesman.
Look at my eyes.
Watch me take them off.
They actually shrink.
Yeah.
(After the game)
Let's do this.
This is hilarious.
They're making a feast.
(A wall)
This shot is fantastic.
So fantastic.
Fantastic.
(Gritting teeth)
The contrast.
Exactly.
It's so cruel.
Honestly, this is
the most unfair moment
I've ever experienced.
Friendship and love.
I'll make yours first.
Ladies first.
Instant noodles made like this
don't taste great.
I soak them first
and then drain the water.
Exactly.
Right?
Also, the egg.
If you want it soupy,
just add a little water.
(Serious)
Turn off the heat,
drop the egg in,
let it sit,
and stir it up. It'll be amazing.
It has that rich egg aroma.
That's how I made it.
I think it's fine.
It'll work.
We're learning
from the gourmet chef.
Learning how to make instant noodles.
Yeah.
We're learning.
(Learning)
Will it be thrown away?
(Some scraps)
Will you toss this?
(No, I'll eat it)
No.
Just give me one bite.
(Guests begging for food!)
I'm hungry.
Just one bite.
I'm hungry, too.
Eat more, then.
Here.
Next bite.
Come on.
(Jealous)
Right in front of me?
(Forced smile)
Sir,
that didn't go in the box.
Can I have a piece?
(Refuse 1)
Nope.
What about that herb?
(Refuse 2)
Nope.
Come on.
That's wasting food.
(Refuse 3)
No.
I'm still hungry.
Spare me one bite.
Begging for a bite.
(Refuse 4)
No, thanks.
I think it's ready.
Right?
That bowl's ready, right?
Go. It's for you.
Let's go.
Grab chopsticks.
We can start first.
We can start
eating a little.
(Wow)
It smells amazing.
This is so good.
Insanely good.
This is so delicious.
You should start a mukbang channel.
Thanks.
So immersive.
You'd be perfect for it.
It's basically your exclusive
mukbang shot.
So good.
Drop the link below.
People will surely buy it.
I'm telling you.
So tasty.
What is this?
Sir.
Chef.
Any comments on our meal?
You've got all.
A rich flavor.
A light flavour.
And mixed noodles.
Yeah.
Mixed noodles.
And soup noodles.
So abundant.
Truly abundant.
Full marks.
I barely ate, but I'm already full.
No idea why.
I just stole it.
Stole it?
You scared me.
What's this?
It's their dish.
The last dish.
I didn't know what it was.
It scared me.
What is that?
That fish.
While no one was watching,
I took a small piece of the dish,
hoping Jiayi would be happy.
So, I felt pretty good.
At least...
Though she lost the match,
I still managed to let her
taste that flavor.
Yeah.
("Live and Love" Release Schedule)
Such a special day.
(Xu Wenting, Wang Yutong, Wang Yiyanyu)
We have guests from S5–7
(Li Yujia)
of An Exciting Offer
(Wang Yunlin)
gathering here.
Welcome.
(Wow)
(Eye-opening)
That's my thing.
(Interested)
I'm so into this.
(Whoa)
(On Thu. 12 PM,)
I like this.
(watch Live and Love)
Me too.
I like this.
(Wow, wow)
(Loving this)
I love this type.
This is how it feels
to watch others fall in love.
(Blushing)
It's hot.
(Suspicious)
Is he in an idol drama?
Could this even work?
(Ridiculous)
Why would he do that?
(Trouble's coming)
This doesn't feel good.
(Loving this)
The love battlefield is great.
Are they gonna make it public?
(Anxious)
Tell me now.
I'm dying to know.
We've got to keep watching
Live and Love S2.
(Hurry and check it out~)