(New islanders, Sparks fly)
Surprise and shock.
Feel like my life was saved.
The brave ones get to enjoy life first.
Maybe in this life,
you're stuck with me.
Don't push too hard.
You don't believe me?
I do believe you.
Era Sisters.
Top Three Models of the Show.
Why do you think
every girl will go for Guanjie?
I think everyone
actually wants to talk to Guanjie.
=Live and Love S2=
=We're on Balance Island=
(Day 3)
The Book of Answers.
How do we play?
Think of a question in your mind.
Then open a random page.
That's your answer.
Will I win tomorrow?
Could be hard to resist.
What?
It means no.
Just the first three words.
"Could be."
(Irrelevant options cleared)
Selective memory, huh?
Only hearing what you want.
Okay, next one.
Who has a question?
I'll go.
(Can't wait)
You go.
Could I come home in love?
The answer is
"Let the excitement build."
I like this answer.
Very likely.
Let the excitement build.
Then let it build.
Michael.
Ask a question.
Ask a question?
Will the right person ever show up?
Set a date.
What does it mean?
It means she'll appear
once you set a date.
So it's a
date to confess your feelings.
(Curious)
What's that thick book?
The Book of Answers.
Ask it a question and
flip it.
Go on and ask.
Will I win tomorrow?
Same as my question!
Yeah.
(Chill out)
Don't push too hard.
That's a terrible answer.
Let me give it a try.
Do you think I can win tomorrow?
You're hoping something grand.
You're hoping for a grand win.
You're just hoping.
Yeah.
Let me try too.
Will I have a good meal tomorrow?
No logical explanation for this.
(Can't answer, just say no)
It's over.
Islanders,
in tonight's affection delivery,
the male and female islanders
with the fewest weights
will have to leave the show.
One male, one female.
Let's go back to our room.
Go.
So thrilling.
Leave the show.
That's harsh.
(Zhu Huiyan & Yang Tinghong's room)
I think you'll vote for Guanjie.
You totally would.
But I've got my own reasons.
Like if I were to…
If I split my vote, I'd get worried.
Yeah.
I want him to stay.
Yeah, definitely.
So don't split the votes too much.
Yijia will surely pick Guanjie.
Yijia?
Can't you tell?
Have they talked?
Shouldn't Yijia
vote for Michael?
Michael will get votes.
Guanjie will get too.
Jiaming will get votes from Huang.
Huang and Guanjie.
Why do you
think every girl will go for Guanjie?
Yeah, I think so.
Everyone may thinks he's handsome.
(Too into, too invested)
He really is.
If they
can't decide who to pick,
then they'll vote
for someone they think is nice.
And that person's gotta be Guanjie.
But how do you know
they think he's nice?
They...
I can tell.
You can tell.
I think everyone
actually wants to talk to Guanjie.
Maybe because you're
always by his side.
Yeah, I can feel that.
Seriously, I'm...
I'm seriously
exhausted from you today.
I can't even move an inch.
Yeah.
(During the afternoon game)
Let's go.
Yeah.
You went all out, right?
You didn't hold back, right?
I held back.
I didn't charge forward.
So you used about
ninety percent of your strength?
Yeah.
Thanks.
So you can still charge forward.
If go all-in,
I can.
But I'm not sure.
But I'm afraid
if I charge, I'll get carried away.
Because I can't
guarantee it.
I'm the type who plays it safe.
I don't dare take risks.
Never have,
even when I'm exercising.
I usually play it safe to ensure
the most
predictable outcome.
But,
you're not like this
in daily life, right?
A bit, actually.
(Liu Jiayi & Wu Yihan's room)
Yanting is sweet.
Yeah, I think so too.
That flower.
He seems more reliable.
Yeah.
I agree.
Just…
He's...
Tell you a small point.
He had jerky, right?
You were gone.
He was
talking to a boy.
And
Zhan wanted to eat it.
She asked, "Can I have some?"
He said, "Sure,
later."
But this bag
is saved for Jiayi.
(During dinner)
She asked what it was.
Beef jerky.
Can I eat it?
I'll get it for you later.
Okay?
This one's for Jiayi.
Like, if this...
I can imagine that.
If this bag of beef jerky
were with Jie,
since I've only met two guys here,
Jie and
that
Beijing boy,
I think they'd probably offer it.
All warm and friendly.
But
girls all like
that kind of...
Unique.
Preference.
Right.
What you just said
really touched me.
Comparing them like this,
yeah, I do feel
Yanting is a lot more reliable.
You know.
He's more suitable for everyday life.
And Xuan Cheng is good for dating.
Like having fun together.
He's perfect for that.
I agree.
But…
there are things he has
that Xuan Cheng doesn't.
Right.
And vice versa.
Honestly, I think
their personalities
are totally different.
Such a contrast.
Honestly,
you and Xuan Cheng
look really good
together.
I'm feeling a mix of
rational and emotional right now.
I think it's okay.
Yeah, I want to
see more.
It's still early.
Today's only Day 3.
(Day 4)
Morning.
Hello.
Aren't you cold?
Nope.
I actually brought a jacket.
Why not wear it?
I thought
the sun's out today,
so no need.
Hello.
Take photos?
Sure.
Taking pics.
Mind if I take some too?
Sure.
You can.
Angus.
Burger.
Alright.
Let's go together.
So sporty.
So beautiful.
Really beautiful.
You're all pretty.
So pretty.
You look amazing.
A gentle vibe today.
Earlier...
You were gentle too.
I laughed too loud.
Now you're being bold.
Yeah.
Are you catwalking, bro?
So cool, village chief.
Like this.
You look like you're walking a runway.
How about you two do another one?
Come on.
Take photos.
Really.
For real?
Let's take photos.
I'll take one for you guys.
We could start with...
Sounds good.
Take photos of each other.
Facing the sea, spring blossoms.
Morning.
Hello.
Meeting this early with everyone?
No, just taking photos.
Grab a Polaroid.
You help take the picture.
You take the photo.
Or maybe Tianyu can do it.
Come on, Tianyu.
I'll take great photos.
Zhang took the first three days' photos.
You don't trust me?
I do trust you.
I'll take photos of the four of you.
Just press the button when you see it.
Era Sisters.
One, two.
Three.
Thanks.
First shot.
Here, let me take yours.
Alright.
Do it together.
Hurry.
This works too.
Let's squat.
Right.
Boys squat below.
So happy, bestie.
One.
Two.
Three.
It should be good.
No wonder you're village chief.
Three.
Two.
One.
Top Three Models of the Show.
Hainan Fashion Week.
Come on.
Give me.
Great, thanks.
Should we go cook?
Sure.
I'm ready to eat.
I'm starving.
I'll make breakfast.
Scrambled eggs or something.
Sounds good.
Want some?
Sure, scrambled eggs with onions.
Alright.
So many onions.
Maybe… oh, I know.
Because I mentioned onions the other day.
So they brought extra.
What would you wish for?
Come on, make a wish.
Beef.
Beef, braised beef.
Shrimp.
Braised beef.
Sweet and sour spare ribs.
A wish first?
Braised pork.
Anything else?
Chicken wings.
Fish.
Fish is okay.
Fish is too hard to handle.
Let's pick another.
Abalone.
Shrimp and crab.
Steak.
We mentioned steak.
Shrimp meat.
Shrimp goes with eggs.
What do you want to eat, Guanjie?
Eggs.
You want eggs.
Just plain eggs?
Raw egg.
(Raw egg?)
No.
Fry it.
Fried egg.
(Stumbling with egg)
No egg? Where is it?
(Egg's right here)
What's the plan now?
Scrambled eggs with onions?
Yeah.
What else?
(Iris)
Iris says he wants a sunny-side up.
(Confused)
Who is Iris?
(Angus)
Angus, want some water?
Want some water?
Who is Angus?
No idea.
I never remember names.
What's my name then?
(Name-blank squad)
Yan.
Full name?
Zhu Huiyan.
Right.
Okay?
Yeah.
Got any toast or something?
Then maybe fry up an egg.
We've got corn.
We've got toast.
It's got veggies too.
We've got cheese, I love cheese.
Wait.
Why are the ingredients so fancy
now that you newbies are here?
Do we have cheese?
We do.
(The two frying eggs together)
Oh no, it's sticking to the pan.
Not enough oil, right?
It's burnt.
(Slightly burnt)
(Need a hand?)
(Seems okay though)
(Ready to go again)
(Completely black)
What happened?
I totally messed up an egg.
Did it burn?
It burned.
That's the real smell of burnt oil.
The heat was too high.
Turn it down a bit.
There's no...
I'm dying laughing. The pan's burnt.
It's fine.
This one is edible.
Let's give it another shot.
Come on.
(Full of energy)
I'll wash the pan.
(They refuse to give up)
Eighty degrees?
Let's go with 100.
(Cautious)
We can add.
Add it.
Lower it.
Lower, so it won't break.
Messed up.
It's fine.
Let's start with...
Let's just try not to burn it.
Yeah.
Not bad.
At least it kept a shape.
Right, it's square now.
(Super low standard)
And it matches the square...
It really fits our sandwich.
Because the sandwich is square too.
Perfect.
Pretty good.
Alright,
I think we can turn off the heat.
(That fast?)
Not yet.
Yeah, it's ready.
Nice job.
Don't be greedy.
Yeah.
(Standard: as long as it's edible)
Nothing special here, right?
(Big improvement)
Let's make some toast quickly.
Okay, I'll do the washing.
It's fine.
Thanks.
Come on, let's...
Two hundred and forty degrees.
I'll get the toast.
Same here.
We'll keep the heat low for now.
Sure, that works.
Good.
Not bad.
Just go with this.
Alright, let's take it off the pan.
Place the egg on top and it's done.
So it's ready now?
Yeah.
(Toast with fried egg)
Smells good.
Yeah.
The rules for Balance Island
have been announced.
Islanders,
please go to the Balance Zone to check.
Okay, let's go.
Off-island dates are open today.
(Balance Island Rules)
Ladies, please take your Date Arrangement Card.
Then head to the Balance Zone,
and write down
your preferred date group.
(Group 1 Off-island Date,
Group 2 Off-island Date)
How should we plan it?
How do you want to plan it?
I think...
I can't make the arrangements.
Just tell me what you have in mind.
Then...
I'll take it as a reference.
Honestly, that's hard to decide.
We just got here, right?
We just got here.
Can I...
I mean you.
I mean
you're new here, huh?
I still can't
recognize...
Can't recognize everyone, huh?
Right.
When see...
This is...
Forget it.
I don't know.
That's possible.
Just random pairing.
Random pairing.
Come on.
I'll set it up for you.
Then hurry and win.
Who's your partner?
(Eagerly)
Decide now?
This question.
We'll talk about it later.
Hurry.
Let's discuss this later.
Help me win this match.
There are lots of fun spots out there.
I want to go skydiving.
I've been thinking about it.
If I go on a date,
I want to try skydiving.
I'm scared girls won't want to.
I really want to go.
Then I wouldn't want to go.
(Wan?)
I'm a bit scared too.
You are too?
But you need to rest well.
My heart's already racing.
Might faint right away.
Like this.
Is it good?
(Eating from a basin)
Yeah.
Really?
They seem to have their own world.
(Their own world)
See.
(Huge mosquito bite)
Became a biggie.
Is it?
I'll get you medicine later.
It's really red.
Don't mess with it.
No touching. Touching makes it bigger.
Want drink more?
No, you finish it.
All done.
You done eating?
Thanks.
(Cleaning up right away)
(Yang Tianyu & Ding Wanning's
off-island date)
The vibe is really nice.
Let's sit here.
Thanks.
No problem.
Wan.
Tianyu.
What do you usually like to eat?
I usually go for Western cuisine.
And…
I like spicy food too.
Yeah.
What about you?
I'm really into seafood.
Fish, oysters.
High protein.
Shrimp.
But beef's off the list.
No.
Got it.
Say,
for your whole life,
you could only eat one thing,
what would it be?
Stir-fried pork with chili.
And you?
I'd go with
crab.
Do your glasses have prescription?
Just for show, right?
Yeah.
Let me try them on.
Don't take them off.
Like a teacher?
Looks great.
You're so good at
making people feel good.
No, I mean it.
Because your glasses look great.
Nope.
You look better in it.
You look good too.
Yeah.
I'm so glad we came out today.
So glad
you chose me.
I set it up.
Thanks.
Do you ever skip mashed potatoes?
I eat them.
Yeah, I do.
They're definitely high in calories.
It's fine, we burned it off today.
(Big energy burn)
(Not me)
You did.
I lost without even sweating.
(Zero game experience)
Do you usually like eating fruit?
Not really.
Same here.
Fruit has
too much sugar.
That's not a good excuse.
It's healthy.
You should eat more.
(Mandatory vitamin boost)
Thanks.
I eat blueberries.
And raspberries.
Because they're good for our body.
Apples too.
Yeah.
But I don't usually eat them.
Is it because you don't want to wash them?
Yeah.
Just not a big fan.
Got it.
You're born in September, right?
Mine's in December.
Birthday's coming up.
Happy birthday in advance.
Thanks.
Happy birthday.
Let's wish tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow, we might...
Nah.
But let's enjoy this meal now.
Because we won't have this tomorrow.
Let me help you.
Sure.
You like seafood risotto?
I love it.
It's delicious.
Not bad.
Maybe it tastes better
because you served it.
I'm so happy.
Suddenly I feel really blessed.
Yeah.
Any other
boys
you're interested in?
Jiawei, I thought he was pretty handsome
at first sight.
He was wearing glasses.
Right.
Wearing glasses.
You remember him quite well too.
Yeah.
He feels really friendly.
Exactly.
That's the feeling.
Yesterday, didn't they leave to
go through the elimination?
Then it was just the two of us left.
Well, I felt
a bit uneasy at first.
But the more we talked, the more I realized
we could have real conversations.
Yeah.
We had so many things in common.
Right?
(Last night)
So, what's your ideal type?
I like someone who exercises.
Me too. Sunny and
athletic.
(Same taste in type)
So what do you like to do
in daily life?
I like...
watching movies.
Love it.
I like watching
all kinds of movies.
Mystery film?
Everything.
(Same here)
I'm into mystery films too.
So, are you a judging person?
What's that?
Like…
Setting goals for yourself.
Having a schedule and a plan.
I set plans
for the week
or specific days.
And then,
I'll tell myself,
"Tianyu, you
made this plan.
Tired?
Will you skip it?
That's being lazy.
Just do it!"
You're the self-encouraging type.
Me too.
Sometimes,
(Common ground +1)
like,
when you're working out,
sometimes you just don't feel like going,
so I push myself anyway,
"it's already late, you still won't go?
If you skip it, then..."
Force myself to go out.
And I find
once I get in the car and start driving,
I'm fine.
Yeah.
(Soulmate!)
The moment you drive,
your eyes light up.
Right.
And then,
I'm actually full of energy.
Yeah, me too.
Do you like chatting with friends?
Yeah, pretty much.
What about you?
I like it.
I really like it.
So would you...
Like, do you keep things to yourself or
share with your best friend
when something happens?
Ask for their thoughts,
or do something else?
I
keep it to myself first.
Then,
if I really can't
handle it,
or feel really sad, I'll
share.
But mostly,
I keep it inside.
I act happy
when I'm with friends.
I'm pretty much the same.
I'm the same way.
Like, when something happens,
I also adjust myself first.
Then,
I talk myself through it.
(Finding more in common)
Seriously.
Like,
I don't reach out for help right away.
Right.
I'd rather...
Think it through on my own first.
Are you the type who
worries a lot about the future, or...
I live in the moment.
I'd say I want to live in the moment.
What about you?
Me too.
You
again.
There you go again.
(Total Sync Loop)
You keep saying, "Me too".
Honestly, when I talk to other people,
I'm not like this.
But,
yeah, me too.
Way too similar. It's scary.
Scary?
No, it's not that kind of scary, it's...
Just surprising.
But yesterday you said,
that Yijia
and Han...
No, yesterday when everyone
was hanging out,
I was seeing
who'd take the lead.
They both talked to me.
Yeah.
As expected. The proactive
and brave ones get to enjoy life first.
Yeah.
I was super nervous back then.
When they take the initiative,
I remember them.
It honestly felt like
they saved my life.
Yeah, true.
Are you adapting to island life?
Yeah, it's good.
You find it fresh?
Yeah.
Me too.
Such a unique experience.
Our
house even has
a rooftop.
You can go there to feel the wind.
Yeah.
I saw it earlier today.
Seems some people
had a date there yesterday.
Ours is way better than that.
Yeah.
So who's the best?
Us.
(You sure?)
Who?
Who's the best?
You.
Finally you said it.
You really are good.
Not really.
I think the competition favors me.
I'm taller,
so
it's easier.
You switched back to this necklace.
Which one do you like?
I have a third one.
A third one?
Different style.
Right.
You have a third one.
I'm looking forward to it.
Actually, there are four.
You have four?
Why do you own so many necklaces?
And so many rings.
Do you usually wear accessories, or
prepared them for this show?
I usually wear rings,
but I don't
have that many necklaces.
I have a few
of my own.
But I don't change them every day.
Got it.
I like rings.
Like rings.
So when you find the right one,
you'll...
Buy it.
Buy.
You like saying that word.
Tycoon vibe.
Buy.
When you're dating, would you mind
the other person's past?
No.
Don't care at all?
I don't think it matters.
She's not that person anymore.
Right.
(Agree)
Exactly.
But you might still get upset.
And then...
Feel jealous.
You can't change anything.
Anyway, you are
who you are now.
Shall we go for a walk?
Sure.
Have you dated a lot before?
Not really.
Could you count them on both hands?
Not that many.
(Lilu)
Your longest relationship?
About three years.
And you?
Around three years.
Same as me.
Yeah, three or four years.
Watch out.
Okay.
You too.
Careful.
Are you any good at singing?
Not really.
Not really?
No way.
Your voice is really nice though.
No, it's not.
Just sing a little.
No.
Okay.
Maybe privately sometime.
Sure.
Live in Hong Kong, China long-term,
right?
Yeah.
Do you go to Shenzhen often?
Not that often.
Right.
Do you go there a lot?
Yeah, I go to Shenzhen pretty often.
How long to get there?
It's about a two-hour flight for me.
Do you need to…
Go to the restroom?
Go ahead and act one out.
(An actual restroom)
Sit on the toilet then.
Each of us takes one.
Come on, one each.
Kinda dirty.
Yeah, pretty gross.
Then just squat over it.
One toilet per person.
If by life you were deceived,
don't be dismal,
don't be wild.
In the day of grief, be mild.
Merry days
will come, believe.
Heart is living in tomorrow.
Back then,
I used to see that quote a lot.
Have you seen it often?
Similar ones.
Yeah, it's pretty
popular and well-known.
Out of the darkness.
Keep the goodness in your heart.
Because you don't know
who would take advantage of your kindness.
Out of despair.
Even in the bathroom,
you see stuff like this?
Inspirational quotes.
They say don't
scroll on your phone in the bathroom.
Read this
fancy-sounding stuff
when you're in the toilet.
Honestly, this design is hilarious.
Let's go back.
Yeah, let's go.
Sure.
(Xuan Cheng & Liu Jiayi's
off-island date)
When you eat out,
do you
care more about
the atmosphere
and fancy-looking food,
or how good the food actually tastes?
That's easy to understand.
Like, what do you eat on
an anniversary?
Yeah.
You'd want...
Need that sense of ritual.
Right.
But if you're traveling somewhere,
or just...
Definitely the good eats.
Right.
You should be after...
Tasty stuff, no doubt.
Yeah.
When
you're with your partner,
will you join him
in things he likes?
Of course.
What are you into?
I like watching ball games.
Then I'd definitely be up for it.
Well, I have a question.
For example,
when you're at home,
would you want to watch
with your girlfriend?
Honestly, with or without.
It doesn't matter.
Even if my girlfriend
can't get into it.
And just does her own thing,
her being there
makes me super happy.
Yeah.
I'm
down for anything.
As long as
it's what you feel like doing.
If doing this makes you happy,
then I'll be happy
to join you.
You keep nodding.
When talking, you...
What?
(What?)
I mean, when talking, you...
Do this thing.
Keep nodding like that.
Sorry, that's my bad habit.
(Is... is it?)
Is it?
I guess so.
It's...
a signature move.
I'll try to change it.
No, I didn't mean you should.
(Your charm)
Don't change.
Sometimes all it takes is one shared look,
or something.
Well, I've been looking at you
this whole time.
I was looking at you.
I kept looking at you.
I wasn't looking at anyone.
When I think back,
I was totally
sitting like this
that day.
Completely facing away from Jie.
Yeah.
Because later you were...
Like, I was here and you were there.
(Jie, you, me)
Jie was there.
And I was sitting like this.
The body never lies.
From now on,
let's enjoy
every second we spend out of town.
Just now,
I couldn't stop thinking how lucky I am.
I'm so happy.
Any idea how to ease thirst?
Think of plums to quench it.
(Clever twist)
Think of you to quench it.
Yeah.
(Think of beauty to quench)
Think of beauty to quench it.
Good.
Nice one.
You're so charming.
I'm totally hooked.
Can't pull myself out.
(Luwan Ranch)
Hello.
There's nutrient paste
for capybaras here.
(Where?)
Where's the capybara?
(Capybara)
Capybara.
What's its name?
Shun.
Yeah.
Good boy.
So adorable.
(Full)
So cute.
(Full and off it goes)
It's leaving.
Shun.
Can't take a compliment.
So aloof.
All of a sudden…
Where are you going, Shun?
(Closing time)
Looks like we can take that boat
over there.
Wanna take this little yellow duck boat
out to the sea?
Yeah.
Once we hit the sea, you know.
Maybe in this life,
you're stuck with me.
Then let's just forget it.
No choice.
(Stunned)
So you'll choose...
No.
Careful.
Why do ducks
swim in a line?
(So neat)
They've got order.
They're polite, too.
Kinda like self-driving.
Let's head to...
Sounds so abstract.
(Self-drive Duck)
If she's gonna write about me,
I'll be the driver.
(Do we have a car?)
Do we have a car?
Borrow one.
(Steering wheel)
Finally get to hold a steering wheel.
You've been dreaming,
dreaming of gripping
that steering wheel,
and cruising down the highway,
looking all cool.
But instead...
Now you're sitting in
a yellow duck boat.
(Self-drive Duck)
A mini yellow duck.
The steering wheel.
Turn it that way.
Yeah.
I'm doing it.
I'm steering.
(Hard to port)
(First Mate giving it all)
Steering.
I'm really speechless.
Seriously.
I'm really..
Really speechless.
How did it come to this?
Quack quack.
Nice to meet you.
Quack quack quack.
(Me too, Quack Quack)
Sit up straight.
At least sit properly for this.
You totally led me astray.
If I came out with others,
I'd totally be on my best behavior.
So what?
Looks nice.
What about looking nice?
See, I was sitting like this just now.
Even better.
Fine.
Haven't you heard a saying?
When you like someone,
you gotta like them at
their most real, even their messy side.
Makes sense.
Relationships are about
living together.
Don't dress up (tomorrow).
Let me see if I'd still care about you.
You'll probably find me annoying.
The more I
spend time with you,
the more I realize you actually
come up with quite a few sneaky ideas.
Right?
You do know me a bit better.
I think...
That's what truly smart people are like.
So in other games,
being a bit silly is normal.
(Hmm?)
Then I'm silly too.
I didn't win either.
I used to be the most well-behaved kid.
I'm not?
I'm well-behaved too.
You're not.
At least I have
a heart
that never changes.
When I realize
I like someone,
that feeling never fades.
Honestly, sometimes I wonder
if I put myself in your shoes,
if I were you,
I'd feel the same.
Because they never meant you harm.
It means
they like you too, right?
Honestly, he's doing pretty well.
Yeah.
Honestly,
with you, it's more about feelings.
With him, it's more about logic.
So basically,
the final question is
whether feelings outweigh logic
or logic outweighs feelings?
They're not the same.
I'm actually curious.
Like, if you and I switched places,
and a girl was taking up
all your time every day,
how would I feel?
But I think you'd
feel the same as me.
What do you mean?
If a girl
asked me
out to chat,
and I went,
you'd probably be like me
and let me go.
Yeah.
I'm wondering if I'd feel upset.
You probably would.
A little bit, maybe.
But I don't know
how I'd react for real.
Maybe so.
Sometimes I think
I'm all that,
you know?
There's an
old saying
I always believe in.
"We'll cross that bridge
when we come to it"
I really like your mentality.
You know what?
Every time
I'm feeling down,
I just tell myself,
"Can't help it."
After all, I fell for
the prettiest girl here.
Honestly,
what really got on my nerves
these two days was
one scene.
(Mm (You go first), Mm (Yeah))
Do you know?
That day after your match,
I saw him
holding your hand.
(Jealous)
That made me so mad.
(Can't be helped)
It's part of the match.
No.
The round one, that match.
On that beach.
It was amazing.
Also,
earlier this morning...
Someone said there'd be
a walk tonight.
I just really like taking walks.
Alright.
(Like you said)
Got it.
From now on, after we eat,
as long as we're in the restaurant,
once I see you're done eating,
I'll be waiting outside.
Just to see if you head out.
(Let's go, then)
Sure.
I'm washing dishes.
Still wanna go?
Nope.
Not going.
Liar, liar, pants on fire.
It's fine.
It isn't that bad.
Liars get caught.
Come be a little duck here.
Be the little duck.
That's great.
Be a capybara.
Nice.
Nice, you'll feed me.
It's fine, at least you still feed me.
You're the real
Queen of Cheesy Pickup Lines.
You're that Queen.
("Live and Love" Release Schedule)
(Every Wed. & Thur. at 12 pm)
Still watching
(Watch Live and Love with us)
with "An Exciting Offer" today.
See? I guessed right!
Earned everyone's respect.
Even though love didn't happen.
(Can't bear to look)
(No way, man)
Fell into the tree.
No way, man.
The comedian.
Messes up at the crucial moment.
(Shipping them)
So sweet.
There's definitely a spark.
(Sweet to the heart)
I'm shipping them so hard.
Zizheng.
(What's this?)
What?
(Watching the drama)
So sad, tears of sorrow.
But this scene is so cool.
Show me the next episode.
(Still wanting more)
How is it already over?