Charlie's the oldest.
Me?
Uncle Charlie.
That's why I fractured a bone.
Getting old.
From the moment I met you,
I knew you were the right one.
If, at the start, the person you liked was
Yijia or Jiayi...
But
I never liked them.
It's you from the beginning.
If I weren't by your side,
would you miss me?
I'd miss you a lot.
Love is about...
accepting someone as they are,
not as you wish them to be.
=Live and Love S2=
=We're on Balance Island=
Do we still need to vote tonight?
I don't think so.
Me neither.
Just enjoy the moment.
But when it comes down to the end,
you'll still need to have
some rational thinking
to make a proper decision.
Honestly, I don't know either.
You don't?
So what do we do then?
Neither
of us know.
You don't either?
Let me hear your thoughts first.
Everyone says
I should listen to Yang more.
I'll hear what Yang thinks first.
I will
follow your lead.
Like when we play games.
On this, I'll hear your take first.
Does your affection
come more from feelings or from logic?
Half feelings,
half logic.
Right now, it's more about feelings.
Why's that?
No idea.
It just feels right, relaxing.
It feels different.
I feel the same way.
Come take a walk with me.
Let's go.
I'll change my shoes first.
These ones are too short.
The height's off.
But if you wear heels,
won't you get tired?
Then I'll wear Yan's big slippers.
Sure.
Would it look too weird?
No way.
Really?
Yeah, really not.
Please don't film my feet, okay?
Cameramen.
(Mosaic)
(Alright)
Let's go.
This way,
I'm much taller.
Why the laughter?
Since when did you get an ego?
Well,
it's because...
It's funny.
Because standing like this will...
Well, you know.
Or it'll end up like this.
(The only way we can look at each other)
If they don't film your feet,
how are we supposed to be in the same shot?
Just shoot the upper body.
Alright.
That's not the point.
Forget it.
(Let's drop this topic.)
Let's sit over here.
Sit properly.
So about that matter,
honestly, I still
want to hear what you think.
Which matter?
About leaving the island.
When I was still here,
I didn't think much about it.
I won't think about...
But once you leave the island...
Yes.
A strong sense of withdrawal.
It's not like
whenever I want to see you,
I can just walk up to your dorm,
knock on your door,
and everything would be sorted out.
Right?
So, there are three possible solutions.
First,
I move to your city.
Second, you move to mine.
Third, we both start fresh in a new city.
No other options.
So long distance is impossible.
What do you mean?
No long distance.
You want a long-distance thing forever?
That's even less possible.
Then...
The fourth option.
We just stay long distance.
Stay that way and...
see how it'd work.
Yeah, and maybe I'll...
If I ever hit the jackpot,
win billions, then maybe
(Fantasy moment)
we'd travel around the world.
That's one possible future,
right?
Who knows? Anything could happen.
Yeah, you're right.
Totally.
(Too good)
It could happen.
Well, let's go through the options.
First,
I go to Hangzhou.
Come join me in an online business.
What would I do?
"3, 2, 1, link's up!"
That's definitely not your thing.
Then...
If you really want in,
I could take some nice photos for you
and you could start your own account.
You think I can pull this off?
Maybe.
Maybe you can.
They're tired of it.
Those two are glued together.
It's so annoying.
And they never have anything new to say.
When the audience sees this,
they're like, did we watch this yesterday?
Didn't they say the same thing yesterday?
Here they go again, repeating it.
It's fine. If they don't ship us, I do.
Nope.
(He takes back a candy.)
Come on, give me one.
(Feeds it over.)
Where's the ice?
Ice?
Ice.
Where is the ice?
Ice cube.
I'm sitting out today.
Why?
He's weak.
I...
My liver's crying for mercy.
(Mercy)
It's begging me to stop torturing it.
But that'll help you keep your figure.
It's turning into one-pack.
Didn't you see?
Let me.
One-pack.
Uh-oh.
He's doomed.
Is he?
After watching you two closely,
I actually think you make a good match.
Why?
Tianyu.
Yeah.
Why?
(Go ahead)
Everything.
Height.
And then personality.
What's so funny?
(Dark skin, light skin)
One's darker, one's lighter.
From
the looks.
Don't you think so?
What the heck?
It's that kind of...
unexpected match.
One dark, one light.
Yeah, that's exactly...
A palm and back combo.
You've never played that Palm or Back?
Which boy and girl match?
(Takes a sip of juice)
I just spit on it.
Tastes good.
He loves it.
We're like elementary school kids every day.
That's exactly the vibe.
The kind of vibe that couples have.
Who's the oldest among you?
Me?
I was born in 2002.
(23 years old)
Not old.
She's younger.
(22 years old)
What about you?
(Don't start)
I'm the oldest.
Yeah, you are.
Crazy.
I'm not the oldest.
Charlie is.
Yeah, it's me.
(34 years old)
Uncle.
How are you feeling?
Uncle Charlie.
(The only uncle)
So I fractured my bone.
Getting old, you know.
Osteoporosis.
(Take care)
Take some calcium.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Pass it over.
Cheers.
(DAY 10)
(Yang and Enda,
ready for date)
Did you sleep well?
Slept like a baby.
Did you miss me?
Of course.
Really?
You've been
lingering in my mind.
Yang.
[*as sheep in Chinese]
One sheep, two sheep, three...
Sounds like you're busy.
Got a date later.
Happy?
Yeah, I am.
Seeing you already makes me happy.
Same here.
Let's go.
Do I look better with straight or curly hair?
They give different vibes.
Curly feels a bit more girly.
(observing)
(Hands on the wheel, safety first.)
(Love is precious, but life matters more.)
This promise really...
fits us perfectly.
Why do you say that?
"We've been together for seven years,
trying to find who we used to be."
So you think...
we can be together for seven years.
Right?
How about seventy years?
Seven years feels a bit too short.
After 7 years, would we still do
things like this?
Of course.
Definitely.
I could hold your hand for 70 years.
I once read something interesting.
It said that
after seven years pass,
the way you treat
the person you love
becomes like how you
treat your hands.
You barely feel anything.
But once it's gone,
you can't accept it.
Then try your best
not to get yourself hurt, okay?
(Don't hurt your hand)
Sure.
I promise you.
Look,
(Little White)
You actually brought our
Little White out with you.
(First date)
Let's call it Little White.
It makes me think of you.
(Token of our love)
I don't want to take it off.
Why not?
Because it has a name.
(Name of the date spot)
Where we had our first date.
Yeah.
I left it on purpose.
So cute.
Seriously, it's adorable.
The weather's perfect today.
This whole day feels so romantic.
Life on the island has been really nice.
Every day is just like
living inside this pink bubble.
So when we leave the island
and go back to real life,
aren't you a little scared that
the bubble might burst?
And then,
you realize some promises
aren't that easy to keep.
How would we handle that?
It could happen.
Let's talk about it.
Honestly...
So in the end, the real issue is still
the distance between us.
It's the biggest problem.
(The problem of distance
is hard to overcome.)
How do we deal with
the distance?
If I move to Hangzhou for you,
what job could I do?
If you were to a job in Hangzhou...
you're lowering your standards for me.
I don't like that.
You've got such a bright future ahead,
yet you'd be choosing another path,
starting all over again from nothing.
I think that's...
unfair.
(Giving up a stable life for someone
doesn't solve the problem.)
Then if I move to your city,
what could I do there?
Model.
Model?
Not many tall people in Singapore.
So you must be the most suitable one.
I don't speak the language.
I can teach you.
Teach me now.
What do you want to learn?
The sun is beautiful,
but not as beautiful as you.
Stop saying things like that to me every day.
I can't handle it.
Teach me.
No idea.
I don't know.
Then how can you teach me?
We can start with everyday phrases.
Like, I want to eat.
I want to order food.
I want this one.
But I know how.
You see, every time we talk,
we never actually try to
to tackle this issue.
We always switch topics somehow.
But the truth is,
it's hard to fix in real life.
Yeah, exactly.
So why not just enjoy this moment?
Enjoy this moment of pure calm,
the sunlight, the sea breeze, the beach.
Feel the ocean breeze.
It's relaxing.
When you're with me,
have you ever thought
that part of this is acting?
Acting?
I mean,
it's because people are watching us?
Or maybe…
No.
There are cameras.
If
it's about acting,
why would I make myself look so pathetic?
Pathetic? How?
I mean,
why does it have to end up
with such a huge problem
right in front of me,
making me feel this awful?
Do you ever regret it?
No, I don't.
I'd still make
the same choice no matter what.
What if the one you liked was
Yijia or Jiayi?
But
I never liked them.
It's always you.
So what now?
You like it
when there's some challenge.
Yeah.
I guess I like hardship.
It makes the relationship feel worthwhile.
You're talking big here.
I want the bittersweet part of love.
No way.
Love won't let you suffer.
Isn't long distance love's hardship?
(If long distance)
(can finally leads us somewhere,)
(then that waiting process is actually)
(worth it.)
I'm heading down first.
Wait a sec.
I want to kiss you.
Did they see us?
Pretty sure they did.
(Yan & Guan's date at Malt Cave Restaurant)
Honey.
Babe.
I set this up.
Which one is your favorite?
That one.
The one at the stadium.
I was sitting next to you.
And you?
The one on the top.
We were
in the supermarket.
Thank you, babe.
You're welcome, honey.
Can I ask you something?
How long do you think people should date
before getting married?
Ideally, for me,
around thirty.
Same here.
Twenty‑eight.
(Innocent look)
How old?
Twenty-eight.
Oh.
(Didn't catch that)
You think how old? Eighteen?
I thought thirty-eight.
How do you think
our married life is going today?
I think it's great.
Aren't you happy though?
I'm really happy.
I'm super happy, actually.
Let me check the photos.
Do you have anything
on your mind?
Our life on the island
is about to come to an end.
My thought is life there is ending.
But we're not ending yet.
Well, of course we're not.
Yeah.
But what I mean is,
have you learned anything
on the Balance Island?
I've learned how to talk to people.
And then,
how to survive on a deserted island.
Survive? How?
Instant noodles.
Living off instant noodles.
And eggs.
Every day it's just noodles and eggs.
(Picks up the photo again)
Do you have a favorite one?
You look so cheerful here.
Of course I do.
Is it the first day?
Yeah.
(First meeting)
I'm Zhu Huiyan.
You can call me Yan.
Yan.
I'm Wu Guanjie.
Guan.
It sounds cute.
We took so many photos that day.
Yeah.
I think the shots here turned out amazing.
What do you think?
You look amazing.
Me? No.
You look great too.
That was the day by the river.
Do you think my cheers that day...
...actually gave you a boost?
Yeah, they did.
You were shouting really loud.
Of course.
Almost yelling my lungs out.
Go, Guan!
Come on, Guan!
Come on, Guan, you got this!
That was awesome!
That day was pretty fun.
You mean that game, right?
Yeah.
Everyone
gave it their all
just to win that championship.
Yeah, totally.
My legs almost gave out.
Same here.
My body ached so much that day.
Sit on my right side.
Why?
I just want you to.
Come sit over here.
Alright, sit here.
Is it because it makes you
feel more secure, right?
Are you happy?
Yes.
The level of your happiness,
one to a hundred.
A hundred.
A hundred and one.
Then I'll give a hundred and ten.
Higher than mine anyway.
Of course.
Competitive much.
Honey.
Why so sudden?
I haven't finished it.
There's plenty over there.
Let's take that home to eat.
Honey.
Okay.
You hardly ever feed me yourself.
What's gotten into you today?
Because we just got married.
Honey.
From now on...
Every single day,
I'll feed you myself.
Honey.
Are you sleepy?
I'm full now.
Honey.
Why do you...
add "honey"
after every sentence?
Right, honey.
Just say it once.
Once when we meet is enough.
You don't have to keep saying...
But I like calling you honey.
Then as you wish.
Why did you buy me pink roses?
Honey.
It suits the way you look today.
Oh?
You're not wearing red.
Do you like it?
I do.
Can you give me a bouquet every day?
That might be a bit hard.
Why is that, honey?
Because we only do that on special
(Unhappy)
days.
Could you...
Or anniversary.
...give me a bouquet each day.
Honey.
I'll pick some for you.
(Changes her mind)
Sure.
I feel like going out.
Okay.
Honey.
What is it?
What's wrong?
I'm so happy.
Honey.
How happy?
Super happy.
I'm smiling so hard right now.
That you can't close your mouth.
Can't stop smiling.
Yeah, totally.
I just can't stop grinning.
Do you usually drink milk tea?
Neither do I.
What a coincidence, babe.
We'd have so much in common.
That's why we ended up being
a married couple.
Look.
It's so beautiful.
This is unbelievably romantic.
If I weren't right next to you,
will you miss me?
Yeah,
I really will.
How much?
A lot.
This feels so chill.
I feel the same.
I don't want to leave.
I think
we should stay here.
Feel the sea breeze.
Listen to some music.
With someone you like.
That's real peace.
Everyone would be so jealous.
I think so too.
(Departing, return to the island)
What do you think they'll do today?
We're shooting our wedding dress photos.
I really can't guess what they'll do.
Will they get their marriage license?
(Just a wild guess)
Then?
Take a guess.
I think...
You think...
Maybe doing some crafts.
Crafts?
Do you like making crafts?
Depends on who I'm with.
What if it's me?
If it's you, sure.
We can make crafts together.
Yeah, let's do that.
If it's someone else,
no?
Not with anyone else.
(Satisfied)
Where do you feel happiest?
Honey.
Taking photos.
What kind?
Wedding photos.
Because I've never
taken anything like that before.
Wedding photos?
A photo shoot?
Not wedding photos.
I mean photo shoot.
You've never done a photo shoot?
Yeah.
No wonder you're so awkward
in front of the camera.
What do you think we'll do tomorrow?
Will there...
be a confession balloon?
A confession balloon?
What do you think?
Who?
Who's confessing to you?
What?
(Playing dumb)
Who else?
Is there a new male guest coming?
Really?
No idea.
Who's confessing to you?
(Glares intensely)
I'll toss you out.
What do you mean?
Not you?
Nope.
(Think before you speak)
Then...
So, you want it?
Of course I do.
You do?
No way.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Just kidding.
Honey.
What's wrong?
I might not
get to call you that later, right?
No way.
You can call me whenever you want.
When you're angry me,
do you change the way
you call me?
I just ignore you.
Like this.
And what do you call me?
Wu Guanjie.
(Full name means trouble.)
Do you think I've been angry?
You're angry every single day.
No way, really?
Yeah.
Why don't you cheer me up?
Because the more I do, the worse it gets.
Why is that?
Cheer me up, then I won't stay mad.
Really?
Really.
Cheer me up and everything's fine.
(Yan's actually easy to please.)
Got it, honey?
Got it.
Time goes by so fast.
Feels like I've been here for about...
a week, give or take.
You came on the
third day to the island, right?
Second.
Second day.
That's when you met me.
Yeah.
Next day, we went to the island.
Time really flies.
Yeah.
No way.
I just wanted to ask you
that deep question I asked earlier today.
If, say, that purple shell wasn't me,
but you saw me on the island,
would you change your choice?
Actually,
I'm not really the type
to make the first move
or start a conversation.
Why not?
Because I'm honestly just not
a very forward person.
I tend to rely more
on attraction than action.
Then we are actually quite alike.
Not really.
How not?
Just not.
I'm a bit cuter.
You're not as cute as me.
Right.
You're the cutest,
babe.
Love you, hubby.
(Charlie & Liu Jiayi)
I love amusement parks.
Yeah.
There are so many kids.
Yeah, lots of kids.
Well,
you're a kid today.
I'm a kid now?
So we're doing the mom-and-son thing again?
I love coming to amusement parks.
Even with my hand hurt.
I really enjoy it.
You're such a playful one.
Liu Jiayi.
You're impossible to say no to.
Yeah.
What do you want to play?
Liu Jiayi.
Definitely not this one.
Why not?
I'm scared.
(Nervous)
I am scared.
Of this one?
(New to me)
For real?
Yeah, really.
The drop tower is worse.
But this one's pretty short.
The up and down motion...
(Thinking about it terrifies me.)
I can't stop laughing.
I'd rather watch a show.
(Fine, your call.)
Here?
There's no show right now.
No show at the moment, sis.
This is driving me crazy.
Can't do much about it.
You're the one who loves it.
Guess...
I just love playing it.
...I'll have to spoil you then.
(One word: spoil)
Baby Jiayi.
I love it.
The game is about to begin.
Please hold on
to the handrail in front of you.
It's okay.
(Yeah, not that great.)
Wait.
Bro!
(This won't end well.)
It's okay.
Wait, bro!
Slow down, man!
It's fine.
Wasn't that fun?
So much fun.
The best.
You silly one.
How romantic.
Let's go this way.
You just have to pass by
all those food stalls,
so I can smell everything, huh?
Act a little cuter.
I'll buy you some.
I'm the one with money, you know.
I'm hungry.
You look like some fluffy white animal.
Like a polar bear or something.
Or maybe a Westie.
You look like a bunny.
I don't.
Yeah, you don't.
Everything you do
is so slow-paced.
You're such a sloth.
So cute.
Super adorable.
That's just too cute.
The way it moves.
(Penguin walking)
(Hello)
So adorable!
(I'll wait for you here)
Penguins are the cutest.
Watch your step.
(New friends are here)
(We came to feed you!)
Everyone's here.
Here comes the squad.
(We want some too!)
They waddle just like ducks.
(Where are your manners?)
(This scene feels familiar)
You really know how to make them compete.
No.
I want to give this to the newcomer.
That's so nice.
Yeah, right.
I misunderstood you.
Let them play for a bit.
Watch this.
Sweetie, want a bite?
See you.
I think
everything inside really suits you.
You give me that kind of vibe.
Like something soft and fuzzy.
You mean I look silly.
No, not at all.
(It's a compliment)
You feel so warm.
Adorable.
Try on this one.
Let me try it on for a sec.
I'll help you.
Actually, it's pretty cute.
Good?
You seriously can't stop showing off,
can you?
I get overwhelmed by it.
(Playfully)
I am cool.
Indeed.
(Helplessly)
Let's go.
I'm craving some food.
Just pretend it cooked it all.
(Promoted to head chef today)
It made all the dishes.
Good boy.
So adorable.
Feels like I should've taken
a few more looks at you
on the day we first met.
Yeah?
Things were too chaotic back then.
I didn't...
I sneaked
a few extra glances at you.
(All I can see is you.)
I'll sum it up with one lyric.
A lyric?
You're making it hard for me.
"Just because in that crowd,
I looked at you a few more times."
It was you.
Yeah.
Me.
I only regret one thing.
Not giving you all votes on day one.
I think
the rightest thing I did ever was...
After my first day's interview,
I saw you were the next.
Somehow I felt like
waiting for you.
So I waited.
(Night of Day 1)
Why are you here?
Yeah, I just couldn't fall asleep.
Let me walk you out.
You've been staying here till now?
Yeah.
I remember seeing you after that interview.
It felt kind of magical to me.
Because...
before you came to me,
I never thought
you actually had any feelings for me.
But back then, did you already know?
Yeah.
I knew at that time.
Remember what I said to you
when I walked you home
after that interview?
What did you say?
I just remember you talked to me a lot.
Right before you left,
I told you something.
And you answered me.
I said,
"If tomorrow there's a chance
to choose someone for a date
and I choose you,
would you choose me too?"
Your answer was,
"Probably yes."
But in the end?
The result was
I let myself down.
I didn't win the match.
What I respect most about you is
that
you never tried to stay
by talking your way into it.
Never.
Like chatting up other girls.
Never once.
And you never seemed worried
or felt the need to explain yourself.
You never asked me
who I'd pick
or
if I'd vote for you at all.
I've never brought up the voting thing.
(I respect your opinion)
Yeah, you never asked me
about my feelings
or asked for my votes
cuz you might be leaving.
Or...
You never said anything like that to me.
Because to me, it's simple.
I came here just because I wanted to
find love.
Then I met you,
and I felt like
you were the right one.
But if you don't like me
and if I leave, I'll still be okay.
No regrets.
At most,
I just feel a little attached to my friends
on this island.
Or I guess I'll miss the feeling
of escaping real life.
That's all.
You're amazing.
But every time you go quiet,
it hits me right where it matters.
(Right on the point)
Go quiet?
Like, you never ask me about this
or about that.
The more you don't talk about
how you're scared of being left out,
or about how few
the votes you got,
the more I'd think of you,
the whole thing.
You're smart.
You too.
Let's go.
Are there fireworks tonight?
Yeah.
There are.
Fireworks are magical, aren't they?
I love watching fireworks.
Me too.
The clouds are moving.
Drifting with the moon.
They're moving so fast.
I can't wait.
(Screaming Carnival)
I think it's gonna be awesome.
Is that a little bat?
Yeah, it is.
A tiny bat.
Or a little demon.
Amazing.
Pretty.
Coming.
We can eat now.
Let's go.
I made you some Luosifen.
Really?
Yeah, really.
These look delicious.
They do.
Not a compliment.
I get it.
Try a bite.
Tastes great.
It's getting cold.
Yeah, it is.
No need to cool Luosifen.
Want some extra soup?
No.
Still delicious.
It really is.
Woke up and dinner's already ready.
I love hearing you speak Cantonese,
though I can't understand it.
Crispy.
Crispy eggs.
It means
eggs with golden crispy edges.
How long did it take you to cook this?
Half an hour?
That's quite a while.
Really?
Right.
I had to chop this and that.
Then wash all kinds of things.
Didn't take that long to stir fry.
But the prep work, that's the tough part.
Yeah, cooking can be a real hassle.
I can make Luosifen and spicy ramen.
I should've...
Let me.
(I should get some sleep)
I should've gone to sleep.
But you promised
you'd make me something tasty.
Right, I did.
Actually, I promised Jiawei too.
About what?
(Sleeping)
He can't leave the island.
I said, I'll cook something nice for you.
Yeah, I told him that too.
Want some more?
Sure.
I'm full.
Really?
You ate so little.
Yeah, I know.
I've got a tiny appetite.
No wonder.
That's why you're so slim.
I prefer to think of myself as gentle.
Being slim isn't my best quality, okay?
Do you think you're gentle?
Not really.
Yeah.
Done eating?
Let's clean it up.
Go get some fresh air.
Sure.
You clean up.
Come on, you do it.
No, you do it.
You clean up.
I can help you
carry the small bowls.
So stuffed.
Are we heading out now?
Yeah.
I wanna go over there.
We can go to the swings.
Let's swing this way.
When I swing out, it feels kinda scary.
Push me from this side.
Use your strength.
I'm actually a bit scared.
If this breaks, you'll fly right off.
No way, it won't.
This feels so nice.
Higher?
Go for it.
You're crazy.
You're not scared, but I am.
Come on and try it yourself.
It's a lot of fun.
I don't really feel any fear, to be honest.
Well, I do.
You won't once you get used to it.
You go first then.
Can you push a bit higher?
You're too heavy for that.
It's nice, right?
Yeah, it really does.
Can you push a few more times?
I'm begging you.
Feels like a workout.
You're running out of energy.
Too tired.
Let's sit on the chair.
Let's go.
Feels nice.
Honestly, it's pretty comfy.
This place is really beautiful.
Here.
This island.
When you first came to this island,
how did you feel?
So many people were talking to me.
Like,
"what's your name?"
"Hi, Tianyu."
Honestly, I was really confused then.
I just smiled awkwardly.
At that moment, I...
(Polite)
did this.
I couldn't process a single thing they said.
But you looked fine.
That day, you seemed calm.
Looked calm, but deep down I was...
A total mess inside.
Exactly.
So did you ever think about
falling in love here?
I mean, I did
think about it,
but...
Not that...
sure?
You mean certainty?
Well,
I kinda
just couldn't believe
it would happen.
For real.
This show just
brought everyone together.
If it really happens one day,
that would be such a happy thing.
Do you think you're a chill type?
What do you mean?
I mean,
calm and a bit distant.
Ah, I get it.
Right.
I'm not.
So you're a passionate person instead?
I'd say so.
Yeah.
It's just that
sometimes I like being on my own.
But you seem like someone who
doesn't really show
how much you like someone, or maybe...
I don't express it that clearly, right?
For example, on the island,
everyone can sense
some people's affectoin.
But,
what exactly catches your interest?
About you?
I think you're very...
straightforward
and then
a little carefree,
which feels refreshing.
For me,
I can't stand people who drag things out.
So personality really matters to you.
It's super important.
The most important thing.
Honestly,
in my eyes, you're a calm kind of person.
You don't talk much when you're in a crowd,
and then...
that day,
when we were working
on that Book of Riddles,
you ran pretty fast in front of me.
That was fast, honestly.
Huang Jiawei, be careful!
At that moment,
you really had that impulse
and passion that I'm looking for.
Also, Wan was there too.
And later you came over.
When we were in the car,
you said you came
because you were worried I'd feel bad.
I didn't want you to overthink.
And I did think about how you might feel.
So I
tried to do something...
Something that can make me...
Feel truly at ease.
But actually, you usually
express yourself quite well.
You seem like someone who's not
too worried about what others might think.
Because I really value
everyone's
own space and world.
When I'm working hard,
she works hard too.
And then,
I don't like telling her what to do
and I don't want her
controlling me either.
I think when two people
choose to be together,
it should come from mutual trust.
Yeah.
I came across a line recently,
it said love is
accepting someone as they are,
not as you wish them to be.
You get it,
right?
Yeah.
Exactly.
All those things I just said.
Back when I was in a relationship,
I didn't really get this.
What were you like before?
Well,
I cared too much about little thing.
Like, all sorts of things,
what the other person was doing,
or why they hadn't texted back.
You know.
When I focused too much on them,
I'd lose track of who I was.
So I think,
liking someone,
loving someone... those feelings,
they can't be forced.
Out of all the dates,
my favorite one was when we went to that
place that looked like a yurt.
Why that one?
Because it felt really cozy,
like being at home.
That fancy western restaurant, though,
was way too high-end.
When you barely
know someone,
it's better to
go somewhere more casual,
right?
You're not like anyone I've met before.
What kind of person am I then?
You know, like you.
(Scratches head)
What do you mean?
Bright, warm.
Keep going.
I'm curious.
Ugly.
Whatever,
you're different.
Do they have the same spark?
A different kind of spark.
Go on, say it.
(Tell me)
Spark is spark.
But yours is different.
Different how?
Just different.
Come on.
Never heard of such a thing.
Your kind of spark
is not even like the village chief's spark.
You get what I mean?
I just like the kind where
the guy's a bit more mature than me.
Two people can connect
in an easy and relaxing way.
We both have fun together,
and actually like each other.
It's that natural attraction.
Sometimes I even hope that guy
can, to some extent,
share some mature advice
or give me real support.
I just think
that's what truly makes
a balanced relationship.
I just don't like
those people who,
you know,
don't understand a word you're saying.
It's not just about
choosing a girlfriend, it's also that I
choose my friends the same way.
If I find someone who is not...
Over time, I'll just...
I'll slowly walk away.
Bit by bit, you realize she's pretty naive.
And then you quietly drift away.
("Live and Love" Release Schedule)
(Watch Live and Love with us)
Islanders!
(on Thu. 12 PM.)
Today, we'll play four rounds of games.
Now this is what I call a real game.
(Click)
What was that sound?
Yang's eating something.
Well done.
Why the laugh?
How am I supposed to eat instant noodles?
You didn't even clean up.
And you're trying to pin it on me?
(Excuse me?)
I helped you win
and you're accusing me instead?
Then your analysis is totally off.
You've lost your mind over love again.
(Shocked)
What?
(Look at me)
Bestie.
That's kinda flirty.
You look like such a goof.
I think we've already won.
Why can't you grab it?
(Hurry)
Can you even play?
(Slides to the ground)