(Love begins with an emotional spark.)
Still him.
The one who you like most?
Yeah.
I swear, you're the one and only.
If you're happy, then I'm happy.
Cheers.
(But lasting love needs rational insight.)
Many times,
our hearts
know the truth before our minds do.
That's kinda scary.
This experiment isn't about judging
or exposing anyone.
Are you lying?
It's meant to help them clear away
the fog around their expression
and see each other's truest reactions.
Each person must take
a polygraph test.
Together, we'll discover
the secrets of genuine feelings
unfolded through our bodies.
=Episode 7 (Part 1)=
=Lie or Truth=
The polygraph.
Could it be the kind
that clips onto your hand
and zaps you whenever you lie?
I'm curious about
the questions they're gonna ask.
Hope the machine
doesn't expose me.
What lie did you tell?
I didn't...
Well,
I don't want to know the result.
I have no idea what they're gonna ask.
You could ask Yang.
But me asking Jiayi feels awkward,
honestly.
If I ask sharp questions,
she'd start to dislike me.
Do you have any questions?
Are you scared of it?
Maybe a little bit.
Are you scared?
No, I'm not.
I'm just worried
that it might mess up.
Why?
Do you have any concerns?
No, none at all.
I'm just imagining.
Sir.
(Ji Yu, psychological counselor)
(Area of practice: relationship issues)
Have a seat.
Professor.
You're professional.
Cool.
We'll start in a bit.
Everyone needs to undergo
a polygraph
test.
(Polygraph with Multimodal Physiological Data
Acquisition & Analysis System)
(Powered by proprietary AI algorithms.)
(Collects indicators from EDA,
pulse rate, respiration,)
(video-based physiological signals,
and micro-movements.)
(Provides data support for
psychological assessment and interrogations)
(Accuracy rate: approx. 80%)
That's interesting.
It's my first time.
Me too.
Before we officially start,
we need to do a prep work.
Let's have some warm water first.
This way,
it helps the polygraph
capture more accurately
the electrical signals
your bodies give off.
Here, pass this over.
Come on.
Here.
Yijia.
It's pretty hot.
Why so nervous?
Why?
Because I don't know
what you're about to ask.
Even those not asking questions
seem excited.
Yeah.
I think I'm a genuine person.
I don't think
this polygraphy
would flag me.
Yeah.
My heart's racing
before the test eve starts.
Can it be accurate?
This polygraph we use
can detect
whether you're nervous
or you're lying.
It can tell the differences.
Impressive.
Nice.
Cool.
Who wants to try it first?
Me.
I wanna try.
Alright, put these finger sleeves on.
Here.
Finger sleeves
can detect changes
of electrodermal activity and assess
one's emotional state
like tension or anxiety.
Alright.
Take a moment to calm yourself.
I'll ask.
Okay.
Sit.
Do you see me as just your sister?
What?
That's hilarious.
Hey, brother.
Hey, sis.
Hold on.
(Huang Jiawei. Chen Family)
Let him calm down.
He's a bit nervous.
He got nervous the moment it started.
Do you still have feelings for your ex?
(Do you still have feelings for your ex?)
He told me that day,
his ex looked kinda like
a mix between Christy Chung
and Cecilia Cheung.
That's pretty fun.
Yeah, I think so too.
No.
(Do you still have feelings for your ex?
No.)
The polygraph shows he's lying.
(Detected as a lie)
Oh no.
His image just collapsed.
Totally doomed.
Guess I know you best, brother.
No way.
I never believed
in this thing.
(Defending)
When your heart rate's high,
even a true statement can look fake.
So I don't buy it.
(Fool your bros if you must,
not yourself.)
Any more questions?
I've got one.
Alright.
Is there any women at present
whom you want to know more
about?
No.
The polygraph shows
he's lying.
(Detected as a lie)
No way.
Bro.
No one would believe me.
You're lying to your own friends?
I didn't lie to you.
Calm down, take a breath.
The graph's a bit messy.
His minds wanders.
Who do you want to know about,
Jiawei?
She asked if there's any female guests
I'd like to know more about.
I said no.
It showed I was lying.
Not accurate.
Impossible.
Okay.
So, who's gonna ask the question?
Me.
(Brother's revenge)
Sis,
do you still have feelings
for your
ex-boyfriend?
(Still hung up on your ex?)
Sibling rivalry getting brutal here.
No, I don't.
The polygraph shows
an obvious lie.
(Detected as a lie)
Lie.
A very obvious lie.
How could you
laugh at me?
Sis.
That's definitely fake.
Totally fake.
I can't believe it.
It showed I was lying?
I can't believe this.
There's a delay
(Expert's explanation)
of your reaction.
Then it'll show the real
data changes.
My reflex is way too slow.
Means you're thinking about
the question.
So professional.
Who else wants to try?
Me.
Seriously?
Who wants to throw him a question?
Please sit here.
Okay.
(Wu Guanjie. Zhu Huiyan)
Ask a random question first.
Anything?
Yeah.
Do you like the color red?
You can answer yes or no.
No in-between option?
He doesn't have
feelings about it.
He's pretty honest.
Is there any in-between option?
Then…
Yes.
(Do you like the color red? Yes.)
That's a lie.
You're lying.
(Detected as a lie)
He lied.
So yeah, that was a lie.
Would you be more proactive next time?
Yes.
No.
He shock his head.
That's a lie.
(Detected as a lie)
Are you lying?
Even the rain couldn't bear it.
I'm speechless
and also a bit awkward.
Hard to tell if he's acting or for real.
I'm hesitant to keep asking.
Have you ever had feelings for me?
Yeah.
That made me even more nervous.
According to the polygraph reading,
you're telling the truth.
(Detected as truth)
You're done for.
Done for how?
You lied to me.
About what?
You're done for.
I don't want to talk to you.
Earlier,
I wasn't serious.
Then, I paused for a second
to think.
Yeah.
And I answered.
It showed truth.
Let me do it, sir.
Sitting there made me nervous.
My heart started racing for a bit.
Have you felt your heart flutter
on the island?
(Felt moved on the island?)
Yes.
She's telling the truth.
(Detected as truth)
What kind of question is that?
I...
Next question.
There's a second one?
Nice.
Do you feel drawn to Tianyu?
(Do you feel drawn to Tianyu?)
Yes.
She's telling the truth.
(Detected as truth)
Any more questions?
I don't want to put pressure on her.
Some things are best felt by yourself.
Any other questions?
Anyone
asking me a question?
I'm really nervous.
Alright, I'll ask one.
Sure.
Come here.
(Ding Wanning. Chen Yijia)
On the island,
is there any man you wanted to
connect with but didn't dare?
No.
It's true.
Come on,
(Detected as truth)
I made a fool of myself.
No more questions.
Anyone else want to ask her?
You haven't asked anything yet,
Tianyu.
Don't feel like asking.
Okay.
Honestly, I was expecting.
But he didn't ask my anything.
He has no doubts about me.
I'll go.
(Yang Tianyu. Wu Yihan)
When we hang out together,
did you feel happy?
Yes.
He's telling the truth.
No more questions.
(Detected as truth)
He and I
have only just met a day ago.
About his answer,
I already felt content.
No need to bring up those things.
No need to rush or ask
"whether I'm the only one"
or "whether you truly like me".
It doesn't matter.
I don't want to pressure him.
So,
what I asked was,
"when you're with me,
are you happy?"
I know he definitely is.
(Yang Tianyu. Ding Wanning)
If you had another chance
for a date,
would I still be your first choice?
That's a sharp question.
No.
He's telling the truth.
(Detected as truth)
Okay.
I was a little upset back then.
I couldn't understand
why things changed so much.
He looks really relaxed now.
Completely
relaxed.
I already know
what I want to do.
After our date yesterday,
my interest in Wu Yihan
just kept growing.
Our date today feels a bit different.
Yeah.
When I'm with Wu Yihan,
I feel a little more relaxed.
Am I gentle?
Super gentle.
And when I'm out with Wan,
I might feel...
There's a bit of distance between us.
My heart is already pounding.
Any questions? Come on up.
Come on.
Okay.
Go ahead.
I'm a little nervous, right?
Yeah, a bit nervous.
(Zhao Enda. Yang Tinghong)
Your mind's kind of a mess.
Calm down.
His mind's a mess.
Oh,
much better now.
Yeah.
Really?
I'm starting to feel a bit nervous again.
Yes.
Again.
Again?
Now you're feeling tense again.
(No electric shock)
You're the most nervous.
Take a moment to calm down a bit.
Okay.
Can I?
Much better.
Sure.
Was what you just did
something you thought through?
Yang,
I like you.
(Was that confession
something you thought about?)
Yes.
It shows he's telling the truth.
(Detected as truth)
Will external factors
affect
our relationship
in the future?
Yes.
He's telling the truth.
(Detected as truth)
When you first asked him,
he was psychologically unstable.
But when he said yes,
it was sincere.
If he'd said no instead,
that would definitely be a lie
and I'd actually be more worried.
It would mean he hasn't
really thought seriously
about our future.
On the island, besides me,
have you ever had feelings
for another woman here?
No.
According to the polygraph,
you were telling the truth.
(Detected as truth)
Your turn to ask.
(Yang Tinghong. Zhao Enda)
Do you enjoy spending time with me?
Yes, I do.
She's telling the truth.
Can you handle a long-distance relationship?
(Can you handle
a long-distance relationship?)
Good question.
I can.
That's the truth.
(Detected as truth)
How did love get this deep?
Honestly, I'm really happy.
I feel like Yang recognized me again.
To be honest, that really touched me.
I'm jealous of you two.
Every answer you gave was true.
Let me do it.
Thank you, professor.
Once he puts it on, the results show
(Lu Yanting. Liu Jiayi)
his thoughts run deep.
What do you mean
by his thoughts run deep?
He tends to overthink a little.
And he carries a touch of
melancholy.
You already seem down,
how can I still ask?
It's fine.
Just ask.
Ask directly, it's okay.
Your feelings for me are more about
reason over emotion.
(Are your feelings for me
rational or emotional?)
Rational.
You're telling the truth.
(Detected as truth)
Any other questions?
The way he cares for someone
is by doing a lot of thoughtful things.
But I've always felt
he's not that happy doing them.
It's not like
something he does naturally
from heart.
But for me,
any relationship has to be built,
at the very least,
on the sense that his feelings for me
comes from the heart, not logic.
If it doesn't,
our relationship wouldn't make sense.
Alright.
Okay.
Who wants to try next?
Me.
I'll ask.
(Xuan Cheng. Liu Jiayi)
Bring it on.
Alright.
My question is,
after you leave the island,
will you still like me the same way?
Yes.
That should be the truth.
The result leaned toward 'true'.
I see.
Any other questions?
I'm good.
No more questions?
No, that's all.
I think that after I leave the island,
things between us
could develop.
So I'm really curious,
is it because the vibe
on the island that makes him
have feelings for me?
Like once back in real life,
he might not like me
as much as I imagined.
(Liu Jiayi. Xuan Cheng)
Outside of this island, is there someone
you could possibly be with?
(Outside the island,
is there someone you could be with?)
That's kind of scary.
Yeah.
The polygraph shows
she's telling the truth.
(Detected as truth)
When I first heard his question,
I actually felt happy inside.
It meant he cared about
my life outside of here.
So I wanted to be genuine
when I answered him.
Because in real life,
generally speaking,
guys tend to
find me likable pretty easily.
So for me, I think
that's just normal.
Yeah.
I never lie.
My motto is...
It is...
honesty.
Be honest.
(Liu Jiayi. Lu Yanting)
He even wrote it down.
We went out together yesterday.
Did you have fun?
(Was yesterday's date fun?)
Yeah, it was fun.
The polygraph shows...
she's lying.
(Detected as a lie)
That's kinda scary.
I'm sorry.
Professor,
there are many factors here.
Were you happy I picked you up?
Of course.
That's awesome.
It was so much fun.
You caught on so fast.
Really?
It was so much fun.
I really like it.
When we went go-karting,
it was
a really fun and relaxing time.
So I honestly didn't expect
the polygraph to show that result.
But during yesterday's date,
we were definitely having a great time.
I truly believe what she said was real.
Professor, what's the margin of error?
The accuracy rate should be around 80%.
About seventy to eighty percent.
Based on data and graphs,
the polygraph
helps everyone
get a clearer sense
of their true feelings.
I hope through this test,
everyone can better understand
their choices in relationships.
Thanks for your hard work, professor.
Thank you.
Thank you, professor.
You two are ridiculous.
Yeah.
It's accurate.
We're ridiculous?
It's insanely accurate.
Not ridiculous.
It's...
super accurate.
So accurate it seems ridiculous.
For me and her,
I don't buy it.
After going through that polygraph test,
everyone's emotions
seem to get stirred up a bit.
Are you happy with the result?
Yeah, I am.
Then what about you,
are you happy with it?
Yes.
That lie detector proved
Enda's feelings for me once again.
I'm pretty happy about it.
You really know how to answer
and how to ask.
Impressive.
Are you satisfied?
No.
Not at all.
What about my answer. Are you satisfied?
Yeah.
Completely satisfied.
Because the answer I wanted
is exactly that one.
You're good-looking.
How could it be that
no one's reached out to you?
Well, it's not just about looks though.
Let me hear it.
What did you say?
Well done.
You made it through the test.
Let's grab a drink.
Have another one.
Let's go.
What?
What are you humming?
Some people...
Honestly, I don't care about the results.
Because I think
there's no need to rely on it
to judge what we have between us.
If I can't get it over,
I'd just drain myself emotionally.
If
Lu comes and asks you,
what would you say?
Like, if he actually shows up
and asks if you'd choose him.
I wouldn't.
His feelings for me are rational.
I wouldn't choose him.
Drop this topic.
Would you tell him directly?
He wouldn't get
a single vote from me tonight.
Attention, islanders.
Here are the rules for tomorrow's date.
There are three invitation cards.
They're hidden somewhere on the island.
You must solve the Puzzle Book
in the mailbox.
It'll reveal where
and when the invitation cards appear.
So...
(The time and location must match)
we
need to know
when and where they show up.
Now?
The first to crack the puzzle
will get the chance to unlock
an romantic luxury date.
Luxury.
Romantic.
Must be something good.
Are you quick to think?
Yeah, I am.
Yeah? Really?
I just talk slow.
Is that so?
Are you smart?
Honestly,
not really.
Well, that's tough.
I'm not smart either.
But I want to
go on a luxury date.
Then I think...
Yang, you...
Let me work my brain
and win my own romantic luxury date.
Right?
I'd definitely think hard too.
Honestly,
I want to go on an off-island date.
This time, it's about reasoning.
No need for physical clashes
or fighting over it.
Feels like there's finally a hope.
Sis, we've got to win this one.
Come on, I'm seriously scared right now.
What should we do?
You don't want it?
I'll go with someone else.
A proper meal is tempting.
Come on, let's go.
I think
Yijia is not interested in any guy here.
And I'm not interested in any girl here.
So...
we can team up for now.
(Caring for family)
Let's hang out.
Gotta make my sister's wish come true.
Let's take it out.
Come on.
They're different.
Here.
Three copies of the Puzzle Books.
This one's a hint.
The hint is "Couple".
(Puzzle Book 1. Hint: Couple)
Why are there two of them?
(Puzzle Book 2)
What is this drawing?
I don't get what this means.
Qiong.
You're the most confident person
in my heart.
(Puzzle Book 3)
My world, ruled by you.
At the card table of life,
I wandered without direction
until you showed up
as that decisive King
and changed everything.
I'm bad with numbers.
Can you make sense of this?
Yeah.
I think,
for example,
letters like A, D, K
must have some special meaning.
Could be about time and place.
Numbers aside,
A, D, K are pointing
to something else.
What are we looking for?
You've got to deduce it
before you search.
Come on.
It's about time and place, right?
Yeah.
Exactly.
We just need to work out
the time and location.
I think all the numbers,
like nine seats,
June, and four seasons,
could point to a time.
(Yang Tianyu: the numbers point to a time)
And this is a place.
I mean ADK.
(The letters point to a location)
I have no idea what these mean.
What does 996 even mean?
Time and place.
What on earth is this?
And what are these?
No clue at all.
(Mind's stuck)
Can't figure it out.
Totally clueless here.
We're just staring
at each other blankly.
We're both acting slow today.
Not a single idea between us.
Can't wrap my head around it.
But honestly, I'm hoping for a date.
I can feel Tianyu getting closer.
So gentle.
The gentle chef.
Han, sit over here.
Why like this?
Your left side looks better on camera.
If we can go out together on a date
and spend more time
to connect,
that's a good thing.
I really want to get the Date Card.
I still want to spend more time
with Tianyu.
Because I feel that
a date can change a person.
And it has already changed him.
If I get the Date Card,
I'll write Tianyu's name on it
and talk about the things
I'm interested in.
Maybe deepen our bond a little.
Get to know each other better.
(Getting tired of reading)
My eyes are so dry.
I'm taking out my lenses.
Can't see things clearly.
Are these two connected at all?
Probably.
They put them together.
This is so hard to crack.
I'm getting sleepier.
It must be linking letters with numbers.
That's what I thought.
It's not that simple.
We need to guess what it really means.
That's the key.
(Qiong)
Village chief.
Big news.
This is a license plate number.
(Chen Yijia: Puzzle Book 3 points to
a license plate)
Come on, let me see.
We couldn't solve this one.
I figured it out.
You did?
I've cracked this one.
Impressive.
Maybe it's because
I like detective stuff,
like novels, movies, and shows.
When I saw that sheet full of text,
the first two words on it
reminded me of a license plate.
(Qiong)
Every day, I see plates
starting with Qiong,
so it instantly reminded me of one.
(Qiong)
Plus, I'm sensitive to
numbers and letters
than to words themselves.
Even when there's a ton of text,
I just tune it out
and focus on the letters instead.
It's like something glows in your vision.
So I connect them together.
(Qiong ADK9961)
I guessed that's a plate number.
But I couldn't work out the time.
I figured it out already.
Did you get good grades?
Of course.
You can tell you didn't.
I don't like reading
words like these.
I already forget the top part.
I once stayed in nine cities
away from home.
This long journey was
just about collecting...
I don't feel like looking for the card.
Maybe it's because my emotions
and my mind are still stuck
in the previous round.
So honestly, most of the time,
I wasn't even really finishing the game.
I was actually thinking hard
about how we could clear up
the misunderstanding.
It all comes down to time and place?
Just this sheet?
This one.
That's simple.
We'll go with this.
It points to one.
All the travels, all the seasons.
I got it now.
You got it too, right?
I should've known the time.
You know the time?
(Xuan Cheng: the Invitation Card
appears at 13:05)
Because it says,
all the travels and
all the seasons
point to the same destination,
which is one.
(All the travels and the seasons point to 1)
So it means the hour and minute hands
both point at one.
I think
I know what time it means now.
You do?
I know the location.
So, can we team up?
Let's trade info.
Sure.
Wait, I have one condition.
When I'm in danger,
you give me one vote.
Sure.
You promise?
Yes.
Deal.
A license plate.
Qiong ADK9961.
The time is in the afternoon.
1:05 PM.
Or maybe 1:10 PM.
Because it says
everything points to one.
Meaning both hands point at one.
That's how I understand it.
And 1:05 PM
feels like a reasonable time.
Well, that's one way
to look at it.
There's no other clues about time.
If this card...
If you crack the other two books,
just let me and Huang know.
Alright.
The time might not be right.
But I'm sure my location is right.
However,
Xuan Cheng,
maybe it's not afternoon.
(It could be 13:05 or 01:05.)
What time is it now?
It's just past one.
It's one-thirty.
What happened?
Exchanging info?
Let's go check it out.
Where?
Tell me where.
That plate.
License plate.
We have to go out tomorrow.
Let me go first.
Sir, I'm the first.
(Roadside Parking Area)
You got it?
Didn't see it.
(No Invitation Card)
The time is off.
(Time and place must match
to get the card.)
How did you know to run this way?
Because all the cars are here.
Your brain works pretty well.
Not bad.
Sharp mind.
You found it?
No.
What did it turn out to be?
It's a license plate.
Right.
The one with AD something?
You're so smart.
This one's tougher.
This part's about time.
(Puzzle Book 1. Hint: Couple)
Couple?
This is about location.
What about that?
(Location)
It should be time.
(Time)
The hint is couple.
(Hint: couple)
I figured it out.
Huang Jiawei, let's move.
Huang Jiawei.
Swimming pool.
Go, now!
There is
a typical puzzle,
where you need to match couples
sometimes based on their jewelry
or other things they wear,
like details about their looks.
You pair one guy and one girl
and see who matches best.
So when I saw the necklace,
I knew right away they were a couple.
(Couple)
Their name tags.
Si Weiming and Pu'er.
Si Weiming, Pu'er.
I repeated it a few time
and realized
it sounded like swimming pool in English.
(Si Weiming, Pu'er)
The place
where I fell in. So I remember it.
I called Huang Jiawei out.
We ran over right away.
Walk around the pool.
What does it look like?
A single card.
(They cracked the clue.)
Swimming pool.
Hurry.
The swimming pool.
Ah!
I figured it out.
Hurry up.
Someone's coming.
I don't know the time.
I didn't crack
the puzzle about time.
(Match the code to a clock face and swap)
(the hour and minute hands
to get the time.)
(Invitation Card appears at 02:00.)
Shoes off.
We're looking for the card, right?
I want that date chance,
a chance to talk about the answer.
I'm really anxious.
I have to find that card.
I really want the chance for this date.
I want to go on an off-island date.
It could be something new and exciting.
No way it's in there, right?
The rain's getting heavier.
It's pouring so hard.
This rain is crazy.
What should we even do?
It's so hard to find it
in such a huge pool.
I can tell Yan really wants
a date this time.
I have to get that Invitation Card.
Still couldn't find it… I'm losing it.
(Congrats! You've found the Invitation Card.
Invite someone you like for a date.)
I got it.
No need to keep looking.
You found it?
Yes, we can leave now.
Yeah.
Really?
Yes.
Where is it?
In my pocket.
Can't let anyone snatch it.
It's glowing.
Finally, I got a date with Yang.
Finally catching up with everyone else.
Seems like it's just me and Yang
haven't gone on a date yet.
I'm looking forward to it.
Because I feel
this date might be the best.
It's a luxury date, after all.
So impressive.
Give me a hug.
I'm really moved.
Honestly, I'm deeply touched.
I never thought he'd actually find it.
I'm happy.
Hooray.
You're amazing.
Do you want to wipe your feet?
It's fine.
I'm so excited.
Let's look for the third one.
But they should've gone to
find it already.
We fools are still cracking puzzles here.
Big dummy.
You too.
Double dummies.
Hopefully no one's competing with you
for this.
They're aiming at that one.
And we won't fight you for it either.
You two are the best.
The four of us living well
is worth more than anything.
(Puzzle Book 2)
This one's really tough.
What's that?
(Puzzle Book 2)
Could it be numbers?
Or maybe like half of a letter?
That's possible.
Let's check the other side.
(Looking at the back of the puzzle)
It really does look like a letter,
honestly.
(English?)
I think it's English.
English?
Yeah.
I think it's an English word.
This one should be a "B".
(Xuan Cheng checking the puzzle
from the back)
I don't get it.
B.
O, right?
(Checking the puzzle from the back)
B, O, C.
No,
it doesn't make sense.
Check the front side.
(Back to the front puzzle)
P, B.
Something about hotpot?
That's not right.
Did you find it?
They found it.
I got it.
Xuan Cheng,
tell me, please.
This one is U.
Pub cup.
The cup from that pub.
(Pub)
(Cup)
Hurry!
Huang Jiawei, watch out!
We've been searching forever.
But still can't find it.
It's hard to spot.
Did you find it?
No.
If we fail,
it'll make us look silly.
It's not over here?
Looks like it's not here.
Could someone else have found it?
Probably not.
(The time and place have to match.)
Nothing yet?
No, still no luck.
Attention, islanders.
The first Invitation Card
has been found by Zhao Enda.
(Zhao Enda obtained the Invitation Card.)
Wow, it's really bright.
It only lights up when you touch it.
It was dark before.
Congrats to the rest of the islanders.
(Puzzle Book 2: Pub)
The other two cards' spots are unlocked.
But the time puzzles remain unsolved.
So we have to crack it.
I'll take care of this tomorrow.
(Puzzle Book 3: Car)
Alright.
Let's head back.
Grab something to eat,
Yang?
Let me.
That was pretty cool.
Why?
Because you found it?
Exactly.
I finally found it.
I've been the only one
without a date.
Guess it's my turn to go on one.
And it's even a luxury date.
Looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Finally, I can go out.
I'll get it tomorrow.
You can count on me.
I promise you that.
How do you get it
tomorrow?
I've got a plan.
You think...
You think I don't use my brain?
Don't judge a book by its cover.
I am careless sometimes,
but I'm a total hopeless romantic.
So honestly, I don't know
why you asked me
that question today.
Maybe it's because you think I look like
the kind of person who often...
keeps feelings to themselves
or sometimes does things
without much attention to detail.
But honestly, you're always on my mind.
And I just realized something.
The best part on this island
is having you with me.
(Lu Yanting & Huang Jiawei's Room)
I'll lock the car tight.
Anyway,
it must be inside the car.
(Xuan Cheng & Zhao Enda's Room)
One of the puzzle is about the pub.
We might need to
wait there directly tomorrow.
What if you can't find it tomorrow?
Then we'd have nothing to eat.
Good night.
I don't feel good.
Been searching for ages.
There's still a chance.
What if we can't find it?
Then...
I'll cook for you.
No lousy meal.
Forever yours, Xiaohan.
Han.
(Puzzle Book)
(Who will get
the remaining Invitation Cards?)
(Day 7)
Morning.
(10:30 AM)
(Two Invitation Cards left)
I realized
I might need to make the first move.
So I got up early
and became the first one
to explore the clue.
I knew the clue was the plate.
When I reached the parking spot,
I spotted the car.
But I still didn't know about the time.
Open the fuel tank?
Open the fuel tank.
(Obtained a phone)
Back then, I really wasn't sure
what the Invitation Card
would look like.
(Tape)
So I did something silly.
I took every single thing
from the car out and started
going through them.
(Files)
(Parts)
I checked everything,
but I still had no clue.
So I came up with another idea.
I decided to wait.
(There's always a way.)
I couldn't crack the puzzle about time,
so I locked the car door
and sat inside.
No one's gonna touch these things.
(10:50 AM)
Anyway, I'll go on a date with Jiayi.
(11:40 AM)
You're not going out at all?
You don't want a date?
I do, actually.
I was thinking about talking to Jiayi.
Because honestly, yesterday…
During that polygraph session,
my way of...
expressing myself…
and even my understanding…
were not on the spot.
(8 AM) So I wanted to make her breakfast
and explain to her
what was going through my mind
at the time.
Because right now, clearing up
the misunderstanding matters most.
(Waiting for Liu Jiayi)
Listen,
don't rush it.
If you're in a hurry
to explain something to Jiayi,
she might get nervous.
Yesterday, I asked that question
about our date.
At that moment, I...
But in her heart,
she feel that
your feelings for her
lean more toward logic.
If you still want to pursue her,
show her
that you genuinely like her,
not just based on
a pros-and-cons list
or whatever she seems suitable.
Don't treat her well
only after weighing the pros and cons.
Right?
You like her. That's enough.
You think she wanted you
to give a more emotional answer?
No, I didn't understand the question.
My Chinese really isn't that great.
But I think you can look at it this way,
if she actually likes you,
no matter what you say, she'll like it.
Don't get too hung up on
a perfect answer.
Because if she likes you,
she won't overthink it.
Also,
you really need to stop being so gloomy.
I'm serious.
Wow, it's pouring out there.
That's crazy rain.
Jiayi's here.
Hey, sweetheart.
Anyone in there?
Yanting and Yijia.
What's with that face?
Where are you going?
Heading back to the dorm?
Come on.
I made you breakfast.
But I've already had one.
I've had breakfast.
I spent the whole morning
cooking for you.
Aren't you coming and having a little?
I don't know what to do.
Come on.
Slow down.
The rain's pouring.
I was staying in the dorm
waiting for you.
Feels like I've waited a century.
Well, I was talking to
Tianyu about...
cracking the code.
We were...
It was frustrating.
I want to eat this one.
Is this washed?
(Yogurt and Fruit Platter)
I can handle it myself.
I'll carry my own plate.
It's fine.
You got breakfast too?
Yeah, all thanks to my bestie.
I'm so happy right now.
Time to enjoy delicious meal.
I got it, I can do it myself.
Thank you.
Come on then.
You didn't even come see me,
my bestie.
I didn't know
you came back.
I waited a century.
So envious.
Yijia, want some noodles?
I'm good.
(noodles)
He's cooking noodles.
Shrimp noodles.
Smells amazing.
Thanks for your kindness.
I should have skipped breakfast.
Look, he's having boxed meal.
You're having that?
I'm fine with this.
I'm already a bit full.
Here, you eat this.
I made it for you.
Take a bite.
Alright.
And the rest is yours.
(Boxed meal)
Otherwise, I'd feel bad.
He sat next to me eating a boxed meal.
No way.
Yeah, I'd feel bad too.
The boxed meal is good.
I'll head back to my room first.
(12:19 PM)
I think you really enjoy code breaking.
Yeah, I do.
I like solving puzzles.
Nice.
So basically,
you handle the puzzles.
and I physical stuff.
Sounds good.
Attention, islanders.
The second Invitation Card appears
right now.
(Second Invitation Card revealed)
Twelve twenty.
Please state the passcode
for the second card.
Passcode?
One three one four.
Congrats to Xuan Cheng
for getting the Invitation Card.
(Xuan Cheng received the second card)
Yes!
Now invite the person you like
to joining today's off-island date.
(One hour earlier)
(Got an important clue — the phone)
Around eleven o'clock,
I already had the phone in hand.
(Congrats!)
At twelve twenty,
(Passcode: 1314)
I saw a pop-up on the phone
(Start your date.)
about the date.
Then there was a code: 1314.
Bingo.
I guess that plan actually worked.
(Waiting by the car for the card)
Congrats!
I envy you.
I wanna go out too.
You look amazing.
Congrats!
I spent the whole morning.
I almost lost my mind over it.
I turned that car upside down.
You're incredible.
Where did you find it?
There was a phone next to that car.
Let's return this first.
No wonder I couldn't find you
this morning.
I was actually about to go look for you.
But when I stepped outside,
it was pouring rain.
So I went to the dining room.
Did you finish your black tea?
Yeah, I finished it.
I was so anxious.
Right after I got the phone,
I stayed here to wait
right by this car.
Yeah.
Waiting for it to appear?
When I first reached
this car,
I immediately locked the car door.
No one is allowed to come in.
I'm inviting you, my lady.
"My lady"?
I'm asking you out on a date.
Sure.
Would you?
Yeah, I'd love to.
They said that.
You didn't even mention it.
Of course no.
I could've gone with you.
I can't let anyone find out.
I told you
I'd get it today no matter what.
Finally, all my effort paid off.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Back then,
I was walking down that road with Wan.
How did you feel when you heard...?
I was thrilled.
Super happy.
I'm gonna take a break.
I'm exhausted.
I'll take a rest.
Then I'll get changed.
Okay?
Let me walk you upstairs.
Oh, so you do remember to walk me.
So you do know...
Yeah, sorry about that.
Okay.
You only walk me
when I've done something big?
That's not it.
Go ahead.
Go have some fun.
See you.
When are you guys heading out?
No idea.
I wanna ask
how you figured it out.
I have no idea.
No clue at all.
Out to have fun again.
So excited.
I forgot to add cilantro for you today.
You even have cilantro?
You can add it tomorrow.
Alright.
Any ideas for tomorrow's meal?
Why that face?
I'll make it.
Honestly, everything.
Then it's up to you.
Yep.
Then get ready for a surprise.
Is this yours?
Yeah.
Mind if I drink it?
Go on, take a sip.
Alright.
Perfect.
(15 mins earlier)
Did you finish that black tea?
Yeah.
Good.
(Xuan Cheng's Tea)
Attention, islanders.
(Third Invitation Card. 12:45 PM)
The third card is coming soon.
Only one Date Card left.
I'm searching everywhere for it.
Turning this place upside down.
I really want to go out with him.
An off-island date.
Please
don't wear yourselves out.
Just wait.
The clue is already in our hands.
I want to know what he's thinking.
That's why I tried my best back then.
Did any of you guess the time right?
(Who will get the last Invitation Card?)
("Live and Love" Release Schedule)
(Next Episode Preview)
I've got a feeling.
If I cannot be with you,
I'll miss you like crazy.
Completely crazy.
But you make me feel kind of unsafe.
What?
You mean you think
we're not a good match
and you and he are better together?
(Dating History; Personal Info & Spending)
Tonight, the Dark Night Forest opens.
The Dark Night Forest on the island
is the mirror space closest to reality.
What do you mean by
"different paths of growth"?
How could you check my dating history?
I'm so mad I could scream.
Now I regret it.
(Every Wed at 12 PM)
(Pursue Love on Balance Island)
Trust me.
I trust you.
You're good at this game.
But I am not.
I have the intelligence
and you have the brawn.
A perfect team.
I've never been to the seaside before.
This feels amazing.
Even my mood's lifted.
Yeah.
The puzzle we had earlier.
The drawing was such a mess.
I've never been on such a formal date.
Me neither.
I got a nickname, Bai.
Because your skin's fair.
(Bai)
I'll put it on my bag.
It'll make me think of you.
What if
you don't want to be with me?
I can't accept that.
Then why aren't we together?
(Every Thu. at noon)
Hi, I'm actor Wang Kaimu.
(Watch Live and Love with us.)
I'm actress Wang Gege.
(Excited)
This is my first time shipping others.
Can't wait to see "Live and Love".
He's secretly pleased.
He secretly enjoyed that.
I take back what I just said.
(Message withdrawn)
Seems
she's...
Handsome and gorgeous.
(Can't help it)
They're a good match.
You really can't remember Huang Jiawei?
(Bringing up the wrong topic)
Focus on shipping others.
(Hold up)
Why does it feel like I'm watching a drama?
(Brilliant!)
(They treated the village chief like an NPC)
He's part of their game.
He intentionally opened it
in front of Jiawei.
They are
(Is this okay?)
right next to him.
Stop it, or he's gonna cry.
(I'm fine)
I can't wait to see what happens next.
(So anxious)
Fidgeting nonstop.
I really hope someone
will break them apart.