Dating's like racing.
You gotta dare to hit the gas.
I think pinching ears works.
Want to try my drink?
Kinda sweet.
Yours looks like cherry blossoms.
So pretty.
But you gotta nail the brakes,
know when to pause
and when to make a move.
(Know when to pause and
when to make a move)
As you move forward, you have to
keep your speed in check.
I've actually been wanting to
find a chance to talk to you.
You're too slow.
You three just enjoy yourselves.
Everyone's happiness is real happiness.
Liu Jiayi and Xuan Cheng team formed.
Before the finish line.
No winner yet.
No.
No no.
What are you doing?
Why are you still...
I picked it.
Looks amazing.
I just like you
staying with me alone.
No one else.
So happy.
I'm so happy.
Your joy is my joy.
Next up,
I'm going all in.
=Episode 6 (Part 1)=
=She Escapes, He Trails Closely=
Their dates might boil down to
picking one of two.
Pick one.
So he picked the other one.
No, just a guess.
Not sure if it's right.
I'm guessing.
Yesterday
girls got to pick two boys.
Why can boys choose two girls?
Not fair.
Haven't you wanted to
get to know other boys?
Yeah.
Let's chat.
Let's chat now.
Yeah.
You can get to know...
Who wants to chat with me?
Totally fine.
Aren't we chatting now?
Didn't we play that
Food Sneaker yesterday?
Wanna play?
How about Pictionary?
Sure.
I think we should play it like this.
Everyone has a paper on their head.
Yeah, that one.
Right?
Like…
Just guess...
Exactly.
And it's right.
Guess ours.
Like I can ask
something.
The other person can only say yes or no.
Fun.
Yeah, just yes or no.
Let's go.
Each person writes one thing.
One sheet per person.
Then pass it to the next person.
We can write anything, right?
Yep.
People,
animals,
whatever.
Done?
Yeah.
Wan.
Here.
Okay.
Give it to me.
Let me see.
Hold on.
Who starts first?
I'll go first.
(Father-in-law)
Is it a person?
Yes.
(Athena Chu)
Is it an adjective?
No.
Is it a person?
(Ultraman)
(King Kong)
Could be.
No way.
Maybe.
No.
(Liu Jiayi)
Is it a three-character name?
Yeah.
I think I've got it.
If you know, just say it.
It's...
Is it Liu Jiayi?
(You actually got it)
I win.
Alright.
Is it a person?
Guess so.
What's yours?
Is it four characters?
Yep.
Knew you'd pick an idiom.
Wow, you're confident.
What's going through your mind?
Honestly, I've been holding back.
Trying not to think about Jiayi's date.
But honestly, I can't.
It's the other way around now, huh?
I'm worried my mood
might affect everyone.
You're done playing?
I'll head back to my room to rest.
First pick
is Jiayi, no doubt about it.
(Group 1 Off-Island Date: Lu Yanting & Liu Jiayi)
For the Group 2,
I had no clue who to choose.
Then I remembered
Yijia was next to me today.
(Chen Yijia)
So I picked her.
My heart was racing like crazy.
I was terrified
I wouldn't pick the option with Jiayi.
Hello.
(Liu Jiayi & Lu Yanting's Date)
What's wrong?
When I saw it was Jiayi,
I finally
felt relieved.
You know, it really scared me.
What happened?
I hesitated for so long.
The right one was just darker.
And somehow, my gut
told me
that darker might symbolize
a kind of affection.
I wasn't sure though,
so I picked the right.
I was so worried
it could be someone else.
You know?
Thank goodness.
Good thing I got picked.
That was scary.
Are you hungry?
Not really.
We just haven't eaten yet.
I brought a ton of food.
Even savory stuff..
I went all out packing.
I stuffed it all in my clothes.
Happy I won today?
Of course.
Alright.
I was so nervous, you know?
I had no idea.
If it was someone else,
you'd be stuck
on the island with Charlie all day.
And then who knows what might happen.
Yeah.
Waiting on the island yesterday
was so stressful,
honestly.
Had no idea how you were with...
I was
stressed too.
Really stressed.
Because of those ducks, right?
Got something exciting for you today.
I like this.
Actually, we both
like driving.
Miss.
You can pick a racing suit here.
Alright.
I wonder what color she'll wear.
- I'll wear the same
- Her?
Changing room is there.
Let's go.
Come on.
Go.
Looking cool.
Right?
So handsome.
You're cooler.
That outfit really suits you.
Your hair's kinda long.
Might need to tie it up.
Can I give you a hair tie?
Yeah, but this one's a bit small.
Small?
Can't even loop it twice.
Wait, you can tie hair?
Nope.
I'm learning right now.
Then you…
You're a pro racer.
That's how
pro racers gear up.
They'll have
mechanics...
Mechanic.
This is how mechanics
gear racers up.
I'll be your mechanic.
Mechanic No. 11.
Come on.
Let's go.
(Welcome to Hai Nan Ji Xing Ka Ding Che)
Karting in the rain.
Come on.
It's a two-seater.
I want to see you drive first.
Sorry.
I'll go first.
Sit on the left.
Step right onto the seat.
Yeah.
Right hand.
Slide it through.
Later,
if rain gets on your face,
just wipe it gently
with the back of your hand.
First time in a two-seater.
Let's go.
I'll sit.
Right pedal.
Let's go.
(Welcome to Hai Nan Ji Xing Ka Ding Che)
Which way?
Turn inward.
That's it.
I can't make the turn.
Nice, take it slow.
(Karting newbie)
Yeah.
Take the corner.
Don't turn.
It's fine.
When you're coming out of a turn,
don't press the gas pedal.
Especially on rainy days,
the car can skid.
(Patient coaching)
Once you exit the turn,
that's when you accelerate.
Not during.
No worries.
We'll take it slow.
Yeah, right.
Let's drive the first lap nice and slow.
No rush.
Before you enter the turn,
you can hug the outer line.
Take it slow.
Pull it back in.
Then turn.
Yeah, press down.
(Getting the hang of it)
Yeah.
Yeah, then head this way.
Pull again, pull it outward.
Right.
Yep.
Awesome.
You're picking this up fast.
(Encouragement)
Alright, next turn.
Lift.
Right.
(Perfect teamwork)
Fantastic.
This is fun.
Okay, go!
Go!
You're learning so fast.
Yeah?
It looks so fun.
I really love it.
No problem, go for it.
Floor it.
Yeah, step on it.
This is so much fun.
I've never driven a two-seater kart
with someone before.
Today
feels totally different.
Because
he's right next to me.
Feels like there's this energy
between us.
So thrilling.
Super fun.
Let me take you for a spin, okay?
Okay.
I basically got a face wash out here.
But it's so fun.
You picked it up really fast, though.
Really?
Yeah, you totally are.
Wait.
Hold on, I...
Let me give you a hand.
I'm coming over to help you.
Hold on to the seat.
Both sides of the seat, yep.
Stand up, yeah.
Nice.
Everything's soaked.
Fun, right?
So fun.
I think it's super fun.
I think it's
even better in the rain.
Come on.
If you get scared, just tell me.
Okay.
So fun.
Epic, huh?
I've always
driven karts alone.
This is my first time having someone
next to me,
and it's the girl I like.
Karting at night
in pouring rain.
It just feels extra thrilling.
This date
couldn't be better.
It feels like we're not karting.
We were at a water park.
You drove so well.
What?
You.
Was it fun?
Super fun.
Pros are different.
I nearly got thrown right off.
I ordered that outfit.
You can change into it later.
It looks great.
Turns out this is
the kind of date I need.
Head up.
Yeah.
Yeah, push it.
Okay.
This is so much fun.
I feel (like)...
I'm a little soaked.
It's fine, you're soaked too.
I'm seriously soaked.
You're soaked.
But somehow,
even prettier.
More fun than watching ducks, huh?
Let's go.
Tired?
Nope, so fun.
Not tired.
Not even a little tired.
Let's not go back.
Let's stay here.
We're back.
Here you are.
Home.
Want to eat?
What's this?
Fried chicken.
It's pretty good.
You skipped lunch, right?
Yeah, but I had a big breakfast.
So it's fine.
I'll cook for you tomorrow.
So you mean...
How are you feeling now?
Maybe you've noticed that...
I'm feeling a bit nervous.
Honestly, I get nervous
around you too.
Yeah.
Feels like we're both the type
who get nervous being together.
I can totally sense that.
Do you think
today was better?
Way better, right?
Me?
I think I was way better.
Not bad.
Ten percent.
Maybe ten to twenty percent better.
That's all?
No, I mean for you it's like,
like…
Letting loose.
Yeah.
In this area.
Hope you can
open up more.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Honestly, if you are...
All my friends always say
that I'm probably the funny one.
Funny?
But I feel like I
haven't really shown that side yet.
I haven't felt your humor either.
Don't I look like a clown?
Nope.
Just joking.
After this date,
my crush level
definitely went up.
I hope their hobbies
are exactly this type, yeah.
Because
they could bring so many
new experiences into my life.
Well, it just so happens that he
is really good at this kind of thing.
I can totally picture
living with someone like him.
Hello.
Have a seat.
Thanks.
Didn't expect it'd be you.
Surprised?
Why did you pick me?
My first choice was Yan.
I did feel a bit more drawn to her.
(Chen Yijia)
The other one was Yijia.
Why did you choose Yijia?
She said she was
sad or something yesterday.
I was kind of surprised.
My guess was totally off.
But...
I also think
it's not bad.
Meeting new people
and getting to know them is nice.
(A Breezy Day)
I mean my
impression of you.
I think
you give off
girl-next-door vibes.
That makes me feel like you're
warm and approachable.
I think.
Oh no, my outfit today's
way too mature.
I think it
suits you.
Thanks.
How've you been feeling
lately?
I was in a bad mood yesterday.
Cried until my eyes were swollen.
So today I've been wearing glasses.
How about now?
If we have something tasty to eat...
I'd feel better.
Yeah.
So you first started with...
We all called him the Beijinger.
Right.
Zhang, Zhang Zizheng.
You called him Zhang, right?
So you hung out with him a bit
more at first.
On the first night, during dinner,
we exchanged a few words.
Then the next day,
I could tell
he might have a little crush on me.
He's the type of guy
I had a huge crush on
back in school.
Flashy.
Outgoing.
Trying to look cool
or to catch girls' attention.
So seeing him
brings back old memories
and feels familiar,
but it's
not love.
If I really liked him,
I would've given him more signs and
he wouldn't
turn to someone else.
But people are complicated.
The moment he looked to someone else,
I still felt a little hurt.
Yeah.
And
I cried yesterday also because
it felt like everyone else has
someone they like.
But
I don't.
Then why didn't you
ask anyone out?
Sometimes I just feel
afraid to move first.
Mostly worried I'll bother them.
True.
It sounds easy.
Everyone says "Be proactive."
But honestly,
when it's your turn to
step up like that,
you hesitate for ages.
Yeah.
Right?
Wonder if there are
any other
activities when we get back.
Probably just casting
the affection weight.
Do you hesitate
when you vote?
Not really.
I voted for
Yan
both times. Yeah.
Wind chimes.
This scene...
It feels just right to me.
The sound of wind chimes
mingling with the sea breeze,
ting-a-ling.
I love listening to the ocean.
Just hearing that sound,
makes me feel so at ease.
I love the sound of rain.
It happened to rain today.
Just yesterday,
I was feeling a bit down.
And I thought,
"I wanna leave."
But this morning, when I woke up,
I thought,
"So what?
then I'll just be myself."
Being myself makes me happy and relaxed.
And tonight,
I even got a date.
Once my mood shifted,
everything started falling into place.
Mood changed a lot.
Yeah.
Cheers.
Tonight was really fun.
Yeah, it wasn't bad.
Thanks for taking me out.
No problem.
(Wu Yihan & Yang Tianyu,
on the way back to Balance Island)
Actually,
our time together today
feels a bit different.
I think
you're interesting today.
Thanks.
Right?
Do you argue with people?
Rarely.
If we ever argue,
it could be kind of fun.
Because your
Chinese...
Your Mandarin
is slow.
Best we don't argue.
Like you panic
in Cantonese,
but not in Mandarin, right?
Can you
- speak (Mandarin)?
- Not exactly.
You can't understand.
But your Mandarin
is slow.
And you can't out-talk me.
I'll try to speed up.
Just have to win, huh?
You go Cantonese, I go Sichuanese.
Own languages.
And no one gets it.
Alien talk.
So, which day in October
is your birthday?
The fifth?
Libra.
Right.
Exactly matches Balance Island.
It's actually my home.
Yeah, you shouldn't have left there.
You'll leave today.
We'll leave together.
Together.
If I'm not happy, neither are you.
We all suffer.
Hurry and go home.
Looking forward to what's next?
Kind of excited.
Me too.
After today,
even more to look forward to.
Really?
Yeah.
Why?
It's tough.
Vote.
Shaken?
So hard.
But I think if
you're interested in me,
like when it comes to
spending time together on the island,
I hope you can be
a little...
(You get me?)
Enthusiastic.
Yeah.
Smart.
I don't think Michael would mind, right?
Michael?
Yeah.
Wait, meaning?
Zizheng.
He wouldn't mind, would he?
But you asking me out,
isn't that totally normal?
Totally normal?
Right.
But this morning, I asked him,
what if...
(This morning)
What if another guy asked her out,
would you be mad?
I would
feel sad.
Not exactly angry though.
After all, I didn't
get the chance to ask her out.
Then would you, because of him,
if he felt a little upset,
would
you give up on asking me out?
I chose you.
Yeah.
Wait.
When are they coming back?
(The ones staying home)
I never thought you two would be here.
Really.
I was gonna say...
Can Hanhan be here?
You're upset.
You can't be with Han, right?
Devastated.
What will you do?
I don't believe
that Han would...
Waver.
You two talked once,
and you're already so sure?
Totally.
She's sad about Guanjie.
Guanjie.
I'm not sad about Guanjie.
Not sadness.
Just speechless.
Alright.
Kinda disappointed.
So you better value...
Value the ones who are sincere to you.
No.
I mean, from now on.
From now on.
(From now on, value who's with you now)
I get what you mean.
You're saying
if she wants to talk to someone else,
then she shouldn't...
Don't keep
- coming to me.
- Don't keep acting like
- you're already decided on me.
- Yeah.
And I hate that feeling.
It's so confusing.
You know?
It's fine.
I've done that once.
(The event passed,
but the feeling didn't)
You mean me?
I was joking.
No, have you ever thought
that all those weird behaviors of yours?
Just kidding.
I was joking.
Did you notice that?
No.
Right.
Every single time, he's like that.
He always loses his temper at me.
(Wronged)
I've never lost my temper at you!
I've never snapped at you.
You have.
None.
Really.
We didn't know that.
I swear.
Earlier, when we played
Undercover,
(Warranted)
I talked to him,
then he left for no reason.
We both go in together
to play that, right?
Then we went in.
He sat there.
(Proof)
I sat here.
He just sat there. Not a word to me.
Like...
(Day 2, Night)
We're playing Undercover.
Okay.
(The longest distance in the world)
So why was that?
(Side A answers:)
No idea.
(Side B answers:)
Strange to me.
So strange to me.
He never told me anything.
I never knew at all.
No.
Explain it.
Why?
I don't know anything.
Then he never talked to me again.
Then I left the island, okay.
Wait.
Let me finish!
Hold on.
No.
Listen to me.
Hear me out.
Ha.
First, when we're about to play,
we were already about to
draw lots.
No.
Almost.
Yeah.
Was drawing colored stones my fault?
No, you...
Were you gonna say it straight today?
You can say it.
It is what it is.
Say it.
Fine, let's be honest.
I think it's totally fine
that you went on a date.
No issue
to me.
Because you drew it.
Right?
OK.
But
when you came back the next day,
you were different.
Watching the drama.
Eating dinner.
How was my vibe off?
Because you
didn't even talk to me.
No, no.
You two...
Back then, the vibes were
really, really, really,
really...
Feels like you two
were meant to be.
You wouldn't talk to me.
No.
I said it before.
When you went to talk to him,
I didn't want to intrude.
You know that?
That was my intention.
It's not that I'm upset.
You said you'd leave me alone
while I got to know him.
Then there's no follow-up.
No need to say anything.
What I mean is,
when you're talking to another person,
I don't want to bother you guys.
And I don't want to pressure the guy.
(Seen enough, Eaten enough)
After your day together,
I felt like you two
were really, really,
really in sync. Locked as a couple.
Am I right, guys?
(Agree, type 1)
Yeah.
(Totally agreed)
Locked.
Yeah, when you came back,
your vibe with Guanjie...
Everyone could tell
you two were basically
glued to each other.
Maybe from your perspective,
you were looking out for him.
Yeah, as someone
who didn't know the details,
I really thought you two
made a great match.
You two talked so well that day,
and your acts were...
You know?
(Not listening, Not listening)
Never heard her talk like that.
I wasn't alive back then.
I was...
I was a warm "corpse".
I think
village chief misunderstood.
You know?
You're...
You never asked me.
You never talked to me.
And you never took the initiative.
You think binding is binding?
What's up with you?
No, I...
Never say anything.
I've noticed
you never take the initiative
to talk.
Yeah.
You always talk to us.
(Opinion trend)
He goes for it with boys.
Yeah.
You never said a word to me.
I had no idea.
Then I can't...
Did I say yes when I said...
I'll go all in.
Fine, I'll be honest.
You're like this,
let's talk it out, okay?
(Lay it out again)
Sure.
Lay it out.
Here's what I'm thinking.
On the first day, after the vote,
you asked if I went all in.
Came up to ask me that.
The next day.
The first day.
After the first day's vote, you asked.
No.
You definitely said that.
After day one's vote,
I was standing there.
And you said, "All in?"
No way.
Will you go all in?
(Day 1, before the evening vote)
I'm fed up.
I barely knew anyone that first day.
Then you said that.
Then the next day, you said that again.
Interesting.
No, I...
No.
I never pushed you to do anything.
Right?
But you never talked to me
about us.
I feel like you're not
in a relationship.
You're chasing her.
You know?
I also told you a lot yesterday.
What did you tell me yesterday?
Say it.
You were just there.
You wished me happiness there.
What did I reply?
"Okay."
"Thanks for wishing me happiness."
I sat there.
Then he came over
and wished me happiness.
I was shocked.
What was I supposed to say?
Wait.
Are you serious?
No.
Hear me out first.
I'd want to leave too if I heard that.
Last night.
Were they alone
together all day?
So after their alone time,
you went
- talk to her.
- Yeah.
It was last night.
I didn't want
things to get awkward.
I also wish...
Wait.
You give me the vibe
that you're way too nice.
Too nice.
But that's honestly how I feel.
Then why are you even dating?
I also did something.
Day one and day two.
Who was as proactive as me?
Who?
Day one and day two, who outdid me?
What exactly did you do
on those first two days?
What did you do?
She can't even remember.
I remember how nice he was to me.
But on our first date,
he only talked about the island.
Never about personal stuff.
(Really?)
Not right.
Village chief, your fault.
We did talk about that.
We didn't.
You kept telling me
what was going on the island.
(Day 2 Date)
Today, while Evan was cooking,
he interacted a lot with one Yijia.
As for Michael,
I think he's pretty nice.
Yesterday they wanted Malatang.
I said it's fine.
I said I'd cook for them.
I actually think about
how everyone feels.
I really enjoy helping everyone
with their love problems.
He was telling me about that.
Why do you talk to girls
exactly like you talk to guys?
Yeah.
When I talked to him that day,
he felt so much like a bro.
It's so ridiculous it's funny.
Even now, I'm still a bit
unsure what to do.
My bad.
Let me toast you.
Sorry.
(Is that right?)
"Toast you"?
Toast me.
Sorry.
Let me apologize.
I need to go get my clothes later.
Get the clothes?
Now?
Let's go.
Are you cold?
A little bit.
Wait for me at the door for a sec.
Okay.
You still have a first-aid kit.
Come on.
Okay.
Why not hang out here?
A comfortable place.
Right.
That works.
It's more fun over there.
Bring the paper and pen over.
Lots of puddles.
Hey,
what do we play?
Werewolf,
or...
Werewolf.
Come on.
Wanna sit next to him?
I'll sit on the floor.
Why sit on the floor?
Sit nearby.
You can sit there.
Move over a bit.
Water keeps splashing up.
Where's that water coming from?
Some spots are
leaking up there.
My clothes are wrinkled.
It's fine.
What's wrong? Did I wrinkle it?
No.
Wrinkled before.
Didn't iron it.
I didn't wear it.
The one you draped over last time.
I know.
Then give mine back.
And used someone else's.
His feels warmer?
His feels comfier?
Honestly, this one.
Honestly.
Which suit do you like more?
The nice design?
The look?
No.
You always have to be like... yeah.
I think a lot should be
talked about in private.
Let's go.
Are you leaving?
We'll chat for a bit.
Chat.
Go to chat.
I saw you two talked a lot yesterday.
Talked the whole day.
No, I...
I...
Lower your umbrella a little.
How should I put this...
I mean...
You know, from the night
before I left the island,
until that morning,
I stayed with him the whole time.
Back then,
me and Guanjie
weren't locked in at all.
After we came back,
you never spoke to me.
So I had no idea what you meant.
You know I'm a bit of
a passive person.
I can't
just walk up to you and say
"Why haven't you talked to me?"
when you haven't said a word.
After that, I basically
stuck with him.
Mostly because,
well,
back then,
I was scared it was all in my head.
So I even
asked someone else.
I said, "Do you get this vibe?"
What vibe?
That you two
were being a bit flirty.
Then?
They said
a little bit.
Honestly,
we had a good talk those couple of days.
I know.
Yeah.
After all, we were...
You never talked to me.
He was the only person I could talk to.
Anyway, I'm the type of person...
Well,
you know me.
Whoever...
Whoever you talk to
or hang with,
you just stick with them.
No.
I wouldn't talk to
someone I didn't like.
I'm someone who cares about
feedback.
I'm the one who...
Don't I need the feedback?
You need the feedback,
not me?
As a boy,
I feel like I also need feedback
from others.
Did I not give you feedback?
Let me be honest.
I've always thought
you were nice.
But
here's the thing I don't like.
Every time something happens,
you'll throw...
You just...
No attitude from me.
You give one to me.
And I just...
I never did that.
The night before I left the island.
I never blamed you.
Wait.
I really don't blame you.
Never blamed anyone.
Wait.
ON Day one, Day two,
I didn't talk to anyone.
Day three,
after you all came back…
Only then did I…
What exactly happened to us?
Day one, nothing happened.
On day one…
We had a little bit of a
flirty vibe.
By Day two, you called it flirting.
I can get it.
But on the first day?
On Day one, it was...
A little bit.
Kind of.
When you came back,
it wasn't the same.
It's in the past now, doesn't matter.
I just think,
even now,
if he came back,
like he was forced to
go on a date with someone else.
The main thing is
I don't know.
So what if...
Why do you keep thinking about him?
Why?
Why...
It's got nothing to do with you.
Because I don't want to...
So the vibe you're giving me now is…
Then what do you want me to do?
How come I'm telling you
what to do?
What do you think you should do?
What should I do?
Now, I just...
Totally normal...
Anyway, I...
can't...
You're so hard to talk to.
How hard to talk to?
I've gone pretty quiet now.
It's just you...
You don't even have an answer
in your heart.
You can think about it.
Wait.
You mean the answer is…
I get what you mean.
You mean,
if he comes back,
he'll explain it to me.
Like, in what way?
In the case of something.
You're saying I'll go by him
and...
You mean that?
Yeah, you mean that too.
Right?
You mean that too.
I just...
How to put it.
Anyway, when I'm with him...
Just...
I...
I honestly have no idea right now.
Anyway, I just...
Well, if
he gave you an explanation?
It hasn't even happened yet.
Shouldn't you wait for him first,
then ask me?
Or I tell you later?
Then it feels like...
Okay, if he comes to explain
and does a good job,
you can go on.
If not,
okay.
We can still stick together.
That's how I feel.
You get it?
But it feels like what you mean is
I either have to stick with him,
or stick with you.
Right?
It's not about "sticking".
But you make me feel like
that I can't be my own free person.
I have to
go register with someone immediately.
Wait, hold on.
Aren't you sticking with
whoever's around?
Two days ago, you stick with me.
Why did I stick with you two days ago?
Then stick with him.
What?
Do you understand?
Wait.
You're really messing with my head.
What exactly did I do?
But on Day one and two,
I felt it wasn't like with Guanjie.
That level of commitment.
Like that...
Because we...
How many times have I dated Guanjie?
Three times.
Maybe that was just my illusion.
Illusion?
That's how it felt to me.
Yeah, that's how I felt.
I think you still...
Wait.
Compared to Guanjie,
if he didn't show up,
I'd feel
you and I had a deeper thing.
But with Guanjie, it feels more like
he's the one I commit to.
I mean, because I've had too much
contact with him.
I get it.
But
back when Guanjie reached out to me,
you didn't reach out to me even once.
That felt
silent to me.
Talking to you,
but no answer.
Let's go inside.
It's freezing.
So,
what do you want to hear?
What do you want to hear?
Like, who do I really
choose to be with?
Right?
I'm dying to know the time.
Me too.
Same here.
Why aren't they back yet?
What time is it now?
I just want to go sleep.
I'm not waiting for them.
I just want to chat.
Chat with who?
He only wants to
talk to one person.
I just want to know
how was the date today?
A bit jealous.
Had fun
on that date?
Why don't they come back?
REally.
Let's rest in the room for a while.
If you go, you won't find...
You don't even know when
they're back.
I feel like I'm the Expectant Wife Rock.
We back...
What if they miss us
when we go back to the room?
And come looking for us.
Waiting eagerly.
When will they be back?
You hurry back.
I just want them to come back soon.
Still not back.
Waited forever, they still aren't back.
Feels like ages have passed.
Why aren't they back yet?
Cold?
Pretty cold.
Not cold?
Give this to the village chief to wear.
Clothe.
Alright.
Not cold?
I'm fine.
Full of energy.
I'm so tired from waiting.
Will they ever come back?
Still not back.
(Wu Guanjie & Chen Yijia
return to Balance Island)
Careful.
Don't step in the water.
Alright.
Will anyone be in the Dining Room
to welcome us?
No idea.
Did you guys do it yesterday?
Can't remember.
Okay, I hear voices.
Sit all together.
Should we go over?
Let's go.
Hello.
Did you two go out?
Why is only us back?
Yeah, you're the first.
We were the first to get back.
Yeah.
What did you do for fun?
We had dinner.
Yep.
You look gorgeous today.
The necklace is pretty.
So pretty.
What's this for?
Why were you out for so long?
The drive was far.
That far?
Yeah.
So you just went out for a meal?
And then had a couple of drinks.
Oh, just some drinks.
Just the two of you?
Nice.
I'd be annoyed too.
So I kept a sour face.
Oh no.
I honestly can't fake it.
I'm terrible at hiding my emotions.
At that moment,
I really didn't know what to do.
I feel stuck whether I leave or stay.
I had no idea what to do.
Is this yours?
No.
I hoped Guanjie would
pull me aside for a talk.
Or just say something to me.
But he didn't.
He just sat there.
I was like, what's he even doing there?
And then
it got awkward.
Why are your pants wet?
It was raining.
I wanna know, did you
actually set up a date?
Or two?
One.
Only one?
That long?
Do you know what time it was?
Getting impatient?
No.
No, I just wanted to ask.
Half past nine.
Half past nine now.
It's about nine forty now.
Okay.
That long.
When we left, it was...
Only three hours ago?
Feels like ten years already.
Because you were anxious.
So Han went on a date
with Tianyu.
Okay.
Han's back.
Hello.
We baked a cake.
Baked a cake?
Yeah.
Tianyu.
Who called me?
Where you headed?
Going for dinner.
Then where were you going just now?
My room.
Let's chat?
Sure.
Let's go.
So jealous.
You made it yourselves?
Yeah.
Is it good?
It's good.
I'm passing.
It's really tasty.
You did this yourselves?
Yeah.
That's actually pretty decent.
Not bad.
How is it?
No good.
Not good.
Is it good?
It's bad.
Right?
Bad?
This is bad?
Is it good?
No!
You're crazy.
Just made a cake.
Didn't eat dinner?
We did eat.
Eat what?
Dinner.
Just...
That many steps?
Yeah.
How does it feel?
Feel what?
What's going on here?
Nothing, just
talked to her.
Did you guys
get along well?
Yeah,
talked really well.
I think
he
isn't quite like I imagined.
I thought
he was
really boring at first.
But
once we talked,
not bad, really.
Yeah, we
got along great.
No awkward silences,
no hard time talking.
Got it.
So when you went out with her today,
like dinner, date, talking or something,
did I cross your mind?
In your head.
At first,
I was
gonna wait for you.
But while you were hanging out with her,
did you think of me?
Did I pop up in your thoughts?
When we were
talking about something,
your name came up too,
along with a few others.
You didn't answer directly.
I'm kinda worried
what do you think of him.
Right?
I haven't thought that far.
I just feel like today
we had a great chat.
But I think,
given everyone's personality
on the Island,
we'd all get along great
when we go out.
Yeah, for sure.
You seem hesitant.
Feels like she likes
outgoing guys.
Just like me.
That warm vibe,
I mean, when two people...
Like that day,
when we just arrived.
That feeling of being happy together.
I really enjoy that kind of vibe.
Just...
Not overthinking,
just relaxing.
It makes me happy.
I'm
all about
that energy too.
At first, I could feel
a little bit of kindness
from Tianyu.
You can just say it.
It's fine.
Yeah.
I mean, I could feel
a little kindness from him.
Just...
Yeah.
That's what I mean.
Because he
asked you right in front of me,
like, if asked me out,
would you be mad?
Remember?
Of course I'd be mad.
I admit I'm still kind of...
Everyone around knows.
I was like, why isn't she back yet?
Anyway,
what I'm sure of won't change.
I won't ask more.
Let's just take our time.
I don't think
her answer satisfied me.
Han was stuttering while
answering.
I could tell
she was
holding back.
I just said,
take our time.
We've still got time.
I need to hit the restroom too.
Let's go.
Just the three of us now.
I'm back.
Come on.
I took a short break.
Besides Werewolf,
what else did you play?
We played...
Pictionary.
I wanna draw.
Is this the paper they gave us?
Okay then, I'll draw.
Go ahead.
Sure.
I'm gonna draw myself.
A super cute version of me.
You're so good.
Everyone here's got lots of talents.
I haven't shown mine yet.
Just kidding and boasting.
There's 1314.
Did you see me dance?
I didn't see you dancing.
Can you show me now?
I did a little for them the other day.
Sitting here, you'll get raindrops.
Then where should I sit?
Move a bit over there.
Do you...
Do you feel it?
Not really.
Only over there it's dripping.
I'll sit here.
When I saw you just now, you looked…
It's fine.
You're wearing a jacket.
Where's my jacket then?
In my room.
You gonna get it?
It's fine.
So why not wear mine?
I was so confused.
No idea why you're chatting with me.
Not talking about the real stuff.
Just random small talk
sitting next to me.
I was just...
I'm already giving you a cold stare.
Why did you take so long?
What?
What are you saying?
Say what?
What did you say?
I need to go to the restroom.
Right now?
I really gotta go.
I have to use the bathroom.
Let's go.
Actually, it tastes good.
Guite tasty.
It's just us two now, village chief.
Just the two of us left.
Yeah, what can we play?
It's fine. From now on,
I'll be like your brother.
You're my brother now.
I've always wanted an older brother.
(Just need one)
When I was a kid, Mom asked if I wanted siblings.
I said I wanted a brother.
No problem.
Come here and find a brother works too.
Brother.
Sounds good.
(Sister's code)
You're my sis now.
(Brother-Sister Pact)
How is it?
How are you feeling?
You look pretty happy, bro.
Why did you go on a date?
No.
This wasn't my choice.
It was fate.
If it's fate's doing,
what can I say?
No, there's no name written on it.
It was a blind selection.
You know?
Those two lipsticks.
One was small.
You thought that was mine.?
Yeah.
And the other one was huge.
You know.
No, it's just I wear more of it.
It left a mark right then.
So, are you happy today?
It was normal.
Meet someone new.
A new friend, or...?
A new friend.
I didn't talk to anyone else.
Just chat.
After your date today,
did you see her as a date,
or just a friend?
Definitely as a friend.
We didn't have...
And it's only been one dinner.
One chat.
Then what about me?
How many times have we eaten together?
Three times.
Right.
So… what about me?
About you what?
Is it a friendship vibe or a date vibe?
Well…
We're together almost every day.
Obviously a date.
Otherwise a friend?
Alright then.
I'm gonna hit the restroom.
Okay, fine.
Hurry up.
Wait for me.
A hard-hitting question.
Just do that to you.
Wait for me.
That's more like it.
Hello.
Why'd you change clothes?
More comfortable.
Let's take a walk.
I've been upset with you tonight.
Just now, when I went to eat,
they told me
I could have free time.
And then you...
I just got really upset.
I just feel like you…
And then someone told me…
They said you still wanna know…
You're jealous.
Totally jealous.
You said… you think…
What do you think?
Why are you laughing?
You look like you're having fun.
Nope.
Wait.
You think I'm enjoying this?
Really happy?
You are happy.
No.
No, you're in a great mood today.
Were you this happy tonight?
No.
Then what is it?
No, I saw you get jealous.
It was funny.
Wait, you think I'm jealous
and it's funny?
Just...
Wait.
So you really think I'm funny?
Not that funny.
I said...
You're cute.
Then tell me, tonight,
will you vote for someone else?
If you do, I'll "stab" you.
I'll...
I'd do this to you.
Will you?
Will you? Answer me.
Why do you think I'd
(choose someone else)?
When I see a girl being sweet,
I just feel kind of
touched.
Cute.
Yeah, it's actually pretty cute.
Yeah, so I usually can't resist.
That was so awkward just now.
What happened?
He asked her,
"Why aren't you wearing my clothe?"
I heard...
Who?
What's up?
What is it?
Whose clothe?
Who?
Yes.
Really?
I was right by her.
It was so awkward.
Who's wearing whose clothe?
It's fine.
Who are you saying wore your clothe?
No one wore my clothe.
I'm so ready for the tea.
Who?
Can you finish before you leave?
Why did you let someone else
wear your clothe?
You go first.
I can explain it to them.
Okay?
It's fine. I'm here.
You can explain too.
Who?
So,
there were some circumstances,
and the tension between
the village chief and Yan was resolved.
Yeah.
So tonight, just...
Yan might feel a bit cold,
so the village vhief just...
Gave her the clothe.
Then Guanjie said...
Guanjie saw it.
(Beijing Guan)
Why aren't you wearing my clothe?
You're not mimicking him right at all.
Well, I am.
But go slower.
He talks slowly.
Why aren't you wearing my clothe?
No.
Then why are Enda's clothe in your hand?
Because he was cold too.
Yeah, he got cold in the end as well.
And then you took Enda's clothe.
Doesn't matter now. It's fine.
Are you cold?
Put it on?
I'm not cold.
Not cold at all?
Really.
Yeah.
The question you just asked me.
I haven't asked you yet.
Go ahead.
Earlier, you
asked me the Truth question inside.
Can we play
(See more in bonus)
Pictionary?
What's the punishment for losing?
Truth or Dare.
Hunk?
This is way too hard.
Then you take Truth or Dare.
Truth.
Let's ask that privately.
Can you save this for later?
Let's hit the restroom.
Sure.
Then I'll ask one.
After these past few days,
including our talk yesterday,
do you think we'll have
a definite outcome on this island?
That's a heavy question, bro.
So I think
this thing just doesn't
need to be said in front of everyone.
Then what about you?
I've been thinking about that too.
But...
You all really overthink things.
I haven't even thought that far ahead.
Me.
I definitely think about it.
Because I don't wanna get to know
any other girls anymore.
I just want it to be me and you.
No need to overthink.
So...
I can only say
I haven't really thought it through.
Maybe,
five days is still too short.
Today's Day five.
Yeah.
Day five.
Still feel nothing at all.
Maybe it'll take until
Day seven or eight.
Maybe it'll take even longer.
Could be.
Okay.
I'll ask you again on
Day seven or eight.
Then you might say it needs
Day nine or ten.
Could be.
Alright.
Yeah.
Or maybe tomorrow.
I'll have an answer.
Could be.
Then will you tell me
once you have the answer?
I will.
Of course.
But before I do,
I want to hear your answer first.
Who even does that?
Yeah.
I'm just afraid that my answer...
Affect me?
Exactly.
Then my answer won't affect you?
It won't.
Your answer won't.
How can you be so sure?
I just know.
I really do.
It just won't.
Aren't you worried about
those real-life issues?
I haven't thought about it.
I just feel...
I just feel like you…
You make me feel at ease.
Honestly.
But what about practical concerns?
What concerns exactly?
Age.
We're not that far apart in age.
Distance.
And then…
Social background.
Or maybe…
You know, work.
Family.
Environment.
Right.
All aspects.
Yeah.
Various factors.
I'm being honest here.
It's on my mind, honestly.
Not thinking about it feels empty.
Definitely.
Yeah.
Because when you get to know someone
in real life,
you first learn about all this stuff.
Right.
So are you
sure
you don't want to
get to know other girls?
I'm beyond sure about that.
Absolutely.
Absolutely certain.
Because
I'm not someone who feels secure easily.
But he's unwavering.
And he's always been by my side.
Even this morning,
before the competition,
I went back to change my shoes.
I showed up a bit late.
And he waited for me.
(Before the afternoon competition)
He was waiting for me.
No need to rush.
You can always call out to me.
You're nice.
Thank you.
He truly understands
long-term, steady feelings.
I guess
Enda should be younger than me.
But I realized
the way he answers questions
is surprisingly mature.
And he thinks similarly to me.
So being around him feels really natural
and comfortable.
Yeah.
I'll go think it over.
Okay, no problem.
Waiting all night was
really torturous.
I was distracted.
Couldn't even focus on playing.
(An hour ago)
Come on, let's play Werewolf.
Wait.
I'm really not feeling it.
I'm not in the mood.
Go.
You go first.
I'll catch up later.
Watching everyone pair off.
Kind of stings inside.
Thinking about what?
It's not all for me?
Can you even eat that much?
Absolutely delicious.
So overall my mood was basically
a tangled mix of feelings while waiting.
My mind was blank.
Not thinking much.
A bit distracted.
No idea when she'll be back.
(23:10, Lu Yanting & Liu Jiayi return to Balance Island)
Watch out.
There's water.
Are they here?
Or is everyone resting?
You just got back?
We're back.
You two
actually brought fruit.
Yeah, he bought it.
That's really sweet of you.
Qingbuliang.
(*Cold sweet soup)
Qingbuliang? Perfect.
Glad I stayed up for this.
Everyone's getting ready to rest.
It's fine.
I'll pass one out to everyone.
Having fun?
Yeah, I am.
The game's fun, or…
Everything's been fun.
Right.
Today was seriously a blast.
I'm over the moon.
It was crazy fun.
Better than yesterday's date.
Definitely.
Let me join next time.
She's super talented.
I'll pass them out first.
Alright.
Bye bye.
Hello.
Here, one Qingbuliang each.
Thanks.
Where did you all go?
It's been so long.
We went go-karting.
Was it fun riding the karts?
It was a blast.
Seriously?
We got soaked all over from karting.
Alright, appreciate it.
Okay.
Thanks.
Take it slow.
Bye.
Go-karts rolling.
Life's "better" now.
You know, I...
You know why I kept talking?
I just didn't want you cutting in.
Bro.
I worried so much
about you.
A little.
Forget it, I'm not eating.
Or just eat it, whatever.
Really?
Anyway, I didn't touch that cake
they brought back.
You eat.
Hello.
Qingbuliang.
How was the date?
Pretty good.
Look at that smile on your face.
It was nice.
Okay.
Smiling like that.
Thanks.
Perfect time for a snack.
Thanks, bro. Thanks, sis.
Thank you all.
Bye bye.
Heading home.
Finally, we're at my place.
Bye bye.
Bro.
I have to say, it tastes bad.
Not good?
(Taking this bitterness for my bro)
Heartfelt Moment begins now.
All islanders,
please proceed to
deliver your affection.
Tonight,
the islander
with the lowest weight score
will be eliminated.
(Xuan Cheng, Lu Yanting)
(The Islander
with the lowest count will leave)
What's that?
Someone's leaving.
What does that mean?
Yes.
Today it should be...
Don't overthink it for now.
It's okay, really okay.
Don't have to comfort me.
I'm not.
Because you've talked to...
and then…
Yan,
you know, it's not certain.
I'm fine.
Nothing's certain.
I'm heading back.
Alright.
Wait.
Let's talk later.
Okay.
Do you think he's the one leaving?
It depends on what Yan thinks.
But what if it's a
surprise upset?
Guanjie is out.
(Chen Yijia & Ding Wanning's room)
So nervous.
Are you nervous?
I'm really scared.
How did your date
with Guanjie go?
It was okay.
Do you think he likes you?
Hard to tell.
He's still
attentive to Yan after he got back.
(Zhu Huiyan & Yang Tinghong's room)
Kind of nervous.
What am I nervous about?
Can someone tell me?
(Yang Tianyu & Wu Guanjie's room)
Today's been great.
(Liu Jiayi & Wu Yihan's room)
Will this add points for Yanting?
Yeah.
What's the score between them now?
I can't take it.
I haven't even started...
I haven't started
thinking about that.
Then how did you cast your vote?
(Huang Jiawei & Lu Yanting's room)
I'm packing my stuff right now.
Bro.
Hey man.
Just stay here.
Keep it up.
I think I should be the one leaving.
I don't have anyone else
to get to know on the island.
No feelings left
for anyone.
So I'm ready.
I think I should go.
After spending the day together,
I believe Jiayi's balance
is leaning toward me.
Of course I was hoping Jiayi
would give me her full vote.
I'm a little worried,
but honestly, not that much.
I still have pretty
strong faith in myself.
The day before,
when Jiayi and I went on that date,
I could tell
she was genuinely happy.
Yeah.
You never know.
Maybe Charlie will get all in.
That'd be hilarious.
That'd be too funny.
I'm scared Xuan Cheng
might get eliminated.
(Liu Jiayi & Wu Yihan's room)
I only told you...
When it was a choice
between two people,
the other name was
Xuan Cheng.
I'm really nervous.
One vote is the lowest.
There's also Jiawei.
So what do we do?
Who's leaving today?
How could Xuan Cheng be the one to go?
It doesn't make sense.
I think the person who leaves
is the one no one likes.
Based on the game rules,
isn't that the logic here?
Right?
Not necessarily.
Then how should I cast my vote?
I don't have enough…
Then pick the one you truly like.
Just go with your feelings.
If both stay, that'd be ideal.
If…
One ends up leaving without staying.
That's the answer you were hoping for.
You're making me tear up here.
Don't cry.
You cry, I cry too.
I never even thought about that.
Now I feel like
no one's voting for him.
Everyone else has someone.
But for him, there's no chance at all.
The most he could get is one vote.
I can't let him leave.
(Delivery finished)
Tonight's delivery of affection is done.
All Island residents,
please gather at the Square.
Who's
leaving today?
Okay.
Time to go.
Let's go.
Seriously?
Stop joking.
It's fine.
Let's not overthink.
Exactly.
So nervous.
Why are you nervous?
Cold, Han?
Not really.
It's fine.
Islanders,
unfortunately,
in tonight's choice round,
those with the lowest weight scores...
There were two.
What?
Now,
the islander with
the highest weight score,
Liu Jiayi.
Please head to the balance zone.
Pick someone to save.
You okay?
No, I'm not.
WeTV "Live and Love S2"
will pause updates
from Feb 16 for a week.
Regular updates resume Feb 23.
Spring Festival Special Project
launches Feb 16.
Islanders on Balance Island
are spending the New Year with you.
Plus surprise livestreams
throughout Spring Festival.
(Preview)
Gentle Head Chef
is about to show up.
Let me take a bite.
Sure.
♪Give your whole life to me♪
Your are like "Oh" and "Wow".
I'm a puppy now.
Procured.
Bye bye. See you.
♪You'll always be my baby♪
♪Baby♪
Keep looking at me like that,
and we'll be the ones
singing Marry Me Today.
Yang.
(February 11, 12 pm)
Let's play word guessing.
(Pursue love on Balance Island)
Is it a person?
(Ex-girlfriend)
Yes.
(Mother-in-law)
Person?
Yes.
(Hunk)
Person?
Yes.
(Cast-wide trend)
(Again; Flag raising ceremony)
Person?
No.
(I'm just different)
Aren't you two
standing way too close?
There's literally
no space to get in.
They're doing it
on purpose.
Fixed the game.
On purpose.
Do you ever feel like…
You can actually
get results on the island?
What about you?
Something really surprised me.
It was yesterday,
I was the one who almost left.
If it really doesn't work out,
then forget it.
Join my side.
Everyone.
(Happy New Year!)
(Woohoo!)
(Watch Live and Love with us)
Why not ask directly?
(on February. at 12 pm.)
Like they're off-topic.
He thought, "Fine, just wait."
One guy is about to leave.
(Shocked)
(Oh no)
Oh no.
This is bad.
(Love can't match brotherhood)
Sworn friends at last.
That stare between them.
(Feeling it)
My cheeks hurt from smiling.
This moment finally came.
(Crowd goes wild)
(Can't believe my ears)
What did I hear?
I'm feeling all heated up.
(Too intense)
Me too.
(Excitement keeps going)
Stay tuned
"Live and Love S2".
Every episode is a thrill.