[English subtitles are available]
[Episode 22]
Don't say that.
Why? Are you worried about her?
No, I'm not.
This is business.
You're not supposed to be involved.
Take my men with you.
Get out of here.
Fine, I'll get going.
But this isn't over yet.
-Explain to me when you get home.
-Okay.
Let's talk at home.
Let's go.
We'll get going then, Mr. Mu Qing.
Goodbye, Kexin.
I'll visit you at your studio someday.
Captain Rong and Zhao Ran are coming out.
That was close.
Command center.
Captain Rong and Zhao Ran have evacuated.
[Yungang Public Security Bureau]
Evacuate now.
-Yes, sir.
-Roger that.
Hurry and leave.
Captain Rong.
What is going on?
Let's talk when we get back.
You're useless.
Are you okay?
Leave me alone.
Explain it to me, the two of you.
What's going on?
"What's going on?"
You have recognized the wrong person.
That man is not a cop.
He's not?
He has been working for Mr. Zhao
for over a decade.
He's probably just a look-alike.
"A look-alike"?
If he was really a cop,
do you think
we would've walked away safely?
I think you're right.
I never expected
that Linda's direct superior
would be Guanyin.
So it's really related to Tieguanyin.
I was also surprised when I got there.
She has really done a lot of things
behind my dad's back.
It's going to be interesting.
Then what was that gunshot about?
Tieguanyin fired it.
I found out through Linda
about Tieguanyin's private dealings.
Tieguanyin thinks
that we've got something on her,
so she shot Linda in a fit of rage.
Linda is hurt?
Where was she hurt? Is it serious?
Well, it's nothing serious.
The bullet just grazed her.
It's just a scrape.
What should we do next?
Should we tell Godfather
that Tieguanyin is selling the goods?
No way.
We can't be snitches.
If we want to destroy Tieguanyin,
it has to be done in one go.
She's so greedy.
Maybe that's her real weakness
and we can use that against her.
Let's play the long game
and catch a big fish.
Please speak Mandarin.
Not only must we keep this secret for her,
but we must also seize this chance
to get closer to her.
When we finally gain her trust,
that's our chance to strike.
Not bad.
You're really good at playing tricks.
You're the one who always tricks me.
Yet you're judging me.
How is that the same?
That's because I like you.
I did it to get close to you.
Aren't we talking about a serious matter?
Stop flirting around.
I'm being serious.
He owes me his life today.
Tell me. How are you going to pay me back?
Will you two stop
showing affection in public?
There's a single man here.
Analyze it for him. Be unbiased.
Did I not just save his life today?
-All right.
-Didn't I?
Okay, carry on.
-I'll go away, all right?
-Tell him.
-I'll take a shower.
-How will you thank me?
Ruosheng.
How are you going to thank me?
How do you want me to thank you?
Your acting is really something.
What do you mean?
Didn't I really save your life today?
He's gone. Stop acting.
We're old friends. What are you afraid of?
That's one thing.
Stop acting. Just be normal.
I am normal.
The sofa is long.
Go on. I'll play with you.
You're too immersed in your role.
What's wrong?
Didn't I save your life today?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Hey.
You're leaving just like that?
Boss, the payment
from Tongzhou has arrived.
It's in cash.
Give it to the accountant.
Keep a third of the amount,
and give it to the girls as a bonus.
Okay. Thank you, Ms. Guanyin.
The cheongsam you ordered just arrived.
Do you want to try it on?
Leave it there.
Get to work.
All right.
Do you know why I shot you today?
I don't like silly and naive girls.
You were so careless.
How could you provoke
Mu Qing and Li Ruosheng?
You caused me so much trouble.
This shot...
You must endure it.
Does it hurt?
Do you know why I like this type of fish?
Because...
they have a beautiful appearance.
They are always
so relaxed in the water
without a worry in the world.
But...
Once they come across other fish,
they'll jump right on it
and never let go,
until they swallow the fish down.
I still think this is a bit too risky.
As long as we can take down Tieguanyin,
I think it's worth the risk.
You and Tieguanyin working together,
that is outright playing tricks
under Godfather's nose.
Once you take that step,
there's no going back.
Can't you think of some other ways?
Tell me then. What other ways do we have?
That's already the least risky way.
If we go against Tieguanyin head-on,
that's how we will lose big-time.
This is called
"using your opponent's strength
against them."
I see.
I hope
that you can be like this type of fish.
Do you understand?
Today, Li Ruosheng called.
He asked how you are doing.
I answered him for you.
I told him that you're all right.
There's also Mu Qing.
He wants to see the new product samples.
You will deliver the samples to them
first thing tomorrow morning.
Yes, boss.
Don't be so courteous.
You can call me by my name.
There's only so much money you can make.
But you only live once.
We're all only trying to make a living.
Let's take it easy from now on.
These samples
weren't processed beforehand.
Let's give them out and see the feedback.
My boss will be waiting to hear from you.
Linda.
Let me change your medicine.
Worry about yourself.
That brat is so thoughtful.
Did he...
save your life twice?
Yes.
Does he make your heart flutter?
No.
He's handsome,
thoughtful,
and also capable.
It's only natural
that you would fall for such a man.
If I were you,
I might have fallen for him too.
Mu Qing just called.
He said the new product samples were good.
He wants to make a deal with us.
He even asked me to bring you along.
He keeps mentioning your name.
Could it be that he has feelings for you?
No, he's...
What about him?
Are you trying to say
there's no way he has feelings for you?
Am I right?
I would like to see
what those two rascals
are up to.
This time,
whether we can take down Mu Qing or not,
it's all up to you.
Guanyin.
This place is not bad.
Welcome.
You made this place so successful
in less than three years.
That's incredible.
This is just an experience center.
It's just a small business.
I'm nothing compared to you, Guanyin.
Are you feeling better?
Guanyin.
Do you want to play a game?
Sure.
Let's talk business while we play.
Deal the cards.
Guanyin.
Linda is my lucky star.
Let me borrow her today.
Do you mind?
What are you talking about?
She's working for me.
How can she be your lucky star?
Linda is our guest today.
I don't think it's a good idea
to borrow her around.
That's not up to me.
Linda, the choice is yours.
This time,
whether we can take down Mu Qing or not,
it's all up to you.
Since I am Mr. Mu's lucky star,
I have no reason to not choose Mr. Mu.
That's a good choice.
A hero and a beauty.
Ruosheng.
Mu Qing has his lucky star with him today.
You have to be careful.
Deal the cards.
Guanyin.
What happened before
was just a misunderstanding.
Don't take it to heart.
Of course I won't.
In all fairness, you did nothing wrong.
However,
you have to understand
that I have my difficulties.
I'm looking after
such a huge fortune for others.
Who wouldn't want more shares?
Am I right?
You're right.
There are so many eyes on me.
I had no choice but to do such a thing.
Guanyin.
From now on,
your business is my business.
Let's let bygones be bygones.
I have my own way of smuggling the goods.
I can tell you.
That's great.
It can save me the trouble.
Guanyin.
Didn't we agree to talk while playing?
But why is there only talk, but no play?
Besides,
if you're discussing business,
shouldn't you be talking to me?
I'm in charge.
But hasn't it always been Mu Qing
who handles business matters
on your behalf?
That was before.
I'll take charge from now on.
If anyone disrespects the hierarchy,
that's not good.
Mu Qing, what do you think?
No matter how and who does it,
isn't it all for our family?
Still, there's always
a head in the family.
Hey, buddy.
Why are you so angry?
Linda.
Pour him a cup of tea.
Sorry, I won.
Let's play again.
Linda.
In terms of seniority,
shouldn't you pour tea for me first?
It's too late.
I don't want it anymore.
Mu Qing, let me tell you.
I'm your superior.
You're working for me.
You'd better know your place.
That's it.
We can't play anymore.
Let's get some fresh air too.
Come on.
As I was saying,
if you disperse your goods
through my dark web,
no one will ever find out.
Including Mr. Ou.
In terms of that,
you can rest assured, Guanyin.
But my goods
worth a lot of money.
Can your dark web handle it?
I can even handle Mr. Ou's goods.
Are you saying
you have more goods than Mr. Ou does?
Although Dakun's traditional sales method
was a mess,
you two brought it back to life.
How can you be so sure
that the dark web you set up
is completely risk-free?
It is risky.
You've witnessed it yourself.
Unless someone tampers with it,
it won't bear any risk at all.
I know.
You have never trusted me.
Mr. Glasses and Mr. Congtou
have always been prejudiced against me.
But no matter how much
we disagree with each other,
we should not disagree with money.
Obviously,
now is not a good time for anyone else.
Only the goods you have in hand
can complement my sales network.
If we can join forces
and use our strengths,
that will be perfect.
Let's make money together.
I don't see why we can't do that.
Besides,
we're in the same boat now.
Am I right, Guanyin?
Your effort in this will not be wasted.
Does that mean you've agreed?
I have another question.
Tell me.
Am I working with you
or the two of you?
I don't want our partnership
to make things awkward between you two.
That's not good.
Don't worry, Guanyin.
Ruosheng is just too caught up
in his temper.
He knows what's important and what's not.
Mr. Mu, we have a problem.
You should take a look.
What happened?
I'm not sure what happened.
But Mr. Li is furious.
Why don't you go and take a look?
Linda should come with you.
Linda, look after Mr. Mu.
Guanyin, I'll go and take a look.
That jerk!
Boss.
Ungrateful brat.
A dog is more loyal than him!
-Make way!
-Leave me alone!
I'll kill whoever stands in my way!
Have you lost your mind?
How dare you come back!
Wait for me here. I'll go check on him.
Be careful.
Have you lost your mind?
If you want to act crazy,
do it at your own place.
What are you doing at my house?
Yes, I've lost my mind!
Whatever you have today,
I gave them all to you!
Everything here is mine!
I can smash them if I want to!
Listen up, Mu Qing!
If you want to do dirty work,
do it behind my back!
How dare you talk business
with Tieguanyin in front of me?
Do you have any respect for me?
How about this?
From now on,
I'll be your lackey
and I'll call you my boss!
That sounds great to me.
You're a good lackey!
What do you mean?
What's wrong? You don't agree?
-Of course I don't.
-Hit me then!
Don't make me!
I dare you!
For real?
Hurry, hit me.
Here.
I'll hit you!
Mu Qing!
-Don't take me for a fool
-Mu Qing!
just because I go easy on you.
Mu Qing.
Li Ruosheng, are you crazy?
Mu Qing, are you okay? Does it hurt?
You two are really something.
Don't touch me!
I'll take you to the hospital.
Luckily, you're fine.
Does it still hurt?
It hurts. How can it not hurt?
Li Ruosheng is so ruthless.
Why are you two doing this?
I've helped him for three years.
Look what happened in the end.
All my effort has gone to waste.
Actually,
you two shouldn't be like this
because of me.
Men are all the same.
But you two are business partners.
How will you work together in the future?
From now on,
we'll stay out of each other's business.
He has no control over what I do.
Are you starting your own business?
What else can I do?
Isn't that what Guanyin wants?
I don't care what you want to do.
But it's not easy to work with Guanyin.
You have to be careful.
You know that too?
That's why you should quit.
I know you're trying to protect me.
I'm very grateful.
But...
You don't have to always care for me.
You'll only sink deeper into it.
What do you mean?
Thank you.
I'm grateful to you.
You'll always have a place in my heart.
Not bad.
Another Qingqing just left.
That's right.
This Linda...
She really is something.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I was only acting for her sake.
It had to look real for her to believe me.
You're such a great actor
with deep emotions.
How else could I have survived
in this industry?
Did Li Ruosheng send you here?
Of course he sent me here.
He's afraid he went overboard.
He wants me to see if you're all right.
It's okay. I'm fine.
I faked it.
Let me see.
I guess you're really okay.
You even got a hug.
Don't hurt me even if I'm fine.
You're okay, right?
Then don't stay here
and waste social resources.
Let's go.
Come on.
Waste of resources?
It's for the sake of the act.
That went well.
Are you still angry?
I was acting, you know?
I am acting too.
I'm acting like I'm jealous.
Your acting is really good.
The same goes for you.
Did you see them fighting
with your own eyes?
Yes, I saw it with my own eyes.
It was quite a fierce fight.
"A fierce fight"?
That's great. I love it.
Once they have a falling-out,
it will be easier to deal with them.
There's no way they could beat me.
Inform Mu Qing tomorrow.
We'll do as he suggested.
Give him 20% of goods first.
Don't give it all to him yet.
Why?
Isn't it obvious?
Who knows if they're having
a falling-out for real?
We need to test them out.
Just do as I say.
Yes, boss.
I've told Director Liu
about the plan you and Li Ruosheng have.
What are you going to do next?
I'll find out the location
of Tieguanyin's factory.
I'll have to sever
the group's lifeline first.
Okay.
By then,
just let me know what you need me to do.
Sure. Cheers.
How long have you known Liu Qingqing?
We've known each other for a few years.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I just feel
that the relationship between you two
is not as simple as I thought.
Look at you. You're asking about it again.
I told you before.
I'm just putting on an act.
You ask that every day.
You're so paranoid.
About that hug today,
tell me the truth.
Does Liu Qingqing have feelings for you?
Be careful.
When she can't hold
her feelings in anymore,
you won't be able to walk away from it.
What do you mean?
You'll see.
I guess
it's better for me to stay away from you.
And why would you do that?
You see.
Although Tieguanyin wants to do
a big business because of her greed,
we can't be sure
that my dad won't suspect you
of pocketing the money.
On top of that, you've always been
a thorn in Mr. Glasses's flesh.
If he spreads false rumors
about you to my dad,
you'll be in even more danger.
So you're talking about work.
What did you think I meant?
I thought it was work too.
-Of course it's about work.
-Sure.
So what are your plans?
Me?
I'm going to play it by ear.
I'll make use of Liu Qingqing's
feelings for you
and pretend to be jealous.
I'll fight with you
and move back to my dad's
so that I can keep an eye on him too.
By doing that,
it can also distract his attention
from you and Guanyin.
I'll also let him know
how important you are to me.
Then he and Mr. Glasses
won't dare do anything to you.
Sure, let's do as you say.
Just now,
when I said it was about work,
deep down inside,
did you feel a little bit disappointed?
You have such bad observation skills.
Why would I feel disappointed?
When did I feel disappointed?
That doesn't make sense.
It's all over your face.
My face? Was it written on my face?
I look the same every day.
I'm always emotionless.
You still won't admit it?
Fine.
Admit what?
What are you looking at? It's the same.
[Traitor]
That's a bit too much.
What?
Mr. Glasses.
I'm sure you have heard.
Yes.
I didn't expect things
to progress so quickly.
Tieguanyin's dark web
has helped her earn quite a lot of money.
Compared to the losses
she suffered before,
it's not worth mentioning.
Are you jealous?
I can't get jealous.
Tieguanyin has one word
written all over her face.
"Greed."
She would go to whoever that has money.
She's a woman.
She has the ability to do so,
but we don't.
We are incapable.
You're still jealous.
It's all for the money.
There's nothing more to say.
But on the other hand,
Li Ruosheng and Mu Qing
have quite a bit of skill.
They only use a few shabby computers.
But they're able to make
a few fold increase in sales.
The profit they make
is like water flowing into their pockets.
Li Ruosheng.
This fool is considered lucky.
If it wasn't for Mu Qing,
he wouldn't be so successful today.
Am I right?
Who cares if he's really a fool?
There's also a possibility
for a fool to be enlightened someday.
What do you mean?
His lackey is more capable than him.
How do you think that makes him feel?
I don't know how he feels.
If it were me, I would never allow it.
Recently,
Mu Qing and Tieguanyin are very close.
She's obviously fond of him.
Who can stop her?
It's okay if she is only fond of him.
What if there's something else?
My friend.
Whatever it is,
it has nothing to do with us.
This matter
is Mr. Ou's concern.
How do you have time to please me?
What are you talking about?
I'm your daughter. Can't I visit you?
Look.
Your house is so big.
It has everything.
But do you have a daughter?
Why do you sound so sarcastic?
What's bothering you?
I just missed you.
That's too sweet for me to handle.
Sit down.
Did Mu Qing bully you?
You're acting weird.
You weren't like this the other day.
I think what you said that day was right.
When you're in a relationship,
you have to be careful.
I've decided
to not see him for a few days.
Tell me. What's going on?
Talking about it makes me furious.
Mu Qing's ex-girlfriend
is causing trouble.
His ex-girlfriend?
Did she get in your way?
Yes.
And coincidentally, she works for Guanyin.
So what does Mu Qing think?
What else can he be thinking?
But Dad, let me tell you.
She's no ordinary woman.
She's quite pretty.
Even Li Ruosheng falls for her.
After Li Ruosheng found out about
her relationship with Mu Qing,
it even caused a conflict between them.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Guanyin has been trying
to get on Mu Qing's good side lately.
She wants to do business
using his sales network.
Mu Qing seems to be unhappy with it.
But in reality, I bet he's more than happy
to be working with his ex.
Dad, be the judge.
Isn't this ex-girlfriend a troublemaker?
You said Tieguanyin
is close to Mu Qing lately?
Yes.
And you know it too.
All of Guanyin's girls
are very pretty.
They have nice figures too.
I'm so jealous.
But I can't tell anyone about it.
That's why
I'm avoiding Mu Qing.
But thanks to him,
I have time to come back and visit you.
Dad, what's wrong?
I'm not telling you all this
to make you worry.
I know.
When women are in love,
we must keep our eyes wide open.
I get it now.
Love is easy, but it's hard to get along.
Are you backing out?
No way.
I'm your daughter.
You don't understand.
Mu Qing is so popular.
That means he's attractive and charming.
What does that prove?
Your daughter has good taste.
What are you planning to do?
You don't understand.
If I want a good relationship,
I shouldn't be reckless.
I need to play some tricks.
I'll just ignore him for a few days.
This is called playing hard to get.
Then how do you want me to support you?
I just need you
to let me stay with you for a few days.
Let him feel how hard life is without me.
I would love that.
I knew you're the best.
Men are nothing.
Only my dad would always love me.
I didn't give you a good massage earlier.
Tell me where it hurts.
Let me give you a massage.
What's going on with you?
Mu Qing's ex-girlfriend
is working for Tieguanyin.
Why didn't you tell me
such an important matter?
Is that true?
Kexin was so mad that she came back home.
How could it be fake?
I'm sorry, sir.
This is my fault.
This woman is not that simple.
["The Most Romantic Oblivion" playing]
♫ It's pouring ♫
♫ The cat is looking at you
from the lonely window ♫
♫ In those eyes ♫
♫ There are disappointment and memory ♫
♫ It's away from you ♫
♫ Half a teardrop away ♫
♫ So much intimacy ♫
♫ Is being remembered ♫
♫ You that I love ♫
♫ Seem to melt in my night ♫
♫ The pain becomes a sigh ♫
♫ Carved onto the pillows as tears ♫
♫ I miss you ♫
♫ You stay silent in my breath ♫
♫ Lie with me as you fall asleep ♫
♫ Until I wake up from my dream ♫
♫ The most romantic oblivion ♫
♫ Is to grow old together ♫
♫ The longest love ♫
♫ Is not to be heard from ♫
♫ I still don't want to believe ♫
♫ So I won't give up ♫
♫ So I cry under the fireworks ♫
♫ So I'm afraid to be reminded ♫
♫ That I miss you ♫
♫ Maybe I'm still in love ♫
♫ I'm still moved by your words ♫
♫ I'm still holding your letters ♫
♫ Until my thoughts turn to ashes ♫
♫ Tears become shooting stars ♫
♫ To prove the greatness of love ♫
♫ The most romantic oblivion ♫
♫ Is to live the way you live ♫
♫ The longest love ♫
♫ Is when things remain unchanged ♫
♫ I'm still waiting for you ♫
♫ So don't worry ♫
♫ So you become a secret ♫
♫ So I try to be happy ♫
♫ Because of you ♫
♫ So I'm afraid to be reminded ♫
♫ That I miss you ♫