[English subtitles are available]
[Episode 17]
[Hello, Director Liu.]
It's me.
Rong Yao?
Now, the dealers, buyers,
and transporters of Group K
are all under our surveillance.
Good job.
Director Liu wants to thank you.
I want to thank you too.
What else do you need?
[Keep an eye on Tieguanyin for me.]
[She's in charge of the drug factory.]
She'll give me a big shipment soon.
When that happens,
we can take down her factory.
I'll have a plan for my next move.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
[Also,]
we can start
from Tieguanyin's cargo point.
She'll have to restock it.
I got it.
Okay, that's all.
[Wait.]
What's wrong?
Be safe.
Mu Qing.
You too.
Remember.
My name is Liu Yuanwen.
Get back to work.
Don't move!
Get down. Now!
Hands up. Don't move!
Police!
Don't move!
Take him away!
Run! Hurry!
Go to the second floor!
Freeze! Don't move!
Stop right there!
Hurry. Take them out!
Come out!
-Come out!
-What are you doing?
Come on!
Stay still.
Move!
-Freeze!
-Don't move!
Get down here or we'll shoot.
-I'm coming down now.
-Faster!
Get down now!
Move.
-Stay still.
-Move!
Let's go. Keep it steady.
Come out!
Move.
Stay still.
Captain Rong.
Do you think our team
deserves a second-rate award?
Stop talking. Hurry up and move them.
-Move them.
-What's wrong with you?
Less talk, more actions.
It's such a happy occasion.
I don't get it. Why the long face?
Director Liu.
It's quite a success, isn't it?
Good work, everyone.
Rong Yao.
You must treat them well.
Do you have any requests, guys?
Director Liu, can we take a few days off?
We are getting exhausted.
Take a few days off?
We can't slack off yet.
Who said we're slacking off?
You two are indestructible.
But I need to sleep.
They're right.
You need some rest.
Don't overwork.
As for taking a few days off,
you'd better listen to your captain.
Rong Yao.
Let's get to work.
Here.
The drug situation in Yungang
is really serious.
You see.
We just busted Dakun's drug network.
Now, there's already a new one.
Here.
If we're doing this,
-Slowly.
-we have to do it one step at a time.
Slow down like you're eating.
You can't rush it.
Here.
I understand, Director Liu.
The only reason I'm here
is to catch drug dealers.
Otherwise, I would let down Rong Yu
and Yuanwen who is on the front line.
So I really can't be happy
about a small success.
I understand how you feel.
Director Liu.
My dad and younger sister
both died for Drug Enforcement Squad.
I don't have a family.
I have nothing.
But I don't want others to be like me.
I hope that this city can be cleansed.
And for that,
I'll keep doing my best.
-I'll get back to work.
-Go on.
Our operation last night was a success.
It was thanks to your dark web system.
On the surface,
it hides the dealers.
But at the same time,
it's also under our surveillance.
The dealers just learned how good it is.
I think
we might as well play the long game.
We'll use the dark web system
to take Group K down completely.
Okay.
Let's go with your plan.
Director Liu.
There's something I want to tell you.
What?
I've made contact with Skylark.
That's great.
You'll have to cooperate well.
I really didn't expect
that the unruly Ou Kexin is Skylark.
I just found out who she is too.
She's Ou Zhenhai's goddaughter.
They're not related by blood.
A long time ago,
her dad was killed by a drug dealer
to protect Ou Zhenhai.
From that moment on,
he has been treating Ou Kexin
as his own daughter.
Afterward, he sent her and her mom
to live abroad.
She was only a few months old then.
Judging from the situation,
no one around Ou Zhenhai
knows this secret.
The bureau didn't tell us
who she was right away
because she has a bigger
and more confidential mission.
On the other hand,
it was to ensure both of your safety.
Of course.
Even for a girl who came back from abroad,
she's too open-minded.
It's so simple and straightforward.
Have you gotten used to it yet?
Being simple and straightforward?
It's okay.
I'm used to it a little.
Kexin, what's the matter?
Dear Mr. Ou,
I'm not a child anymore.
I don't need your concerns and worries.
Please respect my privacy, will you?
Right.
As for those useless things,
I took care of it for you.
You don't have to worry anymore.
[Yungang Municipal Public Security Bureau]
[Rong Yao: Let's have dinner together.]
[Li Yimeng: Okay.]
[Rong Yao: See you at 7 p.m.,
at Yungang Restaurant, Hibiscus Room.]
It's the wrong room. Let's go.
Yimeng?
It's really you.
You're all dressed up, Yimeng.
You're wearing high heels too?
-Where's Captain Rong?
-You guys.
It's my treat today.
Here, have a seat.
Don't stand there.
Come on. Hurry up.
Is this the lady officer that we know?
Yimeng, when you go on the next mission,
you should wear this.
You look so elegant.
What? You've never seen a woman?
Don't wear the jacket.
Your outfit looks nice.
I'm wearing it.
Yimeng, this isn't you.
Is something wrong with you?
Something is wrong with you.
Mr. Bao.
You're drooling.
-Sit down.
-Yes, have a seat.
Where's Captain Rong?
I don't know. I came alone.
-Captain Rong.
-Is everyone here?
I'm not late, am I?
No, we just got here.
Here, have a seat.
Sit here. Come.
It's the same.
Have a seat.
After working together for so long,
it's the first time we eat together.
Today, it's...
Yimeng is very dressed-up today.
Are you hot?
I'm cold.
You can have mine.
All right, stop it.
Here's the deal.
We've won our first battle.
Keep it up.
We have a long way to go.
Let's drink tonight, okay?
Can you?
I'm okay.
How about this?
Let's have some liquor.
Whoever backs down first
has to buy breakfast
for Li Yimeng tomorrow.
All right?
Right, here's the booze.
[Hongtan Jiugui Liquor]
That's good wine.
The warehouse on Qingchun Road
made thousands of shipments last night.
But you were caught by the police.
Don't you want to explain?
Ms. Guanyin.
Ms. Guanyin, I don't know what went wrong.
The police just stormed in.
We couldn't even react.
There was no time to run.
Those are worth millions of yuan.
I...
Ms. Guanyin, we don't know
what went wrong.
Ms. Guanyin.
He wants to ship more?
It's so chaotic now.
He wants to make more shipments?
What is Mr. Ou thinking?
I never thought
that Mu Qing would be capable of this.
After Dakun,
our group can't have anymore accidents.
Otherwise,
Mr. Ou's business with Spectre
will be ruined.
Spectre.
It's Spectre again.
Who exactly is Spectre?
Is this person even real?
Are his products so good
that it's worth risking
everything we built?
Is it worth it? Is it?
Guanyin.
Do as Mr. Ou asked.
Do 50% more.
At this rate,
Mu Qing can handle it.
Back then,
Dakun had hundreds of workers.
He occupied half of the land.
But Mu Qing
is still two times faster than he was.
What exactly is this kid capable of?
How can he handle so much?
I don't know.
Guanyin, why don't you ask him?
I won't.
You're using me.
I won't be your tool.
What should we do then?
Mr. Ou wants me to watch Kexin.
You're the only one
who can deal with Mu Qing.
What about Congtou?
He's being held back.
He has lost his motivation.
Now, he's busy selling and renting out
Dakun's properties.
It's only a matter of time
before he quits.
Guanyin.
Why don't you help me?
Sure.
I'll help you this time.
Ms. Guanyin.
We accidentally killed him.
Do as usual.
Dump him into the sea with cement.
Yes.
Guanyin.
Do you know what I like about you?
You're not only pretty,
but you're also cruel.
I like you too.
When it comes to cruelty,
you're just the same.
[Director Liu.]
[It seems like]
[your undercover agent]
[has made contact with Skylark.]
[Rong Yao.]
[We didn't tell you]
[about her true identity before.]
[It was the bureau's decision.]
[We didn't want to hide]
[our next plan,]
[but after considering all aspects]
[and after asking our agent,]
[we think it's better not to tell you.]
What do you mean, Director Wang?
[The current Ou Kexin]
[is not the real Ou Kexin.]
[Three years ago,]
in France,
Ou Kexin was killed by Mr. Ou's enemy.
She's dead.
[The current Ou Kexin]
[is your sister, Rong Yu.]
What did you say?
My sister is still alive?
Sir.
Rong Yu is still alive.
That's good news.
But...
But Liu Yuanwen and Rong Yu
were in a relationship.
Rong Yu is already dead to him.
Arranging for them to meet...
Director Liu.
Calm down.
Let me finish.
Three years ago,
in order to find more evidence on Mr. Ou,
we thought
that his daughter, Ou Kexin,
was our chance.
[Unexpectedly,]
[his daughter was murdered.]
[For years,]
[we've been keeping it a secret.]
[We wanted to find someone]
[who resembles her to pretend to be her.]
[By appearance and look,]
[Rong Yu, your sister,]
[was our best choice.]
[But again,]
[after we decided,]
[she had an accident too.]
You know what happened back then.
Rong Yu had an accident on a mission.
Everyone thought she was dead.
But before that,
[Rong Yu had agreed to participate]
[in our three years of operation.]
[So...]
[we used the accident.]
[We made it look like she died.]
[Then she told us]
[she wanted to be more like Ou Kexin.]
[She wanted to go to France]
[to learn everything about Ou Kexin.]
She only had one request.
[She wanted to keep it a secret]
[from her family, you, and Yuanwen.]
[She said]
[that she couldn't be distracted.]
[So...]
[we had to respect her decision.]
We've been hiding this from you
for so long.
On behalf of the bureau,
I sincerely apologize.
[Rong Yao.]
Rong Yao.
-Rong Yao.
-I'll ask her.
Why did she do this? Why?
Director Liu. Captain Rong.
Let's talk somewhere else.
I want to meet her.
I want to meet her too.
Rong Yao.
I think
we don't have to worry
about Rong Yu.
She trained for three years.
She must have known
that the insider was Yuanwen.
I'm sure she prepared herself
before she took the mission.
At the same time,
we must believe in the bureau.
The bureau must have known
about their relationship.
They would've taken care of it.
But I'm worried about Yuanwen the most.
If one day...
What if he senses
that he's not facing Ou Kexin,
but his lover, Rong Yu,
who died three years ago,
and can't control his emotions?
Feel free to look around.
I didn't expect to meet her like that.
No matter what,
before the mission is complete,
we can never let Yuanwen know.
We also have to
work with them.
Complete our mission as soon as possible.
Rong Yao.
We should be happy
that Rong Yu is still alive.
And she's still fighting.
You have a great sister.
When did this shop open?
I've never seen it.
It's new.
Not a lot of people know.
So if you like our shop,
-recommend us to someone.
-Okay.
Come back here if you need anything.
We won't be strangers.
You can have a discount.
When did you come up here?
Just now.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
I just wanted some fresh air.
What exactly happened?
Didn't I tell you I'm fine?
I just want to be alone.
Fine then. Why are you mad?
Do you want some coffee?
Americano or latte?
Cold or...
Stop pretending to be cool.
My goodness.
Welcome.
Hello, what would you like?
Sir, a bottle of mineral water
and bread, please.
All right. Hold on.
Here you go. Please scan it.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Here you go.
Hello.
It's the first time you call me.
What's wrong? Did you miss me?
[I just want to know.]
[Aside from me,]
is there anyone else who cares about you?
There are people who care about me.
Why? Are you jealous?
How could I be jealous?
I have confidence in myself.
[Let's go on a date tomorrow.]
I'll prove with my actions
that I'm the best boyfriend.
If I say yes, it will be inappropriate.
It's not my style either.
How about this?
I'll let you know when and where.
See you tomorrow.
All right, it's a deal.
We'll have beer and barbeque next time.
You're finally back.
Is it okay to let Guanyin wait
for so long?
Guanyin, you're here.
You look different already.
We heard about what happened.
I came to congratulate you.
Thank you, Guanyin.
There must be more.
Do you have any orders for me?
I wouldn't dare to give orders,
but I have a favor to ask.
Tell me.
Buddy.
Tell me your method.
You sold a lot of goods
in such a short time.
How did you do it?
Guanyin.
You need to pay to be my student.
You're going to charge me?
I have to make money, right?
Just give Guanyin a discount.
Go.
You're different now.
Now that Mr. Ou has your back,
you're so confident.
It's all for the group.
I'm just doing my job.
You give me the goods.
I sell them for you.
We both benefit from it.
As for having my back,
that's an overstatement.
Does that mean you won't help me?
If you put it that way...
I can't help you.
Okay then.
If you really won't tell me,
I won't force you.
I'm leaving.
Right.
There's a saying.
"Being overly clever
will bring you trouble."
Mu Qing.
You're very smart.
But...
"The wind blows the hardest
at the tallest wood."
You're the one who might get hurt.
Judging from that,
are you the wind?
There are plenty of people
who want to be that wind.
I'm just reminding you.
All right.
Here.
It's the new warehouse.
The person in charge
and the number are here.
Thank you, Guanyin.
You're so handsome.
Be careful.
We'll see you out.
There's no need.
I thought that Guanyin
was always at peace with the others.
After giving her our turf,
she gave it to Congtou.
Why was she so keen?
Do you really think that?
Why didn't you finish your sentence?
Guanyin was with Dakun
because he'd give her over 20% share
every time he made a deal.
Sometimes even more.
He gave her a 20% share?
So the two of them...
Yes.
Guanyin usually looks so uneager.
But actually,
she's the biggest worm in the group.
Now that Dakun is gone,
she doesn't profit much
from Dakun's properties.
So Guanyin is the most anxious one.
I always thought that Guanyin
was the only one loyal to my godfather.
I didn't know that
she was sleeping with Dakun.
I should tell my godfather.
Even if Mr. Ou finds out,
he won't do anything to her.
Ruosheng.
I know what you're thinking.
We're all doing this because of money.
People would just do anything for money.
Not to mention in our line of work.
What about you?
Would you have done the same?
All right.
I know you wouldn't.
You're not that kind of person.
What should we do next?
Next...
We're Guanyin's only option.
In the end, she'll ask us for her share.
So, in the future,
we'll give her 10%
every time we make a shipment.
No way.
How is that any different from Dakun?
Don't push her too hard.
Think of it as paying for our safety.
Ruosheng.
We're only doing this now
so that we can stand here in the future
without any problems
and enjoy this view.
Ms. Guanyin, this is it.
Are you sure?
My man pretended to be a delivery guy.
He saw a lot of computers and servers.
Are we doing this?
Of course we are.
But this is not
how you play the game.
Internet trick.
You little brat
just ran into my gun.
Drive.
Which one is better?
Which one do you like?
This one is pretty.
But isn't this a bit too long?
Let's try another one.
This one.
What do you think?
This one is nice.
But isn't this a bit too thick?
Let's see another one.
What about these?
This one is a bit flashier.
But I think
this one looks more innocent.
Boss, I think you're pretty.
You look good in anything.
Well said.
I'll give you a raise.
Hold this. I'll try it on.
Hey.
No way.
This is blue.
This is also blue.
This is blue too.
It's a coincidence.
It's true love. We're synced.
Come on.
-There are so many people.
-What are you doing?
It's a date.
You should act properly.
Come on.
Smile.
You're too gloomy for a date.
Let me think.
We can look around there.
Sir, how much is this?
It's 100 yuan.
Come here.
Fine, whatever.
I told you to come here.
What are you doing?
Come here.
Quick, look.
Let's get a painting.
It's fun.
Sir, I want one.
Which kind do you like?
I'll do one of those with big eyes
and tall nose.
The very cute one.
Okay.
Look here.
Doesn't it look like me?
Big eyes and a big nose.
Sir, you're good.
What's wrong?
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Are you in a bad mood?
That's not it.
I got it.
You're upset
by those people following us, aren't you?
It's okay. Don't mind them.
Let's have some fun.
Smile.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Let's go.
Come on.
A claw machine?
It's not that simple.
We're competing.
Let's see who can get the most dolls
with the same amount of money.
Can you play this?
Of course.
And I'm not finished.
The loser will get punished.
Get punished?
Sure. How about this?
If I win,
you have to do me a favor.
Can't you be more creative?
If I win,
you'll owe me three favors.
That's impossible.
I'll prove to you
that I only owe you one.
Sure.
Sorry.
I can't see.
["The Most Romantic Oblivion" playing]
♫ It's pouring ♫
♫ The cat is looking at you
from the lonely window ♫
♫ In those eyes ♫
♫ There are disappointment and memory ♫
♫ It's away from you ♫
♫ Half a teardrop away ♫
♫ So much intimacy ♫
♫ Is being remembered ♫
♫ You that I love ♫
♫ Seem to melt in my night ♫
♫ The pain becomes a sigh ♫
♫ Carved onto the pillows as tears ♫
♫ I miss you ♫
♫ You stay silent in my breath ♫
♫ Lie with me as you fall asleep ♫
♫ Until I wake up from my dream ♫
♫ The most romantic oblivion ♫
♫ Is to grow old together ♫
♫ The longest love ♫
♫ Is not to be heard from ♫
♫ I still don't want to believe ♫
♫ So I won't give up ♫
♫ So I cry under the fireworks ♫
♫ So I'm afraid to be reminded ♫
♫ That I miss you ♫
♫ Maybe I'm still in love ♫
♫ I'm still moved by your words ♫
♫ I'm still holding your letters ♫
♫ Until my thoughts turn to ashes ♫
♫ Tears become shooting stars ♫
♫ To prove the greatness of love ♫
♫ The most romantic oblivion ♫
♫ Is to live the way you live ♫
♫ The longest love ♫
♫ Is when things remain unchanged ♫
♫ I'm still waiting for you ♫
♫ So don't worry ♫
♫ So you become a secret ♫
♫ So I try to be happy ♫
♫ Because of you ♫
♫ So I'm afraid to be reminded ♫
♫ That I miss you ♫