[English subtitles are available]
[Episode 1]
[Tiger Shark]
There's a bomb! Hurry!
A bomb?
You guys have less than five minutes.
I'll give you a choice.
Give me money
and I'll get you out of here.
Otherwise,
you'll blow up along with this bomb.
Can you defuse it?
You don't believe me?
I'll get going.
-Tell me, how much do you want?
-Tell us.
Give me 100,000 yuan each.
Also, give me back the money you took.
I'll give you whatever I can.
Defuse the bomb.
I'll give you a more lucrative tip.
Go and save Mr. Li.
I'm sure he can give you more.
Where is Mr. Li?
Mr. Cao kidnapped him.
Where did he go?
My watch has his location.
Please.
Call your godfather.
I know, Mr. Cao.
I know you want the goods, right?
How about this?
Let me go first.
Everything can be discussed later, okay?
We'll talk about it later.
I told you to call him now!
You bet on the wrong one.
I...
Mr. Ou is my godfather.
But we're really not close.
Using me to threaten him is no use.
Okay.
I think your hands
are useless to you now.
-Stay still!
-Behave.
What are you doing?
Stay still!
Mr. Cao!
-Chop it off.
-I'm sorry, Mr. Cao.
I'm sorry!
See, I was right.
Thank you. I'll remember this!
Hey, stay still!
[Three hours ago]
Boss.
Let's go.
Wait here, don't turn off the engine.
All right.
Let's go.
Mr. Cao.
Without a strong mindset,
I wouldn't dare to do business with you.
The rules are the same.
Are five bags sufficient for you?
Mr. Cao.
Not five bags.
It's 50% off.
Mr. Cao.
Can we talk nicely?
The market is very bad recently.
I'd like Group K to show me some respect.
Mr. Cao, your respect should be
measured in catties.
Our goods are measured in grams.
It's not the same.
You'll suffer losses sometimes.
It's not necessarily a bad thing.
What are "losses"?
Is it tasty?
What is this, Mr. Cao?
You came all the way here with this.
I can't let you return empty-handed.
I run a business.
It's all about integrity.
Unlike you.
I'm not done talking to you.
Yet you wanted to leave.
Do you know the drill?
Where is your integrity?
I don't see it, Mr. Cao.
Those who break the rules
will get kicked out.
Are you sure you want to pay
for your mischief?
You're Mr. Ou's godson.
Is your life more valuable
or are your goods more valuable?
Mr. Cao, I told you.
Mr. Ou wouldn't answer my calls.
As his godson, I mean nothing to him.
We're really not that close.
Mr. Ou's company is very big.
He has the Four Vajras by his side
and so many men working for him.
And you're the only one
who calls him godfather.
If I tell you the truth,
don't laugh at me.
I lied to you that Mr. Ou is my godfather.
I did it to live a better life
and not get bullied.
I swear that every word I said is true.
I have only met Mr. Ou a few times.
Mr. Cao.
Buddy!
Who's your buddy?
I...
Hit him!
I'm begging you.
Watch where you're going.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
I'm the new housekeeping director.
A customer lost his luggage.
I'm here to check the footage.
Mr. Cao, I've tried my best.
Toss him.
Mr. Cao, I'll call him again.
-Let's go!
-I'll try again!
Come on!
Mr. Cao!
There was a big deal last time.
I remember now!
He has another phone number!
Mr. Ou has another phone number!
[Hello.]
[This is Yungang police,]
[Command Center 110.]
[How may I help you?]
[Hello?]
[Can you hear me?]
[How may I help you?]
[Are you there?]
[Hello?]
There's an emergency.
Locate the caller quickly!
What's going on?
Boss, I think there's a fire.
A fire?
That's easier for us.
Throw him down.
Come here.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm talking to you.
Kill him!
Move it.
[Due to fire warning triggered]
[by the fire detection system error,]
[please evacuate in an orderly manner.]
[Don't take the elevator.]
[Sorry for the inconvenience.]
Hurry! This way!
Let's go.
I left my phone there.
Let's go. Leave it be.
[Please evacuate in an orderly manner.]
[Don't take the elevator.]
[Sorry for the inconvenience.]
[Please understand.]
[Police]
What kind of bodyguards are you?
I've spent a lot of money on you!
You screwed up at the crucial moment!
I almost died!
Look at him.
Zhao Yun from Changshan.
He fought seven rounds
and single-handedly saved his master.
What is this called?
It's called loyalty!
Do you know where you're lacking?
Here!
IQ.
EQ.
Are you sick?
Well, the one Zhao Yun
saved single-handedly
was Liu Adou.
What do you mean?
This Adou
is the Adou who can't support Adou.
It's not the one you meant.
Who exactly is he?
Did I allow him to talk?
Sir.
He's a security guard at one of our turfs.
He's usually quiet.
It's normal that you don't remember.
I wanted to ask you.
I got in the car and thought,
how did he become a driver?
I told you last time
about hiring a driver.
Didn't Qiangzi...
All right, shut up.
A security guard.
Are you trained?
I trained when I was a kid.
Okay.
Why did you risk your life
to save me today?
I need money.
Money?
I'm afraid of poverty.
When there's a chance to earn more money,
I won't let it slide.
Then how do you get a chance
to earn more money?
By saving your life.
How did you know saving me
will earn you money?
The captain said it.
Do you know what kind of business we do?
It's pretty obvious.
Then let me tell you something.
I won't give you money.
I'll give you a twist instead.
What will you do?
I just want the money.
The captain also agreed
to give me my share.
I'm sure Mr. Li isn't the type
to owe others money, right?
What did I teach you?
Don't make promises so easily.
Am I right?
Give it to him.
Seriously?
The password is the last six numbers.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
You didn't even ask the amount
before thanking me.
Whatever amount you think it's worth,
I'll accept it.
What can I say if I'm not satisfied?
Buddy.
I have to be honest with you.
Actually, I'm kind of annoyed
by your persistence.
But I like your boldness.
If you're willing to work with me,
I promise you'll earn more.
I'll even put your abilities to good use.
I do need money,
but not to the extent
where I'm willing to do anything.
For things I shouldn't know,
I don't want to know or get involved.
I'm just a security guard
at one of your turfs.
I'm working part-time as a driver.
Today,
you absolutely saved me.
If there's nothing else, I'll go.
What's his name?
I think...
What do you mean by "I think"?
Dig up everything about him now!
One more thing!
Gather up all the boys
and capture Mr. Cao!
Director Liu.
It's such an important mission,
but it took you so long to inform us.
I've been watching Li Ruosheng
for so long.
I didn't want to let go of this chance.
This is Mr. Cao's gun.
Good job.
Li Ruosheng is doing
a background check on you.
But your fake identity is fine.
From now on,
you're Mu Qing.
"Mu Qing"?
That's easy to remember.
It's more westernized than Liu Yuanwen.
Yuanwen.
Your undercover mission with Group K
has officially started.
Next,
you have to wait patiently for Li Ruosheng
to invite you to join them.
Get closer to their core.
Capture Ou Zhenhai,
their so-called evidence
of Mr. Ou's crimes.
Lastly, we'll finish them up
with the organization.
Although Li Ruosheng is Mr. Ou's godson,
his power and status within Group K
is the same as an ordinary lackey.
So using him to get
to the very core of this power
might take more time.
There's no rush. Take your time.
It's not hard to find Ou Zhenhai.
However,
gathering evidence of his crime
won't be easy.
Everything must be done with extreme care.
Do you understand?
This is for you.
What is this?
Is this a gift?
Isn't this design a bit old-fashioned?
That's enough. I'm leaving.
Boss, here.
Xiao Wen!
You guys are good.
You managed to find such a remote place.
It's fate.
You guys are spying on me.
No.
It's called "following."
-Yes.
-If you follow back,
that would be great.
We need to know where you are
so that we can deliver the money to you.
Am I right?
Okay.
Okay. Thank you, Mr. Li.
You're welcome.
What is this?
Don't eat this.
Let's go. I'll treat you to a huge meal.
Consider it a token of my gratitude.
I love eating this.
-Bring it along then.
-Okay.
Come on.
Get in.
Mr. Li.
Hot pot in the early morning?
Who says we can't have a hot pot
in the early morning?
Here, wipe your hands.
Mr. Li.
I'll do it myself.
Are you embarrassed?
Sea cucumber.
Here.
Eat up.
Mr. Li, I'll do it myself.
Seriously, I can do it myself.
Okay, help yourself.
Don't be shy.
Mr. Li.
We're two guys eating here.
Don't use your flirting tricks on me.
Let's just eat normally.
Who told you that these are tricks?
I don't do that to women.
I only do that to my brothers.
Am I right?
Yes!
No, Mr. Li. That's not what I meant.
I just feel like...
It's a bit awkward.
I can't fit in.
I got it.
The mood isn't right, so it's not good.
Guys, set the mood.
Sway.
Wave your glow sticks.
That's right.
The mood is all set.
Come on, let's eat.
Mr. Li.
I'll take that as a lesson.
When you're passionate,
it's hotter than this hot pot.
["Love Needs Fighting to Win" playing]
Please get to the point.
♫ You can't help but sigh ♫
♫ When you lose direction ♫
♫ You can't help but be scared ♫
♫ when you're down ♫
♫ It makes you lose hope ♫
You might not know me that well yet.
♫ Living each day in a stupor ♫
But I know everything about you.
♫ Like a scarecrow with no soul ♫
Mu Qing.
You were born in 1987, in Qingshi Town.
♫ Life is like the ocean waves ♫
Your parents worked in a steel factory.
[From now on,]
[you're Mu Qing.]
Your dad, Mu Tian,
hoped that you'd study literature
when you grow up.
So he nicknamed you Xiao Wen.
[That's easy to remember.]
[It's more westernized than Liu Yuanwen.]
There was an accident
in the factory ten years ago.
Your dad fell into molten steel.
There was nothing left of him.
A year later, your mom died of a stroke.
She left behind your 13-year-old sister,
Mu Xiaoyun,
and you to fend for yourselves.
But a year ago,
your sister had lymphatic cancer.
To raise money for her treatment,
you did dirty jobs everywhere.
You even borrowed from a loan shark.
But unfortunately,
you didn't save your sister in the end.
You ended up with a huge debt.
Mr. Li.
You were spying on me earlier.
Now, you looked into my history.
What do you want?
You're a smart guy.
I'm sure you know
what kind of business I do.
I won't beat around the bush.
Didn't I tell you before?
You're talented.
I want us to work together.
I also told you last time.
I have my principles.
What?
"Principles"?
Those are your principles.
Did you ask if others agree?
Even if they agree and understand,
so what?
Will that change anything?
No.
When you can't pay the loan shark,
no one will respect you,
no one will pity you,
and no one will respect your principles.
You'll regret it at that time.
Then it will be too late.
Actually, when I read about your past,
I was quite moved.
It's true.
You're very fortunate.
Your parents spent
all those years with you.
I've never even met my parents.
My grandma told me
that my dad was poor back then.
She refused to give them her blessing.
Guess what?
My mom eloped with my dad.
To give my mom a glamorous wedding
so that everyone would respect him,
he helped to smuggle drugs.
Two months before I was born,
he died on the smuggling ship.
My mom couldn't handle such shocking news.
She gave birth to me
on the factory assembly line
and slit her wrist.
When someone found her...
Her blood had dried up.
Actually, I got into this line of work
without putting much thought.
It's so glamorous on the outside.
My godfather has my back.
I'm actually useless.
I can only rely on myself
to work hard.
You need money.
But what I need is someone
to work with me on my great plan.
I guess we both have our needs.
Let me ask you one last time.
Will you help me or not?
If you agree, let's make a toast.
If you don't want to,
you can leave.
I won't stop you.
A toast to our parents.
Righteous.
Come, let's have a toast.
However, I have three conditions.
Sure, go ahead.
[First, you're the boss on the outside.]
[But the what, how,
and when to do things,]
[you must respect my advice.]
[As for the rest, let me think about it.]
[No problem.]
[You can be the strategist.]
[Tobacco, alcohol, tea]
[A year later]
Sir.
Please enjoy.
You did all this?
Am I virtuous?
Sure.
You seem to be having a hard time lately,
so I made you a little breakfast.
Whom did you learn this from?
"Whom" you ask?
Take a look.
"Breakfast for lovers.
A different recipe for 900 days."
I can't eat it anymore.
Does it taste bad?
It's breakfast for lovers.
Eating it would mean I admit it.
I don't have a lover.
So I'm using you as practice.
What breakfast?
Nobody loves me.
Weren't you okay just now?
Why are you sighing?
We've worked hard enough this past year.
But did it work?
My godfather still looks down on me.
I guess we didn't do well enough.
What should we do then?
No matter how hard you try,
can you be better than the Four Vajras?
Are you close to the four of them?
Do you think they care about me?
They speak directly to my godfather.
Isn't that right?
We're finally getting better.
Dakun is upset now.
He's accusing me of stealing their turf.
He sent me a warning yesterday
and told me to maintain the status quo.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Am I not telling you right now?
[The Four Vajras]
Based on Group K's organization chart,
it's grander and more tight-knit
[Yungang Public Security Bureau]
than we expected.
Even though the photo isn't clear enough,
according to a reliable source,
Dakun is making a deal
with a group of Indonesian drug dealers.
The deal will be done tonight.
Zhao Nan.
Dakun.
How long have you been with me?
Three months.
You're good.
I'm sorry for what happened
when you were with White Dragon,
White Dragon was kind to his men.
A portion of the money I make
belongs to his family.
That's what I like about you.
You're a competent and loyal man.
Do as I say.
From now on,
you'll have a good life.
Thank you for your help.
Where's his position?
It's heading towards Hutou Beach.
If we get our hands on the evidence,
we can arrest Dakun.
It's not just Dakun.
Director Liu.
There wasn't any news
in the last few months.
Everything was revealed
in the past few days.
My master is so amazing.
Yes.
All of this
is the result of Zhao Nan's hard work.
Inform Bao Yunhai.
Get to Hutou Beach right away.
Once he locates him,
move out immediately.
Yes.
Pleasure doing business with you.
The pleasure is all mine.
Spectre's subordinates are very powerful.
Remember this.
In Asia,
even Spectre will have to rely on Mr. Ou.
Don't make a poor judgment call.
I'm just a buyer.
We'll do whatever you say.
Pleasure doing business with you. Bye.
Bye.
Bye!
Dakun.
Zhao Nan.
You're a bit distracted today.
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
No.
This is good stuff.
White Dragon gave this to his men
when he was alive.
Let me see it.
If you like it,
I'll give it to you.
You're too kind.
A gentleman doesn't take what others like.
It's good stuff indeed.
But...
I would never want
a dead man's belonging.
Dakun.
Are you kidding me?
Do you think I don't know who you are?
How dare you spy on me?
I'll kill you!
Same old rules.
I'm sorry, Director Liu.
We didn't get there in time.
Reporting!
Director Liu.
We've informed the police in Indonesia
to round up the drug dealers.
During the search,
there was no sign of our officer.
This is the drug dealers protesting.
Inform all districts
to dispatch police forces.
No matter what, we must find Zhao Nan!
Losing the goods, making a scene.
You almost brought the police upon me.
This is how you do things for me.
What's wrong? Why are you so angry?
Take them to sort it out.
Go on!
What happened?
Everything was fine just now.
My godfather told me
to give some turfs to Dakun.
We sacrificed our lives
for all these places.
Why should we give them to Dakun?
In the end,
my godfather doesn't respect me.
He doesn't treat me like his godson.
Initially, you're his godson in name only.
Otherwise,
why are you working so hard?
Look around you.
You're still speaking so nonchalantly.
You're still drinking.
What's the use of getting drunk?
Someone stole my turf
and I can't do anything.
Can't I have some wine?
Just because Dakun wants it,
you're giving it to him?
What should I do then?
I have to give it either way.
Too bad we can't speak to Mr. Ou directly.
In the group,
Dakun is in charge of sales.
It's only natural
that he takes over the new turf.
All he needs is to whisper unheeded advice
to Mr. Ou.
Mr. Ou won't even know
you're the one who got the turf.
Does that mean we're working for him?
Exactly.
The most important thing is
we need to speak to Mr. Ou directly.
We must take control.
We can't let Dakun do as he pleases again.
Tell me what you think.
As you know,
Scorpion is a troublemaker
for the group now.
Taking advantage of this perfect market,
he's selling some shoddy goods
at a cheap price.
He took business away from the group.
Recently, Dakun is having a hard time too.
So you're thrown under the bus.
Isn't he just a tyrant?
He's scared of Scorpion.
But he isn't scared of me.
Mr. Ou didn't know about this, right?
You've never told him about your hardship.
Shall we fight?
Fight! We must fight!
But how do we fight?
Overthrow Scorpion.
Just the two of us?
Dakun left him alone
for us to take the risk.
If we take Scorpion out
and claim his turfs as our own,
we can expand our power.
Besides, we can snitch on Dakun
in front of Mr. Ou.
Kill two birds with one stone.
Goodbye, Mr. Mu.
Taxi.
Taxi!
["Never Say Goodbye" playing]
♫ In the evening, by the serene beach ♫
♫ From my camera,
you're looking at the shore ♫
♫ I hope our hearts will never sway ♫
♫ I want to fill my world up with you ♫
♫ If love is
the destination of wandering ♫
♫ Your smile blurs my sight ♫
♫ At this moment, I am lost for words ♫
♫ Close your eyes slowly ♫
♫ And let me kiss the edge of your nose ♫
♫ The wind blows past me as I zone out ♫
♫ When I turn around,
I lose you in the midst of a crowd ♫
♫ You are a teardrop away ♫
♫ And I shall quietly wait ♫
♫ If love never leaves us ♫
♫ This beautiful encounter ♫
♫ Let's promise to never ♫
♫ Say goodbye ♫
♫ The wind blows past you
as you zone out ♫
♫ Suddenly, I realized ♫
♫ What we experience is love ♫
♫ And time is my love confession ♫
♫ If love ever comes ♫
♫ It's the sweetest thing
I look forward to ♫
♫ Let's promise to never ♫
♫ Say goodbye ♫