[English subtitles are available]
[Episode 34]
Wait.
I'll go with you.
You can get up.
Where's my child?
Don't worry. Our guys are on it.
Nurse.
How far exactly is the nursery?
Where's the nursery?
It's right in front.
Mr. Glasses.
What a coincidence. You're here too.
Are you not feeling well?
No, I'm fine.
Doctor Zhao is rushing you.
-Just give me the baby.
-Why are you here all of a sudden?
I'm embarrassed to talk about it.
It's a little gynecological condition.
It's nothing.
Take care of yourself then.
Mr. Glasses, tell my dad
that I'll cook for him in a few days.
Ask him to prepare me
some brisket and Chinese yam.
Chinese yam is good for his stomach.
Also, tell him that the monk fruit
I ordered is arriving soon.
Kexin, how about you call your dad
and tell him that?
Of course I will.
I just need you to remind him.
Kexin. I'm really busy right now.
-I need to go.
-Sure.
Mr. Glasses.
Shao Nan, you're here too.
Mr. Glasses, bad news.
-We lost her.
-What?
We've searched all the emergency rooms.
We couldn't find her.
I don't know where they took her.
You idiot.
Mr. Glasses, are you looking for someone?
Do you need my help?
-I'm leaving, Kexin.
-Who is it?
Take care of yourself.
Go to the car park.
[Pediatrics, Ward]
Where are you going?
-What happened?
-He ran away.
After him!
What's wrong?
I think
I have to go back to get my baby.
Don't panic.
We went through so much trouble
to get you out.
You'd cause us trouble if you go back now.
But I can't leave my baby.
Trust us.
Your baby will be here soon.
She's here.
My baby.
Are you okay?
A doctor saved me.
His identity is still unclear.
Get in the car.
Get Xiaoyue and the baby out of here.
-Okay.
-Come on.
How was it? Did you guys get the baby?
She already left.
That's good.
Where is Mu Qing?
Isn't he with you?
Mu Qing.
Are you okay?
How did you get hurt?
It's okay.
Glasses is after me.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
Tell me.
Where is Mu Qing?
The moment you stepped into my house,
I told you he's not here.
Why don't I show you to his house?
Stop the nonsense.
Where on earth is he?
What exactly happened?
Tell me.
Mr. Glasses, we couldn't find him.
Look.
Hello, sir.
[Are you sure Mu Qing is behind this?]
I haven't found him yet.
But don't worry.
Once I find him, I'll check his wound.
Then I'll know if he's behind this.
[Hurry and find him then.]
Yes, sir.
What's going on, Mr. Glasses?
Here's what you should do.
Call Mu Qing right now.
Tell him to go to the hot spring resort.
Take care of your wound carefully.
Don't let it get wet.
Or it will get infected.
Okay.
If you're careless again,
I won't help you
when you're old and couldn't walk.
Even if you don't,
a lot of people will help me.
What did you say?
Liu Yuanwen, you're doing it on purpose.
A lot of people will help you, right?
You don't want me to help you, right?
I'm sorry, okay?
From now on, I'll only let you help me.
I'm telling you. This isn't over.
I'll deal with you when we get back.
If you hadn't gotten hurt, I...
I know you're worried about me.
I'll be careful next time.
Ruosheng told me to go
to the hot spring resort now.
Why did he suddenly ask you to go there?
Could it be related
to what happened today?
If anyone asks where we went today,
just say I went
to the gynecologist with you
for a routine checkup.
Are you really going?
If I don't go,
it will cause a bigger problem.
Is he my son?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't keep my promise.
I failed.
Congtou.
Aren't the three of us together now?
That means heaven has been kind to us.
No matter how long you're in there,
I'll wait for you.
Promise me not to be stubborn, okay?
Come clean with them.
Be honest.
Then they might reduce your charges.
[Yungang Public Security Bureau]
You guys are all here.
Why must we meet in the meeting room?
Captain Rong.
I have some questions.
Go ahead.
Is there something
that you're hiding from us?
No. What can I hide from you?
This morning at the hospital,
a man came out of nowhere
and helped me save the child.
Who is he?
Yimeng, be disciplined.
There's one more thing.
Ou Kexin showing up at the hospital
wasn't a coincidence.
She was obviously helping us out.
Why is that?
[Yungang Public Security Bureau]
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
Let's talk inside.
Come in first.
You were really at the hospital?
What's wrong?
"What's wrong?"
Godfather and Glasses are suspecting you.
That's what's wrong.
Why would they suspect me?
They suspect that you're the mole.
Tell me what happened.
[Hello.]
There's an emergency.
I need to see you right away.
[Okay. Let's meet at the usual place.]
I was at the hospital.
But I'm definitely not the mole.
How can Glasses just decide
that I'm the mole?
Maybe he's trying
to divert suspicion away from himself.
Then tell me.
How could you coincidentally
be at the hospital?
I went to the hospital with Kexin
for her routine gynecological checkup.
Then something so serious
just happened out of the blue.
Don't you think
it's strangely coincidental?
Are you saying
that Glasses is setting you up?
It's not as simple as a setup.
First, he lost Congtou.
Then he lost Xiaoyue and her baby.
He can't bear the responsibility.
That's why he needs someone
to take the blame.
He can't blame it on you or Kexin.
That's why he's making me
take all the blame.
What about the wound?
How did you get hurt?
When I was at the hospital with Ou Kexin,
I ran into Glasses's men.
You know he has never liked me.
I've been an eyesore to him.
He wanted to take that opportunity
to get rid of me completely.
Did he have the guts to do that?
Get rid of you in the open like that?
He certainly won't be able
to get rid of me just like that.
But by leaving a wound like this on me,
he can use it against me
as evidence and as my weakness.
He can use this wound
and say whatever he wants to Mr. Ou.
He can say that I'm a mole
or whatever he wants.
You and Ou Kexin...
You guys are really something.
Whatever disease you're having,
couldn't you have gotten a checkup
another day?
I'm telling you, Mu Qing.
Good thing he sent me today.
Glasses's men are already
waiting for you at the door.
He said if there's a wound on your hand,
he'll finish you off here today.
Look, I told you so.
Glasses is trying to hide the fact
that he lost Xiaoyue and her baby.
So he's putting all the blame on me
and accusing me of being a mole.
Hello, sir.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
If Mu Qing is the mole,
keep one thing in mind.
You don't have to be considerate of Kexin
or hold back.
Yes, sir.
Rong Yu.
You're finally here.
-Yuanwen was taken away.
-Sit down first.
Li Ruosheng invited Yuanwen
to the hot spring resort.
He was injured today.
And he asked to see him.
I'm afraid his identity has been revealed.
What's wrong?
Say something.
Director Wang said this before.
Once things get out of control,
terminate the operation immediately.
What do you mean?
Explain it to me.
Yuanwen is an agent
planted by Director Liu in Group K.
His mission is to split up Group K,
so you'll have more opportunities
to get close to Mr. Ou and catch Spectre.
But arresting Spectre
is not Yuanwen's main mission.
He has almost completed his mission.
Even without this unexpected situation,
he will soon end his undercover mission.
But we can't leave him like this.
Even if he won't participate
in other missions,
you have to save him, Rong Yao.
I'll save him no matter what.
Where is he?
Currently, the whole group is in chaos.
Mr. Ou hates traitors the most.
Glasses is by Mr. Ou's side every day.
He knows everything.
He'll get rid of me first,
then you'll be next.
Soon, the whole of Group K
will be controlled by Glasses alone.
At this rate,
I won't be safe for long.
Ruosheng, you should leave now.
If you stay with me,
Glasses will think
that we're on the same side
and say that you're a mole too.
Buddy, you're really a good friend.
Just worry about yourself
at times like this.
Tell me.
What should you do now?
What can I do?
How about this?
Figure out how to run away later.
I'll talk to Godfather first.
If he listens to me,
I'll call you back.
If he doesn't listen,
you should leave Yungang
and never come back.
Run away?
How?
He's here. Come on out.
Mr. Li.
I'm sorry.
Isn't that a bit too harsh?
Come on.
-Over there.
-Okay.
Mu Qing ran away?
Inform our men.
You must catch him.
If he resists, kill him.
Drive faster.
Yes.
Mr. Ou gave us an order.
If you resist, we'll finish you off.
Mr. Mu, don't make this hard for me.
Is this what Mr. Ou wants
or what Glasses wants?
After him!
Don't lose anyone. Move out!
Yes, sir!
This way.
What are you doing?
What do you want?
I'm a police officer. Sorry.
Go back and tell Glasses.
Sooner or later,
I'll make him pay for this.
Get lost!
[Team One, clear.]
[Team Two, clear.]
[Team Three, clear too.]
Did they move him away?
Bring everyone here.
Let me ask you one last time.
Where are Mu Qing and Li Ruosheng?
Possession of deadly weapons.
Alleged drug dealing.
Alleged assault.
Any one of these is enough
to put you in jail.
Now, speak!
They escaped.
When did they escape?
Where did they go?
Li Ruosheng ran away long ago.
Before you arrived,
Mu Qing was chased into the alleyway.
-Chased by how many people?
-Two people.
Get down.
Mr. Bao, Zhao Ran.
[Look up the three alleys nearby.]
Remember,
there are three men including Mu Qing.
They might possess deadly weapons.
Copy that.
Let's go check up on the alleys.
Only one unconscious lackey was found.
Mu Qing and the other are missing.
-I'll go check out ahead.
-Okay.
Come on.
Captain Rong, there's no sign of Mu Qing.
Contact the Traffic Division right away.
We have to find them
through the CCTV footage.
[Yes, sir.]
Take them away.
Yes.
-Come on, get up.
-Get up.
-Get up. Move.
-Come on.
Let's go.
Mr. Glasses, they seem like our men.
What do we do?
Let's go back first.
Yes.
Mr. Glasses.
Who is this?
He's one of us.
Get in now.
That's what happened.
So that means
you didn't kill Mu Qing
and let him escape?
I...
Mu Qing has a message for you.
What is it?
Well...
Go ahead. I won't blame you.
He said
for whatever happened today,
he'll settle the score with you one day.
He had the guts to say that.
Mr. Glasses, it seems like Mu Qing
wants you to take the blame
for what happened today.
Okay, I understand.
You did a good job. Get some rest.
What else do you want to say?
Have you heard from Mu Qing?
The police were there.
Was he arrested?
No, he ran away.
I really thought
something had happened to Mu Qing.
You scoundrel.
Do you really think you can protect him?
I can't protect him.
But I couldn't just stand here
and watch you kill him
based on Mr. Glasses's claim alone.
His claim?
Fine.
I'll listen to what you have to say.
I'm telling you.
If you can't give me a valid reason,
I'll kill you too!
Okay.
Mr. Glasses tried to kill Mu Qing.
He planned to kill him
before you find out.
But now, it looks like
he didn't just want to kill Mu Qing.
He even called the police
to get rid of me too.
This is such a flawless plan.
What if Glasses was right
and Mu Qing is a mole sent by the police?
If Mu Qing was the mole,
why would he run away?
So you mean
Glasses colluded with the police
to arrest all of you?
Tell me what his purpose is.
He's scared.
He's scared that Mu Qing
will expose him in front of you.
That's why he set him up
to get rid of him for good.
Then Mu Qing will take the blame for him.
That way, you'll be convinced
that Mu Qing is the mole.
Godfather, I really used to believe
that Mr. Glasses is most loyal to you.
I really didn't expect
that he would do such things.
You're overthinking it, kid.
He has been with me for over a decade.
I know him very well.
He doesn't have the guts.
[Yungang Public Security Bureau
Command Center]
[Innovation in technology,
Precision in command]
[Service in action, Strict and efficient]
Something is up with Captain Rong.
What's wrong?
Look at his expression.
He doesn't look like a police officer
who is looking for a fugitive.
What does he look like then?
He looks like
he's looking for his real brother.
Stop making wild guesses.
Keep a close eye.
Director Liu.
-Director Liu.
-Sit.
Director Liu.
Let's talk outside.
Keep an eye out.
Didn't you search that area just now?
[Innovation in technology,
Precision in command]
Am I right?
[Service in action, Strict and efficient]
It was there just now, right?
[Blood Test Report]
The blood found in the alley
does belong to Yuanwen.
That was a lot of blood.
If he doesn't get treated in time,
he'll die.
I've called all the major hospitals.
There's no news on Yuanwen.
He knew you were there to save him.
Why did he run?
Maybe it was urgent.
He had no choice.
Even so, two hours have passed.
Why didn't he contact us?
You mean...
He didn't want you to save him.
Mr. Glasses.
I don't understand what happened tonight.
Why were the police here?
You're right.
Why were the police there all of a sudden?
The fact that the police were there
further proves that Mu Qing
is the police's undercover agent.
Right.
Tonight,
Mu Qing and Li Ruosheng were together.
Why wasn't Li Ruosheng arrested?
Where's Li Ruosheng?
Come to think of it,
I really didn't see him.
Take me to Mr. Ou's house.
Yes.
Mu Qing is injured again?
Where is he hurt? Is it serious?
Where is he?
Don't worry.
My team is looking for him.
Check out the situation at Mr. Ou's house.
What happened to Yuanwen
was Glasses's doing.
[First, you'll go to Mr. Ou's house.]
[Confirm if Yuanwen is in their hands.]
Second, find out if what Glasses did
was Mr. Ou's order.
[Do you understand?]
Understood.
Have faith in me and Yuanwen.
It's going to be okay.
I know.
What are you looking at?
You look so nervous.
I asked you to go home to rest.
Why are you here?
Sir.
I want to tell you
about what happened tonight.
Have a seat.
How many were arrested?
More than ten people.
But don't worry, sir.
They're all newcomers.
They're not familiar
with the business yet.
No matter how hard the police investigate,
they won't find anything.
But Mu Qing...
Didn't Mu Qing run away?
Don't panic.
Under current circumstances,
no news means good news.
He wasn't arrested after all.
Sir.
I suspect what happened tonight
was just a show
put on by Mu Qing and the police.
Who is the intended audience?
You're the audience, of course.
Goodness.
It was such a big show.
It even involved the police and your men
and it caused so much trouble.
All of that was to put on a show for me?
Mu Qing is trying to frame me.
He and Li Ruosheng
have always disagreed with me.
They must be trying
to drive a wedge between us.
Glasses.
You came here in such a hurry
just to tell me that?
So that I won't suspect you?
Sir.
I've been with you for over a decade...
Glasses.
Before this, I had never doubted you.
But someone told me
exactly the same thing you told me.
Do you want to meet this person?
Who is it?
Ruosheng.
Come out and have some tea.
Godfather.
Brat.
You came here pretty quickly.
Do you regret not coming here earlier?
I regret not keeping an eye on you.
And you let the mole escape.
I let the mole escape?
So to you,
I'm also the mole now?
It's up to Mr. Ou
to decide who the mole is.
Ruosheng.
Repeat what you told me earlier
to Mr. Glasses.
Mr. Glasses.
I usually call you "Mr. Glasses"
because I respect you.
But you used Godfather's trust for you.
You went behind his back,
accused me and Mu Qing of being moles,
and tried to kill us.
This is not
what a respectable senior should do.
Now, we don't know where Mu Qing is
and I came back alive.
Are you disappointed?
There has been some unrest in the group.
The dark web had problems,
the factory closed down,
and Tieguanyin committed suicide.
All of these are related to you.
You lost Congtou and Xiaoyue.
Yet you tried to blame me
and Mu Qing for it.
Shut up!
Godfather.
Those were the things that I know.
There are still many things I don't know.
I'm afraid only Mr. Glasses knows.
Sir.
I've worked with you for many years.
I'm loyal to you and the group.
Don't listen to his nonsense!
That's all I have to say.
Whether I'm accusing him or not,
you know that very well, Godfather.
This is not a court of law.
And I'm not a judge.
I don't have anymore patience
to hear any of this.
But...
today is the last chance for both of you.
If you have something to say, say it now.
Sure.
Mr. Glasses.
Haven't you always seen me as an eyesore
and wanted to get rid of me?
Sure.
Today, in front of Godfather,
let's sort things out once and for all.
Are you scared of saying it?
All right.
I'll say it on your behalf.
You pretend to be loyal to Godfather.
But secretly,
how much damage
have you done to the group?
Dakun, Guanyin, Congtou.
You got rid of them one after another.
Now, it's my turn and Mu Qing's.
Why are we all in trouble
and nothing ever happens to you?
What do you plan to do next?
Do you want to overthrow Godfather
and take over his place?
Do you have a death wish?
Give me the gun.
Do you think I won't kill you?
Say it again.
I dare you to say it again!
Of course you dare to kill me.
If Mu Qing and I die,
no one will be in your way anymore.
Great, I'll grant you your wish.
Where is Mu Qing?
Where did you take him?
I think I understand it now.
Now that Mu Qing is gone,
you want to kill Li Ruosheng too, right?
Kexin.
Don't make assumptions.
How did you know Mu Qing is gone?
He called and said
you were going to kill him.
He also said
that if anything happens to him...
Dad, he wanted me to tell you
that he's not the mole.
Do you know where he is?
You're asking me that?
You should know better than I do.
If anything happens to him,
you're all accomplices.
How would I know?
My men are looking for him too.
When you texted him,
I was with him.
You texted and asked him
to meet at the hot spring.
He got into trouble
not long after he went out.
What are you plotting?
You two are working together.
You're something, Li Ruosheng.
When did you learn to collude with others
to kill your own friend?
Was Mu Qing with you the whole time?
Of course he was with me.
I don't feel well these couple of days.
This morning,
he even went to the hospital with me.
Do you want me
to show you my medical report?
Mr. Glasses.
Weren't you at the hospital too?
You didn't tell my dad?
Sir.
I did see Kexin at the hospital.
But I don't see Mu Qing.
Don't think I don't know
what you're up to.
If I weren't there,
Mu Qing would've been dead because of you.
Dad.
Was all of this your idea?
Glasses.
-Sir.
-Go to the study.
Ruosheng, go home.
Mr. Glasses is just your subordinate.
Without your permission,
he wouldn't dare to go that far.
These were all your instructions.
Am I right?
Listen to me.
You're still suspecting Mu Qing.
["The Place Farthest Away" playing]
♫ Against the light ♫
♫ Your vague silhouette ♫
♫ I reach out with my hands ♫
♫ But my hug passes through you ♫
♫ Maybe this is an illusion ♫
♫ A sweet dream ♫
♫ Waiting for you ♫
♫ To notice it and wake me up ♫
♫ I wonder if getting close to you ♫
♫ One swirl will light up the stars ♫
♫ I wonder if someone
will tell you for me ♫
♫ At the place farthest away ♫
♫ Only then will the kites roam freely ♫
♫ If I gaze relentlessly ♫
♫ I wonder if there will be starlight ♫
♫ If the falling fireworks ♫
♫ Give me the sadness of being lonely ♫
♫ If your gaze gives me ♫
♫ A sense of direction ♫
♫ I'll give you an answer too ♫
♫ Looking at your turbulent silence ♫
♫ I really hope you can understand ♫
♫ So I remain extremely quiet and gentle ♫
♫ Waiting for you to kiss my forehead ♫
♫ It seems you're in front of me ♫
♫ Like the four seasons in my heart ♫
♫ Gentle and heart-wrenching ♫
♫ What can I say? ♫
♫ At the place farthest away ♫
♫ Only then will the kites roam freely ♫
♫ If I gaze relentlessly ♫
♫ I wonder if there will be starlight ♫
♫ Standing on your spot ♫
♫ Only then will I forget
the faraway place ♫
♫ Only your gaze ♫
♫ Can give me acknowledgment ♫
♫ Can give me an answer ♫