[English subtitles are available]
[Episode 35]
Glasses.
-Sir.
-Go to the study.
Ruosheng, go home.
Mr. Glasses is just your subordinate.
Without your permission,
he wouldn't dare to go that far.
These were all your instructions.
Am I right?
Listen to me.
You're still suspecting Mu Qing.
Aren't you?
Are you still suspecting him?
Yes, I'm still suspecting Mu Qing.
So many things have happened.
I have reasons to suspect him.
I've said it many times, this is business.
If you make one wrong move,
you'll lose your life.
Do you want that to happen to me?
What you need to do now
is not to question me or irritate me.
I'll just ask you one thing.
Did Mu Qing go to the hospital with you?
I told you he was with me.
I get that you don't trust him,
but you don't even trust me now!
I can't trust anyone right now.
Mu Qing is very lucky.
It will be okay.
I have sent all of my men.
We will find him.
Don't worry.
What are the odds?
You're so unlucky.
Why were you at the hospital back then?
You even ran into Glasses.
Godfather gets suspicious easily.
Now, it's complicated.
If you can shut up,
I'll be fine with that.
Why are so mean to me?
If you didn't call Mu Qing
to the hot spring,
this wouldn't have happened.
Mu Qing is my best friend.
I would never harm him.
He's missing
and we don't know if he's alive.
I don't feel any better than you.
I just want him to be alive.
That's what happened today.
Sir, please let me explain.
What is there to explain?
Hurry and find Mu Qing!
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Kexin.
Don't worry too much.
Wait for my call.
["The Most Romantic Oblivion" playing]
♫ It's pouring ♫
♫ The cat is looking at you
from the lonely window ♫
♫ In those eyes ♫
♫ There are disappointment and memory ♫
♫ It's away from you ♫
♫ Half a teardrop away ♫
You're finally back.
♫ So much intimacy ♫
How did you get so hurt?
♫ Is being remembered ♫
What happened?
If you had come back later,
you might not have seen me again.
♫ You that I love ♫
You're hurt so badly,
♫ Seem to melt in my night ♫
stop joking around.
Let's go over there. Come on.
♫ The pain becomes a sigh ♫
♫ Carved onto the pillows as tears ♫
What happened?
Should we go to the hospital?
♫ I miss you ♫
♫ You stay silent in my breath ♫
♫ Lie with me as you fall asleep ♫
How did this happen?
♫ Until I wake up from my dream ♫
♫ The most romantic oblivion ♫
♫ Is to grow old together ♫
♫ The longest love ♫
Mu Qing.
♫ Is when things remain unchanged ♫
♫ I'm still waiting for you ♫
Mu Qing.
[Hello?]
♫ So don't worry ♫
♫ So you become a secret ♫
♫ So I'm afraid to be reminded ♫
♫ That I miss you ♫
He has gone into shock.
We need a transfusion.
I don't have blood here.
-We have to go to the hospital.
-It's too late. Use mine.
Yours?
My blood type is A. So is he.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
It will be too late if we hesitate.
Okay, come with me.
How is he?
It's still not looking good.
It's not enough blood.
-Then have some more.
-It's already 400ml.
You'll be in danger too.
Don't worry about me. Save him.
Please, Doctor Wang.
I'll do my best, Rong Yu.
♫ Against the light ♫
♫ Your vague silhouette ♫
♫ I reach out with my hands ♫
♫ But my hug passes through you ♫
♫ Maybe this is an illusion ♫
♫ A sweet dream ♫
♫ Waiting for you ♫
♫ To notice it and wake me up ♫
♫ I wonder if getting close to you ♫
♫ One swirl will light up the stars ♫
I'll get you some sugar water.
♫ I wonder if someone
will tell you for me ♫
♫ At the place farthest away ♫
♫ Only then will the kites roam freely ♫
♫ If I gaze relentlessly ♫
♫ I wonder if there will be starlight ♫
♫ If the falling fireworks ♫
♫ Give me the sadness of being lonely ♫
♫ If your gaze gives me ♫
♫ A sense of direction ♫
♫ I'll give you an answer too ♫
♫ Looking at your turbulent silence ♫
♫ I really hope you can understand ♫
You're awake.
♫ So I remain extremely quiet and gentle ♫
Luckily, before you went unconscious,
you gave me a call.
♫ Waiting for you to kiss my forehead ♫
Otherwise, you would've been in trouble.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
♫ It seems you're in front of me ♫
♫ Like the four seasons in my heart ♫
If you want to thank someone,
thank the lady who brought you here.
If she didn't insist
♫ Gentle and heart-wrenching ♫
on giving you 800ml of blood,
♫ What can I say? ♫
you wouldn't have made it.
♫ At the place farthest away ♫
But it was too close this time.
♫ Only then will the kites roam freely ♫
I'll find Director Liu and talk to him.
So he'll give you compensation.
♫ If I gaze relentlessly ♫
♫ I wonder if there will be starlight ♫
All right. Get some rest.
♫ If the falling fireworks ♫
It's safe here.
Okay.
♫ Give me the sadness of being lonely ♫
♫ If your gaze gives me ♫
♫ A sense of direction ♫
♫ I'll give you an answer too ♫
♫ Even after the stars have changed ♫
♫ I hope you'll still recognize me
among the stars ♫
♫ At the place farthest away ♫
♫ I want to wander around with you ♫
♫ Going against the wind, I fly with you ♫
♫ To embrace the starlight ♫
♫ Standing on your spot ♫
♫ Only then will I forget
the faraway place ♫
♫ Only your gaze ♫
♫ Can give me acknowledgment ♫
♫ Can give me an answer ♫
[Doctor Wang.]
We drew so much blood. You need to rest.
Doctor Wang.
I didn't expect to see you again.
Me too.
Three years ago,
I did your surgery.
Back then,
you had to go to France immediately.
I didn't have enough time.
I was so worried that your skin might rot
and ruin your treatment.
But now, it seems like
I shouldn't have been worried.
That's because you have amazing skills.
Doctor Wang.
I know that this is a secret.
I won't tell anyone.
Thank you.
What are you doing up?
Go back to bed.
I'm fine now.
You're not fine. You're badly injured.
Go back to bed. Hurry.
Here.
You haven't found him?
Yes.
You had over 30 people.
You searched all night
and couldn't find him?
Yungang is too huge.
He could be anywhere.
Besides,
30 people weren't even enough.
You're useless.
Come here.
You're all useless.
Mr. Glasses.
Although Mu Qing escaped,
Li Ruosheng is still here.
Don't worry.
If you give orders,
we will definitely get them for you.
Yes, not just Li Ruosheng,
even if Mu Qing is locked up,
we'll still give him a rough time.
You don't know a thing!
Mr. Glasses.
What a coincidence. You're here too.
Sit down and enjoy.
[How did the police know]
[where Xiaoyue was?]
Congtou happens to be missing too.
Come with me.
Mr. Glasses.
What are you looking for?
What exactly are you looking for?
Am I mistaken?
Mr. Glasses.
Should I take a few men
to keep an eye on Ou Kexin?
Given their relationship,
if Mu Qing comes back,
he will surely go to her first.
Do you think Mu Qing
will dare to come back?
Here, drink this.
You made this?
It's good for your health.
I added brown sugar and dates.
What about this?
Pork liver.
You put liver in here?
That's why it smells.
This is why it's good for you.
Stop talking. Drink up.
Is it okay?
It's all right.
Is Doctor Wang related to the bureau?
How did you think of calling him?
Doctor Wang is Director Liu's friend.
All this time,
he has been secretly treating my wounds.
He's one of us.
Do you come here often?
When we're doing undercover work,
sometimes, in order to make it look real,
getting into fights is inevitable.
Getting hurt all the time is normal.
Fortunately, I'm always lucky enough
to make it out alive.
I was never seriously injured.
I have something to tell you.
Why are you so serious all of a sudden?
Group K is being torn apart.
Glasses is the only one left.
Leave him to me.
Just focus on healing.
I've been doing this for so long.
Glasses is the only Four Vajras left.
Everyone else is gone.
You want me to stop right now?
No way.
Your situation with the group
makes things dangerous.
Now, it's not only Mr. Ou,
but Glasses is also suspecting you.
You shouldn't go back now.
Whose idea is this?
It's my idea.
You work for
the Provincial Public Security Bureau,
but the orders we got
only told us to work together.
I wasn't asked to follow your orders.
Unless I'm given an order to stop,
no matter what happens,
I'll finish my mission
and stay undercover.
No one can stop me.
Your cover is blown.
How can you go back in?
I can fix this.
I want to see Rong Yao.
I need to tell him something in person.
Okay.
Thank Doctor Wang for me.
I'll make an arrangement.
Thank you.
How is it? Are they okay?
Yuanwen made it.
Thank goodness.
Rong Yu said
Yuanwen wouldn't give up on the mission.
He has his own plans.
He requested to see you.
I'll go see him even if he didn't ask.
I'll get going, Director Liu.
[I'm thankful to you and Director Liu.]
[But I have to go back to the group now.]
[I need to do my undercover mission.]
You're being suspected now.
No matter what,
I can't let you go back there.
Don't worry about that.
-I have a plan.
-Yuanwen.
Your mission is complete.
With only Glasses left,
he won't be able to do much.
You have to listen to me this time.
I understand what you're saying.
But you're asking Skylark
to do this mission alone.
It's too dangerous.
Besides, Spectre is about to show up.
She needs my help.
That's why he won't come back.
Yuanwen is a rational person.
But this time,
I didn't expect him to do this.
I guess our leader was right.
I don't want him to go back in.
It's too risky.
Make a plan.
Coordinate with Rong Yu
and bring him back.
I'll report to Director Wang.
Yes, sir.
I'll arrange for Yuanwen's matters.
I'll need you to coordinate with me.
This is the new code,
the safe house,
and the emergency contact.
It's all in there.
From now on,
you've entered the next phase.
You need to take over Mr. Ou's business
to find Spectre.
Stay alert at all times.
Know your identity.
I know exactly who I am.
[The shocking case]
[known as "812 Drug Case"]
[is finally over.]
[We should pay our highest respect]
[to the officers.]
Director Wang.
I've made up my mind.
Don't worry.
Arrange it as soon as possible.
I still hope
that you'll reconsider.
Besides, the bureau...
Ou Kexin died in a car accident in France
Although the Interpol
has blocked the information,
the clock is still ticking.
I need to finish the surgery
and head to France to replace Ou Kexin.
This is my own will.
It has nothing to do with the bureau.
I hope
that my ruined face
and French language skills
can still be useful.
Or else,
I'll feel like a useless person.
I understand
what you're saying.
There's one more thing.
I hope Rong Yao and Yuanwen
can forget about me forever.
From now on,
I'll be the only person
who knows your true identity.
I will arrange for you
to go to France soon.
Just get ready.
Yes, sir.
Rong Yu, are you ready?
Kexin.
You look better
than in the photo.
During the three years in France,
I tried everything to become Ou Kexin.
But I haven't forgotten
that I'm a police officer.
At such a crucial time,
I'll definitely be careful.
I have faith in you.
The bureau has approved?
That's great.
I'll contact Li Ruosheng now.
Hold on.
They have agreed,
but you should stick to your role.
The bureau has requested
that you go out of town.
It's to make your previous claim real.
Okay, I'll do it.
Here.
Here are some clothes for you.
Change into it.
In 30 minutes,
at the 101 bus stop,
someone will be there to pick you up.
Okay.
Don't worry.
[101. Next station, Gangdong]
Hello, I'm Xiaozhang.
I will escort you.
Hello.
I heard we're going out of town.
Where exactly are we going?
You'll find out soon.
Get some rest.
Okay, thank you.
Am I not just going on a little trip?
Do you need to come too?
Isn't it safer if I'm here?
Get in the car.
Open it.
What is it?
Take a look first.
[Personal Information, Name: Wang Wen]
[Wang Wen]
What is this?
Stay in Thailand for a while.
You don't have to worry
about matters in Yungang.
Stop the car.
Yuanwen.
It's the bureau's decision.
Stop the car!
Yuanwen.
It's not just the bureau's decision.
This is what Skylark wants too.
The main forces of Group K
have fallen apart.
Your work here is done.
It's Skylark's mission to get Spectre.
I can help her from the inside.
Being Mr. Ou's daughter
can't get her close to the core.
But I can.
Just because I had a little trouble,
you're pulling me out.
I worked so hard to go with the plan.
It will all be for nothing.
What do you mean by that?
Although Glasses was suspecting me,
I managed to turn Li Ruosheng against him.
I made him think
that Glasses wanted to kill me.
After what just happened,
I have my proof.
If I go back to the group now,
I'll have Li Ruosheng
to help me get rid of Glasses.
With help from Skylark,
won't it be great?
Take a look at this.
What?
Take a look first.
[Yuanwen.]
[If you're reading this,]
[that means]
[you're on the way to Thailand.]
[Letting you go is the bureau's decision]
[and also my personal wish.]
[Among the Four Vajras of Group K,]
[we've gotten rid of three of them.]
[Glasses is also losing Mr. Ou's trust.]
[It's a big win.]
[You've almost completed your mission.]
[I appreciate being partners with you.]
[I really hope]
[that I can keep being your partner.]
[But your work is done.]
[And mine is just getting started.]
[The road ahead will be more dangerous.]
[But I'm certain]
[that I can handle this alone.]
[Please don't worry.]
[Have faith in the bureau.]
[I believe]
[that the dawn of victory]
[will soon shine on us.]
[I'll also do my best to protect myself]
[and share the glory of success with you]
[We chose our beginnings in silence.]
[But we return proudly.]
[A person chose the dawn at night.]
[The dawn picked him to be a free breeze.]
[Take care.]
[Skylark.]
[Skylark is your superior.]
She can decide whether you'll stay.
Yuanwen, it's over.
You should go.
No way.
You're asking her to go in alone.
Aside from her cover as Mr. Ou's daughter,
she has no other advantages.
Do you understand?
In this situation,
she's doing this on her own.
No way!
Liu Yuanwen, I'll repeat.
This is an order from the higher-ups.
I don't want to hear any of this.
I want to see Director Wang right now!
Hello?
Hello, Director Wang.
It's Yuanwen.
Yuanwen, what is it?
Director Wang.
I really can't leave at a time like this.
Please talk to Director Liu.
Let me continue my undercover mission.
[What's the reason?]
I want to catch Spectre myself.
That's not your mission.
It's Skylark's.
[Besides,]
[your cover is basically exposed.]
If you go back,
it's going to cause a lot of trouble.
Director Wang, don't worry.
I have confidence and a plan.
I can fix everything.
I just need you to agree.
Hello, Director Wang. I'm Rong Yao.
Yuanwen just told me what he had in mind.
I think he has a point.
Skylark is in the group alone.
It's hard to work.
[Although her cover might keep her safe,]
I'm still worried.
Rong Yao, does that mean
you agree with him?
But of course in the end,
it's for the bureau to decide.
[Put Yuanwen on the phone.]
Okay.
Director Wang.
Yuanwen.
Director Liu is doing this
to protect you.
Also,
you ignored Director Liu
and called me directly.
It's a violation of discipline.
Yes.
I will reflect on it.
[You really should.]
[Since Rong Yao agrees with you,]
I'll talk to Director Liu about this.
Thank you, Director Wang.
Don't be too happy yet.
In the end,
if he doesn't allow you to go back,
you have to obey his order.
This is not negotiable.
Yes. I understand.
[Send all your ideas and plans to me.]
Wait for the news.
Director Liu can't find out
that you contacted me directly.
Yes, Director Wang.
You won't be so lucky every time.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Sir, what are your orders?
[What orders, my friend?]
[There's something]
[I want to discuss with you.]
Wait.
Don't tell me.
Is it about Yuanwen?
I guessed it right.
Does Yuanwen want to go back to Group K?
He couldn't convince me,
so he went to you?
Do you think Yuanwen would do that?
You trained him.
Would he do something
that is against the rules?
I don't think he would do it.
Director Wang.
I put Yuanwen undercover.
He's in danger.
It's right to bring him back.
I followed the protocol.
It's simple.
I hope Yuanwen
can go back and help Rong Yu.
[On one hand,]
[Rong Yu needs someone to help her.]
[Yuanwen is the best candidate.]
[We all know]
[about their relationship.]
[So...]
[I think you transferred Yuanwen]
[because you had no choice.]
I'll send you an operation plan soon
to help Yuanwen get back to Group K.
I'll send it to you in ten minutes.
[After you read it,]
[you can make your decision.]
Although Yuanwen doesn't know
that Skylark is Rong Yu yet,
after what they had been through,
the two of them
were able to work together
to finish such a difficult mission.
This whole thing
is a blessing itself to Yuanwen.
Director Wang.
We'll have to keep it a secret.
I know that.
It's very brutal.
But to complete the mission,
this is a sacrifice
[that we have to make.]
[Hello?]
[Mr. Ou, it's me.]
I'm going to Yungang next month.
You're finally coming.
You're welcome here.
When will you arrive?
You pick the date.
I want security.
I'm sure you know what I mean.
Of course.
Ruosheng, come over.
And bring Kexin with you.
There are two things.
Number one.
Ruosheng.
I want you to be my number two.
From now on,
you'll work with Glasses.
I'll work with Mr. Glasses?
Why?
Just say yes or no.
Godfather, I...
I don't like it.
He'll do it.
I didn't say I would do it.
It's a good thing.
You should thank my dad.
What if Mu Qing comes back?
Whether Mu Qing returns or not,
I have a new plan.
Wait, Godfather.
Mu Qing managed most of our business.
If he's not here,
I don't know enough to do it.
I'm here too.
Stop it.
We're talking about business.
You're not in the group, so stop it.
I may not be a part of it now,
but I can be one day.
Dad.
Teach me about business
so I can help you out.
If you want to help me,
then promise me the second thing.
Tell me.
Go back to France.
Why do you want me to go back?
It doesn't have to be France.
It can be any other country.
Don't stay in China.
Especially not in Yungang.
Why are you asking me to go now?
An important person is coming.
Godfather, is it Spectre?
Kexin.
It's not that I don't want you by my side.
But I'm about to make a huge deal.
The group's survival depends on it.
As you know,
Dakun, Congtou, and Guanyin
were arrested one after the other.
The group is a mess right now.
At this moment,
I can't risk having you here.
Ruosheng.
Get Kexin out of the country soon.
One more thing.
Don't let Glasses find out about it.
Yes.
It seems Godfather
doesn't trust Glasses anymore.
But I didn't think
he would make me his second-in-command.
Do you really think
my dad thinks you're good?
Well...
Either way,
there's nobody else.
Mu Qing isn't here either.
You haven't heard from him yet?
Enough about him.
Li Ruosheng.
Do me a favor.
What?
I don't want to leave.
I can't help you with that.
I've promised Godfather.
Why don't you understand?
I can help you.
All right, give me a break.
I'm taking you home now.
You should pack up.
We'll leave in two days.
What?
You want me to work with Li Ruosheng?
You don't want to?
Of course I do.
If you say so,
I'll definitely do it.
Although Li Ruosheng and I
had a misunderstanding,
after all,
we're all part of the same group.
We need to maintain peace to make money.
Besides, I'm much older than him.
Bowing to a young man
is not that embarrassing.
However,
you're not happy about it.
It's in the past.
It has been over a decade.
I know you well enough.
You're very cautious,
but you're narrow-minded.
You're vengeful.
You're not afraid of anyone other than me.
All right.
Put your issue with Li Ruosheng aside.
I have something more important
for you to do.
What is it?
Next month,
Spectre is coming to Yungang.
Organize it well.
There must not be any mistakes.
Show Spectre what our group is capable of.
This is between you and me.
Don't let anyone else know.
I understand.
Remember.
I want everything to be safe and steady.
During this time,
you and Ruosheng need to stop fighting.
I don't have any problems.
But if...
I'm just saying "if."
If Li Ruosheng goes against me,
what should I do?
That would mean he's against me.
I understand.
You may go.
Wait.
Find Mu Qing as soon as possible.
He knows too many secrets.
Yes, sir.
Take care of things at the shop.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Shut up and just leave.
Don't come back.
-I'm going.
-Hurry up.
["The Place Farthest Away" playing]
♫ Against the light ♫
♫ Your vague silhouette ♫
♫ I reach out with my hands ♫
♫ But my hug passes through you ♫
♫ Maybe this is an illusion ♫
♫ A sweet dream ♫
♫ Waiting for you ♫
♫ To notice it and wake me up ♫
♫ I wonder if getting close to you ♫
♫ One swirl will light up the stars ♫
♫ I wonder if someone
will tell you for me ♫
♫ At the place farthest away ♫
♫ Only then will the kites roam freely ♫
♫ If I gaze relentlessly ♫
♫ I wonder if there will be starlight ♫
♫ If the falling fireworks ♫
♫ Give me the sadness of being lonely ♫
♫ If your gaze gives me ♫
♫ A sense of direction ♫
♫ I'll give you an answer too ♫
♫ Looking at your turbulent silence ♫
♫ I really hope you can understand ♫
♫ So I remain extremely quiet and gentle ♫
♫ Waiting for you to kiss my forehead ♫
♫ It seems you're in front of me ♫
♫ Like the four seasons in my heart ♫
♫ Gentle and heart-wrenching ♫
♫ What can I say? ♫
♫ At the place farthest away ♫
♫ Only then will the kites roam freely ♫
♫ If I gaze relentlessly ♫
♫ I wonder if there will be starlight ♫
♫ Standing on your spot ♫
♫ Only then will I forget
the faraway place ♫
♫ Only your gaze ♫
♫ Can give me acknowledgment ♫
♫ Can give me an answer ♫