"Explore with the Note"
"Episode 2"
Uncle?
Uncle.
What are you doing here?
What kind of ship is this?
How many times have I told you?
Stay out of my business.
Why won't you listen to me?
Uncle.
It was Ning who told me...
...that you had a misadventure.
That's why I...
Comrade.
Rise and shine.
Young Comrade.
Hallucinating again?
What dreams did you have?
You have too much on your mind now,
and you're confused.
Look at me.
Whenever I feel stuck,
I'd chant.
All money go my home.
Hurry, get up.
Hurry up.
Here, this should bring your spirits back up.
I say, when we enter the tomb,
we will slowly unravel the mystery.
Got it?
You guys are already digging in
without waiting for us.
That's so rude.
Eat quickly.
We're almost at the shipwreck site.
These are freshly caught?
When it comes to seafood,
you need to enjoy it on the sea...
...while the fisherman
makes his catch of the day.
Spare your efforts.
We're going underwater later, so no drinking.
The location of the shipwreck
was pinpointed by your uncle.
Apparently, he has also located
the tomb chamber.
Later on,
we'll be counting on you.
You don't even believe me.
My uncle really didn't tell me anything.
I'm just an archaeology fan,
and I've done some reading on it.
Don't worry, though.
Since it's for my uncle,
I will definitely do my best.
Wine is my blood, beer is my tea.
Nothing beats some booze before a raid.
It gets sweeter with every gulp.
I got it from the fisherman.
Where did you swipe this?
What swipe?
I exchanged it with my sorghum wine.
That's what we call...
...cultural exchange of wines.
Not bad.
Have a taste, guys.
Give it to me.
Baldy, you can drink?
I say, deal.
I don't like your temper,
but I'm up for a round of drinking with you.
What's a feast without some booze?
-We're drinking pals.
-Yeah, yeah.
Come, come.
I'll get down to business.
The three of you are experts in this field.
Do you have any suggestions...
...for the expedition later?
Is the location confirmed?
It's confirmed.
The frogmen are cleaning up the rubble now.
All right, then.
For me, this is a potential jackpot.
I'm going to swim all my way in.
Any traps?
Even if there are,
they won't be too complicated.
Firstly, they're underwater.
There's the erosion and water pressure.
Second,
building a tomb underwater...
...is a big trap by itself.
In the past,
when technology wasn't that developed yet,
the tomb owner probably
didn't expect that future tomb raiders...
...would do their homework
underwater for long.
So, even if there are traps,
they won't be too complicated.
That's what we call...
...plain sailing.
Here, have some booze.
Here.
Where's Ning?
Sir. Everything's going as planned.
Soon comes the crucial step.
Keep your eyes on Wu Xie.
The Wus are tricky.
Don't let him...off-hook.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
Was Mr Zhang involved in any of our projects?
No.
What about him?
I have a feeling.
It's just a hunch that...
...something's off about him.
If he threatens the operation,
take him out.
Yes, sir.
Remember.
Your safety is important.
Ning.
You're my most valuable asset.
Okay, got it.
They said that the entrance tunnel
is very long.
A part of the structure has collapsed.
They're placing stilts for support now.
We'll go down once they're done.
"The sunken ship's anchor"
"The sunken ship's anchor is set."
"It must be huge."
"Head forward, everyone."
"The marking to the tomb's entrance,
left by my uncle when he came here."
"Come and take a look."
"My uncle was here,
and the entrance is here."
"Check your equipment, and go."
"What are you gawking here? Move!"
"Stop."
"The guy on the wall carvings,
his eyes are opening."
"Let's go."
"Come here."
"I saw something nearby."
"What's wrong?"
"I see a lot of hair."
"Impossible."
"Look down here."
"What the heck was that?"
"How would I know what that was?"
"Oxygen level: 20.9 percent"
Baldy, what in the world
is wrong with your hands?
What were you doing?
You almost made me vomit my gut out!
I might just throw my intestines up on you!
I had to do it.
If I didn't trigger that trap,
you'd be devoured by
that hairy creature, you know?
Mind your own business.
Stop fighting.
Let's go up.
Young Comrade, what is this place?
There aren't any coffins or caskets here.
This is probably one of the side chambers.
I'm home.
Check this out!
There are some footprints here.
Whose footprints?
Can this be Master Wu's?
This footprint seems new.
It's so tiny.
It's a child's, right?
He's no older than three years.
This isn't a playground.
What's a kid doing here?
Wax.
Yeah, it's wet all right.
Corpse wax?
A zombie.
Have you realized?
These footprints are heading outwards.
They're not heading in here.
This is a coffin for babies.
Was the kid the tomb owner's relative,
or a mere sacrifice?
He's a sacrifice.
There's a lot of good stuff in here.
Especially the stomach.
There are pearls inside, you know.
That's worth a fortune.
Where's the kid?
Baby.
Hey, baby.
Naughty little baby.
I'm going to find you.
Lower your voice.
They were sacrificed at such a young age.
You're disturbing him.
No need for crocodile tears, bozo.
Okay, I give up.
Let me see what's left here.
Wait.
This coffin...
...is different from the rest.
We'd better not open it.
We're not here to loot.
Look for the main chamber now.
Stop dilly-dallying.
This is damn creepy.
Why don't we strike first...
...and blast this open?
This urn was made in
the Yuan or Ming dynasty.
Destroying it would be a cultural loss.
We can't carry this heavy thing out anyway.
Is there another path?
What other paths do we have?
It's either this doorway...
...or the hole
which we came in from.
We can either step over this urn...
...or take a flight back to Beijing.
I'll treat you to dip-boil mutton,
roasted duck and pork stew.
Why are you afraid of a mere urn?
Move.
Why did you hit me?
It hurts.
I'm moving.
Let's go.
This urn sure looks like our tour guide.
Put a red cap and a flag on him,
and he'll say,
"Look this way!"
"Follow me!"
That's enough.
These pranks...
...are used to scare people.
What if he has a mind of his own?
That's very likely.
That's enough, you two.
Let's go.
Wait, such tunnels are usually...
...equipped with traps.
Let me do a check first.
If my uncle was here...
The door in front is ajar.
Someone must have been in there.
It probably wasn't my uncle.
If he did come here,
all the traps here...
...would have been disassembled...
...or triggered.
The way you tread around this place...
...can be consequential.
You sure you can do it, Young Comrade?
Follow me.
Okay.
Damn it, let go of him!
Are you okay?
Fatty!
Move!
Calm down!
Don't touch it!
Don't panic.
-Calm down, it's okay.
-Fatty, look!
Look behind you!
W-Wait a minute...
S-Something's really off here.
Why doesn't it hurt at all?
Yeah.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Fatty.
Does being shot by arrows feel this good?
I've never died before, I don't know.
You...!
There's not even a single drop of blood.
Yeah.
We're really all right.
Move.
Go.
Mr Zhang.
Did you catch it?
It's too fast, I can't keep up.
You two...
We're fine.
Where's Ning?
That lassie is a total crook.
She used us as shields.
She's damn ruthless.
I say, Baldy.
Your mistress is already inside.
Aren't you following suit?
Ning stepped on the trigger deliberately.
You!
Mutey Zhang.
You're here for a cameo?
You deceived us all along!
These are lotus arrows.
They're harmless.
So, the tomb's owner
set up all these traps...
...to scare us off?
I say, this tomb's owner...
...is as nutty as a fruitcake.
He's sick in the head.
He could've just killed us.
What's with all these gimmicks?
Ning triggered the trap on purpose.
It might seem that she wants us dead.
But, actually,
these are lotus arrows.
They're harmless.
Now, that's weird.
With her own ability,
she can definitely enter the tomb by herself.
Yet, she used all means to bring us here.
What's her motive?
She felt that this job's too easy,
and she doesn't need us anymore,
so she's butchering the horses
after riding it, see?
Don't tell me...
...it was my uncle...
...who told her about
the tomb's secrets.
Anyway, she's ditched us.
That means she wants to go alone...
...and do some secretive stuff.
She must know where the baubles are,
and she's having them all for herself.
I say, these foreign antique dealers...
...have no sense of mercy.
They'd kill anyone without batting an eyelid.
Okay, stop dilly-dallying here.
Let's give chase.
Go to the chamber on the left.
Mutey, you can't just show up here...
...and give us blind instructions.
Can you trust a little zombie?
He must be leading us to the zombie hideout.
What will become of us?
We're going to be zombie food.
Just listen to Poker Face.
Go to the left chamber.
Entering the lion's den, aren't you?
Okay, as you command.
Hold on.
Bring the oxygen tanks here.
In case anything happens.
Don't do that again.
We've been circling around for ten minutes.
Where is it?
Don't tell me...
...we're on the wrong path.
Ning has gotten rid of the urn.
Impossible.
She clearly went into the chamber.
Unless there's another path.
Didn't we just pass by here?
The side chamber we were in
didn't have any pillars.
He's right.
The baby coffin at the corner...
...has also disappeared.
The funerary items are also
arranged differently.
And...
...look up here.
How could this be?
Did we go the wrong way...
...or enter the wrong passage?
But, there has only been...
...one single path.
Stop searching.
There is only one single path here.
If we're really in the wrong path,
I'll take a zombie as my wife.
Hasn't your uncle told you...
...about the passageways
in this tomb?
Bro.
Have you been...
...to this tomb before?
I don't know.
You don't even know if you've been here?
Are you getting Alzheimer's?
Maybe I have.
Some of these places seem familiar.
But, I can't recall them.
I say, Young Comrade.
Underwater tombs are huge finds.
Hasn't your uncle told you about it?
Think about it again.
My uncle...
...did tell me a lot of stories.
But, I don't know which of them is true...
...or fake.
Okay.
I'm going to share my part, then.
Before this, I've asked Ning...
...how Master Wu knew about
this underwater tomb.
Ning said...
...that there was a gang of
tomb raiders...
...who detonated a shipwreck
in the Xisha Islands.
They found a tomb there.
The tomb's cover...
...was almost
completely destroyed.
The outer wall of the tomb...
...was also damaged in some parts.
But, they just couldn't find...
...a good way to enter the tomb.
No.
What do you mean it's almost destroyed?
You saw it as well.
There wasn't any severe damage.
It was Ning who said that.
I'm just quoting her.
I'm sharing my story here.
Are you listening?
Really.
Where was I?
Right.
There was also a team of archaeologists...
...who knew about this.
After the tomb raiders left,
this team of archaeologists...
...conducted a secret
expedition here.
The tomb down here is sealed.
The outer wall is waterproof.
It's sealed with plaster.
-It's likely that there's air.
-That's great!
Professor Zhang.
You're the expert here.
Take it from here.
I can only see
the two characters in the middle.
Interior ministry.
The interior ministry
is a palace department...
...that monitors
the production of royal items.
This box...
...may be from the Ming dynasty.
There should be something
wrapped inside this cloth.
If we want to enter the tomb,
we need to push the walls open.
But, we're underwater.
Once the walls are open,
the water will pour in.
No one will know what will happen...
...to this tomb by then.
Besides, this is archaeology here.
Protecting relics is the main priority.
You can't follow my suit...
...and blast everything in the way.
The only thing that's certain...
...is that the water inlet
holds the key.
Someone had suggested...
...to dig a tunnel
underneath the tomb.
But, after evaluating the geology here,
they found out that the soil here...
...isn't native to this area.
Instead, it's vitrified clay
from the Guan kilns in Fujian.
The sealed area is as wide as...
...7000 square meters.
If we calculate with this ratio,
they couldn't reach the bottom
with the technology back then.
But, they still dug on.
And they've dug 15 meters deep.
They still couldn't reach the bottom.
They couldn't estimate...
...how much longer...
...or how much deeper
they had to dig.
Coupled with some other external factors,
the whole team left.
The area was then buried by sand again.
The funniest thing was...
...that their records back then...
...were all gone.
A few years later,
another team of archaeologists came.
Your uncle was part of it.
This is too preposterous.
How could he go out by himself?
He didn't even tell us at all.
Exactly.
What if something happens?
Look over there!
On top of that rock!
-Where?
I see him!
The snake-browed copper fish?
Yeah.
Ning said...
...your uncle felt...
...that the team member
who died accidentally...
...must have gone down
to the tomb.
The copper fish inside his hand
was his proof.
So, they searched around the vicinity...
...and found 40 gigantic
stone anchors.
We saw those anchors...
...on our way here.
That's right.
There's a tomb inside a shipwreck...
...right under our very feet
in this sea.
-Really?
-A tomb inside a shipwreck?
It means the tomb was built on a ship.
Then, they found a valley
or trench under the sea.
They chiseled a hole in the ship
and made it sink down.
After covering it with soil,
the sunken ship becomes a tomb.
It's actually the same as tombs on land.
It's just that it's under the sea now.
This place must have been
a sea valley in the past.
It was then filled up with soil.
Oh, God.
That's a gargantuan task.
Is that possible in ancient times?
-Yeah.
-Wen Jin.
We've finally found it.
What happened next?
After that,
your uncle made a dive down.
Then, the whole team backed off midway again.
Another hanging ending.
Until recently, your uncle...
...approached Ning's company...
...to enter the tomb again.
Let me reiterate this.
It was Ning who told me all these.
I don't know if it's true or not.
But, I think it sounds pretty rational.
She doesn't need...
...to make up any stories
and fool me.
Unless...
Unless my uncle lied to her.
Yes.
I remember when I was little,
my uncle did leave home...
...for a long time.
When he came back, he was tanned and scrawny.
He also looked fatigued.
But, I still remember...
...that he and Grandpa...
...talked the whole day away
inside a room.
Grandpa even scolded him.
I believe...
...that my uncle was here before.
But, this still doesn't explain...
...why the layout here
has suddenly changed.
Going off tangent like me, yeah?
Okay.
I've been here before.