(All characters, organizations, places, cases, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Episode 6)
(Doctor Detective)
Who is it?
Mr. Huh?
Don't you want to know...
about the site in Namil?
Your house is a mess.
Cut to the chase. Abut the site in Namil.
Are you going to keep digging into this case?
Why did you come that day?
Are you following me?
What a rude way of thanking me.
This is the cellphone of the man who tried to kill you.
Why are you giving me this?
The man who tried to kill you...
is trying to kill me too.
It's Executive Director Moh Sung Kuk of TL Oshem.
This is all his scheme.
From fabricating the site, controlling the media,
and even attempting to kill you.
I need to turn the tables in order to live.
That goes for you too.
Are you saying my life depends on you?
UDC should reveal that the dormitory was fabricated.
I'll make the person involved confess that he was responsible.
I'm checking the surveillance cameras...
to find TL Oshem cars going to the dormitory in Namil.
I'll find something soon.
How pitiful of TL.
You're revealing the group's critical secrets...
just to win an internal power struggle?
All I have to do is to announce that it isn't the group's policy.
That Oshem was solely responsible for it.
Choi Tae Young. Is that what the chairman wants?
I know it isn't.
This is your own doing.
The chairman trusts Executive Director Moh,
and you're just trying to come between them.
I'll pretend I didn't hear anything.
We'll continue with the investigation.
Don't even think about using UDC.
Joong Eun, if you survived once,
you should be thankful.
I thought I'd died already three years ago.
Consider it as paying back a debt and do as I say.
And after that?
Open it to the media. And bring down Mr. Moh.
You'll get the justice that you want so much.
And I'll...
regain the chairman's trust.
And also,
leave UDC and live quietly.
Seo Rin should...
grow up with her mom.
Are you...
taking good care of Seo Rin?
Why?
She called me earlier.
But we got disconnected right away.
She's doing well.
Since she's a kid, of course, she'll miss her mom.
I'll take that as a yes and go now. I'll be in touch.
Take care of yourself. I beg of you.
Seo Rin needs you.
(Doctor Detective)
- Ms. Gong. - You startled me.
(Chief Gong Il Sun)
So... In exchange for information, he wants you to make an issue?
Choi Tae Young wants to take down Moh Sung Kuk.
We should thank him if he wants to be a whistle-blower.
He may be using us.
Darn it. We've come too far anyway.
The higher-ups refused everything today.
Let's do it.
You can't go to the site anymore, okay?
Okay.
How much did she drink?
Four bottles.
I guess it didn't go well with her superiors.
She stinks!
She shouldn't have drunk on an empty stomach.
It's not good for her stomach.
We should get hangover soup for lunch.
Should I have it delivered?
Let's eat out.
Ms. Doh is taking the morning off.
Is she sick?
Have you heard from Mr. Huh?
It's not normal for him to come on time.
No. Something's going on.
A fling.
A what?
A fling and not a fight?
Sure, it's a fling.
They left the office together, yesterday.
In Mr. Huh's car.
It feels like you're mine. It feels like you're not...
Whatever. Let's just get coffee.
(Namil Police Station)
(Medical Certificate)
It's Kim Do Hyeong's medical certificate.
He has diabetes and needs insulin treatment.
I'd like to request an official visit as a doctor.
Sir, could you come here a moment?
What is it?
Visits aren't allowed to the UDC.
- Why not? - You know why.
That means other doctors are allowed, right?
Are you going to take responsibility if he faints from low blood sugar?
Stop making a fuss!
I'll allow any other qualified doctor.
Now leave.
We're busy, so please leave.
Get going, already!
You have to leave clear proof...
that you left.
We need a recording of you leaving on the surveillance camera,
and I'll show up right then.
Sir!
I'm the other qualified doctor,
Huh Min Ki.
This is my medical license.
Are you kidding me?
You're both from UDC, aren't you?
Yes. We're from UDC.
First, I'm not kidding.
DKA.
There's a thing called diabetic ketoacidosis.
It's an acute complication that can occur when a type 1 diabetic...
fails to regulate sugar levels.
The patient could die within 48 hours.
Kim Do Hyeong is a type 1 diabetic.
He's under an emergency interrogation.
We need some information before we move him.
- Come another time. - I'm sure...
they're going to start lying about some internal affairs.
Then...
we have to bring up the Human Rights Commission.
Is this Mr. Park of the Human Rights Commission?
Yes, sir. Are you on your way?
Yes. Reporter Byun is accompanying you?
That's all right.
These people are civil servants, so they don't have portrait rights.
I believe people have the right to know.
They should know that the police are completely inconsiderate...
- of human rights... - All right, all right!
Quit it with the act and just leave the medicine.
Type 1 diabetics need insulin injections, not medicine.
You need to be trained to use the syringe.
Would you like to be trained?
However, it will be a violation of medical law.
Do you even know what insulin is?
Hey, doctor!
Go ahead.
Yes, all right.
Good job.
Make sure to reassure Do Hyeong as soon as you get in.
If he has mercury poisoning, he could suffer from anxiety,
paranoia, or show aggressiveness.
If he shows hypersensitivity,
be sure to put me on the phone.
You can tell them I'm his usual doctor.
Go away.
Go away!
I need to persuade the patient,
so let him talk to his usual doctor.
When he calms down, drag it as long as you can.
Remember that it's our only chance.
It's all right.
- Do Hyeong. - Who is this?
It's me, Doh Joong Eun. Calm down, Do Hyeong.
Ms. Doh!
I didn't do it.
I didn't do it, Ms. Doh.
I know.
You didn't do anything wrong.
You went to save Ha Rang, but your hand shook.
That's right, Ms. Doh.
Now, don't talk and just listen.
It's because you're sick. You were poisoned.
We're going to prove that.
You can trust the doctor in front of you.
Hang in there, just a bit.
I brought long-acting insulin.
You've never tried this before, so I'll teach you.
Okay.
- Here. Hold this in your hand... - Okay.
and then...
you hold your belly...
What are you doing? Don't touch him.
He needs to be trained for the new prescription.
How am I supposed to treat him without touching him?
Just finish it up and stand back.
You have to change the syringe...
with every use.
Okay.
For the dosage,
you can adjust it with the dial on the end.
- I didn't do it. - I know.
I'll do a final check-up.
Just a second...
Do Hyeong, push me back hard. Hurry!
What are you doing?
Hey! Stop that!
- All right, kid! - I didn't do it!
Could you run a blood test for the mercury, one last time?
It's Kim Do Hyeong's.
What?
Mr. Huh! You're amazing!
How did you do it?
It's a secret.
Let's keep it a secret until the results come out.
- Good job. - You, too.
Let's get Do Hyeong out of there.
Ms. Gong. Ms. Gong!
Look what I found.
"Under the conditions set by the president,"
"the head of the Undiagnosed Disease Center..."
"can open an evaluation committee for the epidemiological survey..."
"on any substance or disease..."
"that is considered to be of harm to the citizens."
The Epidemiological Survey Evaluation Committee.
It means there's a way.
- Do we have any kimchi? - Why...
would you mention kimchi now?
I know you enjoy having cup noodles,
so I bought some, just in case.
What a smart guy!
Ms. Byun,
don't you think I already brought up the evaluation committee?
The conditions...
set by the president...
needs consent from the head of the corporation.
And the head says he'll give permission...
only if we find proof that it's poisoning.
It's just nonsense.
How are we supposed to find it?
They got Kim Do Hyeong locked up and won't even allow visits.
Joong Eun.
Did you hear anything?
Darn it, of course not.
It hasn't even been a few days.
Ms. Gong, ma'am. Cheer up!
I should cheer up, but darn it!
Everyone's so afraid of TL!
What if...
we have the evidence?
Come on!
I'm sure Ms. Suk is almost done with the analysis.
What analysis?
5, 4,
3,
2, 1!
Kim Do Hyeong's blood test results are out!
The mercury is 60 times the average level.
Do Hyeong didn't commit murder.
His hand was shaking because of mercury poisoning.
But how did you collect his blood?
We were able to visit him using his medical condition...
and collected his blood in secret.
I did it.
And you? This will be useless if you got involved.
I've taken care of that.
It's fine now.
Good job. 60 times?
Great! Gather around.
We got the evidence for the mercury,
and we proved that it wasn't murder.
Now, we're taking this to the evaluation committee.
It's 60 times the amount of mercury in his blood.
We have to find out...
how in the world the mercury got in his system.
Did he breathe it in while working...
or did the heavy metal leak into the dorm?
Let's find that out. How he was exposed.
All right.
They're going to begin a meeting with the evaluation committee.
The Occupational Safety Authority gave their consent.
UDC will come to reinvestigate.
Should we place more guards at the site?
Call in a guard company.
Make sure to keep UDC from getting in.
The reason will be trespassing.
Call a company that's not part of TL Metro.
"Temporary restraining order against the epidemiological survey"?
What is this? Are you kidding me?
We're here by the law and have the right to...
In position, everyone.
Guys, there are no legal grounds for them to stop us.
Let's go.
You guys.
If you lay even just a finger on us, we'll sue you all.
Is that clear?
Il Sun, are we really going in though?
- Hey! - Stop her.
- Who do you think you are? - Get out of our way!
- What do you think you're doing? - Hey!
- Gosh! - Let go!
Gosh, Moh Sung Kuk is going all out to stop us.
He sent a bunch of guys to keep us out.
Hello? Hey, are you listening?
Yes.
It is clearly against the law.
Well, the thing is...
Hey, hasn't Choi Tae Young made a move yet?
You said you two struck a deal.
For now, let's try to find a solution on our own.
Contact Hanil SD's labor union and tell them to cause a stir.
Got it, okay.
Darn it.
We're humans too, and we want to be respected as such!
- We want to be respected! - We want to be respected!
The company is responsible for occupational accidents!
- The company is responsible! - The company is responsible!
Launch an epidemiological investigation!
- Launch an investigation! - Launch an investigation!
The company is responsible for occupational accidents!
- The company is responsible! - The company is responsible!
Launch an epidemiological investigation!
- Launch an investigation! - Launch an investigation!
We're humans too!
- We're humans too! - We're humans too!
The company must right the wrongs!
- Right the wrongs! - Right the wrongs!
The company must take responsibility!
- Take responsibility! - Take responsibility!
Launch an investigation.
- Launch an investigation! - Launch an investigation!
We're humans too!
(Who Should Take Responsibility for the Bui Station Accident?)
(Labor Union Blames the Company)
- Right the wrongs! - Right the wrongs!
- Take responsibility! - The drum and the drumsticks.
They look familiar.
Where did I see them?
- Launch an investigation! - Launch an investigation!
We're...
- We're humans too. - The screen door worker's death.
- We want to be respected! - Was it really murder?
- We want to be respected! - Or was it death by negligence...
caused by heavy metal poisoning?
Now, many are mentioning the role of...
the Epidemiological Survey Evaluation Committee,
which consists of occupational health and safety experts.
I heard TL is refusing to acknowledge the committee's role.
Correct. In fact, what TL is insisting lacks legal grounds.
When it comes to epidemiological investigations,
the committee has the most decision-making authority...
like the Supreme Court does for legal matters.
The Epidemiological Survey Evaluation Committee's role...
is to investigate and determine...
whether the company or employer is responsible in any way...
for the specific disease or accident in question.
Led by the chairperson,
the members follow the committee's majority decisions...
Joong Eun.
Ms. Doh isn't at her desk.
She stepped out saying she has to check something.
I think she's on the second floor.
Was the labor union's protest your idea?
That was clever.
Keep up the good work.
I'll correspond and take Moh Sung Kuk down.
But we need more concrete evidence to take it to the next step.
The Namil site will be empty today because of the labor union.
Just keep it in mind.
(TL Oshem Personnel Restructuring, Including new executive director)
Come to the second floor by yourself.
(Doh Joong Eun)
I'm here. What's going on?
Come with me to the site in Namil tonight.
You want to go to that abandoned building at night?
There will be fewer people standing guard at night.
I found a few entrances we can use.
Well, it's...
You said you'd help me.
The thing is,
we'll be doomed if we're caught.
"An eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth."
Isn't that your motto?
You wouldn't dig without knowing whether we'll find something.
Is there something?
Yes, there is.
My gosh.
Where have you been?
I went upstairs to get this.
Let me warn you once again. Don't go anywhere.
Whether it's the site in Namil or TL Metro,
don't go anywhere near TL. Do you understand?
- Yes. - Tell me that you won't go.
I won't go anywhere near TL.
How did you know there'd be fewer security guards tonight?
We just need to distract those two somehow.
How can we distract them?
Freeze.
Both of you, crawl out through the hole. Right now.
Out, now!
Gosh, Jin Hak!
Mr. Ha.
Ms. Doh, you need to leave at once.
If you get caught, all of us will have to leave UDC.
We won't get caught.
Right. What?
Gosh. Hey, Min Ki.
I'll tell Chief Gong on you.
You, traitor. You're human trash.
What's your problem now?
If you persuade her and get her out of there,
I won't tell Chief Gong anything.
Stop fooling around and get out of there, please.
Get lost.
Goodness, what's with you two?
What are you going to do if you get caught?
We won't. We'll sneak in through the back.
Wait, Min Ki. What about me?
Since you came all the way here, we're now in the same boat.
Stand guard here. If anything happens,
call me right away. Got it?
I'm sorry, Chief Gong.
Darn it. There's a mosquito here.
Be careful.
Be careful. This is heavy.
I served as a medical officer in the Marine Corps.
I had to run tests in the dark,
so this is...
I'm so used to this. Even in pitch-black darkness...
What? What are you doing?
Couldn't you open it quietly? I mean, we snuck in here.
What's this? This thing.
It's a chair.
Let me tell you something though. No one can catch ghosts.
I have a lot of experience working in places...
- like cemeteries. - Over there.
Why? What is it? What's over there?
Hold on.
It must be empty inside.
I think these doors are welded together though.
We should break them.
Didn't you hear me? I think they're welded together.
- Right, exactly. - What are you going to do?
- Step back. - What? Why?
I didn't know you were so... My gosh!
Wait, hold on. Just a second.
I'll do it. Let me do this, okay?
So this is where the mercury spills happened, right?
I got this.
Have a look.
Hurry! We need to open this darn door!
Someone's here. Be quick. You have to hurry!
Darn it. All right, let's decide what to do.
We should have enough time to run to the hole if we leave now,
but we'll be stuck here if we lock the doors. It's do or die.
Are you sure we can find evidence in this room?
Okay.
Then we should...
- They're over there. - Get them!
Let me do it. I can do it quickly. I got it.
- Hurry! - Stop them.
Move. Step aside.
- Open this! - Hurry!
Hurry up!
- Open this! - Gosh, my back...
- Hey, open this door! - Hang on.
Gosh, I think I broke my back.
What is this?
I'm at the basement of the abandoned building at Namil site.
Mercury is flowing out of the pile of fluorescent lights.
Don't move!
This place is full of heavy metal. Don't come inside!
(Epidemiological Survey Evaluation Committee)
These are the results from our analysis.
You found mercury on the second floor of the abandoned building.
The blood from a laborer showed a high mercury rate.
But how are those two results connected?
What is the exact cause of the exposure?
(Epidemiological Survey Evaluation Committee)
Well...
That's...
You're lacking logic in your claims.
Since we don't have time, let's proceed with the voting.
Wait a second.
A UDC researcher is bringing...
a new analysis result right now.
- I have the results. - Let's go.
(Undiagnosed Disease Center)
Let's get going.
- Please wait a little longer... - Don't try to stall time.
The decision has been made already.
- Let's start the voting. - Let's begin.
Goodness, why is there so much traffic?
Come on, move it! Why are they such slow drivers?
(Epidemiological Survey Evaluation Committee)
This is so frustrating.
Isn't there another way?
What can I do? I can't run a red light.
Darn it. We're getting stopped at every light.
- I found it. - Found what?
How they were exposed to mercury.
Ha Rang and Do Hyeong were both in a rock band in high school.
Stuck between a magazine at the dormitory,
I found a pair of drumsticks.
It means he played the drums until recently.
Then they must've had a place where they practiced.
The noise level of drums is more than 100dB.
It must be a closed space, where the sound can't be heard.
Somewhere in a basement.
Have you all received your voting papers?
Let's begin the voting now.
Ms. Gong.
We made it.
We found how they were exposed.
The proof...
is right here.
Hello.
(Korean Elevator Safety Agency)
According to our analysis,
the mercury rate was 20 times higher than the standard rate.
The victim was poisoned by mercury at this place.
Did someone order him to go in there?
It's his fault for going inside an abandoned building.
Yes, it's his fault.
But building a temporary dorm at a place with potential risk...
and not taking any safety measures whatsoever...
is the responsibility of the company.
That doesn't make sense.
How much do we have to take responsibility for?
Goodness, this is just because of their hobby.
Do you take us for fools?
Do you think we're some volunteer group?
Please quiet down. Let's have some order.
The analysis result...
for cross-checking is the same.
Then let's begin the vote.
(Chairman of Committee, Park Hyun Sung)
I'll announce the result of the votes.
Those who agree, five votes.
Those who disagree, four votes.
It has been voted as work-related.
The decision's been made that TL Metro is responsible.
What is this? This is nothing but unfair treatment of companies.
Will you let everyone apply for industrial accidents now?
- This is ridiculous. - All right, then.
Great job, everyone. Thank you.
Chairman Park, thank you.
Let's wrap it up now.
Come over here. What if you got poisoned?
I wasn't even in there for 10 minutes.
So take this vitamin C shot for 10 minutes.
You need to remove any mercury residue.
It'll be over in a second.
I'll be gentle.
"J"? Joong Eun?
How cute.
You're all done.
I have a secret to tell you.
I'll apply for an industrial accident for this.
You'll testify as a colleague, right?
Before that, I'll take a vitamin C shot too.
Come on.
Here. Great job, everybody.
- Good job! - Good job!
TL Metro will go to trial now.
We'll see if they're charged as the main contractors.
The prosecution has to crack down on the biotech complex.
I doubt it. Everyone's making a fuss that it's the new future.
You didn't find them?
They're giving each other vitamin shots. So intimately.
Hey. Don't they seem awfully close lately?
Yes, those two are creating some great synergy.
Even when someone fell down and almost died,
- they didn't even blink an eye... - What who?
- Well... - That looks delicious.
I'll move in at the end of the month.
Okay.
What are you doing? She's a team leader.
He's a team leader too.
- It's fine. - Seriously.
- Ladies first. Take a seat. - Thank you.
Since we're all here, let's toast officially.
- Let me get some food first. - Let's toast first.
- Okay. - Let's keep up the good work.
- Good job. - Good job.
(CEO, Choi Tae Young)
The evaluation committee meeting has concluded.
It's been determined as mercury poisoning.
Tae Young, things have turned out just the way you wanted.
Mr. Moh won't get off easy this time.
Let's report this to the chairman.
Okay.
You did a great job.
(Confidentiality Agreement)
You just need to tell the truth until the end.
Do not ever give up.
(TL Oshem Personnel Restructuring, Including new executive director)
Is the chairman inside?
He's in the garden.
He's with a guest.
This will only take a second.
You've done so well,
it makes me very happy.
How did you manage to do that?
Is that so?
No, it's all right.
They'll have to pay...
if they did something wrong.
All right, sir. Don't you worry.
All parents are soft for their children.
Yes, sir.
I see your son has a peculiar taste.
(Confidentiality Agreement)
(Park Dong Seok)
Will the industrial waste...
be fine permanently?
We checked the soil at the site in Namil,
and there aren't any leaks or exposures.
If it's fine after 50 years,
you can say it's permanent.
All right.
I spoke with the Arizona branch,
and they're very pleased with the automobile plant.
There won't be any more pressure regarding waste from the US army.
You will only need to supervise what you're in charge of.
It's a win-win situation.
Then...
I guess we can just focus on starting the biotech complex.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Park of TL Construction, who is being accused of embezzlement,
handed himself into the hands of the prosecutors this morning.
Mr. Park admitted to all charges...
and said he would cooperate with the investigation.
They're leaving out the biotech complex...
and making it a separate case.
Along with embezzlement,
the investigation on Mr. Park...
Tae Young...
are you really going to...
keep this fight up against Moh Sung Kuk?
It has been revealed that they had...
illegally thrown away wastes such as fluorescent lamps...
- at the site at Namil. - Gosh...
Gosh!
It's receiving so much attention,
but they're completely leaving out the biotech complex!
Well, we expected TL to play the media.
Cheer up.
The world is slowly changing.
It's not like it's anything new to us.
Cheer up.
Everyone, look!
Ms. Doh got her official permission. Congratulations!
She's being transferred?
"Research Team Leader Doh Joong Eun".
Ms. Gong, may I see you?
Congratulations.
(Undiagnosed Disease Center)
Hey, why are you so serious?
Ms. Gong, I have a favor to ask.
Please don't tell our team members about my relationship with TL.
I think it's the right thing.
Sure, all right.
Hey. Where are you going?
(Kim Do Hyeong)
Hello.
Thank you.
Do you know what time it is?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Why are you late?
My other part-time job ran late.
This won't ever happen again. I'm sorry.
Mr. Moh, we've taken good care of it.
We got a waste exporter who works with China,
so there's no need to worry.
Go ahead!
Good job, Mr. Jung.
(TL Medical Center)
There was an uproar at the Planning and Strategy Team.
Leave him to be.
That's it, sir.
And you have mail, sir.
It's only from the people on the list.
No need for this.
(Choi Seo Rin)
What's this?
Let me see...
(Choi Seo Rin)
What's this?
(An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.)
(You'll suffer the same!)
Mr. Kwon.
Where did you get this?
I'll find out immediately, sir.
(An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.)
(Delete history)
(Delete)
(Initializing)
How's the biotech complex coming along?
Construction-wise, are there no more problems?
I heard there's a reporter who's digging...
into the case involving Director Park.
Correct.
Oshem is taking care of it though.
Let's move on to the next item on the agenda.
The Planning and Strategy Team...
will deal with the media head-on.
Right. I heard all the media outlets are being cooperative,
so please don't worry.
We should pressure UDC more.
Next item on the agenda.
Our sales numbers dropped by over 10 percent last year...
after Maomi's expansion into the Indian market.
Let's take advantage of the stable exchange rates...
and try to improve our market share...
Mr. Choi.
I guess you don't know how Planning and Strategy is run.
We're not sitting here to cater to your personal interests.
Let's decide what to do regarding the previous item.
I think we need to be tougher on UDC.
- Agreed. - Definitely, teach them a lesson.
Mr. Kang.
Are you Mr. Moh's minion?
Watch what you say!
I wanted to be respectful to you at this meeting, but I can't.
Are we holding this meeting to carry out Mr. Moh's orders?
Are we here to only talk about Oshem?
You all made it this far because you knew who to curry favor with.
Now, if you can't even do that,
it's time for you to be let go.
Listen up.
I called this meeting, not Mr. Moh.
So all you have to do is listen to me...
and do as I say.
To compete with Maomi, we're going to drop our prices...
starting with the SL-5 series.
Let's make sure our prices are lower than Maomi's.
Well, people are already criticizing the major corporations...
for underpaying their outsourcing service providers.
If we go this route,
we'll be criticized severely given the current situation.
Mr. Choi.
Is this the Ministry of Labor or the Human Rights Committee?
Replace the vendors that can't lower their prices.
And Oshem will handle the media.
Do I need to tell you how?
How could he decide to lower our prices...
without even seeking the lab's confirmation?
He's lost his mind.
He obviously feels cornered.
How dare he call me a minion?
As for the price reduction strategy,
there's an 80-percent chance that it'll fail.
He should clearly give up, but he kept on pushing for it.
Don't be so upset.
You got half of the job done by mentioning UDC.
Good work today.
(Doh Joong Eun)
Oh, dear.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Ms. Doh, we must seize your property for not complying with the order...
to compensate the other party for the damages.
Oh, my. Look at you, Seo Rin.
You can draw so well.
Seo Rin.
Can you write your name?
Write, "Choi Seo Rin".
Here, right here.
(Choi Seo Rin)
Choi...
Seo Rin.
(Choi Seo Rin)
And a heart.
Seo Rin.
You wrote this, right?
Who is it for?
I don't know.
(Choi Seo Rin)
(n-Hexane)
(To Mom)
(Choi Seo Rin)
"That's right. I'm a yellow butterfly."
- "The yellow butterfly..." - How did it go?
Don't worry, sir. I made sure it'll remain strictly confidential.
Good. No one can find out about it, okay?
Yes, sir. Well understood.
As for Seo Rin's daycare, I told the teacher she'll take a week off.
- The hotel's been booked too, sir. - Okay, great.
Also...
(Choi Seo Rin)
What did you say Joong Eun is up to these days?
Ms. Doh, hurry.
There are so many patients in the waiting room now.
Okay, I'll be right there.
UDC?
Is that so?
(Choi Seo Rin)
- Dig more into it. - I will, sir.
And call Mr. Moh for me.
Yes, sir.
- What's happening? - Due to the mercury poisoning case,
we're now known for correctly diagnosing occupational diseases.
When can we be seen by the doctor?
I'm sorry. Please wait just a little longer.
(One dollar)
I'd like to settle up.
Hye Mi.
Aren't you Park Hye Mi?
Ma'am.
I live in this neighborhood.
It's so nice to run into you.
How have you been?
I've been doing all right.
You still paint, right?
- Thank you, sir. - Thanks for your hard work.
I'll be off, then.
I don't want to see you wasting your talent.
I asked to see you because I wanted to have a talk with you.
I see.
I know you haven't been preparing to apply for art schools,
but you're in 11th grade now,
so I think you'll get in with just a little bit of effort.
Thank you for thinking so highly of me.
Hye Mi, I'll help you.
You should tell your parents.
Shall I speak with your parents in person?
Sure.
Eat up.
Thanks for the food.
Is there something you want to say to me?
No.
- Here you go. - Thanks.
Hey, I told you to come quickly. You little...
Get in.
Why are you so late?
Darn it.
(An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.)
(You'll suffer the same!)
(Funeral Arrangements and Data on the Late Mun Song Myeon)
We all remember the vigorous speech of this man...
from 30 years ago.
The ideal society I have in mind is people living in unity,
and where everyone doesn't worry about food, clothing,
and other things like that.
Where people don't commit dirty acts,
and a world where everyone can live their daily lives happily.
To him, there was a heartbreaking death of one man.
Last July 2, at Yeoeuido St. Mary's Hospital,
a 15-year-old laborer died of mercury poisoning.
The name of the boy who died at 15 from mercury poisoning...
was Mun Song Myeon.
He always said he wanted to visit his home in the countryside.
That's what lingers in my head the most.
He said he couldn't wait to go home.
Born from parents who farmed in the countryside,
he was the third son out of six siblings,
and he was a sincere and kind child.
The reason he started working at a factory when he was 15...
was because of his high school tuition.
It was a company that made mercury thermometers.
When he was working,
he didn't have any idea that something was wrong.
He was the tallest one.
He was taller and healthier than friends his age,
and about a month after he started working at the factory,
he started to suffer from an unknown pain.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
- My back hurts, and I can't sleep. - Your back?
The university hospital couldn't identify his disease,
and his body felt numb and sore.
He couldn't even eat properly. The pain was so severe...
that even his teeth started shaking and falling out.
After being hospitalized for two months,
his disease was identified as mercury poisoning.
The company ordered him to inject mercury inside a closed space...
without any safety equipment.
As a result, he suffered from acute mercury poisoning.
But his company...
refused to accept it as an industrial accident,
claiming it was due to pesticides from the countryside.
After this case was covered by the media,
it was finally accepted as an industrial accident...
(Joint Memorial Service for the late Mun Song Myeon)
(June 30, 2019)
I'd like to thank everyone...
who came here, in remembrance of Song Myeon.
But 12 days after it was accepted as an industrial accident,
he passed away without even leaving a will.
It's already been more than 30 years.
But nothing has changed.
I really hope there won't be a second Song Myeon...
and that no one gets hurt or dies.
That's my biggest wish.
Mun Song Myeon is asking from 30 years ago.
"What has changed?"
(The late Mun Song Myeon)
(Doctor Detective)
Oh, no!
What is that?
Stop! No, please!
Who are you?
Me? A doctor.
If it weren't for you, he could've been hurt badly.
The police want us to investigate?
His girlfriend secretly fed him a pesticide.
Ma'am, I really didn't kill Jin Sung.
Please, you have to believe me!
What am I missing?
Is it an industrial accident or not?
Is it, or is it not?
Mr. Huh.
Let's try that again.
I'll carry it with me...
and take care of it.
Peace.
I was thoughtless.
I won't cause trouble for TL ever again.
Like you asked, I made some changes to UDC.
What have you done to UDC?
Do you know how many innocent people got hurt or died?
One day,
you'll be brought to justice.