♪Mother♪
♪I've grown up♪
♪I no longer crave to be surrounded♪
♪No longer need♪
♪So many smiles♪
♪No longer fear broken trust♪
♪Mother, I've grown up♪
♪No longer try♪
♪To fill every void♪
♪No longer saddened♪
♪By all the goodbyes♪
♪No longer blame♪
♪Love that led nowhere♪
=HER=
What are you doing?
Come down, hurry.
Don't break it.
Look, this one's for sale.
This one, yes.
I'll sell that one to buy this one.
No, no. Cheaper?
Don't haggle.
Deal.
You need money fast?
It's for a good thing.
=Episode 17=
What are you thinking?
You're broke,
and you still won't take
half a million dollars?
The compensation should be
over a hundred million yuan.
Half a million dollars
is too little.
Would you accept that?
That number is just hypothetical.
With Putai Group's power,
it isn't something
you can take down
just by digging up a few rats.
Besides,
look at those gamblers.
No one wants to fight a lawsuit
for a bunch of gamblers.
Any money we win for them
would be wasted.
Exactly, so not a single cent
of the money I win will go to them.
What do you mean?
Ideally, here's how it would go.
I'd win the full compensation.
If it's 500,000 dollars each,
that's a huge sum.
Then I'd work
with the gambling rehab center
at the police station
to set up a special fund.
We'd open
a dedicated bank account
and deposit
all the compensation into it,
and everyone involved
would have to go through rehab first.
Only after they
quit gambling
can they claim
their compensation with proof.
How great that'd be.
Impressive.
No wonder you were a top student.
But I have a suggestion.
With just this data,
how do you file a case?
You'll need at least
ten times the number of plaintiffs
to initiate a class action.
You can pursue it as illegal fundraising
or a fraudulent
investment scheme.
That's a good idea.
Why are you here?
I came to talk about something.
Is it okay to drink this so late?
I really can't stand anymore.
Why hasn't the car arrived yet?
Why not talk in your car?
I didn't drive today.
Maybe you should take a cab.
What's up?
I found the right person to apply
for your cohabitation certificate.
Since your current contract
is almost up,
you need to decide asap
whether you want to proceed.
How much time do I have left?
Fifteen minutes.
You'd better make up your mind soon.
You're the one who came to me today.
This doesn't count.
Today doesn't count. It's fine.
Then let me see the documents.
Documents?
I think...
I think it's better
if you meet in person,
see if you two click,
and check
if this person is
honest
and kind.
- So...
- Well.
Well.
How about the day after tomorrow?
In the alley behind your place.
Does this person you picked
have any conditions for me?
Do I need to prepare anything?
No, nothing.
One more thing.
I'll definitely take Li Zan
back to Beijing for college.
This visa is only for use
while I'm working.
When I cancel
the cohabitation certificate,
will that person cooperate?
Well, if...
If it comes to that
and you must leave Gaya,
I promise this person won't
pester you.
See you the day after tomorrow.
Yan.
Mr. He.
Are you heading home?
I'll give you a ride.
It's fine. I'll wait a bit longer.
You're tired.
Why don't you get in the car?
OK, I'm leaving. I'm exhausted.
Mr. He, I'll take the car.
Wait.
How long did you say I have left
on our contract?
Mr. He.
Is 15 minutes enough to get to my place?
It's late. It should be fine.
Thanks for the trouble.
Don't mention it.
It tastes good if you get used to it.
But don't be like me.
With too much iced Americano at night,
you'll lose sleep.
Don't drink mine.
I'll move forward a bit.
Why don't you move up a little too?
Sure.
Thanks.
Then I'll move up a bit, too.
Mr. He,
could you please
turn up the AC a bit?
You mean this one?
Thanks.
No problem.
Are you cold?
No.
OK.
Tell me if you're cold.
I already said I'm not cold.
I just don't want you to be cold.
(Staff Only)
11 minutes before we start.
Hurry, hurry.
Yes, Chef.
One guest ordered Qiangguo noodles.
Nothing else?
No, she said she'd order more
after the noodles.
She also asked me to pick a wine
to pair with it.
She's probably here to make trouble.
What if it's a journalist
or a critic?
This is when they come for reviews.
Better safe than sorry.
She said she just wants
a bite of home-style food.
Qiangguo noodles are easy.
I'll take care of it.
I need tomatoes, scallions,
and that curly Italian pasta.
Got it. Matsuo, pass me a scallion.
Mr. He.
Qiangguo noodles.
Just a moment.
The guest was really satisfied.
She finished the whole bowl.
She said she wants to meet
the chef who made the noodles.
Salty.
Don't let her in.
Salty, Salty.
Sorry.
The kitchen isn't open to guests.
Please take a seat.
I need to talk to you, Salty.
Please sit down.
How is it?
What do you think of the new look?
Am I
handsome?
Are you alright?
Why are you here again?
I came to talk
about the cohabitation certificate.
We had an appointment.
Are you okay?
We need to talk.
What's wrong?
Jiang Fang came to the restaurant today.
What did she say to you?
I didn't hear clearly.
I turned and went back to the kitchen.
Didn't you want to see her?
But she showed up so suddenly...
I didn't know
how to face her.
So, are we still talking
about the cohabitation certificate?
Yes, we are.
Salty.
Salty, don't go. Salty.
Salty, Salty.
I know you're angry.
I know you're upset.
But Salty, please believe me.
I was wrong. I really was.
All these years,
I've been missing you.
I've been missing you every day.
Yet you never contacted me
after 12 years and 6 months?
No, Salty.
That's not it.
After I got here,
so many things happened.
It was a mess. I couldn't handle it.
I couldn't go back and get you.
Do you understand?
I couldn't even go to see you.
But it's all better now.
Everything's settled.
What did you settle?
I was the one who paid your debts.
Yes, yes, I know.
That's why I'm here.
Salty, look.
Look.
Do you remember this?
This was our token.
We said next time we saw each other,
we'd bring it out.
Right?
It must've been hard
for you to find it, Jiang Fang.
It looks a lot like the one I had.
Too bad it's not the same.
Do you know what's the funniest?
I have yours.
You must've been in a hurry
when you ran off
and forgotten to take it.
Yes, yes, really.
When I ran away,
I almost lost my life,
so I left it behind.
Lu Tianchi, take me home.
Even if it's a substitute,
it proves that I...
Don't go, please.
She's made herself clear.
Stop bothering her, okay?
Lu Tianchi, this is
between my daughter and me.
Why are you interfering?
You know him?
Of course.
Lu Tianchi,
you didn't tell Salty
that we knew each other?
You're so cruel.
Lu Tianchi.
What's going on?
I'll explain everything later.
Explain my foot. Let me tell you.
- Don't.
- Don't believe her.
We've long known each other.
Six months? At least six months.
There were several times
I wanted to see Salty,
- and you stopped me.
- One question.
Have you two known each other all along?
Yeah.
I'm such an idiot.
- Liu Yan.
- Salty.
Don't follow me.
- Don't follow me.
- Salty.
Salty, don't go.
I'm dying.
Terminal illness.
Just give me one more chance.
You're back.
Why so late?
Do you get overtime pay
for working this late?
Come in.
Who's here?
Zan.
My goodness.
Long time no see.
Holy hell.
What terminal illness?
Brain tumor.
When were you diagnosed?
Just recently.
Which hospital?
A hospital in Indonesia.
Do you need surgery?
How long do you have?
How much is the surgery?
Where's the medical report?
The results aren't good.
I don't plan to get treated.
I think it's called a brainstem tumor.
I know you don't believe me.
I won't live much longer.
My death will prove it to you.
Jiang Fang,
can you say one thing that's true?
Li Zan,
go to the supermarket
and buy a bedding set.
Sis,
do you really plan to let her move in?
Go now.
She's a liar.
Letting her in is like inviting
a wolf into the house.
Jiang Fang,
I don't believe a word
you just said.
Even if it's true,
don't think we're paying
for your surgery.
Enough, go now.
She never tells the truth.
She's acting.
It's all fake. Don't trust her.
Go.
Why won't you believe me?
Have you forgotten my phone number?
1361106
325.
010443322.
And then 213.
I remember your number.
Then why didn't you call me?
It's a long story.
When I first got here,
I promised myself
I'd bring you over
as soon as I settled down.
To stay here,
I faked a marriage
with Li Zan's father.
But not long after,
he got sick
and owed debts.
Li Zan's dad
was good to me before,
and the kid was too young
to live alone.
So, I thought
if I could make money
to treat his illness
and bring you over,
wouldn't that be the best?
Unexpectedly,
my luck was so bad back then.
Everything I did lost money.
Li Zan probably told you
about what happened later.
Why was there a car accident?
That day I got up late
and missed the bus,
so...
Later,
things just spiraled.
I only found out what happened
from the news.
I owed Mr. Luo so much money,
so I thought
if this accident could make him think
I was really dead,
maybe my debts
would be written off.
I thought it all through.
However,
you suddenly showed up
and even paid off my debts.
I...
I almost died
trying to clear your debt.
Do you know that?
I do.
I really do.
I went to the hospital.
When I saw you there,
your whole leg was in a cast,
and your face was unrecognizable.
The only one there with you
was Mr. Lu.
I thought...
So, you two met there?
Yeah.
I actually wanted
to stay and look after you,
but...
Mr. Lu said it wasn't a good idea.
So, I left.
You sent the dandelions, right?
Yes.
I remembered your birthday was coming.
After all these years,
I never once celebrated your birthday.
I didn't have much money
and didn't dare disturb you.
Didn't dare disturb me?
If that's true,
why did you show up at Highland today?
I had made up my mind
never to see you again.
But a few days ago,
I started getting headaches every day.
I thought maybe my days were numbered.
The more that feeling grew,
the more I missed you.
I've truly hit rock bottom.
You hit rock bottom,
so you came to Highland to eat first?
That's right.
When you hit rock bottom, eat first.
Then why did you run
when I went to the hotel to see you?
That was my fault.
That night, I had a dream.
I dreamed about you.
I missed you so much.
I told Mr. Lu
I couldn't take it anymore.
I wanted to see you.
I wanted to see you, Salty.
I begged him to bring you to me.
But before you arrived,
I suddenly remembered
that he once told me
that in my current state,
if I...
If I stayed with you,
you'd suffer.
You'd be in pain.
I...
Salty, should I not have come?
Was it wrong for me to see you?
Did I commit some crime?
Why are you interrogating me like this?
Neither of you believes me.
Salty,
if I wasn't
running out of time,
and if I didn't miss you so much,
I wouldn't have come.
I had planned
never to see you again.
It's all my fault.
Why couldn't I hold back?
My stomach hurts.
Salty, why are you sleeping here?
The bed's wide enough for both of us.
We can squeeze a little.
We're not close enough
to share a bed, are we?
When you were little, you couldn't sleep
without touching my hair.
Did you forget that?
It's been so many years.
I just want to get closer to you...
I'm fine. Don't move.
Talk to me.
A lot has happened
these years, right?
Obviously.
As soon as I took a bite
of the noodles today,
I knew they were made by you.
That taste was just like mine.
The scallion oil
was perfectly done.
But
the tomato wasn't good.
It was peeled.
I guess that's how
Western cuisine does it, right?
Still, I believe
once you blanch a tomato and peel it,
no matter what you do after...
Jiang Fang, are you here
to teach me how to cook?
No.
I couldn't teach you anyway, right?
Chinese and Western cuisine
are different.
The pay at Highland Restaurant
must be great, right?
How much is your monthly wage?
Do you have nothing better to do?
I have to work tomorrow.
Then I'll ask one serious question.
Just one.
Is that Mr. Lu
hitting on you?
- Go to sleep.
- Don't fall for a man's tricks.
Let me tell you.
I'm not you.
He's not your first love, is he?
- Listen.
- One more word,
and I'm moving out.
So noisy.
Did you forget how you were as a kid?
You couldn't sleep without noise.
I remember every day after school,
you'd run
to the back kitchen
to nap.
- Quiet.
- One day...
Enough already.
You're grown-ups now.
My stomach really hurts.
How am I supposed to sleep like this?
Not being able to sleep
every night
is the worst.
Wow.
Yet you fell asleep so soon.
Don't just stand there.
Eat while it's hot. It's tasty now.
Hurry, hurry.
Jiang Fang, you really are ruthless.
You made this, huh?
I've lived with you for ten years.
Whenever you do something awful,
you make a meal to calm me down.
You must want something.
I know exactly
what kind of person you are.
Let me tell you.
I know exactly
where everything is in this house.
You must've stolen something.
Yes, this house
was furnished by you two,
but I bought
this dining table,
and the pots and pans, right?
I'm part of this family too.
- Where's the money?
- What money?
The money in the box.
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
There was money here.
Now, it's gone. Where did it go?
I really don't know.
- I like money, but...
- Stop arguing.
I gave her the money.
Don't try to fool me.
When did you give it?
You slept so soundly.
I gave it to her when I got up.
It's to go buy groceries.
Go buy groceries.
OK.
What do you want for lunch?
Anything is fine.
Then I'll buy whatever I want.
Eat quickly.
It won't taste good cold.
Don't cry after you finish it.
It's delicious.
What are you doing?
Why did you give her the keys?
It's the key to our house.
Are you crazy?
I'll go after her.
Save me a bite.
(Jiang Fang, you really are ruthless.)
(Fine.)
(You win.)
(A few pieces of steamed buns)
(drove my hatred away.)
(I know)
(you might lie to me again.)
(But I'll accept it.)
(At least I)
(have a mother now.)
Ms. Liu,
here's your car key.
Salty...
Yan? Salty?
Shuangshuang, I've been calling you.
Why don't you answer?
I have something to ask.
Which is the best hospital
for a brain tumor in Gaya?
Do you know any
famous brain specialists?
I shouldn't have hidden
Jiang Fang's situation from you.
But the truth is definitely not
what she said.
The day you were in a coma,
she came to the hospital
and then left.
If she came,
why leave?
Because you were unconscious.
You were worthless to her.
She sees you're getting better now,
so she's coming back
for gambling money.
Can't she get close to me
because she misses me,
loves me, and needs me?
Why does it have to be related
to gambling?
I haven't seen anyone
come to collect debt,
so she doesn't owe money.
That doesn't mean
she quit gambling.
It's okay if she hasn't quit.
She's sick now.
It's okay for me to spend money
on my mom's treatment, right?
No, I don't think a terminal illness
could be used as an excuse.
She's my mom.
She doesn't need an excuse
to see her daughter.
What do you want me to do?
Just watch her die?
If she really dies,
I'll regret it.
If you lend her money
because of another lie,
then you'll regret it.
I already regret trusting you.
I just want to protect you.
At least my lie
is a well-meaning one.
Lu Tianchi,
whether Jiang Fang
has quit gambling or not,
and however well-meaning
your lie is,
shouldn't you
have told me?
That's my mom, not yours.
Who gave you the right to decide
whether I should see her or not?
No, one month is too long.
Is there any way to speed it up?
You have my phone number.
If you think of anything,
call me anytime.
Okay?
Mr. He.
Does this affect your mood?
What?
Since your mom came to Highland
to look for you,
you've been like this.
You have six hours
to be away from the kitchen
before dinner.
Speed it up, speed it up.
Coming, coming.
Everyone,
tonight is very important.
The CEO of ZJ Group
and Mr. He's mother
have been longtime friends.
He was one of our earliest guests.
His reputation carries
a lot of weight in the industry.
We hope everyone can offer him
an amazing night.
This is very important for Highland.
French blue lobster.
Obviously, it was air-shipped
from France.
Are we doing carpaccio again this time?
Or lobster pasta?
Yan,
do you remember the test we did before
with the lobster in puff pastry?
Yes.
You said
it wasn't suitable for Highland.
But it's suitable for ZJ.
Good, then let's do that dish today.
Liu Yan and I will handle it.
Kanta,
you take care of the regular dishes.
Hasn't she been a bit off lately?
I can do it.
I can handle it.
The baking timing is very important.
No mistakes are allowed.
Yes, Chef.
Hurry up, hurry up.
(Clinic)
Small onions.
Easy on them.
- Enough.
- Yes, Chef.
185 degrees, fan speed level 3.
For 10 to 12 minutes.
Yes, Chef.
So many missed calls.
Something might be wrong.
Go ahead. I'll keep an eye on it.
Thanks, Kanta.
Watch the oven for me.
I'll be right back.
Thanks, thanks.
Hello, doctor?
Doctor, can you hear me now?
Sorry, I was inside.
The signal was bad.
Yes, I called you this morning.
I wanted to ask you
about the treatment protocol
for a brain tumor.
I don't understand it.
Please let me
introduce this dish to you.
So, this is the oyster with vichyssoise
and Fuyang tofu skin on top
with a little bit of
Jinhua ham on it.
- Nick.
- Mr. He.
- Hi, Nick.
So, Chef He will prepare
a very special lobster dish
for everybody later.
Toast to Chef.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you very much.
Yes, a family member.
A woman in her fifties.
Where's the lobster?
Where's Liu Yan?
Where's Liu Yan, Kanta?
Where's the head of the hot line?
It's already burnt.
Where did Yan go?
Cancel the lobster.
Bring the beef now.
Yes, Chef.
Mr. He, I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't have left today.
I promise it won't happen again.
You're not right for Gaya.
Your visa's about to expire anyway.
The manager will handle
your severance per the contract.
That's not necessary to fire me.
I asked if you wanted to be
someone indispensable.
You said yes.
I do want that.
So, every second you leave the kitchen
is a betrayal of my trust.
I want to lead Highland
to earn Three Diamonds.
I need someone trustworthy
to stand by my side.
You get distracted too easily.
You won't become
an excellent chef this way.
♪Mother, I've grown up♪
♪No longer crave my embrace♪
♪No longer need my approval♪
♪No longer afraid
to realize I'm still here♪
♪Countless disappointments;
nothing left to hope for♪
♪We're falling through the air,
endlessly falling down♪
♪There's nothing we can hold on to♪
♪No ground where we can land safely♪
♪(When all hope is gone)♪
♪Our hearts will break
before the dream ends♪
♪We drift along in this dazzling world♪
♪Stumbling through every change
life brings♪
♪The true courage
is simply not looking back♪
♪I finally understand:
The only constant is change♪
♪Mother, I've grown up♪
♪No longer try to fill every void♪
♪No longer saddened by all the goodbyes♪
♪No longer blame; no longer blame♪
♪Mother, I've grown up♪
♪No longer try♪
♪To fill every void♪
♪No longer saddened by all the goodbyes♪
♪No longer blame♪
♪Love that led nowhere♪