♪Mother♪
♪I've grown up♪
♪I no longer crave to be surrounded♪
♪No longer need♪
♪So many smiles♪
♪No longer fear broken trust♪
♪Mother, I've grown up♪
♪No longer try♪
♪To fill every void♪
♪No longer saddened♪
♪By all the goodbyes♪
♪No longer blame♪
♪Love that led nowhere♪
=HER=
Drag it over there.
No need. Take it away. Thanks.
=Episode 7=
Dear, I'm back.
Honey.
You're back.
I thought you didn't like the sun
or yoga.
No, I love sunshine.
I like whatever you like.
I've been waiting
for you here all morning.
I nearly passed out in the heat.
I'm sorry.
Mmm-hmm.
Do you plan to come back
to Italy with me?
Let me take you to Tuscany
to meet my parents.
I think Jaya's pretty nice.
And don't you think
it feels really good
being here together?
You're not planning
to live at my place?
Then I'll ask my secretary
to extend the rent
for three more months.
If you like it here,
then we'll stay here.
There's a great show tonight.
Would you like to come with me?
Of course.
- Long time no see.
- Yes.
- How are you?
I'm fine.
She's my girlfriend, Shuangshuang.
Mike.
We came for the match.
Let's see how it turns out.
Antonio,
I'm going to the bathroom.
Wait for me.
Sure, no problem.
Sorry.
I'll wait here for you.
Why are you here?
Look at this ring. Is it big?
Stop messing around.
You know this isn't
a legitimate fight, right?
I know.
I heard some things on the way here.
Then why did you come?
Well, Antonio said
he had a surprise for me.
I didn't know it was this place
until I got out of the car.
I really don't think
you should be watching these fights.
Make up an excuse.
Tell him you're not feeling well
or whatever.
You're good at that.
- Right?
- No.
Antonio is
a lifetime VIP member here.
I can't be
"not feeling well" forever.
Have you thought
about being honest with him?
Like telling him about your past.
I don't need you
to teach me how to date.
I'm not your client.
Why do you care so much about me?
Fine, I'm leaving.
I'd suggest you not watch the fight.
It really matches your eyes.
Thank you.
Wait just a moment.
- Hello.
Come here.
Me too.
Let me introduce you.
This is Mr. He from Highland.
This is Shuangshuang, my girlfriend.
I've heard so much about you.
Pleasure to meet you.
This is Mike.
The show is about to begin.
Everyone, inside, please.
Hi.
And now,
the fight you've all been waiting for.
Coming to the stage...
- Big Beast.
- It's about to start.
Go, Big Beast!
Come on, Big Beast!
Fighting
against Beijing, China, Liu Yan.
Who?
(Liu Yan)
Big Beast, go!
Isn't she from Xiya?
You knew her before?
She visited my mother's grave.
Something must have happened.
Otherwise, she wouldn't have come here.
(Production: Roses)
Scene 1, shot 1, take 1. Action!
Ladies and gentlemen,
get ready to watch another
two warriors facing off in the ring.
There ain't no scoring.
No time limit.
No holds barred match.
Get ready for combat!
Ready? Beat!
Get up.
Where's the referee?
It has to stop. Can't you see?
Go back to your seat.
So, you've made up your mind?
I have.
You're going to die,
right?
Maybe.
Maybe it's better
to rip the bandage off.
I've been running for too long.
I ran from debt collectors
with my mom as a kid.
Now I'm running with Li Zan.
I'm tired.
The best thing Jiang Fang ever did
was send me to sports school.
That's where I learned
how to face my fears.
I used to hope
that by the time she came back for me,
I'd have already won
enough matches,
so she'd never have to run again.
I wanted to tell her in person.
Jiang Fang,
I can protect you now.
Don't hide anymore.
Can you be brave for me just once?
Come and find me.
Even if I die,
I want you to remember
you had a Salty
you could always be proud of.
If something happens that day,
this photo can be...
Be what?
A memorial photo.
Louder, louder.
I can't hear you.
Liu Yan.
Liu Yan?
Stop! Stop!
Why did you hit him?
Stop!
Where are you going?
That was fun.
(Mom.)
(I won.)
(Did you see it?)
Liu Yan!
Don't sleep.
Doctor!
I just had a dream.
I dreamed I went to Jaya Island.
I was drowning in debt
and almost got beaten to death.
You won't die.
Kids with no parents
always survive.
What if I fall in love with someone?
Wouldn't that become my weakness?
Who?
Who's the poor guy you fell for?
56, 57, 58.
59, 60, 61, 62.
Wow.
Wow!
That's a lot.
We're rich, Liu Yan.
We're rich.
We're rich!
I can clear Jiang Fang's debts!
I'm rich!
Are you Jiang Fang?
Thank you for looking after Liu Yan.
I know
I shouldn't be here.
No.
You should've shown up long ago.
She's been looking for you.
You're the one person
who should've been here.
I don't have the face to see her.
She...
As you know,
she was beaten this badly
because of the debt you owe.
But you...
Could you please
face all this bravely?
I don't know
if she'll forgive you.
But she really misses you.
Please stay.
Wait here with me until she wakes up.
Okay?
You're right.
I shouldn't run anymore.
I'll stay. I'll take care of her.
Please, have a seat.
I haven't asked your name yet.
My surname is Lu.
I'm her legal advisor.
Mr. Lu, thank you.
No problem at all.
You should go get some rest.
I've got things covered here.
I...
I'll stay and wait with you.
As for the hospital staff,
I can manage it.
No need.
I'll call a doctor if I need to.
Besides,
she's a girl.
When she needs to wash,
it's not very convenient
with you here.
Then I'll wait at the door.
Really, there's no need.
Go home and get some sleep.
Come back tomorrow morning for her.
Also...
I haven't seen her in over a decade.
I'd like to spend a little time
alone with her.
Well...
Then I'll leave.
Okay, okay.
If the A/C gets too cold tonight,
you can ask her for a blanket.
Got it. Take care.
Alright.
Thank you, Mr. Lu. Thanks.
You shouldn't have come.
Hello.
Jiang Fang.
Wait.
Are you leaving now?
What do you think?
What did you just say to me?
You said you two
haven't spent much time together
in a while.
You said you...
At least wait until she wakes up
before you go.
If I do, I won't be able to leave.
Your debts
have been cleared now.
You two can finally
start a new life together.
Why are you leaving?
Mr. Lu,
don't you get it?
Liu Yan has grown up.
She has her own life now,
and I have mine.
We're not on the same path.
If we force it,
she'll only end up worse off than now.
Why are you acting
like a completely different person now?
You weren't like this in the room.
Even if you're leaving,
at least wait for her to wake up.
Say these things to her face.
Can you?
You're right.
What should I even say to her?
Should I tell her
I made a lot of money
because I bet on her to win?
Should I stay now?
Liu Yan is my daughter.
It's true that I love her.
It's also true that I love money.
Actually,
if I ever really show up
in her life again,
that's when you should be worried.
Just now,
I got you a little turtle.
I hope you can
be strong like it.
Be strong...
Be strong like it.
That's enough.
Hurry and wake up.
Nurse,
can you call the doctor for me?
The patient is awake.
How are you feeling now?
Thirsty.
Here.
Slow down, slow down.
Don't drink too fast.
My hands
and feet...
They're all here.
You have three broken ribs
and a mild concussion.
Listen. You're lucky.
The doctor said if it were someone else,
their spine would've snapped.
They'd be paralyzed.
With your injuries now,
you're not going
back in the ring, right?
Be grateful, will you?
In the ambulance,
your heart stopped for ten seconds.
When I signed the consent form,
my hand was shaking.
Fine, you can't box anymore,
but you can hit me if you want.
Sorry, sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
You must be hungry.
Once the doctor finishes,
I'll get you some congee.
Who did you bet on to win?
What?
Well, to raise the odds,
I bet on you to lose, obviously.
What?
Is that a smile or a grimace?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong, my friend?
I bet on myself to win.
You bet on yourself to win?
In that case,
you must've made a lot of money.
How about this?
Help me cover
the money I fronted.
Including the emergency fees, surgery,
and the hospital stay.
Not a small bill.
I want to be discharged.
You talk like you can
walk out of here yourself.
Are you kidding me?
Mr. Luo covered all the costs.
The room is booked for a week.
You've got four more days left.
Rest a little longer.
Mr. Luo?
His people told me
to pass you a message.
If you ever need anything,
you can go to him.
Also,
Jiang Fang's debt is cleared.
If you're happy, just be happy,
but don't smile like that again.
Or it'll hurt again.
Alright.
Have another sip of water.
Come on.
Good for you.
What's this turtle doing here?
I was worried you wouldn't wake up,
so I hung a turtle for good luck.
I hope you'll be like it.
Come here.
Are you going to kiss me?
Idiot.
Slower.
Ow, ow.
Come on.
It's only 40.
If I go any slower, why not crawl back?
Fine, fine.
I'll drive slower.
Why not wait until you've recovered?
Why insist on being discharged now?
It's expensive.
You're not short on money.
I can cover it for you.
No.
(Big Beast)
What's with this light sign?
Light sign?
What did you do?
The guy on the motorcycle
is my good buddy.
His name's Huang Zongxian.
You can ask him to do it.
Just tell him I told you so.
He'll listen and cooperate.
Just get it done.
(Sexy Girl vs. Big Beast)
Don't worry.
(Yan, Big Beast)
I'm driving. Come on.
What are you doing? Be serious.
Look.
You need
to get your bangs trimmed.
You can't hit me, so now you bite me?
Are you a dog?
Don't tell anyone.
Fine, I won't.
So embarrassing.
Now you're shy?
Pinky swear.
Pinky swear what?
Don't tell.
I won't.
Still laughing?
Am I not allowed to laugh?
This wheelchair probably can't go in.
What are you doing?
Come on.
No, no, don't.
I don't need it. I'm fine.
It's okay.
Stop acting tough. You can't walk.
Sorry.
There's no electricity.
Are we going in or not?
Let's go.
How many eggs?
Three.
How many?
And scallions.
Take them all out first.
There's seaweed
on the top of the fridge.
Grab that as well.
The pot is under the board.
The steamer rack is hanging
to the upper left of the stove.
This goes inside, right?
- Is this the steamer rack?
- What?
I can't see it.
Yeah, yeah.
Remove the roots?
Yeah, remove them.
Cut them into slices.
Just a few slices will do.
Crack the three eggs into a bowl.
Then look at the bowl.
See how much egg
is in there.
Add 2.5 times the amount of water.
Has it been whisked evenly?
Still whisking.
Like this?
Is that enough?
Keep whisking. Make it smoother.
And then pop
all the bubbles.
Once the salt is in,
- put...
- Speak slower.
I just found the salt.
Put it into the pot.
Just put it in?
Put it in, and then slice the scallions.
Are you slicing the white part?
The white part is the end, right?
No.
Don't slice the white part.
Use the green tops.
It doesn't sound right.
Seems like it's done.
Drizzle in a bit of sesame oil.
Add a small spoonful of soy sauce.
Don't feed me.
It tastes better when I eat it myself.
This works way better
than painkillers.
Try it.
Not bad.
Do you know why
you had to pop the bubbles?
Give me another bite.
Did you know?
When I was in the hospital,
I kept dreaming
that Jiang Fang came to see me.
It didn't feel like a dream.
Do you have any news about Jiang Fang?
No.
Not even bad news?
Did she teach you this too?
Jiang Fang used to be the head chef
at a famous state-run restaurant.
She taught me all the fancy dishes.
I made up
these scrap tricks myself
during all those years in Beijing
when I had nothing but time.
Not bad, huh?
What are you working on now?
Did you see my messages?
I sent so many.
Answer me. Hurry up.
Hello, Ke? It's me.
Well.
Didn't you tell me before
you had a friend in Jaya?
Can you give me their contact info?
Yeah, it's urgent.
They're not there now?
If you don't answer soon,
I'm calling the police.
She's sleeping, okay?
Chill out a bit, will you?
Stop shouting.
Why are you crying?
She's not dead.
She's sleeping soundly in there.
She's fine.
Didn't you tell me
it was a minor injury?
When my dad died,
he didn't even end up like this.
If I'd told you the truth,
would you have gone to school?
If you skip school,
your sis will be even more worried.
She's a girl.
With her injuries,
she'll probably need plastic surgery.
Oh, my god.
She'll be fine
once the swelling goes down.
Your sis was born beautiful.
Don't you know that?
You're a boy.
You should learn a bit from her
and be tougher.
It's fine. I'm watching over her.
She'll be okay.
Then I'm going to school.
Go on, go on.
Don't tell her I came back.
I'm still mad.
Still seasick too.
Take good care of her.
Only you would like someone
brave but reckless
and brainless like her.
Are you okay?
When Big Beast lifted me
and slammed me the second time,
do you know what
my last thought was?
What?
Regret.
I hadn't gotten to enjoy anything yet,
and I was going to die.
So why don't you take me out?
Now?
Where are you getting the energy?
How are you going out like this?
With so many broken bones,
you need to rest.
I've been in Jaya so long,
and I haven't done anything fun.
I only focused on clearing debts.
Over and over.
You'd scare people
if you went out like this.
I want to ride the Ferris wheel.
What's so great about that?
It just sways slowly in circles.
Even little kids get bored of that.
I know it's boring.
Shijingshan's Ferris wheel
takes 28 minutes per round.
Yuyuantan's takes 20 minutes.
Longtan Lake's takes 22.
Happy Valley's is more worthwhile.
It takes 35.
I've been on all of them in Beijing
with Jiang Fang
and all her boyfriends.
But every time,
they'd still be on the Ferris wheel
by the time I'd finished
riding every other ride
in the park.
When they finally got off,
I had to take pictures for them.
How boring can a Ferris wheel be?
Will it be more boring than me?
Once you're better,
I'll go with you next time,
okay?
I've heard "next time" too many times.
It's always next time.
I'm always asked to wait.
But it's the middle of the night.
The amusement park is closed.
Next time then.
Where are we going?
You'll find out soon.
Just now,
I actually fell asleep.
It took you so long there.
What were you doing?
As I told you,
you'll know in a minute.
Surprise.
Listen.
You can see everything you can see
on the Ferris wheel from here.
How is it? Cool or what?
♪Is filled with everything I love♪
Look at these lights
I designed.
Compliment me. Come on.
So efficient.
Miss Liu.
(Salt is key to balancing flavors)
Tonight,
you can sit here till morning. Okay?
♪Are filled with all your romance♪
What do you think? Is the music good?
Feels pretty good.
Way more interesting
than a Ferris wheel.
That keeps spinning around
like an idiot.
See the pointy roof over there?
Know what that is?
What?
The place you stayed a few days ago.
When the monster
lifted me and slammed me to the ground,
what were you thinking?
You still owed me money.
No wonder you gave me that turtle.
You were scared I'd die.
You're smiling so happily.
Come on, smile again.
When you laugh, does it hurt?
It hurts so much.
Don't make me laugh.
What did I do?
I'm not making you laugh.
♪Not spinning in circles
within the rules♪
(Salt is key, Liu Yan)
♪I firmly chose what I love most♪
♪Free and true to myself♪
(Salt is key, Liu Yan)
♪How come your heart♪
♪Is filled with everything I love♪
♪Like a breakfast made randomly♪
♪You make everything I want perfect♪
♪Like you studied me
and understood what I love♪
♪How come my eyes♪
♪Are filled with all your romance♪
♪Like a fearless and brave freedom♪
♪I'm the answer to everything you want♪
♪I hope everything I give you
is what you like♪
♪My wish is simple♪
♪I want you to be with me forever♪
♪Playing on repeat, shining with me♪
♪Not spinning in circles
within the rules♪
♪Feelings are simple,
free and true to myself♪
♪My wish is simple♪
♪I want you to be with me forever♪
♪Forgetting time, breaking limits♪
♪Not spinning in circles
within the rules♪
♪I firmly chose what I love most♪
♪Free and true to myself♪
♪Not spinning in circles
within the rules♪
♪I firmly chose what I love most♪
♪Free and true to myself♪