♪The falling snow♪
♪Is bitter cold♪
♪My sigh♪
♪Misted the path in front of me♪
♪The moonlight knows my intention♪
♪I just want to make a place
for me in your heart♪
♪I laugh and I cry♪
♪Quietly building a pond in my heart♪
♪I accept all the gifts from sorrow♪
♪I can't let down my regrets♪
♪I won't admit defeat♪
♪I slowly chew on
the bitterness of life♪
♪The fragrance remains the same
after the bleak winter♪
♪Awaiting spring to color
the way back home♪
[The Double]
[Episode 9]
[Shen's Residence]
A bet?
Yes.
She not only said whoever loses
must kneel and apologize.
But also mentioned that the loser
must go to Zhennyu Hall.
[Delayed Farewell]
Such boasting makes me wonder
if she's lost her mind.
At first, I was worried
she might be Xue Fangfei
coming back for revenge.
But now I feel relieved.
With a brain like hers,
she's nothing like Xue Fangfei
except in appearance.
She's so arrogant.
She even dares make a bet with Mr. Li.
Doesn't she know their capabilities?
That's enough.
I don't want to hear all this.
Yurong,
what's wrong with you lately?
You're always unhappy.
It's nothing.
Things have been getting busier
at the Hanlin Academy.
I'm just a little tired.
Go back and do your revision.
Don't tell me
you're worried about Jiang Li.
Shen Ruyun,
don't cross the line.
What did I do?
Mother asked
if you want
to move back to your room.
After all,
it doesn't look right
to stay in the study.
I'm fine staying here.
Yurong,
you locked your room
and wouldn't let anyone clean it.
You can't go on like this.
How about you give me the key?
Mother and I can clean Xue...
Throw away all her belongings.
Then you can move into your room.
Get out.
The situation has been tense lately.
Just a little while.
I'll buy your freedom.
Hello, Lonely Gentleman.
What are you...
Tidy your clothes before talking to me.
Duke Su,
did I commit any crime?
I'm tired of hearing people
asking me that question.
Is the Bureau of Salt and Iron
running out of money
that you can't afford
to buy her freedom?
What did you say?
I don't get it.
Zhiyan, pour the drinks.
You're one of his people?
What... What do you want?
What are you doing?
Don't come near me.
Where did Judge Kong channel
the Bureau of Salt and Iron's shortfall?
I don't know.
I may be his brother-in-law.
But I don't know anything.
Why waste time talking to him?
I thought we were here
to try out our new torture device.
What... What is this?
That's a good question.
Oh, this? It's something
that would turn you into a eunuch.
But dealing with a real eunuch
is one chop, and the deed is done.
But with you,
I might have to put in some effort.
What are you going to do to me?
Drinking in a romantic atmosphere
and giving yourself a pseudonym
like women.
Lonely Gentlemen,
your life will be completely free
from defilement,
and suffer a sense of emptiness
after this.
I'm not married yet.
I don't have any children.
Fine, I'll tell you.
In my first year,
he wouldn't let me touch money.
When he thought I was honest,
he involved me in moving money
and valuables.
After getting the money,
we'd deliver it to the theater.
Who was it for?
I don't know.
No, wait! Wait!
I really don't know.
These were the secrets
of the Kong family.
If they were revealed,
the Kong family would be ruined.
He wouldn't tell me.
Give him a piece of paper.
Write down the days
you went to the theater.
Any wrong detail...
You can say goodbye to having children.
All right. I'll write them down.
Thank you.
I'm not after money.
Taking this money
will make things easier for you.
Besides, you deserved the money.
I still owe you for your kindness.
If it wasn't for Yu saving me back then,
I would have died long ago.
I became your spy,
hoping to discover General Xiao
and Yu's true cause of death.
My father died in battle,
and my mother passed away from illness.
It's been resolved eight years ago.
What else is there to investigate?
Others believe it, but do you?
The more you know,
the faster you die.
I don't believe
you're this heartless.
Come upstairs and take a seat.
Come on.
Mr. Lin, come and catch me.
Come and have fun.
Come on.
You're hurting me.
♪If there are no happy memories♪
[Great Yan Military Camp, Nanjiang]
Father, I want to go with you.
[Young Xiao Heng]
Xiao Heng,
[Xiao Minghan, Xiao Heng's Father]
we're going to battle,
not military training.
Then it's dangerous for you too.
Don't worry.
I'll bring the Longwu Army with me.
Wait for my return.
Mother.
Heng,
you should go to bed.
No, I don't want to.
I want to be with Father.
[Yu Hongye, Xiao Heng's Mother]
Heng, be good.
Go to bed.
Mother, please.
Let me go with you.
When I return,
I'll sing a song for you.
I'm going.
Peng Guang.
[Peng Guang]
Yes, sir.
Send Xiao Heng back
to General Xiao Senior
at the Duke's Residence.
Yes, sir.
Xiao Heng, come on.
No.
Let me go.
Father.
Mother.
Father!
Father.
Father, open your eyes.
Get him out of here.
Father.
Let me go.
That's enough!
Grandfather,
my father would never lose to them.
There's definitely
something strange about this.
We must look into it.
A scholar dies for his words,
a warrior for his fight.
[Xiao Dachuan Xiao Heng's Grandfather]
Dying in battle is a soldier's fate.
Father's death was unclear.
Grandfather, are you really going
to turn a blind eye?
Victory and defeat are common in war.
I don't care about that.
I don't know
how you can be so heartless.
No wonder Father always said
you were unhappy with him
since he was young.
Even now that he's gone,
you refuse to seek justice for him.
You're heartless!
I hate you!
[Memorial Tablet of General Xiao]
Hurry up.
Come on.
Quickly now.
Keep up.
I said, quickly.
Hurry.
Look how handsome he is.
He sure looks handsome.
Just look at his appearance.
You're right.
- He's so good-looking.
- He does, doesn't he?
Very impressive.
I really like
this gentleman.
Mother.
- Madam!
- Mother!
Mother, what's wrong?
Madam.
Mother.
Mother, are you all right?
Qing.
Mother.
Yes, Madam?
Dress me up.
Is it pretty?
Yes.
Heng, your father gave me this hairpin.
I cherish it very much.
Come
and help me put it on.
Mother,
you look beautiful.
[Tomb of Great Yan General Xiao]
Mother, Father's death is unclear.
All of them refused to listen to me.
Heng, you're still a child.
You will understand many things
after you've grown up.
Your father was an upright man.
He has always taken pride in you.
So after this,
You shouldn't always cry and be upset.
Otherwise, your father and I
will feel heartbroken
when we see you like that.
I hope you can grow up
safely and happily.
Can you do that?
My Lord,
the interrogation is over.
His visits to the theater
are quite fixed.
Shall we go to the theater tomorrow
to investigate?
Sure.
My Lord, this is a significant clue.
Aren't you happy?
His Lordship is not in the mood today.
Let me tell you
something interesting then.
Second Lady Jiang and Li Lian
have made a bet.
If Jiang Li loses,
she has to return to Zhennyu Hall.
If Li Lian loses,
he has to become a monk.
I was surprised when I heard it.
I didn't expect
Second Lady Jiang to be triggered
by your provocation.
Is she risking everything
or overestimating herself?
Is she a toothless tiger or a real one?
We'll find out soon enough.
[Fangfei Garden]
Li,
is your wrist hurting?
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
Li,
I heard about your bet
with the Li brothers.
I'm worried sick.
I wish I could do something to help you.
It's okay, Tong.
I'm quite confident.
Li, are you really not afraid?
Just go through with it
without thinking too much.
I must meet the Emperor and be rewarded.
Is it because you want
to tell the Emperor
about the injustice
against you and Lady Jiang Li?
It's still not the right time yet.
When I get the top score,
only then Second Lady Jiang
is truly back in the capital.
Everyone will look at me differently
and won't dare do as they please.
Also, I want to know
who's behind Shen Yurong.
Li, are you saying
someone is instructing him?
Li, I have no choice.
If she wants to crush us,
it's like crushing an ant.
I'm certain.
This person has immense wealth
that can help Shen Yurong rise steadily.
Although I don't know who this person is
or why
they're targeting me and my family.
But instead of trying to find out,
it's better for me to use myself as bait
and lure that person out.
The imperial palace banquet
is a good opportunity.
When I stand up there,
that person will look at me.
[Princess Wanning's Residence]
[Close to Wisdom]
What are you writing here?
Your Highness,
you're pressing on my sleeve.
What are you writing?
It's an unnamed inscription
I've been practicing lately.
Your Highness, do you want to write?
I'll hold the brush for you.
Sure, I'll try.
[Close to Wisdom.
Respect and Aspire to Virtue.]
Shen,
is there anything interesting
out there recently?
Your Highness,
When practicing calligraphy,
one should focus and be calm.
You're spouting nonsense again.
Yes.
My apologies.
Your Highness may do whatever you wish.
Have you heard about the bet
between the second son of the Li family
and the Second Lady Jiang?
I did not pay attention to these things.
Isn't Second Lady Jiang the one
who commits matricide and fratricide?
How is it?
Is she beautiful?
I forgot.
Shen, you must have been
too busy lately.
Even your memory is foggy.
You've met her twice, remember?
The first time,
at the coming-of-age ceremony.
Another time at the Jiang...
I've never been interested
in paying attention
to irrelevant people.
That's true.
You only need to pay attention to me.
Well, Second Lady Jiang
committed matricide and fratricide.
You see, a woman like her made
a bet with the second son
of the Li family.
Who do you think will win?
It's natural for Mr. Li to win.
You're lying.
You wrote it wrong.
I'll write another one for you,
Your Highness.
No need.
You're not clear-headed now.
What's the point of writing?
Write another one.
You can write it well this time.
I said forget it.
Didn't you hear clearly, Shen Yurong?
I no longer have the mood
to stay calm with you.
A man who can't even lie.
How can you make me happy?
Forgive me for my incompetence.
Do you think my anger will subside
with that apology?
Meixiang.
Stop looking like you're wronged by me.
Go out and help me bet
on Jiang Li to win.
Outrageous!
She's becoming more
and more disobedient.
She even dares to make such a bet.
The power in the capital is complex.
How could she understand it all at once?
If it weren't
for Old Madam's insistence,
Li would have stayed home another year.
But she is already attending
the School of Integrity.
There will be more troubles
in the future.
It's my fault.
I really didn't expect this.
Mr dear, forget it.
Don't be too harsh on Li later.
Young people are always impulsive.
So it's inevitable.
If she admit her mistake,
we can guide her slowly
when she comes home.
If she had admitted her mistake,
she wouldn't have been sent
to Zhennyu Hall.
I want to see
if she has truly repented
in these ten years!
My dear.
My dear,
calm down.
He's coming.
My Lady. My Lady.
Don't help me up.
Master, she has been kneeling
all day and all night.
Please talk her out of this.
Father.
What are you doing?
I made a mistake
and should accept punishment.
Why do you still do it
when you know it's wrong?
Because as the daughter
of the Chief Secretary,
I shouldn't embarrass Father.
My dignity is not something
that's easily lost.
What about your own dignity?
You made a bet,
and it's with the Li family.
If you lose,
you'll become a joke!
Father,
all I want is to study quietly.
But the exam format
at the School of Integrity changed.
If I don't form a team to take the exam,
I won't even have the qualification
to participate.
I've just entered
the School of Integrity
and have no friends.
My sisters have their own group.
I finally found someone to form a team.
But the Li brothers are trying
to snatch him away.
Their attitude is terrible,
and their words are contemptuous.
They said...
What did they say?
I can't stay at the School of Integrity.
They asked me to kneel and apologize.
This is too much!
You don't need to worry.
I'll handle it for you.
Father,
Chancellor Li can't do anything
to you in court.
So he's using me to provoke you.
If I withdraw,
what about Father's reputation?
Don't worry about these things.
I'll talk to Li Zhongnan tomorrow
and cancel this bet.
The bet has already spread
in the capital.
If you resolve it for me,
you'll be criticized.
I don't want Father to be humiliated
in front of Chancellor Li.
Father,
I've grown up.
You've protected me for many years.
Let me take this risk now.
I accept this bet,
risking my life
and the honor of being a daughter
of the Jiang family.
Father,
please help me.
Li,
I'm giving this qin to you.
Since Father has spoken,
I'll help you.
If there's anything else
you need help with,
feel free to let me know.
The qin you've used
can definitely help me win.
You can have this music sheet too.
It's too bad I don't play the qin.
So there's nothing much
I can do to help you.
I'm already grateful
that you have such kind thoughts.
Time is running out.
Li,
you need to prepare quickly.
Madam,
we've sent all the good things to her.
Are we really going to help her?
Yes.
Why not?
She wants to soar high.
So we'll let her crash and burn.
Those hypocrites are just pretending
to be helpful.
I thought Uncle would scold you harshly.
But in the end, he supported you.
Everyone feels the need
to vent sometimes.
Father is also human.
I'm really curious.
What are you good at?
Do you also play the qin?
I learned a bit at Zhennyu Hall.
Your sister can't even
afford decent jewelry,
and you're spending money
to repair her qin?
I'll make sure
to get her proper jewelry in the future.
Mother, don't worry.
But if this qin isn't repaired soon,
her skills will worsen.
It'll be too late then.
I knew it.
You don't care about me and your sister.
We might as well be dead.
Mother, what are you doing?
Why are you being unreasonable?
Leave me alone!
You called that learned a bit?
You clearly play very well.
- My Lady.
- What's wrong?
My Lady.
Is your wrist hurt?
Let's go and see the physician.
I'll bring him here then.
No need.
I'll go see the doctor myself.
You can't go alone.
I'll accompany you.
My Lady.
It's all right.
Let's go.
It's just a minor injury on your finger.
So it's serious.
Speak concisely.
She's the young lady
of the Prime Minister.
[Divine Techniques Sect Hua]
It'll be your fault if she's not cured.
But she has an old injury on her wrist.
Old injury?
Yes.
The old injury wasn't treated properly,
and now there's a new one.
It's a bit troublesome.
But don't worry too much.
With acupuncture daily for a few days
and the medicine I prescribed,
along with proper rest
and no strenuous activity,
playing the qin and riding horses
won't be a problem after that.
Mister, how long will it take
to fully recover?
At least a month, I'd say.
Can't it be faster?
We're treating injuries here,
not some kind of child's play.
It needs to be step by step.
Thank you, mister.
Please prepare the medicine.
All right.
[Divine Techniques Sect Hua]
How can there be an old injury?
I got injured from working hard
day and night
at Zhennyu Hall. Why?
I mean
you knew about your wrist injury.
Why did you make the bet
with the Li brothers?
I even bet...
So
are you just going to watch from afar?
That's not what I meant.
Wait.
I'm serious.
I'm really serious.
My father was a great chess player.
After he joined the official circle,
my mother thought playing chess
would affect his future career.
So she forbids him from playing anymore.
But I learned a few tricks from him
when I was young.
I'm confident
I can handle it.
Go back and play a game.
You even know how to play chess?
They seem to teach everything
at Zhennyu Hall.
It makes me want to go there.
Young Master,
could you please check
if the medicine is ready?
Lady Jiang Li needs to take it.
Of course, I'll go and get it.
Is it ready yet?
Li,
how can you play the qin
with your wrist like this?
There's always a way.
Let's take care of others first.
Your son is not himself.
It looks pretty serious to me.
Xiu,
I have some free time today.
I can play with you.
I need to prepare for the exam.
Don't disturb me.
She's not acting like herself.
She's really overestimating herself.
Jiang Li.
What is it?
How do you get the courage
to compete for the top spot?
Because I'm not content.
I'm not content to be confined
in Zhennyu Hall,
to be trampled on
at the School of Integrity,
and even to be hidden away at home
just to marry a good husband.
I want to compete.
I want to break free
from this stifling place
and fight for justice.
There's nothing to hide about it.
I know
why Ye Shijie was convinced by you.
You have determination.
Only you
can persuade such a proud person
to join us.
I've said
I want to win against Li Lian.
He should also be worthy
of an audience with the Emperor.
This time, whether it's for me,
for him,
or for us.
This time, I'm going all out.
Me too. I'll give it my all.
What's wrong?
I fell off a horse before.
I never want to ride again.
Now, I want to try again.
Liu Xu, don't worry.
I'll ride with you.
Let's first get used to the feeling
of being on horseback.
It's okay.
No rush. Take your time.
Your thumb ring is loose,
don't you know that?
Duke Su?
You were following me.
In your eyes,
do I really have the time for that?
This place is usually for hunting.
As for you,
it's quite dangerous for you
to barge in like this.
We couldn't find anywhere else.
Duke Su,
what did you say about Liu Xu?
What's loose?
This friend of yours
deliberately wore a loose thumb ring
because of fear of an old injury
on the thumb.
You see.
If the ring doesn't stick to the skin,
the ring will rotate due to friction
with the arrow shaft
when shooting arrows.
Before the arrow leaves the bow,
its direction is already off.
A slight deviation can lead
to a huge difference.
How can you shoot accurately?
That's really impressive.
Do you know archery?
No.
A bow and arrow are light weapons.
It's good for women
to learn for self-defense.
Get off the horse and stand here.
Hold this for me.
I never said I wanted to learn archery.
Do as I say.
Hold the bow handle in the middle
with one hand.
Hold it firmly
without looseness.
Your thumb pulls the string.
Just like this.
Remember the position
of your thumb pulling the string.
I'll guide you to pull the bow once.
Once you've held the bow, hold it tight.
Or else you'll be inviting
your opponent to kill you.
Focus on the target.
I'll count to three.
Then release
your thumb that's pulling the string.
Remember.
Don't hesitate.
One, two, three.
I really hit it.
Now you try it yourself.
What's wrong with your wrist?
It's nothing.
How can you say it's nothing
with an injury like that?
How are you going to take the exam?
I'm currently treating it.
Duke Su, you don't have to worry.
The physician said it'll take
at least a month to fully heal.
Can you wait that long?
So you were monitoring me.
I was just passing by.
Jiang Li, what's wrong?
If you want to be completely healed,
come to my residence today.
What's wrong with your wrist?
Don't worry.
It's nothing serious.
I was wondering
why Duke Su came
to give me some pointers.
It turns out you know each other.
I just heard he invited you
to his residence.
You're not going, are you?
The examination is in three days, right?
Yes.
Duke Su is a strange person.
Although he helped us today,
who knows what he's thinking?
It's best not to provoke him.
All right.
Li,
why don't you rest for a bit?
You can't rush with your wrist injury.
We're running out of time already.
We still have Lady Liu, right?
See if any of them can play the qin
and swap with you.
[Duke Su's Residence]
Please send a message.
Duke Su told me to come.
Our Lordship asked you
to come yesterday.
He waited all day.
He doesn't want to see
any visitors today.
I arrived late
and made Duke Su wait.
Today, I will wait for him.
Close the doors.
[Duke Su's Residence]
Second Lady Jiang,
follow me.
Wait.
What's wrong?
My legs are numb from sitting too long.
I can't stand up.
[Return of the Clouds]
Duke Su, what a refined taste.
But I didn't come here today
for roast meat.
Since you're not hungry,
then wait first.
The physician hasn't eaten yet.
[Situ Jiuyue]
Let me introduce you
to the best physician in the land.
Not the best physician.
But the best poison expert.
Xiao Heng,
what's the meaning
of you simply bringing anyone here
and expecting me to treat her?
You're breaking my rules.
I won't break your rules.
I'll take her place to do it.
You'll take her place?
Who is she to you?
What rules?
Xiao Heng hasn't told you, right?
If you want me to treat you,
you need to gamble with me first.
If you're willing to treat me,
I'd naturally take that bet.
Fine.
Straightforward.
I happened to have received
a venomous spider.
I need someone to test its poison.
If you win against me,
I'll cure your hand.
What if I lose?
You'll forfeit your life to me.
How do we do this?
Of these two spiders, one is poisonous,
the other is not.
Pick one.
Sometimes,
staying alive requires luck.
Even if I save you this time,
you might not live long.
Let me remind you.
One of these is highly toxic.
If you pick the wrong one
and it bites you,
you might not survive.
Shall we start?
Wait.
Are you scared?
You said I need to bet a life.
But you didn't say it had to be my own.
This is the life I'm using for the bet.
I introduced the physician to you.
This is an act of betrayal, you know?
If anything happens to you,
I will take my own life in return.
Die with me, huh?
Xiao Heng, I'm warning you.
This spider is truly poisonous.
What are we waiting for?
Let me carefully pick
which one is the venomous spider.
Is it this one?
Or this one?
Open it.
It's not poisonous.
Xiao Heng!
Then I'll pick this one.
Open it.
You won.
This is not poisonous.
It looks like my hand gave you luck.
You can leave now.
I need to do the treatment now.
What a pity
that she can die with me.
Can you walk quickly?
How did you guess it?
When you look at him,
I can see love in your eyes.
So what?
Don't you?
He isn't the one I love.
If you dare lie to me,
I'll kill you.
Women shouldn't show
their feelings easily.
Otherwise, they'll lose the first round.
You speak as if you've experienced it.
Give me your hand.
The meridians are in disarray.
Ordinary methods won't work.
We can only fight fire with fire.
But this method is intense.
You'll endure immense pain,
mental turmoil,
and sleepless nights.
I trust you, Miss Situ.
You have quite the nerve.
No wonder Xiao Heng came
to beg me for you.
Miss Situ and Duke Su
seem well acquainted.
We saved each other before.
Give me your hand.
[Duke Su's Residence]
Did you stay up all night
just to make sure I didn't poison her?
How is she?
The poison hasn't completely
dissipated yet.
Give it two more days.
She'll be fully recovered.
Xiao Heng,
I never imagined
you would care so much for a woman.
She's the pawn I want to groom.
If her hand is crippled,
how can she continue with her act?
Xiao Heng,
have you developed feelings for her?
Stop asking me such questions.
You'd better not let me find out
you're lying to me.
Lu Ji,
send Second Lady Jiang back.
She's asleep.
Do you want me to carry her back
or throw her over my shoulder?
Send a message to her maid.
Yes.
♪Having seen the vast sea,
ordinary water seems dull♪
♪Behind the fleeting life
are right and wrong♪
♪They cannot be pursued♪
♪A heart as strong as iron
and stone is unyielding♪
♪Yet it bows down for love and sorrow♪
♪Forgetting the preciousness
of the soul♪
♪How humble it is♪
♪Some obsessions turn to ashes♪
♪The best remedy is a single ingredient♪
♪Bitter wine should not be indulged in♪
♪Do you know what it means to be drunk?♪
♪The sound of flutes
outside the pass urges on♪
♪Departing but intending to return♪
♪Why insist on flying away back then?♪
How are you feeling?
Thank you for getting
a physician for me.
I will repay this favor
in the future.
You can't repay
my favor yet.
What do you mean?
When one is at a low point,
it's like a fallen leaf
where fate
is beyond their control.
The Duke's Residence can't accommodate
such fallen leaves.
♪If there are no happy memories♪
♪How can we traverse
the forbidden land of sorrow♪
♪Two cold and unfeeling bodies♪
♪Holding hands,
can we get through the snow season♪
♪In the cold wind, in the long night♪
♪Embracing the remaining warmth♪
♪The depth of the sea, unfathomable♪
♪Can it bury yesterday's sighs♪
♪Continue to love,
cherishing it with my life♪
♪Continue to live,
even with only a glimmer of hope♪
♪Whether in sorrow or joy,
I believe in you♪
♪I'd rather be trapped
in the world's extremes♪
♪Continue to live,
exhausting all courage♪
♪Continue to love,
until the breath runs out♪
♪Traversing half a lifetime
of loneliness, just to meet you♪
♪After the hardships,
never to part again♪