[Translate By Machine]
[Good Translate will available later on www.kisskh.do]
Willow Eye might win
But Tang Li Ci
never lose
Don't worry about your revenge
Tang has always been
no sooner said than done
Say I don't deserve to be your friend
Who cares about being friends with you?
Master, I have my own wife
Can you leave?
you
Don't you
Don't even leave
He said that about you
You haven't left yet
Could it be
He really doesn't consider me a friend
i in his eyes
Is it holding him back?
Tang Fox is extremely smart
Then me too
You Tang Fox are extremely smart
But you are always the same
indifferent look
Why is it so abnormal now?
Could it be
You are duplicity
Worrying about me
Then I will reluctantly forgive
Brother Chi
How important are you to Mr. Tang?
it is known
He has a recurrence of an old injury
Just for a moment, I was speechless
He has relapsed into an old injury
I knew he couldn't do it without me
Wanqiaozhai got it
The boat gang’s ledger
our business
I'm afraid I can't hide it for much longer.
No wonder you came today
They are all our own people
The banquet public trial is about to begin
Why haven’t you seen the Sword King yet?
Master urgently calls
Is something wrong?
You use this token as a link
Speed ​​up the batch of goods at the dock warehouse
Escorted out of the city
leave now
master
Everyone in Wanqiaozhai is spreading the news
Several bosses you have good friendships with
Suspected of evil pills
you are so anxious
What is the cargo to be shipped?
That was Tang Li's poisonous plan
You actually believe it too
Go quickly
Asshole
master
The disciple just doesn’t understand the master
Why the rush to cover up this shipment?
The master has always taught his disciples
In everything we do, we must put Sword King City first
now
Sword King City is afraid that it will fall into
A place of no return
Disciple
Never doubted Master
I just want an answer from Master
It's all my fault that I didn't give it to you
explain clearly
you were misled
Tang Lici is insidious and cunning
Let’s take advantage of Jiang Qingyu’s death first
provoke me with
Mr. Puzhu's relationship
Later in the name of business
Get ledger secrets
intending to use his power
Infiltrate water transport
If I hadn't known in advance
He wants to put the blame on me
If I hadn't prepared in advance
I'm afraid Sword King City and I
They are all going to be ruined.
That's why Master asked me
Who doesn’t want to be upright?
just me
I suffer from the inability to prove myself
Come
master
Negative
you
This is the first time you call me that
There are no outsiders now
you can change your words
If you lose your son, you will definitely live up to your mission.
Kaeguru Castle
Eliminate adultery from the rivers and lakes
Bring Tang Li Ci to justice
Negative
Father
Ali
Listen to Liu Yan
You broke his Gu altar to pieces
All in vain
originally
want to give it to you
broken
How could it be
Let me see
Very good
Ali
This moment is not good and can be repaired
Can't be repaired
You can start over
No one is capable of making mistakes unless he is a sage or sage
How much can be improved over time
Go and admit your mistake to Liu Yan
he will forgive you
The night party is about to begin
It's time to go
You said this person
What did you look like when you were born?
Still like this puppet
experienced many things
One knife at a time
That’s why it was carved like this
Bodhisattva becomes a monster
Tang has an inescapable responsibility
Then Shen Lang became Shen Lang’s soul
Whose responsibility is it?
kill willow eye
Only then can I forgive myself
No way
Because I am useless
And you who killed your loved ones
Even if you take revenge
I won't forgive myself
Brother Shen
let's go
The King of Swords has arrived
Welcome the Sword King
Sword King
Something is different
What's going on
Tonight is said to be the public trial of Jiang Qingyu
But all those who came were our people
Not many of the major leaders came.
A group of followers
I sharpen my head on weekdays
Want to follow the sword king
Now it’s hard to see the Sword King
All of them disappeared.
that is
yes
What are you panicking about?
I know Tang Lizi at night
It's a murderer's
People are enough
he's coming
That's all the drama
Mr. Puzhu is here too
This batch of goods
Anyway, I have to send it out tonight
yes
Today's guest of honor
Not Yu
But Tang Lici, the master of Wanqiaozhai
He loaned me Qiongtai for a lot of money
Say yes
Exposing Jiang Qingyu
Show it to you
Sword King
How did you hear about it?
That Jiang Qingyu is already dead
speaking of
This matter is Yu’s fault
Jiang Qingyu went to Yanmen and came back
In my dungeon
Closed well
Just wait for the Central Plains Sword Club to come and judge
But who knows
just yesterday
Suddenly silenced
The murderer also burned down the dungeon
Destroy corpses and destroy traces
Right now
There's not even half a clue left.
The Yu family dungeon is heavily guarded
How could someone
sneak in quietly
The murderer has been silenced
That day
With Mr. Puzhu
Just met the killer
Escape from the dungeon
This person is the master of Wanqiao Zhai
Spending a lot of money
Recruiting those under the curtain
The Thirteenth Floor Killer
Shen Langhun
As everyone knows
Mr. Tang is holding a banquet today
It's for excuse
or for
That day was in a hurry
I didn't catch the murderer
Can't decide
That's Mr. Tang
Send someone to do this murderous act
Mr. Puzhu is compassionate
As everyone knows
Know people, know faces, but don’t know the heart
Mr.Puzhu
Please be aware of everything
Please also ask Mr. Puzhu to be aware of everything.
Jianhui would like to know
Tang’s true face
Why lie to others?
Mr. Tang misunderstood
What kind of person is Mr. Tang?
Of course only myself
Only then can we make a conclusion
Everyone
This is today's guest of honor
Uncle of the current dynasty
Disciple of Lord Zhou Dian Lou Fang Xian
Tang Gongzi
Everyone
Not even a toast to him
The prince of Tang Dynasty is noble and noble
Ordinary wine is naturally unpalatable
This cup of Yu
It's called guest doing as he pleases
Mr. Tang might as well give it a try
please
Hasn't anyone told the Sword King?
Your method of bewitching
Tiger Skin Wind Claw King Xiaolu Tiger Skin Chicken Claw It has to be you Wang Xiaolu WANG XIAO LU
Note: This product is for external use. Prohibited and contraindicated: It is prohibited for patients with umbilical disease. Please read the instructions on the adverse drug or purchase and use it under the guidance of a pharmacist. Co., Ltd. OTC Dinggui Dinggui Er Navel Patch for External Use to Treat Diarrhea invites you to continue watching.
Double hard core and strong internal protection | Royal Meisu Jiaer invites you to continue watching Royal Meisu Jiaer
This Gu
called mantra
Once taken
All questions must be answered
Can't fake
Mr. Tang has always been good at eloquence
It is beyond the reach of ordinary people
today
If you want to make Yu
The truth you want comes to light
You have to drink this cup
That being the case
Tang today
Just as the Sword King wishes
Of course I want to drink this wine
but
Don't let someone drink alone
Tang Mou has already finished drinking this cup.
King Yu Jian
You should also drink this cup
That's natural
Come and drink
The heroism of the sword king
I finally got it
Get the ledger back
Tang Fox went out to have a banquet
Don't even take me with you
We must be here
What are you looking at?
Since it is a secret
The Yu family will definitely be careful
leave no clues
So we're going to
Looking for clues among the clues
I admire you very much
serious attitude
Then you continue
I'm going out to take a breath
Look at that girl
Do you think there is a problem?
This account is a little weird
You see
This is June to September
When passing through several cities along the Huaihe River
Delivery of Ruyiguo, a specialty of Sword King City
Ruyiguo
It is indeed a specialty of Sword King City.
Is there anything wrong with this?
Ruyi fruit blooms in May
September results
Will be available for sale in October
this ship
If June leaves Sword King City
carried
It can't be Ruyiguo
That sister is so smart
No wonder the young master will treat you
Take it with you
We just need to find out thoroughly
this merchant ship
where to place goods
You can find clues
Tang cake
Take a pen to record
yes
Today Tang is the host
Everyone here
Tang has a better wine reception
Shen Langhun
Why is he here?
How dare you, a murderer, come here?
King Yu Jian dares to come
Why don't I, Shen, dare?
Can the truth be concealed?
Good wine is not exclusive to the King of Swords either.
Don't drink
Tang encountered evil pills in Yanmen
If the sword king hadn't taken action
Fear of chaos
This jar of wine
Tang
Jingjianwang
Yu Jianghu
Hard work pays off
Yu Wulin
Leader of Mount Tai
Looking forward to all comrades
power concentricity
Eliminate the forces behind Xiewan as soon as possible
It's a waste of time for the dead to live in peace.
Why did he fall?
Do you dare to drink?
I dare not drink
he drank
Now that the wine has been drunk
Mr. Tang should answer
What Yu wants to know
Is it the truth?
This matter is more serious than Jiang Qingyu's
Making the world more turbulent
Yu has to be here
The heroes of the world
Ask Mr. Tang a heart-wrenching sentence
Mr. Tang, don’t blame me
Death of Lord Fang Xian
Is it your fault(Watch on www.kisskh,at to support Admin)
This is the trick that person taught you
Mr. Tang, won’t you answer?
The Sword King poisoned the wine
Tang Mou naturally wanted to answer
but
Tang
I also put something in the wine.
I wonder if you have ever heard of it
Ming Yue Gui Xin Dan
This medicine?
no other use
But if you are not careful
been taken
People who take the Oranguki Jiuxin Pill
Just two hours
It will poison the heart
Severe pain in Dantian, intestinal piercing, and death
Tang Lici, how dare you poison me?
how can you be right
Jianghu gangsters poisoned
So unethical
Yes, how can you use such means?
Make the decision for us
Sword King
There are infinite possibilities in this world
And human nature
Even more elusive
so
Tang Lici behaves as a person
Just talk about possibility
unreasonable
As for poisoning
Isn’t this what you taught me, Sword King?
And the sword king
what do you want
Let Tang Mou guess
You are stupid
Rely on evil pills to understand the west wind and kill the wild fire
That’s why we have today’s status
And I have supreme talent
And the endless wealth of Wanqiaozhai
you feel jealous
I want to call him Tang
ruined
to be honest
Tang is not afraid at all
Actually, you can be more direct
The person who gave you this worm
What exactly does he want to know?
Zhou Dianlou murder case?
That's right
The murderer of Zhou Dianlou murder case
Kill the people of Fang Zhou
It's down there
Tang
Li
Ci
you liar
hypocrite
You killed Fang Zhou
Destroyed Zhou Dilou
Can you still live so peacefully and contentedly?
OTC Anhui Medicine Yangxiang Granules National Drug Approval No. Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlu Medicine (Shi) No. 251231-00602 AI generation function is used for chronic gastritis and stomach burn. Please follow the drug instructions or purchase under the guidance of a pharmacist and Taizhan is about to
OTC Yangweishu Granules, national drug approval number Z34020289, Hefei China Resources Shenlu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Chengwan Yao Guangshen (Shi) No. 251231-00602 [Functions and Indications] Nourishing yin and nourishing the stomach, [Adverse reactions] It is not clear that it can be used for chronic gastritis, burning stomach, and dull pain [Contraindications] It is not clear. Please buy and use according to the drug instructions or under the guidance of a pharmacist. Precautions: You must first recharge your batteries.
OTC Yangweishu Granules, national drug approval number Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Liwan Yao Guangshen (Shi) No. 251231-00602 [Functions and Indications] Nourishing yin and nourishing the stomach. The adverse reactions are not clear. The contraindications are not clear. For chronic gastritis, please follow the drug instructions or purchase and use under the guidance of a pharmacist. For detailed precautions, start nourishing the stomach today.
OTC Shufen Granules, national drug approval number Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wanyao Guangshen (Shi) No. 251231-00602 [Functions and Indications 1 Nourishing yin and nourishing the stomach, used for chronic gastritis, stomach burning, and dull pain Tang Gongzi
OTC Sinopharm Jiazi Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wan Yao Guang Shen (machine) No. 251281-00602 is still unclear. Why are you standing still with burning stomach?
OTC Yangxiang Shulaizhong is a national drug with the approved number Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Deer Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wan Yao Guang Shen (Shi) No. 251231-00602. It is not clear whether it is used for chronic gastritis, burning and dull pain in the stomach. Please follow the drug instructions or purchase and use under the guidance of a pharmacist. Please refer to the instructions for payment details.
OTC Please refer to the instructions for purchasing and using the drug.
Yangweishu Granules OTC Yangweishu Granules National Drug Approval No. Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wanyao Guangshen (Shi) No. 251231-00602 [Functions and Indications] Nourishing yin and nourishing the stomach, used for chronic gastritis, burning stomach, and dull pain. The adverse reactions are not clear. [Contraindications] are not clear. Please follow the drug instructions or purchase and use under the guidance of a pharmacist. Please refer to the instruction manual for details. The young master has a stomachache.
Didn't that person tell you?
Pretending to test others
It's like grabbing a white blade with empty hands
So natural
But if it is not captured
Then you have to leave your hand
King Yu Jian
You are just his abandoned son
you crazy
Stop talking nonsense here
Mr.Puzhu
Are you trying to protect Tang Lici?
Tang Lici was deeply involved in the case
Pu Zhu wants to be interrogated alone
King Yu Jian
farewell
Puzhu
You figured it out
stand with him
That is to make enemies of the whole world
Tang Lizi
Is what you said true?
This is
The Backlash of Mantra Gu
Could it be said
The murderer of Zhou Dianlou murder case
Kill the people of Fang Zhou
It's down there
Tang
Li
Ci
Sword King
I've heard that legend
Can test the Oranguki Kyushin Pill
Ming Yue Gui Xin Dan
Is there any in this wine?
I'll be fine waiting for you
yes
madness
If there really is something on the rivers and lakes
Ming Yue Gui Xin Dan
Shao Yanping didn’t know
Lord will not know
But it is
Tang Li's deception and coaxing tactics
Mr. Ke Shicai Puzhu
Already on his side
Will we already
What are you panicking about?
The evil pill thing
The Central Plains Sword Club has been investigating for so many years
What have been found?
What to do now
Just pretend to be a little bit more like me
Don't mess up your position
The rest
This Sword King has his own arrangements
It's the King of Swords
Unexpected
Mr.Puzhu
Actually willing to give up
Everyone wants to get rid of him quickly
Zhou Lou’s suspected murderer takes action
He does not hesitate to openly become enemies of the Yu family
Tang Gongzi
your lies today
Too much has been said
What did you put in your drink?
Why did someone fall?
Severe pain in Dantian
Violent poison attacks the heart
Intestinal piercing and rotten stomach
It’s Tang Lici’s medicine
Sword King
save me
Shut up, everyone
Shut up.
Puzhu has not gone far yet
If someone is exposed
Don't blame me for being ruthless
I've finished remembering it all
Take a look
Wolfsburg shoes deer qingshitian
sky
Changfengmen Six Knives
A line of heroes
This group of people usually
A guy who looks like a human or a dog
Jingdu was seduced by the romantic shop
Walk
Tang's
It's just an ordinary laxative.
On the one hand, Tang is pressing harder and harder.
This is the public support of Mr.
Witnessed years of conspiracy
About to be exposed
Even if Yu Qifeng can barely hold on,
can follow him
Those sluggish people
Just like a building is about to collapse
On the verge of collapse
And sir
Aren’t you also taking action for me?
This is Tang’s purpose
Brother Shen
Out of the way
Sir is just
I'm just angry
The list is now available
Tang did not break his promise
as apology
I just want to invite Mr.
Accompany me on a night tour of Fenghuang River
Let's enjoy it together
The beautiful scenery of Sword King City
Good
It's on fire
Put out the fire quickly
quick
It's on fire, hurry up
Hurry up
Come on, come on over there
Li San
How could it catch fire?
I don't know either
Commander Yu can't leave
This will-o'-the-wisp burned until the wind turned
hurry up
adult
The mast is repaired
The boat is ready to sail
Full speed ahead
quick
We've been delayed for too long
accelerate
Pass through the gorge ahead
yes
accelerate
He Fangxiao
Pretend to be a ghost
Dare you stop my Yu family’s cargo ship?
It turns out to be Mr. Tang
Thousands of waterways
We meet on a narrow road tonight
I'm afraid it's not just a coincidence.
Commander Yu was joking
Tang Mou visited this gorge at night
Play the piano and enjoy the moon with friends
Happy to return home
Commander Yu is busy with affairs
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Tang Lizi
Don't go around in circles with me anymore
what do you want to do
speak directly
Night boat trip
Time to watch the fireworks
What
Being happy alone is not as good as being happy together
Everyone who sees it has a share
is gold
Get rich
all mine
Sorry, Commander
All the cargo on the back ship was robbed.
Tang Lizi
rob the noisy ones again
Standing
quick
Thief
put things down
Stop him for me
Yes, don't go
Snow line
follow me
Tang Lizi
You blatantly colluded with the rats
Robbery the Yu family's cargo ship
Do you still have Sword King City in your eyes?
Are there any rules in the world?
Commander Yu misunderstood
That white hair
Tang doesn’t know him at all
Tang Mou tonight
Just enjoy the scenery
set off fireworks
Your goods are lost
But it has nothing to do with Tang
You say so?
Mr.Puzhu
The friends Tang invited tonight
Only Mr. Puzhu
Commander Yu said that Tang was colluding with the Rats
Do you mean Mr. Puzhu?
gentlemen
I don’t know that Mr. is here
How offended
Dare to ask sir
This is what sword society means
Junior understands
What Mr. Tang did today
Presumably Mr.
See more clearly than juniors
Junior, I believe Mr.
With the wisdom of Mr.
You won’t go wrong with Xin Xiaoxiao
I won't associate with thieves
farewell
turn the ship around
let's go
Weibo na Sina Entertainment on Weibo, follow @MangoTV @微博tvtv, participate in #水龙音# topic discussion, and unlock more exciting content!
turn out to be
This is your purpose
All on the same boat
I'm borrowing my name from Mr.
Rights as transfer capital
Why are you leaving in such a hurry, sir?
It’s because Tang’s piano doesn’t sound good.
The fireworks still don’t look good
bully others
Disregard for procedure and evidence
What you did is not dharma
What the teacher taught you is
so
For what Mr.
fairness and justice
I should let them
like before
unconsciously
ship goods out
Is it right
I should also say hello first
Let Yu Qifeng prepare in advance
Visit again
Listen to him clear up the relationship
Finally leave politely
in this way
It doesn’t deserve to be called an upright family.
Is it right
You are the disciple of Master Fang Xian
So what
Lord Fang Xian takes the world as his own responsibility
the name of a gentleman
Well-known in the world
But
he is dead
Tang is different
I
Just want to live
in the future
you and me
No need to go the same way anymore
The evidence you two said
Is this it?
Mr.Puzhu
Disdain to travel with us
Jiangxiewan
destroy them all
I found this product after working hard all night
If you say you don’t want it, then you don’t want it.
That's okay
Throw it away then
Wait a minute
Then what's next
what should we do
Now
The list is complete with evidence
I will immediately send Yu Qifeng
Caught and brought to justice
Sir is wrong
It was Tang who won
Bet with Mr.
And the price of losing the bet, sir
Just can't
Take Yu Qifeng away directly
Tang Lizi
Not only can Mr.
Take Yu Qifeng away
I want sir to do it
You can't interfere
The Remaining Things in Sword King City
The conditions of the bet between Tang and his husband
Never changed
I'm sorry, I can't do it
Give way
Added food to the fish
This is good stuff
I can stay out of it
But the Central Plains Sword Club
I will never stand by and watch
you
Don't kill Yu Qifeng
That being the case
That leaves time for Mr.
Not much left
six hours
It’s the Central Plains Sword Club
The shortest time to and from Sword King City
If a fight really breaks out
I can't guarantee it
Won't take his life
What to do with the rest?
All destroyed
group of waste
Use all the elites of the Yu family
Can't even guard against a snow line
waste
Tang Lizi
Puzhu
You and the Central Plains Sword Club
No one can escape
messed up so many things
Are you still wishful thinking?
It seems that although I have the courage
Not enough brains
Your Majesty is here
I don’t know what you’re doing
old thing
See you still safe and sound
What a pity
I talk to the Lord
It's not your turn to interrupt
let me count
You are good at making decisions today
Did a few stupid things
first item
Not cruel enough
The attempt to poison Tang Li Ci failed.
Revealing other drug users
second item
smart-aleck
Afraid of being cheated
discover your face
In a panic, he chose to take the medicine out of the city.
Falling into their scheme again
third
opinionated
to this day
The sword king thought he could have
Chance to survive
Just these things
You should wake up
Even if the lord wants to kill this sword king
You shouldn't take action now
What's the reason?
Lord, don’t you want to know?
After Tang Li resigned from the mantra Gu
what was said
Do you still need to guess?
He admitted that he killed Fang Zhou
Isn't it?
Since I already know the answer
Why go to all this trouble
My grudge against him
You can't understand
Today's events
I have another idea
Lord, what does this mean?
master
why are you here
If I don't come
How did I know you were so useless?
It's all my fault that it's useless
Please ask Master to punish me
Don't be afraid
I'll come
It's another one
A major matter related to the foundation of Sword King City
need you to do it
Master, please speak
after it's done
Sword King City can be saved
A century of good reputation
Dad can be in front of everyone
I identify with your son
don't let me down
yes
good
You actually took advantage of Fu'er
What's the matter
Come to me
Do not disrespect the Lord
No problem
The Yu family lost
It doesn't mean I lost
I like to fight against Tang Lici
But I prefer saving people
rest assured
your life tonight
I'm protected
I like your ambition very much
So tomorrow
You have to kill for me
Lord
Let your subordinates kill someone
everyone
Search "Super Live" on Mango TV on the dynamic M Mango card and grab massive performance tickets!
Quantum · Da Da Culture Zi Da Da meets again after thousands of times