[Translate By Machine]
[Good Translate will available later]
Jiejun
Faqidan
Mi Yan Lei Yi Ci Hongniao En Tao Wen Han Powder Chao An
Issuing authority: Fujian Provincial Radio and Television Bureau
The All-in-One CS Scanner? Professional scanning becomes more professional. The All-in-One Scanner used by 300 million people takes you to the main film.
Don't hurt Master
Since you want to die for him so much
Then I will make it happen for you
You can still wake up in this state
It's actually because of him
People like you also care about people
Still concerned
Such an insignificant person
How ridiculous
good
Then I will let you
See with your own eyes
Not even close
Someone you care about dies in front of you
pebble
Just like me back then
Ayan
why don't you understand
You back then
also me
pebble
Fang Zhou's
Pure Lotus Heart Sutra
how did you recover
Thousand Gu Needles have obviously been
hit you
Shut up
willow eye
Your Thousand Gu Needles
It did almost kill me.
but
Fang Zhou’s
The heart crystal that blocks my heart veins
It also blocks your needle
I cut out his heart crystal
before his death
The power condensed in it
Converge with my seven meridians and eight meridians
He is doing this in this way
tell me
don't hate myself
I let go
is correct
It's Fang Zhou
saved me again
impossible
Fang Zhou saved you
what nonsense are you talking about
willow eye
do you know
Tang Lici regretted it for the first time in her life
Just regret
Didn't kill you
Use your strongest move
Tang Lizi guarantees
It'll make you sore
Drink in the underworld
Tang Lizi
The sea of ​​karma is shattered
kill empty tribulation
Thunder drum sound
it's over
Come on
I didn't lose
from now on
Senior brother plays the piano
Main plum drumming
I play the pipa
Just play the flute
Big like this
even if you are
Be part of Zhou Di Lou
This one doesn't taste like a fox dragon
Give it back to you
Tang Lizi
You can never get it back
The other half’s rebirth spectrum
And I
can go
Keep company with Fang Zhou
This round
I didn't lose
It's up to you
He deserves to go see Fang Zhou
this time
Stop trying to escape the truth
This is my yin and yang
what is learned in memory
The heavenly wheel opens in the middle
I've experienced everything
you are me
I am you
willow eye
among the heavenly wheels
My consciousness is nowhere to be found
share with you
open heaven wheel
You practice the past life
Use it in exchange for work
Take away the evil spirit from you
switch to me
But you have to promise me first
this matter
Never let Ah Yan
I know Xiaofu
let go
Ayan
Now
You know it
The person who killed Fang Zhou
it's me
Leave him dead
The person who cut off his last chance of survival
me too
Destroy him with your own hands
what one wants
The man who brought peace to the world
Still me
Fang Zhou
sorry
Ali
I was wrong
willow eye
you have done so many wrong things
thought of committing suicide
I tell you
No door
Listen carefully
your life
Only I can take it
And now
i want you alive
alive
Slowly for the wrong things you did
atonement
alive
Such a wonderful play
I came at the wrong time
Guarded against
wrong
It's dissipated
Ten phases of empty tribulation
The power of the past life has disappeared
are you surprised
This Dharma is called Changing Heaven Sutra
The same root and origin as the past life spectrum
Rebirth in another world
Two sides of the body
within this area
Everything is me
I am the universe
All things
Cut into cubes
Move with my thoughts
Are you curious?
Why do I change my Bible?
quicksand
jungle
Fall
Qiankun remake
I am the Creator of all things
Not afraid of the devil
Want to break this situation
Only to kill all things
Tang Gongzi
you can't kill me
Baisuishan Metasilicic Acid Type Mineral Water Noble Baisuishan invites you to continue watching Gan ten
Vita Lemon Tea is now available! You are invited to continue watching
It's all your plan
Ghost Peony
Ayan
As for you
From meeting by the Yellow River
Lord's first day
I know Lord
It’s really easy to master
No attachment
It won't be extreme
If there is no extreme, there will be no narrow-mindedness
Not narrow-minded
You won't let me take advantage of it
commit folly
meaning
cut weakness
It’s all because people have emotions
Without emotion there would be no weakness
There will be no errors
Lord
goodbye
Halloween extradition lotus statue opens
Ayan
remember
try to live
Ali
Unexpectedly
in such a short time
Can break the scriptures
It really is the real spectrum of the past life
pity
are you looking for this
Tang Gongzi
you lose
That one
Please Mr. Tang
Go to Piaoling Meiyuan to talk about it
Tomo no Kokujo
Picked up a man whose throat was cut
You are still alive
It is said
He was also adopted as an adopted son
true or false
You can survive even if your throat is cut
still alive
why are you still alive
Why
This won't kill you
monster
you monster
Why can't I go back to my original state?
Why
look at this poor guy
You can’t kill your own enemy
Still don’t dare to kill again
Pitiful
Deplorable
who is
who is there
ridiculous
who is
Who is pretending to be a fool?
The wine jar that cannot be knocked open
The fire that won't light up
No matter what
Mistuned strings
who do you think you are
What qualifications do you have?
judge me
Can I help you let Tang Lici
regretful person
This is the last one in existence
Please take good care of your hands
it's precious to me
evil medicine
Ayan
remember
try to live
Now
You know it
Ali
I was wrong
Fang Zhou
sorry
Ali
Can't die
Xiaoshi was seriously injured and still in coma
Tang Lici and that one
Don't know where to go
It must be Willow Eye
Take advantage of the chaos and drive them away
The valley behind Qingyang Cave
There are traces of sword energy
Lao Shen is following
hope to find something
listen to me
save
I've been having a dream
kill your dreams
I dreamed countless times
every time
They all kill you in different ways
first-order brutality
More vicious than ever
save
Even I was poisoned by my own cruelty
awakened
But when I see you
Just discovered
all those ways
Not vicious enough
Have you ever tried to be as bright as a dream?
It brings you to your inner demons
Keep thinking of painful memories
Then let you be
in endless pain
tortured to death
save
Tang Lizi
Ghost Peony
Caught
What did you say
Piaoling Meiyuan
save
what is this place
have no idea
Liu Yan said
Where was Tang Lici caught?
The words of the devil Liu Yan
Can we believe it?
What should I do?
We can't ignore Young Master Tang, right?
Whether what he said is true or false
The life or death of Mr. Tang is uncertain
We can only choose to believe
What matters now is
Gotta find a way quickly
Find Mr. Tang
Prince Tang is in danger
Maybe someone can know
Romantic shop witch
Mr.Puzhu
What do you mean?
Puzhu is here today
I want to recommend someone
Join the Sword Club
Nujia Western Peach
Met Sword Master Shao
Shen Daxia
i know who you are
No need
Mr.Puzhu
you
You want to introduce this witch
This battle
she helped us
really
It was she who helped Mr. Puzhu
Killed Qiaoyi Qiankun
The slave family knows the romantic shop well
Do many evil things
Selling evil pills
Bringing disaster to the martial arts world
I have long wanted to draw a clear line with him
I hope all sword masters will put aside their past grudges.
Give the slave a chance
Buy
List of people who have taken evil pills
No one in the slave family knows
Will definitely help the Sword Club
clear romantic shop
Get rid of evil pills
OK
Then tell me now
Where is Piaoling Meiyuan?
Shen Daxia
I'm afraid the slave family will tell you
Innocent people who lost their lives in vain
It will be better than in the Xiuyu Peony Building
much more
Brother Shen
This matter is not suitable for discussion here
Xiaoshi is currently seriously injured
Come with me to see it first
It’s not necessary for outsiders, right?
Shen Daxia
There seems to be some prejudice against the slave family
The slave family is full of martial arts
All taught by Ghost Peony
his strength
The slave family knows best
He can defeat Tang Lici and Liu Yan
These remnant soldiers who met with swords defeated the generals
If you want to attack Piaoling Meiyuan
Just like hitting an egg against a stone
Brother Shen
Just let Western girls
Come in and talk in detail
western girl
Can there be more about Ghost Peony?
Information about Piaoling Meiyuan
Ghost Peony and others
no emotion
The slave family has been adopted by him for many years
But I just feel
he is a
Really without any emotion
monster
my end
no better than those
The rotten puppet
How much better
This is also a slave family
The reason for surrendering to the Sword Society
I know you still have doubts about me
I will prove it with facts
my value
Isn't Mr. Tang very dangerous?
Sword Master Shao
Western girls are very honest
Mr. Puzhu might as well listen to her.
As for attacking Piaoling Meiyuan
The slave family can only say
Every one of his plans
All precise and perfect
every judgment
They are absolutely sane
such a person
If he still stays where he is
That means
He is absolutely sure
to ward off all intruders
Am I afraid of him?
This time I agree
Must save people
People here don’t believe it
Is there me
plus puzhu
Plus Shen Langhun and Chi Yun
Neither works
The slave family doesn’t want to refute the senior’s face
But I have to tell you for sure
no
at least for now
When everyone is injured
Even if we add Sword Master Shao and me
Neither works
i can give
The location of Piaoling Meiyuan
But there is no doubt that
Let everyone die
What monster?
So powerful
But don't worry, everyone
If Ghost Mudan wants to kill Mr. Tang
Then he would have taken action long ago
So what is his purpose?
Although he is not dead
But it’s not alive
What’s the explanation?
resurrection
It requires a body
As long as there is no body
He is not resurrected
He didn't want to kill Mr. Tang
He wanted to use Mr. Tang’s body
Resurrection of Yin and Yang (Watch on www.kisskh.ws to support Admin)
where is this
are you looking for this
really
The inner strength is also sealed
Weibo Sna Sina Entertainment Go to Weibo, follow @MangoTV @微博tvtv, participate in the #水龙音# topic discussion, and unlock more exciting content!
Come out
Mr. Tang insists on seeing me
Only then are they willing to eat
Who is the girl?
means
Really awesome
What a pair of innocent eyes
I really can't see any scheming.
always
Mr. Tang, who considers himself a strong man
You were deceived by a weakling like me
Unexpectedly
It was fake from the beginning
The class leader thinks it's an ordinary strategy
Can't fool the young master
So I wiped out my memory
He exchanged it for the Bible
Exchange my blood with the divine stone
That's why my blood can save the young master
And all this
In fact, it’s all the class leader’s plan
Wait until they get it
what they want
The prince's death has come.
Tang Gongzi
To only you
fool others
design others
Let's circulate in heaven
OK
Tang admitted it
I'm just thinking about a question
what is true
what is fake
Who won't harm you
ok
Who wants to be with Mr. Tang?
no reason
I just want to save the young master
As soon as Mr. Tang asked this question,
Is the loser
Because this shows
you are hoping
There is real existence
so
This makes you happy
Want everything
Mr. Tang is in control
Will also care
Little girl to you
Is it sincere?
How could you be unhappy?
my feelings for you
It's all fake
First meeting from Jinye Temple
It's fake
Sir, please have a meal
The class teacher is still waiting for you
I'm here too
wait for him
There is no wife in a thousand years
Dangyo old Japanese words
I’ll call you Tang Lici from now on.
you can't die
Use the past life spectrum in exchange for merit
Take away the evil spirit from you
switch to me
my body is different
I can heal myself
this is the only way
Tang Gongzi
Good evening
class leader
this drama
I had a lot of fun acting
Compared with whether you have done your best or not
I want to know more
how did i act
clumsy
They all said I acted very well
Because they are not human
You are not human either
you are like them
Just a puppet
Que Yin Yang's Puppet
discovered by you
Might as well
Let Tang Mou guess
Tang is reversing his dream
The one I experienced
Battle of Tiandu Peak
Not the original battle of Tiandu Peak
And the real first
During the Battle of Tiandu Peak
Que Yin Yang wins
All seven masters died
among
Also includes Fang Zhou
But even so
In a yin and yang
on what you really want to do
He failed
Tang Gongzi
Why such a guess?
Yin and Yang are the same as Tang
is a smart person
Won't go to a lot of trouble
So useless
Tang is here
Reversing experiences in dreams
With the full power of Yin and Yang
seven masters
No chance of winning
He asked you to design Fang Pingzhai
Lead me into upside down dreams
Want more than just
The power of bone cleansing silver
Instead, let Tang Mou
Stop him from the past
Kill Fang Zhou
If what he really wants to do
Successful
Why should he suffer?
Looking back in time
So that thing
It must be very important to him
So much so that he did not hesitate
give up one's body
Let this be accomplished too
Tang Gongzi
Really smart
Then let Tang Mou guess again.
What Que Yin Yang really wants to do
what on earth will it be
With his ability comparable to that of a god
What else is going on
He can't do it
All he has left is killing
no weakness
why not yet
Perfect celestial body
Need to complete the practice as soon as possible
Only in this way can great achievements be successfully achieved.
Is there a possibility
Paik Namjoo’s so-called great cause
What I want to do with Yin Yang
It's the same thing
And this thing
I want a bronze pillar
And perfect
celestial body
The cultivation direction of Ketian human body
It was wrong from the beginning
When he first came to China
Encounter in Gumo Junior High School
make his body
infected with malice
No more perfection
therefore
He began to design Tang Mou
so everything
That makes sense
so
He couldn't let Fang Zhou
Died in the battle of Tiandu Peak
because
He wants Fang Zhou, who has great love in his heart, to
Picked up Tang
Bring back Zhou Dian Lou
Teach carefully
Let Fang Zhou die again because of Tang Mou
Cause Fang Zhou to die
Become in Tang’s heart
unbreakable dream
with this
Let Tang Mou reverse his dream
Stop him from killing Fang Zhou
And he did all this
ultimate goal
Just let Tang Mou
Go on a path
A completely different path from his
Experiencing seven emotions
perfect in the end
past cause
That is the current result
It is also the cause of the past
What a perfect closed loop
Just now
Tang said that the cast member's performance was poor
Just because
Zhou Lou’s drama
alive
ill
There is death
And all this
It will make people feel bitter
hatred and bitterness
love parting pain
Can't ask for pain
But if there is no emotion
You won’t feel the pain
That's natural
Of course it can't be acted out
Then Master Tang taught me
It seems
Although the class leader has no human feelings
But there is already people’s curiosity
Curiosity killed the cat
Also killed the puppet
Not as good as
Tang and the class leader
How about making a game?
game
Mr. Tang is a ghost Peony
treated as a child
When Tang first arrived in China,
unreasonable
Fang Zhou
Then based on the Three Character Classic that young children read,
I'll teach you
meaning
I still don’t know what feelings are
So Mr. Tang taught me through games
this makes sense
what game
Que Yin Yang
Designed so much
Here's a trap
Don’t the class teacher want to know?
How is Tang feeling?
The class teacher can ask me questions
and among these masks
choose one
What do you think is in line with Tang’s mood?
interesting
Then let me ask Mr. Tang
Learn about your experience in China
It's the master's secret design
What's your mood
I guess
is anger
Wrong
It's pleasure
I want to thank a yin and yang
if not for him
so carefully arranged
How can I meet Fang Zhou
How can I have it?
Zhou Dian Lou Na
Beautiful seven years of memories
Then Mr. Tang learned that
I designed Liu Yan to come back early
Causing your rescue to fail.
just to make you
A qualified container
Let him be resurrected and return to the world
this time
It's time to be angry, right?
Class leader
you are wrong again
Want Tang
the perfect container
More than one yin and yang
When in heaven and human realm
Tang has already experienced it once
and experience it again
I just think it's ridiculous
Then who is that?
You should be angry about this, right?
Quantum · Da Wenzi · Da Da meets again after thousands of turns