Shajintao Haiyuan originates from the desert organic core production area
Captured the essence
Quite similar
This one is most similar to
Who is this guy with a sinister face?
What bastard drew this?
lower your voice
Don't expose your whereabouts
Do I still need to pretend?
you ask them
You are Chi Yun
brothers
catch them
Where are the people?
over there
chase
Look over there
follow me
Old Shen you
Chi Yun
You're dragging us down again
This picture
He can recognize me
I told you that the one that looks most like you is the one
This is gourd chicken
Fried three delicacies
Potato fish
Ziyang Steamed Basin
Warm shredded duck
Dear bosses
The dishes have been served
Use it slowly
Tang Fox
Where are you?
Looks like he's wanted
You are obviously here to enjoy it
i am indeed
What's this
From Jinzhou to Sanqin
Lots of delicious food
Take notes first
will not be missed
If you miss the delicious food
But you will regret it for the rest of your life
You actually made one
Food map
Let me help you take a look
What is this delicious
This is called honey gulu
Prepared with flour and eggs
hook up with honey
Crispy on the outside and crispy on the inside
Both sweet and fragrant
It is a popular snack in the Sanqin region.
but
You ordered so much
Can you finish eating?
not much
This is not much
More over there
Shangzhi Pork
Stir-fried Pork with Lotus Vegetables
steam pot
guest officer
as you command
All dishes in the store
It's all ready
Please use it slowly
Can you finish it after ordering so much?
Have a good meal and come back next time
OK
How many guests are there?
get out of the way
Get out of my way
I heard there is a yin and yang
with his followers
All in this inn
Where are the people?
Where are people?
Finally able to have a meal
Don't even eat it
I'll come back to eat
Clouds in the sky and clouds in the pond
Who wants to step forward and get beaten?
kill me
Chi Yun said he would keep it for him
he will think
It's what you eat
Shen Langhun, Shen Langhun
Such a delicious meal
Your Mightiness
Not satisfied?
i don't eat much
But I want to try every dish
What do you think?
These dishes are very good
I don't understand what's so good about it
Just this gourd chicken
Whole chicken
Simmer over low heat for half an hour
Salt
sugar
Onion and ginger
Rock sugar soy sauce seasoning
Then add pepper
cinnamon
star anise
Cloves, bay leaves and other condiments
fill in it
Stew to bring out the aroma
Deep fry again
Just this one dish
will cost
More than an hour to cook
Your Mightiness
But the food is tasteless
Make such a dish
to spend
So much time and effort
Is it worth it?
Don't do anything useless
why
Send a life of destiny
If there is no pursuit
What joy is there in life?
meaning
If there is no pursuit
What's the fear of death?
You are a smart man
If this is the case
If a person gets
What you want to pursue
Then you should die without regrets
Maybe
If you chase to the end
Ten found out that it was a cliff
Or never get it
Then don’t hit the wall and don’t look back.
I envy the young master
There is something you want to pursue
I also envy the young master
It takes so long to pursue
Looks like delicious food
Not what I want to pursue
What do you call me?
Ghost Peony
Below
Tang Fox
You ate my honey gulu
It’s not advisable to stay here for a long time
The pursuers will only get more troops and retreat first.
See you later
please
Mr. Fox of Tang Dynasty
Nice to meet you
Furthermore
If a person does
all things to do
Still can’t find what I want to do
Bill, please
guest officer
There are so many dishes left
What a pity
Is there anything you want to do?
Why did the guest officer suddenly ask this?
How can there be a small one?
What do you want to do?
There are old people and young people here.
make money
Make a lot of money
Just in this small life
most want to do
This is enough for you
Earn money for a lifetime
Enough, enough, enough
a small life
You can't make so much money either.
Thank you for the reward, guest officer
Is there anything else you want to do?
there is none left
With all this gold
a small life
I don’t want to do anything anymore
Do you feel suspicious?
Since I feel suspicious
Why not just try him
There is no murderous intent in him
Let him cause the trouble that should come.
Don't pay special attention to it
Tang doesn't care either
Xianggong Inn guest Fuwan
Innkeeper Fuwan Xianggong
Xianggong
come down
Come down
My husband, why are you climbing so high?
All done
nothing to do
Come down
Xianggong
Then there is no need to live anymore
Sir, come down quickly
Xianggong
They all fell like this
eyes
Come in
Why make your own decisions?
I don’t want to see the Lord suffer anymore
When did I say I suffered?
Lord
Even if the Lord is angry, I will say it
The Lord uses his own blood
Refining Thousand Gu Needles
In order to deal with Tang Lici
Not worth it
Tang Lici is not worth it
Lord does this
you are teaching me things
Lord
why are you here
The Lord treats Xiaohong like this
Don't worry
She grew from love to hate
Something to say
The class teacher is here
He is waiting for you at the Peony Pond
Don't keep following him
Something that can slip out of your hands
Only then will people reach out and grab it
my business
Don't worry about it
Oreo Crunchy Looks Thin and Crispy, But It’s Rich Oreo Crunchy Newly Launched
But it is
The person is worth the remaining spring Gagagunashi
The door is heavily closed in the Xiao Temple
Why did the Qing family come so late?
I'm afraid the class teacher forgot
I don't like to listen to opera
Why don't you speak up if you have something to say?
Since the Qing family wants slaves to speak frankly,
Then the slave said it directly
I won't stop you from taking revenge
But you can't take the romantic shop
Come and be a game
The girl next to Tang Lici
Went to the Central Plains Sword Club
She knows the romantic shop
The location of the stronghold?
Stronghold of Sword King City
It’s just an extraneous thing that can be cut off
harmless
That took three years
newly established waterway channel
After Tang Lici's death
There are countless three years left
Are you in trouble?
I'm attracted to you
Reproduce the ability of Kushinmaru the Demon King
You make the romantic shop grow
I'll help you get revenge with a romantic shop
This is mutual benefit
you want revenge
I don't care about you
But ignore the interests of romantic shops
How can the lonely king tolerate you?
cat playing with mouse
There are times when I get tired of playing
I am measured
Since the Lord said so
Then I'll be relieved
Give the Lord a message
I met Tang Lici in Sanqin
He is going west
Where do you think he is going?
obvious direction
Biluo Palace
But what I'm curious about is
The class leader met Tang Lici
But didn't take action
That's the Lord's toy
I don't dare to cross
Please honor me, Lord
Take advantage of this opportunity
Lord
Notify the Lord of the East and West Palaces
Catching up with Tang Lici
yes
Lord
Xiaohong knew she was wrong
let's go
Zaiyan
Tang Lici was not arrested and brought to justice
You just moved out of Tangsai for many reasons
And this time 0
You act so openly
Kill the gangsters
The evil deeds of private criminals
you
Zhong Chunji
Have you ever
Zhongyuan Sword will take it seriously
in the final analysis
This incident in Yanxian County should not be tolerated
If she started
Then he captured Tang Lici and brought him back to the Sword Club.
This Sword King City
How could it be messed up like this?
Although no one was injured
But the cost of destroying this city
You Zhong Chunji ask yourself
Can you afford it?
It’s a waste that you are still the master of Shanfeng Hall
I've said it before
this woman
Nothing big can happen
Pu Jianzhu
What's your attitude?
The real gangsters of Sword King City
It’s clearly Yu Qifeng
The case of Sword King City is full of doubts
The night before the trial
Yu Qifeng also set a trap
Want to frame Mr. Tang for murder
Mr. Pu Zhu can also testify about this matter.
You can invite him over
as if questioning me
In order to find clues about Xiewan
Tang Gongzi
Don’t hesitate to confront Sword King City
Collect past account books of Sword King City
While I'm waiting for the audit
There are not only villains
Destroy the ledger
Still intending to kill
Silencing innocent people
besides
You said I wanted to build the Sword King City
Responsible for the destruction of the city
But when the city was destroyed
I'm rescuing and evacuating people
And you
you
Where is the text?
I
you can question me
What he did in Sword Lord City
Juniors are frank and frank
Have a clear conscience
As a dignified sword master, you
How could you say this
narrow-minded and biased words
The world will think
Our Central Plains Sword Club
what place
Pu sword master you
When will the Central Plains Swordsmen meet again?
Take it lightly
Zhong Chunji
Chuner
Sword Master Shao
Angry Jiang spoke out
in public view
See you all
The golden pupil forehead seal in Tang Dynasty's poems
She said Tang Lici was innocent
That would be more appropriate
Bring Tang Li Ci to justice and bring Chen Ming to justice
rather than a private criminal
If you bring Mr. Tang back,
Isn't it
Just what the fancy shop wants
This is a stopgap measure
this is just
Your wishful thinking
You are a junior
Could it be compared with other sword masters?
Couldn't be wiser
justice in this world
Are you comparing who is senior?
Who has more power
Who has more
Who represents justice?
Zhong Chunji
It’s okay if the origins are not ordinary.
You can't even follow the rules now
Don’t you understand?
Jiang Jianzhu
Just say something stupid
Could it be
Even you don’t understand the rules anymore
To transcend the group generation
Start to replace Sword Master Shao
Have you taught your apprentice a lesson?
Wenbo dare not
Ke Shao Sword Master
you know
Now the people of the world
Everyone is eagerly looking forward to the sword meeting
able to capture the suspect
Find out the truth
And Zhong Chunji
As the master of Shanfeng Hall
But he repeatedly failed in his duty
Also made rude remarks
If not dealt with
I'm afraid it's hard to block the mouth of Youyou in the world.
What Sword Master Jiang said is true
I already thought
Zhong Chunji
No longer fit for duty
The position of the leader of Shanfeng Hall
We should establish new talents
Benefit Sword Club
Otherwise, let this black sheep go unchecked
misbehaving
Sooner or later everyone will follow suit (Watch on www.kisskh. ws to support Admin)
Order Zhong Chunji
Remove immediately
The position of the leader of Shanfeng Hall
As an ordinary disciple of the Sword Society
Dedicate one's crime and make meritorious service
I'm not convinced
You still have the nerve to be dissatisfied
Master often teaches me
Want me to do the right thing
But I clearly did the right thing
Why are you still being blamed?
be punished
Being bullied by these uncles
Chuner
Am I right?
I'm not convinced
The sword masters have made up their minds
Go back and pack your things
Move out of the master's room of Shanfeng Hall
yes
Disciple resigns
What kind of attitude is this?
Become the master of Shanfeng Hall
Isn’t that amazing?
For an outsider Tang Lici
He actually came to argue with us
I've said it before
Born in a lower class
Even more short-sighted
OTC Yang Granules National Drug Approval No. Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlushi AI Generation (See) No. 25123-00602 [For stomach burns, please follow the drug instructions or purchase under the guidance of a pharmacist and Taizhan is about to
OTC Yangweishu Granules, National Drug Approval No. Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Chengwan Yao Guangshen (Shi) No. 251231-00602 [Function and Indications] Nourishing yin and nourishing kidneys. Side effects are not clear. It is used for chronic gastritis, burning stomach, dull pain. Contraindications are not clear. Please buy and use according to the drug instructions or under the guidance of a pharmacist. Precautions: You must recharge your batteries first.
OTC Yangweishu Granules, national drug approval number Z34020289 Hefei Huayouwanyao Guangshen (Shi) No. 251231-00602 Function: Nourishing yin and nourishing the stomach. The adverse reactions are not yet clear. [Contraindications] It is not clear. For chronic gastritis, please follow the drug instructions or purchase and use under the guidance of a pharmacist. For detailed precautions, start nourishing the stomach today.
OTC Borrowing Neck Relief Drug Approval No. Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wan Yao Guang Shen (Shi) No. 251231-00602 [Function and Indications 1 Nourishing yin and nourishing the stomach, used for chronic gastritis, burning stomach and dull pain. Mr. Tang
OTC Yangdang Shusuo Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Anhui Yao Guangshen (Machine) No. 251231-00602 Adverse reactions are currently unknown: back inflammation, burning stomach, why are you standing there?
OTC Yang Sheng Shu Ling Dong Guo Yao Huaian Z94020289 Hefei China Resources Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wan Yao Guangshen (Shi) South No. 251231-00602 The adverse reaction is not clear. It is used for chronic gastritis and gastric burning. It is not clear. It is specially recommended to be purchased and used with instructions or under the guidance of a pharmacist. Please refer to the instructions for details.
OTC Please purchase and use according to the drug instructions or below. Please refer to the instructions for precautions.
Yangweishu Granules OTC 6 Yangweishu Granules National Drug Approval No. Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wanyao Guangshen (Shi) No. 251231-00602 [Function and Indications] Nourishing yin and nourishing the stomach, used for chronic gastritis, burning stomach, and dull pain. The adverse reactions are not yet clear. [Contraindications] are not clear yet. Please follow the drug instructions or purchase and use under the guidance of a pharmacist. Please refer to the instruction manual for details. The young master has a stomachache.
give me a little
Don't grab it
I also have a steamed bun
You said if we let it slip
What if someone comes to your door?
What are you afraid of?
What goes into your stomach
They can also let us
Can't spit it out
That's right
You'd better eat quickly
Next time
Still relying on you
To lure away the boss?
I don't want to go anymore
It hurts when he pinches people
You have to look at our brothers
If you don't go
What shall we eat?
We share blessings and share hardships
right
you have to go
that is
look
they are over there
Chase quickly
Don't let them get away
It was all Boss Tan’s fault that she did
It has nothing to do with us
Run quickly
Little bastard, stop
stop
little bastard
You're pretty good at running.
I see where you are running
You ran out
why betray me
Why
You're from out of town
It would be nice to give you something to eat.
Are you content?
That's right
You are contented
hillbilly
Be content, you
I have understood a truth since I was a child
a person without a home
Wherever you go there are outsiders
People's hearts are divided into distance and distance
Sharing peace and happiness
And share hardships
I thought the sword would be different from the outside
But why am I working so hard?
I want to be a heroine
But he suffered from diseases due to his birth
why i do good deeds
But repeatedly frustrated
Even innocent people suffer
But they are so high in the clouds
It seems someone is still angry
I didn't do anything wrong
Master was in Wanhua Hall before
Didn't answer my question
I told you to do the right thing
But I didn’t say after doing it
No need to pay the price
You have to pay a price for doing good deeds
What's the point?
Have you done something wrong or done something bad?
Don’t you have to pay the price?
Do good deeds
Even if you have to pay a price
Then I can feel at ease, right?
so
Is it difficult to be a good talent?
Our Central Plains Sword Club
Strive for justice
But people
Most of them have selfish motives.
The sword will be heavy but hard to heal
Masters of Swords
Of course, each party has its own strength
But if you want to truly unite people
United as one
I'm afraid it's necessary
more fresh blood
with thunderous means
Master, what does this mean?
Okay, don't be angry
this is only temporary
Master
Teach you a trick
My most powerful kung fu
take it
This is
Iron chopsticks
Yes
Push harder
Fall
go
Throw it away, what am I afraid of?
How about it
Do you feel in the mood?
much better
Fall again
Push harder
How about it
Feeling more comfortable?
Here
He is the most powerful master
The art of throwing chopsticks
Be angry next time
When you want to throw something
Just throw the iron chopsticks
Come on, it won't break
Come loud
It fell loudly
People will know you are angry
I don’t dare to mess with you anymore
Look at you
Those who smashed these vases and porcelain
It’s not worth losing money.
What if I hurt my hand?
That would be even less worth it.
This vase is nice
Gave it to me
I bought this with my own money
I want to take them all away
mean
alright
Then keep packing your things
Master is gone
Clean up slowly
Don’t forget the iron chopsticks
The new exercises that Master said yesterday
Have you studied
I studied but I don’t understand
that girl
Brother Gu
Sword Master Shao asked me to take you
Go and settle down
This way
here is us
The residence of the disciples of Shanfeng Hall
Usually there is no one around during the day
Everyone went to practice sword practice
Go ahead over there
It's where you live temporarily
If you need anything at ordinary times
you can find me
Senior Brother Gu
can't find me
The same goes for finding them
Thank you, Brother Gu
If it weren't for you and Miss Zhong's help,
I don't even know where to go
Don't say that
Before Mr. Tang left,
But you told me well
let me take care of you
It's just a little effort on my part
Tang Gongzi
Tang Fox
I really don’t want to take that girl with me.
Return to the Central Plains Sword Club with Miss Zhong
for her
is a better choice
What I said just now was a bit harsh.
but
i hope you remember
your physique
Never mention it to others
don't let yourself fall into
in unnecessary danger
Where is Mr. Tang going?
Take good care of yourself
Don't worry
that girl
I'm fine
Then I'll take you to your room
pebble
Stop playing
It's time to eat
Stop heaping rocks like you
I'm talking to you
Did you hear that?
Don't
Senior Brother Gu
You just wanted to bully Xiaoshi
No no
Absolutely not
Put the food here
When Xiaoshi wants to eat
He can eat it himself
yes
Is your name Xiaoshi?
that girl
Little stone
don't talk to anyone
half a year ago
There is a leader of a small sect in Lizhou
Together with the disciples suddenly went crazy
massacre
an entire village nearby
Sword Master Shao went to investigate in person
In a shabby house in the village
Found
The little stone huddled in the corner
He must have been stimulated by something
That's how it will turn out
It seems now
It should have been
The romantic shop is causing chaos
Spread the Oranguki Kyushin Pill there
Sword Master Shao
What a kindhearted person
After Xiaoshi arrived at the Sword Club,
Never said a word again
like this every day
Keep piling stones
So we called him
He can move such a big stone
Xiaoshi's strength
Much older than ordinary children
But character
you saw it too
pebble
Weibo na Sina Entertainment on Weibo, follow @MangoTV @微博tvtv, participate in #水龙音# topic discussion, and unlock more exciting content!
what do i think
He looks a bit like Mr. Tang.
That girl, are you kidding me?
Tang Gongzi is handsome and unrestrained
eloquent and eloquent
Xiaoshi can't talk at all
Can't even speak
I don't know either
Just an intuition
that girl
Let me take you to your residence first.
you two
I'm so exhausted
Still eating
It’s like watching a show
I'm taking action
Immediately left behind
I am a patient
How is your injury?
Can't die
But take action
Avoid it if you can
Just ask me to work
You were originally my guard
Even if you are a cow
It needs to take a breather while plowing the fields.
this is already
This is the third wave today
Let's keep showing off like this
Hit the road
That's not an option either.
The whole world is looking for it
It doesn't matter where I hide
These ordinary martial arts people are okay
But we have been dragged along like this
Sooner or later the romantic shop will catch up
Especially those willow eyes
And what?
You're talking about Western peach
peach tricolor western peach
she is strong
Deep internal strength
but
This is nothing
she
Very good at waiting for the opportunity
That time she stabbed me in the stomach
Almost cut off the meridians
It's a well-disguised snake
romantic shop
Won't give you a chance to breathe
Bait like Tang
It's worth all their efforts
Who knew you were Tang Hu?
What kind of medicine is sold in the gourd?
So what should we do now
Should I still follow your map?
Brother Zhao Brother Zhang
Brother Wang
haven't seen you for a long time
this time
He must be arrested and brought to justice
Someone is chasing me again
Leave first
that girl
tea please
Do you have anything to do with Shao?
The case of Sword King City
The one who followed me from beginning to end
Mr. Tang really wanted to
Find out the truth about the Oranguki Kyushin Pill
Just got framed
Do you have evidence
Mr. Tang and Miss Zhong
Found the account books of Sword King City
elementary school girl
I took note of the suspicious things
Please take a look at it, Master Shao.
Wasn't the ledger burned?
Although those ledgers with clues
All have been burned
But the little girl still remembers
The suspicious location found at that time
X then sorted it out and memorized it.
It's all in this book
You have a good memory
Someone has already taken action on this matter
that girl
Can you accompany Shao for a walk?
That girl
This may be a bit offensive
But I've always wanted to ask you
Since you are
Survivors of the Hao Mansion Murder Case
Then why follow one?
suspected murderer
Although
He and that one
The black pipa player looks like
But after I saw him
Have an intuition
he is not that person
Mr. Tang not only found out the real murderer,
Still willing to take me in
The time spent with him
Who thinks
He doesn't want to be a bad guy
Not that he is a good person
Rather, say
He doesn't want to be a bad person
This is quite interesting to say
Don't blame him
Put you in danger?
He let one
He should have been
a person considered an enemy
Not only do I not resent him
Still willing to take risks for him
Doesn't this prove more
Can Mr. Tang be believed?
That
Shao
I want to trouble that girl
The group of people chasing now
Skills are weird
It should be a romantic shop
finally here
I bet you are here on purpose
wait for them
Talk to you later
Chi Yun
are you here
Send a signal
I really don’t miss the old feelings
It seems
Miss Bai doesn't want
has something to do with you
Then she is also my wife
learn to respect others
How can I not respect her?
Bai Su car meets the Lord of the East Palace
Lord of the West Palace
Where is Tang Li's resignation?
I followed it here
don't know why
lost track here
It seems that Mr. Tang
Not good at hiding and escaping
Then send a hammer signal
Are you trying to scare the snake?
Fucui
You can't hit a woman to vent your anger
you are my subordinate
I can't understand this at all
I'll tell you something next time
Can't do it better
I will tear you apart
The way to Biluo Palace
There are only two in the southwest
Let's go south
Always able to intercept Tang Lici
What about West Road?
No one can leave there
Walk
Just rub it and it'll be fine soon
Thank you Lord West Palace
All girls
Take care of each other
Subordinates dare not
He dared to hit me just now
Dare to hit Miss Bai
Don't let me catch you
If he catches me, I'll beat him to death.
Don't worry
that person
You will definitely meet again
next time
with interest
Where did the pigeon come from?
We are running away
who are you writing to
Mr.Puzhu
Report to Mr.
boats from pier
Fifty boxes of evil pills were found
then
It’s the Jingnan sect
I go first
Now you two have a relationship
It's all so good
What the hell is going on?
He has been checking
The romantic shops along the road
When did it happen?
when you sleep
I asked Brother Shen to check for me.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
The reason why you deliberately exposed your whereabouts
That's it
Who arrived at the Sword Club
Will definitely say it
The clues we found
The Sword Club will definitely follow this
Check the location of the romantic shop
expose one's whereabouts
Attract the main force of romantic shops
to the maximum extent
Avoid casualties caused by swords
Brother Shen, please help me investigate along the way.
The rest of Fengliu Shop’s strongholds
Can you be a swordsman?
Get rid of more popular shop influence
One more thing
Go to Biluo Palace too soon
no meaning
Really go to Biluo Palace?
It seems
The reputation of Biluo Palace
Like thunder piercing the ears
That's the most mysterious place
More mysterious than the thirteenth floor
No one has been to Biluo Palace
Or rather
no one can live
Coming out of Biluo Palace
everyone knows
It is located in the northwest
But I don’t know its specific location
then
Someone has been there
and
Came back alive
Search "Super Live" on Mango TV on the M Mango card you want to get married, and grab a huge number of performance tickets!
Quantum · Da Da Wenzi · Da Da meets again after thousands of turns