[Translate By Machine]
[Good Translate will available later]
Now that Mr. Puzhu has arrived,
Why hide
It's cold and windy outside
Please join in
have a taste
Prepared by Tang himself
Good wine and good meat
It's Mr. Puzhu
Keep the commandments
Mr. Tang’s wine and meat
I'm afraid I can't bear it
Or sacrifice it to those of the Ranqing sect?
It's a waste of your life
Mr. thinks
I was the one who killed those people
Even if you are not Mr. Tang
It's also about you
It's really blinding
Still say
Mr. Pu Zhu and the Central Plains Sword Club
willing
Being teased by this Sarukimaru Shinmaru
The sword cuts off all the people in the world
On the 13th floor
Shen Langhun
this is
The evidence you want me to see
Injured
West wind cuts wild fire
The Sword King is always by my side
When did you meet him?
Very strange
Mr.Puzhu
I'm afraid I fell into Yu Qifeng's trick
Yu Qifeng kills people and silences them
Not surprising
Damnable
will not become alive
Yu Qifeng will always be exposed one day
So Mr. Tang deliberately
Take me to Tianyan Jianbi
The purpose is to force Yu Qifeng to take action
Putting the blame before the public trial
Shen Langhun
it's you
And Mr. Puzhu
I happened to be this witness
to prove
The Shen Langhun I’m chasing
is fake
Just give in
King Yu Jian who relies on his cleverness
Make one for Brother Shen
alibi
Shen Langhun
A good general knows everything
Rat steals food
Is it possible to be caught by a cat?
And coincidentally at the same time
Trapped in a mousetrap
Of course I can't
That
Mousetrap
Mouse with tail clipped off
Not the one on Cat's hand
This is just
The words of Tang Gongzi and his family
I won’t try to clear myself of suspicion.
Just for Mr. Puzhu
I know someone else is suspicious
Don’t just stare at Tang
Don’t you want to know, sir?
You didn't catch it today
that mouse
Where do you come from?
tomorrow noon
Sword King City
Huxinting
Please give me a call, Mr. Tang.
You still didn't say
You and the monk outside
What's the point of selling?
Mr.Puzhu
He is a lay disciple of Tianjing Pavilion
You and that rat
What's the point of selling?
Mr. Puzhu is a cat
What about the mouse?
Of course the mouse is
Lao Shen always wears black
He also likes to hide in the shadows and kill people
Really looks like a mouse
This makes me angry
Not so much
Brother Chi, what's wrong with you?
Zhongmei
That
Old Shen also went to the dungeon
How to prove
He didn't kill Jiang Qingyu
No proof required
Because no elution is needed
my suspicion
Just let Pu Zhu
Doubt Yu Qifeng
Purpose
Just reached
Tang Fox
You can do it
Don't be too happy too early
Why
I guess
The subsequent public trial in Qiongtai
That's Yu Qifeng
The key to a comeback
Hongmen Banquet
Then let's go
Of course I want to go
One is the time
It’s mainly anti-customer
red girl
Unexpected
Puzhu's Light Technique is really powerful
Almost exposed
You put all your effort into
Bring Puzhu in
He didn't take anyone away
Shen Langhun was not captured
Why
You didn't reveal anything
But that Yu Qifeng
Revealed
I do not understand
Lord why?
I have to borrow this idiot's hand
To deal with Tang Lici
Even if the Lord doesn’t believe us
Call the Lord of the East and West Palaces
Still can't deal with Tang Lici?
We are in Sword King City
There are more important things to do
That Yu Qifeng
Don't worry about his life or death
The leader has been lost
Brother Chi
Drinking on an empty stomach is not good
Have some sugar water
Not happy
Lao Shen followed
Don fox goes to fight
Thanks
I am a great master and the clouds are in the sky
You can only drink sugar water here
This move
Could it be him
It's an old friend here again
He is too sarcastic
That's really a hello to say hello to
Rarely seen in my life
Swearing without exposing one's shortcomings
little beauty
That scene just now
It’s the people from this mountain who are meeting you.
Everyone has a sad face
Deliberately making you happy
And carefully prepared
Is it realistic?
Just accept that girl
otherwise
Senior Xue is afraid that in the next year
Everyone will be embarrassed because of their talent
And not a single day's sleep
thank you
Yuki Xianko-senpai
I was the most worried person just now
Do I have it too?
flower
have
Have food to eat
Eat first
Let's eat
I didn't say that
My snow line
Born to enjoy happiness
you see
Although I owe you money
But don’t you still have to
Will you provide me with fine wine and delicious food?
Just focus on this
you are interesting enough to me
on this clothes
If there is one more fingerprint
What is your repayment period?
I'm afraid I'll have to add another year
This little fox
Wear gold and silver every day
Wealth should not be revealed
Do you know
I'll come
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming
Seniors, seniors, seniors
I have admired my senior for a long time in Chiyun
Senior is on Tiandu Peak
Fight against the nine villains of the Bliss Sect
Sweeping thousands of troops on Mao Ya Peak
One move of sword energy
Just let the Jiangling Yu family
Head of the Yang family in Jiangling
Don't even dare to fart
What a heroic gesture this is
This native has been lazy for a long time
Don’t mention trivial matters again.
Don't mention it again
senior
I'm here
There is a treasured portrait
would like to invite you
Me me me this
Come
Senior, press this button
Press on your heart
Like pressing on my heart
But seriously
Old Man Yu's West Wind Cutting Wild Fire
There is indeed something wrong
Eight Winds Phoenix Sword Code
It has always been driven by Haoran’s righteousness
But in his sword intention
There is a very serious evil spirit
so
Just a Yu Qifeng
It's already enough of a headache
if
Your neck friend
Come to your door proactively
The two join forces
You fox brain
I have to be chopped down by someone again
Dragon Tiger Skin Wind Claw King Xiaolu Tiger Skin Phoenix Claw It’s still you Wang Xiaolu WANG XIAO LU
Note: This product is for external use. Contraindications: It is prohibited for patients with umbilical disease. Please read the instruction manual or purchase and use it under the guidance of a pharmacist. Tuan Co., Ltd. OTC Dinggui Dingguier Umbilical Patch for External Use to Treat Diarrhea invites you to continue watching.
Fri so PRESTIGE double hard-core strong inner protection | Royal Meisu Jiaer invites you to continue watching Royal Meisu Jiaer
certainly
if there is one
A rare expert in the world helps
Just twenty thousand
I can barely do it
Need not
How about we negotiate a price?
Before leaving Sword King City
If I still need you
you have to help
Don't play Puzhu
Don’t beat Yu Qifeng
I won’t hit your mortal enemy
Of course not
If you are beaten to death
Tang
Who can I go to to collect my debt?
Hello little fox
Ten thousand is ten thousand
Yingke live broadcast Yingke live broadcast meets the beautiful TA
Noon is approaching
Should Mr. Tang set off?
Went to the appointment with Mr. Puzhu
Why do you need tactics to get along with your husband?
Sincerely
Mr. Puzhu last night
And Zhu captured Brother Shen
What happened this time between Yu Qifeng and Fengliudian
Killing with a Borrowed Knife
Already disintegrated
Want to win from behind
The Yu family must be
Contact us
exposed to the world
Leveraging your strength is the best option
But Yu Qifeng is not stupid
I will definitely hide the incriminating evidence.
A dog is in a hurry to find its owner.
Tang Fox
Where is my mission?
I'm such a big person standing here
Can't you see it?
Be calm and don't be impatient
Mr.Puzhu
Blessings come this time for evil pills
We have to help him
Find Yu Qifeng
Evidence of getting involved in evil pills
Only then can we have the bargaining chip to cooperate with him (Watch on www.kisskh.at to support Admin)
only
Is this evidence of guilt?
Hidden very deep
But I have my own way
Let the evidence of crime come to your doorstep
This most difficult task
About to fall
On your head, Chi Daxia
Am I so important?
Say it
What do you want me to do?
this task
Natural, interesting and beautiful
and
There are three more hands
Guaranteed to be very stylish
Just what I want
What?
What kind of job is this?
So Mr. Tang
Tell us to gather here
just for
Take a look
It's fragrant and sweet
Shaobing
boss
Have a bowl of wontons
It's you who come
There are too many people here
You come
What
Master of Wanqiao Zhai Zhai
yes
It's the Master of Wanqiao Zhai
It is said
This person is a relative of the emperor
In charge of royal procurement
Money handled each year
There are half the world's giants
That is purchasing
Then there is always water transport, right?
Just don't know them
Which boat company did you use?
It seems that what I heard is
them
They are here this time
Just to find one
suitable fleet
Come and help them transport the goods
Wanqiaozhai
Rich all over the world
What kind of treasure doesn’t exist?
The deal is done
Must be rich
only
don't know how
connect with them
It's easy to say
Wanqiaozhai in Sword King City
Open a semicolon
It's when you need boat help
they only ask
Cooperate with major customers for more than three years
Then we can go to the pier to discuss it in detail.
I think this is an important place for water transportation
There should be quite a few people who are qualified.
There should indeed be quite a few
I
I just happened to have collaborated with King Yu Jian
Where do you want to come?
It meets the conditions of Wanqiaozhai
Yeah
I am now
Just go and let the guy
Prepare the account books
so
This will prove your qualifications
I also have to prepare well.
no
Did you hear that?
What a great opportunity this is
I have to hurry too
Prepare the ledger
If you go late, your chance will be gone.
Tang fox fish has entered the pond
Sir comes and goes in a hurry
Not finished last night
I have to disturb you today
Before the young master quibbles
Puzhu
I have a few questions to ask
teacher's recitation
Hao Wenhou Murder Case
With the power of a young master
As long as the emperor takes action
Yang Shangqing will not
Killed and silenced
Jiangcheng
It’s not like I have to die.
Having an affair with Kyuki Kushinmaru
for them
It's just the difference between dying early and dying later
Yanmen incident
Even the master of Jiangmen
There is nothing you can do about it, Mr.
Young Master voluntarily entered the Yanmen Cage
It's to lure romantic shops into taking action
If not so
how to elicit
Yu Qifeng, the big fish
Then have you ever thought about it
Miss Zhong and your side
Yanmen was in danger because of this
There may be innocent people involved
People who were poisoned by the Oranguki Kyushin Pill
Isn't it innocent?
Sacrifice the innocent to save the innocent
not justice
It’s not something a hero would do
Tang is not a hero
I never thank myself for justice
These are real
In the face of conspiracy
It's all useless stuff
sophistry
stubborn
Please also invite young master
Leave Sword King City immediately
As for Yu Qifeng
The case of colluding with a romantic shop
I'll check it myself next time
Put it this way
Mr. Bao Jing knows
another mouse
Where did it come from?
The whereabouts of the romantic shop
gentlemen
With Sword Master Shao from the Central Plains Sword Club
Also been looking for
but found nothing
Is it right
want to find
The man behind the romantic shop
you
indispensable for me
As for the rest
Tang is not interested
So others live and die
Young master doesn't care
you can sacrifice everyone
Just to force that one out
Take care of human life
Leaving you here will cause endless troubles
Different ways
OTC’s national medicine Anhui Gongtai battle is about to begin
OTC Yangweishu Granules, National Drug Approval No. Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wan Yao Guang Shen (Video) No. [Function and Indications] Nourishing yin and nourishing, adverse reactions are not clear, used for chronic gastritis, stomach burning, contraindications] are not clear. If there is dull pain, please follow the drug instructions or purchase and use it under the guidance of a pharmacist. Precautions: You must recharge your batteries first.
OTC Zhishupin Pills National Drug Approval No. Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Anhui Medicine) Review (View) No. Tang Gongzi
OTC Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. It is not clear why the stomach is burning and it is stunned.
OTC pharmaceuticals are limited to side effects and side effects that are not yet clear. Dosage is regulated by the drug tax and must be purchased and used under the guidance of a pharmacist. Move your chopsticks.
OTC counts
OTC Yangweishu Granules, national drug approval number Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wanyao Guangshen No. [Functions and Indications] Nourishing yin and nourishing the stomach, used for chronic gastritis, burning stomach, and dull pain. Adverse reactions] are not yet clear. [Contraindications] are not clear yet. Please buy and use according to the drug instructions or under the guidance of a pharmacist. Please refer to the instructions for stomachache for precautions.
6 OTC Yangweishu Granules, national drug approval number Z34020289 Hefei China Resources Shenlu Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wanyao Guangshen (See) No. [Function and Indications] Nourishing yin and nourishing the stomach, used for chronic gastritis, burning stomach, and dull pain. The adverse reactions are not yet clear. [Contraindications] are not clear yet. Please buy and use according to the drug instructions or under the guidance of a pharmacist. Please refer to the instructions for precautions. I brought Sanjiu Weitai Yangweishu
It can also be a conspiracy
You and I are talking here
These useless thoughts
The man behind the scenes
Maybe something has been done
If the city is stormy again
This sin
After all, it belongs to Tang
Still belongs to Mr.
Sir, please let me take your pulse.
Candied haws
Come and take a look
small pendant
Fragrant and sweet
Thank you, guest
Please walk slowly
Mom, we have a paper kite
Finally I can fly the kite
Yes, you've got it
paper kite
Come and see
Fox Kite
guest officer
This is the third day of Mu Sword Festival
It happens to be the Double Ninth Festival
This fox kite symbolizes happiness and profit
do you want to buy one
This is the Double Ninth Festival
Best for flying paper kites
put
How could I let him go?
Get away
What kind of medical treatment do you have if you don’t have money?
Roll as far away as possible
Don't dirty our place
I still want to see a doctor if I have no money
Please do well
My chest
I'll do it
Get away
Consumptive ghost
I look at you
I can't live for more than a few days.
I'll do you a favor today
Take it to buy straw mats
This consultation fee
I accepted it
Try breathing three times
It really doesn't hurt anymore
Awesome
This young man has great medical skills.
The disease can be cured with just three injections
No more coughing or itching
benefactor
Thank you benefactor
My benefactor is really
The miracle doctor who hangs the pot to save the world
What a miracle doctor
amazing
Thank you benefactor
good
So awesome
miracle doctor
Awesome, awesome
good
miracle doctor
Awesome, awesome
I've been holding the murder knife for a long time
I almost forgot
What does acupuncture feel like?
Ali
This young man is not only kind
He looks so handsome
shallow
Who are you talking about?
You even appreciate Tang Fox
You definitely don’t understand this
Let's go to that girl
Only you have aesthetics
I don’t have aesthetics, who has aesthetics?
Don't know how to kill
Your new friends
what does it feel like
What's wrong, Brother Chi?
Let's go
fine
What was found?
Heartbroken
Qi pulse has been severed
Your time is running out
Why bother
Tang’s mood is no better than Mr.
No awareness to help all sentient beings
If you want to live
It must be
Find the owner of the romantic shop
He can save your life
Of course I can't
Then what do you want?
he can't
but find him
able
My husband and I are not antagonistic
can cooperate
Otherwise, both sides will suffer losses.
It will only make the oranguki Kushinmaru
Continue to poison the world
everything you do
All to save your own life
Just because
Tang only cares about himself
so
What I want from my husband
no contradiction
why should i
The unintentional people are complicit in everything
Extraordinary times
do extraordinary things
If we talk about everything
Nothing will be accomplished
Mr. Pu Zhu and Master Shao
You use fair and aboveboard means
no evidence found
As far as Tang is concerned
But it's not difficult
That's it
It's enough to make Mr.
Arrogant
Tang certainly has the arrogance
otherwise
Neither will Mr.
Come and test my truth in person
Civil strife in the Central Plains Sword Society
Sword Master Shao
Want to start from Sword King City
Clean up the romantic shop
But missing a good sword
Tang is not afraid of notoriety
Just this characteristic
for you
Just right
only
The point of the sword
It can only be the direction I want
Sir, if you still don’t believe Tang,
Not as good as
let's make a bet
What bet
Inside the Sword King City
List of all those who have taken evil pills
as well as
Sold by Yu Qifeng
Evidence of the Oranguki Kyushin Pill
tonight
I will send the list with evidence
Serve with your own hands
and
Never hurt an innocent person
What do you want
Mr. Chang cooperates with Tang’s actions
besides
Sir, please don't interfere.
The rest of the things in Sword King City
You won't join forces with me
Want me instead
Stop interfering
What to bet on
Sir, if you interfere in the affairs of Sword King City,
It means that Mr. lost
on the contrary
If Tang fails to
Give the list and evidence to Mr.
or
While catching Yu Qifeng
In the process
hurt any innocent person
It’s Tang who lost.
If Tang loses
I will hand it over to the Central Plains Swordsman Association by Mr.
Whatever happens
Red leaves are floating
red leaves around
Photos of the phoenix flower blooming
Test the sword
Flying a paper kite
Climb high and enjoy the Yanhuang Road together
Battle of Tiandu Peak
Fortunately the devil is dead
seven masters
Someone who is almost unbeatable
What kind of monster are you talking about?
If it weren’t for Patriarch Xuanqing
With Fang Xianzhu
How could there be such a prosperous situation as it is today?
What a pity, Lord Fang Xian
Such a good person
He died just like that
Ali
Ali, why do you want to kill me?
Thank you sir
What was the young master thinking just now?
So lost in thought
Can you help the little girl take a look?
These two hairpins
Which one is more suitable for the slave family?
This one
More suitable for girls
This hairpin looks better
This hairpin
Sharper and sharper
When a girl meets a bad guy
can be used to kill people
There are a lot of bones here
stab here
easier to get
Young Master is really interesting
The slave family remembers it
The owner of the restaurant wants to give him 30,000 taels of gold
Sincerely rent a treasure land in Qiongtai
For tomorrow’s banquet
Jiang Qingyu is dead
The person who committed the crime is Shen Langhun
Regarding this matter, Mr. Puzhu and I
For all to see
If Tang Lici cares about the truth
He should be the general Shen Langhun
hand it over
and explain it to all my martial arts comrades
Why do people commit crimes?
Will be his subordinate
The owner of the restaurant said that someone was setting the blame
The master also said
Only those who blame
Only then would he be as angry as the Sword King?
The master knows everything
It seems that the King of Swords is nothing more than that.
That's all
Tongyanwuji
Please also invite Sword King Haihan
but
Have this banquet
On the truth for everyone in the world
This is also what Mr. Pu Zhu meant
I don’t know the sword king
Can you change your mind?
I will allow you
Thank you Sword King
Please
Tang Lizi
Weibo Sna Sina Entertainment Go to Weibo, follow @MangoTV @微博tvtv, participate in the #水龙音# topic discussion, and unlock more exciting content!
I have given my own flesh and blood
Refined for four years
Wait until it is refined
it will be your weakness
Lord
you
What's up
Lord Yu Qifeng came to ask for an audience
Go back
The Lord doesn’t want to see you
Everyone thinks good plans and good things happen
Hidden scheming
Something big happens
Decisions are often made in a split second
Mostly driven by emotions
such as jealousy
anger
sad
Irrational behavior
Being looked at twice
Just scold the other person
Being insulted
It must be a fistfight
If a loved one suffers misfortune
I even want to let the other party
The entire clan was wiped out
Huiniang
blood for blood
promise me
If you meet Liu Yan
Never act rashly
why
I have my own way to help you take revenge
But now
see him
Want to escape
promise me
Normally speaking of righteousness
It's just that things didn't happen
on myself
Once it harms oneself, I will worry about it in my heart
It must be blood for blood
tit for tat
do you think
am i right
It's my method
but who are you
This look
you hate me
We have a grudge
Great revenge is avenged
are you happy
I remembered
your eyes
you like him
pity
With your little tricks
Can't kill me yet
Shen Langhun
life history
Although Tang Lici’s stuff is disgusting
But it still has some effect
Go to hell
Search "Super Live" on Mango TV on your M Mango Card and grab massive performance tickets!
Quantum · Da Da Culture Zi Da Da meets again after thousands of times
China Vision and Quantum: The cultural son Otter meets people thousands of times