"Simply One Song" - Hu Zhengjun
♫ Fortunately, I can't get what I want ♫
♫ The sky returns one night and the world is already in song ♫
♫ Unattainable in this life ♫
♫ It's an honor to have the privilege of parting ways at the end of the world ♫
♫ Heaven wishes for eternity, and people cherish the expanse ♫
♫ Not far from her, but nowhere near ♫
♫ The sky is turbulent, the finale about a hundred years later ♫
♫ Fortunately, my longing finally turns into a song ♫
♫ The leaving person waves and the shadow smiles,
racing all night through the vast sky ♫
♫ The trees of tranquility have not yet disappeared ♫
♫ Tears of the kind-hearted never cease to disappear, but they never stop ♫
​♫ Fortunately, the vast sky is wide open ♫
♫ I think and yearn for one night, I don't dare seek to grow old ♫
♫ There is no need to explain much in this world ♫
♫ If the heartache remains, it'll never stop ♫
♫ How? ♫
[Nancheng Banquet]
[Episode 10]
Where would Xiao Wanli put the list?
Xiao Qiangzi, what are you doing here?
Sister Xue Ru, I ate too much and my stomach hurts.
Where is the toilet?
- The toilet is over there.
- Okay.
Go quickly and come back soon.
This is the Chancellor's residence, don't wander around aimlessly.
All right, I'll be right back.
The weather is dry, be careful of fire and candles.
Boss, it's the dead of night.
- Split up and take action.
- Yes.
Boss, Xiao Qiangzi said he'd take care of the list.
She's going to steal the list?
Did you tell her to do that?
Yes.
I'll settle accounts with you when I get back.
Who is there?
There's a thief in the mansion! Search quickly!
Okay, let's go.
What are you so anxious about?
Lord, it seems a thief has entered the courtyard.
- A thief?
- Yes.
Father, what's the matter?
He says it seems a thief has entered the courtyard.
If there's a thief, why not hurry up and search?
Yes, sir! Let's go.
Father, have you destroyed the list of vermilion silver powder?
This is bad!
There's trouble, the list has been stolen.
Someone come here!
It's not here either.
Come and look over here.
Yes.
Search carefully.
Why are you here?
I… I came to look for the list.
I've already found the list, it's here.
Make sure you hold onto it well.
Take care, I'm leaving.
Quick! Come over here and take a look.
You two, go check over there.
Yes.
I knew it, you were worried about me.
My residence is strictly guarded, how could thieves get in?
Father, I believe there must be a traitor among us.
Why not gather everyone in the Xiao Residence and see who is missing.
Good! This is a good idea.
Xiao Qiangzi? Xiao Qiangzi, why isn't he here?
- Has anyone seen Xiao Qiangzi?
- Search carefully.
Xiao Qiangzi! All members of the Xiao residence, assemble.
Yes.
I must go back, otherwise they'll become suspicious of me.
What's wrong?
Be careful and stay safe.
You too.
Has anyone seen Xiao Qiangzi?
Reporting to My Lord, no.
Find that eunuch Xiao Qiangzi for me.
Yes.
I am here.
What's wrong? What happened?
Where did you go?
I just had a stomachache and went to the bathroom.
Sister Xue Ru gave me directions.
Sneaking around, there must be something wrong.
Guards, seize him.
Yes!
Stop!
He is not a bad person.
Father! Brother! Xiao Qiangzi would definitely not steal.
He is still useful to me.
Don't harm him.
Your Majesty.
Don't be afraid, I'm here.
Heng'er, be obedient and go back to your room first.
I trust Father will certainly handle this matter fairly.
Rest assured, I'm here.
We will definitely seek justice for Xiao Qiangzi.
Xue Ru, take the young lady back to the room.
Yes.
The thief is there; chase after him.
Yes, quickly, chase!
Quick, stop!
Take the imperial edict and notify the Ministry of Justice.
Advance tonight's action to avoid further complications.
[People Involved in the Vermilion Silver Powder Case]
All officials of the Ministry of Justice, heed my command.
By imperial decree, execute all involved in the vermilion silver powder case tonight.
[Household]
All on the list must be eliminated before dawn.
- Yes.
- Quick.
Thousand Feather Guards, heed my command.
Everyone on the list is a major criminal involved with vermilion silver powder.
Detain them all.
Kill without mercy anyone who obstructs.
Yes!
Listening to the movements, Xiao Quan is going to take action tonight.
Yan Changyun, you must be safe and sound.
[Fang Mansion]
You are…? This…
Let's go.
I wonder how they are doing now.
Dear Heaven, please bless them.
Don't let anything happen to Yan Changyun.
Bless him to come back alive.
Stop!
The Ministry of Justice is handling the case as per His Majesty's decree.
Are the Thousand Feather Guards defying the order?
The Thousand Feather Guards act according to national law, apprehending the criminals.
Anyone who obstructs us will be executed without mercy.
Kill all of the Thousand Feather Guards who defy the order and conspire against it.
Give it a try!
- Then bring it on.
- Everyone stop!
It's so late into the night,
you don't have to protect me anymore.
I'm very safe.
Lord Xiao has ordered that no one is allowed to enter or leave the Xiao Residence tonight.
I'm not going out; I'm just showing my head.
You two brothers have worked hard.
[Tumult at the Imperial Workshops]
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Xiao Wanli was so ruthless this time.
I'm afraid it's not just about eliminating vermilion silver powder.
Boss, we owe a lot to Xiao Qiangzi this time.
He got the list in time.
Why not call him back, then?
The two of you go to the other residences listed now,
and see if more people can be rescued.
- Yes.
Then what about you, Boss?
I have my own arrangements.
[Baisheng Gambling House]
[Sounds of Footsteps and Chattering]
Move, it's time to change shifts.
They're gone?
Jade Bone Whistle.
[Chancellor's Residence]
You were okay last night. Right?
You weren't caught by them, were you?
That's right. If you were caught, how could you be here?
The list, was the list useful?
Very useful. You've made a great contribution to the Thousand Feather Guards this time.
However, don't do this again in the future.
It's very dangerous, you know?
I know. How did you get the Jade Bone Whistle?
You threw it away. Of course, I took it back.
What? You want it back?
I was just asking.
Be careful in the Xiao Residence.
I'll leave first.
Wait a minute.
I told Her Majesty I'm taking leave; I can return to the palace early.
Can you take me back?
Yan Changyun. It's Yan Changyun again.
Why does he always have a conflict with my family?
This youngster acts in mysterious ways.
His interrogation methods are even more ruthless.
Now, half the people on the list are in his hands.
I really don't know what they will end up saying.
Father worries too much; they can't do anything to us.
What do you know?
Since he dares to openly oppose us,
His Majesty must be backing him.
Zhao Yuan has toughened up his wings now.
He even dares to scheme against me, both openly and secretly.
He wants to play the pig to eat the tiger.
And he thinks I can't see through it.
This coward Zhao Yuan can't stir up any trouble.
One Zhao Yuan is not a concern.
But when you add a Yan Changyun, it's hard to say.
With his strategies and malice,
he'll sooner or later become a formidable foe to my Xiao Family.
No, I must write a memorial to denounce him immediately.
Yan Changyun must die.
I'm afraid that Zhao Yuan won't execute Yan Changyun so easily.
That's not up to him.
I had Heng'er marry him, just to make him be of use to me.
But unexpectedly, this Zhao Yuan thinks too highly of himself.
But it doesn't matter.
As long as Heng'er can get pregnant with a prince,
then the older one can be deposed if he doesn't obey
and the younger one can be promoted to the throne.
Heng'er!
Could it be that father had me marry His Majesty just for this?
You want me to have a child just so you can dethrone His Majesty?
So what?
Don't think that marrying Zhao Yuan means you bear the Zhao surname.
Don't forget, you're a Xiao.
If you don't obey, you'll be abandoned by the Xiao Family all the same.
Heng'er!
Heng'er, listen to me.
You are not anyone's castaway; you're my sister.
And even more so, you are of the Xiao Family.
Father just spoke in anger for a moment.
Don't take it to heart.
Brother, are you going to be like Father?
Desiring the power from His Majesty's hands.
How could I? What I want is not any of this.
I feel so confused right now.
Suddenly, this place feels so unfamiliar.
I don't want to stay here anymore.
The Imperial Palace is my home now.
Heng'er...
My Lord.
What's the matter?
Right now, the master wants to fight with Yan Changyun.
Yan Changyun's gaze will surely shift to the Chancellor's residence.
This may not be to our advantage.
Actually, the people Yan Changyun captured are of no use.
Why don't you tell the master that the list is fake?
Letting my father make a fuss like this might not be a bad thing.
Only in this way can we truly deceive Yan Changyun.
When the fake passes for real, the real also becomes fake.
As long as we play this act more realistically,
our people will be safer.
How should we deal with the matter of the vermilion silver powder?
Of course, we can't stop.
Vermilion silver powder can trouble the Southern Kingdom and help me raise an army.
Why not do it, then?
I've been planning this for so many years.
How could I possibly allow it to be destroyed overnight?
This is just the beginning.
Understood.
Where is he? Gone?
Boss, how is it going?
[Affidavit]
These people have nothing to do with the powder.
But they all have some grievances with the Xiao Family.
The list is fake.
Fake? Then why did the Ministry of Justice kill them?
Xiao Wanli is using vermilion silver powder to eliminate his adversaries.
He also wanted to use vermilion silver powder to harm the loyal and good 15 years ago.
So many people died unjustly overnight.
With so many new and old grudges, his crimes are unforgivable.
Your Majesty, the memorial by the Chancellor requires your immediate attention.
They won't even let me rest during my period of rest.
Your Majesty, Her Majesty has returned to the palace.
What? She's come back after just one day?
I don't know.
Her Majesty has returned to the palace, and locked herself alone in the room.
She looks as if she's not sick or troubled.
This is not like her. What happened?
[Petition for Your Majesty to Eliminate the Treacherous Yan Changyun]
Xiao Wanli wants me to kill Yan Changyun.
Good. It seems that Yan Changyun has caused Xiao Wanli quite a bit of trouble.
He was even forced to personally submit a petition asking me to execute someone.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
My beloved minister, come and tell me.
What happened last night?
Last night, Xiao Wanli, along with the Ministry of Justice,
killed many people under the pretense of investigating the vermilion silver powder.
I have snatched a few witnesses from the Ministry of Justice.
After investigation, it was found that these witnesses
had no connection with the vermilion silver powder.
I suspect Xiao Wanli intends to eliminate his opponents.
This Xiao Wanli.
Blatantly breaking the law; he's too arrogant.
I beseech Your Majesty to decree a thorough investigation into Xiao Wanli.
[Emulating the Worthy]
This is the petition he just submitted.
He accuses you and your people of not obeying orders, and wants me to have you executed.
If Your Majesty thinks that I have done wrong,
then you can do whatever you want with me.
What are you talking about?
Xiao Wanli manipulates the government and forms factions for personal gain.
Without you, I would truly become a lonely ruler,
and become his puppet.
If I agree to your thorough investigation of Xiao Wanli,
do you have full confidence in bringing him down?
I do not.
Indeed, most of the court are now his supporters.
If there is not full confidence,
I'm afraid this man cannot be touched.
But if you can find evidence,
then perhaps we can turn the situation around.
I will certainly try my best, I will die for you.
Good, I will permit you to investigate him.
But this matter must not be rushed.
Thus, you will personally visit the Chancellor's residence tomorrow.
Ask him to cooperate with the investigation of the murder case at the Ministry of Justice.
Then severely punish the ministry personnel involved in the case.
I obey the decree.
Your Majesty, I believe in Commander Yan.
He certainly has the ability to overthrow Chancellor Xiao.
Of course, I believe in him.
It's just that I can't wait any longer.
The food of the Thousand Feather Guards is still the best, no?
You think this food is good?
Try it. Is it good?
Quite good.
Really?
Does the Thousand Feather Guards have no bowls left?
What's with him?
Commander Yan, don't be angry.
It's really not bad, you try it.
I won't drink it.
Boss, the porridge today is really good.
You should try it quickly.
You are responsible for serving food to everyone.
There are not even enough bowls for our brothers.
You have neglected your duties and still speak so artfully.
Go out; run 30 li as a punishment.
Get out of here quickly.
Yes.
Come on.
Commander Yan, I have something to ask you.
Speak your mind.
Were you scolded by His Majesty today?
He definitely got scolded.
His Majesty sings really well.
He is good at everything he does.
Why is His Majesty in disguise today?
And isn't he usually in the Miaoyin Pavilion?
Perhaps it's for me.
From His Majesty voice to his demeanor,
it's really quite like a woman.
Your Majesty,
do you think a man can possess feminine charm?
Perhaps.
Then do you think I have it?
It's over.
I've been pretending to be a man for so long, I've lost all feminine charm.
I won't always be like this, will I?
Where are you going so late?
I am going to the palace to bring Heng'er the toys from her childhood,
and cheer her up.
As the only son of the Xiao Family,
you don't consider the grand plans of our Xiao Family.
Running to the palace all day, what kind of example is that?
Father, for the power of the Xiao Family,
you've forced me to learn so-called power from a young age.
When I didn't want to learn, you found ways to torture me.
When you beat me until I was bruised and battered,
it was Heng'er who applied medicine to my wounds.
When you locked me in the woodshed and left me hungry,
it was also Heng'er who stayed by the door and fed me.
It was then that I swore to myself,
I would protect Heng'er for a lifetime,
and never let her suffer the slightest grievance.
Are you foolish?
Is Heng'er or the Xiao Family more important?
Let me ask you, Father.
Heng'er is my sister and also a member of our Xiao Family.
If I can't even protect my own family members,
what's the point in pursuing power and status?
She is not even born of your mother.
I know.
You know?
I saw with my own eyes when I was young, after you were drunk,
you forced yourself on a girl who came to deliver flowers to the mansion.
You…
Afterward, she became pregnant.
To cover up the scandal, you imprisoned her in the mansion.
After the birth of Heng'er, you then plotted to kill her.
And then you put Heng'er under my mother's name.
I'm right, aren't I?
But what you don't know
is that she was already pregnant before she entered the mansion.
Heng'er is not your child at all.
She has nothing to do with the Xiao Family.
What did you say?
Let me tell you! Now I'm the only support Heng'er has.
As long as my plan unfolds step by step,
that dog emperor, Zhao Yuan, will have to abdicate in my favor.
And for Heng'er, only I can give her happiness and freedom.
You beast.
You actually defy your father for a wild child.
Don't you dare give it to her.
[Chancellor's Residence]
Commander Yan, please wait a moment. I'll report your arrival first.
No rush.
Commander Yan, what a rare guest.
Lord Xiao,
I'm here to probe a murder and injustice within the Ministry of Justice.
I need the Chancellor's cooperation.
Since it is Your Majesty's decree…
[Chancellor's Residence]
Father, Commander Yan is here.
Father.
Father!
- Master.
- Dad.
Dad, what's wrong?
- Dad!
- Lord Xiao.
- Lock down the scene immediately and help Lord Xiao away.
- Yes.
- Speak to me, Dad!
Lord Xiao.
- Dad!
- Lock down the scene.
- Yes.
- Who harmed you, Dad?
[Guanyou]
Dad!
Great winds arise and clouds soar.
With strength to pull mountains and a spirit that covers the world.
Xiao Qiangzi. Xiao Qiangzi.
Take a look at how well I play the role of the overlord.
Your Majesty, don't you always play Yuji?
Why are you playing the overlord today?
Starting from today, I will learn how to play the overlord well.
I have many roles to play in the future.
Something happened.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, Chancellor Xiao is dead.
What?
Half of the Southern Kingdom has collapsed.
Chancellor, you have left us,
then what about the court?
- Your Majesty.
The dead cannot be brought back to life.
The Chancellor knows how much you value him,
then he must be grateful on the journey to the underworld.
He would also thank Heaven's grace, Your Majesty.
You must take care of your body, Your Majesty.
Who could be so cruel...
to murder the Chancellor?
Commander Yan, you must find out the murderer.
We must seek justice for the Chancellor.
I accept the decree.
Your Majesty, my father was killed in his own residence.
I would like to personally investigate this matter.
Lord Xiao, I'm sorry for your loss.
Since Your Majesty has already handed over this case to the Thousand Feather Guards for investigation,
then please stand back.
Yan will certainly uncover the truth.
I'll give everyone an explanation, and give Lord Xiao an explanation.
Your Majesty, my father was killed while investigating the vermilion silver powder case.
The words "Guanyou" have been found next to my father's body.
This must be related to Duke Ding's old case.
I believe it is definitely the old enemies of the Qin Family seeking revenge.
- Lord Xiao, what evidence do you have?
- The two characters "Guanyou" are the evidence.
Merely on the basis of the words "Guanyou," it is concluded that it was done by the old members of the Qin Family?
As the Ministry of Justice, Lord Xiao, aren't you being a bit hasty in concluding the case?
Commander Yan, what's your intention with these remarks?
Yan is simply speaking about the matter at hand.
Lord Xiao is so nervous like a man who fears the bow is a snake.
Could it be that you have a guilty conscience?
You defend the Qin Family so vehemently, perhaps you're the one guilty?
My beloved ministers, please stop the argument.
No matter if it was the work of the Qin Family or not,
the murderer must be thoroughly investigated.
A country's chancellor has been murdered just like that.
The killer is utterly lawless.
Where is the dignity of the Southern Kingdom?
Where is my dignity?
Such a major issue of defending the dignity of the Southern Kingdom,
is the responsibility of every citizen of the Southern Kingdom.
Not only the two of you can investigate,
all civil and military officials, state government offices,
anyone with clues can investigate.
No matter who it is,
as long as the murderer is caught, I'll reward heavily.
It must be related to Guanyou's old subordinates.
I can't figure it out.
Young Master, we've gone through untold hardships to find that Xiao Wanli is the man behind the vermilion silver powder.
How did he suddenly die and also write down the words "Guanyou"?
Who on earth did this?
It couldn't be Uncle Lei and the others acting on their own, could it?
Xiao Wanli held sway over both court and country.
Killing him would be an action that would affect everything.
Uncle Lei would never act recklessly.
Young Master, could it be that we have been investigating the wrong person from the beginning?
No.
It's precisely because we're getting closer and closer to the truth,
someone wants to confuse us.
This person...
knows Xiao Wanli better than we thought.
So, you're saying that the mastermind behind the Guanyou Incident isn't Xiao Wanli?
"Promise" - Jiang Yu Han & Wang Hong
♫ A vast sea of ​​people, long roads ♫
♫ A childhood meeting that is unforgettable in the passing years ♫
♫ There are many vicissitudes of life in the world, each side at the ends of the earth ♫
♫ The twilight falls and scatters, the moonlight comforts the parting dead ♫
♫ Going in circles, it's still the same as before ♫
♫ The human world has tender sentiments,
the word "love" is hidden in the palm of your hand ♫
♫ Drawing a sword to cut the water, the water keeps flowing ♫
♫ Time flies like water, yet I trust you have been well since we last met ♫
♫ Fierce horses and bright clothes, all to marry you in your bridal red ♫
​♫ Love amidst the vast sea, it's intoxication is the hardest to let go ♫
♫ What harm is there to give up this life for you? ♫
♫ I keep this tenderness to myself ♫
♫ To be drunk with you for a time ♫
♫ If I could truly fall in love with you ♫
​♫ Why should I be afraid of the wind and snow disturbing my heart? ♫
♫ Never giving up, never forgetting, never regretting is my heartfelt wish for you ♫
♫ If I could fill pages with my affection for you ♫
♫ Why fear the world's high mountains and long rivers? ♫
♫ One thought, one dream, a lifetime, I place you in my heart ♫
♫ If I could truly fall in love with you ♫
♫ Why should I be afraid of the wind and snow disturbing my heart? ♫
♫ Never giving up, never forgetting, never regretting is my heartfelt wish for you ♫
♫ If I could fill pages with my affection for you ♫
♫ Why fear the world's high mountains and long rivers? ♫
♫ One thought, one dream, a lifetime ♫
♫ I place you in my heart ♫