"Simply One Song" - Hu Zhengjun
♫ Fortunately, I can't get what I want ♫
♫ The sky returns one night and the world is already in song ♫
♫ Unattainable in this life ♫
♫ It's an honor to have the privilege of parting ways at the end of the world ♫
♫ Heaven wishes for eternity, and people cherish the expanse ♫
♫ Not far from her, but nowhere near ♫
♫ The sky is turbulent, the finale about a hundred years later ♫
♫ Fortunately, my longing finally turns into a song ♫
♫ The leaving person waves and the shadow smiles,
racing all night through the vast sky ♫
♫ The trees of tranquility have not yet disappeared ♫<
♫ Tears of the kind-hearted never cease to disappear ♫
♫ But they never stop ♫
♫ Fortunately, the vast sky is wide open ♫
♫ I think and yearn for one night, I don't dare seek to grow old ♫
♫ There is no need to explain much in this world ♫
♫ If the heartache remains, it'll never stop ♫
♫ How? ♫
[Nancheng Banquet]
[Episode 21]
Xiao Quan already knows my true identity,
and he has admitted it himself. He's the mastermind behind the Guanyou incident.
This time, he failed to frame me by using the princess's death.
He'll surely take new actions next.
Young Master, shall we kill this despicable villain,
and avenge the deceased Qin Family and subordinates?
A'Cheng, calm down.
Killing Xiao Quan is not difficult.
But the injustice suffered by the Qin Family can no longer be redressed.
It would be more loss than gain.
Uncle Lei is right. Xiao Quan's death is not enough.
But first, we must vindicate the Qin Family.
Now, I'm nothing but a commoner.
Dealing with Xiao Quan is even more difficult.
So, if necessary, I will meet with His Majesty.
Young Master, isn't this too risky?
After all, the Guanyou incident was decreed by His Majesty.
If he finds out your identity, it would be dangerous.
His Majesty has long been aware of Xiao Quan's ambition.
Now, for His Majesty,
only I can help him against Xiao Quan.
So, even if he knows my identity, His Majesty might not necessarily kill me.
Young Master, that's the best outcome you're talking about.
I aimed to spark a conflict betweenthe countries with the princess's demise.
So, I could accomplish a great task amidst the chaos.
And at the same time, eliminate Yan Changyun.
I didn't expect him to luckily escape again..
and ruining our big plans.
Hasn't he already been dismissed?
Although he has been dismissed,
but who knows when His Majesty might reinstate him?
When that time comes, he will be able to control the military power of the Southern Kingdom once again.
What do you plan to do?
Yan Changyun has always cared deeply for the Qin Family's former subordinates.
I just need to strike at the Qin Family's former subordinates.
Bind his hands and feet, and distract his attention.
By then, we can initiate the plan.
Rest assured, the grudge for crippling your legs,
I will certainly find a way to help you avenge it.
But now there's something more important.
That requires action by you.
It's your turn.
Guo Zhen's jade ring is in your beloved disciple's hands.
Inside, there may be hidden the tripartite agreement that you, I, and Guo Zhen signed back then.
That is the evidence of the Guanyou incident.
Wasn't the tripartite agreement destroyed that year?
And both you and I were present.
I'm afraid we were played by Guo Zhen.
What if the agreement that was burned that year was a fake?
Now, while your beloved disciple still hasn't recovered her memory,
let's get rid of her directly.
This way, the tripartite agreement will never see the light of day.
Only then will you and I have no further worries.
How come, Sir, you can't bear to part with your precious disciple?
You must understand, once this jade ring falls into Yan Changyun's hands,
then he'll know about the Guanyou incident.
That the entire Qin Family's execution was orchestrated by you and me.
And I will die when the time comes.
And the Ning Kingdom won't have peace either.
If you're unwilling to do it, then I'll go.
There's no need.
If you act, you'll inevitably alert the enemy.
I'll do it.
Then I'll have to trouble you, Sir.
Xiao Quan, that old fox, has always been using me.
As long as I get hold of this tripartite agreement,
then I can use it against him and make him obey me.
Why haven't you gone to sleep yet?
You've come to see me about something.
Actually, there is something.
- I was thinking—
- You want to talk about Princess Jiayang's case. Right?
I've heard about it from A'Cheng. You checked the princess's wounds while I was in prison.
The murder weapon was identified as a plum blossom tri-edged short blade.
It's very likely the weapon of your senior sister, Qing Li.
That's right.
So, that means, the murderer is the woman who tried to assassinate you in Beggar's Alley.
I'm not certain, I've asked my master.
My master said that my senior sister has never been to the capital.
Your master?
Yes, my master came to see me.
Even though I still haven't recovered my memory,
but when I see him, I feel a special sense of closeness.
He also said he wanted me to leave with him.
But I can't bear to leave you.
Let me accompany you to meet your master in a couple of days.
He is your elder, so he is also my elder.
Turns out you're more anxious about it than me.
If you want to see him, then go ahead and meet.
Actually, by all rights, my master is like a father to me.
Whether you meet him or not, our relationship stays the same.
But if you really want to see him, then go ahead.
My master is a particularly good person.
He'll definitely like you once he meets you.
Do you believe what your master says? Princess Jiayang was not killed by Qing Li.
No, that's not the case.
But Master said he would ask Senior Sister to clarify.
If she did it, there would be no favoritism.
And I firmly believe my master is a good person.
I believe you are a good person, too.
Thank you.
Tired? Come on, lie down and rest well.
Previously, you were always occupied with official duties. There was no time.
Take this opportunity to take a good leave and enjoy it.
True,
finding the assassin is just the first step.
The most important thing is still to find the real mastermind behind the scenes.
But let Tianjiao, that cheap commander, do all these.
Right now, my task is to rest well.
Really getting a good rest?
[Yan Residence]
Good morning.
How did I end up sleeping here?
Yesterday, I was thinking to watch over you for a while
after you fell asleep and then leave.
I didn't expect I would just…
Open my eyes and being able to see you,
that's really nice.
Why are you still keeping this smelly pouch?
I'm taking it away. Didn't I embroider a new one for you?
I'm keeping the new one.
The pouch I embroidered is a token of love.
Whoever takes my pouch is mine.
All right, it's a deal.
I was just kidding.
But I'm serious.
Fu Xiao.
If there are things I haven't told you, would you mind?
Would you feel that two people who truly love each other shouldn't lie?
Sometimes, lies are told to protect the ones who are important.
Honesty is just a matter of time, after all.
Perhaps because the time is not right.
Or perhaps it's a matter of life and death.
It's hard to fulfill both love and righteousness.
But what I just said doesn't include hiding private money.
If I find out you are hiding private money, then no mercy.
I wouldn't dare.
What's wrong, Fu Xiao?
Fu Xiao? Fu Xiao.
Fu Xiao!
How is she?
Commander Yan, the poison in Miss Xiao's body is getting deeper and deeper.
Without the antidote, I'm afraid she won't last much longer.
Boss, someone came claiming to be Fu Xiao's master.
Quick, the antidote.
How can I trust you?
If she doesn't take the antidote soon,
I fear it may cause irreversible damage to her body.
Master is here to save Senior Sister. Why are you still stopping him?
How do I know if you are here to save her or harm her?
There's no time left, are you going to wait?
Commander Yan, let's give it a try.
You know Fu Xiao's purpose for getting close to you.
I know, those who are unaware are not guilty. I don't blame her.
And it's not your place to blame her.
Up to now, in my heart, you're still an utterly unforgivable sinner.
I don't care how you see me.
As long as Fu Xiao believes I'm a good person, that's enough.
I won't let Fu Xiao stay with you. I'll take her away.
I won't let her go with you. After all, she is the safest with me.
One day as a teacher, a lifetime as a father.
Whether you can keep her or not, still depends on Fu Xiao's choice between us in the end.
If you really cared about Fu Xiao,
then you wouldn't be eager to take her away from my side.
But should instead thoroughly cure the poison in her body.
Xiao Quan provides us with the antidote every month.
However, this antidote can only relieve the symptoms,
but can't completely eradicate the poison in her body.
So, you've known Xiao Quan for a long time.
Xiao Quan, this despicable person,
uses poison to coerce Wanshi Pavilion.
I'm also helpless, that's why I obey him.
Is it coercion...
and not collusion?
I know you don't believe it.
But it doesn't matter, you just need to know one thing.
If Fu Xiao doesn't kill you, then she will die instead.
Moreover, the two of us are both unable to cure the poison in her body.
And now you're just a commoner.
How can you possibly resist Xiao Quan, who now has immense power?
Master.
Fu Xiao.
You're awake.
Master, why are you here?
I was worried about you and came to check on you.
Master, your legs must not be exposed to the cold.
- I'll take you back to rest.
- It's alright.
You just took the antidote; your body is still weak.
I'm fine.
[Minister's Mansion]
My Lord.
What's the matter?
Bai Yi has already gone to meet Yan Changyun.
There's no news for the moment.
Do you think Bai Yi is really willing to kill his disciple?
No matter who he's going to kill,
it's to our advantage.
If Yan Changyun is the one who dies, that would be ideal.
If it's that Fu Xiao who dies,
then we'll just repeat the old trick.
Use Qin's old faction to force Yan Changyun to comply.
As long as the two of them die,
your Majesty Zhao Yuan will be isolated and at our mercy.
Keep a close watch on Qin's old faction as well.
We're ready to act at any moment.
Understood.
Bai Yi, as a man of the martial world,
yet has connections with Xiao Quan.
The prime suspect in the murder of Princess Jiayang,
is also his disciple, Qing Li.
This person is not simple.
Go check out Bai Yi's background.
Also, don't tell Fu Xiao about this.
I don't want her to be harmed.
Yes.
Master!
Fu Xiao.
Master, isn't dipping watermelon in spices a Ning Kingdom's way of eating?
I traveled to the Ning Kingdom to study in my youth, and was influenced by the customs there.
I grew fond of it over time.
Master, you've studied in the Ning Kingdom, too?
In that case, the wind is strong here.
Let me push you back to the room, and you can tell me all about it.
Okay.
Could it be him?
It's indeed you, Ning Kingdom's Second Prince, Yi Heng.
Unharmed as ever, Qin Yan?
15 years ago, you pushed me off a cliff.
I survived by a hair's breadth.
It's time to settle that account now.
It's been 15 years.
Back then, you crippled my legs,
and made me spend the rest of my life in this wheelchair.
This account also ought to be properly settled.
Then it depends on whether you have the ability to do it.
If you kill me, Fu Xiao will never get the antidote.
15 years ago, even if the Ning Kingdom did not make a move,
with the Qin Family's power and influence, and achievements overshadowing the master,
Southern Kingdom's emperor would not have spared you either.
Even to this day, as a descendant of the Qin Family,
you still can't escape the fate of being hunted down.
So, why must you implicate Fu Xiao as well?
Only if you die, can Fu Xiao live.
The poison in Fu Xiao's body is only temporarily suppressed.
If the medication cannot be continued,
she'll surely die within ten days.
As long as you die,
I'll ensure her life is without worry.
It seems it's time to meet with His Majesty.
[Imperial Spring Palace]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Changyun, to me, you have always been Commander Yan.
Please rise quickly.
Thank you, Your Majesty, for your great kindness.
I have something important to tell Your Majesty.
Go ahead.
Xiao Quan visited when I was in the Ministry of Justice's prison.
He admitted in person, that he himself is the mastermind behind the events 15 years ago.
This time, Princess Jiayang's death is also related to him.
And the second prince of Ning Kingdom was also involved.
Xiao Quan's intentions are deserving of death.
Starting from when he wanted to execute the old followers of Guanyou,
I felt he could no longer restrain himself from coming out from behind the scenes.
Exactly, so, Xiao Quan can't be left alive.
Then, do you have a way to deal with this?
Since Xiao Quan returned to the capital city,
and has tried several times to kill me.
Now, he is even using Fu Xiao's life to threaten me.
Therefore, I want to fight him with his own strategy this time.
Use my life to lure Xiao Quan out of hiding.
Then, Your Majesty, you can capture Xiao Quan, and clarify the truth behind the Guanyou incident.
Changyun, this is unacceptable.
The Thousand Feather Guards can't afford to lose you.
I can't lose you either.
When the time comes, I'll restore your leader status
and capture Xiao Quan immediately.
Your Majesty, I'm afraid we don't have time anymore.
Please grant your permission, Your Majesty.
[Yan Residence]
Come in.
Boss, as you ordered, the house has been purchased.
The rest of the wealth has also been fully converted into silver,
and stored and sealed in the bank's vault.
This is the bank's key and the deed to the property.
[House Deed]
Tianjiao,
I have an unreasonable request.
Go ahead.
Take good care of these brothers in the future.
[Purple Aura Coming from the East]
Watch the sunrise together.
Why are you being so childish?
When did you arrive?
I just arrived.
What are you writing this for?
This is the 100 little things we're going to do when we're together.
It'll help us grow closer.
Does our relationship still need to be improved?
[100 Little Things in Love with You]
Of course it does; you don't have time for me.
I used to be busy with official duties and had no time to spend with you.
Now, I have time to spend with you properly.
Really?
From now on, you'll belong only to me.
Good, then I need to hurry up and plan tomorrow's itinerary.
Come, let me tell you, look at this.
The first thing is definitely to watch the sunrise together.
After that, I also want to watch the sunset and go shopping.
Miss, how did it go? Did you arrange a meeting with Commander Yan?
Tomorrow is your birthday.
Wangyou, sit down and eat with me; don't waste it.
I don't know what's so good about Fu Xiao.
An unmarried girl, fraternizing with men in a room all day.
Even the girls of our Yunshao Bureau must be discreet in their dealings with men.
Usually when going out or getting a bit too close to men,
it has to be permitted by Mom.
Miss, I heard A'Cheng say that back when she was with the Thousand Feather Guards, she…
I find it hard to even say.
If you're going to say it, then say it all.
They actually slept together.
It's really indecent.
Miss, you must find a way to win back Commander Yan.
[Minister's Mansion]
What's the matter with Miss Chu Yue? You look so unhappy.
Lord Xiao, why haven't you taken action to kill Fu Xiao yet?
As for me, killing Fu Xiao would certainly eliminate future troubles.
But when I think of your original intention, Miss Chu Yue,
I feel that the matter can't be settled like this.
Lord Xiao, what do you mean?
Miss, think about it.
Right now, Yan Changyun and Fu Xiao are in the midst of a loving relationship.
If Fu Xiao dies,
then Yan Changyun will certainly be devastated.
And his heart still lies with Fu Xiao.
What you have gained, is none other than Yan Changyun's empty shell.
Moreover, based on my understanding of Yan Changyun,
you might not even get that empty shell in the end.
According to your meaning, sir, Fu Xiao can't be killed?
Miss, you have misunderstood my meaning.
I mean, you need to make Yan Changyun and Fu Xiao
turn against each other, and part ways like the swallows.
That is truly breaking up a pair of lovers.
Only then can you win Yan Changyun's heart.
Lord Xiao, what do you want me to do?
Getting up so late, the sunrise is already gone.
It's all your fault.
I did get up early, though.
Then why didn't you wake me up?
Seeing you sleep so soundly, I couldn't bear to wake you, and wanted to let you sleep a bit more.
Those are all excuses.
Fine, it's all my fault.
Nonetheless, we didn't catch the sunrise.
But coming out for a walk is also nice, it's fine.
It does matter. If the first small affair in our love doesn't go well from the start,
then it means that our love will face many trials ahead.
Rest assured; I won't let you go through hardships again.
You'll always be happy.
I'm very happy right now.
I really wish time would stop at this moment.
But then again, it is really too cold here.
Perhaps we should go home.
All right, then I will take you to a place.
Let's go.
You seem very familiar with this area.
As a child, I often sneaked out to play here,
and practiced martial arts here as well.
Practicing from a young age, no wonder your martial arts are so good.
Even with great skills, there're times one can make a mistake.
When facing an expert, it's either a fatal move,
or you must quickly escape.
Even Commander Yan has times to flee?
I'm talking about you.
The martial arts I taught you must be diligently practiced,
no slacking off.
I'll definitely practice the martial arts you've taught me, and never slack off.
Also, don't act rashly and put on a show of bravery.
Such a beautiful view.
Can't you just stay quietly by my side?
Dad.
How could you go to Xiao Quan?
Do you realize how important that ring is to us?
If Fu Xiao is killed,
the thing inside the ring is concealed,
then our 15 years of effort will have been in vain.
It's been so long, yet Fu Xiao still hasn't regained her memory.
Why still pin our hopes on her?
I think she's just been playing dumb all along.
She just doesn't want to hand the ring over to the young master.
But you can't do something as foolish as that.
She was the one who stole Brother Yan away first.
If it weren't for her, Yan and I would have been together long ago.
She deserves to die.
Chu Yue,
how have you become like this now?
15 years.
I've been in Yunshao Bureau for a full 15 years.
All these years, I haven't had a single complaint.
Because I know that Father gave up saving me to save the young master.
For him, I'm willing.
I know that one day in the future, I'll marry him.
Then all the suffering I've been through these years,
will turn sweet in that moment.
Dad, I've never asked you for anything over the years.
But now, I just have this one wish,
which is to marry Brother Yan.
I'm begging you, Dad. Please accompany your daughter to act out a play.
[Civil and Military Strategies]
Today, I missed both the sunrise and the sunset.
But I'm still very happy.
I hope you will continue to do even better, and fulfill one of my small wishes every day.
What's the matter, you don't want to?
No.
Fu Xiao.
I've deposited some silver in the bank, here is the passkey.
For me?
Take good care of it, there are still many days ahead.
Remember, steady streams last long.
Isn't this too sudden?
You're letting me keep house?
I'm not prepared yet.
I have already prepared everything that needs to be.
You just need to accept it.
It's getting late.
You've been tired all day, rest early.
I can't bear to part with you.
Be good.
Your Majesty.
Look what this is?
What's this that makes you so happy?
This is the key to the bank account.
Yan Changyun personally gave it to me.
He said I would be in charge of his money from now on.
From now on, I must start taking charge of the household.
Your Majesty, you are my best friend.
That's why I want to tell you my good news first.
Do you love Yan Changyun?
He is the one for me in this life.
Then, does Yan Changyun love you?
Of course.
That's wonderful…
to know what it feels like to be loved.
Your Majesty.
Actually, there has always been an unresolved issue between us.
I never wanted to bring it up again in my life.
But now I must tell you.
Go ahead.
I have never been pregnant with His Majesty's child.
Then you and His Majesty…?
It was all lies he told to save me.
Moreover, I have no affection for His Majesty.
Yan Changyun has always been the one in my heart.
It was all fake.
Then, you have never had a miscarriage.
Then, why was the miscarriage incident blamed on my brother?
Isn't that because of Xiao Quan…
Her Majesty, there are some things I can't tell you.
But what I want to say to you
is you should try to stay away from Lord Xiao.
Your elder brother is no simple man.
Your Majesty, please don't mind me telling you these things.
I sincerely wish for your happiness.
I know you care about me.
You don't need to worry about me.
I'm looking forward to having a drink at your and Yan Changyun's wedding.
[Yan Residence]
What is she sneaking off to do?
Dad.
You're here, come in quickly.
Isn't this the person who wants to kill me?
He is Chu Yue's dad.
Dad, are your injuries better?
Much better.
I've brought you some food, here.
Don't rush, sit down.
Yesterday was your birthday, Chu Yue.
Dad, I should have come to see you.
But now, it's inconvenient for me to visit Young Master's residence.
I'm sorry.
Did Young Master accompany you on your birthday yesterday?
He went to accompany Fu Xiao.
Don't feel wronged either.
Changyun had no choice.
He's just doing this to gain Fu Xiao's trust.
He did it on purpose for her to see. Don't blame him.
Of course not, Father. I understand Brother Yan's intentions.
Very good! Young master played this game well.
Now Fu Xiao has fallen in love with him,
and she trusts him completely.
As long as Fu Xiao can help Young Master get that jade ring,
then she'll just be a useless person in the future. Right?
Father, I'm still a bit worried about him.
What are you still worried about?
I'm worried that he'll take the pretense too seriously,
and then won't be able to go through with it.
Don't worry about that.
Who is the young master?
He is the son of Duke Ding, a man destined for great things.
The son of Duke Ding, Yan Changyun, is Qin Yan.
15 years ago, Fu Xiao saved the young master.
Later on, the young master, fearing the leakage of his whereabouts,
ordered Fu Xiao's parents to be killed.
No. Impossible. He wouldn't do this to me.
Yan Changyun, I want to hear it from you personally.
"Promise" - Jiang Yu Han & Wang Hong
♫ A vast sea of ​​people, long roads ♫
♫ A childhood meeting that is unforgettable in the passing years ♫
♫ There are many vicissitudes of life in the world, each side at the ends of the earth ♫
♫ The twilight falls and scatters, the moonlight comforts the parting dead ♫
♫ Going in circles, it's still the same as before ♫
♫ The human world has tender sentiments,
the word "love" is hidden in the palm of your hand ♫
♫ Drawing a sword to cut the water, the water keeps flowing ♫
♫ Time flies like water, yet I trust you have been well since we last met ♫
♫ Fierce horses and bright clothes, all to marry you in your bridal red ♫
♫ Love amidst the vast sea, it's intoxication is the hardest to let go ♫
♫ What harm is there to give up this life for you? ♫
♫ I keep this tenderness to myself ♫
♫ To be drunk with you for a time ♫
♫ If I could truly fall in love with you ♫
♫ Why should I be afraid of the wind and snow disturbing my heart? ♫
♫ Never giving up, never forgetting, never regretting is my heartfelt wish for you ♫
♫ If I could fill pages with my affection for you ♫
♫ Why fear the world's high mountains and long rivers? ♫
♫ One thought, one dream, a lifetime, I place you in my heart ♫
♫ If I could truly fall in love with you ♫
♫ Why should I be afraid of the wind and snow disturbing my heart? ♫
♫ Never giving up, never forgetting, never regretting is my heartfelt wish for you ♫
♫ If I could fill pages with my affection for you ♫
♫ Why fear the world's high mountains and long rivers? ♫
♫ One thought, one dream, a lifetime, I place you in my heart ♫