"Simply One Song"- Hu Zhengjun
♫ Fortunately, I can't get what I want ♫
♫ The sky returns one night and the world is already in song ♫
♫ Unattainable in this life ♫
♫ It's an honor to have the privilege of parting ways at the end of the world ♫
♫ Heaven wishes for eternity,and people cherish the expanse ♫
♫ Not far from her, but nowhere near ♫
♫ The sky is turbulent, the finale about a hundred years later ♫
♫ Fortunately, my longing finally turns into a song ♫
♫ The leaving person waves and the shadow smiles,
racing all night through the vast sky ♫
♫ The trees of tranquility have not yet disappeared ♫
♫ Tears of the kind-hearted never cease to disappear ♫
♫ But they never stop ♫
♫ Fortunately, the vast sky is wide open ♫
♫ I think and yearn for one night, I don't dare seek to grow old ♫
♫ There is no need to explain much in this world ♫
♫ If the heartache remains, it'll never stop ♫
♫ How? ♫
[Nancheng Banquet]
[Episode 15]
Imperial Physician Qu, you have been examining her for quite a while.
How is she?
Imperial Physician Qu, my child cannot be saved. Right?
- I'm afraid—
- Imperial Physician Qu, my child is blessed by God.
We won't lose it so easily.
Do you agree?
I'm afraid…
That makes sense, Your Majesty.
Imperial Physician Qu, no one knows a child better than their mother.
I feel my child definitely cannot be saved. Right?
- I think...
- Imperial Physician Qu, your medical skills are exceptional.
Surely with more prescriptions, the imperial child can be saved. Right?
Imperial Physician Qu, this child is quite ominous.
Yesterday, it caused a maid to die.
Who knows who will be the next one to suffer misfortune?
If a baby isn't born, my fate is the same, death. It's better to seize this opportunity.
- Imperial Physician Qu.
Your Majesty, I can't help it. It's beyond my ability.
The b-b-baby is gone. Please restrain your grief, Your Majesty.
What? Everything was fine yesterday.
And today, it's just gone?
Empress Dowager, it's not my fault.
It's on Xiao Quan. He deliberately bumped into me hard.
And I lost the baby as a result.
How ridiculous!
How can a baby be lost from just a bump?
Well then, since the baby is gone,
there's no need for you to stay by His Majesty's side anymore.
I'll give you two choices.
One, become a nun to pray for the departed child.
Two, go to the restroom to scrub squat toilets. Choose for yourself.
I choose to scrub squat toilets.
Good choice.
Guards, take Fu Xiao to the restroom to work immediately.
Grand…
Your Majesty.
Scrubbing squat toilets is both dirty and tiring.
How can you still be so happy?
I don't have to lie anymore. I feel relieved inside. Of course, I feel happy.
You'd rather scrub squat toilets than live with me?
Why? What's wrong with me after all?
I am the emperor of an empire.
Not just that, I have wealth and power, and I am handsome too.
We get along and are good friends.
I don't understand.
So what?
I neither like money nor do I care for power.
I just want to live a free and easy life.
Your Majesty, you should hurry back.
You are not suitable for such places.
Look, you've scared them all away.
I want to find someone to share the burden with me but can't.
Hurry back.
I am leaving.
I am really leaving.
Fine, keep scrubbing squat toilets for the rest of your life.
What are you here for?
I am scrubbing a squat toilet now.
You came to laugh at me. Right?
I'm not that bored.
So what are you here for?
I came to tell you
you were right to use an excuse to rid yourself of the false pregnancy crisis.
But you shouldn't have provoked Xiao Quan.
Do you realize that it'll put you in even more danger?
I only know an eye for an eye.
Can you not be so reckless?
What's wrong with being reckless? At least I feel good about it.
It's still better than someone.
Worrying about this and that every day even more than a woman does.
- You—
- Commander Yan, you don't have to lecture me here.
You're delicate and not suitable for such places.
Please leave.
One moment you care for me, the next you neglect me.
Are you playing with me?
I'm done with you.
You didn't hear how resolute her words were.
It feels like she'll never return to me again.
Your Majesty, one must not indulge women.
You are the heaven, our emperor.
You can't let a woman lead you by the nose.
Ignore her for a couple of days. Teach her a lesson.
Then she will miss your kindness.
I hope so.
Don't worry. Your Majesty, I'll take care of it.
I'll definitely make Ms. Fu Xiao come and apologize.
All right, then I will wait a little longer.
The most unfortunate thing of my life
is meeting this calamity and bringing her into the palace.
Still thinking you're carrying His Majesty's heir?
You're destined to be scrubbing squat toilets.
Don't slack off. Get to work now.
What are you doing?
What's the matter? Angry?
You just lost a baby, and now you are eating sunflower seeds. So heartless.
How can you guilty woman be so smug?
Just by looking at her face, I can tell she's a ruthless woman.
His Majesty is kind and was momentarily deceived by her.
Since you are so delicate, why bother coming here?
I need to scrub squat toilets.
So stubborn. You're asking for a lesson.
Everyone, come on.
Beat her up.
Come on. I was just thinking of having a fight with you.
Xiao Daozi, come help.
Xiao Daozi!
If you don't finish scrubbing before nightfall, you can't eat dinner.
Let's go.
Truly asking for a lesson.
- Are you okay, Brother Qiang?
- I'm fine, Xiao…
My goodness, Xiao Daozi! You're so nice.
You're the best. I ended up scrubbing squat toilets.
Only you came to keep me company.
If it weren't for Yan Changyun forcing me, I wouldn't have come to this darn place.
Who did you say forced you to come?
Yan Changyun forced me.
Feng Shixi, has she admitted her mistake yet?
Ms. Fu Xiao is still holding onto her last bit of dignity.
In my view, she won't last a few more days.
Everything is under my control.
Don't worry, Your Majesty. I will put in extra effort.
All right, I will wait a bit longer.
A bit longer.
What are you going to do?
- Let's use words.
- No need for words.
You are going to beat me again?
- Yes, I'm hitting you.
- I—
Commander Yan is here.
- Yan Changyun.
- Let's leave.
Hurry.
Commander Yan, you finally came.
If you had come just one step later—
Are you all right?
Whether I'm all right or not, it's none of your business.
For you. You've worked hard scrubbing squat toilets these past few days.
Hand cream. Apply three times a day.
Those maids won't come to bully you anymore.
Is it for you?
Yes, it's for me.
He even said it was for Liu Yidao.
I knew it was for me.
This is really bad.
Bad luck.
What do we do now? We were seen by Commander Yan.
What can we do about this?
We can't afford to mess with Commander Yan.
But Eunuch Feng ordered us to punish Ms. Fu.
We can't just do nothing.
Right! We're really caught in the middle and it's tough.
That's right. We're always the ones in a difficult position.
Exactly.
Feng Shixi, when is she finally going to admit her mistake?
Your Majesty, don't worry. Based on my estimation, it should be within these two days.
I have already instructed others if Ms. Fu Xiao comes, no one should stop her.
All right, I will wait a bit longer.
You still know to come?
I really should come.
Your Majesty, who would have thought you could be so despicable?
And you, too.
What's the matter, Feng Shixi?
I shall take my leave.
Don't go!
Your Majesty, you say we are friends,
but you plot against me behind my back and even let the maids bully me.
That was all Feng Shixi's doing. I was unaware.
Don't explain.
From now on, I never want to be friends with you again.
Fine by me. I never wanted to be your friend.
Fu Xiao.
Your Majesty, please let me go.
You…
Your Majesty, the Xiaos sent someone here for Xue Ru's corpse,
saying they want to take it back for burial.
Give it to them for the sake of the empress.
Your Majesty, you've got paint on your hands. Ask the eunuch to wash it.
I shall take my leave.
You're here.
Boss, the case of Xiao Wanli.
You asked me to investigate secretly the cosmetics used in the palace.
Here are the investigation records.
[Cosmetics Order]
Why did Eunuch Feng need cosmetics?
I asked him. He said His Majesty needed them.
That day, when painting the facial makeup, he felt the colors were not bright enough,
so he added some at the last minute.
Tianjiao.
What was His Majesty doing the day Xiao Wanli died?
Just like usual, nothing different.
But quite a few people in the palace saw him dressed in a theatrical costume,
with stage makeup on, performing in a play.
Dressed in a theatrical costume with stage makeup.
Was Eunuch Feng there?
No, he wasn't. At least, nobody mentioned him when I asked.
And that day, not long after Xiao Wanli's body was brought back for examination,
His Majesty ordered us to return the body.
Ms. Fu Xiao, those maids were arranged by me.
I did it because I wanted you to return to His Majesty sooner.
His Majesty was not aware of it.
His Majesty is innocent. Please do not blame him.
I'm just a commoner. How can I blame His Majesty?
So are you saying you're willing to reconcile with His Majesty?
I have no right to blame His Majesty.
How would I have the right to reconcile?
When can we stop doing this?
Of course not until Ms. Fu Xiao does.
Ms. Fu Xiao, can you do me a favor?
Would you reconsider it?
Xiao Daozi, look at how you clean it.
It's not clean at all.
Look at Eunuch Feng. He's truly deserving of the inner court chief manager.
Look, he's doing so well.
Stop scrubbing. Even I think it's still dirty.
Not to mention the masters.
Leave these tasks to someone capable.
Let's go.
Let's go. take it.
I was wrong.
What did you do wrong?
I should not have disrespected your thoughts.
But I did mean well.
Of course, it truly did damage the brotherly bond between us.
I promise you that from now on, I'll treat you solely as a brother.
Once bitten, twice shy.
I don't believe what you're saying now.
You...
just go back and see how I behave.
I'm not going anywhere. I'm quite fine here.
I've been here so long that I don't even notice the smell.
Besides, I'm no longer the person I was back then,
who you could deceive with just a few words.
I will consider forgiving you.
Go back and wait for news.
Brother Qiang, don't go too far. Just take the way out offered.
I was just thinking, if I didn't teach him a lesson, how could he learn?
How long is this endless scrubbing supposed to last?
Look, my hands are like dried radishes now.
How much longer can I do it for you? You'll have to do it alone.
With the weather so cold, can you endure it?
That makes sense. I'm a bit worried now.
Was my act just now a bit too much?
It's hard to say.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, it has been over a month since the chancellor's death.
The murderer remains a mystery to this day.
Rumors are rife among the people,
all fearing that it's the remnants of the Qin Family.
To console the chancellor in heaven,
to quell the rumors and reassure the people,
I suggest that all the remaining members of the Qin Family should be executed.
I find it inappropriate.
Your Majesty, I think Minister Song's words are too radical.
If we blindly execute the remaining members of the Qin Family,
it will inevitably harm many innocents.
By then, it will surely arouse public outrage, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I agree with Minister Song's suggestion.
15 years ago, the Qin Family committed a monstrous crime.
Those vicious and evil felons.
Keeping them is always a hidden danger for the kingdom.
It's better to kill them all to eliminate future troubles.
There is no conclusive evidence that the chancellor's death was the Qin Family's doing.
If I were to execute them all based solely on conjecture, wouldn't I become a tyrant?
Your Majesty, you are wise.
Please don't show mercy to the remaining members of the Qin Family.
He's right.
[Prosperity]
Enough! No more arguing.
Dismissed if there are no other matters.
- Long live the Emperor!
Lord Xiao, can we really lure out Qin Yan by doing this?
As long as he lives.
He's been living in hiding.
I guess he will not easily take the risk to show up.
He definitely will.
The Qin Family values their reputation the most and loves to pretend to be good.
Back then, Duke Ding used the lives of his entire family
in exchange for a glimmer of hope for his subordinates.
I believe that Qin Yan will do the same.
Lord Xiao, you're so smart.
Take care.
[Imperial Spring Palace]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Commander Yan, what is the matter?
I have already found the real murderer who killed Xiao Wanli.
Who is it?
The murderer...
is you.
Commander Yan, what do you mean by this?
At first, I found traces of cosmetics on the chancellor's corpse.
And given the wound, I thought the murderer was weak
and believed the murderer was a woman.
But I overlooked one point.
That kind of makeup is not exclusive to women.
How can men use makeup?
Why can't men use it?
Those who perform in operas use it.
And the killer could pretend to be weak.
That doesn't necessarily prove it was my doing.
I did not leave the palace that day. The servants can testify to this.
Before coming, I had already conducted an investigation.
You were performing an opera on the tower that day.
But the strange thing is that you usually perform operas in the Miaoyin Pavilion and never wear makeup.
But that day, you did.
I suspect it was Eunuch Feng standing in for you.
Brilliant. No wonder you're the leader of the Thousand Feather Guards.
So, you admit killing Xiao Wanli?
Yeah, kind of true.
[Bright Moonlight]
I'm really loyal to the kingdom and you.
I truly do not understand you.
You form cliques for private gain and make arbitrary decisions.
You coerce me and grasp control of the government.
And now, you even want to manipulate me to eliminate dissidents.
This is what you call loyalty?
Your Majesty, the vermilion silver powder brings disaster to the kingdom and the people.
If you're soft-handed and don't kill them all,
they will surely bring endless misfortune to our kingdom.
Hypocrite.
You're just an unscrupulous who will do anything to achieve power.
Just like 15 years ago when you forced me to kill Duke Ding.
He deserved to die.
He was ambitious and greedy for merit and acted rashly.
He caused chaos in the military. The evidence was irrefutable.
Xiao Wanli, you…
[Bright Moonlight]
Lord Xiao, you should not talk back to His Majesty.
His Majesty is merciful. But you're disrespectful and repeatedly anger him.
Who do you think you are to speak to me this way?
I deserve death.
What do you mean by that?
Five years ago, you conducted a private visit in disguise.
You found me poor so you gave me money
to bury my deceased mother and brought me into the Imperial Palace.
I can only repay you this way.
I am asking you what exactly do you mean.
I mistakenly killed Xiao Wanli without your order.
Your Majesty, don't worry.
To mislead others, I have already written "Guanyou" beside the body.
You…
Xiao Wanli has committed heinous crimes, murdering the loyal and good and coercing me.
If I wanted him dead, I'd have made his crimes known to the whole world
and conduct a public trial.
Leave the capital and never come back in this lifetime.
All this time, I believed Xiao Wanli plotted the Guanyou incident,
but he did not admit it even at the point of death.
- You believe his words?
- Not entirely.
But I trust Duke Ding. He was loyal to the kingdom.
He would never do anything that would harm the kin
You've never doubted Duke Ding over the matter of the vermilion silver powder?
Never.
Father, can you hear this in heaven?
His Majesty believes you were innocent.
I thought, since "Guanyou" was written on it,
I could take the opportunity to find out the real culprit behind the Guanyou Incident.
However, it implicated the families of those involved in the Guanyou Incident.
I really do not know what to do.
I believe someone must be advising Song Ting from behind the scenes.
It's Xiao Quan.
I have long felt that Xiao Quan was no simple character.
So after his father's death, I probed him.
I even made him the Minister of Justice, waiting for him to become complacent and expose his flaws.
I didn't expect him to exploit the incident
to try to eradicate the former members of the Qin Family.
He's even more vicious than Xiao Wanli.
Your Majesty, don't worry.
I have a plan that can temporarily suppress Xiao Quan.
I just need something from you.
What is it?
Commander Yan, now I'm giving you the weapon.
You trust me so much. I will certainly not let you down.
I knew I could trust you at any time.
Can I ask for one more thing?
Miss Chu Yue.
Yes, Miss Chu Yue is still in the prison of the Ministry of Justice.
I am truly worried.
You worry about her so much.
Do you like her?
Since Miss Chu Yue has promised herself to me, I have the responsibility to protect her.
Good! You are a real man.
Don't worry. I will help you protect her at any time.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Then I shall take my leave.
Eunuch Feng, you're a good actor.
It seems you have learned quite a lot from His Majesty.
He knows it.
It won't cause any trouble, will it?
It's okay. It's good that he knows.
He has agreed to help me find the real culprit behind the Guanyou incident.
It's just that I'm growing more and more suspicious of his identity.
Hide this dagger in Song Ting's residence.
But Song Ting is a man of Xiao Quan.
Wouldn't this expose you even more?
This is the only way.
Only then can I protect the ones implicated.
Only then can I save Chu Yue.
Xiao Quan already suspects you. What if they use this as an excuse to make it hard for you?
I have my own methods. Listen to me.
Go and get ready.
Duke Wei. Xiao Wanli.
The two great burdens weighing down on me have already been toppled.
But it is Xiao Quan who truly worries me.
Yan Changyun, if you truly are Qin Yan,
help me safeguard the kingdom.
Of course, we must thoroughly eradicate all evil.
If none of you will go, then fine, I'll say it.
I'll do it.
Your Majesty, for the peace of the kingdom,
I suggest executing all remnants of the Qin Family.
Your Majesty, no.
If we kill them without evidence,
I fear it would lead to great chaos throughout the land.
Your Majesty, I found the real culprit behind the murder of the chancellor.
You found the real culprit?
Who?
Song Ting, the Lesser Director of the Imperial Manufactory.
What?
Song Ting?
Him?
You're slandering me. You're framing a loyal person.
Don't try to deny it, Lord Song.
I have already found the murder weapon in your residence.
What weapon?
The blade of this dagger matches the chancellor's wound exactly.
The servants at your residence saw the dagger being found with their own eyes.
Here are their testimonies.
Nonsense. I don't have any dagger at all.
Besides, this kind of dagger is common in the market.
On what basis do you claim this is the murder weapon?
What Lord Song said is right.
But I also found a strand of silk thread in the chancellor's fingernails.
Whether you're the murderer or not will be known soon.
Could it really be Lord Song?
It seems true.
This thread...
is from Lord Song's left shoulder.
Really?
There really was one at the scene of the crime.
Lord Song, you've worked hard.
You took this silk thread from me.
You're framing me.
Song Ting, take it easy.
Commander Yan, please continue.
Your Majesty, to determine the guilt of Lord Song
based solely on a common thread
is far too childishly whimsical, isn't it?
Didn't you condemn Chu Yue for killing the chancellor
simply because she is the daughter of Lei Bao?
How can these two cases be equated?
The crime scene contained "Guanyou".
Chu Yue is the daughter of Lei Bao, a former subordinate of Duke Ding.
She has been suspected of murder for revenge.
But Lord Song has always had a very good relationship with my father.
- Can you tell me...
- Yes.
why he'd kill my father?
Yes.
That makes sense.
Commander Yan, do you have any more evidence?
This is the conclusive evidence that Lord Song killed the Chancellor.
You're really vicious.
[Account Books]
He killed someone to cover up his corruption.
[Steward Liu's confession]
The chancellor was going to report him.
In a moment of desperation, Lord Song killed the chancellor.
For fear of exposure,
Lord Song then framed the former subordinates of Duke Ding.
- Song Ting!
- Here.
You engaged in corruption, hired an assassin, and committed murder.
With so much evidence here, what else do you have to say?
Your Majesty, I did covet some money,
but I did not kill the chancellor.
Your Majesty, the remnants of the Qin Family killed the chancellor.
It was the remnants of the Qin Family.
It's clever for Lord Song to mislead us with the two characters "Guanyou".
Do you have some entanglement with the Qin Family?
And you intended to eliminate your biggest concern by killing the chancellor?
You're venomous.
Guards, drag him out and deal with him according to the law.
Your Majesty, I am being wronged.
Secretary Xiao! Your Majesty! I am being wronged.
I am unjustly accused, Your Majesty!
The murder of the chancellor.
We have starved her for three days, but she still doesn't say naything.
As long as you confess the rest of the Qin Family, we will let you out.
Still stubborn. Quite the temper.
The chief courtesan of the Yunshao Bureau is beautiful.
Why not talk with us?
Right, come chat with us.
Come on, let's talk.
Brother Yan.
Here.
Yan Changyun, I was waiting for you to break into the jail.
I didn't expect you to actually come.
Capture him!
Xiao Quan, you're even more shameless than your father.
You should know that breaking into the Ministry of Punishment
and kidnapping the imperial court's most important criminal will cost you your head.
His Majesty has already issued an order to release Chu Yue.
Lord Xiao, do you intend to defy the imperial order?
Are you still doubting the authenticity of the imperial edict?
- What are you thinking about, Your Majesty?
- Nothing much.
Chancellor Xiao's killer has been found.
This eases my mind quite a bit.
Who is the murderer?
Song Ting, the Lesser Director of the Imperial Manufactory.
Song Ting?
I seem to have heard of him.
They say he's a corrupt official. Serves him right.
Then it was Yan Changyun who found this out, right, Your Majesty?
Yes, Commander Yan has been working tirelessly to find the murderer these days.
- It's both for the public good and a personal matter.
- What do you mean?
His childhood sweetheart, Miss Chu Yue, has been wronged for so long.
How could he not be anxious?
Today, he carried my edict to personally pick her up from jail.
And he asked me to annul her servitude.
It seems he intends to redeem her and take her home honorably as his wife.
Commander Yan dares to follow his heart.
He is truly a hero.
I am greatly comforted by this.
I want to see their happy reunion.
Just such a woman.
Due to my status, it is not convenient to leave the palace.
Why don't you go on my behalf and take a look?
Then I'll go right now.
[Commander's Mansion]
Chu Yue, it's not convenient for you to return to Uncle Lei's place for now.
So stay at my residence temporarily.
I've had the servants prepare this room for you.
Rest here and recover from your injuries.
Thank you, Brother Yan. I'll do as you say.
You've suffered these past few days.
This bit of suffering is nothing.
But do you know the pain in my heart?
I do.
Chu Yue, you're finally out.
Changyun and I were worried about you every day.
Changyun, I told you before to visit Chu Yue a lot.
But you wouldn't listen.
Changyun, I was just pregnant.
- You don't need to be so nervous, watching me every day.
- What are you saying?
You were not carrying the Boss's child. Why would he be worried about you?
Shut up.
Chu Yue, it's getting late.
- Changyun, escort her back to the Yunshao Bureau.
- No need.
His Majesty has granted you a special pardon and removed your status as a courtesan.
From today onwards, you are free.
Really?
Brother Yan, you not only redeemed my freedom for me
but also let me stay at your house.
Thank you.
I'll take you inside to have a look.
"Promise" - Jiang Yu Han & Wang Hong
♫ A vast sea of ​​people, long roads ♫
♫ A childhood meeting that is unforgettable in the passing years ♫
♫ There are many vicissitudes of life in the world, each side at the ends of the earth ♫
♫ The twilight falls and scatters, the moonlight comforts the parting dead ♫
♫ Going in circles, it's still the same as before ♫
♫ The human world has tender sentiments,
the word "love" is hidden in the palm of your hand ♫
♫ Drawing a sword to cut the water, the water keeps flowing ♫
♫ Time flies like water, yet I trust you have been well since we last met ♫
♫ Fierce horses and bright clothes, all to marry you in your bridal red ♫
​♫ Love amidst the vast sea, it's intoxication is the hardest to let go ♫
♫ What harm is there to give up this life for you? ♫
♫ I keep this tenderness to myself ♫
♫ To be drunk with you for a time ♫
♫ If I could truly fall in love with you ♫
​♫ Why should I be afraid of the wind and snow disturbing my heart? ♫
♫ Never giving up, never forgetting, never regretting is my heartfelt wish for you ♫
♫ If I could fill pages with my affection for you ♫
♫ Why fear the world's high mountains and long rivers? ♫
♫ One thought, one dream, a lifetime, I place you in my heart ♫
♫ If I could truly fall in love with you ♫
♫ Why should I be afraid of the wind and snow disturbing my heart? ♫
♫ Never giving up, never forgetting, never regretting is my heartfelt wish for you ♫
♫ If I could fill pages with my affection for you ♫
♫ Why fear the world's high mountains and long rivers? ♫
♫ One thought, one dream, a lifetime ♫
♫ I place you in my heart ♫