QUEEN OF TEARS
EPISODE 4
Mr. Oh, have you left? Where are you?
What? Here it is.
It was in my pocket.
What?
Hae-in, wait.
Wait.
Wait!
What are you doing?
I'm not sure.
What am I…
doing right now?
I'm glad
that you found your phone.
It could've been a hassle to get it.
Why wasn't I…
confident?
What?
What did you say?
Right.
I told you, right?
I'm going to try
new things from now on.
Good night.
Right. Good night.
Are you going to bed?
Well,
I'm not sure.
It'll recharge in no time.
What was that?
He could've just said
he wanted to come in.
What's with him?
Hae-in's birthday?
The day the department store went public.
My birthday?
It can't be our wedding anniversary.
One Trillion Club?
TRY AGAIN IN 30 SECONDS
Damn it.
Don't tell me…
It's 1031?
9 UNREAD MESSAGES
DELETE
8 UNREAD MESSAGES
Okay, done.
My God.
You startled me.
What are you…
doing here?
Well…
I couldn't sleep, so…
You couldn't
sleep,
so you came to my room?
So…
because of me?
You can't sleep because of me?
It's not that.
It's not like that at all. I just…
I just couldn't sleep.
For no particular reason.
So I came to see
if you were feeling the same.
And
if you wanted to talk.
But you're too tired, right?
I'm a bit tired,
but let's do it. Let's talk.
So where?
Should we sit here?
You're tired.
I guess I thought…
only of myself.
You had a few drinks,
and it's pretty late.
That's true, but…
So you're tired.
Well, I think
I've sobered up a little. Let's sit.
No. Don't sit.
I was being thoughtless.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot to do tomorrow.
You should rest.
Have a good night's sleep.
Lie down.
He cares…
so much for me.
That was so close.
No way…
It's 1031?
Congratulations.
You're four weeks pregnant.
Well…
Four weeks…
Then when will the baby be born?
It's due on October 31.
I see. October 31.
That's a good date.
October 31.
Please use top-quality
eco-friendly interior materials.
Right. I hear that thing
is a must for a baby's room.
I ought to…
How could you go there?
I mean, we've never met her properly
since they got married,
-but they suddenly mentioned divorce, so…
-Mom, I tried to stop her.
And you went with her?
Anyway, what did she say?
She had no idea.
-Yeah.
-Only Hyun-woo was thinking of divorce.
Really?
And she said she'd come visit us soon.
-And, Dad.
-Yes?
I finally added her on my messenger app!
But what about Hyun-woo?
He says he won't divorce her.
They're doing well. Don't worry.
-That's a relief.
-No, they are not!
He was considering divorce
while his wife had no idea.
You think they're doing well?
Neither of them know how the other feels.
Invite me in the chat.
I won't say much or send photos.
We will now take a photo
of the family members and relatives.
Ms. Kim.
Yes?
I know
that you don't like Hyun-woo
as your son-in-law.
I'm not sure if I should say this,
but when Hyun-woo told us
he was seeing someone,
he said that the girl might get fired
and become unemployed soon,
so he'd have to provide for her
if he married her.
Then our family said
he could find a better girl
and that she was too poor.
Even a family like us
was being so calculating.
I can't imagine how you felt.
There's a great difference.
I'm sure you were upset and disappointed.
We're all human after all.
So,
I understand.
Right. I'm glad that you understand.
I know
my son lacks a lot.
But I hope you take good care of him.
He lacks a lot?
You clearly don't know your son.
He managed to marry my daughter.
He's really something.
Pardon?
It's a compliment.
As a lawyer, he should be
good at calculating, being practical,
and taking what he wants.
-What do you--
-I'm saying he's smart
he didn't miss this opportunity.
What do you mean by "this opportunity"?
I'm sure you know.
Right.
Whatever you mean by it,
it's a marriage between our kids.
I know that.
Exactly. I just wanted
to say that it'd be nice,
as their parents, if we could help them
lead a happy marriage. That's all.
If it's their marriage,
it's their business to lead a happy life.
Why should we help?
Who's she to tell me what to do?
Divorce or not,
I'm so worried.
Please live a good life, will you?
Shoo!
Don't forget to drink orange juice
in the morning.
That's your hangover cure.
Isn't that too cold?
Want me to make you some tea?
Something warm would be better.
I'm good.
Hold on.
Keep yourself presentable.
You're not a kid.
My goodness.
I wondered why my heart was pounding.
It was because I was scared. That's it.
That's why my heart was racing so much.
What do you think?
I'm wearing this to the meeting tonight.
I see.
It's a Hercyna vintage jacket from 1982.
-Is that so?
-There are only two pieces in the world.
CEO Hermann's wife has one,
and the other is this one.
You don't like it?
That's not it.
Well…
It looks fine.
Why does she look pretty?
Why?
Why on earth?
What are you doing?
Let's go.
I like your suit.
My suit?
Yes. You look good.
You must be in a good mood.
No, not really.
But you were humming.
-Was I?
-Yes.
-When?
-Just now.
Are you excited?
Because she complimented you?
Is that why you were humming?
God, have I gone crazy?
Maybe I have since she hasn't
complimented me in so long, or…
Look at her frown.
She's unhappy with something.
She'll throw a fit soon.
Five, four, three, two, one.
What happened to decorating
the personal shopper room like a gallery?
-Oh, no.
-The artist's reputation and colors
don't suit the interior design!
Yelling and glaring like that,
she looks so mean.
That's why I get scared
and my heart races.
Yes, this is what I was talking about!
What happened? She's excited.
Not bad.
What the… What's wrong with me?
Why did I smile?
Get a grip.
Hey, that's dangerous.
You know how actors fall in love for real
while filming romantic scenes together.
Like Hyun Bin and Son Ye-jin.
That's not the case.
And yet you bought her shoes?
Goodness.
The whole point of an escalator
is to avoid having to walk up.
She's so impatient.
I can't believe her.
Watch out!
Did someone just yell?
I heard it too.
What kind of lunatic yells like that here?
Sir?
Can I help you?
Well…
Do you have a pair of these in size 240?
That's why you bought the shoes for her?
She hasn't changed her will.
I can't let her
-fall and die.
-Right.
-So that's why?
-Of course.
Even I was surprised
that I was so calculating
and cold-hearted.
So? What did she say?
So, you bought them
because they were 50% off?
And today is the last day.
Plus, 240 is a popular size,
and the white ones
are sold out all over the country.
Except for this pair.
I had to buy them.
I'm sure you did.
But my shoe closet
is full of expensive shoes
that I had to pay extra to buy.
Would I ever wear ones
bought at half price?
Of course, I know that you have
a lot of expensive, luxurious shoes.
But none of them are comfy.
-They're pretty.
-You're pretty even without them.
Besides, the heels are so thin and high.
I'm worried you might fall.
So why don't you
wear comfy shoes once in a while?
Leave them here, then.
She didn't like them then.
I couldn't believe her reaction.
But even more unbelievable?
What is it?
She wore them.
-Wow, Ms. Hong looks so…
-Right?
Pretty, right?
No, she looks so feisty today.
As if she's ready to crush anyone.
Exactly.
Anyway, those two meet
so often these days.
-This is Secretary Na.
-Oh, hi.
Right.
It's because of the Hercyna store.
Recently, Mr. Yoon
has been visiting every day,
having meals and coffee,
and even taking walks with her.
It seems you don't know this,
but workaholics even use
mealtimes and coffee breaks
to talk about work.
That's why.
Mr. Yoon may be her friend,
but he clearly doesn't know Hae-in well.
Hae-in hates it
when someone touches her hair like that.
She's smiling.
It seems she doesn't really hate it.
So is it bothering you?
Does it make you jealous?
Were you even listening?
Don't you get my point?
That's your point. You're jealous.
Don't you know what "jealousy" means?
That's what you feel when you like someone
and a rival happens to show up.
That's the wrong premise.
I don't even like Hae-in.
Why would I be jealous?
-So it doesn't bother you?
-No, not at all.
I don't care if they're close
or if they go anywhere together.
I got it, but what are you grilling
instead of meat?
Are you wearing those?
My husband bought them for me
and asked that I wear them. What can I do?
Still, we're meeting the CEO of Hercyna.
Wouldn't it be better to wear their shoes?
Want me to find you some?
I'm wearing their clothes.
Their shoes are uncomfortable.
And he's worried that I might fall.
Who is?
Hyun-woo is.
What a worrywart.
Right.
What?
Whatever Hermann says, just listen.
When he's done,
just say one thing.
Sara Lopez?
She's a popular designer in Europe.
We're planning to open up a store.
What about her?
She's Hermann's new mistress.
I see.
And his wife doesn't know?
She's a hot-tempered, competent lawyer.
If she finds out,
he'll never see his baby girl.
Hermann was glaring at you.
Because besides the two,
I was the only one who knew.
Aren't you in a fix, then?
It's all right.
I have a few more cards
to play against him.
Ye-na was right.
You're not the Eun-sung I knew.
What's happened?
I've worked very hard
to hear this from you.
A debt or kindness, I always repay it.
I owe you one.
All right. I'll hold you to it.
WALNUT AND PEANUT SNACKS
One bag of peanut cakes, please.
Sure.
Please pack it in two layers.
Okay.
-You're bringing it home?
-Yes.
This is why I'm suspicious.
In my eyes, if you think of her
when you see these snacks
when you're drunk,
it means you love her!
Love, my foot.
-They're just peanut cakes.
-Here.
You want one too?
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
They're just…
peanut cakes.
Where are you? Hurry home.
I have something to tell you.
Don't worry.
It's good news that you'll love.
Something to tell me?
Good news that you'll love?
Wait! No way.
-What?
-"I leave all my assets
to Baek Hyun-woo."
Changing her will.
-Come on. No way.
-Yes way!
It must be it! Yay!
Congrats, you punk!
-Don't forget about me.
-It can't be that.
Let go.
You punk!
Hey.
These are peanut cakes. Want some?
I wanted to give you this
before it got cold.
So I rushed home.
How is it?
It's good.
It's still warm.
Right?
By the way,
what is this good news I'll love?
Right.
Why don't you open it?
This?
Open it?
Don't be surprised.
Okay.
I won't.
I got it just earlier.
It's from one of the best cancer centers
in Europe.
On the next pages
are their research papers.
Yes.
That's right.
They think they can cure me.
-What?
-And the chance…
is over 50%.
Over?
I knew you'd be so happy.
Here.
The chance is about 51%.
And they'd like
to do clinical treatments on me.
-It's true.
-What did I say?
I said I'd never lose to that illness.
That God's on my side.
You're on my side,
and so is God.
My goodness.
I feel so reassured.
If
she is cured,
then…
The team dinner finished
-at 9:30 p.m. last night, so why…
-Why did you have to bring it up at…
Didn't I tell you?
I'm just worried.
-Say something!
-It's not Hyun-woo.
-You're a part of our Hong family!
-Hyun-woo!
Hurry up. We're going to be late.
This is why you're always late.
-I'm sorry.
-You're so frustrating.
A life like that
for 50 more years?
No.
I should get a divorce
as I originally planned.
DIVORCE AGREEMENT
Right.
Now that I've been cured,
you're going to betray me?
You got your life back,
so I want mine back too.
Right.
People can feel that way.
It's understandable.
However…
Not my people.
It might be worse than my imagination.
God, I'm exhausted.
-Goodness.
-Are you okay?
Yes, I'm all right.
Goodness, it's exhausting.
Goodness.
I've gotten a lot better.
Dad, aren't you thirsty? Have this.
Right. Thanks.
Can I really drink this?
You didn't poison it, did you?
Come on, Dad. Just drink it.
What's gotten into you?
I was always like this.
Look at this.
We used to be so happy together.
I mean, we used to be,
before some bitch entered the picture.
We weren't this messed up.
Mr. Hong, I'll go inside first.
Dad, do you remember
how much you adored me?
You doted on me.
You always bought a gift for me
on your way back from your business trips.
That was ages ago.
You always told me to live
with you forever without getting married.
And see? I'm still by your side.
I didn't tell you
to get married and come back.
Come on.
Love is about coming back, Dad.
Why did I come back within three years
whenever I got married?
That's because
your lovely daughter loves you.
Hey, stop. I'm eating soon.
-I'll lose my appetite.
-Oh, no.
You shouldn't lose your appetite.
At your age, it's more dangerous
than running out of money.
What is it? Just say it.
Why are you being like this?
You know, it's my birthday
the day after tomorrow.
I don't want anything else.
I just want to go on a date
with my beloved dad, just the two of us.
-Please?
-My God.
Please, Dad?
I want to have
something delicious with you.
-Stop it.
-Will you treat me to something nice?
Hey, stop. That's gross!
Stop! Go away!
Hey.
-Hello.
What are you doing here
in the morning on a weekend?
For the negotiation with Hercyna.
Oh, then I should join you.
The Legal Team should be in the loop
to work on the details.
That'll come later.
We're discussing the negotiation
between the CEOs
to get rid of any deal-breaking factors.
Are we bothering you?
We can go somewhere else.
What about my hotel?
You can just do it here.
Here, comfortably.
Thank you.
I should thank you.
You're helping my wife.
Want some coffee?
-Yes, thanks.
-Sure.
You too? You don't drink coffee
on an empty stomach.
That's true.
-An espresso for you, right?
-Yes.
She cares for me so much.
What?
She says coffee's like poison
on an empty stomach and it's unhealthy.
She doesn't let me drink it.
I mean, I'm not her kid, you know?
I guess she can't stop
worrying about me.
Hae-in must care so much for you.
I envy you.
Well, yes. I think so too.
She's not like that to me.
She always asks me for help,
saying I'm the only one who can help her.
She was always like that.
She'd call me anytime asking for help,
saying I was the only one she had.
How could I not help then?
Even this time around. This kind
of negotiation could even take a year.
But she asked me
to finish it in two weeks.
I won't have time to do anything else
while I'm in Korea.
It seems
I have to be stuck with her all the time.
That's
reassuring.
Are you bringing this to him?
I'm suddenly curious.
About what?
Don't you hate it
when someone touches your hair?
-What?
-I mean,
when I touched it last time,
you yelled at me,
saying I was ruining your hairstyle.
What are you saying?
Put it simply.
You got mad when I did it,
so why didn't you when Mr. Yoon did it?
What?
Oh, that's because--
I want you to be fair.
Not just Mr. Yoon.
If any guy touches your hair,
you should get mad.
Except for your hairdresser.
She just left…
without saying anything.
How could she do that?
Darn it.
Goodness.
God…
This is unbelievable.
I've never been this annoyed
at someone's smile.
He really is something.
He's still smiling. What?
That jerk. Why is he pulling it down?
Hey, you bastard. Wait.
Wait. Hey.
What's wrong with him?
You think I can't watch you
if you do this?
I'll find a way, no matter what.
I'm…
just walking by.
Walking around.
It's not because I'm curious.
Goodness.
What?
What is it?
Didn't you say "Honey"?
No, I didn't.
I see.
I must've heard wrong.
All right.
Well, carry on.
Call me if you need me.
No, I won't need you today.
Just go and rest.
I am resting.
-Hey.
-Yes?
No, not you.
Eun-sung!
I heard my sister
was bothering you on Sunday, so I came.
Hey, get lost.
We're working.
You know,
I tried to contact you many times,
but your secretary
doesn't suit your international,
clean-cut image.
She hung up on me without knowing
how close we are. I was so hurt.
Really? I'll talk to them, Mr. Hong.
Don't be so formal with me.
Just treat me like your little brother.
Seriously, I feel closer to you
than Hyun-woo,
who's been my brother-in-law
for three years.
You're still here?
I'm leaving.
-No, don't come out.
-Right.
I won't.
Have you eaten yet?
Why are you so down?
The way I see it,
Eun-sung's like your new hope.
What do you mean?
Hae-in has a 51% chance of living now.
Of course, you should be happy for her.
But your hope is gone.
Your hope for a rich and safe parting.
So?
What if Eun-sung and Hae-in fall in love?
You'll get alimony.
No, not Yoon Eun-sung.
Why not?
That guy's creepy.
Who cares?
Hey, I think he's your savior.
You should be grateful
that he's come to save you.
There is something off with him.
-I can feel it.
-Come on.
Who cares what your savior is like?
If you're drowning, and you don't like
the rescuer, will you not
grab the rope?
In any case,
I can't let it be that bastard.
I said no.
Are you okay?
Eun-sung.
See this land? It's a million pyeong.
Neverland is 430,000 pyeong,
and Souland is 280,000 pyeong.
It's bigger than the two combined.
Impressive.
You know the two most important things
in the resort business,
securing the land and licensing.
As you can see, we have the land,
and as for licensing…
We have our person
in the Ministry of Land.
Is that so?
He studied with Queens scholarships.
And he was my tutor.
-I see.
-Right.
K-pop, K-drama.
Korean content is so popular these days.
Let's outdo Disney together, Eun-sung!
I'll think about it.
Oh, my.
He meets all these people?
Do you know Robert Bailey,
the legendary hedge fund manager?
Among his 12 apprentices,
this guy's the best one.
Robert even entrusted his asset management
with him. What more is there to say?
Really?
He's perfect
as Mr. Hong Soo-cheol's partner.
But he's quite picky, so…
But he's willingly
helping Hae-in regarding Hercyna.
Yes, since the two are so close.
And that might be why
Mr. Yoon isn't getting close to Mr. Hong.
What do you mean?
Think about it.
For Ms. Hong,
if Hercyna opens in her mall, she'll reach
one trillion won in sales for sure.
Then the chairman will lean towards
giving the group to her, as he promised.
Are you saying
Hae-in doesn't want Soo-cheol to succeed
in attracting investment for the resort?
Yes! Soo-cheol could turn the tables.
I mean, I don't know
what Ms. Hong told Mr. Yoon,
but it seems he doesn't consider
Mr. Hong as a potential partner.
He's having dinner
with Chairman Yeom's grandchild tonight.
Fortune telling doesn't lie.
I told you, didn't I?
Ms. Hong's fated
to prey on her siblings all her life.
Anyway, you don't need anything else
to deal with her.
Fortune telling is like the Bible to her.
If you look up anything online
and tell her,
she just believes it.
But that worked to your advantage.
That's true. I've benefitted
a lot from it for about 15 years.
What brings you here?
I knew it.
If I hadn't withdrawn the suit, your mall
in Gwanggyo wouldn't even be happening.
Do you want that?
Stop beating around the bush.
Just tell me.
What did you tell
Eun-sung about Soo-cheol?
What did you say that made him
not consider investing in Soo-cheol?
What do you mean?
It's obvious.
"If Soo-cheol gets investment, it's bad
for me. So invest in Sang-jin instead."
Because that would make
the chairman furious.
Do you think that even makes sense?
Yes! I think
you're more than capable of doing that.
Because you're a bitch
who's selfish to the bone.
You don't care if anyone around you dies.
You just find a way to save yourself.
And that's why your older brother…
She's been feeling unwell
since this morning.
I think she needs to rest.
I'm sorry, Mother.
So are you telling me to leave?
When I'm still talking to her?
I'm sorry.
Let's tell your family.
I said no.
Situations like earlier
can happen anytime.
They might find out.
I'll get treated.
You're acting
like I'll drop dead tomorrow.
You're being
selfish and irresponsible.
Yes.
You're thinking about your money, stocks,
and the One Trillion Club. I get it.
I get that you're worried your family
could take what's yours if they find out.
But,
keeping this important matter from them
because you don't want anything
to be taken.
Is that right?
I don't want to shock them.
My parents…
They already lost a child.
So why scare them?
I can never be a good daughter anyway.
I just
don't want to be
a more terrible existence to my family.
And more importantly,
I'm confident I'll be cured.
So stop treating me like a patient.
Can you leave?
I want to rest.
And the stock purchase?
We bought 14.7% in total, 4.9% per person.
And the directors supporting the chairman?
The rate of return of the last blind trust
was close to 90%,
so they're eager to join the next fund.
We need to lead them to put
Queens stocks up as collateral next.
The minimum amount is so high,
I doubt they can come up
with that much cash in days.
If we rush them,
they'll put their stocks up as collateral.
Next is Chairman Hong.
The prosecution investigation.
I feel bad for him.
He hates jail.
By the way, how will you do it?
The chairman's real safekeeper
is Song Jeong-beom in Finance.
He's siphoning off his own share
as well as the chairman's slush funds.
We'll hand all the evidence
over to the prosecution.
And as they look into the higher-ups,
they will end up investigating
the chairman too.
You can see the Queens Tower from here.
And I like that.
It feels like
I'm looking at a delicious meal.
Damn it.
I told you to make the font bigger.
Darn it. Prepare the documents again
and set another meeting.
I can't believe them.
Get out!
Out!
I think I can let you join
the private equity fund.
The minimum amount is 20 billion won.
And you can put your Queens stocks up
as collateral if you're short of cash.
The earnings rate's expected to be higher.
First come, first served.
So make a quick decision.
Confidentiality is a must.
-Thank you.
-I understand.
That's possible.
She's already here.
What's gotten into Beom-ja?
Why does she suddenly
want to treat me to a meal?
The chairman has arrived.
No, Dad. You can't leave.
-Over my dead body.
-Move.
Dad, just hear me out.
I don't want anything else.
Just give me a chance.
You bastard.
Did I not give you a chance?
I gave you one, but you sold me out
to the prosecution to save yourself!
While I was locked up,
you schemed to take my place
with the directors who supported you.
-Have you forgotten?
-I wasn't in my right mind.
I heard you were trying
to pin the embezzlement charge on me,
so I lost it.
I'm so sorry.
It's been 20 years.
You would've even forgiven a stranger
after this long.
Why are you so harsh on your son?
I would rather forgive a stranger!
How could I forgive my own child
who betrayed me?
I just can't.
So never do something like this again.
Dad!
I missed you.
That's really why I came.
Well, you've seen me now.
I don't want to
see you again.
You ingrate.
Don't even come to my funeral.
Darn it.
Why do you look so down?
It seems you haven't eaten.
When you're not feeling well,
there's nothing better than
a bowl of this.
My mother always made me this
when I was sick.
Back when I used to sell newspapers
and shine people's shoes in Myeong-dong.
When I was hungry or sick,
I always thought of this.
Have some.
From sleeping on the streets
using newspapers as blankets
to owning one of Korea's
top department stores and mart franchises,
it took 60 years.
But why does it feel like
I'm standing alone in the wilderness?
Something must've
hurt your feelings badly.
Only I know how tenderhearted
you are.
It tastes just like
my mother's.
Why can't you give us a refund?
My baby's skin got ruined
after she used this,
but you can't give us a refund,
let alone compensate us?
Sir, it's been over eight months
since you purchased the product,
and you've almost used it all.
Hey. I'm glad you brought it up.
My face looks like this
because I used this much.
If I hadn't, my skin
wouldn't have become like this!
Babe, don't get worked up.
It'll get worse.
Just give us a refund right now.
Sir, we can't do that.
Didn't I make myself clear enough?
Sir, please calm down.
How can I calm down?
Right. You think I'm one
of those obnoxious customers, don't you?
Want me to show you the real thing?
Sir, you can't do this here.
I wanted to use our security deposit
for her surgery, but my mom won't listen.
This is an unreasonable demand.
We cannot help you.
"Unreasonable"?
You're hopeless. Come here.
How dare you talk to me--
Who the hell are you?
Let go.
Let go of me.
This is not the place for such behavior.
Look, I have no business
with you small fry.
Bring your CEO.
Bring your CEO right now!
-She's here.
-What?
I'm the CEO.
Are you the CEO?
Why didn't you
train your employee properly?
You're right.
I don't think I did it properly.
Ms. Kim Min-ji?
Deal with our customers only.
As for criminals, report them
to the police without warning.
What? A criminal?
You call your customers criminals?
Babe, are you filming this?
Yeah.
The CEO of this mall
looks down on her customers.
Let's sue her and teach her a lesson.
Let's do that.
Make sure to do it.
I will too.
I know well
since my husband is a good lawyer.
You can be charged
with obstruction of business,
special assault,
and property damage.
And I'll file another suit
for the sales loss you caused.
-Did you all film it?
-Yes, we did!
-I did. Here!
-Please make way.
Take them to the police.
Let's go, babe.
Thank you.
By the way, Mr. Baek, about Park Seok-hun.
What about him?
He's going around saying
that the Yongdu Pear you're promoting
as our village specialty has no future.
He claims the Yongdu Apple will be
the new K-food craze around the world.
Apple? Goodness.
That's just ridiculous.
Traditionally, apples
are no match for pears.
Of course… Really?
Just think about memorial services.
We put pears on the tables, not apples!
Besides, persimmons and pears go together.
Persimmons and apples don't.
How dare he downplay the importance
of pears, our traditional fruit?
Anyway, this guy's running
an election campaign in such smart ways.
You know his mom's restaurant?
He's offering half-price lunches,
so everyone's eating there now.
You idiot!
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
That little…
He's not playing fair, is he?
Are you going there?
HALF-PRICE LUNCH
Hello.
Hey, Mr. Park.
The soup is especially good today.
Come on. It's always been good.
What is this?
It's like a feast.
We should compete with pledges and plans.
But he's trying to win people over
with a popular song.
I mean, if he wins the election like this,
it's not his victory. It's the singer's!
It should be considered
an election law violation. Yes.
Chun-sik, gather the evidence.
Those who entertain and those
who play along. I'll report the whole lot!
Come on!
You're all doomed.
Wait. What…
-Mr. Baek.
-What?
Seok-hun! I'll have one more pork platter.
One more soju, too!
It's so delicious!
That piece of…
You son of…
I ought to…
How bad is it?
He walked right into their trap.
Family corruption. It's an issue even
the country's presidents couldn't avoid.
The current village head's son let
the opposite side treat him to a meal.
People say the head's family is ruined
because his children
weren't properly disciplined.
You idiot!
I can't believe you!
Dad, I'll change their opinion
from now on.
What can you do?
My salon produces roughly 90%
of the rumors going around Yongdu-ri.
You know, gossipers!
-We can use them.
-Like a smear campaign?
Exactly! Seok-hun stole snacks
from our store
when he was a kid.
We'll expose that.
"He who will steal an egg
will steal an ox!"
What do you think?
Got a cigarette?
I quit smoking.
Mi-seon, are you coming?
Your father and Seok-hun
will have a big face-off.
Go ahead.
I don't think so. Your family needs
as many people as possible on their side.
-Why?
-What do you mean, why?
Because the head is at a disadvantage now.
Just go!
Just come!
For God's sake! Just go!
No, Pinky!
You go back in.
I am standing here
because our village needs young people.
As I said earlier,
I will make the Yongdu Apple
a K-food loved by people around the world!
I, Park Seok-hun, will recover
the two years Yongdu-ri lost!
He's well received.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Everyone, our Yongdu-ri
is like the heart of Korean pears.
Well, isn't the heart of pears
Naju or Seongju?
That's right! Yongdu-ri
isn't the heart. It's more like…
How do I put it?
It's more like the intestine.
Am I right?
Right. If it were the heart, our pears
would be sold
at his daughter-in-law's department store.
You're right!
What? Why bring that up here?
My daughter-in-law
keeps her work and private life apart!
I get that she's a good CEO.
But her private life?
To be blunt, we only heard
she and your son got married.
-We've never seen her.
-Didn't she come on a chopper?
Right. I thought war had broken out then.
It's true that she's never visited
since they got married.
It was before they got married?
-What?
-What's going on?
-Is it an earthquake?
-What's happening?
YONGDU-RI COMMUNITY HALL
-What's that?
-Film it.
They brought a lot.
Father?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my.
No way…
She came.
Finally.
What are you doing here?
I'm glad you're all here.
I missed your last birthday,
so I came to treat
the villagers to a meal.
Hello, I'm Hong Hae-in,
the village head's daughter-in-law.
What's going on?
I texted her.
You said you'd visit us one of these days.
Can that day be today and right now?
My father's running for reelection,
and it's not looking good.
I think he needs to show people
someone influential is supporting him.
Oh, she read it!
It says "read."
She came because of that text?
I can't believe it either.
Good job!
Hong Hae-in!
It's not much.
Expensive nutritional supplements,
ginseng,
cosmetics, silk scarves,
cashmere mufflers,
Italian leather gloves, so on.
I was going to buy
just a little for Father,
but I went overboard.
You can share.
Oh, my. I can't believe you.
You bought too much.
-Baek Du-gwan!
-Hae-in!
Everyone! What's Yongdu-ri's specialty?
Apples or pears?
-Pears!
-Baek Du-gwan!
-Hae-in!
BAEK DU-GWAN
A HARD WORKER WHO PROTECTS YONGDU-RI
Hyun-woo. Hae-in's here.
-Hey.
-Mom, I missed your call.
It's all right. How are you?
I heard Mi-seon and Hyeon-tae went there.
You must've been surprised.
No, it's okay.
Nothing bad happened, so don't worry.
And Hae-in is…
Yes, she's doing well too.
What do you mean?
Did you two fight?
Of course not.
Then why don't you know where she is?
She's here.
What? Why would she be there?
You should come ask her yourself.
The whole village
is having a feast thanks to her.
What's she talking about?
Where's Hae-in right now?
BAEK HYUN-WOO
Who are you?
Me?
I'm the daughter-in-law.
-Who are you?
-I know everyone in this family,
but I've never seen you.
I don't come here often.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm part of the family.
Then what's the dog's name?
Musty.
Spotty?
They have no dog.
You look suspicious.
Why are you so suspicious?
I'm the wife of Baek Hyun-woo,
the son of this family. Happy? Now go.
You're the building owner.
You should've told me sooner.
-What?
-My dad told me
Uncle Hyun-woo's wife
is the owner of our building.
Let me properly greet you, Aunt.
-I'm Baek Ho-yeol.
-I see.
You're my nephew that I only heard about.
Yes, I am.
I saw an unfamiliar car
in front of the house.
Is it yours, Aunt?
Yes, it is.
That's sick.
A V8 engine,
the horsepower and speed tuning.
That rare car is really yours?
Could I have a ride, please?
If I let you, will you stop talking to me?
I promise you.
Can you drive him around the village?
Maybe three or four laps.
Yes, ma'am.
My youngest is here!
Gosh, Hyun-woo.
The massage chair you gave us last time.
It's so good. Thank you so much.
My friends told me to take a picture
with you when I met you.
Is that okay?
Two, three.
I'm sorry, but can you step aside?
Come on.
Your arm, too.
-Even my arm?
-Just the two of us.
Now, now. He installed air conditioners
and boilers in our senior center.
Hyun-woo's the pride of Yongdu-ri.
Give him a round of applause!
He's my brother.
My brother.
Eat your fill.
Well…
I heard it from your brother and sister.
But don't worry about me.
I never mentioned
the divorce to your wife.
You're mentioning it now, Dad.
Don't worry.
She's not here. She's at home.
-No, she's not.
-What?
I just picked up Ho-yeol.
She wasn't there.
What are you talking about?
She's not there.
Hello, Mr. Baek.
Where's Hae-in?
Is she not at the community hall?
When I came back, she wasn't here.
Hong Hae-in!
Hae-in!
What happened?
-Why are you here?
-Why are you yelling?
I heard you came here out of the blue,
so I came, but you weren't home
or at the hall.
No one knew where you were.
You didn't answer your phone!
So,
-why are you here--
-Hold on.
I came out for a walk.
A walk in this neighborhood?
Yes.
-I was worried!
-Why would you be?
I'm not a patient.
Right.
Yes, you told me that.
I'm sorry I yelled.
The truth is…
I don't remember.
I don't remember at all why I was there.
I was in front of your house,
then suddenly I was somewhere else.
I don't know when I went there
or how.
I have no idea.
I was…
so scared.
NAMED OUTSTANDING SCHOOL OF 2006
-We're here.
-Okay.
-See you later.
-See you.
Wait, Hyun-woo.
Seoul people aren't that different.
Don't feel discouraged.
Stand firm.
-Firm.
-Stand upright.
And try to glare like this.
-Okay.
-Good. Go in.
-Bye, Dad.
-Bye.
-Listen to your teacher.
-Drive safe!
Hae-in's going to the States to study.
Say goodbye to her, okay?
-Yes, sir.
Look at her face.
She's still so full of herself.
There's a rumor that she's
being admitted to a mental hospital.
I heard it's because she went mad
after her brother died.
Wait.
Take it.
I don't need it.
Clean it and put some ointment on it.
Are you crying?
I'm not.
You are.
QUEEN OF TEARS
Don't you dare mention the divorce.
You got it.
Divorce is nothing.
I wanted to get a divorce too.
-What's wrong?
-Don't mind me.
How could their love die?
They used to be madly in love.
The woman I love right now is you.
Your white blood cell count is too low.
I will find a way.
Even if I have to search the world,
I'll find a way to live.
So I should be…
by your side at times like this.
I wanted you
to be by my side.
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu