QUEEN OF TEARS
EPISODE 13
This is our house. Come on in.
Okay. This is my secret room.
When I open this handle
and press this button…
Okay. What do you think?
It's empty.
Look here.
It looks like something has been moved.
The marks look fresh.
Gosh, my dear father.
He must've secretly stashed it here,
but I guess that bitch got to it again.
He didn't even tell
his own children about this secret room.
Did you send him off well?
It was you, wasn't it?
You killed our father.
-Why would I?
-Because you didn't need him
after taking his money.
Where is it?
I don't know what you're saying.
Your father is dead,
and you still want his money.
-Your poor father.
-Cut the nonsense.
Leave this house right now.
You have no right to be here anymore.
I'm a legal resident here.
If you want to kick me out,
the court needs to order it first.
Aren't you aware of this, Attorney Baek?
Is this true? We can't just kick her out?
There's a procedure,
but you'll have to leave.
We'll see about that.
We're moving back in.
-Do you still want to stay?
-Why not?
We've been living together
for over 20 years.
You said we were family.
-But--
-Suit yourself.
We'll be back soon.
Let's see if you can bear it.
Hae-in.
Grandfather?
I would've loved to speak to you
in person.
But still,
I'm glad I can talk to you like this.
Thank you.
I briefly come to my senses
every now and then
like a basement
that receives limited sunlight.
But there's not much I can do.
I don't remember much either.
I'm just full of regrets.
I've been a money-grubber all my life.
I did everything in my power
to keep the money I gathered.
I wasted most of my years doing that.
What am I left with?
I'd like you all to know that I regret
the life I led.
FORMER CHAIRMAN HONG MAN-DAE
I hope you live differently.
I truly hope
that you won't look back in futility
at the end of the road.
Dad…
I love you all.
And…
I'm sorry.
You need to eat even if you're not hungry.
Do you want to go
inside the car if you're cold?
It's okay.
This feels
very strange.
It feels like I'm doing a rehearsal.
A rehearsal?
A death rehearsal.
I didn't know
a funeral was so complex.
They dig a hole in the ground,
place the coffin,
have some rice soup in a tent,
and mourn by the grave.
Then when it's time,
they'll all go home.
And I'll be all by myself.
You know that the three months
I've been given
have already passed.
I could even die tonight.
But my family
would have to mourn again if I died.
That wouldn't
look good for our family, right?
Was that
what you've been worrying about?
That your family would mourn again?
No.
I kept thinking that I wanted to live.
It's sunny.
The clouds look pretty,
and the birds are chirping.
This world is annoyingly beautiful.
So, of course, I want to live.
CHECKING ID
PLEASE WAIT
How did you find it?
DREAMLAND THEME PARK
Okay. This is my secret room.
When I open this handle
and press this button…
Thank you.
I told you.
I loved you in my own way.
This money will keep you safe.
His daughter is sick,
and now, he lost his father.
Mr. Hong must be devastated.
Right.
But you can say
things are looking up for his family
after the chairman passed away.
-Is that so?
-Gosh.
Hear me out.
Look.
Chairman Hong had entrusted
21% of his shares
to that woman, Moh Seul-hee.
But now that he's passed away,
-his family received it.
-I see.
Yoon Eun-sung's total shares were 59.1%.
But now, it has plummeted to 38.1%.
Once our in-laws get hold
of their frozen shares,
-they'll have 34.7% in total.
-I see.
Then the gap will be 3.4%.
-That's quite neck and neck.
-Right.
How do you know this so well?
-I'm a club member.
-What club?
The Queens Minor Stockholders' Club.
We're waiting for the management
feud results with bated breath.
What for?
I know I'm being calculating.
But what do you think
-will happen to Hyun-woo?
-What do you mean?
Let's be honest. He's been doing
his utmost best to help them
after everything.
Perhaps, they'll thank him in some way.
Maybe they'll give him some shares
or appoint him as a CEO later on.
I don't ask for much,
but could you do me this one favor?
Sure.
What is it?
If someone asks you who your father is,
please don't tell them it's me.
Jeez.
Why not?
Why not? Hey, wait for me.
Thank you for everything.
Gosh, don't mention it.
Things will look up
once you return to Seoul.
Do you think so?
You see…
These persimmons
used to be very bitter.
But there's a way
to turn this awfully bitter fruit
-into a sweet one.
-How?
It's by soaking them.
You pour some soju on top,
wrap the bodies,
then let them sit for some time.
Then they become sweet.
Here. Try it.
It's sweet.
Life can be bitter
just like these persimmons.
Life is tough as is,
so imagine pouring
some bitter soju on top.
Gosh, it'd be utterly unbearable.
But if you endure it,
life will become sweet again.
And that'll motivate you to stay strong.
Don't you think so?
Right.
Hey, come and have a drink with us.
Sure.
INTERNATIONAL CALL
I got a call from Germany. Excuse me.
Does that mean she can receive surgery?
Yes.
Thank God.
Her case was a difficult one
since they couldn't open up her brain.
But they can destroy the tumor cells
using high-intensity ultrasound.
They had a successful case recently too.
Good. Things are looking up now.
Thanks, Hyun-woo. Does Hae-in know?
-I should tell her.
-However…
there's a problem.
Goodness, Hae-in. This feels like a dream.
Gosh, this must be a gift
from Father.
Is it true?
-Can she receive surgery?
-Yes.
I'm so happy for you.
Goodness.
I'm so grateful.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, sweetie.
How did they reach you? Via email? Phone?
Was it a video call?
They called me.
A phone call?
You don't think
they were scammers, do you?
No, they weren't.
I see.
Okay. Good night.
By the way, are you sure
the surgery works in rare cases like mine?
Yes.
I'm sure.
I see.
And the date?
Tell them I can go right away.
I did.
Good then.
Are you saying
that this surgery
will save my life?
Does Hae-in know?
I should tell her.
However…
there's a problem.
A part of the hippocampus will be damaged
-during the process.
-And?
It's highly likely…
that she'll lose her long-term memory.
Hold on.
What are you saying?
She could lose all her memory
from before the surgery.
But this is our only choice
if we want her
to live.
Her WBC isn't going up quickly,
so she can't receive the clinical test.
We really have no time now.
She might refuse the surgery
if she hears about the side effects.
But what if
she runs out of time?
Hyun-woo.
Keep this a secret.
Why don't you take her to Germany first,
then persuade her there?
I beg you.
She needs the surgery to live.
Will I be able to live then?
What is it?
Yes, you will.
Don't worry.
All right.
Night.
Hae-in.
It's okay.
I'm fine. I really am.
It's just been ages since I felt fine.
These are tears of joy.
Yes, I know.
It feels like
I woke up from a long nightmare.
You're okay now.
Let's go to bed.
HAE-IN
HYUN-WOO
You don't have to go to work today, right?
No.
Then let's hang out.
Okay, let's do that.
GURANG-RI STATION
TICKET OFFICE
Two people.
All right.
-Okay, good.
-What?
Other than our honeymoon,
isn't this our first trip?
You're right.
I've been too much of a workaholic.
Let's go on many trips
after I receive surgery.
Promise.
Okay.
Listen.
I want everything to be smooth
before I receive surgery.
You know I only drink extracted juice
for the same reason, right?
I do. What's on your mind?
I wasn't planning on hiding them,
but there are three things
I kept from you.
Three?
I'll come clean before I go.
I'll tell you one for today.
Sure. What is it?
You said
that you found this MP3.
I did.
It's mine.
-What?
-Do you see this "H"?
It stands for "Hae-in".
I had lost it in our schoolyard
before going abroad for my studies.
And look where it is now.
That can't be.
It sure can.
I don't believe it.
Something unbelievable happened to us.
It may not mean much to you
since I was just a nobody in your life.
No, you're wrong.
Listen. I actually--
Don't be afraid.
I'm not scolding you. Why?
Because I'm not the old me.
I'll be reborn soon.
I'm going to be optimistic
and only see the good in life.
Is that so?
Yes.
This MP3
is a living witness to our history.
So I'm only going to focus
on that positive point.
That's good.
Eun-sung told me
how he had saved me in the past
and made it seem like we were fated.
What? Fated?
Jeez.
Has he gone crazy or what?
How dare he say that?
So what? We have our own movie-like story.
When I saw you at the schoolyard,
I thought, "Does this handsome kid
go to my school?
I can't believe I'm leaving.
I feel terrible."
That's what I thought.
Black slip-ons.
You were wearing
black slip-ons.
You had white socks
and very fair skin.
And your hair was in a high ponytail.
I did wear ponytails often back then.
The moment I saw you, I thought,
"I found her."
"My dream girl."
I looked everywhere for you
starting the next day.
I didn't have a chance
to look at your name tag.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You were like Cinderella.
You had only left behind your MP3.
It drove me crazy.
But look at us now.
We crossed paths again, got married…
We did get divorced, but still.
This is what you call true fate.
All right.
Since I'm your dream woman,
and this is fate…
From now on…
I didn't know
that phrase was this beautiful.
I'm getting teary-eyed.
I thought I wouldn't be
a part of your future.
But now, we have a future together.
Speaking of which…
I'll withdraw our divorce like you asked.
What's with that face?
Don't take it back.
I run a department store.
I hate customers
who return things and demand a refund.
You can't take this back
even if you wake up one day
and dislike me.
A change of mind is not a valid reason
to get a refund. That's a given.
Even if we get
into huge fights
and you're sick of me…
Even if you claim that you don't remember
making this promise,
there's no taking back.
I'll still be by your side.
All right. Fine. Do that.
So stop talking.
I love it the most
when I can just focus on your heartbeat.
I did some calculations.
Five percent would be
forty-five billion won.
But I'll just ask for 40 billion.
I even have a car waiting outside
in case it's cash.
-A big one.
-Are you a creditor?
I may sound rude for saying this,
but perhaps our history
made me into who I am today.
I was betrayed several times
after doing all the work.
Check.
KO JEONG-JA
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten…
I respect you, ma'am.
A gorgeous face, a silver tongue,
and alluring charisma.
It's rare for one to have all of them.
I want to live wisely like you.
-The payment is suspended.
-Sorry?
You can only spend that money
when I let you.
Ma'am.
Our history made you
into who you are today?
Likewise. I was betrayed several times.
-Look.
-I'll lift the suspension
once I'm content with your work.
Then you can take it.
Goodness.
You sure are wise.
Mom!
What's all this?
It's not even kimchi-making season!
Hae-in's family is leaving,
but I have nothing to give.
I'll give them
some pear extract and kimchi.
This isn't little at all.
I thought I could share with our neighbors
and the elderly.
You can't do this alone.
Then go get some gloves and help out.
Well, I need these hands to make a living.
Let me help.
-Should I slice the radish?
-That'd be great.
Jeez, she's so fast.
She knows how to chop.
Her chopping skills
were out of this world.
-I see.
-And she has guts.
-Why?
Hey.
Do you think
I'll take you back if you do this?
I don't expect you to.
I'm going to leave once I'm done here.
Don't worry, Mother.
Yet you still call me that.
Are you teasing me? Don't call me that.
But I'd like to.
What?
You're the first person
I ever called "Mother."
So please let me do that.
-Here you go.
-Hey.
-Are you done?
-Anything else?
That's enough.
I'll chop the green onions.
Unbelievable.
-I kind of like her.
-Why?
I like how she's not intimidated
and speaks her mind
in front of her mother-in-law.
Hae-in.
Come sit. They all heard
about your surgery and were happy for you.
I'm so happy for you.
-I'm glad.
-It all worked out.
Thank you.
By the way,
what were you doing?
Right. Have you done this before?
Dyeing your nails with balsam?
-No.
-Legend has it that if your nails
are still colored by the first snow,
your first love will come true.
That's why Bang-sil here always dyes hers
in the fall, not summer.
How romantic.
Actually, I'd say
she has an ulterior motive.
I wouldn't say it's an ulterior motive.
He happens to be divorced.
-Hey.
-I didn't feel like this before,
but we've been running
into each other often lately.
So my feelings…
Shut that mouth of yours.
-That's enough.
-Stop.
-Shut it.
-Sorry.
I guess I was too blunt.
I hope you're not offended, Ms. Hong.
-Why would I be?
-You see…
Hyun-woo used to flirt a lot with me
at church back when he was in high school.
When did he ever do that?
Didn't you know?
They used to hand out snacks at church,
and he'd always give me more than one
in front of everyone.
That's because
you always ate other kids' snacks.
Hae-in, please don't misunderstand.
Don't talk such nonsense, Bang-sil.
Until the first snow, was it?
-Check this out.
-Balsam?
It's not that simple.
-Then?
-It signifies my excitement, hope,
and anticipation for the first snow
that I thought I'd never see.
I didn't think I'd ever see winter again
let alone the first snow.
But it's possible now.
Of course.
And it'll come true
if the color still remains by then.
-What will come true?
-My first love.
By "first love,"
do you mean that guy
on the bus or taxi from before?
You're happy to watch them from afar.
You can't stop thinking about them.
You take a detour
just to see them once more.
You were happy to watch him from afar.
You couldn't stop thinking about him.
And you took a detour
just to see him once more.
That bastard?
Why are you cursing him?
Fine.
-That guy?
-Yes.
I hope it'll snow sooner
this year.
Hae-in, you even took my ring back.
Your first love shouldn't come true,
or it'll really complicate things.
Are you listening?
Hae-in.
-Michael met with Hong Beom-seok?
-Yes, as the CEO of Ever H.
I guess the eldest son wants to return
now that his father is dead.
Ever H recently appeared
on the stockholder's list
as a non-institutional investor.
He must've been gathering stocks
ever since they plummeted.
He's been asking
the anchor LPs for my spot.
He can try, but you'll be safe
with what I've given you.
As you said,
we founded paper companies
in Hong Kong and Switzerland
and opened up an IEBC business account.
You're the only one who can manage it.
-What will your first transaction be?
-Make it 2.1% in CD.
CD(CAREFUL DISCRETION): BUYING SMALL
AMOUNTS OF STOCK AT REGULAR INTERVALS
-Yes, sir.
-He took the bait.
He's finally using the secret fund.
He's probably worried
that my uncle might take his spot.
Is Mr. Hong still in New York?
Yes, he's still meeting with the LPs.
Keep Eun-sung in the loop
so that he'll feel anxious
and use the secret fund to buy stocks.
-Yes, sir.
-Once we have concrete proof,
we can charge him for embezzlement,
malpractice, and violating
foreign exchange transaction laws.
By the way,
about that guy, Pyeon Seong-uk…
Isn't he the land broker
who kidnapped you?
Yes, he had agreed to hand over
the double contract
and information on Director Jo.
But he never showed up,
and I can't reach him.
He hasn't been spending any money
or using his phone for over a week now.
Maybe he stowed away.
Oh, God!
A man, presumably in his 40s,
was found dead last night
near the Sambang Reservoir
in Yeongjin-gun, Gyeonggi Province.
He had been stabbed with a weapon,
and his identity remains unknown
due to severe decomposition--
How could this be mine,
but not mine at the same time?
Ms. Kim!
The amazing Grace is here!
Jeez, why is she back?
What are you doing?
Can't you see?
I'm making dried persimmons.
Goodness.
Your hands have gotten rough.
Look at those dark circles.
All the freckles
I worked hard to erase are back.
You'll be making a comeback soon.
It's a battlefield there.
Everyone will take sides between Ms. Moh,
that sly fox, and you.
What's the best way
to intimidate your opponent?
With your face, of course.
Lie down right now.
You need to look tight and radiant.
I've never done this before.
It's ticklish.
Don't smile, or you'll get wrinkles.
Keep these words in mind.
Whitening, resilience,
recovery, and comeback.
The best way to make a comeback
is through recovery and resilience.
Don't worry.
Everything will go back to its place.
We'll return to Queens,
and Hae-in will get surgery
and become healthy again.
Is she getting surgery?
I thought surgery wasn't an option.
We found a hospital that could do it.
She'll be leaving for Germany soon.
Is that so?
I'm so glad.
-Right?
Hello, I wanted to see you.
-See me?
-Yes.
-I have something for you.
-What is it?
But I didn't think I'd run into you,
so it's at home.
Shall we meet tonight?
-At night?
-Yes.
Sure then.
Why does he want to meet at this hour?
He's such a go-getter.
He's dangerous.
You were here already.
Yes.
-So I--
-Let me go first.
Okay. I'm listening.
I'll be leaving
tomorrow.
And I don't know when I'll ever revisit.
I heard that you were leaving so--
I know what you want to say.
I caught onto it
from the mulberry incident.
-But no.
-Sorry?
What do you--
I have
a lot on my plate.
Not only do I have movable assets,
real estate, stocks, and bonds,
but I also have three ex-husbands.
I had no idea.
Right?
Anyway…
I'm complicated
and carry many burdens.
So I can't
accept it.
I hope you still will.
What is this?
Did you write a letter?
You really shouldn't…
CONDOLENCES
KIM YEONG-SONG
It's condolence money.
I heard about your father.
I don't need this.
-I should go.
-No, wait.
Come on. This isn't right.
This isn't for you.
It's for your father.
Even the wealthiest
start off with no money in the afterlife.
It's not much, but I'm sure
he'll be able to enjoy
some rice soup and drinks tonight
with his friends.
He'll be enjoying good food
and having a great time with his friends.
So don't be too sad.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
What do you mean?
You want to stay here?
I'm dumbfounded.
It's temporary.
Just until we find a place in Seoul.
Your mother doesn't understand
why you need to find a place.
I've had two training wheels
throughout my whole life.
One was you.
And the other one was you.
What are you saying?
But now,
I want to remove them
and stand on my own two feet.
Don't be ridiculous.
Hey, did you persuade him?
-Did you urge him again?
-Honey, be quiet.
Don't say a thing.
Plead the Fifth.
You're forbidden
from speaking to her directly.
-If you want, speak to our attorney.
-What?
-Please do that, Hyun-woo.
-Sorry, but I refuse.
Hey, you can take care
of your own family issues.
Since we're on this topic,
let me say something too.
I'm not going home either.
You too?
We're moving
into his studio apartment in Seoul.
We'll be leaving for Germany soon,
and it's closer to the airport.
No, it's actually farther from there.
Best of all, it's newly built
and fully furnished.
It has everything we need
in that small area.
But back home,
we need to take the elevator
to reach the kitchen.
It just takes way too long.
Hey, your excuses are lengthier.
You just want some alone time.
Yes, ma'am.
I'd like to spend
some time with her alone.
Please let us do that.
Sure, if that's more comfortable for you.
Sure, you can do that.
Let me know if you need anything.
Gosh.
Is this what discrimination feels like?
This is my first time experiencing it.
It's something new, though.
They're packing up and returning tomorrow.
You should be ready for them.
I also met with Da-hye.
What is this?
Why did you come back?
Don't let Ms. Moh know.
You idiot.
She was the one who told me you were here.
Seriously?
She knows how you came here
in a taxi with the golden Buddha
in the middle of the night.
Her men are watching you.
So tell me. Why are you here?
Is it guilt or a grudge?
What grudge could I have?
It's my conscience.
I didn't know you had one.
Me neither.
He was the first person
to love me for who I was, and I felt bad.
Goodness.
Unbelievable.
He grew on her.
I'm sure you know
that those feelings can't be stopped.
How dare she betray me
after all I've done for her?
This is exactly why
you shouldn't trust people.
And about Hae-in…
She might be able to save herself.
She's getting surgery.
Hyun-woo looked everywhere for help,
and they finally found
a hospital that can help.
They're leaving for Germany next week.
You startled me.
Find out which hospital
and what kind of surgery she's receiving.
What are you doing?
Nothing much.
I can see many stars.
I even saw a shooting star recently.
Really?
I dreamed of one
when I was pregnant with you.
I always wanted a pretty daughter.
I was ecstatic…
after having that dream.
I don't know which attitude to take.
We were like cats and dogs
for over 20 years,
so I feel awkward to suddenly act
so affectionate toward you.
But deep down,
I feel so guilty
and regretful.
I want to treat you well.
This is good enough.
Is it?
I'd feel awkward, too,
if you suddenly changed your ways.
We'll have a lot of time,
so let's take it slowly.
This will do for now.
All right.
Once you return from Germany,
we can gradually warm up to each other.
I didn't know it was this suffocating
to act as a mediator.
Right. They say it's just as stressful
as joining the military.
We need to move out of the house
if I want to protect Da-hye
from my mom.
Gosh. What's taking them so long?
Mom, Dad.
I packed your stuff.
Really? Okay.
You'll run into traffic soon,
so you should go now. Hurry.
I'm sorry for all the inconvenience,
but I feel the most guilty
about leaving him behind.
It feels like leaving
a bag of trash behind after a trip.
-Father--
-Gosh, don't worry.
And why are you in a hurry?
Have lunch with us.
Should we?
No! Our house has been empty
for over a month now.
There's a lot to take care of.
-I was going to make kimchi pancakes.
-It's okay.
Kimchi pancakes?
How about some crispy kimchi pancakes
and delicious makgeolli?
That's ridiculous. He needs to drive.
I can drive instead.
Or better yet, you can leave tomorrow.
-You should.
-We could.
Do you know how beautiful it is
to know when to leave?
Must I know that?
We'll get going first.
We don't want to run into traffic.
Okay, you should go before then.
Thank you for everything. Goodbye.
Good luck with the surgery.
Hae-in.
Let's meet again.
Hyun-woo.
I trust you.
Don't worry.
Here.
Your mom made
some kimchi and pear extract.
Carry it for him.
Should I? Give it to me.
Goodbye.
Mom, your handbag…
You're the bachelor on the 11th floor.
-Hello.
-Hi.
He's not a bachelor.
I'm his wife.
Didn't you say
you were living here by yourself?
Did you get married recently?
-Yes.
-Goodness!
You're newlyweds!
You must be so happy.
Yes, we are.
It's official that we're newlyweds now.
Why is it official?
Because of that lady.
A woman like her will tell everyone
in this building about us by tomorrow.
"The bachelor on the 11th floor
married a gorgeous woman."
Okay. So?
We should act like newlyweds then.
How?
Normally, newlyweds in love
are always touching each other somehow.
It could be their hands, feet,
or shoulders.
Anything.
They stick by each other
and spend their everyday lives together.
We're bound to run
into hardships again one day.
I'm nervous. Did you smile?
Then we can pull out these happy memories
as if they're candies in a candy jar
and endure those moments.
That's why we need to gather
as many good memories
as possible right now.
That looks tasty.
I'm going to focus more
on collecting happy memories
than stocks or money from now on.
The most important thing for me now
is filling up my candy jar.
Why did you come here so often?
Is baseball that fun?
That's not why.
All I need to focus on
is hitting the ball.
That's what I liked.
Does that
make you feel better?
Well… It was nice to focus on one thing
when things were complicated.
I just need to concentrate
on what's the most important.
And what is that
right now?
Saving you, of course.
That's all that matters.
I'll only focus on that.
Soo-cheol is staying
in Yongdu-ri for some time.
Hae-in decided to stay with Hyun-woo too.
Only the vice-chairman
and his wife are returning.
The vice-chairman?
I'm sorry.
But now that they have their shares,
wouldn't he want
to take back his position?
Says who?
They'll regret coming back here.
I was meaning to see you.
Can we talk?
I heard Hae-in
is getting surgery in Germany.
Don't be so alarmed.
I'm just happy for her.
Is that so?
Of course.
I have feelings for her,
so it's natural for me to be happy
that she can live.
I heard you're going with her.
Please take care of her.
Okay.
Can I leave now?
I found out
that the surgery has a side effect.
Does she know?
Of course not.
Given her personality, she'd refuse
to get the surgery if she knew.
So she probably doesn't know.
What are you getting at?
Make sure you keep that secret
so she gets the surgery.
I told you.
I want her to live.
Remove all of their belongings.
And give Mr. Baek back what's his.
You wanted to come here
as a customer instead of the CEO,
so I even took a leave.
Yes, I'm here as a customer.
-What'll you buy?
-I'm just looking.
Didn't you hate those
who didn't buy anything?
Is this a sauna?
Why are they chatting
and not spending any money here?
-Get rid of the chairs.
-Mom!
Why are they running around?
They should do that at an amusement park.
That's why
we got rid of all the rest zones.
Fine.
I'll spend some money then.
Do you want anything?
-What do you need?
-Lip balm.
My lips are dry.
Why am I so tired after shopping?
Are you tired?
That's not good.
Let's go rest somewhere.
No.
This is good.
The layout is incredible.
There's no time to rest.
We shopped for lip balm
and bought cream too.
We shopped for some knitwear
and bought a coat too.
We didn't even plan on buying a muffler
or gloves, but we got them too.
And now, the smell
of perfumes is alluring us.
That was your strategy.
You wanted to keep the customers busy.
That's why you set up
so many pop-up stores.
When I get reinstated,
I'm going to get rid of them.
-Why?
-It's tiring.
I feel stupid for spending money.
I feel duped.
Would you want to come back here?
I'll get rid of them
and set up chairs once again.
Expensive and comfortable ones.
I'll renovate the square
on the first floor and hold concerts.
There will be an area
where kids can run around.
What?
And a place for couples.
The parents can bring
their kids here
when it's cold or hot outside.
It'd be nice.
I will give them happiness.
Seriously?
Seriously.
You better not take that back
after the surgery.
Why would I?
I saw it in the movies.
Your personality can change
or you can lose your memory
after a brain surgery.
You're wrong. I just simply want
to become a slightly better person
to reciprocate
for being able to live longer.
Mother.
Isn't that your wife?
Hello, Mother.
Sweetie, what is that modest look
in your eyes?
You're making me anxious.
-Mother--
-I can't fix him.
You can't return him!
I'm sorry.
I tried to keep our promise,
but I'm afraid it's time.
Fine.
Let me hear your reason.
-Tell her.
-Me?
Right.
I lied to you about attending a funeral
and spent the night gaming with friends.
No? It's not that, Mom.
Right.
Did you find my game console?
It's secondhand. It's cheap.
You even bought a game console?
Can't you just tell me what it is?
Mother, Hyeon-tae spent
our savings on buying stocks.
He lost half of it.
Hey!
He even invested in cryptocurrency.
It's minus 90% now.
You lunatic.
I'm sorry.
Hyeon-suk.
I don't know what to say.
Return him to me, and I'll get rid of him.
You should go on your way
-while you still have time.
-Mom…
Still,
I'll text you when I make kimchi.
So make sure you come.
Even I think someone as wise
and pretty as you is out of his league.
I'm truly sorry, Hyeon-suk.
Mother…
You need to come to your senses!
Honey, I--
Let me go!
Honey, I think I'll be getting some money!
Hae-in had bought a building,
but didn't have time to look at it.
This must be it.
Yes. I cleaned and swept
the building twice a day,
waxed and washed all the signs,
and disinfected the septic tanks.
I'm also going to paint the building soon.
I see.
There's a good floating population
and visibility due to the two-lane road.
It'd be easy to get rents.
Yes, you're right.
It's not bad at all.
But why do you ask?
Do you plan on selling it?
I spoke with Hae-in.
We'd like to gift the building to you.
What did you say?
Our tax accountant
will contact you once we go to Seoul
and tell you what documents to prepare.
But still,
it's an entire building.
It's a thank-you gift.
Gosh, it's a huge gift.
My parents will become building owners!
Will you still return me?
Honey.
-You shouldn't be here.
-What?
Go to the building owners.
Hurry.
I'm thinking
about renovating the first floor
and setting up a fitness center.
Hey, just focus on your current gym.
Mom, I've been wanting
to relocate my hair salon.
The first floor would be perfect.
Don't butt in.
I was the one who cleaned and swept--
I removed all the stickers on the stairs.
And you have the third floor.
-Hyeon-tae.
-Yes, Mom?
Get rid of the gym as soon as you can.
Mom, that's a harsh joke.
It's not a joke.
You haven't been paying rent.
Come on, Mom.
-Dad.
-Son.
Yes?
This is when a contract becomes useful.
"If a tenant fails to pay rent
two times or more,
the contract can be terminated."
-Do you want to see?
-So what?
-Are you kicking me out?
-No.
I'm telling you to pay up.
Pay on the tenth of every month.
Dad.
What about me?
The first floor costs a million.
Move in if you can manage it.
That's more expensive
than my current rent.
Our building has a better location.
Anyway, we look forward
to this new tension between us,
thanks to this building.
We're very excited.
Come on, Dad.
We don't need tension in this family.
I do!
There were times
when I felt like you were impudent.
This building will prove
your loyalty to us.
-You're wrong.
-What?
I just want to receive rent.
Did you now?
You should've told me so.
Anyway…
-Our Dubong Building--
-What?
-What is that?
-Du-gwan and Bong-ae's building.
-Oh, my God.
-How tacky.
We expect you to pay rent religiously
despite being our children.
Keep that in mind.
It's only October,
but they're preparing for Christmas.
It was your order.
Mine?
Are you going to relax
because Chuseok is over?
Christmas is upcoming. Winter is coming.
We should liven up the mood
so they'll want to buy winter jackets.
We shouldn't wait
until the other stores begin.
We need to prepare in advance
and start the Christmas sale
right after Halloween.
Right.
-Are they testing the lights?
-Yes.
The Installation and Marketing Teams
have been busy today.
Am I hallucinating
the snow?
I see it too.
But isn't this just a rehearsal?
One minute.
It's snowing in the fall.
You wanted to see snow sooner.
Your wish came true.
You're right.
Things are looking up.
All my wishes are coming true.
I think my first love will come true too.
Well…
I don't think
that's what this snow is for.
Why not?
I bet it'll come true.
Who the hell is he
that you're so hell-bent on it?
I wasn't ever going to tell you
in case you'd become too arrogant.
But here's my second secret.
-What is it?
-Was it bus number 372?
-What do you mean?
-The bus you took
back home after work.
Right. Yes.
You're right.
And you always sat
in the back next to the window.
Yes, I did. How did you know that?
How do you think I know?
I followed your bus home
and crossed the Han River numerous times
despite all the traffic.
It took 1.5 hours.
Why?
That bus I told you about
was bus number 372.
And the guy is you.
Okay.
How did you even get into SNU?
What?
So it's me?
Me? I was the guy on the bus?
Yes, it was you.
How lovey-dovey.
By the way, why did
the Installation Team sprinkle snow?
It was Director Baek's request.
Sir, please test the snowmaker
during the rehearsal.
I don't think that's necessary.
The Legal Team
needs to prepare themselves.
You know it'd be an issue
if a customer slipped and fell.
I need to determine
how slippery it'll get.
Sure, if you must.
I'd like big snowflakes if possible.
All right then.
-Thank you, sir.
-No problem.
I sense love in the air.
Right?
Divorce then remarriage.
It's possible?
Was it really me?
Was I your first love?
They must've left already.
I wonder when they'll arrive.
It'll take some time.
My morning prayers were answered.
Hae-in will get better after the surgery
and be happy with Hyun-woo.
You see…
There's a problem.
What problem?
After receiving surgery…
Oh, dear.
She might lose her memory.
What do you mean?
That could be a side effect.
But what choice do we have?
She needs to live.
We had no choice.
I asked Hyun-woo to keep it a secret.
That was…
wise of you.
She has a terrible personality
since she takes after me.
So she might've refused
to get the surgery.
But…
Still…
What'll we do about our poor baby?
Poor baby…
Are you okay?
Of course I am.
Don't worry.
Are you going to Frankfurt?
Yes.
BODY FOUND NEAR SAMBANG RESERVOIR
IDENTIFIED AS LAND BROKER, MR. PYEON
What's the third one?
What do you mean?
You had three secrets
to tell me before the surgery.
You only told me two so far.
Oh, that?
The third one is…
-Yeong-suk.
-Yeong-suk?
-The raccoon on the rooftop?
-Yes.
I never got to see her.
Seriously.
Not even once.
-What about her?
-I made it up.
How could a raccoon live there?
Did you really believe that?
Gosh.
You duped me for four years.
I called out her name
every time I was up there.
You fool.
Is this it?
Hae-in.
What is it?
There's something
I didn't tell you as well.
What is it?
Tell me.
Is something wrong?
Can they not operate
on me?
No, that's not it.
It's…
highly likely
that you'll lose your memory
after the surgery.
What do you mean?
What memory?
Probably…
all of it.
You'll forget
everyone, the places you've been,
and all the experiences you've had.
Even still, this is
your only chance
to live.
So…
you're telling me
to make a decision?
I'll lose my memory if I get it
and die if I don't.
Are you telling me
to pick the lesser evil?
No.
Then what?
Forget it.
I'll pretend like
this was all a good dream.
Let me go. I said, let go.
Don't make a choice.
Don't think.
Just listen to me.
Just… live.
Do that.
Please…
live.
Okay?
Hi, Hae-in.
I'm Baek Hyun-woo.
I'm your husband.
You must be confused and scared.
Me too.
You don't remember anything
and a stranger
is claiming to be your husband.
You must be so confused.
But…
this is good news.
You…
You were very sick,
but you're better now.
You must be curious
about what kind of person you used to be.
It must be upsetting
that you can't remember.
But don't worry.
Because I…
I remember everything.
I'll tell you everything…
that I know.
I shouldn't cry.
This will be the first time
you see my face.
And let me warn you.
Even if I'm not your ideal type,
I'm sorry, but I can't break up with you.
Because we agreed
not to part ways just because
of a change of mind.
Even if you don't like me…
No matter what happens…
Even if…
you forget
the promise we made,
I promised
to be…
by your side.
Let's welcome the first snow,
stick by each other,
and spend our everyday lives together.
Let's fill up
that empty candy jar
of yours.
We can do it.
Because it was fate
that brought us together.
I love…
I love you, Hae-in.
I've always loved you…
and will continue to do so.
QUEEN OF TEARS
I still remember
the smell,
the moon, and the wind of that day.
Don't pray
about dying.
That so-called family of yours
will get hurt.
Da-hye…
I lived as myself,
and I'll die as such
I won't let that happen.
That's how he found that hospital.
I'll help you.
Don't do this to me.
Don't make me want to live.
Hae-in!
Subtitle translation by Soo-ji Kim