[English subtitles are available]
[Divine Destiny]
[Episode 3]
The two modes produce the four images.
The four images produce the eight trigrams.
The eight trigrams produce...
produce...
sliced beef in hot chili oil.
West Lake fish in vinegar gravy.
Tofu crab roe soup.
What are you looking at?
Are you stunned?
Why are you here?
You are receiving punishment here because of me.
Do you think I can feel at ease?
You must be starving.
Here.
Xixuan's rules are really strict.
The punishment is too heavy.
It's not your fault.
I'll just think of it as cultivation in seclusion.
Don't hide anything from me anymore.
Senior Qiushui made these for you.
They are your favorites.
After I eat them,
I'll reluctantly forgive you.
-Eat slowly.
-So delicious.
Tofu, this is my favorite.
Your mouth...
You eat. I'll go find something.
What are you looking for?
I'm looking for a treasure painting.
A treasure painting?
Yes.
According to Senior Xuanzhen,
there is a painting of the secret techniques of the eight schools.
It can help me pass the Annual Exam.
I want to see where it is.
That painting.
Stop looking for it.
It's over there.
Over there.
What is this?
A treasure painting.
It's a masterpiece drew by Xuanzhen last year.
I think I won't pass the Annual Exam this year.
Since you didn't let me down,
I'll tell you this.
The painting is about the unique skills of Zhenren of the eight schools.
Ziyun Zhenren
is the best at making pills
and moral swordsmanship.
Taiwei Zhenren is the best at the tactical deployment of troops.
Yuxuan Zhenren is the best
at inner cultivation methods.
She is also a healer.
You can go to her if you're hurt.
Of course,
my father's Grand Five-Element Swordsmanship
is the most powerful.
And...
Stop.
You're so sincere to help me.
Aren't you afraid that I'll get the first place in the Annual Exam
and steal the limelight?
The stronger you become,
the fairer and squarer I win.
And it will be more interesting.
Do you remember
what I just told you?
Then do you know among Zhenren of the eight schools,
who look down on each other,
who are jealous of each other,
and who are friends to each other?
I don't know.
According to you,
there is still hope, right?
Listen.
Taiwei Zhenren
hates Ziyun Zhenren the most.
They are always against each other.
They intrigue against each other.
They are jealous of each other.
And they compete for everything.
In the eyes of Ziyang Zhenren,
Taiwei Zhenren and Yuxuan Zhenren...
Finally I'm done talking.
I don't have to worry about the Annual Exam anymore.
What are these?
Tianxin Cave was formed by fluorite rocks.
There are plenty of fluorites.
As long as we power the true spirit,
it can illuminate the cave.
Very beautiful.
Really?
It's so beautiful.
Hold me tight.
This place is so beautiful.
It's like
the starry sky in the desert.
You lived in a desert when you were young?
Yes.
I am an orphan.
Back then,
I was wandering outside.
I was almost eaten by a group of wild wolves.
Fortunately, Boss saved me.
Then I became a clerk.
Until I met you.
Were they good to you?
Although they often scolded and beat me,
they
treated me like their own child.
They taught me to read, write,
and knock sheep.
I don't know
how they are doing now.
I don't know whether they are alive or dead.
I miss them so much.
Don't be too sad.
Didn't I just teach you the secret techniques of the eight schools?
As long as you get good results
in the Annual Exam,
I think they will be happy for you.
Thank you.
You're so nice.
This guy is so shameless.
You are pushing your luck.
Let me see what you want to do.
Right.
Tell Shui
that he needs to put more crab roe
in the tofu crab roe soup.
And the tofu was too soft.
It was hard for me to pick it up.
And when I leave this cave,
you must be here for me together.
Has Ruochen made any progress in cultivation recently?
Master.
In the past 15 days,
Ruochen seems to have known the temperament of Zhenrens.
He learned how to deal with different sects.
He also obtained secret books of Zhenrens
and got many weapons.
His cultivation has improved a lot.
It looks like he is smart.
He's so impatient.
He must be preparing for the Annual Exam.
All disciples of Xixuan Mountains
are waiting to see what this banished god is capable of.
It's understandable that he's impatient.
Yes.
His ability is not good enough.
Many people here
are talking gossip.
If he can't get good results in the Annual Exam,
I'm afraid it'll be hard to shut their mouths.
Morning, Ruochen.
Senior Qiushui, morning.
Morning.
You lazy bug.
Put on your clothes.
Have you forgotten
our senior will leave Tianxin Cave today?
I forgot.
Wait for me.
He is dilatory.
Ji.
Yuxuan Zhenren of the Danyuan Palace wants to see you.
The Danyuan Palace?
Sorry.
I have other things to do today.
Can I take a rain check?
Before I came here, Master repeatedly told me
I had to take you there.
Please don't refuse,
so that I won't fail Master.
I'll go with you.
Please.
We are going to pick up Senior Yinyin.
[Danyuan Palace]
Master Yuxuan.
Master told me
that the unique inner cultivation methods of the Danyuan Palace
are the most effective in recuperating the true spirit.
I hope you can teach me
so that I can improve as soon as possible.
I asked you here today
to explain the Eight Elements Manual to you.
This is the key to learning the inner cultivation methods.
You must learn it carefully.
Thank you, Master.
Hanyan.
This is my disciple, Hanyan.
Today, you'll study the manual with her.
Ruochen. I'm Hanyan, a disciple of the Danyuan Palace.
Senior Hanyan, don't stand on ceremony.
Take Ruochen to the Sutra Pavilion.
I'll be right there.
Yes, Master.
Please come with me.
The schools are competing.
It's not up to you with the Fantasy Incense.
Yinyin. Senior Yinyin.
Why are you two here?
It's time.
Have you forgotten?
Senior Qiushui and I are here to take you out of the cave.
Right.
I forgot.
-Zhen. You're finally here.
-Yinyin.
Come on.
You haven't visited me for days.
Shui is nice.
You made so many delicious dishes for me.
Look.
My belly is bulging.
Yes.
Where is Ji Clerk? Why didn't he come?
He was called away by the Danyuan Palace
early in the morning.
He hasn't come back yet.
The Danyuan Palace?
Why?
He knows I'll leave Tianxin Cave today.
Besides, the Danyuan Palace only has female disciples.
Why did they ask him to go there?
He asked me to tell you something before we came.
-What?
-Let's go.
We are supposed to go to the Sutra Pavilion.
This place is isolated.
What exactly does the Danyuan Palace
want to do?
Snake!
Senior Hanyan.
Did you mistake grass leaves for snakes?
There are no snakes here.
Let's just go.
Otherwise, Master Yuxuan will be angry.
You were lying.
I think you know
whether I lied to you or not.
I'm here for the inner cultivation methods.
Look at us now.
We are holding each other.
It's inappropriate.
Ruochen, it hurts so much.
It really hurts.
It hurts!
Help me.
Are you okay?
I wanted to help you.
Why did you do that?
Ruochen.
You can't wrong a good person.
When did I ever hurt you?
Since the first time I met you,
I've fallen for you.
Why would I hurt you?
But I don't understand
why you refused me.
Is it because
I'm not good-looking?
Why can't I understand that?
I'll teach you later.
Okay.
After today's cultivation,
I'll visit you.
OK.
Let's go.
No!
Help! Help!
Let's go.
-Senior, help me!
-How dare you!
How dare you do such an immoral thing
in broad daylight?
Senior, help!
Ziyang.
Don't be afraid.
Master will seek justice for you.
All right, take a rest.
Master.
Junior.
Senior.
I wanted to teach him
the secret inner cultivation methods of the Danyuan Palace.
I didn't expect Ji Ruochen
took the chance to molest my disciple.
As the acting hierarch, you should give me an explanation.
Please calm down.
Ruochen, what happened?
Master, the road is dangerous.
Senior Hanyan accidentally fell.
I just went to help her.
But she...
Don't cry. Hanyan.
I wanted to take the main road.
But...
But he insisted on
taking that less-traveled road.
Then...
Then he...
You...
Ji Ruochen. You dare not admit what you did.
Is this what your master taught you?
We don't know the truth yet.
What she said is unfair.
Ruochen, now tell us
what happened today,
so that Master can seek justice for you.
Okay.
I wanted to take the less-traveled road.
I just wanted to go on a date with someone.
What did I do wrong?
It's good that you admit it.
Ruochen.
At your age,
it's normal for you to think about love.
Considering what you did to Hanyan,
you have to marry her so that they won't gossip.
Master Yuxuan.
The person I wanted to go on a date with
is not Senior Hanyan.
Why should I marry her?
The person I was waiting for is my lover.
Then who is your lover?
She...
Ji Clerk.
Senior, what are you doing?
Yinyin. Senior Yinyin.
Stop running.
Why are you beating us too?
Senior. Senior.
Stop running.
Get out of my way.
Senior, stop!
Help!
You are smart.
Yinyin.
Don't chase them.
It's done.
Done? What do you mean?
How come young people nowadays
are frivolous in love?
That's the end of it.
Don't mention it again.
We're leaving?
She just left like this?
It looks like nothing happened between Ji and Hanyan.
Forget it.
Ji Ruochen!
Ji Ruochen, come out!
Ji Clerk, come out!
Ji Clerk, what are you doing?
Senior,
don't you think you overacted?
I just asked you to save me.
I didn't ask you to beat me.
How dare you say that?
On my way here,
I heard from people of the Danyuan Palace
that you secretly dated Hanyan.
In the name of the inn's boss
and boss lady,
I really didn't.
They drugged me.
I just feel uncomfortable.
I feel
uncomfortable.
They drugged you?
Let me see.
Let me see if you're okay.
Why is your face so hot?
What are you doing?
I really want to kiss you.
How dare you!
Ji... Ji Clerk.
I dare not.
You are bad.
Why are you always flirtatious?
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
No.
You'll hit me again if I let you go.
I won't.
Since you won't hit me,
let me hold you a little longer.
Since you took me to Xixuan,
I've dreamed of you every night.
I think of you day and night.
I...
It's been a long time
since there were lovebirds here.
Finally, I saw a pair today.
Are you crazy?
You're so ugly.
You are definitely not one of Xixuan's members.
Let's go.
Aren't you a banished god?
It's embarrassing that you are running away.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Get up.
Be careful.
Why is there
a bronze tripod here?
Could this be Xixuan's secret technique?
Ji Clerk.
Clerk.
Dissociation Mantra.
Sink your breath to the lower belly.
Fortunately, I read the Shangqing Mantra
so that I can memorize whatever I see.
I didn't expect
to use it here.
Clerk.
Clerk. Be careful.
Clerk. Are you OK?
Clerk.
Clerk, wake up!
Clerk!
Ji Ruochen, you're finally awake.
Master.
His injury is temporarily under control.
But he still needs several months to recover with the help of medicine.
Ruochen.
You are very lucky
that it didn't kill you.
Be careful.
Master, I'm sorry
for making you worried.
Ruochen.
The demons you saw
have black cloaks and disfigured faces, right?
How did you know?
That faceless man
is my junior.
His name is Shen Boyang.
He was a rare martial arts genius.
But due to the death of Yu Chan,
his lover,
he went off the deep end during cultivation
and ended up like this.
His existence
is a secret of Xixuan Sect.
So from now on,
don't tell anyone about this.
Master, in the mountain...
I know.
Yinyin told me everything.
I didn't expect him
to destroy the sect's important weapon.
He is really unreasonable.
Ruochen,
have a good rest.
Don't tell anyone about what happened today.
Yes, Master.
You told Master
the bronze tripod was destroyed by the faceless man?
Do you want me to tell him you destroyed it?
Don't.
I don't want any more trouble.
What are you looking at?
I saw it in the cave that day.
What did you learn
through the tripod?
Well...
I don't know.
I just read the mantra in the illusion.
And my true spirit got more powerful.
Are you a genius immortality cultivator they mentioned?
Just by reading some mantras,
you can improve your true spirit.
Unlike me.
It's useless no matter how hard I try.
And I have the Huanyao Root in my body.
Are you thinking about your headache disease?
Maybe it can be cured.
What are you doing?
I'm giving you my power.
You are so unhappy.
What's the use of keeping it?
What are you talking about?
Didn't you say
you are mine?
Then what's the difference between yours and mine?
You are right.
You are really nice to me.
Don't move.
Let me feed you.
It's hot.
Try again. Is it still hot?
No.
And it's very sweet.
This is a blessing in disguise.
Did you hurt your brain?
You almost died.
What kind of blessing is it?
Drink it.
Is the medicine sweet?
Yes.
Why haven't I drunk sweet medicine before?
You don't need it.
Senior.
I heard that Ji Ruochen
was in trouble in the back mountain.
Don't you know?
Ruochen is a banished god.
Don't worry.
He's fine now.
A banished god?
When he came here, he was chosen by the magical stone.
The Psychic Mirror illuminated.
That's why we accepted him as a banished god.
Someone in Xixuan Sect has suspected his identity long ago.
Can't you tell?
He had been in the mortal world for too long.
He just started cultivation.
Of course it will take some time.
In the long history of Xixuan Sect,
there were people ascending too.
All of them were better than ordinary disciples.
I don't know anyone
as ordinary as Ji Ruochen.
Taiwei.
The banished god is the last disciple
selected by the hierarch.
What are you still suspecting?
Don't pressure me with the hierarch.
Since you said he just started cultivation,
I'll give him some more time.
In the Annual Exam,
if he still can't prove his strength,
he must be a fake banished god.
Senior.
I'm afraid by that time, I won't need to do anything,
because Zhenren of all schools will punish him severely.
Ji Ruochen is getting more arrogant.
Let's teach him a lesson.
Ming Xin and Ming Yun.
Nice to meet you.
Ruochen.
You went to the Taixuan Palace
for the Grand Five-Element Swordsmanship.
But now you're in the Xuanming Palace.
Junior.
I hate to say this,
but you are ungrateful.
You are not loyal.
I heard
you said the Moral Swordsmanship of the Xuanming Palace
is the best in the world.
Does that mean
the Grand Five-Element Swordsmanship of the Taixuan Palace
is not as good as the Moral Swordsmanship?
I never said that.
I have other things to do.
Let's talk another day.
Wait.
Let's have a competition.
Let me show you
what the Grand Five-Element Swordsmanship really is.
Junior.
Just admit defeat.
You're being very polite
to kneel.
They are having a conflict.
You're so weak.
How about this?
Apologize to me in front of everyone.
And I won't make things difficult for you.
People say dogs don't bite when they bark.
Why are you two barking so fiercely?
Ji Ruochen.
You asked for it.
Senior.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Senior, get out of my way.
It is none of your business.
Ming Xin.
This is the Xuanming Palace.
Ruochen is practicing the Moral Swordsmanship.
Of course it is my business.
Besides,
your master Jingxiao Zhenren
was once defeated
by my master, Taiwei Zhenren.
As disciples of the Taixuan Palace,
it's fine that you are not ambitious.
But you want to hurt people in the Xuanming Palace.
Why?
Ji Ruochen.
You're lucky today.
Let's wait and see.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
Ruochen.
Is your hand all right?
I'm fine.
Why didn't you
draw your sword?
We are fellow disciples.
If we fight against each other,
how do we face each other in the future?
I hope they can understand your kindness.
Senior.
-Senior!
What happened?
Senior. You must take revenge for us.
Who is bold enough to bully
the people of the Taixuan Palace?
Who else could it be?
With his identity as a banished god,
he has looked down
on the Taixuan Palace and you.
Who else could it be
except Ji Ruochen?
Senior, you can't ignore this.
Why did he hit you?
Because we heard
he said the Grand Five-Element Swordsmanship of the Taixuan Palace
was nothing.
He also said...
He also said that Taiwei Zhenren
beat the crap out of our master.
We were angry
and quarreled with him.
And he beat us.
Ji Clerk is really ungrateful.
I was kind enough to teach him the Sword Flying Mantra.
I can't believe he said our swordsmanship was nothing.
I think he is nothing.
Senior.
You can't judge a book by its cover.
He was just pretending to be good-tempered
in front of you.
In fact, he is despicable and shameless.
Fine.
I'll show him what I'm capable of.
-Senior, calm down.
-Senior.
We need a reason.
Otherwise, it will be a private fight.
People will gossip about it.
How about we challenge him first?
So that we can find a place
to teach him a lesson with a proper reason.
Do as you say.
This
is my new technique.
A plate of braised eggplants?
Vulgar.
It has a beautiful name.
It's called
Jinxin eggplants.
Jin...
So much for your cultivation in seclusion.
You just went to learn cooking.
You don't understand.
You will gradually understand
it is more important
to learn to cook
than to be admitted into a sect
or practicing
powerful swordsmanships.
This is so delicious.
Ruochen, taste it.
Ming Xin.
Senior.
Didn't you say you made an appointment with Ji Ruochen
to compete here from 5 a.m. to 7 a.m.?
It's been two hours.
Where is he?
He must be delayed by something.
I'll teach him a lesson when he comes.
Senior, let's wait a little longer.
He doesn't have the guts to fool us.
One more.
Don't touch me.
Keep drinking.
Drink.
To be honest,
it's my honor
to be friends with you and Xuanzhen.
Senior Qiushui.
One day,
if I give up my immortality identity and become a mortal,
or
I am a mortal,
will we still sit together
drinking like this?
It has nothing to do with immortality cultivation.
Immortality
and mortality
both have
their own benefits.
But what matters most
is your own choice.
But
you will
always be my friend.
Yes.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
I feel relieved
because of what you said just now.
Now I feel relaxed.
Come on.
Drink.
Put it down.
Bad luck.
It never rains but it pours.
Will we freeze to death here?
What?
You can't stand it so soon?
I'm still here, right?
The sun shines after the rain.
Senior, did you draw it in a wrong way again?
Senior, let's find a shelter.
-Let's go.
-That's right.
Let's go.
That's strange.
Why does it
look like Senior Yinyin's Sunlight and Rain Charm
on the Sword Forging Mountain?
The charm can summon wind and rain
and clear the mist and rain.
But it's late.
Why did she go up there?
Ji Ruochen!
Ji Ruochen, come back.
Eat these dishes together.
Ming Yun. Ming Xin.
There's a cave here.
We can take shelter from rain there.
Senior, we can't go in.
I heard there's a forbidden area on the Sword Forging Mountain.
People will be punished for trespassing.
Maybe this is it.
We are just here to take shelter from rain.
What are you afraid of?
Let's go.
-Yeah. What's there to be afraid of?
-Senior.
Senior.
Isn't this just an ordinary cave?
Where does it look like a forbidden area?
But
don't you think it's very cold here?
This is my fault.
With spotted nine tails,
I jump over the Nanshan Mountain.
Do you hear anything?
When the Big Dipper appears above the Nanshan Mountain,
the dead water ripples.
Senior, how about
we go somewhere else to take shelter?
That's right. Senior.
Let's go somewhere else.
It's too dark. Don't go there.
Who is inside?
-Senior.
-Senior!
Senior, come back!
Senior. Don't go inside!
The dead water ripples.
I see nothing every day.
I am heartbroken.
On the full-moon night,
the Big Dipper moves.
The gate of hell is open,
and the yin energy is the strongest.
I didn't expect to see you again today.