[English subtitles are available]
[Divine Destiny]
[Episode 26]
Xuanzhen.
Help me.
-I'll save you. -It hurts.
I'll save you
even at the cost of my life.
Xuanzhen.
Zhen.
Yinyin, what should we do?
How could this happen?
We haven't avenged Senior Yunfeng,
now you've hurt Li Xuanzhen.
No one can leave here today.
Ji Ruochen.
When Feng arrives,
you'll all die.
So what if he comes?
He'll die with you.
We must find a way to save him.
We must save him.
Xuanzhen.
What should we do?
Take him back to Xixuan Mountains.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Ji Ruochen disregarded others' lives
in order to destroy the spiritual cave.
How cruel he is.
Two spiritual caves
have been destroyed by Ji Ruochen so far.
Qing will definitely follow him
to destroy the last spiritual cave.
I'm going to tell Qing
before they set off.
-Right. -Feng.
No.
Banished God, all the best for your trip.
Did Feng find out
that we killed these villagers?
Of course
not.
We are helping him.
As for Ji Ruochen,
since his fellow apprentice was hurt by Her Highness,
he must be furious.
If these two sides meet each other,
it'll be a tremendous disaster.
Ji Ruochen will be in danger.
I hope so.
Master Yuxuan.
How is he?
Xuan Jade has removed all the flames around him,
but somehow,
the flames on his face remain.
Looks like we still need to
find a way to completely eliminate it.
Master Yuxuan.
Even if we can't fully eliminate it,
is there any way to suppress the flames
and keep him from suffering?
Right.
As long as there is a way,
we'll do it
at all costs.
Your Ice Cave is made of thousand-year-old cold jade.
It may be helpful.
Okay, I'll take him to the Ice Cave now.
I'm not going.
Xuanzhen.
Look at the situation I am in right now.
What's the difference of moving to a new place?
There must be a way to save you.
You have to go to the Ice Cave with me.
It's useless.
Xuanzhen, listen to me.
It will work.
There's no way.
Xuanzhen.
-Come on, Xuanzhen. Listen to me. -There's no way.
Mirror!
How did I become like this?
Look at what I've turned into.
Why don't you kill me?
-Why don't you kill me? -Xuanzhen.
Xuanzhen, calm down.
-Why won't you kill me? -Xuanzhen.
Why don't you kill me?
Why?
Xuanzhen.
Go away.
Xuanzhen, come with me to the Ice Cave.
Forget it. I'm not going.
I asked for it.
You don't have to do this.
I know you're suffering.
I swear
I will cure you no matter how long it takes.
I don't need you to swear.
Go away. Go.
Xuanzhen.
Go.
Calm down, Xuanzhen.
Xuanzhen, calm down.
Get lost!
-Calm down. -You too. Get lost.
Xuanzhen.
Get lost!
Alright, Xuanzhen. Li Xuanzhen.
Xuanzhen.
It's okay.
You're not a monster.
You are Li Xuanzhen.
You're the diligent and thrifty
Li Xuanzhen who is well-behaved, good at cooking
It's okay.
You are my friend.
You are our friend
You are
my best friend.
You are also
Right.
It's okay. Xuanzhen.
Don't be sad.
You're also my best...
Yuxuan.
How is Xuanzhen?
The divine flames can't be extinguished completely.
I'm still working on it.
Senior, do we really have to
destroy the last spiritual cave?
I disagree.
Yunfeng has gone.
Fortress has lost Xuanzhen.
Now all the major sects are angry.
They'll definitely try their best to stop him.
Are we going to sit by
and watch Ruochen court death?
Right.
Although Xixuan Sect is the number one sect,
we don't want to be an enemy against the world.
We've already destroyed two spiritual caves.
Let's forget about the last one.
Do you think
the other sects will appreciate us
if we keep the last one untouched?
Since we've started it, we must do it to the end.
That's also what Hierarch wants.
If Hierarch insists,
let us old guys
to go with Ruochen.
Otherwise,
I
will never agree.
Sun Guo is gathering all sects across the world
to attack Xixuan.
If we all go,
who will protect Xixuan?
Are we going to watch Ruochen court death?
Ruochen has the ability
to destroy two spiritual caves in a row
with the help of the Demon Emperor of Netherworld and the men of the two banished gods.
Isn't that enough to prove his ability?
Ziyun.
You need to have faith in Ruochen.
Senior.
What if Ruochen ends up like Xuanzhen?
Then his whole life will be ruined.
Ruochen.
You came at the right time.
Come here.
Greetings, Master.
Masters, Master Yuxuan.
Ruochen, think carefully. You...
Master.
I heard it outside.
Please
rest assured.
When I was in the Sand Sea,
I got the divine weapon, Demon Spear,
and tamed Chaotic Thunder Dragon as my main weapon.
They can't stop me.
Okay.
Great.
Juniors.
I believe even if the two banished gods cooperate,
they are no match for Ruochen.
Let us old guys
guard Xixuan in peace
and wait for Ruochen to return victorious.
Ruochen, when will you go down the mountains?
Master, I plan to go down the mountains in two days.
Okay.
You've destroyed two caves in a row.
You do need some rest.
If you need someone to help you,
you can choose anyone from our sect.
Master, I can do it alone.
Ruochen.
I'll entrust you
with Xixuan.
Master, don't worry.
Xuanzhen.
I know you don't want to see me,
but you can't delay healing the wound any longer.
If you really hate me,
I'll leave the Ice Cave.
Then you won't get annoyed.
I've told you.
I will never go.
Bingxian.
This has nothing to do with you.
I've told you.
You don't have to think of me for everything.
Although this medicine
isn't that helpful for putting out the divine flames,
Master Yuxuan said
it can relieve your pain.
Xixuan, drink it.
Come on.
I don't want it.
What's wrong?
Are you going to take care of me for the rest of my life?
I said
I'll try my best to find a way to cure you
no matter how long it takes.
Senior.
Hierarch ordered you to move to the Ice Cave
for better healing your wound.
Xuanzhen.
You don't have to listen to Bingxian
or me.
[Ziyang]
But are you sure
you want to disobey this order?
I don't believe it.
Why would Hierarch
bother with such a small thing?
Since you don't believe the order,
I'll ask him to come in person.
My wound won't heal.
It doesn't matter where I live.
If you don't go,
I'll ground myself in the Tianxin Cave as punishment
until you go.
It's wet and cold
in the Tianxin Cave.
How can you stay there?
So you knew she can't stay there.
But you've been rejecting Bingxing.
Do you think she will feel at ease?
Okay, I'll go.
You two, pack up.
Yes, Senior.
Senior, you did a good job.
Thank you, Yinyin.
Xuanzhen has finally moved to the Ice Cave to heal his wound.
I hope he can recover soon.
Ruochen.
You must take us with you
to destroy the spiritual cave.
Xuanzhen
must think so too.
Qiushui.
Don't persuade me on this anymore.
The reason I don't want to bring you
is
something big will happen in Xixuan.
You must stay.
But...
Will there be anything more important
than destroying the spiritual cave?
Master got the news
that Sun Guo is persuading the other sects
to attack Xixuan Sect.
The Demon Emperor of Netherworld
is mad at us
because the spiritual cave at the Sand Sea was destroyed.
If they cooperate
to fight Xixuan Sect,
I'm afraid this will be a fierce battle.
It won't be easier than destroying the spiritual cave.
Besides, I’m confident
I can destroy
the last spiritual cave on my own,
so everyone must stay
to protect Xixuan Sect.
Everyone?
Including Yinyin?
She is
like a plaster now.
You can't get rid of her.
I think
Yinyin seems to
have feelings for you again.
If she falls in love with you
and forget you again,
isn't it like a poison
to both of you?
Right.
So I have to think of another way.
What do you need to think about?
They are blaming me
for not taking them with me
to destroy the spiritual cave.
You don't have to take them,
but don't try to dump me.
Don't forget.
I know
where the last spiritual cave is.
Don’t play tricks.
It's okay if you can't go.
I'll give you
half of my credit.
You are so generous, Yinyin.
After all, I've been your senior for so many years.
Okay.
Senior Ji.
Has Xuanzhen been settled?
Yes.
Take Shi Ji and me to have a look.
Okay.
Let's go.
When Xuanzhen recovers,
this place is also suitable for him to rest.
Yes.
Once I finish my mission,
I'll bring Xuanzhen here
to live with me.
Qiushui and Bingxian
will take care of him.
I'll be relieved then.
When are we leaving?
Once everything's done,
we'll set out immediately.
You'd better hurry up.
I also have something to do.
We've been searching for the Kunlun Golden Sand
for years,
but we didn't see any.
I didn't expect there's so much
in Xixuan Mountains.
I heard that you two
are very knowledgeable in making weapons.
I asked my disciples
to bring these things here.
I don't know if these
can be helpful to you.
Of course they're helpful.
That's good.
You two can
go to the weapon warehouse of Xixuan Sect sometime.
Tell my disciples
if you need anything.
Thank you, Master Ziyang.
Please rest assured.
With these good things,
we will
create more
invincible and powerful
Dragon and Tiger Universal Cannons for Xixuan.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Master.
Sun Guo set a sinister formation
for the battle at the Fortress.
We were almost trapped inside.
It took a lot of effort for Mr. Ji and Yinyin
to destroy the spiritual cave.
I'm afraid it'll be more difficult
to destroy the last one.
Are you sure you want Mr. Ji to continue to destroy the spiritual cave?
This is Ruochen's destiny.
He was born
to take this responsibility.
Life is so unfair.
He fought the banished god after fighting the Bamboo Snake.
Now he's fighting against all the cultivators.
It's a narrow escape.
Qing.
Since ancient times, people who carry great responsibilities are always like this.
I have things to do.
I have to go.
Are you saying Mr. Ji will be fine?
But it's okay.
Even if life is unfair,
he still has our help.
Am I right, Ling?
Qingyi.
Didn’t Master say
we Endless Sea can't interfere in destroying the spiritual cave?
Why did you forget again?
With you around,
I don't have a chance to interfere even if I want to.
I've received Master's order.
He wants me to get back to the Endless Sea as soon as possible.
You're going back?
So,
you must remember what you promised Master.
Don’t interfere in destroying the spiritual cave,
but you can protect Mr. Ji and Yinyin.
I know.
Let me walk you out.
Well, then...
As for these two fools,
even if they've got the Kunlun Golden Sand,
they won't be able to take it away.
Just let them work on it.
Be careful.
Ling, are you really leaving?
It’s Master’s order.
Your master even asked you to protect Qingyi.
That mask guy is weird.
How could he not keep his words?
How about
you pretend you didn’t receive your master’s order
and continue to destroy the spiritual cave with us?
Then you can protect me and Qingyi.
Ji Ruochen will protect you.
What are you talking about?
He pushed me to you when you came last time.
It won't happen again.
Trust me.
Take care, Yinyin.
Why didn't he get it?
Who needs your protection?
I just want you to stay
and hang out with us.
I'm gonna go find Master.
Junior Ji
is indeed amazing,
but I'm also good.
My fox tail
even made Yinfeng dizzy.
Anyway,
my junior and I cooperated well.
We destroyed the spiritual cave in front of them.
Am I good?
What’s your junior’s name?
The one who destroyed the spiritual cave.
His name is...
His name is Ji…
I usually call him Junior.
I forgot his name.
Forget it.
I don't really want to know.
You've been talking for a while,
your junior
seems to treat you well, right?
Well...
It's hard to say.
Why not?
Xuanzhen and Qiushui said
he likes me,
so I asked him in person.
He denied it.
If he doesn't like me,
he is really nice to me
and takes care of me.
But if he likes me,
he always pulls a long face on me
and pushes me away.
Master, you are knowledgeable.
What do you think
is wrong with him?
I think
he's just forgetful.
Forgetful?
Master.
Do you think I was born yesterday?
What about you?
You didn't leave even if he pushed you away.
Have you fallen in love with him?
I...
I didn't leave because I wanted to destroy the spiritual cave.
I wanted to help.
Besides,
I just met him at the spiritual cave in the Sand Sea.
How could I have fallen in love with him?
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
You don't believe me?
Whether I believe you or not,
the result is still the same.
But it's not a bad thing.
Master.
What are you talking about?
Why didn't I get it?
You'll get it sooner or later.
Go back.
Okay.
Yinyin.
Be careful when you're out there.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Don't worry, Madam.
I will take good care of her.
Ruochen, Yinyin.
We'll wait for you two to come back.
Alright.
We're just going to destroy a spiritual cave.
Why is the vibe so heavy?
We'll be back soon.
Right, Junior?
We're gonna go.
Yinyin.
Qingyi.
Dragon Elephant, White Tiger.
Are you coming along?
Uncle asked me to help you.
Master Ziyang also agreed.
You can't get rid of me.
Okay.
Let's go.
Qiushui.
Please take care of Xuanzhen.
Don't worry.
Someone from the Xuanming Palace got injured.
Why should Bingxian
give up the Ice Cave?
What can she do?
He got injured for destroying the spiritual cave.
Didn't he know his capability?
He's only been on the Qingyun List several times.
He overestimated himself too much.
Even he wanted to fight for credit?
He's our fellow apprentice.
If I hear you saying these again, I'll cut your tongue off.
Senior.
Xuanzhen.
I'm sorry
for causing you trouble.
What are you talking about, Xuanzhen?
We're brothers.
Don't mention it.
Let me see.
Luckily, it's not burning again.
Get some fresh air.
It may be helpful for the recovery.
Xuanzhen.
Don't take what they said into heart.
Not everyone has the same relationship
like what you have among you, Qiushui and Ruochen.
Exactly.
Don't care too much
what they said.
Let's go.
I learned a new way to cook medicine yesterday.
I'll cook it for you.
They were right.
I'm no different from a loser now.
But now,
I can't hold Ruochen back anymore.
I hope he can come back safely soon.
Don't worry.
He's managed to get out of danger
after going through so many hardships.
This time, he will definitely come back safely.
He's also got Yinyin with him.
Don’t worry.
Let's go.
Delicious food is calling you.
Let's go, Senior.
Ji Ruochen is really bold.
He's really coming.
We can't let him get in the Qingyuan Holy Land.
We can't let him find the spiritual cave.
We'd rather capture him
at the spiritual cave
than let him go.
Check this out.
The scenery here is completely different from Xixuan Mountains.
Qingyi.
It’s a very dangerous trip to the Qingyuan Holy Land this time.
I will find a way
to make Yinyin forget me again
and forget about destroying the spiritual cave.
Please send Yinyin back
to Xixuan Mountains then.
Qingyi.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Did Ji scold you again?
No.
Yinyin, stop asking.
He is always like this.
He's serious when he cares about others.
Don't worry.
I'll teach him a lesson for you.
What should I do?
I don't want to be this bad guy.
I’ll feel guilty when I see her.
You’re quick.
You came out to get water so quickly.
You should stay inside and keep warm.
Why did you come out?
Of course I'm here to see you.
Did you scold Qingyi?
She was so upset when she came to me.
She just wanted to stay and help.
Why are you so strict with her?
Fine.
Plum blossom.
That girl
only cares about food
and those small tricks.
She has no idea what love is.
Last New Year's Eve,
I picked some plum blossoms
and gave them to her for the Spring Festival,
but she used them
to make dumplings for me.
Is it pretty?
Yes.
It's hard for them to blossom in this cold whether.
Remember, don't make dumplings with them.
It's good to boil them in water.
They are my flowers.
I can eat them in whatever way I like.
It's none of your business.
Is the water full?
Yes.
It's snowing.
We are so lucky.
I haven't seen
such big snow for years.
Let's have a snowball fight
after dinner.
Junior.
Are you still worried
about destroying the spiritual cave?
No.
What's wrong?
It's okay. Just tell me.
I am good
at consoling people.
Are you a blockhead?
You always blow hot and cold.
I have to go.
Yinyin.
I'm sorry.
It's snowing.
I don't want to…
Forget me completely.
Leave me
and be happy like now
for the rest of your life.
Letting Yinyin forget him again
must be
heartbreaking for Mr. Ji.
In that case,
I'll ask her on his behalf.
Yinyin,
do you love Mr. Ji?
Cut it out.
You're so young.
Do you know what love is?
Just tell me.
Do you love him or not?
No.
How could you not love him?
He's capable,
kind and humorous.
You think so highly of him.
Do you love him?
You can't love him.
Yinyin.
You don’t love him,
and you don't allow others to love him?
He's not your boyfriend.
I'm his senior.
A senior is like a mother.
I have the final say
on who he is with.
Time to eat.
Anyway,
you can't love him.
Do you hear me?
Yinyin.
You can control everything
but not this.
Mr. Ji,
I wanted to force Yinyin to admit her feelings for you,
but she said
she doesn't like you.
What are you trying to hide from me?
Tell me.
What are you plotting with Qingyi?
I asked her to send you back to Xixuan Mountains.
Again?
Other than those bullshit
that you don't want me to get hurt,
is there any other reason?
Isn't that enough?
Aren't you curious at all?
I'm your junior.
We've always been together,
but you never remember my name.
What's your junior's name again?
The one who destroyed the spiritual cave.
His name is...
His name is Ji…
I usually call him Junior.
I forgot his name.
You're the one who's capable of destroying spiritual caves.
My master must know you,
but why did she ask me your name on purpose?
She was open with me about planting the Huanyao Root.
Why would she hide this from me?
Because I told them not to mention me in front of you.
Because every time you thought of me,
you would have a severe headache.
Are you kidding me?
I've never had such a weird problem.
Think about it.
When you were at the spiritual cave of the Sand Sea,
you had a lot of headaches
because you remembered something.
Didn't you have a headache
when you saw this bracelet
at the spiritual cave of the Sand Sea?
Think about it.
Have you forgotten all of these?
At whose wedding
did you see this bracelet?
Ring a bell?
I don't want to recall.
Think about it.
Think about it carefully.
I don't want to recall.
Yinyin.
You must recall.
Let go of me!
Yinyin.
-Go away. -Yinyin.
You must recall.
Yinyin.
-Yinyin. -Let go of me!
You have to recall.
Yinyin.
I… I remember now.