[English subtitles are available]
[Divine Destiny]
[Episode 35]
Qing.
I will do my best
to save the people.
When everything is over,
we'll return to the Wuding River.
The Demon Tower has started to absorb spiritual power.
Hierarch.
Hierarch, what's going on?
The Demon Tower has absorbed all the spiritual energy in the world.
From now on,
there will be no more spiritual energy in the world.
In the blink of an eye,
almost all the spiritual energy around here
has been absorbed by the Demon Tower.
If this continues...
No. I have to think of a way.
The Demon Tower has been born.
No one can stop it anymore.
Don't waste your time.
Sun Guo.
What are you doing here?
Master has succeeded.
I can follow him to the God Realm.
Succeeded?
The birth of the Demon Tower
was designed by you?
That's right.
Ji Ruochen destroyed the spiritual caves
to prevent the Demon Tower from being born.
That's why I incited all sects
to deal with him together.
Yinfeng.
Are you surprised?
Tell me.
Who is the shadow on the divine cloud?
It doesn't matter anymore.
What matters is
in half an hour,
the Ascending Platform will appear here.
By that time,
I will stand on it
and become an immortal.
You're going to stand on the Ascending Platform?
Master gave me the Soul of Immortal Cloud.
I'm no longer a mortal.
You think you can become an immortal?
Senior.
Hierarch.
Congratulations. Hierarch.
Where is Ji Ruochen now?
Ji Ruochen.
I'm going to destroy the Demon Tower.
If you don't want to go with me,
just collect my body later.
If you go,
I will definitely go with you.
The spiritual power in the world is at my disposal.
From now on,
I will be the ruler of the God Realm.
If anyone disobeys,
I'll tear him into pieces.
The Blue Fire of the Nine Hells.
My tower!
The tower has been destroyed.
Yes.
Really.
The tower has been destroyed.
It's been destroyed. Look.
Yes.
Look, the tower has been destroyed.
My spiritual power is back.
Great.
Mine too. My spiritual power is back.
It's back.
This is...
The Demon Tower has been destroyed.
The Three Realms are safe for now.
So Ji Ruochen...
Brat, he even hid it from us.
Yinyin, look.
The spiritual power is back.
I've been waiting for ten million years.
But I still failed.
Ji Ruochen.
What's going on?
Silly girl, don't you understand?
He set a trap
and tricked us.
That's right.
When I left the Nine Hells,
I left a wisp of the Blue Fire of the Nine Hells in the tower.
Yinyin.
What should I do?
Maybe this time,
our good days will really come.
It's time to end all of this.
Actually,
I have never changed the original intention of destroying the tower.
If I destroyed the tower at that time,
I wouldn't be able to find the one behind this.
That's why you set this trap
to make everyone think you've given up destroying the tower.
The enemy was also fooled by you.
So he absorbed the spiritual energy of the world happily,
until he found the Blue Fire of the Nine Hells.
In this way, the tower has been destroyed.
And the mastermind has been caught.
Kill two birds with one stone.
Impressive.
Mr. Ji, don't be too modest.
Although I hid it from every one of them,
I failed to hide it from Mr. Ji.
What do you mean?
In the battle at the Endless Sea,
your uncle didn't do his best to stop me.
That day,
I was just guessing what you were planning.
It was just a counterplot.
Actually,
if we really fight,
I won't be your match.
You're being too modest, Mr. Ji.
Ji Ruochen.
You even lied to me?
I'm sorry, honey.
I had no other choice.
It seems that Ruochen
has hidden something in the Demon Tower.
But Senior,
what do you mean by "safe for now"?
Could something still go wrong?
Ruochen set a trap to destroy the tower.
The ten million years of efforts
of the person who built the tower are in vain.
He must be very angry and he will show up
to take revenge on Ruochen.
I'm afraid there will be another fierce battle.
You mean...
Ruochen is willing to sacrifice his life for the world.
As his master, I can't sit by and watch.
I'm going to help him.
Senior.
Everyone,
I'll leave Xixuan Sect to you.
Senior.
Farewell, Hierarch.
Mr. Ji.
But there's still one thing I don't quite understand.
When did you know the secret of the Demon Tower?
And why did you create the Endless Sea
to stop the Demon Tower from being born?
When the time is right,
you'll know the answers.
Now I can only say
I've done everything I can do.
Mr. Ji has protected the world
for ten million years.
It's time you take a rest
and accompany Master.
Leave the rest
to us.
But it's too dangerous.
Yinyin.
Do you want to stay?
You know it's too dangerous.
Why do you push me away
whenever it's dangerous?
I've inherited Master's power
and become a heavenly fox.
Of course I will face these things
with you.
Yinyin has really grown up.
Of course.
Otherwise, I would let you down.
In this case,
don't talk me out of going with you.
Maybe
you need me to save you.
Okay.
Remember not to act tough.
I know.
So nagging.
We're going to leave now.
Goodbye.
Take care.
Qingyi.
Come back.
-Uncle.
-Why do you want to go?
Your power is not strong enough.
Even if you go,
you'll only get yourself killed.
Come back.
Every time there is a disaster,
there will be someone born to face the calamity.
They are the chosen ones.
All the hardships
were a test for them.
Let them
shoulder the responsibility of saving the Three Realms.
I see.
What's going on?
Master.
Looks like your master succeeded quickly,
but failed more quickly.
You...
Divine stairs.
The Ascending Platform.
I am Sun Guo, a cultivator in the mortal world.
High Immortals.
You are standing on a divine lotus.
You must be a new immortal
who is going to the Ascending Platform.
Yes.
Since you are from the mortal world,
do you know why the spiritual power in the mortal world suddenly surged?
Please look.
The surge of the spiritual power in the mortal world
is because of the birth of the Demon Tower.
All of this was done by Ji Ruochen, the Demon King.
He destroyed the spiritual caves in the world first,
and then planned the birth of the Demon Tower.
If you don't believe me,
you can go there to check.
The Blue Fire of the Nine Hells in the Demon Tower is the evidence.
It really is the Blue Fire of the Nine Hells.
Do you know where Ji Ruochen is?
High Immortals.
Since Ji Ruochen has become the Demon King,
his power is unfathomable.
It's not easy to catch him.
However,
the banished god is familiar with Ji Ruochen.
He knows him well.
With his help,
you can yield twice the result with half the effort.
General Hao Ming.
General Yu Yun.
Don't stand on ceremony.
You have gone through countless tribulations in the mortal world.
You are here today
to stand on the Ascending Platform
to return to the God Realm, right?
High Immortals,
I
don't plan to return to the God Realm.
I'm here today
not to stand on the Ascending Platform,
but to stop the Demon Tower from being born.
Although I failed,
fortunately, the Demon Tower was destroyed
as soon as it was born.
That's great.
This is also why
General Yu Yun and I came to the mortal world.
Would you help us
capture Ji Ruochen?
High Immortals.
Why do you want to arrest Ji Ruochen?
He planned the birth of the Demon Tower
and broke the balance of the spiritual power in the mortal world.
We need to arrest him to the God Realm and punish him.
High Immortals. Please forgive me.
I've decided to stay out of everything in this world.
As for capturing Ji Ruochen,
please find someone else to help.
You...
Since the Demon Tower has been destroyed,
I'll take my leave.
You stop right there!
How dare you!
You were exiled to the mortal world
because you violated the heavenly rules for Bluestone God.
Today,
do you want to make the same mistake?
All immortals, listen up.
Border Patrol God despised the God Realm and colluded with demons.
I should punish him on behalf of the Heaven today.
Arrest him immediately.
Yes. Sir.
Qing.
Now I know
I was wrong.
Ji Ruochen once asked me
what immortals and demons are.
He scolded me for thinking all demons are evil.
I thought he was so stupid.
Immortals represent justice.
Demons should be despised by the world.
This is
a general rule.
But now I finally know
immortals and demons
are just titles.
How dare you
slander the God Realm!
You asked for this.
Yinfeng.
Ji Ruochen, why are you here?
Leave now.
What happened?
I was on my way to the Endless Sea
to stop the Demon Tower from being born.
But I met immortal generals, Hao Ming and Yu Yun,
who were coming to the mortal world.
They believed what Sun Guo said.
They are trying to catch you.
Leave now.
Immortal generals?
Catch me?
Good.
I was just going to meet them.
But you are a banished god.
Why are you helping me?
Because...
Because I was wrong.
You were wrong?
Yes.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have guessed the heavenly secret
and thought I represented righteousness.
The real righteousness
varies from time to time, from places to places,
and from person to person.
There is no definition at all.
Whether it's a demon
or an immortal,
it doesn't matter.
What matters is whether the heart
is good or evil.
Back then,
I used Qing
to try to kill you.
If anyone was demonized,
it should be me,
not you.
Why are you suddenly so clear-minded?
Where is Fairy Gu?
Qing.
Qing turned into a bluestone again.
This...
How did Gu Qing become like this?
What happened?
Let's talk about this later.
We should deal with the trouble first.
High Immortals.
This is Ji Ruochen.
You are Ji Ruochen, the Demon King?
Yes.
I heard that you want to arrest me.
But there should be a reason for everything.
Since you want to arrest me,
you should give me a reason.
Demon King.
You destroyed the spiritual caves first
and then planned the birth of the Demon Tower.
The Blue Fire of the Nine Hells above the tower
is the best evidence.
A thief crying "stop thief!"
You divine generals in the Heaven,
I want to see
what you are capable of.
Let me show you what a real demon is.
This must be the Ascending Platform that leads straight to the God Realm.
Immortals can do whatever they want?
I'm going to eliminate
the root of the chaos in the Three Realms.
Ruochen, we don't know what is up there.
Come back.
How dare you mortals
climb the heavenly stairs!
Master.
Master, it's me.
Kill Ji Ruochen now.
Otherwise, he will fight his way to the God Realm.
Stay calm.
I'm going to put out the blue flame
and bring peace to the Three Realms.
High Immortal Taiyi, you're finally here.
You're High Immortal Taiyi?
You know me?
Of course I do.
It was you
that killed the people of the Nine Hells and my parents
and built the Demon Tower,
right?
And the flame face in the tower
was you too, right?
You're a smart guy.
You actually figured out the heavenly secret.
How can I fool you if I'm not smart?
High Immortal Taiyi.
You don't feel good being fooled, do you?
Brat.
How dare you mention this!
Back at the Nine Hells,
I should have torn you into pieces.
Ji Ruochen,
you went against the Heaven.
Today, you must die.
Who are you to convict me?
I'm in charge of the law and rules in the God Realm.
You have the Blue Fire of the Nine Hells
and became the Demon King because of it.
How can I sit by?
You can call him
whatever you want.
But who is the real demon?
You destroyed the Nine Hells and built the Demon Tower.
You did all those things.
You are the real demon.
You call this rubbish
an ancient divine weapon?
Today, I'll show you
what the grand divine power is.
The Linglong Tower
was specially created to put out your Blue Fire of the Nine Hells.
Ji Ruochen.
Die!
Let me send you to hell now.
Master.
They are just two clowns.
No need to get your hands dirty.
Leave them to me.
Hierarch Ziwei, you've finished your seclusion?
Master.
Ruochen,
do you still accept me as your master?
Master.
I've found the person who built the tower.
I didn't fail you.
High Immortal Taiyi. You are too ambitious.
You caused chaos in the Three Realms.
Surrender now!
Ziwei, you alone
dare to stand against me?
He is not alone.
You...
Senior, you love your disciple so much.
But don't forget that
Ruochen is also our disciple.
That's right, Senior.
We can't miss this battle.
Ruochen,
we misunderstood you before.
Masters.
Cut the crap.
I'll grant your wish today
and let you die together.
I was in seclusion for a thousand years
just for today's battle.
Hierarch.
Master!
No.
Master.
♫With my sword, I face the world, breaking through the swirling sand♫
I've been
the acting hierarch long enough.
♫How many high positions were obtained through deceit and trickery♫
Please let me
help my disciple, okay?
Senior.
♫Amidst the shifting sands, who will emerge as the winner in the end?♫
That's what I'm thinking.
Senior.
♫Amidst the chaos and distractions, who can truly let go?♫
That's what we are thinking too.
♫Not for leaving a mark in history or the glimmer of swords♫
Ziyang.
♫The turbulent times change in an instant♫
You old man.
♫It's all because of you and me, braving obstacles♫
Having a gang fight is very interesting.
Why didn't you tell me?
♫I traverse the currents of time to be with you again♫
Master!
♫I cross endless hills, vowing to stay true to our promises♫
Alright, buddy.
Let's go engage in a gang fight.
Let's go. Please.
Go engage in a gang fight.
♫The sun and moon witness the eternal enmity and grievances♫
♫I only wish to hold your hand and be by your side♫
♫As long as I have you by my side, what more could I ask for in this lifetime?♫