[English subtitles are available]
[Divine Destiny]
[Episode 11]
Sir.
I'm Zhang Yinyin. I'm passing by.
I'm really thirsty.
I want to get some water from you.
Do you know how to play Go?
No.
Boring.
The Heaven is boring. The Earth is boring.
The sea is boring, and the people are boring.
Me too.
What a weirdo.
I don't mind if you don't give me water.
And you said many useless words.
I'd better find water on my own.
What...
Aren't you Ling?
You're back.
Why are you here?
So
after all this time,
I just rowed myself back.
Mr. Wu,
I know your place is big.
Show me a way.
How can I get out?
You can't.
Qingyi is cultivating her power again.
If it weren't for you,
she wouldn't have gotten involved in what happened in Haofang
and disturbed her mind.
Now no one is here to chat with me to relieve my boredom.
Since you're here,
why don't you take her place?
Are you kidding me?
I'm the chief disciple of the Taixuan Palace of Xixuan Sect.
I ranked first in the Annual Exam and ranked first on the Qingyun List.
How can I stay here to play Go with you?
What about Xixuan Sect?
It's been years
since Ziwei
passed the death calamity.
But has he ascended to a High Immortal?
He always goes out whenever there's any trouble.
He's not determined at all.
You can joke with me.
But how dare you insult our hierarch!
Master.
So you are Su He's disciple.
You are not that ignorant.
My master is the Nine-Tailed Heavenly Fox.
Are you afraid?
After hiding for a thousand years,
I still can't hide from it.
Then let me out.
When she comes,
she will make the Endless Sea disappear.
No, no.
If she comes, everything will be over.
What are you waiting for?
Send me out.
If that's the case, I can't let you out.
If you inform her
and stir up trouble,
what should I do?
You
stay here.
Here again?
Xichen.
Xichen, where are you going?
Luo Feng.
Did I mistake him for Luo Feng?
Feng.
It's you. It's really you.
Luo Feng you mentioned
died in the inn outside the city long ago.
The person in front of you is Yinfeng.
Now that I have regained my consciousness of god,
I will definitely return to the God Realm in the future.
Both you and I
should forget
what's in the past.
Luo Feng.
What are you talking about?
Who is Yinfeng?
What God Realm?
You are Young Master Luo of the Luo Mansion in Haofang.
Not anymore.
I'm a banished god now.
I've cut ties with everything in the mortal world.
What about me?
Have you also cut ties with me?
I gave up everything
for you.
If you abandon me,
where can I go?
You already have the King of Haofang, Li An, right?
High position and great wealth are within your reach.
This is
good for you.
You were right.
You are not him.
Feng
is dead.
It was all my wishful thinking. I deserve it.
Leave.
Go back to the God Realm.
This is the Book of Heaven.
I'll give you one volume.
But you should know
I have repaid
what I owed you.
From now on,
we have nothing to do with each other.
Feng.
Xichen.
Why are you here?
Feng.
Oh no.
You lost all your divine energy.
There is no difference between you and a mortal now.
You insisted on inviting Master to come here.
What should you do if he feels uncomfortable out of anger?
You are so silly.
No matter how important your divine destiny is,
you shouldn't lose your dharma-laksana
for Ji Ruochen.
Master.
What's done is done.
It's too late to regret.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have spoiled you.
No.
I can't just let this go.
Ziyang
is good at playing tricks.
He just can't stand it because Yun Zhong Ju
has surpassed Xixuan Sect.
So he used Ji Ruochen as a bait
to make you lose your dharma-laksana.
I'm so angry.
I'm going to see him.
Ziyang.
Ziyang!
Where is he?
-Bro?
-Ziyang.
Ziyang.
Jin Shan.
Welcome, Hierarch Jin Shan.
Cut it out.
Through the battle in Haofang,
Xixuan earned fame and the treasure.
Look at us.
I lost a fairy.
Yes.
I'm here to ask you to give me an explanation.
If you don't,
I'll go to your senior.
I'll talk to him.
Bro. Bro. Bro.
Wait.
Please calm down.
Let's talk it over, okay?
No need.
Just give me a solution.
Bro.
In order to save my disciple Ruochen,
Fairy Gu Qing lost her dharma-laksana.
She won't have a chance to return to the God Realm.
Xixuan Sect will never forget
her sacrifice.
On behalf of my disciple Ruochen,
I deliver my gratitude to Fairy Gu Qing
and Yun Zhong Ju.
That's it?
Your solution is bowing to me?
Don't forget that
Qing and Ji Ruochen are engaged.
I know what you think.
You think Qing is no different from a mortal.
She doesn't deserve a banished god.
So you want to go back on your words
and cancel the engagement.
How could you say that?
Yes.
Xixuan did gain fame through the battle in Haofang.
But we also offended many people.
I'm afraid there won't be peace anymore
in Xixuan Mountains.
I'd love to become relatives with Yun Zhong Ju through their marriage
considering the situation.
Bro.
If you don't mind,
we can choose an auspicious date as soon as possible,
so that my disciple can marry Gu Qing
to repay her.
What do you think?
Good.
However,
I'm afraid...
What are you afraid of?
If you're afraid that Xixuan Sect will get you implicated,
just forget what I said.
What a joke.
When did Yun Zhong Ju ever fear
those evil sects?
Then what are you afraid of?
I'm afraid...
I've heard
Ji Ruochen has fallen in love with
Jingxiao Zhenren's daughter.
-I'm afraid Ji Ruochen will…
-He dare not.
He is my disciple.
He's the one in Xixuan who should face the calamity.
He has the responsibility of promoting the sect
and saving the Three Realms.
Marriage is important.
He can't make the decision himself.
His master should make the decision for him.
Does your disciple Ji Ruochen
look like someone who obeys his master?
She saved his life.
He has to repay her.
It's not up to him.
Besides,
he owes a bigger favor.
What?
Nice!
I lost a fairy first.
Now you want to take the secret technique of Yun Zhong Ju.
I knew
I'd be fooled by you sooner or later.
I only care about
the future of Xixuan Sect and Yun Zhong Ju.
I have no selfish motives.
Hierarch Jin Shan. Please.
Fine.
For Qing,
I'm willing to do anything.
You are very kind.
But I have one condition.
As long as I can do it,
I'll do my best.
You must
invite all sects to Qing's wedding.
It will be a grand wedding.
She won't feel wronged.
Let's make this clear.
Xixuan Sect begged Yun Zhong Ju
for this marriage.
I agree.
The Endless Sea is a legend.
No one knows where it is.
How are you going to find it?
Qingyi told me about it before.
So
I think I may be able to find some clues.
Really?
It's great
if you can bring Yinyin back.
I really miss her.
Take the medicine.
Thank you.
By the way,
you should pay attention to your health.
Gu Qing transferred her dharma-laksana to you
to temporarily stop the aftereffect of the Dreadstar Fate-Infusion Technique,
but
this is just a temporary measure.
Yes.
Speaking of Gu Qing,
when we heard you two were engaged,
Qiushui and I were worried.
But after knowing you and Yinyin
love each other so deeply,
we can rest assured.
Don't worry.
I'm fine now.
I hope so.
Senior.
What can I do for you?
Master said
Senior Ruochen needs time to recover.
So he ordered us to come here
to be at your disposal.
Thank you.
Sorry to bother you.
What is it?
It seems that I can't go to the Endless Sea.
I wonder how Ruochen is now.
And my father, my mother,
Xuanzhen, and Shui.
You scared me.
Why are you standing there?
Don't you need to sleep?
My master created me with monster arts.
I have no soul or spirit.
So I feel nothing. I don't sleep or eat.
Of course I don't need to sleep.
How can I sleep if you stand there?
I'm not the reason why you can't sleep.
You can't sleep because of Ruochen, Xuanzhen,
your father, your mother, and Shui.
Enough.
You win.
Remove the barrier and take a walk with me.
Sit with me for a while.
♫Moonlight clear as snow, my thoughts are hidden♫
♫Who plays a farewell tune in the alley♫
♫Lovesickness is like a butterfly. Floral fragrance fading away♫
Look.
The moon is so beautiful.
♫Robes swirling, intoxicated, dancing to a poetic verse♫
♫Moonlight bright as snow, loneliness fills the long street♫
♫Shadows remain while forms intertwine with belief♫
♫Bustling sounds vanish between branches and leaves♫
♫Emotions turning, tears unseen♫
♫I feel as if I'm distant from this bustling world of crowds♫
♫Frowning, heart aching, love and hate entwined♫
♫Your tenderness separated by distance and time♫
♫And I can only embrace myself in care♫
♫As the dim lights fade away, troubles come to a halt♫
♫Still entangled with many emotional trials♫
♫You wrote a letter to make an appointment with me♫
♫Leaving a startled glimpse in my heart♫
Ling.
Do you have someone you like?
Someone I like?
What does that mean?
No matter where you are
or what you do,
you want to see her every day and night.
In order to meet her,
you are not afraid of
the distance or challenges.
Yes.
My master.
I'm not talking about this.
I mean
the person you are hiding here carefully.
The person I'm hiding here?
Who is that person?
Dragon Elephant. White Tiger.
Are you okay?
Hurry. Get up.
-My Cannon!
-What are you two doing?
It's been so many days.
Why didn't you come to me?
Master lent the warehouse of the Endless Sea
to us.
We can use whatever
in the warehouse.
It's not that we didn't want to see you.
We're busy improving the Universal Cannon.
An accident happened,
and it has become like this.
It's all your fault.
I told you to ignite it later.
How can you blame me?
-I told you.
-It's all your fault.
Enough.
Stop arguing.
Can you two be more ambitious?
You called him Master, just because he gave you treasures.
What a bootlicker.
Well. Yinyin.
The owner of the Endless Sea
is the master of all monsters.
If we become his men,
we won't have to worry about
the rest of our lives.
I can't stand you two.
When do you plan to leave?
Well...
What? You don't want to leave?
You blew up the warehouse.
These treasures are scattered all over the place.
Do you think he will spare you two?
Right.
Do you think he will
treat us like how he treated Qingyi?
Will he put us in the Ice Prison
and torture us?
What happened to Qingyi?
You tell her.
Yinyin.
You were in a coma.
So you didn't know.
Qingyi
offended the owner of the Endless Sea
because of her trip to Haofang.
So she was thrown into the Ice Prison
to suffer.
Where is the Ice Prison?
At the bottom of the Endless Sea.
Every day, Qingyi needs to purify her heart with blood
and practice her skills with ice pitons piercing her bones.
Master said
only in this way
can she cut ties with everything in the mortal world.
Isn't your master her uncle?
Why did he do that to her?
Qingyi volunteered to go.
Yinyin.
Qingyi getting punished
is a family matter of the Endless Sea.
We can't do anything about it.
Right.
He is abusive.
I must intervene.
When can you fix the Universal Cannon at the soonest?
Well...
Ling.
Deliver a message to your master.
I, Zhang Yinyin,
want to fight with him decently.
Juniors.
Senior Qiushui.
Thank you for guarding this place.
In the middle of the night,
it's easy to catch a cold.
I specially made this soup
for you.
-I'm hungry.
-Come with me to have a taste.
Come. Don't stand on ceremony.
Let's go.
If this is not enough, there is more in the kitchen.
Is my medicine so effective?
They all passed out?
Yes.
Am I good?
You're amazing.
Do you plan to open an illegal restaurant?
You can make a fortune.
You are wrong.
Qiushui doesn't need it.
As the saying goes, be thrifty at home and spend liberally while traveling.
I'm giving you a little money.
You can use it on your way.
Take it.
Did you call this a little money?
Do you know how many illegal restaurants you can open with the money?
I'm not taking it.
Just take it.
Take it.
His family has run money shops for generations.
He has a lot of money.
When he first came here,
some of the masters fought fiercely with each other
to make him their disciple.
It's not worth mentioning.
Alright, it's getting late.
Go now.
It's a long journey.
You must take care.
Ruochen,
you have money now.
If you and Yinyin
find a better place
where you can be free and happy,
you don't have to come back.
What are you talking about?
All right, I'm leaving.
Okay.
Why is he here again?
Ruochen.
You took the responsibility of eliminating the demon in Haofang.
I really envy you.
Many people can't have such a chance even if they want.
So you should cherish it more
and live up to the expectations
of Master and other Zhenren.
Senior.
What are you talking about?
I've killed Bamboo Snake.
I know.
But if I didn't come today,
would you leave without saying goodbye?
No.
I'm just going out.
I'm going to take Yinyin back to Xixuan.
Yinyin is still waiting for me.
If there's nothing else,
I'm leaving.
I haven't used this for years.
I'm a little unfamiliar with it.
Senior.
What do you want?
I know you love Yinyin so much.
If you insist on leaving here,
I have no choice.
Are you here to force me
to get married like them?
No.
Then why?
Master asked me to ask you
if you forgot to give something important
to him.
That's it?
Why didn't you finish it all at once?
What is the thing that I haven't given to him?
Think about it.
The Shenzhou Energy Map?
What?
Ling told me that you wanted to fight with me.
I have no other choice.
I don't want to stay here
anymore.
Why don't we have a fight?
If I win,
you need to let me go.
And you need to let Dragon Elephant, White Tiger, and Qingyi
go with me.
Who are Dragon Tiger and White Elephant?
We are Dragon Elephant and White...
The two people
who blew up your warehouse last night.
Don't be afraid.
I can see it.
This mask man
doesn't dare to leave this tree.
You can aim the Universal Cannon at him.
I'm sure no shot will be wasted.
OK.
After you were brought here by Qingyi,
you caused an explosion. And now you want to fight.
My island has become lively.
If I let you all go,
Ling and I
will be left alone.
No.
I can't agree to any of your conditions.
Even if you win,
I won't let you go.
There are rules in the martial arts world.
If you lose, you have to let us go.
This is not the martial arts world.
On the Endless Sea,
I am the rules.
But I'm Zhang Yinyin.
You need to change your rules.
Dragon Elephant. White Tiger.
Ready the Universal Cannon.
Come on.
Wonderful! Wonderful!
The Dragon and Tiger Universal Cannon.
Wait for me!
These two cowards.
No.
Qingyi is still suffering.
Ruochen is waiting for me too.
I'm going to cut your mask into two pieces today.
Your secret technique of the Heavenly Fox is good.
No wonder Su He made an exception to accept you as her disciple.
But
you've only learned a little.
You want to find Qingyi, right?
Go.
Mr. Ji.
Don't move.
Qingyi.
Yinyin.
You came at the right time.
Come and teach me how to kiss.
Ruochen.
My Ji Ruochen.
Yinyin.
You broke my Ji Ruochen.
You already have one.
Why can't I have one?
Why don't you give yours to me?
Qingyi. Good for you.
I thought you were suffering in the Ice Prison.
I didn't expect you to play here.
Why did you transform your puppet into Ji Ruochen?
And it looked like him a lot.
I'm warning you.
Don't do that again.
And
I won't give my Ji Ruochen to you.
Yinyin.
What you said is unreasonable.
I can transform my puppet
into anyone.
It's none of your business.
Besides,
you broke my Ji Ruochen.
It's fine that you don't apologize.
But you're so overbearing.
I even regarded you as my sister.
Good for you.
Give it to me.
Do you believe I'm going to smash it?
Give it back!
You are really bold. Qingyi.
Do you believe I'll beat you?
How dare you!
Master. I'm here.
Ruochen.
How are you feeling now?
Much better now.
I'm still resting my body.
In Haofang,
you lived up to everyone's expectations and achieved success.
I haven't congratulated you yet.
Although I killed Bamboo Snake,
I don't think
I deserve your praise just now.
When I was fighting with Bamboo Snake in Haofang,
I lost the Shenzhou Energy Map.
Sorry to disappoint you.
Master,
please punish me.
Do you really not know
where the Shenzhou Energy Map is?
All right, Ruochen.
No more nonsense.
Give me the map now.
Master.
The map was taken by a powerful man.
I really don't have it.
Did you meet two powerful people
when you were looking for the map beside the Hao River?
I met two old friends.
I have something for you.
What is this?
Don't ask. Just take it.
Could it be...
So the map has been with me all the time.
Xuanxin Ring isolated the spiritual energy.
That's why I didn't notice it.
Master.
Is this the place where
Shenzhou's spiritual power gathers?
Yes.
The place where the spiritual power gathers is called the spiritual cave.
You are
very lucky
to feel
the flow of the spiritual energy in the map.
But the flow of the spiritual energy
is unstable.
When the time is right,
I'll tell you more.
I asked you to recultivate your power.
But you
were playing.
And you.
You're a guest after all.
I've showed my hospitality.
Look at her.
What did you do to her?
It's all because you didn't teach her well.
You allowed your disciple
to do such a shameful thing.
She transformed her puppet into my fiancé
and kissed and hugged him.
Even I felt so embarrassed.
I learned it from you.
You kissed Ji Ruochen.
I just thought it should taste good.
I just wanted to have a taste.
You don't understand.
Ruochen and I love each other.
What does that mean?
Well...
We have feelings for each other.
What does that mean?
Well...
It means someone
you are hiding here carefully.
What are you talking about?
Are you all trying to rebel?
Ling, tell me.
Who taught you that?
Something bad will happen.
You're just like your master.
If you stay here any longer,
I won't find peace on this island.
Little Fox.
Go back to where you came from.
I'll see you out.
My small island
is not somewhere you should stay.
You should have done this earlier.
Isn't it good for everyone to be harmonious?
You just wouldn't listen to me.
The Shenzhou Energy Map
concerns the safety of the Three Realms.
Since Xixuan has the map now,
we can finally find a way
to survive the calamity.
From now on, the future of Xixuan Sect
will depend on you.
Master.
I don't think I can shoulder
the responsibility of facing the calamity for Xixuan Sect.
Are you scared?
I'm not.
I just don't want to lie to you anymore.
I think
you want me to
help you refuse your marriage with Fairy Gu Qing, right?
I'm guilty.
Please punish me.
What guilt?
Master admitted me to Xixuan,
because I...
Because you are a banished god.
You can promote Xixuan.
And you are the one who will face the calamity for Xixuan.
But Master,
I'm not a banished god.
I know.