[English subtitles are available]
[Divine Destiny]
[Episode 17]
Ruochen.
Ruochen, what's wrong?
Let go!
Ruochen.
Ji Clerk.
I'm Zhang Yinyin.
Wake up!
Wake up.
Ruochen.
How are you?
Don't make me worried, Ruochen.
Senior.
What happened to Ruochen just now?
He has never been like this before.
What is the blue true spirit?
Xixuan Sect doesn't have such techniques.
I'm afraid it's not an ordinary  technique.
Then what is it?
Was it because of the Ecstasy Needle?
Yes. Or no.
Yinyin.
No matter what,
we can't let Ruochen know what happened tonight.
Understand?
Yes.
We're the only ones
he can rely on now.
Don't worry.
We'll find a way together.
Ruochen will be fine.
Feng, it's really you.
Why are you here?
Are you here for me?
Did you find traces of Ji Ruochen?
So you're here for him.
We didn't find anything.
However,
he was shot by the Ecstasy Needle I made with divine power.
He has lost his mind.
He won't go far.
Why did you deliberately set a trap
to kill him?
Did Sun Guo ask you to do that?
Because he killed you
outside the city back then.
Because he stole your identity as a banished god.
Feng,
I want to avenge you.
This is between me and him.
I'll put an end to it myself.
You should stay out of this.
No.
I must let him die in front of me,
so that it will
be equal to
my sacrifice all these years.
If it weren't for him,
I wouldn't have ended up in Haofang.
And I wouldn't have been with Li An.
I taught you immortal arts,
because I wanted you to learn to protect yourself,
not to become a toy.
I don't want you to end up like me,
deeply troubled by love and hate
and unable to escape.
I want to help you.
Xixuan Sect is hypocritical
and helped Ji Ruochen bully you.
It doesn't deserve the title of the number one sect in the world.
If Qingxu Sect can replace it,
all sects
will be at your command.
-By that time, I…
-Do you really want to help me?
Or do you want to use the power of Qingxu Sect and me
to fulfill your desires?
Feng.
You don't trust me?
After I kill Ji Ruochen,
you should go back and be your Crown Princess.
Don't be troubled by love or hate in this mortal world.
But you are troubled
more deeply than me.
With your current power,
can you really kill Ji Ruochen?
Feng.
Luo Feng!
Ruochen.
Hurry.
The first elixir
Get up.
has finally been completed.
Here.
I made it just now.
Senior.
Why do I think this medicine
smells differently
from the medicine made by Master?
Of course.
The formula is different.
Besides,
I made this with my own furnace.
It's obviously not as good as Master's Golden Elixir Furnace.
I think it smells not bad.
Eat it.
It took Senior Yunfeng
two days and two nights to make this.
How does it taste?
Senior.
I also learned elixir making techniques.
I still don't think the taste is right.
Why?
Normally,
this medicine should be made
in a furnace.
Why does this pill
have a foul smell?
It smells like
mouse droppings.
Oh no.
It's the trogopterus dung.
After I took it back from the mountain,
I forgot to dry it and fry it.
Please forgive me.
I'll make another one.
I'm going to make another one.
What is the trogopterus dung?
The trogopterus dung
is the droppings
of mountain rats
that can fly.
So you were right.
Will you get poisoned after eating it?
No.
But it might cause complications
if it's efficacy is not strong enough.
It will make my illness worse.
You'd better spit it out now.
Spit it all out.
How are you feeling?
Is the elixir ready?
Mr. Ji, you're here.
What happened to your neck?
Mr. Ji, that night...
Thank you for your warning.
Mr. Ji.
Do you know anything
about what's inside Ruochen?
I don't know anything more than you do.
This time, Ji Ruochen
will face a great calamity.
However,
he is very lucky
to have a senior like you.
Mr. Ji. That day...
Did he eat the elixir?
Yes.
It's just I used a wrong ingredient.
It doesn't matter.
You continue.
I'm going in to check on him.
Senior.
Yinyin.
What happened?
Ruochen lost his mind again.
It's fine.
Let me take a look inside.
Zekai.
It's good that you came back safely this time.
I've asked Taixuan and Taiwei
to go to the capital
to save those imprisoned disciples.
Don't worry.
Sun Guo plotted against Xixuan this time.
I won't let it go.
Once the time is right,
I will avenge you.
Thank you, Master.
Did you see Yinyin and Ruochen?
Yes.
They fought their way to the dungeon
and saved me.
If it weren't for them,
I wouldn't be standing here today.
That's great.
You stay here for several days
to recover your body.
Thank you, Master.
How are you, Ruochen?
I feel much better.
It's done.
Ruochen. Ruochen.
Today, you have a new piece of elixir to eat.
Here.
Eat.
What's that smell outside?
I am making
sophora flower pancakes on the stove
for Ruochen and you.
It smells so good.
Do you want some?
Senior, let me help you.
Okay, let's go.
I'll be waiting for you.
Mr. Ji.
To be honest,
I feel that Senior Yunfeng's medicine
is not very effective.
Do you have a better way?
If Yunfeng's elixir doesn't work,
there's another way.
What is it?
Yourself.
Myself?
What kind of method is this?
Do you remember the calamity
I told you a few days ago?
The God's will
keeps changing.
Doing things as we wish
is the way to solve the problem.
Maybe
the solution
is up to you.
I'm going to eat pancakes.
Why am I here again?
Maybe the solution to this problem
is up to me.
No matter what you are,
I'll give it a try.
Why are you here?
I heard that
you broke into the jail in the capital to save people
and were badly injured.
And Zhenwu Temple is tracking you down.
I didn't thank you
for saving me last time in Luoran School.
I'm sorry you had a wasted journey this time.
As you can see,
they tried to murder me.
But they failed.
If my guess is right,
this is the Ecstasy Needle of Zhenwu Temple, right?
I didn't expect that
Yinfeng has a little sister either.
Her name is Luo Xichen.
She's now a disciple of Zhenwu Temple.
All these years,
she has been looking for a chance to avenge her brother.
I was too careless.
I fell into her trap.
The blue flame that appeared when you used your power
doesn't look like Xixuan Sect's techniques.
Where did you learn it?
I don't know.
I think I've had it since I was born.
I used to use it on the inn's guests.
But I don't know how to use it.
Now it seems
very mysterious.
Demon.
He is a demon.
Ji Ruochen is a demon.
I saw it with my own eyes.
He has the energy of the Nine Hells.
Ji Ruochen must be a demon.
Qing, you must trust me.
I see.
Do you know this technique?
Why are you crying?
I don't know it.
I was just asking.
Since you're fine,
I should go.
I still want to ask
why you chose Zhang Yinyin
instead of me.
I don't know.
I just want no one else
except her.
Ruochen.
Take care.
Come out.
Are you satisfied now?
You should know
what is in his body.
According to the Book of Heaven,
that is the demon flame
left in the mortal world by the Demon Lord in ancient times.
If it keeps growing,
it can destroy the world.
It's a demonic object
that should be eliminated by everyone in the Three Realms.
Since it's a demonic object,
it's not tolerated by God's will.
God's will?
You value God's will so much.
But have you really understood it?
Let me ask you.
I just saw that on the Ecstasy Needle,
besides the demon flame,
there was still divine power left.
Did you do that?
Luo Xichen, a disciple of Zhenwu Temple
and the current Crown Princess,
is my cousin in this life
in the mortal world.
I gave her a volume of the Book of Heaven
to make us
even.
How could he be a demon?
Qing.
The flame
can bewitch people.
Even a deity will lose his mind
if he touches it,
not to mention Ji Ruochen.
If he's not a demon,
why did he kill me outside the city?
And why did he steal my identity as a banished god
to bewitch people?
Qing.
Since you've known this,
you should eliminate the flame with me.
Otherwise,
when he really turns into a demon,
it'll be too late.
I can't do it.
But we are gods.
You can ignore our 100-lifetime promise.
But you have the responsibility
to follow God's will with me.
Ji Ruochen
teamed up with the Nine Hells and gave up himself.
Gods and demons are different.
How can you let him go?
But even if he is a demon,
he was the one I loved.
Qing,
why are you so muddle-headed?
You should know
he is a demon.
We are gods.
Gods and demons are irreconcilable.
Either he dies
or I die.
You have chosen to abandon God's will.
I will uphold it.
Yinfeng.
Am I really wrong?
What is supposed to happen will happen sooner or later.
Yinfeng,
it's time for us to put an end to it.
Today,
it's not about our grudges.
It's only about God's will.
There is karma in the vast universe.
Ji Ruochen.
Killing you is an act of justice.
It may sound a bit harsh.
But I don't want you to die without knowing why.
What a joke.
What did I do wrong?
Who are you to convict me?
You're just here to avenge yourself.
Why did you make such an excuse?
Don't you think it's tiring?
Do you know
what is burning in your hands?
Tell me.
This is the Blue Fire of the Nine Hells.
It's from the Nine Hells.
I don't care where it comes from,
as long as it's easy-to-use.
You are so arrogant.
Let's make a deal.
If I win,
you'll die without anything to regret.
If you lose,
I hope you can rest in peace.
Ji Ruochen,
take this and die.
Knock on the fat sheep.
So much
for so-called divine power.
You're dying.
Do you know why?
If I had known you gods were like this,
I shouldn't have stolen your identity.
Listen carefully.
The blue fire you have
is called the Blue Fire of the Nine Hells.
It's the demon flame
left in the mortal world by the Demon King in ancient times.
It can destroy the world and kill all living things,
so that there will be no light in the Three Realms.
You were born
with the demon flame.
If you're not a demon,
what else could you be?
What's with that look?
Even if others have never told you,
don't you know that?
You are a demon.
You're a demon that everyone should kill.
So, you have a name.
The Blue Fire of the Nine Hells.
But why me?
An orphan
and a clerk of an inn.
Everyone says I'm the one who will face the calamity.
It's my responsibility to save the Three Realms.
But why am I a demon?
The so-called demon
is just like this.
It's not too late to know this now.
At least you know I didn't wrong you.
I know.
It's justice.
That's right.
You are a deity, and I am a demon.
It's natural for you to kill me.
But that's just your idea.
What is immortality? What is a demon? What is God's will?
How can you decide them alone?
It's what the people say.
Am I one of the people?
The so-called people you mentioned
are just
sheep without a shepherd.
Fine.
At this moment,
no one will plead guilty after all.
Ji Ruochen.
Arguing about this with you
is a waste of time.
You can use whatever techniques
you've learned.
I'm giving you a chance.
Okay.
Let me see
how powerful this demon is.
The smallest may hold the largest.
The Heaven and the Earth can be moved.
As expected,
a demon is a demon.
My name is Ji
Clerk.
Back then outside the city,
if you had destroyed my body,
now
you wouldn't have suffered so much.
This time,
don't be merciful.
What?
You remember the sand and wind in the desert?
You remember what you did?
Leave.
I'm going to spare you
from this stick.
I'm surprised that you still have a sense of shame.
From now on,
there are no grudges between us.
We are even.
Is this what a banished god does?
I let you go.
But you attacked me behind my back.
You forgot to clear
the divine power on the Ecstasy Needle.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have had the chance
to use it
to disturb your demonic energy.
But your behavior
is really nasty.
Nasty?
I'm a deity.
It's my duty to kill demons.
Methods don't matter.
It's useless.
The divine power has disturbed your soul and spirit.
You can no longer summon the demon flame.
Everything has its rules.
What goes around comes around.
Ji Ruochen.
Just die.