Grandma Chen.
Hua.
Hua!
Mom, this is Grandma Chen.
Look, I bought you this!
Thank you, Grandma Chen.
Hua.
Grandma Chen.
Why hasn't Xiaohu come?
I saved some candy for him.
Good girl.
Xiaohu is
at kindergarten.
Grandma Chen.
After he finishes school,
can you bring him over?
Hua.
=Endless Protection=
=Episode 9=
You're really Xiaohua
and Xiaohu's grandma, right?
Do they know that?
Why don't you tell them?
Seeing your grandkids every day
but pretending not to know them.
Isn't it absurd?
Tu Huaiwei said,
as long as I don't admit I'm his mother,
I can live with them.
And he'd give me money
to buy food for the kids.
How long do you live together?
More than a year.
Didn't Yang Xiaoying notice anything?
I am just a nanny.
Nothing special.
Did those two
ever hit the kids?
The two kids are quite unfortunate.
Yang Xiaoying
really spoils her daughter.
Every time Huihui complained
the two kids bullied her,
she would argue with Tu Huaiwei
and even raised hell.
Who hit the kids,
Tu Huaiwei or Yang Xiaoying?
Tu Huaiwei.
Last time Xiaohu was found injured
at kindergarten.
It was Tu Huaiwei who hit him, right?
Who took Xiaohu to the hospital
for a cast?
I did.
Where's the medical record?
I put it on the back of the sofa.
Ma'am,
can you testify in court about this?
No, no.
Tu Huaiwei's actually in a tough spot.
He...
Ma'am!
Xiaohu has passed away.
And Xiaohua is now
lying in the hospital.
If you turn a blind eye to this,
how will she face
the rest of her life?
It's your stubbornness and indulgence
that hurt these children.
Where are you going, Bai Enyu?
What else? To issue a search warrant!
Ma'am, let's calm down.
Think about it.
You can't pretend this
as if it never happened.
Xiaohua is only six years old.
How is she going to live
the rest of her life?
This will be her lifelong trauma.
What are you doing?
Step aside.
We're from the Procuratorate.
Here, a search warrant.
What are you looking for?
(Tu Xiaohu, Orthopedic ward)
Alright, alright.
Bai said
he found the evidence
of injuring Xiaohua and Xiaohu.
Injuring, right?
Right.
That's not enough for murder.
Abuse works.
Arrest him.
(Police)
(Yunhai First Detention Center)
Tu Huaiwei, Yang Xiaoying!
What now?
You two are suspected
of abusing Tu Xiaohua and Tu Xiaohua.
With the approval of
the People's Procuratorate
of Chanquan District,
you are hereby arrested.
- Cuff them.
- Is there a mistake?
I've said everything I can.
Take them away.
Wait.
Alright.
Captain Du.
Thank you.
They're arrested.
Finally, we got them!
Serves them right.
It's about time.
This's already late.
Charging Tu Huaiwei
and Yang Xiaoying of child abuse
is just the first step.
To get them on attempted murder,
we have a long way to go.
Keep it up.
Bai, Director Lu.
- Lin.
- Director Lu.
I've got something.
See if you can use it.
I don't need it.
Tu Huaiwei's arrested,
so my mania is already cured.
You are not manic anymore,
but you have problem in understanding.
What's wrong?
Director Lu is
letting us to consult the doctor
to help Xiaohua, right?
Right.
I heard Xiaohua has woken up?
She's the key witness in this case.
Communicating with her
must be methodical.
- Right.
- I get it.
Just like conducting evaluations.
Step by step. Don't rush.
That's why I brought this
to you for reference.
Consult them.
Alright. We'll go consult
and learn.
Okay.
About asking Xiaohua,
I think we shouldn't rush for now.
Let her recover first.
Then we'll proceed.
Director Lu.
(Chunyu Psychology Workshop)
Is this effective?
Hello.
- Hello.
You're sent by Director Lu?
Yes, that's right.
From the Procuratorate.
Please sit.
I'll introduce myself first.
Okay.
My name is Su Jianyue.
I specialize in childhood depression
and trauma treatment.
We're here for a child.
Is it your child?
Yes, it's my child.
Mine too.
Shut your mouth.
Wow, blue sky, white clouds, beach.
The Truman Show?
Is that what Truman Show means?
Isn't it?
This is called sandplay therapy.
How does it work?
Look at those sand tools behind you.
You can let the children
pick any and place them
however they want.
From that,
you can analyze
and discover some of their thoughts
or issues.
Well,
just placing toys
in the sand
reveals their thoughts?
Maybe it sounds simple.
However, sandplay
is like drawing and writing a journal.
It helps children lower their guard
and express themselves
in the most comfortable way.
Understood.
You can try it first.
Try placing some items.
Okay, I'll start with these.
And then?
Just place them.
- Can I move the sand?
- Sure.
It's blue underneath.
Yes, it is.
You can imagine it as an ocean.
Or a river, right?
Right.
This goes here.
Then...
Done.
The first thing you picked is a boat.
Right.
It represents yourself.
The shells and bottles on the shore
are all far away.
Except this one in the corner.
I just wanted to put it here.
Alright.
The boat is isolated
in the middle of the vast ocean.
The bottles and shells on the shore
are a bit far from the boat.
Right.
Of course, I think you care about them.
But in your view,
between the boat
and the bottles and shells,
there is quite a distance.
In other words,
this is
a solitary boat.
Wait, a solitary boat?
Aren't I still here?
Right?
I think...
Miss. Su.
I think this result
is not that accurate.
Please interpret mine.
All be together.
To understand a child,
it's best not to have preconceptions.
That
only blinds you to their deeper thoughts
in their unconscious mind.
But that's precisely
where their
truest emotions lie.
Got it. Don't predict.
Think from their perspective.
Right.
To understand a child's inner world,
as I suggested,
your first lesson is
to learn to squat down to speak.
Talk to them eye to eye.
It's the first step.
Understood.
I may remind you,
given your current situation,
you're not suitable
to communicate with the child.
Well,
then
I will play the role
of a warmhearted brother.
Kid,
let me tell you
a story about a little white bunny
and a big bad wolf.
One day, there's
a meeting in the forest.
All the little animals came.
Little rabbit, little turtle,
little tiger, big wolf,
and the little bear.
Just then,
the starting gun went off with a bang.
The little rabbit
dashed out like a flash,
leaving the little turtle far behind.
Then, the big wolf appeared.
Bai.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
What little rabbit?
Little rabbit?
I said little spots.
Look at the mirror.
There's one here, and here, and here.
So many!
They'll ruin customer experience.
I'm just cleaning.
I'll clean it later.
Can you help me
put this on that counter?
I can't reach.
You shouldn't
lift such heavy stuff anymore.
What if you hurt yourself?
Right?
For these things below,
the lighter ones
that are easy to lift,
I'll also help.
Okay. It's all your job.
You give birth too.
That's your job.
I'll help with the second kid.
I'll help.
Now, let's play a storytelling game
with our new friends.
Sound good?
Yes!
Awesome.
Let's get started then.
Let's start.
In the fairy tale kingdom,
there was a beautiful big forest.
Many cute little animals
lived there.
They liked to travel in groups.
Xiaohua,
which animal do you think you are?
I am this little rabbit.
You're the little rabbit, right?
Does the little rabbit have a friend?
Yes.
The little tiger and the little rabbit
are good friends, right?
Right.
So, besides the little tiger
and the little rabbit,
who else went to play out
with them?
Was the little rabbit a bit scared?
Why?
Because the big wolf
and the little fox were both bad.
The little fox scared the little rabbit
and the little tiger.
The big wolf's bad too.
He threw the little rabbit
and the little tiger
into the water.
But don't worry.
They had
life jackets.
Don't worry.
No.
The big wolf taught us
to sing and to unbutton.
How do you unbutton?
♪Little rabbit, be good♪
♪Open the door♪
Look at daddy.
♪Open it quickly♪
♪Let me in♪
Does the little rabbit know
why the big wolf threw her
and the little tiger
into the water?
Because daddy doesn't want us anymore.
Mom is here.
Mom.
Mom is always here.
I'm sorry.
(Protect the Nation for the People,
Secure Stability for the Country)
Xiaohua,
take a look.
Do you see the big wolf
that pushed you into the water?
Look, both of us are here.
Look back at him.
See?
We are all here with you.
So don't be afraid, Xiaohua.
Tell me,
is there the big wolf inside?
Xiaohua, don't be afraid.
Through this layer of glass,
the big wolf can't see you.
Only you can see him.
Dad is the big wolf.
Auntie, I know it's you.
Xiaohua,
don't be afraid.
Auntie will always protect you.
I'm not afraid, Auntie.
Xiaohu said
both of us are very brave.
Right. You and Xiaohu
are brave little heroes, right?
No. Xiaohu is not a hero.
He is a pirate.
Why is Xiaohu a pirate?
Because his eye was hurt by dad.
He said after he became a pirate,
he would protect me.
Does it hurt?
No.
Xiaohua, do I look like a pirate?
Yes. Be a pirate and protect us.
Good girl.
In the future, we will protect you.
I promise.
Okay?
Defendants Tu Huaiwei and Yang Xiaoying,
charged with attempted murder
and child abuse.
The court is now in session.
Bring Defendants Tu Huaiwei
and Yang Xiaoying to court.
(Yunhai Intermediate People's Court,
Prosecutor)
(Defendant)
Xiaohua, tell me,
is there the big wolf inside?
(Defendant)
Dad is the big wolf.
Does the little rabbit know
why the big wolf threw her
and the little tiger
into the water?
Because daddy doesn't want us anymore.
Your Honors, please allow me
to make an explanation
on victim Tu Xiaohua's testimony.
She didn't directly say
that her dad threw her into the water,
because Tu Xiaohua
is only six years old.
We can only use a storytelling method
to help her recall what happened.
When Tu Xiaohua said
"Dad is the big wolf",
the big wolf refers
to Tu Xiaohua's biological father,
Defendant Tu Huaiwei.
Judge,
Xiaohua is only six years old.
She...
She made all these up.
Or someone told her to.
My ex-wife hates me.
It must be her.
She taught the kid to say this!
Prosecutor, is there objective evidence?
We request
to present the next set of evidence.
We restored the scene
of the incident on the boat
by video simulation.
Please allow
the expert, Director Lu Wenzhao
of the Judicial Evaluation Center
from People's Procuratorate of Yunhai
to give an explanation.
The boat was 4.2 meters long,
(Investigation Report)
1.2 meters wide,
and 1.5 meters high.
The total weight
of the four people aboard
was 142.5 kilograms.
When they were on board,
the draft depth of the boat
was 32 centimeters.
Based on the wind speed, water speed,
the boat's own weight,
and the total weight of the four people,
we can calculate
that to throw the child overboard,
it would take
at least 5,200 Newtons of force.
Let me elaborate on this concept.
The force of a kick
of a professional male football player
is approximately 4,900 Newtons.
When the Defendant was interrogated,
he claimed that the ten-year-old girl
Yang Huihui sitting in the front row
rocked the boat
and caused the children to fall.
Do you think this is possible?
Collegial tribunal, please watch
the simulation video
of the boat rocking to its limit.
(3D modeling reconstruction of the incident
issued by the Judicial Evaluation Center)
Chief Judge,
the inner width of the boat
is 90 centimeters
and the defendant's hip width
is 45 centimeters.
The hip widths
of the two children in the back are
20 centimeters and 23 centimeters.
Even if the girl in the front
is a strong person
who rocked the boat to the extreme,
the two children in the back
would be wedged
and stuck inside the boat.
Therefore, for Tu Xiaohu to fall out,
the only reason is
an external force.
Director Lu, please explain
in simpler terms.
The children were thrown into the water.
Impossible.
They fell out of the boat on their own!
That animation is fake!
They fell by themselves, really!
Chief Judge,
I request to present
the next set of evidence.
(DNA Analysis Report)
We found human skin tissue
human skin tissue
under Tu Xiaohu's
right fingernails.
DNA analysis
confirms it belongs
to Defendant Tu Huaiwei.
That indicates
when Tu Xiaohu
was thrown into the water,
he scratched Tu Huaiwei.
I-I...
He did scratch me
because I was trying to save him.
The boat captain! They all saw it,
They can testify.
How did you save him?
I just grabbed him.
Show me.
Just like this.
Okay, don't move.
You grabbed his hand like that?
If so,
the injuries on you hand
wouldn't be like these.
(Defendant Tu Huaiwei's hand injuries)
The photo shows
the place where Tu Huaiwei got injured
is the upper part of the right fingers.
Right here.
This kind of injury
could only be caused in one way.
That is, at that time,
Tu Xiaohu's hand was
clinging tightly to the boat railing,
and you used your right hand
to pry open his fingers one by one,
which caused the injuries.
Is that right, Tu Huaiwei?
I... I was too panicked at the time.
I really can't remember clearly.
The situation was too urgent.
I really don't remember.
(Tu Xiaohu's Autopsy Report)
This is Tu Xiaohu's autopsy report.
As we can see,
three fingers of Tu Xiaohu's right hand
had varying degrees
of soft tissue contusions.
After identification,
they were caused
by external force and twisting.
So, Tu Xiaohu was
in an extremely fearful state,
he gripped the railing tightly,
and Tu Huaiwei
pried open his fingers one by one,
then threw him into the water.
The next set of evidence
relates to the joint crime
by the two defendants.
I don't know.
What does it have to do with me?
Stop using the word "solve"
to justify everything, okay?
I do not plead guilty.
Defendant, pay attention to court order.
Without Chief Judge's consent,
Defendant is not allowed to speak.
Prosecutor, please present the evidence.
(Chat Records)
This is the transfer records
between Tu Huaiwei
and Tu Huaiwei's ex-wife, Jie Yangyang,
the victim's mother.
The records show
that in addition to
a regular living expense
payment of 2,000 yuan,
Jie Yangyang also made
irregular transfers to Tu Huaiwei,
which cover what Tu Huaiwei claimed
as the children's
exorbitant living expenses,
entertainment and educational costs.
Yang Xiaoying.
Are you aware of this?
Impossible.
That woman never cared
about those two kids.
And Tu Huaiwei promised me
he'd never contact that woman again.
Defendant Yang Xiaoying.
Take a look at this chat record.
"Today I took them
to eat fried chicken and fries."
"After all, they're our kids."
"Don't worry."
Here's another message.
"If you send me 520,"
"I wouldn't mind."
What does 520 mean?
Think about it.
Aren't they too intimate?
Don't listen to his provocation.
They spliced it together like this.
I... I never said such things.
They spliced it to frame me!
Tu Huaiwei receiving money
from Jie Yangyang
has no bearing on
whether my client incited murder.
I request to present
the next set of evidence.
At that time,
Yang Huihui was steering the boat.
She constantly rocked the boat.
I tried to stop her
because the two kids were scared.
She ignored me.
She kept rocking it.
I reached out to stop her,
but it made
the boat shake more.
When I turned back,
the two kids had already fallen in.
You mean, Yang Huihui rocked the boat
to make the kids fall in on purpose?
This was Tu Huaiwei's first statement.
He deliberately suggested
that it was Yang Huihui's rocking
that caused the incident.
Thereby
he tried to mislead the investigation
onto Yang Huihui.
Defendant Yang Xiaoying.
Yang Huihui is just a child.
Bearing such a terrible accusation
would ruin her life.
This is malicious editing!
I didn't say that!
It's really malicious editing!
Chief Judge,
I request
witness Chen Bixian to testify.
Witness Chen Bixian.
What is your relationship
with Defendant Tu Huaiwei?
I am
Tu Huaiwei's mother.
He...
Didn't you tell me
your parents were died?
Defendant, pay attention to court order.
Chen Bixian.
Please tell us what you know
related to this case.
Yang Xiaoying
and her daughter have terrible tempers.
Xiaohua and Xiaohu often got beaten,
very severely.
Let me play.
Give it to me.
Let go! Give it!
- No.
- Give it to me!
- No!
Give me!
No!
- No.
- Give it to me!
No!
Mom, they're bullying me again!
Give it to me!
Huihui, move.
Stop it!
Give it or not?
Give it or not!
What did I tell you?
Why are you so meddlesome?
Why annoyed her?
Why so meddlesome?
Are you being nice?
Dare run?
Stop!
Pretending here?
Xiaohu
even got
his bone broken.
Who did that?
Should I tell the truth?
Yes.
It was
Tu Huaiwei.
Mom, don't help them.
Witness Chen Bixian.
When you saw the children being abused,
why didn't you call the police?
I... I thought,
my son isn't a bad person.
I talked to him in private
not to treat the kids that way.
He told me
he was just acting out of anger.
He promised that Xiaohua and Xiaohu
would live a good life.
What did he mean by "a good life"?
Housing compensation.
My house is being demolished.
That's my house!
You're coveting my house?
Shameless!
Your whole family is nothing
but a bunch of thieves.
You deserve
to be wiped out!
Objection.
The witness's statements
are irrelevant to the case.
Shut up!
I paid for your expenses too!
Tu Huaiwei.
Now I finally understand
why you tried to frame Huihui.
You just wanted both of us
to get into trouble,
so that you could take over my house!
Tu Huaiwei!
What did you say the night before?
What did you say to me?
Chief Judge,
my client is emotionally unstable.
I am perfectly stable!
Tu Huaiwei.
You said I was your family,
your only family,
the closest person to you.
Is this how
you treat your closest family?
Objection.
He said...
He said
there were no cameras out there.
The kids would die
without anyone knowing.
Let's go down together.
Defendant Tu Huaiwei.
Do you admit
to conspiring
with Defendant Yang Xiaoying?
I do not.
I've been framed.
Son,
we cannot
live like parasites anymore.
We need to live like human beings.
It's all my fault
for not educating you well.
It is all my fault.
Judge,
can I take the blame for him?
I'll take it, okay?
Judge.
Can you stop pretending?
What are you doing?
You are pushing me to my death!
What good does it do you if I die?
Even a tiger doesn't eat its cubs.
I can't believe that's from your mouth.
Tu Huaiwei.
You
took Xiaohua
and Xiaohu
for a boat ride.
Do you know how happy they were?
A tiger doesn't abandon its cubs?
Then how could you hurt Xiaohu?
Thinking of this makes me hate you.
How could you be so cruel?
(Out of the maze)
Why are you looking for us?
I plead guilty.
Yang Xiaoying,
you are an instigator
of intentional homicide.
Your actions are as vicious
as Tu Huaiwei's.
Are you clear?
Even you plead guilty now,
it won't affect your sentencing.
Will having a letter of forgiveness
save me from death?
What?
A letter of forgiveness.
I'll pay the money.
I'm willing to pay.
800,000.
I have a house. I can pay.
Is it okay?
Xiaohua will need a lot of money
on medical treatment.
They have no money.
I'm willing to pay for that.
I have a house, I can do it.
Even a million.
Only if it can save me.
You regret it now?
What were you doing back then?
I also have a daughter.
You realize you have a daughter now.
(To Sister Huihui)
As a Prosecutor,
I know
I should be calm and rational.
But at this moment,
I am furious.
A child aged five or six
should be running around outside,
laughing loud,
and be loved and cherished.
But at such a young age,
Xiaohu has left this world forever.
His sister
will carry the trauma of her injuries,
and the shadow
of her own biological father
wanted to kill her,
for the rest of her life.
I don't know how this girl
will face
her future life.
Even a fierce tiger won't eat its cubs.
But he used such cruel means
to kill his own kid.
This is a complete loss of humanity,
utterly heartless.
Tu Huaiwei and Yang Xiaoying
regarded Tu Huaiwei's
biological children
as obstacles to their marriage.
They conspired together
to murder the children
by faking an accidental drowning,
resulting in one child's death
and the other's severe injury.
Their actions severely violated the law,
disregarded human morals,
and trampled on societal conscience.
Their motive was despicable,
their conduct particularly vile,
their methods heinous,
the consequences extremely serious,
and the social impact extremely adverse.
They should be severely punished
according to the law.
Defendants Tu Huaiwei and Yang Xiaoying
violated Articles 232 and 260
of the Criminal Law
of the People's Republic of China,
constituting intentional homicide
and abuse.
According to Article 29 the Criminal Law
of the People's Republic of China,
multiple crimes applies.
We suggest to sentence
Tu Huaiwei and Yang Xiaoying
to death penalty.
The court pronounces the judgment.
(Supervised by
the Supreme People's Court)
All rise.
According to Articles 232,
Article 260 and Article 29
of the Criminal Law
of the People's Republic of China,
the judgment is as follows.
One.
Defendant Tu Huaiwei,
for the crime of intentional homicide,
is sentenced to death penalty,
and for the crime of child abuse,
sentenced to two years in prison.
Combined punishment,
Tu Huaiwei is sentenced to death.
Two.
Defendant Yang Xiaoying,
for the crime of intentional homicide,
is sentenced to death penalty.
Defendant Yang Xiaoying,
for the crime of abuse,
is sentenced to two years in prison.
Combined punishment,
Yang Xiaoying is sentenced
to death penalty.
Is it necessary to come here?
We're all quite busy.
You're not the sentimental type.
It's been years.
Still can't get past this?
Come on.
I can.
They've renovated this place.
Look, the decoration.
There's even
a legal education room here.
(Legal Education Room)
Look.
Now there are desks and chairs.
When we first met,
you were barely
taller than this podium, right?
Right.
At that time,
I am a headstrong prosecutor.
I wanted to do everything
and convince everyone.
But when it comes to actual practice,
it's not that simple.
Did I do something wrong?
If I did,
you can criticize me.
Feel free.
Don't be that nervous.
No.
It's not like that.
I just
want to say thank you.
Because it was you
that made me feel
my persistence was meaningful.
Look at the pamphlet.
Full of words.
I remember those I read
when I was a kid,
are all picture books, barely any text.
The literacy rate really has gone up.
Everything is changing for the better.
Your hometown as well.
Back then, people were used
to those backward things.
When you told them it was wrong,
they simply wouldn't listen.
That's why
we must send Lin Zhengfeng in prison.
Only then would people understand
that domestic violence is illegal.
I was lucky to have met you
when I was a kid.
You don't blame me for recommending you
to juvenile prosecution?
I can do well anywhere.
Juvenile prosecution
has a beginning but no end.
Understood.
When you were a kid,
you planted a seed in me.
Now, we'll watch the tree
grow together.
You've made me a tree
gets too much attention.
I'm just worried that one strong wind
might knock it all down.
Who taught you to talk like that?
I'm talking seriously to you.
It used to be so hard
to make progress on one case.
Now, you've got support
from so many departments.
Don't waste the opportunity.
The case of Xiaohua and Xiaohu
is not over.
I know what to do.
Don't worry.
Prosecutor Zheng.
You're back!
We're her to see you.
Here, I brought you some dried fish.
This is mine.
Please accept it.
You have helped us so much.
We are so grateful to you.
- Please, take it.
- Please.
- Take it.
(Mandatory Reporting System)
Today I want to share with you
about the Mandatory Reporting System
for child abuse cases.
This system requires
that state agencies, organizations
and officials authorized
to exercise public power by law,
and personnel working in sectors
that frequently interact with minors,
If they found
or even suspect,
that a minor has been harmed
or is at risk of unlawful harm,
they must immediately
report to the police
or authorities.
Let me
tell you
about
a case I handled recently.
There are two children
who are twins,
both six years old.
One named Xiaohua and the other Xiaohu.
(The father of the two children)
(remarried.)
(From that point on,)
(the twins never had a good day.)
(Living under another's roof,)
(being beaten and scolded,)
(and getting many injuries.)
(During the whole year,)
(the happiest day for them)
(was when)
(their dad said he'd take them boating.)
(They were so excited.)
(But they never expected)
that on that day,
their dad
tried to kill them.
You might ask,
when such things happened
and the children suffered,
didn't anyone see it?
Didn't anyone try to stop it?
Someone saw that.
The neighbor saw it.
The teacher knew it.
The doctor knew it.
Even pedestrians on the road knew it.
But among so many people,
not a single person stood up to help.
Not even one.
Maybe they were
afraid of retaliation
from the parents.
Or they believed
good people don't get rewarded.
Is there any chance
that some of those people are kind?
I think there is.
But,
we indeed never encouraged them
to stand up.
We never told them
that they could
and should step in
and help,
even if it was a misunderstanding.
Actually, I've been through
the same things these kids have.
I know very well
the color of those bruises
and the pain it is on the body.
When I was very young,
I truly wished someone could stand up,
speak for me
and help me.
So in this case,
when I meet Xiaohua,
I promised her
that I'd protect her.
I want to keep that promise.
So,
today,
I sincerely ask you all
to join me in helping children
like Xiaohua and Xiaohu,
and help them live their lives in peace.
(Dear Xiaohu,
I will always remember you.)
♪My dear, it's been long
since we last met♪
♪Have you grown up a bit♪
♪The worn-out past
and the fishing bay you couldn't leave♪
♪Were frozen in the vast wild grass♪
♪Back then at home,
Mom was always covering her face♪
♪Outside the window,
the smell of alcohol lingered♪
♪You wanted to forget all the bruises♪
♪And grow wings and fly far away♪
♪Longing was surrounded by loneliness,
filled with flowing unease♪
♪Every step of every night
was on nightmares♪
♪You will cross the mountain
and see a vast, clear sky♪
♪And birds flying over the sea♪
♪You will face the wind,
sing a song bravely♪
♪And see all the scenery♪
♪You will cross the mountain
and see a vast, clear sky♪
♪And birds flying over the sea♪
♪You will face the wind,
sing a song bravely♪
♪And see all the scenery♪
♪You will cross the mountain
and see a vast plain♪
♪And daylight piercing
through the clouds♪
♪You will clench your fists, sweating♪
♪And climb over
countless perils barefoot♪
♪Outside the window, a child is humming
over the rippling water♪
♪And a ship has sailed away♪