Great Master Buddha, they're here.
Sit.
Normally,
I don't welcome the Zhang family,
but since you're here,
I can't make you leave now.
Should we catch up first
or get down to business?
Zhang Hailou,
tell him why we came here.
Great Master Buddha, here's the thing.
We're all surnamed Zhang, right?
We are distant relatives after all.
When we were in Xiacheng,
we encountered something tricky.
I suppose you knew.
Now,
we're short-handed.
We... well... well...
Since we are relatives,
c-can you lend us several divisions?
If he's still
joking around,
take them both away.
Yes.
What's your relationship with Mo Yungao?
I know you are investigating him.
You even sent someone
to the Archives.
A few days ago,
I intercepted a telegram
from Mo Yungao.
I found that he was
secretly looking for the Archives.
The Zhang family
has always been secretive.
But Mo Yungao
found out about the Archives.
That means
something went wrong in the Archives.
So I sent the adjutant to investigate,
lest the Archives' secrets get out.
So it's a misunderstanding.
In that case,
we can tell you what we know.
And you tell us what you know in return.
We have the same goal.
Don't waste time.
Let's get down to business.
I-I'll make it short.
So,
the Southern Archives
was taken down by Mo Yungao.
Besides,
you think
he's going to spread
toxic weeds across the land.
If you can provide
the exact sites where Mo Yungao
plans to deploy the toxic weeds elsewhere
and secure evidence,
I can report the matter to my superiors
and forcefully take over his command,
so that his troops will be held in place.
You can also deal with him
as you wish.
But...
if you can't,
I'm afraid the higher-ups
don't want to cause more trouble.
You want me
to mobilize the Changxiang defenses
to attack Beilian.
That's utterly impossible.
If you're willing to cooperate,
we can give you the sites.
But you must give us
Mo Yungao's information.
Mo Yungao is eccentric
and very cautious.
He doesn't have a regular residence.
He has been living on the train,
and this train has been running.
So no one knows
where exactly he is.
The train he is riding on
has been specially modified.
Even if you find the train,
I'm afraid you won't be able to board it.
How has it been modified?
I sent many experts
to investigate
the whereabouts of the train.
Mo Yungao's armored special train
[Special Armored Train Blueprint]
has 12 carriages in all.
The second and the last ones
are gun carriages.
Two cannons are mounted on the roof.
The rotating turrets provide
all-around 360° fire,
with an effective range
of 8,000 to 10,000 meters.
Next come 2 machine-gun carriages.
Twelve heavy machine guns
are fitted along both sides,
firing through side-wall firing ports.
Their effective range
is 800 to 1,000 meters.
As for the 7 carriages in the middle,
no one knows exactly
which one Mo Yungao stays in.
Soldiers inside the carriages
keep watch around the clock
via side observation windows
and sight devices on the turrets.
[Special Armored Train Blueprint]
Any unauthorized approaching target
will come under intense combined fire
from cannons and heavy machine guns.
No one
can survive that fire.
There must be a way to get on it.
The train,
due to special modifications,
is very fast.
And...
and it will never halt
before reaching the destination,
and no one else
will be allowed to board it.
Don't even think about it.
It's impossible for you
to force your way in.
With your intelligence,
you surely can't get on it.
You may think all you want,
but you won't live to get on board.
Anyone who even attempts to board it
will be riddled with heavy fire.
We are different.
I must have a way.
You said no one could find him,
but you never said you couldn't.
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 20]
Mo Yungao
is on his way to Nanling from Guangchuan.
He will pass Changxiang Station soon
and pass Chuhan Station at 3 a.m,
then he'll continue heading for Nanling.
At 1:30 p.m,
the train will arrive at Nanling Station.
All 4 stops along Mo Yungao's route
align with the locations
deduced by Shrimpie.
A few years ago, I met Mo Yungao
on a few separate occasions.
He once told me a story.
About 20 years ago,
there was an operation
to suppress bandits in Nanqiang.
When Mo Yungao was a platoon leader,
he led a suicide squad
and encountered an ambush by bandits.
Everyone else died.
He was the only one who survived.
H-Hero.
If you don't leave quickly,
you will die.
You will die.
I won't die.
Where are you going?
Into the mountains.
Something is coming out.
Help me up.
Hero.
Hero!
Is there anyone alive?
How many days have I slept?
How did the body rot so badly?
Who is it?
Hero?
Did you kill these bandits?
Wait,
s-since you are so capable,
why didn't you save me then?
Shut up.
It killed them.
That thing is coming out soon.
Immortal.
It's not safe here.
Go back first.
According to him,
the mysterious man
is surnamed Zhang.
From then on,
he thought
he met a man of extraordinary gifts.
A man of extraordinary gifts?
Zhang Hailou,
wait for me outside.
My speculation
lines up pretty closely with yours.
His men tried to enter the Archives
to find a file.
It seems to be File 003.
He's looking for that person.
Miss Zhang.
I don't know much.
And I've told you everything.
Separated by mountains and seas,
this is our appointed place.
I will wait for your news.
We will pinpoint all exact sites
where Mo Yungao
plans to deploy Twilight Grass this time.
You must help us then.
[Zhang's Residence]
The Great Master Buddha has prepared food
and accommodation for you.
This is the address.
I have something to do.
I won't see you off.
[Zhang's Residence]
Mentor,
what secret stuff did you chat about
with this snobbish relative
that I'm not allowed to hear?
Mo Yungao knows about the Zhang family.
Everything he's done
is most likely targeted
at the Zhang family.
But this deployment of Twilight Grass
will also cause
massive civilian casualties.
We must stop it as soon as possible.
What about Shrimpie?
Zhang Qishan intends
to wipe out one of Mo Yungao's strongholds
along the Xiao River area.
Currently, Zhang Haixia is the one
who knows Twilight Grass the best.
So, Zhang Qishan
needs Zhang Haixia's help.
I've ordered someone to take him there.
What?
[Regional Map of Nanling City]
The situation is getting better.
We are on the same boat with Zhang Qishan.
We must find Mo Yungao
as soon as possible.
Zhang Haixia has done a lot for this clue.
We can't let his efforts go in vain.
With Shrimpie's current situation,
how can we let him act alone?
He's with Zhang Qishan's troops.
If anything goes wrong,
they will step in.
To kill him?
If he could be killed so easily,
he wouldn't be Zhang Haixia.
What if he's not?
If that's the case,
it's his fate.
Don't try to find him.
You can't do whatever you want now.
Haven't you learned enough
from the lessons before?
Find Mo Yungao quickly.
He's on the train to Nanling.
What we need to do is to board it
and kidnap Mo Yungao directly.
Then interrogate him
about the exact deployment sites,
send a telegram to Zhang Qishan,
and arrest him, right?
Have you figured out
how to get on the train?
This is the regional map of Nanling.
Twenty li before reaching
Nanling Terminal Station,
[Regional Map of Nanling City]
the train passes through
a cave tunnel.
This cave is 500 meters long.
This is the only way
we can get on the train.
We just need to lie in wait
inside the cave in advance.
When the train passes by,
we jump onto the train.
But we only have 20 seconds.
To get on a speeding train
within 20 seconds.
I'm fine with it.
What about you?
I suggested it, so I'm fine with it.
What only matters
is whether Zhang Qishan
is worthy of our trust.
While Zhang Qishan helps us,
he can also completely seize control
of all Mo Yungao's defense zones
and station his troops in Beilian.
If we have caught
Mo Yungao by then,
as long as we know the deployment sites...
Zhang Qishan will take his Beilian,
and we
will take Commander Mo.
It sounds perfect.
But you are drinking here
and can't sleep.
Why?
I'm gonna test you.
Outbreaks from Twilight Grass
[Regional Map of Nanling City]
hit countless villages
at the same time in Nanyang.
That means
outbreaks may hit
these 4 cities at the same time.
The key point
is the time when Mo Yungao arrives
at Nanling Terminal Station.
The signal must be sent
the moment he arrives
at the terminal station.
Then the Twilight Grass Poison
will erupt in 4 cities all at once.
Once the poison breaks out,
the cities will be in chaos.
The water and land resources
in these cities
will suffer irreversible consequences.
What else?
The Panhua Reef Case,
the Nanyang Twilight Grass Poisoning Case,
the trap on the Nan'an,
and the slaughter in the Archives.
These things
seem to have no connection.
But I guess
they're all driven
by the same underlying objective.
Look here.
If I'm not mistaken,
they hung up the bodies
to collect corpse fluids.
N P.
And the Nanyang Evil God Case
over 10 years ago.
He is also the mastermind behind this.
Twenty years.
What could the Zhang family have
that can make him plan
for 20 years in a row?
You can think before you act now.
Good.
I taught you so well.
Did you teach me that?
Shrimpie did.
I'm asking you. What's your purpose?
Who is this?
He's here to pick us up.
I've sent my suspicions—
same as yours—
to Zhang Qishan via the guards.
We can solve the problem soon.
Hope everything goes well with Shrimpie.
[Outskirts of Mo Yungao's Base,
Xiao River]
Mr. Zhang,
a few days ago,
we found that
Mo faction warlords maintain
a hidden base deep in the Xiao River area.
The Great Master Buddha suspects
this may be linked to Twilight Grass
you've spoken of.
But we don't know much about it.
That's why we need your judgment.
Get off!
Stand guard!
Mr. Zhang.
That is human skin.
The black fuzz on top
is residue left from burnt roots
of Twilight Grass.
Twilight Grass mixed with corpses
emits a distinct odor,
which will linger for a very long time.
I smelled it before.
Unforgettable for a lifetime.
This is Mo Yungao's doing.
To be precise,
Mo Yungao's men did it.
Before we set out,
we investigated Mo Yungao's
situation in Beilian.
In the information,
a military officer
named Li Pinrui is mentioned.
He came back from Denasien.
Now, he
specializes in cultivating Twilight Grass.
He's kind of Mo Yungao's henchman.
This man has an eccentric disposition.
He personally carried out
all previous Twilight Grass poisonings
across multiple regions of Nanyang.
Over thousands of people died in Nanyang.
This is the man
we are to deal with.
Mr. Zhang,
do you think we can win?
It doesn't matter.
When dealing with villains,
we should have a way to deal with them.
Let's hurry on our way then.
The enemy camp is right ahead.
Guys, get in!
Mr. Zhang.
Coming.
We've conducted a preliminary survey,
and this place is indeed
where the Mo faction
cultivates Twilight Grass.
It's under Li Pinrui's jurisdiction.
The whole base is surrounded by mountains.
[Outskirts of Mo Yungao's Base,
Xiao River]
[Twilight Grass Cultivation Area]
Judging from the scale of the base
and the number of patrols,
there's likely an entire battalion
stationed here.
On the other side of the mountains,
there's a huge cave.
The cave
is where they cultivate Twilight Grass.
Why didn't the Great Master Buddha
send more people here?
The Great Master Buddha and the Mo faction
[Main Gate] [Armory] [Sentry Tower]
have different responsibilities
and jurisdictions.
His reach can't extend this far.
If he can't handle it well,
we'll be in big trouble.
Our Great Master Buddha
can only do so much at best.
So,
our Great Master Buddha needs you.
We need to outmaneuver them,
wipe out all Mo faction warlords,
and destroy all Twilight Grass completely.
[Main Gate] [Armory] [Sentry Tower]
How are the troops deployed inside?
According to my observation,
the bulk of their troops
are concentrated in the front base.
They have adequate firepower.
They train troops
and conduct experiments there.
Since the cultivation area
lies within the cave
and Twilight Grass is extremely hazardous,
only a small detachment is stationed here.
They only escort
local villagers here periodically
to harvest Twilight Grass.
The Great Master Buddha's mission
is to exterminate the Mo faction warlords,
save the people,
and destroy all Twilight Grass.
Besides,
we must finish the operation
by the time Mo Yungao's train
arrives at Nanling Station
and prevent any communication
between the two parties.
Your Great Master Buddha
really thinks highly of me.
You just said
they'll all be exterminated,
right?
Mr. Zhang,
what's our plan?
This is where they plant Twilight Grass.
Should we get ready?
No need.
Our operation must align with
the Great Master Buddha's timeline.
They kidnapped villagers
to harvest Twilight Grass for them,
and once the villagers die,
their bodies get used as fertilizer.
Truly making full use of everything.
Burn this place down!
-Yes!
Mr. Zhang,
what instructions do you have?
Gather all Twilight Grass
for me.
Pack it into these crates.
Aren't we going to destroy it?
I have my own uses.
The grass is poisonous.
Our men just
come into direct contact with it.
Are you certain this is safe?
Yes.
I was infected
by the Twilight Grass Poison before,
yet I'm unharmed.
Go collect.
Come on,
start collecting.
I won't let you die in vain.