=The Missing Snowflakes=
=Episode 15=
See for yourself,
smiling like a blossom.
I asked you here to discuss something.
What is it?
What is this?
It's too big to swallow.
It's precious.
The name of it
is the Faked-death Drug.
I secretly made it in Qingshui County.
The Faked-death Drug?
What do you need it for?
I wanted to leave without notice.
So that's all I have left.
I see.
You...
you're still into the Crown Prince.
You want to fake your death
and marry him instead.
Then you need a new identity.
Let me think.
You can be our distant relative,
our cousin.
Then we can be the Crown Prince's
brother-in-law.
A royal brother-in-law.
Stop.
That's enough.
I wanted to leave,
to be free,
and to fly away.
Are you not free in this Mansion?
Does His Highness treat you unwell?
No, he doesn't.
He treats me nicely.
But it has been my dream
to be a rich physician.
I can travel everywhere.
I can see how the flowers blossom,
and how the snow thaw.
You can see how the flowers blossom,
and how the snow thaw in here.
That's a metaphor.
Anyway,
I don't know what to do.
Do I leave?
Or do I stay?
Bro,
we can't let her leave like that.
His Highness...
We must count on him.
You are right.
This time,
we need to be on his side.
Soft-boiled eggs of love.
Steamed bun of love.
Radish of love.
Your Highness.
please enjoy.
These two fools
took my job.
Thanks to Shangshang, who made the cure,
and saved thousands of lives.
Tell me,
what reward do you want?
- I'd like...
- Shangshang and I
went to Qingshui County
for mending our mistake.
We need no reward.
Besides,
Shangshang has mercy.
The well-being of people
is what Princess Peace hopes.
(I never said that.)
Princess Peace.
That's good.
What a Princess Peace!
I would
reward you greatly.
- Much obliged, Father.
(Benevolent Physician)
He's really stingy.
What a coincidence.
Shangshang, I...
Your Royal Highness,
I know we had history before.
But,
I am Princess Peace now.
Li treats me well.
I like him as well.
You will find a better girl
in the future.
I'll take my leave.
Li is waiting for me.
I doubt that
the fake drugs in the army
have connections with Qingshui County.
Please take a look, Father.
What is this?
It is the totem on the neck
of the one who delivered the drug.
Moreover,
the magistrate of Qingshui County,
Xu Qingfeng,
had this totem on his neck.
This arrow
was the weapon used
to attack me in Qingshui County.
It had poison on it.
It aimed to kill me
at once.
How dare they do that!
Assassinating the Prince
in the public.
Such villains.
Keep investigating.
Yes, Father.
Your Highness.
(Zhao)
They lose their patience.
Send the token
to the imperial palace.
Yes, sir.
(Benevolent Physician)
Look!
It was given by His Majesty.
It's the first one
in the capital city.
We should visit here from now on.
The physician is even a lady.
You're right.
Is everything alright? Your Highness?
Do you often find a funny smell on you?
Is it hard to clean it?
I give you some Golden Lotus Pill.
Take it for two weeks.
And,
your underwear
should be dried by sunlight.
Got it?
(Benevolent Physician)
Next.
Come here.
Shut up. Come.
What's this all about?
Forget it.
Pick them up.
What are you looking at?
Look at me.
What are you doing?
Are these for you?
They're for Her Highness.
You two fools, come on.
You're in my way.
Honey,
look!
I prepared so many things for you,
and you just want gold?
You prepared it?
What do you think?
What day is it?
It's so special.
You don't know what day it is?
No, I don't.