=The Missing Snowflakes=
=Episode 12=
Your Highness,
wait for me.
I thought we wouldn't come.
Wait a second, please!
Your Highness,
have some water.
Your Highness?
Thank you.
Your Highness,
why are you so interested
in the golden lotus banana
that you'll look for it in person?
(That's my little secret.)
I'm running a clinic
in the capital city.
When women
have gynecological problems,
they're unwilling to see a physician.
But the herb can cure them easily.
You're my role model.
A royal member looks for
medical herbs for common people.
How great...
My women patients are all loaded.
If I can cure them,
I'll make a big fortune.
Making money in this way
is a good thing.
You're making a profit
in a noble way.
We should go now.
It's getting late.
Wild beasts
will walk around when it's dark.
OK.
Oops!
Your Highness,
they're over there.
I saw them.
I'm dizzy.
It's OK.
She may be tired.
What's wrong?
I got a head rush
from standing up too fast.
Your Highness.
What happened?
Your Highness!
Are you OK?
She's fine...
Your Highness!
Hurry up!
Bummer.
Your Highness,
I have to do it.
Jerk!
What are you doing?
You're a jerk!
How could you
offend Her Highness?
Your Highness,
don't get me wrong.
Her Highness is intoxicated.
What?
I was trying to find the wound.
Get out.
Now!
Move.
Look what you did!
I don't see any wounds
in her limbs.
It should be in the body.
Your Highness,
it was highly toxic.
You need to find the wound now.
After the toxic goes to her heart,
she can't be cured.
(Huanhuan,)
(I don't mean to offend you.)
Your Highness,
did you find it?
I think I did.
What does it look like?
May I see it?
No!
Don't come in!
Your Highness,
your jealousy may harm her!
She might die!
You can't come in!
Four bleeding spots.
Seemed...
A snake bit her.
I think you're right.
Your Highness,
suck out the toxin, please.
What?
Wait...
It's...
I can't...
I can't!
Allow me, please.
No way!
I can do it.
Save your crap!
Your Highness,
hurry up, please.
I'll go get medical herbs.
You'll have to
clean the wound
in a little while.
Your Highness.
I'll go with him.
You really should thank me for this.
You woke up!
Huanhuan, are you OK?
You undressed me?
How dare you?
You were injured!
Nonsense!
Stop fooling me!
Save your crap!
You're a liar!
How could you do this to me?
What a jerk...!
A snake bit you, understood?
A snake!
I...
Why are you here?
Did you stalk me?
I...
I'm picking mushrooms!
Seriously?
Put your clothes on.
By the way,
you're a physician, right?
How could a snake hurt you?
I'm a human, OK?
I'm not omnipotent.
I could be intoxicated.
And I could get sick and die.
I agree with you.
Physicians can't treat themselves.
It happens all the time.
Your Highness,
remember to change dressings.
Save it, OK?
Enjoy it, please.
The couple needs some privacy.
Let's go.
I want to watch the stars with you.
No.
I don't want to.
Yes.
You do.
Lin Huanhuan,
I want to be with you.
What did you call me?
Lin Huanhuan?
Lin Huanhuan.
Anything wrong?
It's been a long time
since someone called my name
last time.
I thought
I had become Lin Shangshang.
You...
You're Huanhuan.
Lin Shangshang
was highly cultured
and steeped in propriety.
She was edified by
the traditional culture.
But you...
Get lost!
Don't!
Be careful!
-Don't!
-Get lost!
Hi, there.
I need some air.
I feel sleepy.
I feel cold.
The moon is beautiful.
On my back.
What are you doing?
I'll carry you.
No, thanks.
Let's go.
We'll go home.
I want to look for
the golden lotus banana!
You don't need to.
His Highness will buy you a lot.
Your Highness,
the way home is here!
Where are you going?
To look for the herb.
Seriously?
The golden lotus banana
can help many women.
Your wound has recovered?
My wound?
Yes.
It's not important.
Believe me.
I'll be with you for my lifetime.
Stop!
The golden lotus banana!
We have found it!