-How is my father's condition?
-If he keeps pushing himself, at this rate he will suffer a myocardial infarction.
I'll do it. I'm going to protect his company.
If Irie-kun is feeling uneasy and needs help...
If there is something that I can do, I would do anything.
At this rate, Pandai may have to undergo a merger.
We need an enormous amount of financial support immediately.
This is Hokueisha's Chairman Oizumi
and his secretary, Mr. Yokoyama.
On behalf of my father
I would like to discuss the investment plan with you.
My father is actually not doing well.
If I take over the company,
all of the problems will be solved.
I'm delighted that you paid us
a visit at our company, Chairman.
-Thank you very much for coming.
-Well, well...
I had something to do in this area today.
Are by alone today?
I came here to talk to you
about a personal matter, Naoki-kun.
Talk to me?
Naoki-kun, would you like to have
an arranged marriage meeting?
I know it's not the best time
since Mr. Irie is in the hospital...
I have a granddaughter.
She is your age and goes to
Seishin Women's College.
It's a really prestigious school.
What do you think, Naoki-kun?
Would you at least like to meet her?
You are young.
I'm sure you need time
to think about it.
After discussing it with your parents
please give me your answer in the next few days.
We will talk about the
investment plan afterward.
I'm sorry for visiting you
without notice.
Please don't apologize.
Well then, Naoki-kun.
Please consider this carefully.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Naoki-san.
This meeting is...
going to be a great advantage
for the company, isn't it?
What is this all about, Naoki?
Wait, Honey. Calm down.
However, out of the blue you're having
an arranged marriage meeting with...
The Chairman's granddaughter?
-What is going on?
Nothing.
Don't tell me that...
you are doing this for the financial support?
We didn't tell them that we were coming.
Don't you think Daddy will be surprised?
What should we do?
It might be bad for his heart if we surprise him.
What are you talking about?
If he sees Yuki-kun's face,
he will get better right away!
Don't underestimate us!
I don't want to protect my company
by sacrificing your life.
He's right. Marriage? I won't allow this.
"Marriage?"
Naoki is?
I'm proud of myself for building Pandai
this big in just one generation.
So don't take us the wrong way.
You have to marry
someone that you really love.
I like her.
I saw her in a picture.
She was my type.
Naoki!!
-Are you serious?
-Yuki!
Are you really getting married?
But...
Kotoko-chan. You are here too, Mr. Aihara.
Irie-kun.
Is it true that you're going to
have an arranged marriage meeting?
Yes.
This coming Sunday.
Since my father is not doing well,
we are going to have a casual meeting.
I need you to come with me, Mom.
Please.
Oh no...
Irie-kun is going to have an
arranged marriage meeting...
I can't believe this.
What am I...
supposed to do?
♫  Have you noticed?
I keep updating myself ♫
♫ Hopefully, I'll reach you someday ♫
♫ Where are your true feelings? ♫
♫ To think that you can neither avoid nor love me,
Isn't that boring? ♫
♫ I thought about this many times ♫
♫ Please share it with me, even only half is fine ♫
♫ Rather than counting the efforts that surely won't be rewarded ♫
♫ if you make up tomorrow's strategy,
Now go for it ♫
♫ Make an update,
I can't understand these days full of mischief ♫
♫ But I still like them a lot ♫
♫ Notice me, I always keep updating myself ♫
♫ Hopefully, I'll reach you someday ♫
♫  Have you noticed?
I keep updating myself ♫
♫ I can't stop worrying about little things,
but I really want to catch up with you ♫
♫ I want to go on a date with you soon,
and hope that we might be the best couple someday ♫
♫ I can't understand all of this mischief,
but I still like it a lot ♫
♫ Notice me, I always keep updating myself ♫
♫ Hopefully, I'll reach you someday ♫
[Mischievous Kiss]
[Love in Tokyo]
That punk Irie is going to have
an arranged marriage meeting?
[Episode 14: A Fork in the Path of Love]
The other person is the granddaughter
of their business partner.
That's like a marriage of convenience!
Does that still happen nowadays?
I don't know.
Irie-kun said he liked the girl.
I'm sorry, but I should go.
Oh, do you think Kotoko is okay?
There is no way that she is okay.
Don't you know how many years
she had a crush on Irie?
You are right.
But I didn't think that damn Irie would have
an arranged marriage meeting.
That punk Irie, I can't forgive him.
Really.
How much does he have to toy with Kotoko until he is satisfied?
Well, actually Kotoko is the one
who is toying with her own feelings.
But what about Kotoko's feelings?
She has been working so hard for him.
But he's going to have an arranged
marriage meeting with another girl?
Kin-chan, you almost sound like...
you want Kotoko and Irie to be a couple.
That's not what I'm saying!
I just want to see Kotoko smiling.
If I take over the company,
all of the problems will be solved.
But your dream is to become a doctor, isn't it?
It's hasn't been long since I had that dream.
So you're going to give it up?
Irie-kun . . .
At that moment, I felt like
our hearts were connected, but . . .
Ah, I broke it.
Ouch.
Are you okay, Kotoko-chan?
Oh no, you're bleeding!
It looks painful.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
I'm sorry. I was spacing out.
It's because of Naoki's
arranged marriage meeting, isn't it?
I can't believe him.
But I still think you should be
Naoki's wife, Kotoko-chan.
Nevertheless, it's something that
Irie-kun has already decided on.
About that...
No matter how I look at it, I just can't
believe he was telling us the truth.
About the company, too.
I admit that I was hoping
Naoki would take over Pandai.
But I've been watching him
working at the company...
I feel like something is wrong.
I said to myself, "This is not what
Naoki really wants to do."
I think Naoki feels responsible for
the fact that my husband collapsed.
That's why he is sacrificing himself
and trying to save the company.
But do you think he would
go as far as getting married?
That's changing his life.
When he starts thinking about something,
he gets obsessed with the idea.
That's why...
I have a great idea.
A great idea?
I heard that Irie-kun is going to have
an arranged marriage meeting.
The girl is a granddaughter of the chairman
of a company named Hokueisha.
What? Chairman Oizumi's?
Do you know him?
Of course I do.
Don't you read the newspaper?
Chairman Oizumi is one of the big shots
of the financial world.
He has influence on many politicians.
He is the boss of the Japanese business world.
I didn't know it was the granddaughter
of such an important person.
Now that you mention it. I heard she has attended
Seishin Women's School since kindergarten.
I see.
She is a real princess, huh?
Irie-kun said he liked her right away
when he saw a picture of her.
She must be beautiful.
I don't like it.
Right?
Why does the perfect girl appear
out of nowhere to take Irie-kun?
I can't let her take him.
Well, Mrs. Irie might be able
to do something about this.
Hmm? Mrs. Irie?
What are you talking about?
Oh, me?
Oh, it's nothing! Nevermind!
What do you mean "nothing?"
Hurry up and tell me.
I'm sorry, It's top secret...
that she has a plan to ruin the meeting.
Ah!
I see...
"Ruin the meeting," huh?
You two never change.
What is it?
But...
Only this time, I will join you.
What?
[The Day of the Arranged Marriage Meeting]
This way, please.
Oh, Naoki-kun and Mrs. Irie.
I've been waiting for you.
We are sorry for making you wait.
Please sit down.
I'm sorry for doing this when
Mr. Irie is in the hospital.
As for our side, only my
granddaughter and I are here, too.
We shall have a formal meeting
with her parents...
when Mr. Irie gets better.
On another day.
Oh my, I wonder if that day will ever come.
Mother!
One, two. One, two.
Why do we have to wear this?
We have no choice. This is the only way
that we wouldn't look suspicious in the garden.
Look, over there.
Hmm
How does she look?
The granddaughter of Chairman Oizumi.
It looks like she is not there yet.
Wha is she doing?
Sahoko is getting ready right now.
She will be here soon.
I'm sorry for being late.
Oh Sahoko, we've been
waiting for you.
Oh my.
You are from...
Are you OK?
Do you remember me?
I never forget a beautiful lady.
Great, you two have met before.
It's simple then.
Sahoko, you should sit down.
Hey.
What are you doing?
You shouldn't space out.
Let me see.
Hmph, she might be pretty,
but she probably has no brains.
You are right! You are right!
Alright, let's get closer and
listen to their conversation!
Crawl and advance!
Let's go!
Are you serious?
I can't do this.
What is your hobby, Sahoko-san?
I'm not good at anything special.
I'm only good at cooking,
sewing and crafting.
very boring things.
Yes, indeed.
Boring.
Mrs. Irie, nice!
Shh, they can hear you.
It's not something that
I should say, but...
Sahoko is quiet and perfect as a lady.
She is like a modern version of
an old traditional Japanese woman.
Sounds very nice.
I like quiet women.
Wow, an "old traditional Japanese woman?"
So old.
No wonder you seem like
you are missing your youth.
Um... Naoki-san,
what do you like to do?
Well...
I like to read books.
And I play tennis a little bit.
"A little bit?"
I've heard that you won many competitions.
That's amazing.
I can teach you next time.
-What?
-Huh?
I'm glad to hear that.
But I'm very bad, so you might get fed up with me.
I'm sure he will be fed up.
Mother!
Well, my son, Naoki is very mean.
He looks down on people who don't
get it right after teaching them once.
Not only that, in an obvious way!
-Mrs. Irie, you are amazing.
-Yeah.
Actually, she is the one who is obvious.
You excel in academics and sports.
And you are so handsome.
I'm sure you are very popular among women.
Not so much.
Yes, he is very popular.
But, please do not worry.
He has never had any
relationships with women.
Really?
He must be straight-laced.
Yes, he is very straight-laced.
He's even rejected a love letter from
a girl who wrote one.
She gathered her courage together
and gave him the letter.
He turned her down in front of everyone.
He really is very straight-laced.
Was she talking about you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I didn't know he hated you so much.
But...
it's better than a man who would
put on a nice face to everyone.
I think a man is more attractive
when he is a little bit cold.
You are absolutely right.
And you don't have to worry about cheating.
But, that doesn't mean he has never had a girl around him.
Actually, there is one girl who is the same age as Naoki.
They lived together for three years.
Enough already.
What do you mean by "lived together"?
-It's called "sharing a house".
-It's the same.
Oizumi-san, there is a reason.
That's right.
We might end up having your precious
granddaughter marry into our family.
You should know our circumstances, too.
It is a fact that there is a girl who is
the same age as Naoki living in the house.
Although we may say he is straight-laced,
he is also young.
I can't guarantee you that nothing
has happened between them.
Sahoko-san, would you like to go the garden?
Oh, that's a good idea.
Just Sahoko-san and I!
Oh, I should have noticed earlier.
Please, enjoy each other's company.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
Ow, my back hurts.
I'm sorry, my mother said many rude things to you.
It's okay.
I can tell your mother likes her.
The woman who lives with you.
She is the daughter of my father's best friend.
Our families are friends.
That's why my mother said things like that.
But the person who likes her is not me.
It's my mother.
I hope your mother likes me, too.
Ah, but before that,
I hope you like me, Naoki-san.
Does that mean that you like me?
Since the moment we met in front of the elevator.
What a coincidence....
It's the same for me.
Oh my.
I'm pissed.
Look at their mood.
Hey, you.
What happened to Strategy 1?
Yes, roger!
Let's move on!
The secret weapon of
Strategy 1 is this sprinkler!
When they get close to it, we'll turn it on!
Then her kimono will get soaked.
She will have to go home.
Isn't it too easy?
A simple method works better.
Yes, let's go!
I've heard that the oldest bonsai tree here is over 500 years old.
-That old?
-Yes.
They are coming.
-Now!
-Yes!
Anyway, what a beautiful day.
I would love to play in the water.
-Huh?
I didn't think you would say that, Sahoko-san.
Hey, what are you doing?
Are you a klutz?
They already passed!
- Hey, let me do it.
-That's strange.
Hey, what is going on?
This switch doesn't work at all!
Hmm?
I think it's a sprinkler malfunction.
Let's keep walking.
Yes.
Oh gosh... It stopped.
Geez, why do I have to go through this?
Stupid!
Let's put ourselves together and try Strategy 2!
Let's go!
My eyes... It hurts.
All your pranks are something that elementary kids would do.
But aren't they disgusting?
They are.
Well,
when that Sahoko girl walks over there, I will throw this on her.
Then she will scream
and fall into the water.
It serves her right.
But do you think this is too much?
Geez, You are a real pushover, aren't you?
That's why Irie-kun has never turned to you.
I have nothing to say back to you.
I'm the same, too.
Here they come
-Hurry up!
-Wait, wait!
Geez, she will pass again.
-I'll do it. I'll do it.
Hurry!
Yes!
Don't worry, I'm here for you.
-What?
Oh, it looks like someone fell into the pond.
I think they are the cleaning ladies.
I assume they are cleaning the pond.
Let's go.
You had some bad water accidents, Kotokoo-chan.
I think I've been punished.
Since I tried to do mean things to such a beautiful girl.
You're talking about Sahoko-san, right?
It's true. She was a little bit beautiful.
When did you take that?
But she is not Naoki's type at all.
Naoki needs stimulation in his life.
A girl who is too perfect and quiet...
I know he is going to feel unsatisfied right away.
I can easily tell.
But they looked like they really liked each other.
And not only that, I made a really good impression as a mean mother-in-law!
I'm sure Chairman Oizuma is furious!
I don't think he will give his precious granddaughter
to a family with a mother-in-law like me!
I bet they are the ones who will refuse this.
It's them.
It's the phone call to tell us about the refusal!
Yes, I'm coming!
Hell, this is the Irie residence.
Chairman Oizumi?
It's from him.
I apologize for what my mother did today.
I see.
That's fine with me
Yes, please.
How was it?
Did they refuse?
He said Sahoko-san liked me,
so he wants to move forward.
What?
So I told him that we could move forward.
Naoki.
I like her.
So please don't try to ruin it like that again.
Mom
You, too.
Huh?
It was so obvious.
I'm sorry.
Naoki's serious. I don't believe this.
Since then, Sahoko-san has been calling him quite often.
They go on dates many time a week.
Mrs. Irie is frustrated because Irie-kun comes home late.
I see.
There is nothing that we can do.
Are you giving up?
Well, we are talking about Oizumi Sahoko.
There is no way that we can win.
But,
If I have to give up Irie-kun for someone...
I wish it was you.
Huh?
Because if it was you, he would regret it eventually.
He would think "I should have chosen Matsumoto back then."
Are you making fun of me?
I feel like I lost to that Sahoko girl who didn't even fight for it.
But in your case, I admit to your effort.
What you've been doing is so useless, but you try as much as possible.
You make me laugh.
Leave me alone.
I know...
that you kissed him.
Oh... but that was...
I'm rooting for you.
What was that?
Could it be a cheer?
I'm home.
Yes.
That's fine.
I will see you tomorrow.
Yes.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Are you going out with Sahoko-san tomorrow?
I'm just wondering . . .
I'm sorry
It's not my business, is it?
We are going to Omotesando.
-It's a solo show opening reception for
an artist that Chairman Oizumi supports.
- I see.
Are you going to follow me again?
Are you going to pretend
you are cleaning the toilets at the party?
Kin-chan.
Look, doesn't it look delicious?
Eat this and cheer up.
We told him that Irie started dating the girl from the arranged marriage meeting.
That's right.
After all, we can say that...
he is in fact dating her.
Here, have some.
-Here, here.
-Have some.
Here you go.
I'm going to borrow this.
Let me try a little.
Geez, if you eat it looking like that,
even delicious food will taste awful.
Kotoko, cheer up.
You would feel better if a heartless person like Irie got married.
He's right.
It's just...
I know this is just my imagination...
But lately, I felt like the distance
between Irie-kun and I got closer.
That's why...
I can't accept
the reality yet.
I know.
No matter what happened, I thought you two would be together.
Jinko. It's cruel to tell her that now.
Irie is getting along with the girl.
That's right.
This time around, it's not like before.
Because an arranged marriage is between two families.
You can't just say,
"I don't like her anymore" and quit.
That means Irie is aware of that and still wants to move forward.
You are right.
Ah, let's eat, okay?
Okay.
Have some, okay?
-No eating, no life, okay?
-Right
-Cheer up!
-Eat as much as you can!
It's good to eat sweet stuff.
All of the art work was amazing.
Did you think so too, Naoki-san?
That party was very peaceful.
I could tell what a great person the artist was.
You must be hungry since they only have a small buffet.
Would you like to have dinner with me at a restaurant?
I would love to.
Straight ahead, there is an Italian restaurant that my grandfather goes to all the time.
The restaurant that Chairman Oizumi likes...
I'm sure it's good.
Let's go there.
Naoki is late.
I'll go look for him.
No, don't.
It's dangerous for a girl to be walking around in the middle of the night.
But I don't think I can fall asleep.
I'll take a walk and stop by a convenience store to buy some juice.
Kotoko-chan.
No matter what she says, she still cares about Naoki.
Hey, Handsome man.
Are you on the way home from your date with the rich girl?
Hey you, wait!
Just how do you feel about Kotoko?
It's none of your business.
Yes, it is!
You have always been leading Kotoko on.
Kotoko is a precious person to me.
You've been toying with my precious person's feelings.
How can I keep my mouth shut?
The what are you going to do?
I will take Kotoko away from you.
No...
I will protect her.
So please don't bother us.
I'm sure you understand since you have a girl you want to marry.
If she is very precious to you...
Kotoko is very precious to me.
I can't stand looking at Kotoko
suffer so much.
What do you say?
Irie-kun, please say "Kotoko loves me"
You used to say that.
Please.
Do whatever you want.
Sure.
I will do whatever I want like you said.
So don't meddle anymore, got it?
This is a promise between men!
This time... is it really the end?
Do I have to give up on Irie-kun?
It's impossible.
Brother...
Are you really going to marry the woman
you had the arranged marriage meeting with?
What is it all of a sudden?
Please answer me.
It's probably going to happen.
Do you really love her?
What is going on, Yuki?
Please answer my question.
Because...
Because the person you love is...
Kotoko, right?
Because in the hospital room, you gave Kotoko...
a kiss - - -
-Next time...
I will introduce you to Sahoko-san.
She is beautiful and she is supposed
to be good at cooking.
I'm sure you will like her.
She is a good match for me.
I'm sure everything will work out...
Good morning, Kotoko.
Oh, good morning, Kin-chan.
Are you going to work at the cafeteria?
Yeah.
Today's lunch special is...
chicken cutlet.
You like it, right?
I will give you an extra portion in secret.
So you have to come and eat.
Okay, thank you.
Hey...
Next Sunday...
If you have time...
Do you want to go out with me?
Oh, well...
I got tickets for a movie from a customer at Aihara.
I thought you might enjoy it for a change.
Uh... it's an action movie... you will feel exhilarated.
After all, you don't want to go out
with just two of us, right?
- Sure.
- How about Jinko - - -
What?
Sure. Let's go, just the two of us.
Uh, this means...
It's a date. Are you sure?
You helped me a lot with Mr. irie.
I want to thank you, so let's go on a date.
Okay.
Well, see you later then.
Alright!
I was told that the president will be
discharged from the hospital next week.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
About the arranged marriage meeting...
After the president settles down, with the presence
of parents from both families...
They want to have dinner and talk about future plans.
That's fine with me.
I appreciate your help.
Thank you very much, Naoki-san.
Chairman Oizumi promised us an
amount of financial support.
Now our company is safe.
Irie-kun and I are...
about to start walking our own paths.
And further down those paths
I wonder, what future awaits us?
♫ My overgrown bangs are ♫
♫ gently shaken by the wind ♫
♫ It's still slightly chilly ♫
♫ on the way home in the evening ♫
♫ Suddenly I think of the little happiness ♫
♫  that blossomed in my heart ♫
♫ I realized many things ♫
♫ when I passed through the cycle of the seasons ♫
♫ Many tears were shed ♫
♫ and there were many arguments ♫
♫ Above all, thank you for your irreplaceable time, ♫
♫ your smile, and today ♫
♫ Many tears were shed ♫
♫ and there were many arguments ♫
♫ Above all, there's the irreplaceable time, ♫
♫ your smile, and surely tomorrow as well ♫
♫ Your memories and your future ♫
♫ Hold onto them tightly, so they won't be ruined ♫
♫ More than anyone else, ♫
♫  I always want to walk by your side ♫
[Preview]
Will you marry me?
What?
We are dating while considering marriage in the future.
I don't mix up my love and work life like someone else does.
Doesn't that depend on the person?
It was fun. Time flew by so quickly.
I decide about my own life.
I've wanted to talk to you.
We should move out of Iri-chan's house.
You should find a good guy soon.
No matter how much I'm hurt,
I decided by myself not to give up on my feelings for Irie-kun.