[Harold] My memories are back, sir.
[in English] Welcome back, Rustia.
[Marcus] When you're back at the NLEA,
keep quiet about what you know.
Especially around Felix.
About Cuchy…
[Felix] I adopted her. I took care of her.
But she disappeared all of a sudden.
Who is this "Cuchy"?
You really do have a lot
of things you don't remember.
[in English] Good to see you, Felix.
[Harold] If you really are
the traitor among us,
I'll make sure you pay.
[Villanueva, in English]
You are hereby fired
as the director of the Special
Investigations Division!
Effective immediately,
Task Force Alpha
is hereby dissolved!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Marcus] You need to watch your back
and find somewhere to hide.
You'll definitely be targeted.
They could strike back
and use you against us.
[Norhana] As long as you're in
our community, you're safe.
[Marcus] When this is all over,
we'll have so much to catch up on
and discover about each other.
But for now, we need
to take down General Carillo.
The sooner, the better.
I need your help.
[Edrick] Datu Rahman
gave an envelope to Ms. MMK.
- What's on it?
- Substantial evidence, sir,
against General Carillo.
[in English] The answers
we are searching for
- are just here.
- [gunshots blasting]
[screaming]
[Maya Mae] And because these documents
will reveal everything.
[Maya Mae] And when we did
our preliminary investigation,
we saw a lot of familiar names
in this document.
[Maya Mae] But the most
frequent one of all
was the name of retired
police general Manuel Carillo.
[Manuel] I won't let
that damned Marcus and Jalil
bring me down!
[reporter] Retired police general
Manuel Carillo was arrested.
This was after Maya Mae Kalaw
made an exposé
linking General Carillo
to a gun-smuggling syndicate
and an alleged plot to overthrow
the government.
[mysterious theme music playing]
[morose music playing]
Sorry… I'm sorry, General.
[handcuffs click open]
[breathes sharply and loudly]
I'm exhausted.
At last,
the people behind all this chaos
have finally been locked up.
I know, right?
Can you believe General Carillo
was behind all of it?
He seemed nice, but he was evil all along.
You really can't judge
a person's true character
just by how they look.
[Norhana] That's true.
But I'm even happier because…
I finally get to see my children again
and be with them.
[knocking on door]
[in Arabic] Praise be to God!
- Ma…
- Marcus.
Auntie.
[softly] How are you?
Gabriel…
[emotional music playing]
[sniffles]
- Mama.
- [sobs]
My son!
[crying]
- Mama…
- [crying, sobbing]
[sniffles, sobbing]
- [smooches]
- [crying]
[in Arabic] Praise be to God!
[indistinct]
Gabriel.
Marcus…
I'm so glad you're both safe, my children.
General Carillo's accomplices
are still in hiding,
but we'll find them.
We're still not completely safe, Ma.
Not until everything
has truly been resolved.
You two still need
to be careful, my children.
Even though Carillo is in prison,
he's still dangerous because his influence
reaches far and wide.
- Sir!
- Oh!
Azuelo, what do you need?
Sir, now that General Carillo
has been arrested,
and it's been proven
that I had nothing to do
with the gun smuggling
and the destabilization plot
against the government,
- I'm hoping you could reconsider--
- [Villanueva] Do you want to know
if you'll be reinstated as SID Director?
- [in English] Yes, sir.
- [Villanueva] Azuelo.
We have standard procedures
that need to be followed.
We can't rush the process.
[in English] I understand, sir.
[in English] How about…
Agent Marcus Reyes
and Jalil Abubakar, sir?
I've already removed them
from the most wanted list.
They're no longer under
the neutralize-on-sight order.
But they still have
a lot of charges to face.
And they still have
a lot of explaining to do.
[in English] That would be all, sir.
- [in English] Sir!
- [in English] Carry on.
[tense music playing]
[door clicks shut]
[Sean] That's all
General Villanueva said, sir?
He removed you
from your position fast enough.
[Eve] Exactly.
But now he's saying…
there's a process that can't be rushed?
Sir! My goodness.
Sir, they're intentionally
doing it to cause delay.
[stirring music playing]
You're right. I've also noticed that
he seems to be acting differently now.
It's as if he's waiting for something.
What do you mean, sir?
I'm not yet sure.
But he's really acting
suspiciously right now.
[footsteps approaching]
[Manuel inhales and exhales deeply]
[in English] Madam President.
How may I help you?
[in English] But as you can see,
I'm… currently indisposed.
[in English] How dare you?
[in English] I trusted you,
but you played me for a fool!
You even killed Ahmad.
The only person I trusted a lot.
I hope you know, General Carillo,
that you didn't just betray me.
You betrayed the whole country!
[tense music playing]
I never denied it.
[chuckles, inhales]
[Manuel, in English]
Look at yourself. You're so weak.
You're too weak.
You have to trust me.
You know nothing.
I was just playing you.
I'm…
weak?
You're the one in jail.
Remember this, General Carillo.
I will do everything in my power
as president of the republic
to make sure that you
and your collaborators
will pay for all of your sins!
[pensive music playing]
[Jalil sighs]
What's your plan now?
I'll return to the SID.
I'll make sure to bring back
the Task Force Alpha.
And you?
I'll bring back my father's corpse
to the island.
That's what I promised him and Jamilah.
And after that?
What will you do then?
I don't know.
Will you stay in your island or…
will you stay here in Manila?
Maybe… It might be better
if you stay here in Manila for now.
You know.
Mom will miss you if you leave right away.
I'm a member of CDSU-Mindanao.
- My life is really there.
- You know, that's another thing.
Why don't you just continue
being a police officer here?
Is that even possible
after everything that happened?
We don't know.
It'll be a shame.
You're great.
I know you really want
to be a police officer.
Not everything we want will happen.
Right now, I'm happy to…
meet you and Mom.
The most important thing for me now is,
how do we find
Carillo's remaining accomplices?
[stirring music playing]
Especially Felix.
Especially that bastard.
I will give justice to Father,
to Sir Mustapha,
and all of Carillo's victims.
[in Arabic] God has willed it.
We're here on Alejandro Avenue,
where a public protest is ongoing.
This is just one of the many protests
happening across different parts
of the country.
According to the people,
they have fully lost their trust
in the government
and in public officials,
especially now that they found out
that General Carillo,
who they thought was a decent man,
was actually the mastermind behind
the chaos across the country.
Sir, what do you have to say?
Nothing! This government
can't really do anything!
You should resign!
The people in power are useless!
They're just thieves!
We can't expect anything from you!
She's right. We were
all counting on Carillo.
But he's also useless!
- [chanting] Quit! Quit!
- Mendoza, resign now!
You're weak! We need someone strong!
- Someone with an iron fist!
- That's right!
[chanting] Iron fist! Iron fist!
[foreboding music playing]
The protests
are no longer limited
to Metro Manila and Luzon.
There are now protests
across the Visayas and Mindanao.
In fact,
my police officers
can't come home anymore.
[in English] I understand.
We'll also discuss that
at the emergency meeting tomorrow.
General Villanueva,
everyone who'll come tomorrow
is in the succession of power.
They can all take over as president
in case something happens to me.
So make sure that
our meeting will be secure.
If not,
we'll have a constitutional crisis,
and the whole country will be in chaos.
[in English] You have my word,
Madam President.
[in English] Good.
I don't think I've ever
seen you here before.
[in English] Yes, Madam President.
SPO4 Felix Domingo.
I was formerly
in Task Force Alpha, but now
I'm a part
of your Presidential Security Group.
Oh.
[in English] TFA, one of the elites.
If so, then you can easily protect me.
[in English] With my life, madam.
[dramatic sting]
If you'll notice, out of 82 provinces,
we've secured 37.
That's not even half.
You're right.
But every province we've secured
is a first-class province or region.
And every one of them has a military camp
and an NLEA regional office.
The 93rd Infantry Battalion in Region IV…
I went to the academy
with their commander.
Leave them to me.
Once Martial Law is declared…
And when the march is declared,
they'll back the movement.
And then,
nothing will stand
in General Carillo's way.
By tomorrow, we'll have a new republic.
To the new republic!
- To the new republic!
[dark music playing]
Malacañang is now preparing
for a special emergency meeting
called by President Natalia Mendoza.
This comes in response
to the public's demand
for stronger and more
effective national security.
Officials in the presidential
line of succession
are expected to attend,
including Vice President Kevin Flores,
Senate President Joshua Manzon,
Speaker of the House of Representatives
Samantha Santos,
and Chief Justice Leona Caluag.
As long as Carillo's accomplices
are still out there,
our mission isn't over.
That's why we have
to find them immediately.
I'm calling in Task Force Alpha.
We urgently need to address
the country's security concerns.
[Villanueva] That's why we've invited
the highest-ranking government officials,
from the Vice President
to the Senate President,
the Speaker of the House,
and even the Chief Justice.
[reporter] And they've all
confirmed they're coming?
[Villanueva, in English] Yes.
[in English] Each and every one of them.
They're all coming.
[ominous music playing]
The very people who are next in line
if the President dies or is assassinated.
If that place is attacked
and they all die,
there'll be no one left
to lead the Philippines.
And taking over the government
will be easy.
MALACAÑANG IS PREPARING
AN URGENT MEETING FOR NATIONAL SECURITY.
[suspenseful music playing]
Is that Felix?
That conference.
That's their target.
That's where General Carillo will strike.
How did that bastard get assigned
to the President's Security Group?
General Villanueva.
No one else.
He's the only one who could've
recommended Domingo
to join the President's security detail.
He's working with General Carillo.
General Carillo's been able
to keep operating
because of him!
[music intensifies]
[ominous music continues]
[music stops]
What's Marcus and Jalil up to now?
They're always sabotaging our plans.
Relax. Don't worry.
If those two interfere again,
General Carillo has our insurance.
[ominous music playing]
[Usman] Auntie.
- Thank you so much, Usman.
- You're welcome.
Come on. Let's grab a snack inside.
- [Jamilah] Okay.
- Sure.
[tires screeching]
- Hey!
- You're coming with us!
- Wait, wait!
- Help!
Help!
[tense music playing]
[man grunts]
[Jamilah grunts]
[Jamilah grunting]
[Teresa gasps]
[Jamilah grunts]
Stop it!
Doctor Teresa!
[Usman grunts]
[man 1] Get them in the van! Move! Hurry!
- What do you want with us?
- [Jamilah] Doctor Teresa!
- [Teresa] Let us go!
- [man 2] Stop fighting!
[tires screeching]
What do you want with Doctor Teresa?
Wait. I'm not your enemy.
I'm on your side.
[woman 1] What's taking so long?
[woman 2] We've been waiting for hours.
- [woman 1] Where is it?
- [woman 2] Right there.
[indistinct dialogue]
Alright. Go find the President.
[man 1] What time
is the press conference starting?
[Maye Mae, in English] Go.
[man 2] Get the camera.
It's about to start.
[woman 1] Go. Call them!
- [man 1] Did they even give a time?
- [woman] I don't know.
[man 2] Not answering.
[ominous music continues]
- [indistinct chattering]
- [door thuds]
- [man 1] Hey, why'd they close it?
- [man 2] Why'd they lock it?
- [man 3] Sir, please open the door!
- [woman] What now?
[security] Stay where you are.
Nobody leaves.
Sir, please let us out!
- There's no signal.
- What do you mean?
- Our signals are being jammed?
- Huh?
[man 4] I think we're being jammed.
[ominous music continues]
- Let us out!
- [banging on door]
[woman] Please!
[security] Nobody's leaving!
Stay where you are!
- [knocks on door]
- [woman] What?
[man] Let us out!
[music intensifies]
- [rapid gunfire]
- [people screaming]
- Get down!
- [screaming continues]
[sinister music playing]
‪[gunshots blasting]
[people screaming]
Bud, did you hear the gunshots?
Yes, I think they came from over there!
- Come on!
- Let's go!
- [gunshots]
- [bodies thud]
[gasping]
[gunshots blasting]
- [Felix] Come with me!
- [Natalia] Wait--
- The president is under attack!
- Come on!
Who are you working for?
- Tell me!
- Shut up!
- [Felix] I will kill you.
- [Natalia gasps]
[Felix] Move!
- [tense music playing]
- [gasping]
- What happened in there?
- Bud, they need backup inside!
Come on!
[guns cock, shots blasting]
[people crying, screaming]
[gunshots blasting]
[tense music continues]
[music turns grim]
The president's not here.
We need to find her.
[tense music playing]
EMBLEM OF THE PRESIDENT OF THE PHILIPPINES
[dark music playing]
[dark music continues]
Let me go!
Where are you taking me?
What are you-- Oh, security.
Security, help!
Help me! [gasps]
[Natalia] Traitors!
What are you going to do with me?
- [Manuel] Ah…
- [Natalia grunts]
[chuckles]
[in English] Finally! Good job, Felix!
Alright. [clicks tongue]
Go get my leverage.
‪[dramatic sting]
[in English] Yes, sir.
‪[thud]
[Manuel sighs loudly, chuckles]
Madam President,
your chair is quite comfortable.
[in English] I think
I'm going to like it here.
[in English] Not on my watch.
[tense music playing]
[grunting]
- [Natalia grunts]
- [Solares grunts]
Mustapha taught me how to defend myself!
[gun cocks]
Go ahead.
If you want to keep
fighting until you die,
go ahead. Make my day!
[scoffs] But do not forget.
The vice president and everyone else
in the line of succession are gone.
This will all be mine the moment you die.
Damn you, Manuel.
[line beeping]
Did you get a signal?
- Not yet.
- [beeping continues]
- Let me go!
- [in English] Madam President.
The Philippines is in turmoil.
Everywhere you look,
if there isn't a crime happening,
there's a protest.
People are angry.
You have to declare Martial Law.
And you have to convince the public
that this is what the country needs!
I know a psychiatrist. Get checked out!
[in English] You're not a savior,
you're a psychopath!
[Manuel scoffs]
We need change, Madam President,
and it won't be possible
with leaders like you
because you are weak.
[in English] We need to burn
the whole system down.
[in English] The system that allows
weaklings like yourself to rule!
And from the ashes,
peace and progress will be reborn
for The New Republic.
[in English] No.
I'm not going to give you what you want!
[Manuel] But, Madam President…
your vice president is dead!
And everyone else
in the line of succession!
My people are ready
to launch a coup d'état.
I will get what I want
once you're gone.
That is, if…
you want the bloodshed to continue.
[in English] You can kill me,
but you will never succeed.
Don't underestimate the Filipinos.
Because even if I'm gone,
there are people who'll take
my place to fight against you.
Because they will never be fooled
by a psychopath like you!
- [grunts]
- [Natalia yelps]
[Natalia gasps]
[Manuel] No!
You're wrong!
You're wrong! This is mine!
Do you understand? This throne is mine!
This throne is mine!
[laughs maniacally]
It's mine!
[tense music playing]
- It's Axl Rosales!
- No, wait!
- Wait!
- Calm down!
He's on our side.
- What?
- [Azuelo] Sabdani.
What's going on?
Sir, Jamilah, Jalil's sister,
and Dr. Reyes
was kidnapped by armed men.
Dr. Reyes?
Yes, sir.
She is the mother of Jalil and Marcus.
Jalil is Marcus Reyes' missing brother.
He's Gabriel.
Who kidnapped them?
Felix Domingo.
I recognized one of the armed men.
He's one of Felix Domingo's men.
Felix Domingo, you bastard!
Why would Sir Felix do that?
Sir, they're right.
When I broke into
General Villanueva's office,
I found out that he recommended Domingo
to become part of the PSG.
That's right, sir. I saw it on the news.
Sir Felix is now part
of the President's security detail.
Sir, they're attacking Malacañang now.
[Usman] What? Sir.
[in English] Move! Move out!
You won't succeed!
Even if you kill me,
someone will stop your evil plans!
[Villanueva on radio]
Lawin to Alpha. Come in. Over.
- [in English] Go, Villanueva.
- [radio static]
Marcus Reyes and Jalil Abubakar are here.
- [Villanueva] They're inside.
- [radio static]
[suspenseful music playing]
[in English] See?
My allies have arrived.
The people who are helping me
stop your evil plans.
[in English] And I'm sure
they're not alone.
The entire Philippines is behind them
to fight against you!
[in English] Kill them, Villanueva.
Make sure none of them survives.
- [Villanueva, in English] Roger, sir.
- [radio static]
[walkie-talkie thuds]
[music intensifies]
[grunting]
This way.
Hey! Stop!
[gunshots blasting]
Let's use this to block the door.
[grunts]
This is Sir Mustapha’s office.
He had an armory at his house.
He probably has one here too.
Let's look for the lock.
- [door rattling]
- [breathing heavily]
Open the door!
You have nowhere left to go!
[grunts]
- Here!
- Okay!
[man 1] Come out!
You have nowhere left to go!
[man 2] Just surrender! You can't escape!
[gunshots blasting]
[police siren honking, tires screeching]
- [guard 1] Someone's coming!
- [guard 2] Who is it?
- [tires screech]
- [siren blares]
I am Director Azuelo
of the Special Investigations Division.
I'm with Task Force Alpha.
We need to talk to the President.
You can't talk to her. She's busy.
She's currently in a meeting.
[guard 1] Leave!
[Azuelo, in English] Fire at will!
- [both yell]
- [rapid gunfire]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Azuelo, in English] Move! Move!
[metal gate creaks]
Do you hear those gunshots?
[Solares] Those are your allies.
The people you expect to protect you
are being killed.
[in English] You wish.
I know they're all good fighters.
That's why Ahmad trusted them.
[cackles]
Natalia! Natalia!
I pity your naivety!
If you really love this country,
you will give me what I want!
Manuel, if you really love the country,
can you please just drop dead? Now!
[in English] We move on to Plan B.
[in English] Yes, General.
[Manuel snaps fingers]
What is this?
In 15 minutes,
the Philippines will lose its president.
[dark music plays]
[in English] You really are a psychopath.
And the news will say
that you were killed by Marcus Reyes
and Jalil Abubakar
to seize power.
While I will declare a military junta
to save the Republic!
And
it will all happen in 15 minutes.
Which means I have 15 minutes
to beat you.
[in English] Be my guest, Natalia.
It never hurts to try.
- [bomb activates, ticking]
- [in English] In 15 minutes…
- [in English] Tick-tock-tick-tock…
- [huffs]
[chuckles]
[Manuel sighs deeply] In 15 minutes,
the Philippines will be mine!
[tense music playing]
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
[Teresa] Let us go!
- [stirring music playing]
- [heavy breathing]
[Teresa, Jamilah breathing heavily]
[Felix] Teresa.
[bullet clinks]
- Felix…
- Jamilah.
Felix…
- [Teresa] Felix…
- How are you?
What does this all mean?
Felix, what is this?
Jalil is your brother.
[stirring music continues]
And Marcus is your son.
[Felix chuckles]
I'll invite them over to see you guys.
I'll have them watch me kill you.
[suspenseful stinging]
Because they…
are my…
worst enemies.
[breath quivers]
[stirring music continues]
[gunfire blasting]
[in English] Reload!
[tense music playing]
[rapid gunfire]
[Felix] Shall we play a game?
Do you know how to hold a gun?
Do you have any idea what we have to do
to fix this goddamn government?
This is what the country needs.
We don't need an iron fist.
We need justice!
You can't keep us apart anymore.
[rapid gunfire]
- [officer] Let's force it.
- [beeping]
It's gonna blow up.
[grunting]
- [gunshots blasting]
- [Felix] Marcus! Jalil!
I have a surprise for you!