[Marcus] The ones who abducted
Datu Rahman,
they definitely have people inside here.
Everything happened so fast.
They always know our movements.
[man] But even if they sensed our arrival,
how did they manage to get Datu Rahman out
that quickly and that clean?
[reporter] Sir, is there any update
on Datu Rahman's whereabouts?
And was he really taken by the syndicate?
[Jamilah] Agent Marcus Reyes,
you'll pay for what you did to us.
I need an update on your progress
in finding Datu Rahman.
As of now, all of my leads are dead.
[key clacks on floor]
- [Lara] My keys.
- [Marcus] I got it.
What's that? Why is there
a GPS tracker in my car?
We need to be careful.
We don't know who our enemy is.
Sir! Have you heard?
[Felix] Condencido and Vinluan
were gunned down
last night while on patrol.
This is scary. We're in danger.
We need to be careful.
Wasn't there a CCTV camera on the street
where Condencido and Vinluan were shot?
The footage is corrupted,
including the backup files.
- How did that happen?
- We don't know either, sir.
[Jalil] Rashid, what are you going to do?
[Rashid] Jalil?
Just ignore it. It'll only cause trouble.
Do you know Zylverix?
I saw the police who raided our place
with Marcus Reyes.
- [tires screeching]
- There were cars going in and out.
I don't know if this is
related to your father,
but I thought it might help you.
Are you also looking for Father here?
[mysterious theme music playing]
[in Arabic] Peace be upon you.
And peace be upon you.
I saw Marcus Reyes
surveilling outside Zylverix.
I knew something was hidden there.
And I need to find out what it is.
But the place is too big.
Don't worry. I'll help you.
I'll help you search the place.
It's on my route anyway.
[in Tausug] Thank you.
[reporter] At midnight last night,
police officers PO3 Condencido
and PO3 Vinluan were shot while on patrol.
The incident is said
to be a random attack,
but there's still no clear evidence
on who's behind it.
I think it was intentional.
[reporter] The families and friends
of the victims
are now calling for justice.
- [Usman] Sir.
- [sinister music playing]
I spoke with Buster earlier.
I found out all CCTV footage
from the time of the incident
was wiped out.
Do you think that's just a coincidence?
Everything's been erased.
There's no way that was all a coincidence.
That's what I'm thinking too.
I knew Vinluan and Condencido.
They were hardworking officers.
And they had no enemies.
[pensive music playing]
You're right.
It wasn't just an accident.
[Marcus] Does this building
have a hidden exit?
Where did they take Datu Rahman out?
How did they outsmart us?
[line ringing]
Please check all vehicle movements
at the Zylverix Limited Building.
I'll send you the date and time frame.
[sighs]
[knock on door]
[man] Sir.
Thank you.
[tense music playing]
[Lara] What are you up to, Marcus?
‪[dramatic music]
That's it, sir.
Aside from your fellow officers,
no one else entered or exited Zylverix
within that 24-hour window.
I also checked the previous days.
There's really nothing, sir.
Are you sure you checked all the CCTV
covering the compound?
Of course, sir.
Everything. Over and over.
There's really nothing.
Sir, what's really in there?
It looks like only rats are living there.
[Marcus] If no one came in or out
before and after Usman and I arrived,
that means it's possible he wasn't moved.
He's still there.
Datu Rahman wasn't taken out.
We were just searching in the wrong place.
[stirring music playing]
[Marcus] What's the history of Zylverix?
Who owns it?
[pensive music playing]
A shell company?
Why is the building still intact
if no one's using it
and it has no legal owner?
[Marcus] Clear!
[Marcus] He's not here.
Not here either.
[exhales]
[Marcus] Where are you, Datu Rahman?
[reporter] At midnight last night,
police officers PO3 Condencido
and PO3 Vinluan were shot while on patrol.
The incident is said
to be a random attack,
but there's still no clear evidence
on who's behind it…
- Sir!
- Reyes?
- …are now calling for justice.
- Sir.
We need to lock down
the Zylverix Building.
- What? Why? You've already been there!
- [tense music playing]
Sir, we made a slight miscalculation.
But I think Datu Rahman
hasn't been taken out.
They're still hiding him there.
Perfect timing.
We're being criticized
by the media right now
over the deaths of Condencido and Vinluan.
[in English] We need a win!
[in English] Yes, sir.
[stirring music playing]
[line ringing]
Usman, we're heading back
to the Zylverix building.
Go on ahead. I'll catch up to you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[police siren wailing]
[policeman 1] Sir.
Carry on.
[foreboding music playing]
This is a full-scale search
for Datu Rahman!
Seal all exits.
Lockdown the whole perimeter.
If he really is in there,
you better make sure
that he won't get through us.
Understood?!
[all] Yes, sir!
[in English] Alright!
Unit 1, secure the perimeter
and the lobby.
Unit 2, take the second floor.
Unit 3, take the third floor.
Remaining units,
take the rest of the floors.
Move!
[Felix] Move!
[tense music playing]
Usman, you and your men stay here.
Secure this perimeter.
Yes, ma'am.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Jalil] My hunch is right.
They also believe that Father
is still possibly in here.
[door creaks open]
[foot stomps]
[suspenseful music continues]
[in English] Suarez,
Domingo, check that area.
[Felix, in English] Clear!
Angeles, Reyes, take care of this area.
We'll head on to the second floor.
[in English] Yes, sir.
[man] Chief.
Reyes, let's go.
[suspenseful music continues]
Men, have you checked
that corner over there?
Check that area.
[officer] Sir Marcus,
it's negative on the other wing.
Unit 1 has also cleared
the storage already.
- Looks like it's a cold lead.
- No.
Search the entire area.
Including the ventilation.
[in English] Copy.
How about you, sir? Seen anything?
[Lara] Looks like everyone's here.
Director Azuelo is upstairs
on the second floor.
They might be looking for us. Let's go.
[whispers] Okay.
[suspenseful music continues]
Oh? Got anything?
Negative, sir. We didn't find the target.
[Felix clicks tongue] Aye yay yay!
[Azuelo clicks tongue, sighs]
Sir Marcus, looks like
you're losing your edge.
[Azuelo, in English]
Operations terminated!
- [in English] Return to base! Everybody!
- [officer 1] Yes, sir!
[all, in English] Yes, sir!
[stirring music playing]
[van engine starting]
[car engine starting]
[car door clicks open]
[grim music playing]
[Azuelo] Diez, Yambao!
- [officer 2] Sir.
- Listen. You're on gate duty.
- Delima!
- [Delima] Sir!
- Orendo!
- Sir.
You'll be on roving duty.
Keep a close eye on the perimeter.
Be sure to report any unusual movements
as soon as possible.
[in English] Understood?
[officers in unison] Yes, sir!
[Azuelo] Let's go.
[van engine starting]
[suspenseful music playing]
[van door clicks shut]
They weren't able to find Father!
[tense music playing]
[Azuelo] You gave me your word,
Agent Reyes!
- You told me that Datu Rahman was there.
- [suspenseful music playing]
But what did we find?
Dust!
[sighs]
Sir. It's just
that I haven't found him yet.
But I'm certain that they didn't move
the subject out of the Zylverix building.
Datu Rahman is still in there!
[in English] That's ridiculous!
We've turned the building
upside down twice,
but it's still negative!
[in English] You've wasted
the purest time and resources!
I committed four officers
to guard a ghost building because of you!
This is why we've become a laughing stock!
[smacks]
Sir.
I am positive
that I will find Datu Rahman.
[in English] Just give me more time.
[in English] I'm giving you
until 0200 hours.
If you still come up empty-handed,
abort the operation,
let go of that lead.
[in English] Yes, sir.
[door clicks shut]
Marcus. Are you okay?
[sighs] I'm fine.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
[in English] We followed protocol.
We'll track the subject down eventually.
Maybe we just need new intel.
Maybe.
Thank you, Lara.
[door thuds]
[intriguing music playing]
[officer] Sir Marcus.
Negative on the other wing.
Unit 1 has also cleared the storage area.
[sighs]
If I'm right,
the elevator should be here.
But why isn't it here?
[intriguing music continues]
The elevator isn't on the blueprint.
It's an off-the-books modification.
[music turns stirring]
[vehicle honking]
[tense music playing]
Jardin, have you seen Agent Reyes?
Oh, yes, ma'am. He left in a hurry.
He must've gone somewhere important.
[line ringing]
[mutters]
[mutters, sighs]
- [disconnect beeping]
- [sighs sharply]
[line ringing]
Get Datu Rahman out of there now!
[cell phone thuds]
[breathing heavily]
- Sir!
- Good evening, Sir Marcus.
[Yambao] I've already removed
the CCTV cameras.
[unsettling music playing]
Yambao.
There are CCTV cameras
at the building entrance.
Remove them. Make sure no one sees you.
Stay out of sight.
Good job. Thank you.
[Yambao] Open the gate!
- Escort Sir Marcus. Hurry up.
- [chains clattering]
[officer] Okay, sir.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Marcus] If this elevator isn't
in the original blueprint,
this could be a ghost shaft.
They could be hiding something here.
[suspenseful music continues, ends]
[stirring music playing]
[elevator dings]
[whirring sound]
[stirring music continues]
[man grunts]
[heaving]
[elevator dings]
[music intensifies]
[metal rod clatters]
[padlock clatters]
[tense music continues]
Psst!
[grunting]
- [groans]
- [shouts]
[both grunting]
[man grunts]
[tense music continues]
[grunting and groaning]
- [bones snap]
- [man screams]
- [man] No!
- Take me to Datu Rahman.
[man grunts]
[tense music swells]
[Marcus] Who are you, Datu Rahman?
Why are they ready to take
so many lives just for you?
[Jalil] I need to uncover the truth
before they kill me.
[Lara] What happened?
[sharp inhale] They've found
the CCTV cameras.
[suspenseful music playing]
- [kick lands]
- [gunshots]
Reyes, Angeles, what the hell happened?!
[Marcus] My hunch was right.
This is where they brought Datu Rahman.
It looks like they just moved him.
Who took him, and where did they go?
Keep an eye out for any concealed keyway
or suspicious-looking access panel.
[Azuelo] How did this happen, Agent Reyes?
You said you would find Datu Rahman,
but how did he manage to evade you again?
[reporter] Why did it end in a shootout?
Was the intel wrong?
Has Datu Rahman escaped once again?
Jalil is in that very building.
What is he doing there?
He believes Datu Rahman
is being held there.
Oh! We must go there!
Did something happen to Brother Jalil?
[frustrated scream]
How did this happen?!
Who took you?! Who?!
[suspenseful music playing]