[Lara, in English]
Marcus, they're heading south.
They're on the way to…
to S. Trinidad Hospital.
[Jalil] What's so special
about S. Trinidad Hospital?
[Usman] His mother is a surgeon
in that hospital.
[Jalil] I'm coming for you, Jamilah.
I'm coming to save you.
Operate on my brother,
and make sure he survives.
If you don't want me to kill you all!
[Marcus, in English] Listen up, everyone!
[in English] Our objective now,
secure the perimeter.
[Lara] I've identified the patient.
His name is Tommy Rosales,
the youngest brother
of Axl and Jovi Rosales.
They're members
of the criminal group, Metal-13.
[Marcus] We can't be careless right now.
[in English] We have
to negotiate with them.
[Marcus] We will use the negotiation
as a distraction before we attack them.
- [monitor beeping rapidly]
- [Axl] What's going on?!
What did you do to him?!
[Axl] If you can't save our brother,
I'll shoot you straight in the head.
Agent Angeles, what's going on?
[in English] Agent Reyes,
your negotiator just arrived.
[Marcus] Put him to work.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Teresa] Your brother is safe.
[Teresa crying] I've lost a child once.
Sometimes, I wish I could've saved him
the same way I save all of my patients.
[female reporter] The hostage-taking
situation is still ongoing
inside S. Trinidad Hospital.
The group, Metal-13, is armed
with high-caliber weapons,
keeping the police force in high alert
for widespread gun smuggling operations
of syndicate groups.
[mysterious theme music playing]
- [monitor beeping steadily]
- [somber music playing]
[grim music playing]
‪[music intensifies]
You're giving us
high-caliber weapons for free?
Is there a catch?
[Felix] Of course, there is.
You'll rob a bank, as you do,
with those weapons.
And however much you get from that,
we'll divide it 60-40.
Of course, the 60 is for me.
[laughs]
Wait, that's not fair.
We're the ones doing the hard work,
and you'll get more than us?
[Jovi] We can't allow that.
Let's do 50-50.
That's the deal.
Alright!
Let's do it 50-50!
Okay!
Like always.
If you fail,
I'll help you out.
Just don't give me a hard time.
Okay?
‪[music intensifies]
Do we have a deal?
Huh?
[tense music playing]
[music turns morose, concludes]
My gosh, sis.
Just when I've completed
my requirements for Canada,
I'm gonna die.
I can't take this.
That's what you get for teasing people.
You got your karma,
but you dragged us along with you.
- I'm sorry, sis.
- [somber music playing]
‪[clicks tongue]
How about you, mister? How are you?
I'm alright.
Hey! What are you doing? Stand up!
- [thug 1] Guard the doors!
- [thug 2 sighs]
Son of a…
[Jovi] Axl.
What's the plan?
‪[sniffles]
‪[gun thuds]
[softly] We have to get out of here.
But how?
The TFA is waiting for us outside.
They haven't moved.
I think
they're going to negotiate first.
[telephone ringing]
[tense music playing]
[sniffles]
[telephone ringing]
Hello?
‪[suspenseful music playing]
I am Director Emil Azuelo
of the Special Investigations Division.
May I talk with your leader?
Why? What do you need?
[Azuelo] you're Axl Rosales, aren't you?
I know that this isn't part of your plan.
All you wanted
was to save your brother
who got shot, right?
I'll let you get out of there alive,
but only if you promise
not to hurt the hostages.
[suspenseful music playing]
Do I make myself clear, Axl?
Did you really think
you can trick me that easily? Hmm?
I know what you're doing.
You're trying to distract us
as you find your way in.
[line rings]
- Yes, Boss?
- Keep a close eye on the CCTVs.
Keep your eyes on the TFA.
Yes, Boss. I'm on it.
[tense music playing]
Felix, you come with me.
We'll enter here.
[Jalil] I'll enter
from the right with Sabdani.
[tense dramatic music continues]
Hey, you two.
Keep an eye on the TFA outside.
If they make a wrong move,
everyone in here will die!
[hostages screaming, crying in fear]
[tense dramatic music continues]
[in English] Agent Reyes, armed hostile
approaching your corridor.
[in English] Maintain position.
[in English] Marcus, clear to cross.
[suspenseful music playing]
Major Espina.
[Lara] Slow down. There's
a movement to your right.
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[in English] Espina, proceed.
[in English] Monitor his vitals
every 15 minutes.
- Include the painkiller in his IV.
- Copy, Doc.
Now, if you want the people in here
to come out alive…
give us our demands.
What do you need?
[in English] A helicopter.
A big one. For all 13 of us.
It's difficult to get a helicopter.
It'll take a lot of time.
If you want,
I can give you a vehicle.
You can go right now.
How many do you need?
What, so you can attack us
when we leave? Hmm?
[suspenseful music playing]
I said… I want a helicopter.
Can you give me that or not?
And I told you, it's difficult to get one.
Can you wait three hours?
In three hours,
all of the people here would have died.
‪[dramatic sting]
- One hour?
- Thirty minutes.
Alright.
[in English] Thirty minutes.
- [suspenseful music continues]
- [sigh of relief]
Marcus.
[in English] Marcus, you have 30 minutes.
- [Lara, in English] Thirty minutes.
- [in English] Copy.
[tense music playing]
[Azuelo] Hello? Axl?
I can't let you be the only ones happy.
I need to make sure
that you don't hurt the hostages.
What do you mean?
You're asking for something.
So, it's just fair that you give us
something in return.
I want you to release ten hostages.
And why would I do that? Hmm?
Because you demanded something from us,
so you have to give us something as well!
What if I just kill them all right now?
[people weeping]
[music intensifies]
Then, do it.
But the moment we see blood,
even just a drop,
my men will rush in
and make sure you never get out.
[Azuelo] But that's why
we're negotiating, right?
I'll let you get out of there alive,
but make sure that no one gets hurt.
[tense music continues]
Well?
What do you say, Axl?
Alright.
But make sure
the helicopter arrives in 26 minutes.
Otherwise…
everyone in here will die.
[frustrated grunt]
[in English] Goddammit.
‪[music intensifies]
[in English] Good job, sir.
[in English] Boys!
Choose ten hostages to release.
[shouts] Now!
Only ten? It should be all of us!
Girl, shut up! I don't want to die yet!
- Don't say that!
- Stop it!
- You! Come with me! Now!
- [woman sobs]
You too!
No!
Prioritize the patients! They matter more!
Whatever!
- [thug 1] Move!
- [hostages screaming]
- [thug 1] Go!
- [screaming continues]
- [screams, sobs]
- [thug 1] Get out of here!
Hurry!
[clamoring, screaming]
[thug 1] There!
You too! Get up!
[thug 1] Move!
- Come here!
- Hey!
Let me go! I can't leave!
- Come on!
- Doc! Doc!
Go with him!
- I'll see you outside!
- [woman sobs]
- Go!
- Cut that out!
Move!
[tense music playing]
[Jamilah] What are you doing?
- Doc!
- What are you doing?!
- Put him in the wheelchair.
- [Teresa] Huh?
We can't! His wounds are still fresh!
I don't care!
- [Jovi] Put him in the wheelchair!
- [woman] Let's go!
- Ken!
- [woman] Help!
- [Teresa] Help us.
- Hurry.
- [Tommy groans in pain]
- Be careful.
- One.
- [Tommy groans]
- [Jovi] Be careful!
- [Tommy grunts]
[intriguing music playing]
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Go help them!
Move!
[suspenseful music playing]
[in English] Domingo, next left.
- The third one's the control room.
- [radio static]
- [in English] Copy, madam.
- [static crackles]
[sirens wailing]
[tires screech]
POLICE
[suspenseful music playing]
Sir, where are you going?
My niece is inside.
It's not safe to go inside.
Please move back.
Omar, what if Jamilah's in danger?
We're barging in there.
We'll save Jamilah.
[music intensifies]
[thug] Keep moving!
Go!
[suspenseful music continues]
Be quiet!
[in English] Agent Castillo,
hostile approaching your way.
I'll take care of it.
- Move forward.
- Are you sure?
I got this.
[in English] Yes, sir.
[suspenseful music continues]
[both grunt]
[Castillo grunts]
[assailant grunts]
[suspenseful music continues]
Weapons down!
[thug 2] Down!
[thug 2] Put 'em down!
We come in peace.
We're here for the hostages.
[suspenseful music continues]
[policeman 1] Go! Double-time!
[policeman 2] Move!
- [hostages screaming]
- Come on! This way!
[suspenseful music continues]
[assailant grunts]
- [hostages sobbing]
- [woman] Don't hurt us!
[suspenseful music continues]
[in English] Espina, stand by
for rendezvous with Agent Reyes.
Be alert.
- There's a guard outside the ER.
- [radio static]
[music turns tense]
[in English] In position.
- [in English] I'm in position.
- [static crackles]
[keyboard clacking]
[breathing heavily]
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [Guard] Boss!
The cameras are on a loop!
They hacked the CCTV system!
They must be inside already!
- [rapid gunfire]
- [guard grunts]
They tricked us.
[body thuds]
[unsettling music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music playing]
You bastards!
I'm going to kill everyone!
Everyone!
[yells]
[tense music playing]
[screams]
[music intensifies]
[tense music continues]
I'll take care of him. Get out of here!
- Where are you taking her?!
- Jamilah!
[Axl] Go!
[Jalil] We need to split up.
Lara, where are they?
Agent Reyes, they're heading
to the north wing.
Hey!
[Norhana] Allah! Allah,
please keep Jamilah safe. Allah!
They have another hostage. A Muslim girl.
Jamilah.
- [gunshots]
- [grunts]
Dr. Teresa and I already
treated your brother.
- [Teresa] Just surrender.
- Get up!
[Jovi] Protect yourself.
[Marcus] Face me.
[both grunting]
[Jalil] Freeze!
- [Jalil] Don't hurt her!
- [Axl] I'm going to kill her!
- [blow lands]
- [groans]