[Norhana sobbing] Miss,
do you know Jamilah?
[nurse] She's still inside.
- [Jalil] We need to split up.
- I'll go this way.
[Tommy] Leave me behind and save yourself.
I'm just going to be a burden to you.
[Jovi] I'll come back for you.
Think of your brother!
His condition might get worse!
[Lara] I've located Miss Teresa.
[Lara] They have another hostage.
A Muslim girl?
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
- Help!
- [Marcus] I have eyes on one suspect.
[Marcus] He's got Jamilah, a nurse.
[Jalil] Reyes, save that hostage.
I'll save your mother.
[Marcus] Release her. Fight me instead.
[Jalil] Hostage secured.
Your mother is safe.
- [Jamilah shouts]
- [shouts in pain]
[Marcus, in English] Hostage clear.
Target secured.
Are you okay?
I'm just making sure that you're safe.
[tense music playing]
[Marcus] Thank you. You saved my mother.
[Jalil] Thank you, too. For saving my--
For saving our fellow Muslim.
Thank you, Reyes.
[mysterious theme music playing]
[morose music playing]
Jamilah.
- Gracia.
- Are you okay?
I need to check the patients in bed 6.
If you need someone
to talk to, I'm right here.
Thank you.
Go check on the patients.
The life of a nurse.
No trauma leave.
We dreamed of this, remember?
You should go. Thanks again.
[sighs]
[morose music continues]
Jamliah, how are you holding up?
Did those jerks hurt you?
Um…
I'm fine.
[breathes deeply]
Your son came to my rescue.
That's good to know.
Honestly, Doctor…
I'm still angry with your son.
[melancholic music playing]
I don't know how I can forgive him
after what he did to my father.
Including our neighbors.
[exhales heavily]
‪[deep breath]
But…
I know I should be grateful to him.
Because he saved my life.
I understand you, Jamilah.
We all have a mission in life.
For us, our mission is to save lives.
Meanwhile, my son's mission is…
to fulfill his duty.
It just so happened
that it was the mission
he was given at the time.
[camera shutter clicking]
However, he suspects
that something had gone wrong.
That someone had sabotaged them,
which was why everything
turned into chaos.
‪[Teresa inhales]
Believe me, Jamilah.
My son wants to correct his mistake.
- There she is!
- Jamilah! Jamilah!
- [Norhana] Jamilah!
- Auntie!
[sobs] Jamilah!
- [Jamilah] Auntie!
- [Norhana] Jamilah!
- Jamilah…
- Oh, Auntie…
[Norhana] I'm so glad you're safe!
[Norhana sobbing]
[softly] Are you okay? [sniffs]
- Uncle.
- [Omar] Jamilah…
I'd never forgive myself
if something happened to you.
How could I ever explain that
to your brother?
‪[dramatic whoosh]
[sighs] Uncle Omar, you don't have
to worry anymore.
The important thing is that I'm safe.
That we've been reunited.
That I'm going home in one piece.
‪[dramatic sting]
[morose music continues]
- [officer 1] Go away!
- [reporter] One question, Agent Reyes!
[reporter] Let me ask
Agent Reyes this one time!
[crowd clamoring]
[reporter] I just have one question!
- [officer] You have to go now!
- [reporter] He's here! Agent Reyes!
- Agent Reyes, a question!
- [tense music playing]
Don't you ever lay
a finger on our brother!
Or else, we'll make all of you pay!
- [overlapping chatter]
- [camera shutter clicking]
[reporter] Agent Reyes!
Agent Reyes, congratulations
on the successful rescue.
What was the key to this operation?
- [Azuelo] Agent Reyes!
- [officer 2] Make way!
[in English] Agent Reyes, congratulations!
[in English] Team Task Force Alpha
is back!
[crowd whooping, clapping]
[music becomes unsettling]
Our priority is the safety of civilians.
Our mission was a success
thanks to the coordinated efforts
of the entire team.
As of this moment, everyone is safe
and in the care of medical professionals.
Agent Reyes, how were
you able to execute--
[Azuelo] Agent Reyes.
I'll take it over from here.
- [tense music playing]
- [camera shutter clicking]
First of all,
I would like to personally commend
the new Task Force Alpha.
[crowd clapping, whooping]
And under my supervision,
it has been proven once again
that they are the best
and truly reliable, above all.
- [tense music continues]
- [whooping, clapping]
If not for them,
our streets would be overrun
by heartless criminals,
like these two!
- [woman] That's right!
- [man] Lock them up!
- [woman] Put them behind bars!
- [man] Make an example out of them!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Azuelo] This was a successful operation
by Task Force Alpha
under the SID.
After a long time,
we finally captured the Rosales Brothers.
- [crowd whooping, clapping]
- [camera shutter clicking]
They will lead us
to the syndicates that supply them
with high-powered firearms.
[gunshot]
- [crowd screaming]
- [officer] Get down!
[gunshot]
- [thrilling music playing]
- [crowd screaming]
[crowd clamoring]
[officer shouts]
- [officer 1] Stay out of sight!
- [officer 2] Keep your heads low!
[crowd clamoring]
‪[music intensifying]
‪[tense dramatic music playing]
[gun cocking]
- [overlapping shouting]
- [suspenseful music playing]
Stay low!
[in English] Stand down!
- [Lara] Please, calm down!
- [Marcus, in English] Take cover!
‪[tinkling]
[cartridge case clinks]
[in English] Search the area.
Look for evidence.
Shell casings, anything at all.
[in English] Move!
[thrilling music playing]
Go check there.
‪[suspenseful music playing]
[grunting and groaning]
[tense music playing]
‪[grunting and groaning]
‪[Lara grunts]
[thug grunts]
- [sighs]
- [neck cracks]
‪[grunting and groaning]
[panting]
‪[heaves]
‪[sharp inhale]
[sinister music playing]
Montes.
What are you doing?
Tying my shoes. Obviously.
Can’t a man tie his shoes peacefully?
What? You miss me already?
[tense music playing]
[Marcus] They killed the suspects,
so they couldn't reveal
where they got their weapons.
That means…
[tense music continues]
[in English] Listen up, all units.
[in English] Target priority.
Protect the remaining suspect
in the hospital.
Tommy Rosales is in danger.
I repeat, protect the suspect.
[in English] Roger, sir.
[in English] Copy.
Come on.
[tense music continues]
[in English] Move!
‪[sniffles]
[whistles]
[Tommy grunts, exhales]
‪[music intensifies]
‪[twinkle]
[ominous music playing]
- Hey!
- Back off!
- [officer] Take it easy, sir!
- [Tommy sobs]
Sir, the suspect is secure.
All threats have been neutralized.
We're good.
- [officer] Sir, please calm down.
- Sir!
- [officer] Put the gun down.
- [people clamoring]
[tense music playing]
- [gun fires]
- [people screaming]
[officer] What happened?!
- [screaming continues]
- [tense music continues]
- [people clamoring]
- [sinister music playing]
[clamoring continues]
[gasps]
[Marcus] What happened?!
Sir, he grabbed my gun and shot himself!
- [man] Why would he do that?
- [people clamoring]
[sinister music continues]
- [man screams]
- [people clamoring]
[woman speaks indistinctly]
‪[man gasps]
What's up, brother?
Bro, I need to speak to the other suspect.
[in English] Copy, sir.
- [cop] Sir!
- [Felix] Step outside.
‪[Felix sighs]
Did you hear the gunshots outside?
Those were for your brothers.
Mm?
Now, I'll give you a choice.
Either I kill your mother…
or you kill yourself.
Hmm?
[grim music playing]
Choose wisely, kid.
‪[Felix chuckles]
[dramatic sting]
‪[dramatic sting]
[TV reporter] Breaking news.
We have confirmation
that Tommy Rosales is dead
following an apparent
self-inflicted gunshot wound.
This happened moments after
an unidentified suspect
shot and killed his two brothers,
Axl and Jovi Rosales.
No! [sobs]
Axl!
Jovi! Tommy!
[morose music playing]
[wailing]
‪[tense morose music playing]
[mother] My children! [wails]
[in English] This is outrageous!
Those crooks were supposed
to lead us to their supplier
of high-powered firearms!
And now you're telling me
that their brother,
the only surviving suspect,
- committed suicide?!
- [slams table]
[in English] Goddammit!
Sir, this means they fear
the syndicate more than us.
[in English] Sir, I'm sorry.
I don't know how this happened.
I should've seen it coming.
The brothers were calculated.
Sir, there is no one to blame.
[in English] That's the point!
It is unacceptable
that they outsmarted us!
You should've been one step ahead of them!
With all due respect, sir,
we shouldn't have faced
the press right away.
What did you say?
- Are you asking to be suspended?!
- What do you think, sir?
[unsettling music playing]
Have you learned nothing?
We keep messing up.
We're a laughing stock!
All our hard work is for nothing.
Is this all just damage control for TFA?
Our friends died.
We replaced them!
But why has nothing changed?
Suarez, enough.
- Enough.
- [Felix] Don't worry.
We'll get back at them eventually.
This isn't over.
Right?!
Right?
‪[music intensifies]
- Sir.
- [door slams shut]
‪[door creaks open]
Sir, the sniper left this behind.
I hid it before someone could find it.
Don't worry.
No one saw me.
[in English] Good job.
Sir, why was the leader
of those crooks killed?
What's going on?
[tense music playing]
Why are you asking so many questions?
It's none of your business.
Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
[tapping]
[music intensifies]
[Ahmad] This bank robbery
that escalated into a hostage situation,
it wasn't a random incident.
Those brothers wouldn’t
have been silenced like that
if this was just an ordinary crime.
Oh my goodness, Mama Loi.
This is too much to handle.
- [Loi] What happened, Mother?
- It's the NLEA and SID, Mama Loi!
There was a hostage-taking
at S. Trinidad Hospital!
- It's all over social media!
- [brooding music playing]
- [man] Right?
- It was that group…
- Metal-13!
- [man] Metal-13.
They may be ordinary criminals,
but they were carrying
high-powered weapons!
- Oh my gosh!
- [man] Yes!
They had big guns?
Everyone thought
the mission was a success,
but it was far from over.
Maybe Task Force Alpha's
so-called rescue mission
was just staged.
Someone is definitely
pulling the strings here!
Our country is still in danger
because of the spread
of these high-powered firearms
that we still don't know
where they're coming from.
- So many people have died.
- [woman] Yes.
Those people have families,
for Christ's sake!
I wonder, who shot those crooks?
Why were they killed?
Are you sure you can
handle this, Task Force Alpha?
Just resign if you can't!
Wherever these weapons are coming from,
the authorities must trace them
and put a stop to it.
Our countrymen have suffered enough!
- Amen to that!
- Amen!
I hope both parties can reconcile.
- Then be the mediator!
- No, I don't want to!
- [notification sound]
- [netizen 1] It was staged!
Those hostage-takers
were killed to hide the truth.
This has a cover-up written all over it!
[notification sound]
[netizen 2] Are we really safe?
High-powered guns in the hands of crooks?
A sniper in front of a hospital?
What the hell, Philippines?
[in English] Goddammit!
‪[thudding]
[notification sound]
[netizen 3] Task Force Alpha?
More like Task Force Idiots.
[netizen 4] TFA is just a PR stunt.
We need real protection.
Not just photos and poses.
[netizen 5] Photos like this? [laughs]
[grunts angrily]
- [tense music playing]
- [huffs]
‪[music intensifies]
[Ahmad] Someone is orchestrating this.
They’re deliberately causing trouble.
Is this a destabilization attempt?
[Marcus] A lot of people have died!
And more will die
if you don’t tell me the truth.
I don't have anything to do with that!
I'm not a part of the syndicate!
[Marcus] I thought you wanted
to get justice for your people.
This is your chance.
Tell me what you know.
[Felix] Madam Lara is confused.
She hasn't realized
that the General is right.
[boy] Why won't you leave me alone?!
[man] You're an embarrassment! Go home!
[Felix] He will learn to love us one day.
I cleaned it already. Are we good?
[in English] Shut up! Get out of my face!
I'm just doing my job, Lara.
Don't forget how important our mission is.
[reporter] There are strict policies
on gun ownership.
So who is supplying these weapons?
[woman] Crime is on the rise today.
[Norhana] I pray that Jalil
and Jamilah are always safe.