- [Felix] I know who did this.
- Who?!
[Felix] Datu Rahman's son.
[Lara] Find Datu Rahman!
I don't care how you do it.
- [in English] Bring him back to me!
- I'll take care of it.
[Norhana] Jalil, be careful, okay?
The people chasing you are dangerous.
[Jalil] Don't worry.
Everything will be okay.
The truth will soon come out.
Father, let's go back to the island.
Not yet, my dear.
[Datu Rahman] We still
have unfinished business here.
- Where is it?
- The CCTV cameras were deactivated.
Someone from the inside did this.
[Manuel] I will make sure
that our efforts won't go to waste.
[Jalil] Do you know who did this to you?
How many times did they abduct you?
Father, what do they need from you?
[Datu Rahman] My silence
will protect my children.
What happened?
One of the men who abducted
Datu Rahman took him.
Was he wearing a mask?
It could be Jalil Abubakar.
[Ahmad] You can't tell anyone
the true identity of Major Allan Espina,
not even your friend, Marcus.
You need to help Allan Espina.
You need to help Jalil in his mission.
Can I count on you, brother?
[mysterious theme music playing]
I'm sorry, buddy.
I couldn't rescue Datu Rahman.
There's nothing we can do about it, buddy.
They found the safe house.
[Marcus sighs]
I suppose it's better
that it's Datu Rahman's son who took him.
That means Datu Rahman's alive.
And the time will come
when we get the information
that he is hiding.
[knocking on door]
The food is ready, Father.
We should eat while it's still hot.
Alright.
[Jamila] Come on.
[gentle music playing]
I still can't believe
that you're with us, Father.
Jalil kept his promise.
[Jamilah chuckles]
This will all soon pass, Jamilah.
[In Tausug] Thank you, Omar and Norhana.
I will forever be in debt to you
for taking care of my children.
That's nothing, Rahman. We're family!
Jamilah is my niece,
and Jalil is my nephew.
Exactly, Datu. No matter what happens…
we are family.
- Let's eat.
- [In Tausug] Thank you.
- [Norhana] Let's eat.
- Uncle, let's eat!
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Hm!
- It's Jalil. He wants to talk to you.
- [Datu Rahman] Hm?
[music turns unsettling]
I sent you something.
Take a good look at it.
I know he's Datu Rahman's son.
I know this guy.
I've encountered him before.
- [Jalil] Surrender!
- What do you take us for?!
You think you can stop us?!
We are so much bigger than you think!
You don't know anything!
The real fight hasn't started yet!
He's Jalil Abubakar.
A member of CDSU.
[Arthur] From what I know,
he's still teaching recruits
in various parts of Mindanao.
[unsettling music continues]
I've confirmed it, sir.
This is the bullet shell I've retrieved.
A different group caused the riot
on the island that night.
These are also the photos
of the smuggled firearms
buried in a mountain.
Sir, Datu Rahman is telling the truth.
They're not the ones
smuggling those firearms.
They just hide it,
so syndicates can't use it.
Sir… Datu Rahman is innocent.
[pensive music playing]
That means, sir,
someone planted the intel we had.
Colonel Del Mundo
was an accomplice to this.
He was the one who gave us the wrong intel
about Datu Rahman.
That's why he was killed.
He was silenced.
[pensive music playing]
The question is…
Who does he work for?
[pensive music continues]
I confirmed another thing
on the island, sir.
[smuggler] You'll confiscate our firearms?
You think you'll succeed
when our allies are also from your agency?
They even have high ranks within the NLEA.
So, no matter how many times
you confiscate these firearms,
these will eventually come back to us.
[Marcus] Those words
came directly from the mouth
of the high-ranking smuggler
I fought on the island.
Their protector is from NLEA.
Someone with a high-ranking position.
That's why these smugglers are brave.
Now, I don't know if…
they have other allies outside of NLEA,
but I'm sure, sir,
there is a wolf in sheep's clothing
on our side of the fence.
[pensive music continues]
There's something else
you should know, sir.
You're not done yet?
Sir…
I'm the one who took Datu Rahman
from the Zylverix building.
I only saved him from the people
who abducted him.
Agent Reyes!
[grunts]
Where is Datu Rahman now?
Where is he?!
While I was on the island,
he was tracked down by his kidnappers.
[in English] Goddammit, Reyes!
But he was saved…
by his son.
It's Jalil Abubakar.
How--
He's also a fugitive.
Both of them need to be arrested!
That's why we need to know
where they are, sir.
They're certainly both in danger.
[Azuelo sighs]
Agent Reyes.
I'm not sure anymore
if I should be mad at you or applaud you!
You've lied to me, Agent Reyes!
You've concealed and hidden
very important information from me!
Now, give me one good reason
- why I shouldn't suspend you right now!
- [loud thud]
I'm the only one you can count on, sir.
I'm the only one who can
help you solve this case.
What we really need to know, sir…
Who is the mastermind behind all of this?
‪[dramatic sting]
[music turns suspenseful]
[tense music playing]
[Marcus] Edrick.
- Anything?
- [Edrick] Sir. Did you see that?
There is no trace
of the crazy person you told me.
Check it thoroughly.
[Edrick] Sir, I was just wondering…
how that happened.
[breathes deeply]
How are they so strong?
How did they clean up
the traces of killings?
[sighs]
[scream echoes] Why?!
Hey! You're being loud again.
Calm down. Be quiet.
If someone hears you,
you'll be asking why in heaven.
I'm sorry, sir. I was just joking.
Sir. They do seem pretty tough.
Be careful, sir.
[tense music continues]
[music turns somber]
[Azuelo] These problems
really came up now.
Right before I'm about to be
a General and retire soon.
But I can't just walk away from all this.
I can't leave NLEA and SID rotting.
If I leave now,
many more people will get hurt.
That bastard Reyes.
I was supposed to be at peace.
Why do you have to tell me all of that?
Why do I have to know all this?!
- [grunts angrily]
- [objects falling]
[phone vibrating]
Sweetheart, what is it?
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
Our son…
got into a fight at school.
What?
Come on.
[Azuelo] Kyle.
Why did you get into a fight?
I've already got a lot of problems,
son, and now this?
My classmates pissed me off.
[breathing sharply] They kept annoying me.
That's not enough reason
to get into a fight.
Just ignore them.
[Kyle] How can I ignore them?
- They were calling you names!
- [tense music playing]
They said you're a no-good cop.
How can I just ignore that? [sobs]
They said Datu Rahman got away
because you're inept…
and incompetent…
[sobbing, sniffling]
…and that you're not smart.
- [music turns somber]
- [sobbing]
I can't just ignore that, Pa.
‪[Kyle sobbing]
[Kyle] I can't just let them say
those hurtful words against you.
But that's not true, Pa, right?
You're great.
You're smart.
And above all, Pa,
you have integrity.
[Kyle] That's why I look up to you.
So I'd punch everyone
who spreads lies about you.
[exhales deeply]
Okay, son.
We'll talk again when I come home, okay?
[Kyle sobbing]
[pensive music playing]
[Azuelo] My son thinks of me highly.
[exhales]
[line ringing]
Reyes.
Come here right now.
We have something to do.
[in English] Goddammit.
[music intensifies, concludes]
Check the CCTV footage. Around 10 p.m.
The possible exits in the shipyard.
Copy, ma'am.
Ma'am, what exactly are we looking for?
[scoffs] Obviously, I don't know either.
That's why I asked you to check it.
Check all the possible exits
because I want to know the movement there.
Ma'am, where do we start looking?
A lot of cars are passing by.
We don't have any reference
because you had the CCTVs disabled
in the shipyard.
[tense mysterious music playing]
Okay, okay.
No more questions. I'll just shut up.
- T-This car. Follow it.
- [Buster] Copy, ma'am.
[Lara huffing]
Hey, Buster.
No one must know about this, alright?
[in English] This is top secret.
My mission would be compromised
if someone found out.
- [in English] Do you understand?
- [in English] Understood, ma'am.
- [gloomy music playing]
- [digital chiming]
Where's Buster?
Uh, he just went on a lunch break, sir.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
You're new here, aren't you?
[chuckles softly] Yes, sir.
I'm your new IT specialist here, sir.
I'm Ethan, sir. Nice to meet you.
Okay.
Now, since you're new here,
I'd like you to make a good impression.
Do you see this?
Find this guy in the CDSU database.
Jalil Abubakar.
Get to work.
[suspenseful music playing]
When Mister Omar asks, I can't say no.
Besides… [scoffs]
Look, it's easy peasy.
[Ethan exhales deeply]
What's wrong?
- Uh, nothing, sir. It's--
- Do you know him?
No. I just really wish I had
a beard like his.
Let me find him now, sir.
[suspenseful music continues]
[Ethan] "Jalil Abubakar."
"Jalil Abubakar."
One more time.
Sir, the CDSU database shows
no record of Jalil Abubakar.
Try it again!
- Alright, sir.
- Hurry up.
"Jalil Abubakar."
[suspenseful music continues]
No luck, sir.
‪[dramatic sting]
[knocking on door]
[unsettling music playing]
Madam. I've identified
the son of Datu Rahman.
His name is Jalil Abubakar.
I had the CDSU's new hire
run a background check.
It's strange.
When I checked his files,
I couldn't find anything.
No results came up.
It's like he doesn't exist at all.
‪[dramatic sting]
[music intensifying]
How's that possible?
It was deliberately erased.
Someone must be helping him
so that he can move around freely.
We need to find him.
[in English] Definitely, madam.
What are you implying?
That there is a traitor in this agency?
[tense music playing]
At first, I did not want to believe it.
But there is evidence.
All I want is for them to be caught
before the NLEA and the SID
are completely destroyed.
[in English] These are
serious accusations.
We have confirmed
Datu Rahman's statement is accurate.
Colonel Del Mundo's intelligence report
was intended to set him up!
Then, conveniently,
he committed suicide
before he could be questioned.
[in English] Colonel Del Mundo
was a very good police officer!
Don't trample on his name!
He must have had the support
of someone powerful!
[sniffles]
That's why he did what he did!
And most likely, he still
has accomplices in this very room!
‪[dramatic stinging]
[in English] How dare you!
You'll create enemies
with your accusations.
Both of you!
[suspenseful music playing]
To hell with that!
I am about to retire.
I will make sure the SID
and the NLEA are left in good order
when I leave!
[dramatic music playing]
‪[dramatic stinging]
[Usman] I can't lie to Marcus.
Why don't we just tell him the truth?
After all, you both want the same thing.
He might not be in cahoots
with the bastards who murdered our people.
[Jalil] Still, he was manipulated by them.
I can't trust him.
[Datu Rahman] My name is Rahman Abubakar.
There's no truth to the accusations
they're making against me.
Their weapons are being dropped
into the sea near our island.
Agent Marcus Reyes,
the people responsible for this
might be in the NLEA.
Do you really want to ruin
the reputation of the NLEA and the SID?!
[in English] I feel like
I'm losing control of everything!
Reyes is under my command!
[Azuelo, in English]
You are overstepping boundaries!
[Manuel] The worse
the crimes being committed,
the more people will lose
confidence in the government.
Power will soon be in our hands.