=Mountains=
=Episode 24=
The immortal guards the horse,
traveling far and wide.
It roams freely across the three realms.
Clad in armor
and wielding a sturdy sword,
it strides swiftly through all lands.
Zhang Beichen,
how much longer do you need?
Guard the formation.
Protect the banners.
It's merely a Demon-Subduing Formation.
There's no way it can trap me.
My thirteenth needle
strikes straight into the throat.
Let go, Duan.
I must help Chen.
The thirteenth needle
can stimulate one's potential, right?
Duan,
the thirteenth needle
may stimulate one's potential,
but
it'll make you forget everything.
Zhang Beichen.
Don't forget our promise.
If I had a choice,
I'd like to
meet you again.
It would be like
two strangers catching
a glimpse of each other in the crowd,
and many stories could happen
between them.
Will you come back?
I will.
I'll be back when you wake up.
Death.
What does it feel like?
You'll never see the person
you want to see.
That means I can never see you again.
What are you doing, Little Tag-along?
I don't want you to get hurt.
My name is Duan Siyan,
not Little Tag-along.
This is something very important to me.
I'll pawn it to you.
♪Youth is always fearless♪
Keep it safe.
I'll get it back.
Trusting someone
can be easy.
Duan Siyan!
Zhang Beichen!
♪Under dim, lonely lights,
the story of love and hates is written♪
♪Everyone scatters,
leaving only the storyteller behind♪
The last time I saw you smile
was when you were Little Tag-along.
If you like her,
why didn't you tell her?
Liking someone
makes one feel inferior.
If I were her,
I'd definitely let him know.
♪Walk the mountains, asking directions,
divining fortune or misfortune♪
I didn't expect you to have this.
I won't let you all die.
None of you will die.
♪Ride away, a lone figure
through countless waves♪
♪Mountains upon mountains♪
♪In this mortal world,
drifting into dreams♪
Break!
♪I wish to ride the western wind♪
♪But where does the wind go,
leaving me empty-handed?♪
Give it back to me.
Sir, we've found the Fusang wood.
What's the next plan?
Zhang Beichen has accomplished the task.
Next,
the knife lender prophet.
What about Ms. Duan?
She's useless now.
Give it up.
(Three months later)
Old man, here's the roasted chicken.
Roasted chicken!
It smells great.
The old ghost doctor sent a letter.
He said Ling'er's condition
has improved a lot.
But
I haven't heard any news
from Ma Tianhong for a while.
Not long ago,
he told me he wanted to live longer.
So, I gave him Grandfather's Twelve
Mountain-Turning Talisman Technique
I guess
he's probably out there
searching the mountains
for the rare herbs to prolong his life.
Is Zhang Tianzheng in?
Who are you?
We're here to collect the knives.
To find out more,
stay tuned for next time.
Shan, what do you think about the story?
It was great.
Then,
what will happen to him?
Who's the knife lender?
Why?
Are you curious?
One-month salary.
Can we not talk about money?
In that case,
you will
find out next time.
You!
Hey!
You! Jeez!
(Mountain Roamer Tales)
♪Walk the mountains, asking directions,
divining fortune or misfortune♪
♪Gazing afar, like a fleeting glimpse
of a youthful elegance♪
♪Advance or retreat, even in despair,
one should not yield♪
♪Ride away, a lone figure
through countless waves♪
♪Mountains upon mountains♪
♪In this mortal world,
drifting into dreams♪
♪The human heart is too hazy to discern♪
♪I wish to ride the western wind♪
♪But where does the wind go,
leaving me empty-handed?♪
♪Chasing the wind,
the moon, and the stars♪
♪Listening to the spirits
of the plants and trees♪
♪All the joys and sorrows
of union and parting♪
♪Resonate with me in the wind♪
♪Alone, I carve out my world♪
♪Looking back at the road traveled♪
♪By your side,
the passing of time is fearless♪
♪Facing crossroads, the wind whispers
a kiss without asking love or hate♪
♪A sorrowful song plays,
a healer's skillful touch♪
♪Never forgetting the word "compassion"♪
♪That youth,
with a few loyal friends by his side♪
♪Carrying liquor,
the heart still burns hot♪
♪The world bears witness
to my sincerity♪
♪In the mortal world,
drifting into dreams♪
♪The human heart is too hazy to discern♪
♪I wish to ride the western wind♪
♪But where does the wind go,
leaving me empty-handed?♪
♪Holding the same fervent hopes♪
♪For nameless souls♪
♪With light in my heart,
I fear no darkness♪
♪Restoring the purity
of mountains and rivers to the world♪
♪Hand in hand, looking up to the dawn♪
♪Looking far into the road ahead♪
♪Together through this passage of time,
what is there to fear?♪
♪Chasing the wind,
the moon, and the stars♪
♪Listening to the spirits
of the plants and trees♪
♪All the unions and partings,
the joys and sorrows♪
♪Resonate with me in the wind♪
♪Alone, I carve out my world♪
♪Looking back at the road traveled♪
♪By your side,
the passing of time is fearless♪