=Mountains=
=Episode 11=
The year a plague struck the village,
my sister was the only physician there.
Lian,
I'm so uncomfortable.
He, it's all right.
We'll be fine.
Even though she was sick, she went
into the mountains to gather herbs
to search for a cure.
She miraculously recovered
after returning from the mountain.
To save me,
my sister decided to use
her own blood as a remedy.
Surprisingly, my condition improved.
Everyone said
my sister encountered
the mountain spirit in the mountains,
and her blood could cure diseases.
Hence, they began demanding her blood,
like leeches.
Thank you.
One bowl after another.
Endlessly.
Blood!
My brother is still young.
Physician Mu.
I must stop doing this.
Please give us a bit more, Physician Mu.
We're begging you, Physician Mu.
Please, Physician Mu.
Please help me, Physician Mu.
I beg of you, Physician Mu.
Physician Mu.
My sister had no more
blood left to give.
But he,
as the village head,
led a mob
to storm into my house
and took my sister away.
Hurry!
Take her away!
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- He.
Go.
He!
Lian!
To justify their actions,
they actually accused my sister
of being a cursed thing.
Just how selfish can one be?
You drained my sister's blood
for your benefit.
You're murderers!
But Lan...
She truly loved you!
I didn't love her!
I've been hiding my identity for years
just for this revenge.
She was nothing
but a tool for my vengeance.
As for you,
I'll drain every single drop of blood
from you.
An eye
for an eye.
And you too.
I told you to leave,
but you didn't.
You helped these murderers.
Now
you can't blame me.
Chen He,
mend your ways.
I have no way back.
Protect the villagers!
All right!
The sun rises!
Sir.
Corpse Feng.
Chen He, you...
Sir,
do you think I was wrong?
Don't you think they should be punished?
If I'm wrong,
will my sister blame me?
Chen He,
you're not wrong.
It's the world.
It's the people.
Thank you.
Chen He.
I'm sorry.
I deceived you.
I came to Lianhua Abode for my revenge.
If only Corpse Feng
could bring you back to life.
Lian,
I'm coming for you.
Can love
be a tool for vengeance?
What are you talking about?
Love is love.
Hate is hate.
The moment he used Chen Lan's love,
there was no love in him.
Chen, I feel so sorry for them.
If times could rewind,
would they have lived a happy life?
Fate brings people together
and separates them when it ends.
But there's no ifs.
Hold on.
Hold out your hands.
Keep it safe.
I'll get it back.
Sir,
did you really search for it?
That's very important.
Miss,
I almost turned the place
upside down,
but I couldn't see the Phoenix Gall
you talked about.
I only found Mu Lian's body
in the cave.
It shouldn't be.
The Phoenix Gall and the Corpse Feng
share a symbiotic relationship.
How could it not be in Mu Lian's body?
I remember now.
I saw a cripple in the mountains.
He lives somewhere near the mass grave.
A cripple?
Again?
What's wrong with that?
I'm not sure yet,
but I have a feeling
this person has been around us.
I suspect
there's a connection
between Chen He's Corpse Feng
and that person.
What should we do now?
Without the Phoenix Gall,
your grandfather's condition
can't be cured.
Young chap,
there's something
I've been meaning to ask.
What has happened to your grandfather?
Why does he need the Phoenix Gall?
The Phoenix Gall belonged
to his grandfather in the first place.
As far as I'm concerned,
only Zhang Tianzheng
ever owned it.
You knew my grandfather?
How much do you know
about the Jinwu Incident?
Hold on.
I knew him,
but we weren't close.
Back then,
he asked me to go somewhere with him.
On that day,
I was too drunk
to go,
so I sent my junior brother.
However, that was the last
I saw of him.
Afterward,
I quit drinking
and came here
to look after his mother.
Where were you planning to go
and what for?
What for?
I don't know.
But I heard
the place was called
Tang Valley.
Tang Valley?
Sir,
can you take us there?
Forget it.
I'm not young anymore.
Besides,
I have to look after my mother.
In that case,
let's leave.
Wait.
Maybe
Ma of the North
could help you.
Ma of the North?
(Mount Lianhua)
(Mihe Town)
♪Walk the mountains, asking directions
,divining fortune or misfortune♪
♪Gazing afar, like a fleeting glimpse
of a youthful elegance♪
♪Advance or retreat, even in despair,
one should not yield♪
♪Ride away, a lone figure
through countless waves♪
♪Mountains upon mountains♪
♪In this mortal world,
drifting into dreams♪
♪The human heart is too hazy to discern♪
♪I wish to ride the western wind♪
♪But where does the wind go,
leaving me empty-handed?♪
♪Chasing the wind,
the moon, and the stars♪
♪Listening to the spirits
of the plants and trees♪
♪All the joys and sorrows
of union and parting♪
♪Resonate with me in the wind♪
♪Alone, I carve out my world♪
♪Looking back at the road traveled♪
♪By your side,
the passing of time is fearless♪
♪Facing crossroads, the wind whispers
a kiss without asking love or hate♪
♪A sorrowful song plays,
a healer's skillful touch♪
♪Never forgetting the word "compassion"♪
♪That youth,
with a few loyal friends by his side♪
♪Carrying liquor,
the heart still burns hot♪
♪The world bears witness
to my sincerity♪
♪In the mortal world,
drifting into dreams♪
♪The human heart is too hazy to discern♪
♪I wish to ride the western wind♪
♪But where does the wind go,
leaving me empty-handed?♪
♪Holding the same fervent hopes♪
♪For nameless souls♪
♪With light in my heart,
I fear no darkness♪
♪Restoring the purity
of mountains and rivers to the world♪
♪Hand in hand, looking up to the dawn♪
♪Looking far into the road ahead♪
♪Together through this passage of time,
what is there to fear?♪
♪Chasing the wind,
the moon, and the stars♪
♪Listening to the spirits
of the plants and trees♪
♪All the unions and partings,
the joys and sorrows♪
♪Resonate with me in the wind♪
♪Alone, I carve out my world♪
♪Looking back at the road traveled♪
♪By your side,
the passing of time is fearless♪