=Mountains=
=Episode 7=
Old man,
time to take your medicine.
Fun! This is fun!
Little Tag-along,
what are you doing?
I saved your life before.
My name is Duan Siyan,
not Little Tag-along.
You remember everything now.
(Mountain Spirit Temple)
I see.
No wonder that tailor
had the ghostly threadworms.
What does it have to do
with this old man?
Because
I'm here to kill him in the first place.
Are you insane?
Why do you want to kill a mad old man?
It seems you don't know
your grandfather well enough.
What are you getting at?
Grandfather,
why are you holding the soup?
Drink this.
Who's there?
Stop chasing.
Do you know that person?
It's none of your business.
But this old man is.
Speak up.
What is going on?
Your grandfather is responsible
for the destruction
of Four Strange Gates
and the Jinwu Rebellion.
He's also the reason I became an orphan.
Grandfather, get up.
He's not the kind of man you said.
That's only your side of the story.
There must be more to it.
It's not up to you
to decide what kind of person
Zhang Tianzheng is.
You said you became an orphan
because of him,
so you want to take revenge.
Fine.
Let me ask you this.
What have you done?
Why were you attacked just now?
No one knows the truth
behind the Jinwu Rebellion,
and you have no evidence to prove
the old man did it.
What do you want, then?
I'm going to find the Phoenix Gall
to cure the old man's madness.
You can confront him later.
Why should I trust you?
This is something very important to me.
You'll keep it for me first.
Not to mention
I saved your life before.
Trusting someone
cab be easy.
All right,
but I'm coming with you.
Beichen.
Um...
Well.
Sun from Black Street
is looking for you.
He said it's something
about your grandfather.
Mr. Sun.
No refunds here.
What refund?
Didn't you call me over?
Oh, it's you.
Why?
Any luck
with the Phoenix Gall?
I told you
the Phoenix Gall
is a rare treasure.
The price of this news
will be high.
I could see that coming.
Go on. Name your price.
It should be at least this figure.
Three silver coins?
Thirty.
Thirty silver coins?
I don't have all day.
Tell us now.
Easy.
Don't be impulsive.
This rifle is pricey.
Mr. Sun,
do you value money more than your life?
Now that your life is at stake,
just tell me.
She's very dangerous.
Shut up.
If you don't want your head
to get blown off,
spill it.
Wait.
Calm down.
All right. I'll tell you.
Ten years ago,
the Phoenix Gall
was last seen
at Mount Lianhua.
Mount Lianhua?
Ten years ago?
Is this source reliable?
Absolutely.
However,
whether or not it's still there
depends on your luck.
No wonder Ling'er went to Lianhua Pond.
She knows the whereabouts
of the Phoenix Gall.
Be... Be careful.
Mr. Sun,
I want to buy my knife back.
Buy your knife back?
Do you even have money?
Hey, you.
Don't put it down.
That's your business,
not mine.
Careful with my rifle.
How much?
Ten silver coins.
Luckily, the case is resolved,
and I have some rewards.
I gave you an extra one silver coin.
One minute.
Give me a minute.
Careful with my rifle.
Hurry!
I found it.
Here you go.
This is the one, right?
The old staff is always
the most reliable.
This notebook
belongs to Mr. Zhang.
It's no use keeping it here.
Take it away.
(Twelve Mountain-Turning
Talisman Technique)
It's Grandfather's Twelve
Mountain-Turning Talisman Technique.
I thought it had gone missing.
So it's been here all along.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Can we leave now?
Yes, let's go.
Wait.
You haven't paid for the rifle.
Pay up.
Pay up, man.
Hurry up.
How much?
Give me all of them.
Are you a robber?
This money isn't enough.
Are you serious?
Still not enough.
Take care. See yourself out.
Please come again.
Shan,
while I'm away,
I'll leave my grandfather to you.
Don't worry.
My reward is gone.
I paid for your clothes
and riffle.
Besides,
the journey is long.
Are we really going to walk there?
Are you a mountain roamer, too?
Miss.
Finally, we've found you.
The family leader
sent us to bring you home.
Tell him
after I'm done with what I want to do,
I'll come home.
But the family head
is worried about you...
I'll be careful.
All right, then.
Hold on.
Do you have money?
Huh?
Money.
Oh, all right.
Leave the car as well.
Huh?
Understood.
You're full of surprises.
Little Tag-along,
can you ask for more
if we run out of money later?
Stop calling me Little Tag-along.
Sure thing, Ms. Duan.
By the way, we're taking their car,
how are they supposed to get back?
(Anyang Town)
(Mount Lianhua)
♪Walk the mountains, asking directions
,divining fortune or misfortune♪
♪Gazing afar, like a fleeting glimpse
of a youthful elegance♪
♪Advance or retreat, even in despair,
one should not yield♪
♪Ride away, a lone figure
through countless waves♪
♪Mountains upon mountains♪
♪In this mortal world,
drifting into dreams♪
♪The human heart is too hazy to discern♪
♪I wish to ride the western wind♪
♪But where does the wind go,
leaving me empty-handed?♪
♪Chasing the wind,
the moon, and the stars♪
♪Listening to the spirits
of the plants and trees♪
♪All the joys and sorrows
of union and parting♪
♪Resonate with me in the wind♪
♪Alone, I carve out my world♪
♪Looking back at the road traveled♪
♪By your side,
the passing of time is fearless♪
♪Facing crossroads, the wind whispers
a kiss without asking love or hate♪
♪A sorrowful song plays,
a healer's skillful touch♪
♪Never forgetting the word "compassion"♪
♪That youth,
with a few loyal friends by his side♪
♪Carrying liquor,
the heart still burns hot♪
♪The world bears witness
to my sincerity♪
♪In the mortal world,
drifting into dreams♪
♪The human heart is too hazy to discern♪
♪I wish to ride the western wind♪
♪But where does the wind go,
leaving me empty-handed?♪
♪Holding the same fervent hopes♪
♪For nameless souls♪
♪With light in my heart,
I fear no darkness♪
♪Restoring the purity
of mountains and rivers to the world♪
♪Hand in hand, looking up to the dawn♪
♪Looking far into the road ahead♪
♪Together through this passage of time,
what is there to fear?♪
♪Chasing the wind,
the moon, and the stars♪
♪Listening to the spirits
of the plants and trees♪
♪All the unions and partings,
the joys and sorrows♪
♪Resonate with me in the wind♪
♪Alone, I carve out my world♪
♪Looking back at the road traveled♪
♪By your side,
the passing of time is fearless♪