=Mountains=
=Episode 6=
Yue Xiang.
Yue...
How could you do that?
Zixuan.
Trust me.
I didn't do that.
They did.
They bullied me.
Please believe me,
Zixuan.
I can't believe you just said that.
Zixuan,
please believe me.
Yue Xiang,
do you believe me?
Yue Xiang.
(I wanted to take Li Juntao
down with me)
(but I didn't expect...)
Listen,
Guo Zixuan.
I've already done what you asked for.
Can't you even get me
a position now?
It's not that.
Juntao,
I only wanted you to ruin
her reputation,
I never wanted her to die.
You were saying otherwise
when you wanted to
get rid of that trollop.
Now that she's dead,
and you're trying to deny it?
No, I'm not.
She killed herself.
It had nothing to do with us.
I'll tell Xiuzhi about your request.
You're shameless.
Zixuan,
is that true?
No.
Don't listen to him.
I didn't do that.
Still denying it?
I'll send you to meet Yue Xiang.
Zixuan!
Ghostly threadworms?
So those weren't hair.
They were the bodies
of ghost threadworms.
Arrest him.
Yes.
Don't go!
Today, you'll witness
my wedding with Yue Xiang.
Father.
- Father.
- Step back. Hurry.
Move the injured to the side.
Step back, all of you.
Guo Zixuan must die.
You weren't...
Is anyone here?
Little Tag-along.
What are you doing?
I don't want you to get hurt.
He taught me to let go of hatred,
to stop blaming others,
to change myself.
Do you believe me?
♪Bow to thank my audience♪
To change my attitude,
to not dwell on the past,
To free myself from the bitterness,
to awaken sooner, and to cherish the marriage.
♪No one has called for a performance
since then♪
♪Washing away the old makeup at night♪
♪With fewer people, good things
encounter more obstacles♪
♪A pretty face grows old,
a sweet dream won't last♪
♪Heartless performers stir up madness♪
♪Singing this incomplete verse alone♪
Shan,
you can brag about the shot a lot.
I...
I'm the greatest detective in Anyang.
In this world,
the one with love cannot love,
- It's all right.
- while the one who has it destroys it.
If he loved Yue Xiang that much,
why didn't he marry her?
It's not that he didn't want to,
but he couldn't.
(Yue Xiang)
(Sorry,)
(if I had expressed my feelings
for you,)
(you wouldn't have died, would you?)
Because he was born impotent.
Poor him.
Exactly.
Except for him,
probably no one believed Yue Xiang.
Trusting someone
can be easy.
By the way,
why did he suddenly become so powerful?
It's the ghostly threadworms.
They gave one
a power surge in a short time.
They are a very poisonous kind
of parasite.
After a long period of parasitism,
ghostly threadworms
breed in large numbers
and form thread-like shapes, like hair
enveloping the host until they die.
Burning ghostly threadworms' bodies
produce thick smoke.
If absorbed,
it causes illusions.
We encountered
the ghost marriage procession
in the mountains a few days ago
because of that?
Maybe.
But why did he have such a thing?
Is Little Tag-along's situation
caused by this as well?
It consists of both mother
and child worms.
The ones in Little Tag-along's body
might be the larvae.
They can only control her behavior.
The toxin isn't strong.
However,
if the mother worm dies,
the larvae shouldn't survive.
Help her.
How?
All living beings
with Yin and Yang coexist,
the counterpart
to ghostly threadworms should be
Blood Spirit Grass.
Blood Spirit Grass can save her.
- Blood Spirit Grass?
Where is the Blood Spirit Grass?
I have it.
Give it to me.
Rest well.
I'll take care of the old man.
Old man,
time to take your medicine.
♪Walk the mountains, asking directions
,divining fortune or misfortune♪
♪Gazing afar, like a fleeting glimpse
of a youthful elegance♪
♪Advance or retreat, even in despair,
one should not yield♪
♪Ride away, a lone figure
through countless waves♪
♪Mountains upon mountains♪
♪In this mortal world,
drifting into dreams♪
♪The human heart is too hazy to discern♪
♪I wish to ride the western wind♪
♪But where does the wind go,
leaving me empty-handed?♪
♪Chasing the wind,
the moon, and the stars♪
♪Listening to the spirits
of the plants and trees♪
♪All the joys and sorrows
of union and parting♪
♪Resonate with me in the wind♪
♪Alone, I carve out my world♪
♪Looking back at the road traveled♪
♪By your side,
the passing of time is fearless♪
♪Facing crossroads, the wind whispers
a kiss without asking love or hate♪
♪A sorrowful song plays,
a healer's skillful touch♪
♪Never forgetting the word "compassion"♪
♪That youth,
with a few loyal friends by his side♪
♪Carrying liquor,
the heart still burns hot♪
♪The world bears witness
to my sincerity♪
♪In the mortal world,
drifting into dreams♪
♪The human heart is too hazy to discern♪
♪I wish to ride the western wind♪
♪But where does the wind go,
leaving me empty-handed?♪
♪Holding the same fervent hopes♪
♪For nameless souls♪
♪With light in my heart,
I fear no darkness♪
♪Restoring the purity
of mountains and rivers to the world♪
♪Hand in hand, looking up to the dawn♪
♪Looking far into the road ahead♪
♪Together through this passage of time,
what is there to fear?♪
♪Chasing the wind,
the moon, and the stars♪
♪Listening to the spirits
of the plants and trees♪
♪All the unions and partings,
the joys and sorrows♪
♪Resonate with me in the wind♪
♪Alone, I carve out my world♪
♪Looking back at the road traveled♪
♪By your side,
the passing of time is fearless♪