This show is sponsored by the world's thinnest smartphone, E-Life.
The United States does not cover the
world's thinnest smartphone, E-Life.
I'm going to the UK.
Go back safely.
I'm going back with Su Kai.
What are you doing?
Chen Yu, Chen Yu, I like you.
Hello, welcome to the new life.
I have only one dream in college.
To have a romantic relationship.
Your love life is a bit harsh.
Lin Jiang Mo, I declare that I like you.
I declare that I like you.
Your love life is a bit harsh.
Lin Jiang Mo, I declare that I like you.
I declare that I don't like you.
It's really you.
I really don't want to see you.
Can you stop bothering me?
I can't.
You promised me before.
The meaning of life is to torture.
Then let's torture you today.
Do you want to have a relationship with me?
I have a girlfriend.
Are you serious?
I'm joking with you.
You scared me.
The rain is a little smaller.
Let's go.
I love you.
love you.
I am the one, my heart is through the ocean of eternity or rage.
I always first pure contracts even devotees interview me,
but that delicateness is never enough.
Otherwise it will be
Will you be with me?
I will.
Why are you here?
I'm here to visit my class.
You're here to visit your class?
I brought you some food.
You're really good.
Han Xun, let's go.
Let me introduce you.
This is my girlfriend, Fang Hui.
This is Shen Xiaotang, whom I often mention to you.
You must be from the school of food and drink.
Hello.
She is a singer from our school.
I heard that you know a lot about star-studying.
I'm just a little bit of a researcher.
What's your star-studying?
I'm a virgin.
Virgin girls are very serious when they fall in love.
Chen Xin, someone is taking care of you.
Yes, yes.
Hi.
You're back.
Where did you go to play?
I didn't go anywhere.
I just stayed at home.
Look, my mom is so fat.
By the way, there are many letters for you.
Really?
New semester, new signs.
The competition has begun.
Girls, come and have a look.
Come and have a look.
Boss.
Sign up with me.
A man's star.
Sing a song.
What's the rush?
You're going to sing your little song.
I guess that girl will be very confused.
Don't tease me.
Come and have a look.
What?
I'll sign up for that song.
Hi.
Do you have a girl named Pan in your department?
She just broke up with her boyfriend.
What's the situation?
How would I know?
Introduce her.
Why are you keeping it a secret?
I don't have time for that.
That new student is not a good person.
You must not talk to him.
I know him.
Don't worry.
He is not a good person.
He knows that he is going to meet a girl every day.
He doesn't do anything good.
You should be polite.
This is for you.
I have something else to do.
You give it to him.
Hello.
Where is your umbrella?
Thank you.
You are welcome.
Are you tired?
Take it easy.
Thank you.
You sing very well.
You are too polite.
Why are you here so late?
Hurry up.
The movie is about to start.
You didn't go to class today, did you?
What time is it?
I asked for leave for you.
What's wrong with you?
You skipped class right after the school started.
I came back late yesterday.
I didn't get up today.
Why are you always like this?
You can't delay your study even if you work.
I have to stay in school to study.
I can study in the society.
Why are you still being so polite?
Didn't you promise me that you would go to class?
Alright.
I was wrong.
Let's go.
I don't want to go to your concert.
Why?
I worked so hard
just to take you to the concert.
You don't want to go now.
Why?
Don't worry.
I'm not tired.
Really.
You are happy.
But you didn't think
how worried I would be
if you worked in a bar
and hang out with those people.
I'm not worried about you.
After all,
you just don't want me to go to your bar.
I didn't say that.
You didn't say that.
But you think so.
I can't think about it.
Can you stop being like this?
If you have something to say,
don't keep going around.
I have nothing to say.
Wait.
What's wrong with me?
What did I do?
Why are you like this?
I'm really boring.
Yes.
Who are you looking for?
Wait.
Why are you here again?
Police officer.
I received a lot of emails.
They said the address was wrong.
They were looking for a person.
Can you help me look inside?
Let me see.
This person has been released.
How come I don't know?
When did this happen?
Some time ago.
Xiao Ye.
Auntie.
I want to ask.
This family...
This family?
They moved out.
They moved out?
I heard that their son
committed a crime and went to jail.
He came back two days ago.
He must be embarrassed to see people.
Do you know where they moved to?
I don't know.
Did they go to jail?
Thank you.
Why are you so unhappy these days?
Nothing.
Your husband is here.
I'm leaving.
Li Qi.
Let's go together.
What are you doing?
You two talk.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Tomorrow, the singer will have a performance.
Come and see me sing.
I have a class tomorrow.
Don't go.
It's boring if you don't come to see me sing.
I really don't have time.
I'm leaving.
Don't go.
You made a mistake.
I'm leaving.
Girl, Miss!
muscles are burnt
the sun caught on eyes
Keep warming yourself
please make you think
Cute girl
still Strategy A
Still Strategy A
Kingdom!
We're Everyone's favorite
Silly girl
I wish to have a bright place
I can go to the sun every day
Put all my things on the ground
And relive the old times
I didn't have long hair back then
My eyes were bright and clear
There is a paradise in my heart
And my most beloved girl
I haven't heard you sing this song
I wrote it myself
Really? You are so talented
You can rock and rock
How about you sing this song when you are rich
I am rich?
I thought I would be eliminated today
No, they all like you
Xue Yinchang is very good and very strong
You are so strong today
You left a few days ago
I have always been like this
I am happy and unhappy
Everyone is like this
I thought I was talking about you
Don't be narcissistic
You are not as capable as me
Where is your girlfriend?
She didn't come?
She doesn't like me singing these songs
She is noisy
Yes, she is
Girls don't like it
You are not a girl
You were dancing
So I am a psycho
Psycho?
You should be treated
Get out
Here
What?
The test is on the floor
Here you are
Chen Gregory
Hey
Chen Xin
You even told her
what went wrong with the mill
I know
I was so busy
Hurry and eat
Keep it
I will be back
Elle
are you selling it to me
No
After I want to leave
I will ask her about this
grenades
Everyone
I hate you
and her
I am telling you
I am indignant
Chen Xin
Don't be so gloomy.
Go for it, Singer Contest!
What are you doing?
So handsome.
Shut your mouth.
The sweat is almost running down your neck.
Wait, why are you here?
I just learned to play the instrument.
I'll play it for you.
Chengxu.
You can go back to your room.
I'll be back soon.
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Zhao Ye has been released from prison.
But he moved. I can't find him anywhere.
When did this happen?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
It's too late to say now.
Let's go.
Call Fang Hui.
You call her?
Me?
You two are making trouble again.
Okay, leave it alone.
Zhao Ye is like this now.
Can you two stop making trouble?
Can you let me save my heart?
Is he here?
The boss said
he hasn't seen him for more than a year.
It means
he hasn't been out since he came out.
Where did he go?
Don't worry.
Zhao Ye is a big trouble.
He can't disappear by chance.
Let's go eat first.
Okay.
I'm not going.
Don't. Let's go together.
Let's go.
This is braised beef.
I often come here. It's delicious.
Try it.
Shen Xun.
It's getting cold.
Eat it while it's hot.
Don't sit here.
Drink some water.
I'm not going.
What's wrong with you?
Turn around.
Why are you so careless?
I said I'll give you a massage.
You didn't.
Does it hurt?
You two.
I'm going.
Well.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Fang Hui.
I'm not going to
work at the bar.
Why?
I went to the bar
to get a job.
I wanted to make you happy.
Now you're not happy.
What's the point
of working there?
Actually,
you can't do it on purpose.
Fang Hui.
You can do it on purpose.
Look at me.
In the college entrance examination,
there were three big questions
in the final question.
Do you remember?
Three questions.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I did it
to get into the university with you.
I want to be with you.
I...
You...
Why didn't I hear you say it?
I just want
to be with you.
Be with you well.
You understand?
No.
For this goal,
I can't do anything.
Do you understand?
So,
don't doubt me anymore.
Let's not talk about it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Where is he?
Big sister.
You've been sleeping all morning.
Why are you so tired recently?
Li Jiang Mo.
I can help you.
What can you help me with?
I can help you with
the exam.
what?
Help you with finding someone.
Don't find your friend
who has been in the university.
I have my own way.
It's none of your business.
You're looking for so many people.
How can you find him?
It's none of your business.
It's mine.
Luo Jiang Mo.
Don't be so rude.
You don't appreciate me helping you.
He's hiding from you.
I'm telling you again.
Don't meddle in my business.
You'd better stay away from me.
Do you understand?
You just said you wouldn't do it.
I was in a hurry.
You haven't finished this month.
Just take some money.
I just got this money.
I'm fine with it.
Why did you suddenly quit?
I've been called many times.
If I don't go to class,
I'll be in charge of teaching.
When did you start to be so sad
about studying?
Can't we bow to the world under the roof?
Who is the roof?
What do you want to say?
I think you have something to say.
I just don't want to do it.
Okay?
Okay.
As long as you understand.
I have nothing to be confused about.
Shen Xiaotao.
Do you think you know me that well?
Chen Xu.
I don't have time to know you.
Do whatever you want.
Goodbye.
I'm sorry.
The food is not good.
I'm not hungry.
Boss, don't eat cabbage.
Have some braised pork.
No need.
I like cabbage.
And someone likes cabbage.
I'm a meat seller.
When I first came to Dongtian,
there was no other food.
It's cabbage.
I don't like cabbage.
I always tell them.
Boss, I don't eat cabbage.
If someone doesn't eat cabbage,
he will die.
From then on, I like cabbage.
You believe that?
Then you haven't eaten cabbage for more than ten days?
Of course.
When I was a kid, I ate cabbage in a thin layer.
This time, I ate cabbage for a month.
Next time, I ate potatoes.
I can eat cabbage for a month.
Then later on,
you didn't find out that grandma said
that she would die if she didn't eat cabbage.
Did she lie to you?
People who know how to kill people are all liars.
People's lives are like weeds.
Police can do anything.
No matter what, they can't leave.
They can do anything.
Why is it you again?
Here.
What?
Look. Look.
Look.
The person you're looking for is Zhao Ye, right?
Huo Hua Ye.
I've been working in the Public Security Bureau for a long time.
Help me check this person.
Work here.
Right here.
Thank you.
Okay. Go ahead.
Go ahead and settle down.
Or I'll go with you.
It's very messy over there.
No need. I can go by myself.
Okay.
Then be careful.
Call me anytime.
24 hours a day.
I'll pay for the rest and you can leave in the morning.
It's already veryursed.
Can you help me to BLACK headphones?
Then with this help of mine,
there is only a few of us left.
No need.
Hallo.
Hello.
Mr. whatsapp.
Yin Jia Mu.
You smile?
I'll do it.
You're making a movie.
You're playing in the real world.
What are you waiting for?
This is called theory.
Can you be more clever?
The first one, the second one,
the third one,
You're so sincere.
And this one,
Come and see this girl.
She's so bad.
How about it?
I tell you,
All women are the same.
You have to listen to your partner.
Understand?
Xing Kuang Ling,
I want to remind you.
You can be careful with your words.
What are you listening to?
Don't bother me.
Wait.
What do you mean?
Why are you doing my computer?
I'm not doing anything.
I don't like you.
You talk to me after you talk to me.
I tell you,
I've seen you not sleeping for a long time.
Can you appreciate this movie?
Look at you.
How many women have you seen?
You're still a cook.
Stinky cat.
Who are you talking about?
I said you're a stinky cat.
You let me say it again.
I've said it.
I'm not stinky.
What do you want to say?
You're stinky.
I'm not stinky.
I'm not.
You're not.
Sit down.
Chen Xun.
You wrote the wrong question.
What's wrong?
Are you uncomfortable?
Headache.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll send you to the hospital.
Chen Xun.
Those who want to go to the sun
don't hide your face.
Which school?
The school that I went to last time.
I'm sorry.
Who is it?
Xing Xun.
Yes.
What are you doing this afternoon?
Practicing the zither.
Stop it.
Let's go shopping.
Well...
The song contest is about to start.
I should practise the song well.
How about another day?
What about tomorrow?
Tomorrow...
I don't know.
I really don't have time these days.
When I compete in the competition,
I will definitely be with you.
Why don't you have time to be with me
when you are working?
If you don't work now,
will you still be so busy?
What do you have to do with your time?
I didn't do anything.
Didn't I tell you?
I'm practicing singing.
Is the singer contest so important?
Am I important?
I didn't mean that.
What does that mean?
No, I'm singing
to let you hear it.
That singer contest
is organized by Shen Xiaotang, right?
No, what do you mean?
Can we not talk
like this?
Why didn't we stay together
in high school
when we were in college?
Do you think
it's boring to talk to me?
It's boring
to stay with me.
What do you want to say?
I think it's boring.
Really?
She will make you
not be afraid to leave.
How I wish you and I
could be as kind as children.
Give you a pure heart,
give me a pure look,
I'll go back to them.
I hope this song
you can sing with me.
I have to sing
the song I like
to let go of my classmates.
Chen Xin,
those who want to go to the sun
don't be so sad.
Good luck in the singer contest.
Hello,
hello.
Oh no, it's on fire.
The clothes are all burnt.
It's on fire.
What?
No way.
I heard it was the fire from the front door.
Really.
What about the people inside?
I don't know.
Let's go and have a look.
Let's go.
People always say goodbye.
But many of them
happen suddenly
when we don't realize it.
We can't just say goodbye
and say goodbye.
Because it's easy to say goodbye,
it's hard to say goodbye.
If you love her,
unless you're living or dead,
don't ever
separate from her.
Never,
never
separate from her.
What are you doing, Xia Mo?
In this matter,
if there must be a bad person,
I hope I can be the bad person.
Have you forgotten
our friendship?
One person leaves another person
because he doesn't love her enough.
Why are you following this person?
Tai Yi.
Don't be so cruel.
I'm not.
Don't tell them you saw me.
You're a
bad person.
Do you like Shen Xiao Tao?
Back off.
I hope I can have a bright bed.
I can sunbathe every day.
I can put my things on the ground.
I can live longer than before.
Back then,
my hair wasn't that long.
my eyes were clear.
I can see the sun.
I can see the moon.
My eyes are clear.
I have an ideal paradise in my heart.
And I have the girl I love most.
I hope that you and I
will be kind as children.
I'll give you a pure heart
and a pure look.
Run back to their side.
I hope you can sing this song with me
With your story and beautiful image
Back to the time of that year
I hope you and I can walk to the end
And shine the sun every day
We can climb to the top of the mountain to see the sunset
And sing about the old times
The breeze has already stopped the rain
And the wind has already stopped the rain
Back to the time of that year
The breeze has already stopped the rain
And the wind has already stopped the rain
I give you pure eyes and my pure appearance
And return to their path
I hope you can sing this song with me
With your story and beautiful image
Back to the time of that year
I hope you and I can walk to the end
And shine the sun every day
We can climb to the top of the mountain to see the sunset
And sing about the old times
The breeze has already stopped the rain
And the wind has already stopped the rain
There are many things to tell me
I hope the story will be in this place
I hope to have a bright landing pad
I hope to be able to shine the sun every day
And put my things on the ground
And sing about the old times
Translated by Hua Chenyu English Subs