♪Ready, count down: four, three, two, one♪
♪Dispel the dark clouds in the sky♪
♪Because of you, I begin to believe♪
♪That everything is a prelude
to our encounter♪
♪In the depths of fate,
there's a kind of attraction♪
♪Bringing us closer to each other♪
♪Perfect logic, you are the weapon♪
♪Against the world's dullness and monotony♪
♪Life is disheartening sometimes♪
♪But you are the solution to many puzzles♪
♪There's an innate tacit understanding
between us♪
♪Thanks to you, I dare to be paranoid♪
♪You and I are the definition of love♪
♪Ready, count down: four, three, two, one♪
♪Dispel the dark clouds in the sky♪
♪Because of you, I begin to believe♪
♪That everything is a prelude
to our encounter♪
♪In the depths of fate,
there's a kind of attraction♪
♪Bringing us closer to each other♪
♪I am destined♪
♪To run to you among all stars♪
=No, Handsome Guy=
=Episode 6=
Ye Ran,
what exactly do you want to say?
Zhuangzhuang, I like you.
Not only do I want you to become
the main character of my manga,
but I also want you to become
the main character of my life.
So,
will you be my boyfriend?
(Boss.)
(Should I say yes to this too?)
- Ye Ran...
- Secretary Chen.
We'll be late for the meeting.
Right, right, Ye Ran,
we can talk about this after work.
But you haven't answered me yet.
It's work time,
have you completed all your tasks?
That was so embarrassing.
Why did you confess your love so early?
Ye Ran, this isn't like you at all.
I thought even if there were feelings,
you'd wait a couple of months
before acting.
I didn't want to do it so quickly either,
but the situation forced me.
Mom, why are you here?
I bought this house.
Why can't I come?
Pack up your things
and come home with me.
Now?
Sit down.
Ye Ran,
two years ago, you insisted on
coming out to be independent.
I agreed,
on the condition that
you find a boyfriend within two years.
And now?
Where is he?
Come home with me.
Mom, I'm not going back.
And who told you
I don't have a boyfriend?
Where is he?
You've spent the past two years
either working or drawing.
Your career hasn't progressed,
and you haven't even
found half a boyfriend.
Now, two years have passed.
Time to inherit the family business,
and go on blind dates.
Mom,
why are you worrying about me?
Why don't you go worry about Ye Dang?
Your sister is not like you.
She's carefree.
Besides,
she doesn't have a phobia
about handsome men,
nor does she keep thinking about
that guy called Yu Feng.
Mom...
Ye Ran,
Mom is genuinely worried about you.
It's for your own good.
Just come home with me.
The Saturday after next,
the Saturday after next,
I promise I'll bring my boyfriend home.
You really have a boyfriend?
Yes,
I really have a boyfriend,
and he's a wonderful person.
Fine,
I'll give you one last chance.
The Saturday after next,
bring your boyfriend home for dinner.
If you don't,
I'll rent out this house immediately.
The Saturday after next, then.
I'm leaving.
Where can I find a ready-made boyfriend?
He's right
before your eyes.
You're right.
I need to land Secretary Chen asap.
Secretary Chen?
Secretary Chen,
this is the final plan confirmed
by the marketing department.
You can organize it later.
(Conference Room)
What are you doing here again?
Boss,
it's lunchtime now,
and it won't affect work.
You've got some excuses.
I haven't finished talking yet.
Boss,
do you have anything else to say?
Look at me and talk to me.
Look at me.
Why do you keep
running away from me?
What?
You are afraid I might eat you alive?
Open your eyes.
Ye Ran.
I didn't see anything.
Boss, I'll go explain to her right now.
Hold on.
Confiscated.
You drew this more carefully
than your manga series.
Boss, this is the final plan confirmed
with the marketing department.
Leave it here.
Boss,
what was going on this morning?
Why did Ye Ran suddenly confess to me
and mention the comic?
It's the first time
someone has confessed to me,
and it's embarrassing.
Should I accept her?
Do you like her?
I've been busy with work all this time,
so I haven't thought about it before.
Are you saying you are starting
to think about it now?
Not really.
Then reject her.
If you don't like her,
there's no need to force it.
Okay.
Boss,
is another girl trying to
get close to you?
I'll take it away.
No.
♪Ready, count down: four, three, two, one♪
♪Dispel the dark clouds in the sky♪
♪Because of you, I begin to believe♪
Boss,
do you want some?
No.
♪Bringing us closer to each other♪
♪Perfect logic, you are the weapon♪
♪Against the world's dullness and monotony♪
♪Life is disheartening sometimes♪
♪But you are the solution to many puzzles♪
♪There's an innate tacit understanding
between us♪
♪Thanks to you, I dare to be paranoid♪
Are you coming?
♪Ready, count down: four, three, two, one♪
♪Dispel the dark clouds in the sky♪
♪Because of you, I begin to believe♪
♪That everything is a prelude
to our encounter♪
♪In the depths of fate,
there's a kind of attraction♪
♪Bringing us closer to each other♪
♪I am destined♪
- Boss.
- Secretary Chen,
get in the car.
Thank you, boss.
This Tiger Meng
is everywhere.
Could it be that
he also likes Secretary Chen?
♪Count constellations in the night sky♪
(Silence)
Secretary Chen,
I want you to come home
with me next Saturday for dinner.
I hope this won't give him the wrong idea.
To meet my parents.
Will that
make him feel pressured?
Ye Ran, would you like some fruit?
(Secretary Chen, I want you...)
No.
I'm going to sleep.
(A Leaflet)
Secretary Chen,
I want you.
♪No need to recall♪
♪Nor will I forget♪
♪You honestly embrace my life♪
♪That year I fell to the bottom♪
♪Once lost the courage to move forward♪
♪But you broke your wings♪
♪Accompanying me through♪
♪Supporting me to the end♪
♪People around come and go♪
♪Where are they going♪
♪Love written in time and air♪
♪A lifetime of warmth continues in the sequel♪
♪I can take off the mask♪
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)