EPISODE 15
Then what should we call
our dear Da-jeong now?
Leave out "our dear."
She's not your dear. She's my Da-jeong.
Then is she like
my younger sister-in-law now?
More like older. You were born in August.
Then let's all just be
brothers and sisters.
I'll have to ask my mom
if she wants to adopt more kids.
All right. Then let's all be friends.
Let's be casual. What do you say?
I say no. I've seen too many people
completely lose their manners
when they get casual.
Then should we use honorifics
like we're at work?
Hey, are you always like that?
Do you always say everything in your mind
until people agree with you?
Eun-ha, you remind me of a crow.
-What?
Crows are actually very smart.
They ignore other slow-witted crows
and have the ability
to infer cause and effect.
-Again, it was a compliment.
-Of course.
Oh, no. Ga-yeong can't come today.
-What?
-She can't?
We were going to watch
the last episode together.
We can watch it by ourselves.
I'll go get the projector.
No, I'll bring it.
You stay here, Da-jeong.
Gosh.
Let's say we'll all just
be formal with each other.
How do you two address each other?
I'm sure it's not too formal,
like "Ms. Kang, Mr. Ju."
We do call each other Ms. Kang and Mr. Ju.
I forgot what Young-do called
his ex-girlfriend.
Boo-boo. Ssing-ssing. Something like that.
-What the…
-Hey.
What's with you? Cut it out.
Right, it was Ssong-ssong.
Her last name was Song. Ssong-ssong.
I see. My ex was a Song too.
Ssong-ssong.
I can't believe I get to see
Young-do dating again.
I'm deeply moved,
Da-jeong, da-da-da.
Cut it out already.
What? It's all in the past anyway.
Right, Da-jeong?
Of course. I've dated about 100 guys too.
A hundred? A hundred guys?
Young-do was the first
to teach me how to drink.
He's allowed to drink a little
on a day like this, no?
He'd better not.
Did he used to be a heavy drinker?
He used to drink a lot for a while.
No, Young-do didn't actually drink a lot.
He just stayed until the end.
He was the "designated cleaner."
He'd wake up drunk friends
and get them a cab to send them home.
Then he sent his girlfriend away too.
Into Young-do's heart
But he sounds exactly like Da-jeong.
She used to be the "designated helper."
She'd tie drunk girls' hair
and pat their backs when they threw up.
Then she patted her boyfriend's heart too.
-I see.
-Right.
Was that okay?
Da-jeong, Da-jeong, da-da-da.
How many tranquilizer darts is that?
That's enough to…
Young-do.
Da-jeong, where should I put this?
Hey, nice definition, nice ambiance.
Will you be like this?
You won't help me out?
What's with you?
Okay.
Take this. The car is yours.
Sorry? The car is mine? What is this?
That car is now yours.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, wait.
I…
This is really mine?
This car is mine?
Princess.
Is that you?
Is that really you? What happened?
I came a long way to see you.
I missed you.
Gosh, can we really do this?
-Even Coke is expensive at this hotel.
-Hey, look.
I decided to give up everything…
The photos are on the phone.
Why did you print them?
Prints are always better
than digital files.
You're so weird.
Young-do, take a look at this.
It's you and Da-jeong.
Cheol-do.
-Thanks.
-You have nothing to worry about.
-You can now stay with me here.
-This is me.
-It's really clear.
-Drink.
-Cool.
-This is mine. This one too.
THE PRINCESS OF FOREVER
What? Who are you?
-Honey.
-"Honey"?
THE PRINCESS OF FOREVER
TO BE CONTINUED IN SEASON 2
GUGU BUILDING
Who did you draw?
It's obviously us.
Oh, I see.
Why? Is it weird?
Do you remember
how I analyzed a kid's drawing?
There was a lot of rain,
which means he was under lots of stress.
He didn't draw any hands
because he couldn't communicate--
Don't do that. Analyzing me.
All right.
I told you to stop it.
I didn't say anything.
You just smirked as if you found out
something I'm not aware of.
All right. I'll stop.
No, tell me. I need to know.
No, you'll grab me by the neck again.
It's something that weird?
No, it's nothing.
If we're done cleaning up, let's--
Tell me. What is it?
You really won't regret this?
First off, you drew
our eyes round and big.
You want to view the world clearly.
You're willing to communicate.
It goes well with your career.
And?
In this portrait,
the thing that stands out the most
is your hair.
And you drew lots of hair.
When adults draw a portrait,
their eyebrows and hair mean energy.
Sexual energy, in particular.
In other words,
it means sexual desire.
My gosh, unbelievable.
My goodness.
Where are you going, Da-jeong?
This is your place.
-She wouldn't tell me.
-Gosh, why not?
-She never…
-Hey.
-Hey, you're here.
-I heard Da-jeong is dating.
You just can't keep a secret, can you?
-You and your big mouth.
-But it's good news.
What does he do? How old is he?
I heard he's good-looking
enough to be an actor.
-Da-jeong's pretty too.
-Right.
If she were my girl,
I would've had her enter a beauty pageant.
How do you two live
in this tiny Gangneung with your nosiness?
And do you have nothing to ask
except such cliche questions?
So who is he?
Just tell us.
What does he do?
You're being so weird, Mi-ran.
You would've been the first
to come and tell us
all kinds of details to show off.
Why? Does he have some kind of flaw?
Has he been married once before,
or is he disabled in any way--
-What?
-Why do you keep digging for flaws?
How can you blurt out everything
that comes to your mind?
What's wrong with you?
Who cares if he's not well?
So what if he was once married?
You should apologize!
Why would Da-jeong see such a man?
Goodness.
-Mi-ran, do you want something?
-Forget it.
Stop making me flip out
and keep flipping jeon.
Hey…
You should be happy.
Why are you getting angry?
-She has an odd personality. Gosh!
-What's with you?
Hello?
Hello, ma'am.
This is Lee Yun-ha of Myeongin Card.
We have a brand-new loan
we'd like to offer you today--
I'm sorry, I don't need it.
What's wrong with you!
Are you okay?
I thought you'd lose my money
from running this so-called cafe,
but you made a profit.
Great work.
You did well too.
I'm done eating. May I go?
I came to see you after months.
That's why I ate with you.
Just stay.
You praised Cheol-do
for running the business well.
Now, you're going to tell me
to get married.
I feel sick when I hear that so…
Then what? You'll never get married?
Have you ever
asked me what kind of life
I want to live?
As if you'd tell me.
Have you ever really listened?
-Just let it go.
-You let it go.
You can because he's your dad.
He never failed to attend your entrance
and graduation ceremonies.
You never even bother to call me,
yet you're still that heartbroken
over how I didn't go to your graduation?
Yes.
You've lived your whole life
only as Cheol-do's father.
When anyone called you at home,
they'd ask for Cheol-do's dad.
No one asked for Eun-ha's dad.
And the cafe?
If anything, I worked harder.
Have you ever complimented me
saying I've done well,
acknowledging my hard work?
Have I ever been more than a daughter
you need to marry off?
Have I ever
been a beloved child to you?
You must've been busy all by yourself.
Sorry.
No, I wasn't too busy.
But about Ms. Ahn Ga-yeong
who calls you Galaxy…
Yes, is she here again? Where is she?
No, she's not here, but the news said
she got into an accident.
An accident? Not a love scandal?
When the car suddenly stopped,
her foot got stuck.
She sprained her ankle a little,
but she won't have any trouble on set.
Yes.
-Are you all right?
-Yes, I'm fine.
Then I'll go wrap things up.
-Sure, go ahead.
-Okay.
Hey.
No, I'm fine. It's not so bad.
What?
Anyway, I can't work out,
so don't snarl at me.
Okay?
-It was true!
-Are they really…
Jin-ho, I'll call you later.
-It's true!
-Are they really going out?
-He's so handsome.
-I'm a fan!
Ahn Ga-yeong.
Ga-yeong.
It's really Ahn Ga-yeong.
Goodness, Patrick. Hello.
I heard your cousin is here--
-My gosh.
-They're really dating.
-What is this?
-Are they really dating?
Are you crazy?
You can't shock me like this.
I was more shocked.
What will you do now?
What are you going to do?
-They really must be going out.
-I told you, didn't I?
I'll get there in an hour.
You're headed to Gangneung, right?
Make sure you don't go to Busan.
Oh, it says something on the sign.
What is it?
Is it telling me to shut up again?
No. It says, "Ju Young-do, drive safely."
I'll call you when I leave.
Okay.
EUN-HA
Hey.
I'm on the rooftop,
and someone just showed up.
Can I leave her in your place?
-Is it Ms. Ahn Ga-yeong?
-Yes.
But she's not alone.
She came with something tall and handsome.
Open the door, give her water,
and order some dumplings for her too.
The number is under the sink.
She has nowhere else to go.
I'll do that. Drive safely.
Okay. Did you get in?
Hello? Yes.
Yes, I just got in.
Yes. One second.
-It's Da-jeong.
-Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm about to be a huge nuisance again.
I might end up
repaying you for generations.
I'll behave as much as I can.
Thank you.
You should thank her too.
Thank you so much.
Yes, I'll thank you in person later.
Bye.
Okay.
Hey, okay.
Don't worry about them.
Bye.
You must be thirsty.
Lemon water and ice is
refilled automatically here,
so feel free to have some.
The number of your favorite
dumpling place is under the sink.
Let me know if you need anything.
Please excuse me.
-Thanks, Galaxy Park.
-Sure.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your order.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
You're here.
Yes, I'm here.
You've been coming often.
I have.
Mom, what should I do?
Nothing. Just go wait at home.
You work all the time in Seoul.
Mom.
Yes?
Mom, there's…
something I want to tell you.
I'm sorry.
What?
Although I wasn't able to raise you well,
you grew into a good person on your own.
Yet I still want to take credit for it.
You're like my winning lottery ticket,
so I guess I don't want to let you go.
I've become such a petty person.
Mom, but you know…
Young-do is a really great person.
I know.
So I'm trying.
I'm so petty, aren't I?
Of course not, Mom.
You can never be petty to me.
You're the least petty person I know.
Thanks for saying that.
-Let's go back inside. I have to work.
-Okay.
Okay.
Let's go.
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
PATIENT: MA ***-GUK
SURGEON: IAN CHASE
I'd also like to ask
if he had anyone he could lean on.
Had there been someone. Just one person…
What if he had no one?
Then I would've reached out to him
and said that it wasn't…
too late to change his ways.
Even if I were in your shoes,
I would have said the same thing.
Even if it's you…
who needs my help, I will help you.
You wanted to know what I was hiding.
I did.
And I'm guessing
you came to tell me.
I don't know where Hwang Jae-sik is.
However,
I do know who has him.
Who is it?
Who are you?
It's me, you bastard.
Hwang Jae-sik.
You're under arrest for murdering
Kim Myeong-ja, Lee Jeong-beom,
Cho Gwang-hun, Noh Hyeon-ju, threatening
Choi Jeong-min, and housebreaking.
I'm sure you know everything you say
could be used against you.
Get an attorney if you want.
Hello, I'm here.
Hey. It must've been a long drive.
-Have you eaten?
-I have.
You can't lie,
so I guess you really did eat.
We need to clean up.
Do you mind waiting a bit?
No, I'd like to help out too.
Mom.
We cleaned up everything.
Let's go home right away.
Da-jeong.
Can you grab
three popsicles from the mart?
-I'll go.
-Let's go together.
No, Da-jeong, you go.
Young-do, you and I need to talk.
Okay, Mom.
You must be disappointed in me.
I adored you so much,
then now that I know
you're sick and were married once,
I seem to have changed
my opinion of you, right?
Not at all.
And I'm grateful
you were willing to meet me.
I was…
awfully bruised
because of this love I was in.
Literally, not figuratively.
I'd turn red, then blue.
I'd wear scarves even in summer,
so all the neighbors would talk about me.
And when I left
such an awful guy on my own,
I still…
ended up crying.
I must've been more heartbroken
because you're such a good person.
It's okay to be sick.
Don't hide anything or be sorry.
Just tell me everything.
Tell me what I can do for you.
Tell me what you can eat
and what I shouldn't do.
And as you told Da-jeong,
do your best
to live as long as you can.
Can you do that?
I'll make sure to do that.
I'll keep my eyes on you.
-Thank you.
-Don't thank me.
I should be sorry a little longer.
I guess I'm just
another materialistic mother.
Stop standing there rustling
and bring the popsicles over.
Okay, Mom.
I got all of your favorites.
Let's eat breakfast.
Yes. It's been a while
since I had a home-cooked meal.
What are you doing? Let's go.
-Let's go.
-To where?
Oh, Da-jeong is really picky,
so I can never cook for her.
She'd complain about onion peels,
uncooked beans,
that there's no kimchi
in kimchi fried rice.
She'd nag at me all the time.
Come on out.
What did you eat as you grew up?
Pizza.
Here.
Mom, me too.
Eat up.
This pizza is great.
Remember. This is
my mom's most delicious dish.
I see. It's really good.
Isn't it?
Come by whenever you want.
I might make you kimchi stew next time.
No, it's all right.
I'd like to have this next time as well.
Will you? Right.
My pizza is great, isn't it?
-Yes.
-Eat.
Come with me. Let's go grocery shopping.
Okay.
Mom.
What will you do with Mr. Ju?
What do you think? I'll boss him around.
A bit of hazing, you know.
Oh, dear.
You can stay here
until the part-timer gets here.
Let's go.
Are you ready?
Ready for what?
Have you ever thought
about how a fish would feel
when it spins round and round
in a microwave?
No.
You'll find out soon enough. Buckle up.
BUCKWHEAT JEON
Stay here. I'll get some fruit.
Say hi to him.
-Okay.
-All right.
Take your time.
Wait, I…
Hey.
You look just like you did on TV.
-What's your name?
-Ju Young-do, ma'am.
My gosh, even his name sounds cool.
What do you do for a living?
She wouldn't tell us anything.
I'm a psychiatrist.
Goodness, this is great.
My daughter works,
so I babysit
my ten-year-old granddaughter.
But she gets distracted way too easily.
She'd be on her phone
with the TV on in front of her.
She'd eat while
playing a game on her phone,
then she'd call her friends too.
Does this mean she's ill?
-No, there are lots of kids like her.
-There are?
If she's still ten years old,
you should guide her
to use her phone properly--
Just lock it.
-Lock it?
This thing. I'll let you know.
-Okay.
-Anyway,
how do you stop someone
from having affairs?
-Is he having affairs?
-Hey!
No way, are you crazy?
He is, isn't he?
It's not about me. It's about Mak-ryeon.
Darn it, I knew he'd be like that.
Right?
There's only one way to stop him.
She should get a talisman
and stick it in his underwear.
-What?
-No one gets a talisman these days.
-My gosh.
-Come on.
Da-jeong's boyfriend will laugh at us.
-We aren't like that.
-That's embarrassing.
She can go see
a fortune-teller or a counselor
because there are
positive effects in sharing her story
-with other people.
-See?
But it's not very easy
for experts to give advice.
But it could be a little dangerous to
leave something like this to non-experts--
Mi-ran knows this one place.
-Right.
-She recently got a talisman.
You should ask her.
-Da-jeong, you're here.
-Goodness.
-Hello.
-Hey.
Where did my mom go?
Mi-ran went to get some fruit.
Goodness, Da-jeong.
You came to get your hubby, didn't you?
Tell me about it.
You two can run along.
Let's see. Here.
Run over there and grab some hotteok.
Only 5,000 won? You're so cheap.
Give him another 5,000 won.
-Give him more.
-It's 5,000 won for 10.
-Goodbye, I'll come again.
-Okay, bye.
-Goodbye.
You know that we're her aunties, right?
You'll be in trouble
if you do her wrong, okay?
Of course. First off,
I'll cut you like I cut raw fish.
I have a fryer at my place,
so I'll fry you,
then put gochujang on you.
That'll hurt, right?
I'm going to flip you over, okay?
-Be careful.
-Be good to her.
Do you get it? Okay.
I'm sorry. I didn't think
she would abandon you.
This is a first.
Is the hazing over?
Then carry this.
Here. You take this. And this. Come.
Okay.
I heard Da-jeong and Young-do
went to Gangneung.
Yes, I heard.
Should we go too?
-But we did not long ago.
-Not like that.
You want to tell your mom?
Is it too early?
I'm not sure.
She already knows you well.
That's the problem. She knows everything.
She knows who my dad is,
how I was a delinquent in middle school,
the boys I've dated,
and what I'm like when I'm drunk.
Do you think I don't know?
We first met when I was 12.
I remember your bangs.
Your mom will be shocked.
Then what about your dad?
Let's take our time.
When will you return to Seoul?
I mean, it's not that I'm bored.
I just miss my bestie a little.
I'm still in Gangneung.
I think I'll stay a bit longer.
Is your boyfriend gone?
He still has to work.
But you're in Gangneung? That pizza place?
How did you know?
I see. I have my sources.
All right, don't mind me,
and have fun on your date.
Okay.
You were a part
of the in-crowd in Gangneung.
You have many aunties.
They're the ones who fed me.
I almost grew up
eating uncooked beans in rice
and chewing on onion peels.
Oh, dear.
You have to try this
since you're in Gangneung with me.
-This is my soul food.
-I see.
So this is why you eat tteokbokki
when you get stressed out.
How old were you when you first had this?
Eleven years old.
Maybe 12.
Lots of neural networks are formed
when you're around ten years old.
The imprinting effect. I still root
for the baseball team I loved then.
And that's why you still love candy.
That's because it was from my first love.
I used to come here often
with Eun-ha in middle school.
We promised to write down
the names of the guys
we come to like in the future.
Should we write our names?
Sure.
DA-JEONG, YOUNG-DO
Hey.
Eun-ha's name is here too.
Tae-jeong's name is beside hers.
Goodness.
That's odd. Their names aren't common.
I'll show it to her later.
You have to go back to Seoul, right?
Oh.
That's why I got this.
I wanted to give it to you
at home yesterday, but I couldn't.
Open it. I'll get some water.
Did you get me two watches
for my two hands?
So that I can look at both
to be more punctual?
Oh, dear.
One is for your mother.
My gosh.
I didn't want it to seem like a bribe.
Could you give it to her for me?
She'll be thrilled.
How did you come up
with the idea to get watches?
I wanted to give time as a present.
It means I'll be with you for a long time.
So it's like a promise.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
-What is it?
-Come to the convenience store.
Why?
You'll see when you come.
Darn it.
Go sit with him.
If you're worried, you do it.
I'll only end up arguing with him.
Can't you just give up?
Give up on what?
Dad won't change.
He'll be rude to everyone,
he'll keep showing off his money,
and he'll think women have to
get married and have kids.
And he will continue…
to grow older and smaller.
So I should just put up with him?
At the very least,
you were never beaten.
I was beaten a lot
until I got into high school.
Back then, I also despised him
to death.
But I learned to give up.
We aren't such loving twins who get sick
when the other one gets sick either.
And Dad is just a dad.
Even if you don't like him,
he's still our dad.
Dad.
What are you doing here?
What? Hey, I'm just…
That could've been bad.
Why are you wearing sunglasses this late?
And the crutch?
Hello.
Wait, you don't know who I am?
Who are you?
I see. You don't watch TV.
Hello, I'm Ahn Ga-yeong, an actress.
I'm the most scandalous and hated person,
Da-jeong's bestie,
and Galaxy Park's close friend.
What's she saying?
So you're Da-jeong's friend?
I'm Mun Mi-ran, Da-jeong's mother.
Really? Seriously?
You're her mom, not her sister?
How?
Did you have her when you were seven?
Where did she find a girl
who says the sweetest things?
Have a seat.
But how did you know about this place?
Da-jeong isn't even here.
Well, our communication fell through.
Do you want anything to drink?
I'll get it myself.
Is the fridge over here?
I'm the type
who always does things on my own.
Everyone has a few boxes of beer
in their fridge, right?
Is this it?
What's with this novel and pretty psycho?
Wait.
So you're the one
who was married to Young-do?
Ju Young-do, who gave this to me?
We had a wedding.
But we were never registered.
And you're Da-jeong's best friend now?
Yes. That's true.
I've watched too much Newflix.
I've watched
too many episodes of Stranger Stuff.
Where are you going? I'm not done yet.
My dear Ms. Mun, the moon lady.
I got married to live,
and he got married to save me.
Others get divorced
because their marriages fail,
but we got divorced
because ours succeeded.
I became quite all right in just a year.
So you must be very grateful to me.
I can't believe this.
What am I listening to right now?
Anyway, you're saying
you're better now, right?
You don't want
to kill yourself now. Right?
What's with you and Da-jeong?
You're comforting me after hearing this?
She must take after you.
Who else would she take after?
If you're better now,
then be grateful and live more diligently.
Be good to Young-do.
And even better to Da-jeong.
I'll do that.
My dear moon lady.
Ms. Mun.
Cheers.
Listening to your lectures,
it seems like you're very tolerant
when it comes to underage delinquents.
Do you think their age
and background at home
should be taken into consideration
when we punish them?
No, I'm sure there is
no one in this world who thinks
their crimes should be forgiven
for those reasons.
I don't think so either.
There were three children
walking down the street with bloody feet.
Let's say they each met
different types of adults.
Those darned kids.
Come out! Hey!
Don't you lay a finger on them,
or I'll kill you.
One kid had a mother
who took her shoes off for her.
No one will find you here.
I'll come for you very soon.
-What will happen to him if I stay here?
-Another one
-He'll be okay.
-was hidden to make him stop
hurting himself for others.
-The last one got criticized and abused
-Eat quickly.
instead of shoes or comfort.
-I told you to smile.
-"Some kids don't even have feet.
-Don't you dare.
-So don't whine about not having shoes."
How do you think that affected the lives
of those three kids?
The kid who put on her mother's shoes
and the one who couldn't help his brother
may live a troubled life
because they couldn't be of help.
But they'll eventually
be able to heal their wounds.
Because that's guilt, not a crime.
However, the last one.
There could come a moment
when his lonely devastation
turns into anger,
because no one saved him.
There will come a moment
when there's no turning back for him.
Hey, Young-do.
-Come and hold him down.
-What? Cut it out already.
-Hurry up.
-I have to go.
-Come on. Don't go.
-Seriously.
I have to go.
JU YOUNG-DO PSYCHIATRY CLINIC
The man named Ju Young-do
at the clinic in that building.
I want to see what he looks like.
I thank the medical staff
who participated,
especially Dr. Chase,
who was willing to lead
this difficult surgery.
As a daughter and a fellow businesswoman,
I'll do my best to make sure
the chairman recovers well.
Thank you.
Go get Dr. Chase immediately.
I'll show him
what it's like to make an enemy of me.
Hwang Jae-sik will be punished soon.
And there will be reports
on Mr. Choi Jeong-min too.
I'm sure you knew that already.
Do you have something else to say?
The 18-year-old
who went to find Hwang Jae-sik
wasn't Jeong-min, but me.
I had thought that he must be
living a good life in my place.
But his life was more miserable than mine.
Take it off.
The so-called mother
who abandoned me was
lying there dead.
And the man
who used to exploit kids for money
had become a worse monster.
So as he was dying, I…
Hit me.
Make me look like you.
Hit me and make it look
like I was beaten by him.
Don't you know how?
Take a cab.
Don't talk to anybody.
Stay in the room.
I pretended to be my brother
and lied to the police.
When I got home,
my mom was lying unconscious.
So I was about to call 119.
But he threw a chair at me
to stop me from calling.
CHOI JEONG-MIN
And then
I tried to run away…
I heard something as I ran away.
He was suddenly on the floor.
Don't forget.
A shadow shouldn't covet the light.
Because it'll vanish.
And then I found that book.
"'No one wants to live with vermin.
Something that should die must be killed.
And someone has to do that job.'
When the man finished talking,
people began to give him
a big round of applause."
PURE MURDER
THE MOST SCANDALOUS ONLINE NOVEL OF 1997
GROTESQUE CONFESSIONS OF A MURDERER
Did you really write that?
PURE MURDER
Prove it.
I thought I could put a stop to it.
Just that once.
If those people disappeared,
I thought everything would be okay.
At this point…
No.
Why are you telling me this now?
"I want everything to be over."
I WANT EVERYTHING TO BE OVER
That's what Jeong-min said.
I get that he can get out of touch,
but something didn't feel right.
You said things don't just feel wrong.
You said it's because micro-expressions
all show on your face.
Do you remember
the last thing Ian Chase said?
He said he wanted everything to be over.
He said Choi Jeong-min said that.
Wait!
Hey!
Have you come for me?
Where have you been?
How did you find me here?
Compared to what I've done for you…
this is nothing.
You know that, right?
Hey.
There's a problem.
But this time, I'll take care of it.
I can do it.
No, don't do anything.
I'll take care of it,
-just as I always have.
-No, this time, I will.
I'll take care of this.
I'll just send someone.
I told you not to use anyone--
Why did you put your foot under mine?
Is that what you mean?
I'm here as a patient.
That way, whatever I say,
you have to keep your mouth shut.
To keep your license.
You have two cars?
You had a different car yesterday.
Hey, are you in Korea?
Didn't I tell you
never to make anything too precious?
That it'll become your weakness.
So you went to see Ju Young-do
like a complete lunatic?
Don't meet
with Kang Da-jeong or Ju Young-do.
And come to the States
once this job is over.
Do you understand?
I purposely came early.
I don't want her to think I'm a stalker
for real.
In that dream of yours,
was there a cat too?
Yes.
Definitely.
Do you like music boxes?
Should we go get one?
Excuse me for a minute.
I made a mistake
and sent that woman a photo.
Erase it before she sees it.
Oh, right.
The passcode to her phone is…
DELETE MESSAGE
Anything can kill you.
A glass of liquor,
or even a sip of Coke.
If you don't kill yourself,
the next body will be found
on the fourth floor of Gugu Building.
I have no idea how I can get out of this.
I just want everything to be over.
Is that your best solution?
Then go ahead and do it.
The shadow
will vanish.
Why are you here?
I heard you said
that you wanted everything to be over.
That sounds way too obvious
for a psychiatrist like me.
I came to ask you not to take
the easy way out like a coward,
if you want to find peace.
If you really wish to be forgiven.
Should we turn off our phones today?
Really?
The lovey-dovey couple disappeared,
but an even more lovey-dovey couple
took their place.
Why does this seem like a Greek tragedy?
I was the shadow, not you.
It says you're enlisting in the army.
That's how you save a life.
"I will listen to you."
Even if you dated someone for ten years,
the next person you meet
could actually be your true love.
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son