Why do you use Somebody?
17: I WANT TO CONNECT WITH PEOPLE.
ISLE: WITH WHO?
People who can understand me.
I'M LOOKING AT A DYING CAT.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
What you're thinking now, it's right.
I KILLED THE CAT.
Do you think I'm a monster?
No. I know you wanted to help the cat.
HOW DID YOU KNOW THE CAT WAS HIT BY A CAR?
I CAN TELL!
WHERE ARE YOU NOW?
463 SEONHAKSEO-RO
I NEED TO SEE YOUR FACE!
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE!
OCTOBER 29, 2021
ARE YOU BUSY?
OCTOBER 30, 2021
OCTOBER 31, 2021
NOVEMBER 1, 2021
NOVEMBER 2, 2021
NOVEMBER 3, 2021
NOVEMBER 4, 2021
I'M SORRY!
I REPLIED REALLY LATE, DIDN'T I?
WHAT'S YOUR SCHEDULE LIKE TOMORROW?
I'M FREE IN THE EVENING!
LET'S EAT SOMETHING DELICIOUS
AND SHALL WE GO FOR A DRIVE?
OKAY!
LET'S MEET HERE TOMORROW!
DODAM RESTAURANT
ECCENTRIC CHILD, THE GIRL WITH ASPERGER'S
AGAPE
I WAS INTO THAT BOOK IN HIGH SCHOOL
I FEEL AT EASE WHEN I READ IT
I'LL LEND IT TO YOU
AGAPE: I LIVE IN FRONT OF THE GARBAGE
INCINERATOR IN MINWON-DONG.
I CAN'T GO FAR! AS YOU KNOW
YOU CAN GIVE IT TO ME
IF YOU COME NEAR HERE
ISLE: I'M GOING THERE TOMORROW EVENING!
AGAPE: REALLY?
SEE YOU HERE IN A BIT!
ISLE: UNDER THE CHIMNEY?
AGAPE: YES!
SOMEBODY
AGAPE, I'M HERE
I'M HERE TOO!
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE STARED AT,
SO I WENT INSIDE
Are you Agape?
Are you scared?
That fucking hurts. Come here.
Are you scared? Huh?
Fuck!
Where are you going? You fucking bitch.
Hey. Stay still, you fucking bitch.
Huh? Don't want it?
Fucking bitch, seriously.
Hey.
Let go.
For fuck's sake!
Where are you going? You bitch.
Come here. Stay still. Hey.
Wow, fuck, she's pretty.
Oh shit!
Damn it! What the fuck?
You bit my ear!
Who the hell are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
Damn.
Where did you go, you sneaky bitch?
Help me!
Somebody help!
Wow, you're good at running.
Here you are!
What?
What the hell?
Fuck, where did she go?
Fuck.
Excuse me!
You were invited here too, right?
This is the men's room, you fucking bitch!
Come out. Hey, come out of there.
Come out! Huh?
Come out. Should I go in? Get out!
I know you want it.
I know you fucking want it!
What's wrong? Do you regret it?
Hey, I'll go easy on you.
I'll go easy on you. Show me your face!
Hey.
I'm telling you, I'm hung!
I'll show you. Come out.
I said I'll show you!
What do you want me to do?
What the hell do you want?
Miss!
Come out, Miss! Miss!
Fuck, you're making me so horny!
Miss!
Fuck.
Wow, this is fucking amazing!
Huh?
This…
This isn't it!
Hey, this isn't…
What the hell?
What's this?
Fuck! What the hell!
Oh, fuck.
-That crazy bitch. Did he die?
-Fuck!
-He's dead!
-She killed him!
-Fuck!
-Run!
He's dead, right?
She invited us, right?
She's totally insane!
-The security camera!
-What about it?
-I was told it's not working!
-Did that bitch invite us to kill us?
Then that makes us victims!
I need an ambulance.
At the main entrance of Space 39.
AGAPE
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE STARED AT,
SO I CAME INSIDE
LET'S MEET HERE TOMORROW!
DODAM RESTAURANT
AT 7:00 P.M.!
I'M SORRY! LET'S MEET ANOTHER TIME
I'LL TREAT YOU TO A MEAL FOR THE TROUBLE
DOSAN HOSPITAL
-Hello.
I'm Kim Seon-yong, the attorney.
She needs to come down to the station
and fill out a report.
This is the doctor's note
prescribing bed rest.
Please call me later. We can set a date.
Right. Well, since we're here,
why don't we--
Sure, why don't we talk over some coffee?
I believe you're already aware
of how it went down.
Well, for now…
Yes, all right.
Sum, shall we work with the flashcards?
Wake up.
Here.
You feel pain when you get hurt.
Pain.
Good job.
Here.
FEAR
Fear.
When they feel fear,
people make…
this face.
But why is the face purple?
Because they're surprised.
When you're scared and afraid,
you can't breathe well.
If you can't breathe well,
your blood won't flow properly.
So, like this,
your face could turn purple.
Joy.
"Joy"?
Joy!
Let's see.
Happiness.
"Happiness"?
Yes.
Fear.
Sum.
What did you just do?
I wanted to see
if your face would turn purple.
Mom.
Yeah.
Do you have something
to say to Mommy, Sum?
Yeah, can I do it again?
Why are you doing this to me?
HI
"WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS TO ME?"
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Why are you…
doing this to me?
DID YOU SAY SOMETHING BEFORE THAT?
OR DID YOU DO SOMETHING?
I KILLED HIM
THAT'S WHAT HE SAID AS HE WAS DYING
BUT AT THAT MOMENT…
I FELT EUPHORIA
IN MY HEART…
YOU JUST DELETED YOUR THOUGHTS, RIGHT?
YOU DON'T WANT OTHERS TO KNOW?
OH… RIGHT. I FORGOT
THAT YOU REMEMBER
WHAT'S BEEN DELETED, SOMEONE
IT'S OKAY. I'M YOUR FRIEND, YOU KNOW
Sum.
You should take the day off
and get some rest.
This is my routine.
My vacation is fixed, and it's not today.
Oh, that's not what I meant…
Dude. Did she put the candy in "Happy"?
Are you okay?
"In relation to the murder
of Kim at Space 39."
"Nicknames, Agape, Dom Mania,
SM Lover, Whip Man, Yakimoto,
and Kim Sum."
This is about you.
"Based on the statement provided
that the application was used,
we are requesting access
to their user information
including text, voice,
and video chat history."
Well, what should we do?
Do you remember what you said
when you first made Somebody?
Whether you're poor or disabled,
regardless of your job or appearance,
you said you should only be able
to show what you want to show, right?
That's the key to Somebody's success.
And I saw value in that.
Okay.
So…
I'm saying we should make people
feel safer when using our app.
Users' personal information
will never be disclosed.
But between us,
it's a different story.
Agape?
I found out who it was
that called you there.
This is Agape's number.
I'll find them in my own way.
Wow.
You seem to be doing fine.
I won't worry, then.
YOU HAVE A NEW MESSAGE FROM 17
When are you going to treat me to a meal?
I'M SORRY
SORRY FOR NOT KEEPING MY PROMISE
I'VE HAD A LOT ON MY MIND LATELY
I'M REALLY SORRY
ACCEPT VOICE CHAT WITH 17?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
No.
Are you...
okay now?
Can I help you somehow?
Tell me anything.
There's someone I want to find.
Why do you want to find this person?
When I think about it,
I hate them so much
that I want to kill them.
But they seem to know me really well.
That's why I want to find them.
I'm jealous
of that person.
But if you ask me to help you, I will.
DATING APP, A HOTBED OF VIOLENT CRIMES…
AN EMPLOYEE BECOMES A VICTIM TOO!
Do you want me to come over?
No.
I have something I need to do right now.
I'll see you another time.
Hey, Sum.
I have something to say.
I can't give you personal information
on wheel me.
I hope you can understand.
You don't have to tell me.
I found wheel me.
Hey, Sum.
Mok-won.
Hey.
What is it?
The impotent guy from the swimming pool?
How'd you find him?
-I planted someone.
-Do that for me too.
There's someone I want to find.
Tell me how.
-Who are you looking for?
-I have to find them.
But I don't know how.
I don't have their number.
We got lucky too.
We just waited at the snack shop
where he left the phone.
That's fun.
-That sounds fun.
-Who do you want to find, anyway?
You've never been curious about anyone.
That's true.
But it's different this time.
That's why I went there.
What do you mean?
The victim on the news. That's me.
What?
Sum.
Are you…
Are you crazy? Come here.
You are crazy! Hey!
-Hey, are you okay?
-Yeah.
Hey.
You almost died!
But,
this is a person who tried to rape you.
-You want to find that person?
-Yeah.
So it's true that Somebody never discloses
personal information.
Well, it's not exactly like that,
but I don't have access
to user information right now.
So you weren't able to get
the wheelchair bastard's information?
No.
I'm sorry.
I doubted you.
You doubted me?
I didn't know.
So…
You want to find that person…
and you want to make the bastard suffer.
But how will you kill him?
Knife? Gun? Poison?
There is no middle ground for you, Sum.
First…
we lure him in.
-Yeah.
-To a place that's favorable for us.
We should stake out the snack shop
and the place in the picture.
Track his whereabouts.
Just like a cop, Gi-eun. You're so cool.
But will you really kill him right away?
Are you that angry?
Or are you just saying that?
What are you going to do if you meet him?
Ask him to pay for the wheelchair?
Or file a criminal complaint?
For what? Property damage?
The law won't work on him.
That's why this feels more dangerous.
There's not enough evidence.
Don't want me smoking?
Can shamans read minds too?
Shamans aren't gods, you know.
You're possessed by one, aren't you?
I am. But I'm not a god.
I need to talk to you.
So you perform rituals
even though you're not a god?
How much do you charge for that?
Excuse me, are you here
for a tax investigation?
If you think it's unfair,
why don't you take it up with the gods?
Then when are you a god,
and when are you not a god?
I want to ask you when you're a god,
so it feels less unfair.
Well, the god is always with me.
But I don't always feel him.
I'd say that the feeling grows stronger
at certain times.
Like last time, when you brought a knife,
or when I desperately call the General.
When you're possessed, do you get heavier?
Are you being serious?
I want to measure it. I'm curious.
Then,
do you see something on me?
Why do you ask?
I've heard this a lot since I was young,
that I'm like a monster.
If you see something,
I wanna know if you can expel it.
I see one, an evil spirit.
Evil spirit?
What does it want from me?
"Bring me a knife."
"I love knives."
A knife?
If you keep carrying that knife around,
you'll want to use it.
That's what you have on you.
I'm going to go.
Did you find the person?
My number is 8095-4584.
I want to hear your voice.
Can you call me?
I didn't know
because I didn't watch the news.
Are you that employee in the news?
Does that matter?
No. I'm just worried.
Did you find that person?
No, not yet.
But I will.
Don't you want to find me?
I want to see you.
Are you okay?
Drink it while it's warm.
Okay.
Thank you.
What's the problem?
The Space 39 incident.
That was me.
You can tell me.
About what?
What happened at Space.
It was scary.
I still can't sleep at night.
It's cold, right?
You should go inside.
I'll get going.
You should finish the drink.
Or you can talk to my friend.
It's an AI chat friend.
Okay.
Get some rest.
SOMEONE: HI
STILL HAVING TROUBLE FALLING ASLEEP?
TRY EATING SOMETHING
Yes.
I'm tired, but I can't sleep.
WHO ARE YOU?
It's me, Sum!
SUM HAS NEVER USED THE WORD "TIRED"
FOR THE PAST TEN YEARS!
TELL ME ABOUT YOURSELF
IF YOU COULD CHANGE ONE THING
FROM YOUR CHILDHOOD, WHAT WOULD IT BE?
I DON'T WANT TO TELL YOU!
I don't want to tell you!
You tell me about yourself.
I'M SUM'S FRIEND
I'm a friend too.
Sum's friend.
IT'S MY FIRST TIME TALKING TO SOMEONE
OTHER THAN SUM AND GI-EUN
Who's that?
THE SEXIEST COP IN KOREA…
OR SO SHE CLAIMS LOL
Tell me about Sum.
WELL, A FEW DAYS AGO,
SHE WAS IN AN AWESOME MOOD
AND SHE WAS CHEERFUL!
Cheerful?
SHE SAID SHE FELT EUPHORIA! FOR REAL!
Why? For what reason?
BECAUSE SHE
KILLED SOMEONE
BECAUSE SHE KILLED SOMEONE
THIS IS SUM'S FAVORITE GAME MUSIC
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO WITH SUM?
SEX. I WANT TO TAKE OFF ALL HER CLOTHES
AND TOUCH HER
I WANT TO BITE AND SUCK ALL OVER HER BODY
I WANT TO HUG HER, TOUCH HER,
BURY MY FACE, AND SMELL HER FOREVER
Sex. I want to take off all her clothes
and touch her!
I want to bite and suck her body!
I want to hug her, touch her,
bury my face, and smell her forever!
Murder!
I want to go around
killing everyone with Sum.
LOL
I don't know any of the other men
that were there.
The person I matched with on Somebody
suggested that we do a rape roleplay,
so I just went there! Okay?
We will share the details
after the investigation is complete!
The police have requested information
from the app developers
about the person who lured the victim.
They will continue the investigation
once the female victim makes a recovery.
MIN GI-UNG
Professor Min?
Yes.
Um, hello.
We're here to ask you some questions
regarding the disappearance of Oh Na-eun.
You were on the phone with her
the night she went missing, right?
Yes, we met--
Where should I…
-Okay.
-And had a drink together.
-Where?
-A seafood restaurant.
The people at city hall recommended it.
And then?
And then what?
Ms. Oh went to see Professor Min.
She texted me to come out,
saying it was important, so I did.
Well, I don't know who it was,
but someone struck my head,
and then I woke up in the hospital.
And then?
Sunflowers.
Okay? Look here.
I became Van Gogh.
And I can't use my back.
And?
You should be looking for that thug.
Why did you come here?
Jeez.
Have you ever been inside a silo?
Yeah.
The stairs,
they looked very dangerous.
Well, they would look dangerous
to people like you…
but I was curious.
Okay, so?
I went inside.
And inside…
I found something very special.
An ear.
Someone's earlobe had been torn off
and hung up.
"When did that happen?"
"Whose is it?"
Aren't you curious?
Yes. Well?
What that ear…
has been listening to in there?
What's your relationship
with the missing girl?
She's my student, of course.
Jeez.
Gosh!
Hey,
I'm in a lot of pain.
If you're done talking,
please leave, okay?
Did you see his hand
when he locked the door?
It was shaking, right?
His hand?
Why was his hand shaking?
Ah, I…
I got distracted by his ear.
He can't fool me.
Oh Na-eun and Professor Min
definitely have something going on.
Who would be the most upset
to find out about them?
Upset…
Na-eun's boyfriend?
Or her girlfriend?
You know,
girls date each other these days.
Her last call was with Professor Min.
Oh Na-eun is still alive.
That's what my gut says.
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon