♫  For whom will the summer slow down  ♫
♫  Loud cicadas chirp complicated feelings  ♫
♫  I wonder what kind of scenery awaits us  ♫
♫  For whom will the movie change its story  ♫
♫  A sudden storm, blurred vision  ♫
♫  I wonder if it's going to be a starry night  ♫
♫  As the last spark from the fireworks fade  ♫
♫  It reminds me something's better to be said earlier than later  ♫
♫  Just like that I've never stopped loving you  ♫
♫  In the sleepless winter night  ♫
♫  A season to say goodbye  ♫
♫  I try my best to be brave  ♫
♫  We will keep on going like this  ♫
♫  The secret of the answer  ♫
♫  An insoluble question  ♫
♫  All comes down to a simple thank you  ♫
Siyue, care to join me in a game of pool this Sunday?
Are you hanging out? I want to go, too.
I'll think about it.
The competition is happening soon.
Xianxian, why don't you come with us?
You guys have fun. I don't know how to play.
Me neither.
Anyway, when the time comes, when you see the ball, you poke it.
You... I'm not going with you.
Oh, my god!
Like I would want to go with you!
Join us. I'll show you how.
Yes!
Should we ask Jiang Chen to come as well?
Don't. None of us is going to have fun if he's there.
Just tell me if you can't see clearly.
I'll copy the notes for you.
What about your competition paper?
I can work on it later.
- Come and have dinner.
- Coming.
Come on, time for dinner.
Here you are.
Mom, can I discuss something with you?
I want a pair of glasses with a higher prescription.
Is your myopia getting worse?
A little.
Xianxian, you were pseudo-myopic before.
The glasses are to correct that. Why is your myopia getting worse?
I don't know. Sometimes things can get blurred.
Which row are you sitting in right now?
The fifth. Talk to your teacher and move to the row in front.
Try not to wear your glasses.
If the prescription keeps increasing, you may have to wear them forever.
If you feel awkward talking to your teacher, I can do it.
Never mind. I can hold on for longer.
Your dad said that you were about to choose between liberal arts and science.
You could take the chance to switch seats
after you are transferred to a liberal arts class.
But I might choose science.
Why would a girl choose science?
Why can't a girl choose science?
That's not what I mean.
I'm saying that girls will have a hard time with science subjects.
You may feel you are doing well in both now.
Things will get harder in your second and third year of high school.
- But...
- Stop fighting this.
I'll make that decision for you. Liberal arts it is.
Why? This is my business.
Don't I get to choose by myself?
You are too young to make that choice.
Liberal arts is the safe choice for you.
Your dad can tutor you so that you will get into a good university.
We are doing this for your sake.
Would we hurt you or what?
And you are fighting with me.
Enough. Let's all calm down.
This is a really important choice.
Let's sit down and talk about it.
Xianxian,
be patient when talking to your mother.
I'm done.
That's not the way to bring up a child.
And you are good at this?
And you are?
You are so good at this that she's refusing to have dinner now.
Xianxian, go online.
I've applied to be your contact. Accept my request.
Wow. Welcome, Little Monster.
Put down the cell phone and focus on your homework.
Xianxian,
didn't you tell your mom the other day that you want a cell phone?
Your mom and I talked about it and bought you one.
What?
Sorry, Dad.
I kept you in the dark.
About what?
Zhou Siyue lent me this.
I saw it this morning.
How about this?
Return that one to Zhou Siyue when you have the chance.
Xianxian, we bought you this cell phone,
but there are some conditions.
First, you mustn't bring it to school.
It will affect your studies.
Second,
I hope you can consider what your mom just said.
She's not wrong.
Dad, do you also think
that I should choose liberal arts?
Your mom and I are on the same page.
We think that you are a girl.
Choosing science will make your life harder.
We don't want to see you having a hard time.
What about you, Dad?
Why did you choose politics?
I...
I wasn't doing well in science back then.
Doesn't that mean it is wrong to assume
that girls should choose liberal arts and boys should choose science?
Besides, I'm not mad at you for not letting me choose science.
I'm mad because you won't let me make my own choices.
Xianxian, grown-ups might be unreasonable,
but that's because we are worried that you might make mistakes
that have consequences that you can't bear.
And if you thought it through,
I will respect your choice.
Thanks, Dad.
Oh, another thing. Stop being so stubborn with your mom.
Don't be fooled by her words. You know how she is.
Besides, I think she might be going through menopause recently.
I understand. I will stop being mad at her.
Good girl. Get back to learning.
Hello, Senior Brother.
I'd like to ask if you can find me some exercises and materials
of second-year science class.
This is the topic of the essay in the NCEE this year.
I'll give you two periods to finish it.
No break until you do.
Are those second-year science exercises?
Yes.
They're not that hard.
I agree.
I can do a lot of them right now.
If I choose science,
I might do better than you
if I put in some effort.
- Teacher.
- Where is your essay book?
I've finished it.
Come to my office before study hall at noon.
You did well on the essay.
The style is good.
You are choosing science?
Mr. Liu, what's up with the girls in your class?
Kong Shadi was talking about choosing science yesterday.
And now, here's another one.
Have you turned in your form of intent?
Not yet.
Think about it.
- Excuse me.
- Come in.
Mr. Liu, I want to participate in the math competition, too.
The placement test is close.
- Do you have enough energy for that?
- Literature is important.
Actually, He Xingwen, competitions are not the only way.
You are quite balanced in all the subjects.
You could get into a good university by participating in NCEE.
If Zhou Siyue can do it, why can't I since I have better performance?
How about this?
I have a set of exercise papers here.
Go back, finish them, and turn them in tomorrow.
Ding Xian, are you listening to me?
I am, Teacher. I will think about it.
All right.
Don't do other things in literature classes.
Did the literature teacher give you a hard time?
Not really.
Zhou Siyue,
do you think it's better for girls to choose liberal arts?
What does gender have to do with this?
I don't know.
But my parents and the literature teacher all said
that girls should choose liberal arts.
They won't let me choose science.
So, do you think you are better at liberal arts or science?
Actually, it doesn't matter which one it is
and don't mind what others say,
just choose what you are good at or like.
I got your back either way.
Really?
Would you still support me if I choose liberal arts?
Sure.
Never mind. I'll take a nap first.
Deng Wanwan, what was that about?
He Xingwen, are you the only one who needs to study? Don't I need to do that?
Aren't you ashamed that as a guy, you left all the cleaning duties outside to me.
You can do the cleaning if you want. And I can make my own choices.
I'm participating in the math competition.
I'm busy.
- Don't be mad.
- He Xingwen, you are a guy.
Can't you take care of Wanwan a little?
Zhou Siyue is also participating in the competition.
Why isn't he having so many problems?
No wonder Mr. Liu likes him but not you.
Everyone knows you like Zhou Siyue.
What are you talking about?
I'm not.
Mr. Liu thinks of him as his own son.
He's prepared to give him the recommendation quota.
I don't have the nerve to mess with a Huaqing candidate.
He Xingwen, I used to think you could get into Huaqing.
Now I think you are lucky to get into a basic public university.
Just focus on your own things. Why cynically talk about others?
If one of my friends can be recommended, I would be happy for him.
You are saying the grapes are sour because you can't have any.
You shouldn't be so narrow-minded.
Not bad. The little rabbit is biting now.
Aren't you a good teacher?
Are you stupid or not?
Zhou Siyue.
I'm not stupid.
I know.
12 to 12.
You really terrified me when you were firing at He Xingwen.
How did you become so brave?
I didn't think too much.
I just think that He Xingwen is outrageous.
Now you are standing up for Zhou Siyue?
13 to 12.
Do you remember when I was called up by Mr. Liu?
He was the first one who defended me when I arrived in the city.
That's why I'm defending him now.
Oh, Shadi. Go to a hair salon with me after the exam.
What?
I want to get bangs.
I want to look pretty.
You had a sudden realization!
Listen! I know a really good hairdresser.
Not everyone can get an appointment.
I will take you there after the exam.
Ding Xian.
Xian, are you all right?
Ding Xian, I didn't mean to do it.
Are you all right?
Is she okay?
What happened?
Let me see.
It hurts. Don't touch it.
Sorry.
Why don't I take you to the infirmary?
You guys go back to class. I'll bring her there.
Okay. Go back!
Time for class.
I've checked for you.
But I would suggest getting it checked up at a hospital.
It would be really bad if your retina is injured.
Let's go. I'm taking you to a hospital.
I think it's fine. We have a class later.
Okay. You can stay blind here.
I'm going. Should we ask for leave first?
Is it done?
Go back to your nap.
The test result won't be out for another half hour.
You only injured your eye.
Why are you talking so gently?
Zhou Siyue, you don't have to copy the notes for me anymore.
I'm worried that this will slow down your preparation for the competition.
After the exam, I'll ask my mom to get a pair of glasses with a higher presecription for me.
Don't get distracted because of me.
Okay.
Zhou Siyue.
Thank you.
What are you thanking me for?
That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about...
when everyone is against my choice,
you are the only one who told me to choose what I like.
So, thank you.
Just think it through yourself.
Ding Xian, come on!
I'm late.
I'm going to leave now.
Just a second.
When are you turning in the form of intent?
In a few days.
Finish filling it out soon and deliver it.
Okay. Got it, Mom.
- I'm leaving now.
- All right, be careful.
Zhou Siyue, do you have brain damage?
Excuse me.
Ding Xian, what is it?
Mr. Liu, should I come back later?
It's okay. Come in.
Mr. Liu, this is my form of intent.
Just leave it there.
Do you have anything else to do?
No.
Go back to the classroom, then.
Okay.
You chose science?
Are you sure you have thought it through?
I have.
I'm going to prove to everyone that even if I chose science,
I would still do a good job.
Why was Mr. Liu so mean to you?
What's wrong?
It's just that I've been making mistakes when doing exercises.
That's why he's annoyed.
But he shouldn't have been so mean.
You are tired enough already.
How should you deal with the stress if he keeps pressuring you?
Don't worry.
I've got it.
Zhou Siyue.
Whatever you do, I got your back, too.
I know.
Oh, right!
My dad bought me a new cell phone.
So, you should take this back.
Thanks.
More reading and less cell phone playing.
You too.
Two girls were peeking at you in the examination room.
Did you notice that?
Really?
It seems that you've done well.
You even have the time to look at someone else.
It's not bad.
I'm pretty sure about Chinese, English, and comprehensive literature.
And I think I've done well in math.
As for science, I did finish writing it.
You are still talking about the exam.
Did you forget what we weresupposed to do after the exam?
I didn't.
Let's meet up at the pool club after dinner.
Come on.
Did you forget what you promised me?
Of course not.
- Let's meet up at your place after dinner.
- Okay.
Shadi.
How do I look?
It's a nice outfit. This one is it.
Ding Xian!
- I prepared some fruit for you.
- Mom.
I'm changing clothes. Just a second.
What are you doing? You won't even let me in.
Here.
All right.
I'm going to pick up your brother.
You two stay at home and keep an eye on things.
All right. Don't worry.
Take me to the hairdresser when my mom is out.
Or we won't get back in time.
Don't worry. We have sufficient time.
Don't tell me the hairdresser you mentioned is actually yourself.
You...
Are you sure?
Please.
I've been cutting bangs for 15 years now.
No hairdresser is more reliable than I am, all right?
Oblique bangs, neat bangs,
European style, Korean style, and Japanese style.
I can cut all the bangs that you can think of.
Pick one.
Maybe not this time.
No.
Pick one.
- This one.
- That one doesn't look good.
It's not fashionable at all.
How about this one? That's a nice one.
Look how fashionable it is. We are going with this one.
Don't move.
Should we use it like that?
Trust me.
You will be the focus of the crowd tonight.
Shadi.
I'm a little afraid.
Don't be.
You have a small face structure. I'll just cover your face a little.
And according to my experience,
this length of the bangs is of perfect ratio. Okay?
- Just a second.
- I'm cutting now.
Take it slow.
All right, it's done.
How do I look?
I think
I forgot to count the radian of your forehead in.
What do you mean?
Shadi!
I think I can find a hoe and go work in the fields.
You are exaggerating.
It's not bad once you get used to it.
It's just that I'm not quite used to it at first sight.
So, do you have any solutions to make it look good at first sight?
Let's break up.
Slow down. I can't see the road.
Your hat completely blocked your eyesight.
Naturally, you would slow down when you can't see the road.
You did this to me.
Take care.
I'm so thirsty. I'll go get a drink.
- Hurry up.
- All right.
Excuse me, a bottle of water.
Is there no one there?
No.
Coming!
Sir!
Young lady, you are quite bold.
What are you trying to do?
Come here. Come.
What is it?
Is there a problem?
No. It's a misunderstanding.
I'm here. Let's go.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Sir, give us a table.
Okay. Just a second.
Did you smell anything?
Like what?
The smell of hair gel from Zhou Siyue.
Just a second.
This guy is using hair gel now.
What does that mean?
Come on. Let's begin now.
I'll go put the drinks down.
What are you smirking about?
Nothing. It's nothing.
Why are you wearing a hat in the room?
Stop looking.
What is it?
It's quite cute.
Really?
Stop wearing a hat.
You will lose more hair if your scalp can't breathe.
Here. There is no room for two kings in one Shenhai High School.
Why do we need so many famous people?
Watch me.
What kind of famous person are you?
Zhou Siyue might be pretty good, but you can stop bragging.
Let me try that.
Let me.
It doesn't look so hard.
Have a try. Here.
I don't know how to do that.
Let me show you.
I would suggest that you give up right away.
Have you heard of a mathematical method called "half-ball hit"?
It would take me forever to teach you. Let go.
The right hitting point should be aligned with the center of a hole
and the ball you are targeting.
Point to that spot
and you will most likely get the ball in the hole.
Have a try.
You are not putting your hands right.
Do it like I'm doing.
What's with the smile?
Your bowl cut.
It cracked open.
Zhou Siyue!
I've learned how to do it.
Let me.
That's just luck. Newbies' luck.
Impressive.
Ding Xian,
have you been practicing in secret?
No. I just learned it.
Siyue, did you notice that this girl is not good at studying,
but she's good at all the things like this?
It's just like when we were in the game room.
It's so strange.
She's talented.
And she has a good teacher.
Let me try.
You are always protecting her. I can't say anything.
- Hello. Are you Ding Xian's mom?
- Yes. That's right.
Hi. I'm Liu Jiang, Ding Xian's class adviser.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, Mr. Liu.
- Come in, please.
- Okay.
- Sorry for intruding. Shoe changing?
- No, it's okay.
Please. Come in and have a seat.
- All right.
- I'm going to get some water for you.
It's okay. I won't stay long.
It's okay. Sit.
Now I know that you two are cooperating to bully me today.
Blame it on your lack of skills.
You are good. Your cue never touched the balls.
That's because I had a bad teacher.
Give me my wallet.
I'm going to pay the bill.
It's in my overcoat.
Did Ding Xian do something at school?
Or did she not do well in the exam?
That's not it. Ding Xian's mom, calm down.
I'm here today for a school task.
I'm just here for a short home visit.
The vacation sessions are just over.
The kids are about to start their second year.
You know about liberal arts and science, right?
I know. I told her to choose liberal arts.
- Liberal arts?
- Yes.
But Ding Xian chose science.
That's not right.
I told her to choose liberal arts.
Well...
Look.
Ding Xian wrote it in the form of intent.
She chose science.
That girl. She didn't tell me.
I'll change it for her. Please let me use the pen.
Ding Xian's mom. Just a second.
I think we should ask Ding Xian's idea about this.
What if we make this decision for her and she detests it?
Am I right?
Well.
I have some thoughts about her choosing science.
- Let me explain, and you can see if I'm right.
- Okay.
I think that the science classes all have better performance.
All the students in science classes are the best ones among the elites.
When those students get together,
Ding Xian's advantage would be less outstanding.
No. Mr. Liu, look.
You see, Ding Xian has always been one of the best in junior high.
I've never had any worries about her academic performance.
She's not getting worse, right?
And my kid is quite resilient.
She never complained that she can't keep up.
As her teacher, you should encourage her.
How could you say that?
No. Ding Xian's mom, don't get agitated just yet.
That's not what I meant.
Mr. Liu, I'm really sorry.
I have other plans today.
How about we call it a day?
Okay. Don't let me keep you for longer.
All right. Thank you for making the trip.
Ding Xian's mom, I think you misunderstood me.
Here. Take care, Mr. Liu.
- I just...
- Thanks a lot. Thank you.
I just want to say that...
See you, Mr. Liu.
Take care.
Here's your change.
- All right. Thank you.
- You are welcome.
Let's go sing karaoke.
I'll do whatever you want.
Maybe another day. My parents are coming back.
How boring would it be if you are not there?
Come with us.
Shadi, I'll come with you next time.
You guys should go.
I'll walk her home.
- All right. Let's go.
- See you.
Let's go.
It's cold outside. Put on your clothes.
The bangs you got look good.
Don't try to fool me.
I know how I look.
Oh, right!
When is your competition?
In October.
So, I will be joining a closed training after school starts.
You will be on your own for a while.
Be careful.
Okay.
Don't worry about me. I can do it.
That's some big words.
Since I chose science, I will work twice as hard.
Even if you are not here, I will still do well in exams.
I will prove it to you.
All right!
I'm looking forward to your monthly exam results.
What are you looking at?
I'm back.
Xianxian, you are back.
Mom.
You cut your hair!
It's ugly.
Stop the nonsense.
It's late. Go to bed.
I'm not sleeping.
Who said that you can cut your hair?
Mom,
don't I even get to cut my own hair?
She's right.
She's not little anymore.
She has her own ideas.
We should respect her choice.
I've been working so hard to take care of everything for you.
And look what I got.
One of you ignored my decision and chose science,
and the other one knew about it and didn't tell me.
My words are nothing in this family, right?
I should have been doing all those things
without saying anything. Right?
Things are clear to me now.
Our daughter is not little anymore. She gets to make her own choices.
There's nothing I can do about that.
But there's still something I can do about you.
I don't care.
I don't care what you have to do, transfer her to a liberal arts class!
♫  The night breeze sweeps over your hair  ♫
♫  Seeing your smile  ♫
♫  It makes me want to jump in your arms  ♫
♫  You make me smile unknowingly  ♫
♫  That wonderful taste is the chemistry of love  ♫
♫  Lean on your shoulder  ♫
♫  My longing for you has left a beam of light in my heart  ♫
♫  Reminding me of the love you gave me  ♫
♫  I want to go somewhere far away with you  ♫
♫  Finding each other's sea  ♫
♫  Let the light of love heal the pain  ♫
♫  Make a wish under the starry sky  ♫
♫  After a long journey  ♫
♫  Our dreams have come true  ♫
♫  I want to go somewhere far away with you  ♫
♫  Finding each other's sea  ♫
♫  Let the light of love heal the pain  ♫
♫  Make a wish under the starry sky  ♫
♫  After a long journey  ♫
♫  Our dreams have come true  ♫