♫  For whom will the summer slow down ♫
♫  Loud cicadas chirp complicated feelings  ♫
♫  I wonder what kind of scenery awaits us  ♫
♫  For whom will the movie change its story  ♫
♫  A sudden storm, blurred vision  ♫
♫  I wonder if it's going to be a starry night  ♫
♫  As the last spark from the fireworks fade  ♫
♫  It reminds me something's better to be said earlier than later  ♫
♫  Just like that I've never stopped loving you  ♫
♫  In the sleepless winter night  ♫
♫  A season to say goodbye  ♫
♫  I try my best to be brave  ♫
♫  We will keep on going like this  ♫
♫  The secret of the answer  ♫
♫  An insoluble question  ♫
♫  All comes down to a simple thank you  ♫
I have an announcement.
The city is having a painting competition.
Each school needs to send several students to the competition.
- If anyone of you would like to sign up...
- Kong Shadi.
Come and get the application form right now.
Mr. Liu, Ding Xian can do it.
Yeah, she's good at it.
Mr. Liu, she can do it.
Come on.
What do you think, Ding Xian? Do you think you can do it?
Mom,
have you thought it through?
It's good.
But...
you are already at the last second of your second year.
I would never have stopped you at another time.
But we are at a critical time right now.
You have to focus on your studies right now.
Painting is just a hobby for you.
Don't waste your energy on that.
Okay, I got it.
Ding Xian,
I'm trying to have a good conversation. What's with that face?
You will not agree anyway.
Can you just talk?
I'm saying this for your sake.
Would I try to damage your interest?
Mom, have some water and calm down.
Is it your essay?
Let me see.
"My family."
My family is always noisy.
My mom and my sister are quite alike.
They are always angry.
Whenever things don't go their way, they will raise their voice in an instant.
"It feels like thunder, piercing through my ear."
Is this how you think of me?
It feels like thunder...
You are good with metaphors.
Rewrite it.
Can't I tell the truth?
Dad,
I will never get married.
What kind of nonsense is that?
I can relate.
Go. Rewrite it.
What's there to hesitate about?
Come on, I'll go sign up with you.
What is it?
You two, talk to her.
She doesn't want to sign up for the painting competition.
I heard that Yang Chunzi has signed up.
What is it, Little Monster? Are you afraid?
It's the heart that matters.
Never mind. Let me think about it.
The class is beginning.
Don't be afraid.
- Hey!
- Oh no!
- Sit tight.
Dad, why are you dressed like that?
Dad did something great this time.
Listen. Follow my lead later.
Ding Wencheng.
How do I look?
Great. Just great.
- Nice.
- Is the lipstick too bright?
Is it? I don't think so.
Xianxian, what do you say?
Doesn't your mom look nice?
Yes, she does.
Mom, the lipstick color is so nice.
Where are you going dressed like this?
Your dad wants to be hip.
He's taking me to a concert and a fancy dinner.
I've never been to places like that before.
We should try the classic life once in a while.
Your mom and I can take Juncong
to uplift his mind and spirit in the meantime.
People say that good habits are formed in childhood.
Xianxian, watch the apartment.
Don't worry, I'm not a kid anymore.
Right.
Ding Juncong!
Ding Juncong, hurry up!
Juncong, come on. Let's go.
What is it?
What are you doing?
What?
I'm not going. I want to watch cartoons at home.
Why would you do that? You have no ambition at all.
Your dad went through so much trouble to get the tickets.
That's right. The ticket is so expensive. You have to go.
Yeah, the concert would be excellent.
If I didn't have to do homework at home, I would love to go.
Then why don't you?
Suit yourself. I'm not going.
Then don't go. You are so spoiled.
Ding Xian, keep him under check.
Make him do his homework, and I will check it when I get home.
Come on, let's go.
Dad.
I can only help you this much.
Ding Wencheng.
Hurry up!
Hello?
Come down. I'm taking you to the venue.
I don't think I can go.
What?
What do you mean by that?
Okay.
Hello?
You two should get here now.
Do you want it?
Leave it there.
All right.
Old little brother,
the weather is great today.
Don't you want to go out?
No.
Mom and Dad are finally out today.
Haven't you been wanting to go to the game room?
You can go now. I'll keep it a secret for you.
Don't treat me like I'm clueless.
I'm not going. I just won't. What can you do?
Hi.
What are you doing here?
We're here to babysit for you. Just relax and go to the competition.
I'm the boss of the childrenat Shenhai High School.
Just head downstairs.
My brother is really...
Don't hesitate. Take your things and go.
- My brother...
- Go!
Come on!
Buddy,
why don't you hang out with me today?
What are you playing?
Stop snooping around.
This kid!
It doesn't hurt even if I look.
Handsome, what are you playing?
Can I see it?
Sure.
Why don't you hang out with me today?
Okay.
Tell me how to play it.
This is my favorite game.
Wen is a flying flag.
Isn't that Jiang Chen's vehicle?
Hop on.
Put on your helmet.
Are you ready?
We have successfully escaped!
Where is my motorbike?
Jiang Chen, are you taking me out for a ride on that?
That's right.
Look.
The weather is great today,
and you would look good on this yellow bike.
Come on.
I'm not going. It's embarrassing.
You are a nice-looking girl.
But why are you so picky?
Hop on.
I'm leaving if you are not coming.
Who's being picky?
I'll get on.
I'm going to be late.
- Go ahead.
- See you later.
Ding Xian.
Fighting!
We've prepared three themes for the competition.
All candidates should pick one among youth, family, fight for the future,
and do a piece about the theme you picked.
What was your painting about?
It's a secret.
Whatever.
With your skill, you will get a certificate or something.
The result doesn't matter.
I suddenly understood what you said to me before in the competition.
You said that there are things that may look ordinary,
but they would mean something when they come together.
Now I feel like painting is no longer
just a hobby for me.
Anyway,
thank you for what happened today.
Play!
Smash and scored!
5 points for Ding Juncong! Victory! You lost!
Ding Juncong!
He's not an elementary school student! He's the devil walking amongst men.
I don't care, do my homework.
Or I'll tell Mom about this.
Mom.
What time is it now?
Oh, no. My mom is about to be home.
What should we do?
I'll help you with your homework.
Come on, clean this place up.
- Which part?
- Here.
There's a crowd.
Hello, Uncle and Auntie.
You guys are...
We are in the same study group.
Zhou Siyue is tutoring Ding Juncong for his homework.
Yes, Auntie.
Great. That's great.
Come on. Let me see your homework.
Not bad.
You've got them all today.
How did you solve this one here?
This one...
Didn't Siyue just teach you?
- This one...
- Did you forget?
I knew you would forget right away.
You have so many people here tutoring you,
you should grab the chance and learn from them.
Copy this question to your error notebook later and do it again.
You guys are all here. I'll go make some food for you.
Wait here.
- No. It's okay, Auntie.
- Uncle, we should leave now.
- See you, Uncle.
- Auntie, see you.
My mom called me.
How did it go?
You should watch out this week.
Beware of the words of the villain.
Who's the villain?
Who is it?
Ding Xian.
Come to my office.
Did you do something this time?
No, I didn't.
Is it really so accurate?
Are you all right?
Did he scold you?
It's okay.
Did you see a ghost or something?
Xianxian, you are impressive.
You really are my little painter.
Look! Xian got first place.
Not bad, Little Monster.
- That's brilliant, Ding Xian.
- Give it back!
Oops!
You guys are acting crazy.
Can you act a little more mature?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
And a marinated egg.
Come on. Little Monster is treating today.
I'm going to order things that I don't usually order. And I want the expensive ones.
Why are you always trying to take advantage of people?
It's my plan to thank you all today.
Without you, I wouldn't have been able to even go to the competition.
Brother Song is right. I would also like to order more food.
Go ahead.
Haven't you ordered enough?
Can't I?
It's okay. Order anything you want.
Would we be able to finish all that food?
You are all acting like beasts.
Of course, we can.
You've been acting as if you starved to death in your last life.
Your food expense has set us back recently.
Did you have another spat with your dad?
What is it this time?
Things are a little different this time.
It's a little serious. It's just that I want to...
He wants to join the army, and his dad won't let him no matter what.
Are you the only one who can talk?
You are going to say it anyway.
I'm going to order more food.
Dude, I got the menu. You are...
Don't try to persuade me.
I've thought this through.
I'm not trying to persuade you.
You told me that you wanted to join the army when you were eight.
Did you forget that?
I told you that if you join the army,
I will join the national defense research.
Then, we will be protecting our country together.
How could I forget that?
No backing off from that.
It's a promise, then.
It's a promise.
Don't worry.
We are all here.
There's not too much food here.
Why don't we go back?
Everyone has a dream.
My dream is to be a pilot.
If you can be a pilot, I'll become a flight attendant.
I'll graduate sooner.
I'll start sooner.
Right. The clumsy bird should start sooner.
Who are you calling a clumsy bird?
That's me. I am.
Xianxian, how about you? What do you want to do?
Have you finished ordering?
I'm going to take it to the owner, if you are done.
Owner!
Coming.
I want... Yes, these.
All right!
- Have you ordered toast?
- Yes.
We did.
Right.
What is my dream?
Isn't his dad in the military?
Why won't he support him?
Jiang Chen has always had a conflict with his dad.
He always does the opposite of what his dad says.
That's why his dad thinks he doesn't have what it takes to join the military.
And you don't know Jiang Chen very well.
That guy...
will never give in to his dad if he sets his mind to it.
What are you thinking about?
Everyone has a dream or a target.
That's impressive.
Didn't you just get first place?
Why would you think so much?
Painting is a hobby of mine at most.
Shouldn't one's dream be big and powerful?
All dreams start from hobbies.
And I believe that you can do anything if you want to.
Hobby.
I want to be a painter.
This is not that simple.
Ding Xian, why aren't you sleeping?
I'm going to.
Are you all right?
I wouldn't have stayed up late if I knew this would happen.
Why do I feel like you are passing out?
That's nonsense.
How could you possibly understand the torture of that time of the month?
Don't. I have no desire to understand that.
This is torturing.
Maybe you should skip PE class.
Where did you get that?
The infirmary.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Xianxian, I'm going to leave now.
You are awake.
What are you doing back here?
It's too hot outside.
I don't want to join the class.
Zhou Siyue,
have you always wanted to go to Huaqing?
Why are you asking that all of a sudden?
After you told me about it the other day,
I've been thinking about it myself.
You said that dreams start with hobbies.
And since I like painting,
I should be a painter.
But...
I've never learned to paint systematically.
I can't just do whatever comes to my mind.
What's with that smile?
I'm seriously thinking about this.
I shouldn't have.
Actually, I think it's good to be realistic.
For example.
I've always wanted to join Huaqing...
only because I wanted to go to a bigger place...
and see how far I can go.
Is that all?
That's all.
Dreams...
and targets...
are just giving us the power to keep going.
So,
can I call it a dream if I want to do better in exams?
Why are you smiling this time?
I just want to say...
that your dream could be a little bigger.
Then, getting into a first-level university.
I have to take the first step.
Everyone thinks that I should settle with a basic university.
But I thought about it,
and I can't accept that.
I can get into a first-level university.
Okay.
I'll help you.
You should take a nap.
I'll explain the questions to you when you wake up.
You will feel dizzy and confused if we do that now.
You won't remember anything.
Sleep now.
♫  The night breeze sweeps over your hair  ♫
♫  Seeing your smile  ♫
♫  It makes me want to jump in your arms  ♫
♫  You make me smile unknowingly  ♫
♫  That wonderful taste is the chemistry of love  ♫
♫  Lean on your shoulder  ♫
♫  My longing for you has left a beam of light in my heart  ♫
♫  Reminding me of the love you gave me  ♫
♫  I want to go somewhere far away with you  ♫
♫  Finding each other's sea  ♫
♫  Let the light of love heal the pain  ♫
♫  Make a wish under the starry sky  ♫
♫  After a long journey  ♫
♫  Our dreams have come true  ♫
♫  Turns out time can be so magical  ♫
♫  Looking forward to seeing you  ♫
♫  Wishing time could stop at this moment  ♫
♫  Nothing can take away our love  ♫
♫  That wonderful taste is the chemistry of love  ♫
♫  Lean on your shoulder  ♫
Zhang Haojie.
Tang Jiamin.
Sounds like you did well on the test.
Safe.
You won't get bad grades with my tutoring.
Our class ranked first
in the whole second year.
But...
I can see someone has already grown proud.
Song Ziqi!
You are not about to join the senior year.
You are seniors now.
Xianxian.
We will start the extra sessions right after summer vacation.
Don't forget about camping.
This is the last time we go big before senior year.
Don't play too hard and put your mind on learning.
Do you understand?
I'm back.
Xianxian, look who's here.
Xianxian.
Senior Brother!
Why are you here?
It's vacation time. I'm here to visit you. How have you been?
I'm good.
Mom,
I want to ask you something.
Kong Shadi asked me if I could hang out with her next weekend.
- I want to ask...
- No.
Mom, this is the last summer vacation.
I said no because this is the last summer vacation.
Where are you going?
We agreed that we will go camping.
The camp beside the museum.
Auntie, this is the last vacation.
The pressure in Shenhai High School is huge.
It's good to let off some steam at this point.
I also went out back then. It didn't affect me.
You are one thing, and Xianxian is...
I'm also going there with several peers from the university.
We could watch over them. That should put your mind at ease.
Mom, just let me go.
This summer vacation is the last time I can go out.
Mom!
All right! All right!
But there's one condition.
You will focus on learning afterward.
I promise.
Thanks, Mom.
Okay. You two keep talking. I'll go prepare some food.
Auntie, let me help you.
I'm so excited.
The last summer.
Senior Brother!
Xianxian.
He looks so handsome.
He's looking better after graduation.
You've brought a lot of things.
Senior,
I've heard so much about you.
You are Zhou Siyue, right?
I know.
I grew up with Xianxian.
She mentioned you before.
This is the devil's arena. Let's leave now.
Don't get involved here! Let's go!
Senior Brother, where should I leave this?
You guys are over there. I'll get it there for you.
It's okay.
I got this.
Come on.
Xianxian,
we will have dinner at the campfire. Care to join us?
Sure.
Let's all go together.
Then, you guys get ready.
- I'll come back for you.
- All right.
Go.
See you, Senior Brother.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hey.
Why do I feel that Senior is getting more handsome?
I don't see any change in him.
It's probably because you grew up with him. You are used to him.
Anyway, I think he has become more handsome after going to university.
So, would you like to go introduce yourself?
It would be awkward if I go introduce myself.
Why don't you introduce me?
As long as Senior is around, even the air tastes sweet.
Song Ziqi!
Why are you grabbing my food?
It's too late. That's the cost of you leching over a boy. Don't grab me.
This is not so good.
Why are you also stealing food?
What?
Have you been so focused on talking about Su Bocong with Kong Shadi
that you got careless.
I didn't!
I saw it myself.
Childish.
Who are you calling childish?
Stop chasing me. I... I can't keep running. I can't.
- That's the price for stealing my food.
- Sorry.
Oh, right! I solved the question from last night by myself.
Impressive.
And what about the last function question?
Don't take this too far.
Why are you talking about studying since we are hanging out?
We didn't invite you to this conversation.
I don't want to join you.
Come on, let's go watch the sunset.
One second.
The last question from last night was not a function question.
It was about solid geometry.
What you are talking about is the 18th special exercise.
Our homework is the 18th mock.
Kong Shadi,
did you remember the correct homework as I asked?
Yes, the 18th.
Right. 18th. But 18th what?
What's your problem? There's only one 18th.
How ridiculous is he?
What are you doing? Where are you going? Aren't we going to watch the sunset?
We are going to a printing shop, My Lady. You got the homework wrong.
School is starting the day after tomorrow, dude.
Not that one.
The one from last year.
That's right.
Jiangsu University.
Thank you.
C.
Because this and this added together
is 16.16 out of 3.
That's why this is π and 16 out of 3.
Mark it here.
Xianxian.
They are talking about dancing at the campfire. Are you joining us?
Sure.
Dancing by the campfire is nice.
Let's go together.
Do you know how to do it?
You can show me.
Senior, you don't mind that. Right?
Of course.
Come on, let's go.
Senior, come and dance.
Leave us.
Have you had fun today?
Yes.
And this place is nice.
Come on, let's dance. Dance!
Dance. Let's dance.
Come on.
How do we do this?
Left, right, left, right, left, right.
Guys!
We have a tradition here.
By dancing around the campfire,
our bond will be more intense.
So, let's all dance around the campfire together. What do you say?
Great!
All right. Let's hold each other's hands.
Hold hands. Come on.
Hold hands.
Here.
Hey!
Come on, you two.
Hold hands. Am I right?
Yes!
You can sing pretty well.
What's this?
You lost your diary, right?
So,
I built a website when I had the time.
Something like a blog.
But it's not connected to the internet.
So, you can write down anything you want to say in it.
No one can see it.
That's impressive.
This is basic.
Think of it as a reward for you doing well on the exam.
I like it so much. Thanks.
I lied...
back then.
What?
I told you that my dream was to get into a first-level university.
But that's not what's on my mind.
I have been thinking about
what kind of person I want to be
or what dreams I have.
After thinking about it for a long time, and I thought of you somehow.
Don't take this the wrong way.
I...
I just think that you are wonderful.
You are doing great academically,
you care about others,
and you are not afraid to take responsibility.
I suddenly realized that
it would be great if I can become someone like you.
So, my dream back then was to...
become someone better.
But you know me. I'm a slow learner.
I don't know where to start.
And after putting some thought into it, I decided to do what you said,
which is to start with something small.
Get better performance and then get into a good university.
I shouldn't give up painting, either.
And if I ever have a chance...
Do you also think I'm dumb?
You are not dumb at all.
You were right.
To become someone better,
you need to get to a bigger,
grander place first.
That's what I think anyway.
Besides, you are already on your way.
Look.
You got a certificate in the painting competition,
and you improved your performance
after you chose science class.
Now...
I also got to know you guys.
I used to be introverted.
I didn't have any friends.
And I didn't know how to get along with people.
Anyway, now I think it's great to have Ziqi, Shadi, and you around.
You are wonderful as well.
♫  The night breeze sweeps over your hair  ♫
♫  Seeing your smile  ♫
♫  It makes me want to jump in your arms  ♫
♫  You make me smile unknowingly  ♫
♫  That wonderful taste is the chemistry of love  ♫
♫  Lean on your shoulder  ♫
♫  My longing for you has left a beam of light in my heart  ♫
♫  Reminding me of the love you gave me  ♫
♫  I want to go somewhere far away with you  ♫
♫  Finding each other's sea  ♫
♫  Let the light of love heal the pain  ♫
♫  Make a wish under the starry sky  ♫
♫  After a long journey  ♫
♫  Our dreams have come true  ♫
♫  I want to go somewhere far away with you  ♫
♫  Finding each other's sea  ♫
♫  Let the light of love heal the pain  ♫
♫  Make a wish under the starry sky  ♫
♫  After a long journey  ♫
♫  Our dreams have come true  ♫