♫  For whom will the summer slow down  ♫
♫  Loud cicadas chirp complicated feelings  ♫
♫  I wonder what kind of scenery awaits us  ♫
♫  For whom will the movie change its story  ♫
♫  A sudden storm, blurred vision  ♫
♫  I wonder if it's going to be a starry night  ♫
♫  As the last spark from the fireworks fade  ♫
♫  It reminds me something's better to be said earlier than later  ♫
♫  Just like that I've never stopped loving you  ♫
♫  In the sleepless winter night  ♫
♫  A season to say goodbye  ♫
♫  I try my best to be brave  ♫
♫  We will keep on going like this  ♫
♫  The secret of the answer  ♫
♫  An insoluble question  ♫
♫  All comes down to a simple thank you  ♫
Jealous... Jealous.
Good morning.
Xianxian.
Dad.
Your mom said that you want a cell phone.
How about this?
You can use mine and I can use the feature phone.
It's okay, Dad.
I just want a cell phone to contact my classmates.
It's nothing serious.
I'll ask them to call our landline.
Okay. So...
Maybe when the time is right, get your classmates to hang out at our apartment,
so that you can bond with them.
Okay.
You didn't write this, did you?
The handwriting is pretty neat.
Zhou Siyue wrote that.
I fell asleep during the English class and he helped me with my notes.
You fell asleep again during class!
Siyue is a nice kid.
He helped you to switch seats and made notes for you.
He does look after you.
Dad.
How do you know about the seats?
Did you ask him to do all that?
No wonder I saw you talking to him the other day.
And he has been looking after me.
No, Xianxian.
I just don't want you to be bullied.
That's why I told Siyue that...
Dad!
Please don't do that again. I don't need you to do all those things.
I can take care of my own business.
Stay out of it.
Besides, I don't want someone else to do things he doesn't like because of me.
How is he doing something he doesn't like?
Dad and Siyue...
Good morning.
Morning.
Why are you all alone? Where is your deskmate?
I don't know.
Did you fall out?
No.
We were never close.
I'm going and memorize the text at the teacher's office.
Hey, you...
Did you piss your deskmate off?
She stood me up this morning.
I was almost late.
How could I have pissed her off?
Huh?
To the other friend, I like wine.  The older, the better.
You did well.
Clearly, you spent some effort. Keep up the good work.
Thank you, Miss.
Your deskmate is Zhou Siyue, right?
You should practice with him more.
He has a standard accent.
Don't feel shy.
It's common for classmates to help each other.
I've troubled him enough already.
All right, go back.
I merely took a sip of your coke! You are so...
Sorry, I...
I didn't mean that. Sorry.
Just clean it up when you get back to the classroom.
Sorry.
What's there to look at?
Let's go. Come on.
Sorry.
It's okay. I don't need it.
Keep it on.
You are not trying to get back to the classroom like that, are you?
Thank you.
Why didn't you wait for me this morning?
I know it all.
My dad asked you to take care of me, didn't he?
That's what that was about?
Sorry for your trouble.
If you don't want to help me, you can stop.
What's with the smile?
Never mind.
I don't think you would remember.
What are you talking about?
Tell me!
I actually owe you a favor.
When I was five, I went back to my grandpa's place.
There was a flood, so I stayed at your place.
Hey. I want to use the toilet.
It's just outside. You can go by yourself.
You wet the bed. Shame on you!
You don't have a toilet.
I can't hold it anymore. That's why...
It's right outside.
I don't know how to use it.
How could you not know how to use a toilet at your age?
I'm telling my mom.
Don't tell your mom.
I'll take you to fun places when you visit the city.
You had such an awkward moment.
I can't believe you...
If you can tell the others about this, you will be dead.
So, where are you taking me?
What?
You promised!
You are taking advantage of the situation.
Hey.
How could you do that?
1:00 p.m, Saturday.
Wait for me in front of your building.
Did you leave to be thief last night?
I couldn't sleep.
You look pretty energetic to me.
Help Ding Juncong with math later.
I have plans this afternoon.
What plan could you have on a weekend?
I need to do the blackboard newspaper at school.
The school inspection is next week.
I thought you lost the election.
I'm just helping out.
Try not to do that next time.
Your effort will be in vain. And it's taking your time for learning.
Okay.
♫  The night breeze sweeps over your hair  ♫
♫  Seeing your smile  ♫
♫  It makes me want to jump in your arms  ♫
♫  You make me smile unknowingly  ♫
Checkmate!
- Withdraw!
- Don't! Don't do that.
♫  That wonderful taste is the chemistry of love  ♫
Li.
- Zhou, you are here.
- Playing chess, are you?
♫  My longing for you has left a beam of light in my heart  ♫
♫  Reminding me of the love you gave me  ♫
Checkmate!
- Are you sure?
- Checkmate!
♫  Let the light of love heal the pain  ♫
No withdrawing.
I'm sorry about this.
I didn't see it clearly.
Come on, Uncle. That's the fifth time!
Just one step!
Just one!
There you are.
Uncle, I have to go now.
You guys play.
Are you afraid to lose?
What's with you today?
Uncle, let me.
What are you doing?
It's all your fault. You took so long.
Little snail.
Girls are all like that.
What's that smell?
Hm?
Nothing.
Fried chicken wings.
- Thank you, owner.
- All right.
Let me pay for this.
I'm not used to letting a girl pay.
Sounds like you hang out with girls quite often.
How is that possible?
Just eat your food.
Are there any fun places in Shenhai?
Fun places?
The Science Museum.
And the Seaward Theater is also nice.
I know a bridge nearby with a really nice night view.
It used to be a fishing village.
As the economy has developed, this place has been booming.
Sometimes I feel like you are invincible.
You know everything, and there's nothing you can't do.
Compared with you, I'm more than enough.
And you have lost yourself over a compliment.
Ding Xian.
Actually, when you are not so stubborn, you can be...
Can be what?
You can be quite normal.
You are the one who's not normal!
All right.
If you have any place you want to go, just tell me in advance.
I will take you there when I'm free.
Okay.
Xianxian.
Senior!
What are you doing here?
I'm doing some shopping.
Is this your deskmate?
You are pretty close.
It's okay.
I think I've heard of him.
He's Zhou Siyue, right?
Yes. Do you know him?
He's the man of the hour. I heard a lot about him.
Right. You heard the CDs I gave you last time, right?
Yes, after listening, the teacher praised me.
Thank you, Senior.
No need to be polite with me.
I'll get you several more and ask Uncle Ding to bring them back.
Great.
Okay.
Go back to your meal.
Okay, Senior! See you.
See you.
Why did you eat all my fish balls?
You were having a pleasant conversation.
How could you be in the mood to eat?
But I didn't ask you to finish them all.
There's only one left.
I'm full.
Let's go to a movie this afternoon.
My treat.
All right.
What do you have in mind?
This one.
A Hollywood blockbuster.
"2012?"
Yes.
Okay. Wait for me.
I'll go get the tickets.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
Thank you.
What's this?
3D glasses.
Have you never seen these before?
I have.
Of course.
Let's go.
Sorry.
This row.
Siyue!
Ding Xian.
Are you a little sad?
Why would I be sad?
You should be sad.
Idiot!
I have returned the favor.
We are clear.
I won't need your help anymore.
Really?
The final exam is coming.
I wonder if someone will have questions for me.
Don't worry, that won't be me.
Ding Xian!
The class adviser!
Ding Xian! Why are you running?
Ding Xian, stop running.
Hello?
Hello, sir. Are you buying an apartment?
No.
It doesn't hurt to hear about it.
Buying an apartment with a loan is a great choice right now.
I'm not getting a loan, either.
Sir, even if you don't want an apartment, you can check the loans.
Why would I get a loan if I'm not buying an apartment?
Is he gone?
I have a place to stay.
And I don't need...
No, I do need money.
About your interest, let me tell you.
What's your interest rate?
You call that a low-interest rate?
Listen!  You can't fool me.
Do you know what I do for a living?
I'm a teacher. I teach math. This is nothing...
Keep talking.
This is not right.
Just a second. Don't hang up. Just a second.
Hello?
Let's do it this way. Tell me how did you get the interest?
So, what do you think
the end of the world in 2012 would be like?
I think it would be like in the movie.
Earthquakes, tsunamis, volcanic eruptions, and so on.
I don't think so.
If humanity...
is really facing distinction,
then there should be fireworks all over the sky.
To welcome death with the last bit of beauty.
Can you think of something good?
For example, what are we doing in 2012?
I might be...
watching West Lake in Hangzhou.
Hangzhou, again!
How about you?
I would be in Huaqing, doing experiments.
You want to get into Huaqing.
That makes sense.
You have such a good performance, you will get in.
And what about you?
Don't you want to see some better scenery?
I...
I can't do that.
A bigger goal...
will make a worthier challenge.
Besides,
I haven't seen many people who work harder than you do.
Trust yourself. You can do it.
I'll tell you a saying.
"There is still glory on the other side."
Nice shot!
I'll be back soon. You guys play.
There you are.
Nice work, Song.
I'm so tired.
Siyue, will you bring Little Monster to our New Year's Eve party?
Little Monster?
I thought you all find her annoying.
Why do you want to spend New Year's Eve with her?
We had some misunderstandings.
Later we found that she's a little stubborn, but she's quite a fun person.
How about you, Jiang Chen?
Do you want to join us for New Year's Eve?
You should have told me sooner.
I have an appointment with someone else.
It seems that you made some new friends in high school and forgot all about your sworn brothers.
We invited him to play basketball, and look how he's dressed.
I'm quite busy. It's hard for me to visit you.
- Just great.
- Who are you trying to fool here?
- Come on, let's go. Let's play.
- Just go.
Forget about him. Come on.
Have a good game!
What did Little Monster write on your card?
What card?
The festival card she made. Shadi and I both got one. Didn't you get one?
I'm heading to school now, Mom.
Siyue, just a second.
Wanxian told me that she has been making Xianxian Chinese medicine to make her more energetic.
You work so hard.
Let me do the same for you.
I'll pass.
Wanxian said that the medicine is really bitter.
But it's effective.
I've seen Xianxian taking it every day.
Really?
Good morning.
Morning.
Did your mom make you Chinese medicine again?
My mom said that it's winter.
I need more energy.
You are so weak that you look sleepy during classes all the time.
You should get more energy.
I'm not weak!
Just drink it.
Is it really that bitter?
It's really bitter.
It's candy.
The bitterness is gone, right?
It's blueberry flavor.
I thought you don't like candy.
Let's get to the classroom.
Aren't you coming?
Song Ziqi needs to pick something up from me.
You should go.
Let's spend the holiday together tonight.
You know that I'm not interested in festivals.
Can you not be the exception every time?
You leave earlier every year.
Can't we spend New Year's Eve together once?
Students, it's time for morning class.
Turn to Page 6 of the English text book.
Read the text from yesterday together.
Where's my stuff?
I know it all.
Kong Shadi and Song Ziqi have received your holiday card.
It's almost New Year, and I haven't received mine as your deskmate.
I thought you didn't like festivals.
I did say that, but I didn't say I don't like gifts.
Everyone except me has got one.
Zhou Siyue! Ding Xian!
Stand outside the classroom.
I never said that I didn't prepare one for you.
I drew this myself.
The original one was ruined by my brother, so I got you this one.
It arrived a little late.
Don't look at it now. Check it when you get home.
It's not bad.
You didn't go out with us the other day, and you are not learning at home.
With the time you spent on this card, you could have raised your math score by 20.
You should know when to take a win. Give it back if you don't want it.
Give it back!
You two!
Come to my office now.
Copying the text 10 times! That's cruel!
It's 15 times!
Aunt Liu saw you getting lectured. He added 5 times on top.
You two are so unlucky that you hit the tiger's belly.
He's going through menopause.
You should be thankful that he didn't put in an extra set of exercises at the end of this month.
Xianxian, are you free on New Year's Day?
Let's hang out.
I'll think about it.
I don't even know how I did on the math test last time.
You missed it the last time.
You have no idea how miserable I was.
It's not fun at all to hang out with the two of them.
How about this?
If I can do well on the math test this afternoon, I'll join you.
Really? It's a deal.
I hope you can do great on the math test this afternoon.
Here, take another bite.
You need the energy to keep writing.
With her blessing, you will be ruined on the math test.
Shut up!
What?
You said that we were not fun to hang out with.
Like we want to take you out. Am I right, Siyue?
This is not Shadi's fault.
You are quite boring.
That hurt my feelings deeply.
If you don't want your feelings to get hurt, why did you eat so much of my lunch?
Sorry, it's...
I didn't want you to be tired, so I wanted to share your burden.
That's sweet of you.
Since you are so sweet, why don't you help me out a little?
I'm a little hungry.
I mean, the handwriting will be different.
You ate all the meat!
I'll do it.
Don't say that my handwriting is ugly later.
Here, Deng Wanwan.
Send out the test papers.
Xianxian, how did you do?
Don't even ask.
The answer is that I can't go out.
You are making progress.
Let me see.
You scored twice as she has.
Enough.
Stop chatting.
Look at your scores.
How can you be in the mood to chat right now?
Aren't you worried?
The holiday is coming and you have all lost your focus.
Being late, sleeping, and chatting during classes.
You just make me proud.
Some of you haven't learned much over the semester
but got familiar with the others sitting around.
They just keep talking all the time.
We are rearranging the seats according to the final test result.
I'll see who you are going to chat with by then.
Get back to your seats!
No one leaves before I say the class is over.
Find your papers!
What are you sighing for?
Do I owe you anything or what?
Check the second to the last question on the test paper.
Question 17.
That's a question of 10 points.
We are switching seats next semester.
Where are you going to find a deskmate as nice as me?
Stop flattering yourself.
Are you really going to stay home studying during the holiday?
He said that you were making progress.
This is nothing.
I only passed two people.
Ranks and scores are not the same.
No one can progress overnight.
You've been stressed all the time.
You should relax a little.
Besides, you said that passing one person is enough.
Have you changed your mind?
The final exam is right behind the holiday.
I hope the next semester...
What?
I hope the next semester can be easier.
I have had a hard time keeping up already.
From the first year to the third is just a blink of an eye.
Easier.
Okay.
But I have to tell you, this is just the first year.
It will only get harder.
Don't say that I never reminded you.
I'm going to say this again.
NCEE...
is a competition with countless contestants and few winners.
Fine.
You remembered that.
But... don't just pretend that you are working hard.
The result will reveal the truth.
Enough of that.
The New Year's Day holiday is just three days long.
Don't spend it on slacking off.
When you come back from the holiday, whoever makes the same mistakes
will copy the question 10 times.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Go home.
School is over!
Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
We are rearranging the seats according to the final test result.
I'll see who you are going to chat with by then.
Work hard if you don't want another deskmate.
Look. Those two young people look good together.
Xianxian hasn't left her room for the whole day.
Is she all right?
I'll go check on her.
The others would want their children to spend more time learning.
And you keep visiting her room.
You will delay her process.
She needs rest.
And it's a festival.
Don't keep worrying for no reason.
She will come out if she's tired.
Forget about it.
Here. Have some fruit.
Mom, I want to go play with the fireworks.
No.
- I don't care! I want to go!
- Lower your voice!
- I want to go! I want to play with the fireworks.
- Stop yelling!
All right! All right! Fine!
Our child wants to go play. Just take him out.
People say that it's more festive outside.
We can go together.
Xianxian can take a walk with us.
Wait here. I'll go get your sister.
Great.
All you care about is playing.
Xianxian!
- All right.
- Take a picture!
It will be out soon.
Hurry up!
How do I look?
Nice.
Really?
Lower.
Like this.
Wait. Check the camera and see how I look!
Okay. I looked. You look nice.
- Really?
- Yes.
Are my legs in the picture?
Okay.
Come on, the fireworks will be gone.
Okay. I got it. Look.
What is that?
You asked me to squat down for the picture.
Where is my face?
What should we do?
The firework is almost out.
Get me a new one.
Okay. I'll go get you some.
They are all yours.
You should practice first.
All my money is gone again.
You spoiled her.
What can I do?
We grew up together.
Everyone will know if she makes a scene.
I have to make her happy.
Do you know Pavlov's dog?
That's me.
I don't know if there's a conditioned reflex,
but you do look like a dog.
I'll bite you!
Right, the New Year countdown is beginning.
Let's go watch the fireworks.
You are not in the mood?
What's wrong?
We don't have enough people.
I keep feeling something is missing.
You want to ask Little Monster to come out, don't you?
Master Zhou, I didn't notice this before.
You are worried that she will feel lonely staying home by herself, right?
How is that possible?
Then who do you want to see right now? Tell me.
I want Ding Xian here for your sake.
Why?
Think about it.
If she's here, Kong Shadi will be happy.
They can hang out together, and you will be relieved.
And the two of us...
Master Zhou, nice move!
That's right.
Song Ziqi, look!
I got two different ones.
They look nice.
The other kids will envy you.
Let's go.
Come on!
Where are we going?
I'll find you someone who can take pictures. Let's go.
Xianxian,
we are taking Juncong to watch the fireworks.
There are cut-up fruits in the kitchen.
Take things easy.
If you want to join us, call me and your mom.
I want to watch the fireworks with the others.
Little Monster!
Ding Xian!
Come out!
Hi!
What are you doing here?
The two of them say that
they don't want to watch if you are not there.
Don't blame that on me!
Come on! Get down here!
What do you say? It's almost midnight.
We will catch a cold if you don't come down.
I'm coming!
We won't get there in time.
We won't get to watch the fireworks today.
You would have been better off if you hadn't come to get me.
Hey.
It's okay. The streets are severely jammed.
We can find another place.
But at this point, I don't think we will get there in time.
You guys get off. I have an idea.
Here, sir. Keep the change.
I know a place.
We can get there in time.
Come on!
Let's go.
♫  It's okay, because you are everything I can see  ♫
♫  It's okay, to be the reason that I let you leave  ♫
♫  It's okay, because you are everything I believe  ♫
♫  Can't let this moment end, because it's about a dream and me  ♫
Sorry.
It's okay.
It's fine. The city center is jammed anyway.
And we did see it.
Hey. Look!
Oh, my god! Look! Fireworks!
Fireworks!
Impressive!
Happy New Year!
♫  It's okay, because you are everything I can see  ♫
♫  It's okay, to be the reason that I let you leave  ♫
Happy New Year!
♫  Can't let this moment end, because it's about a dream and me  ♫
♫  The night breeze sweeps over your hair  ♫
♫  Seeing your smile  ♫
♫  It makes me want to jump in your arms  ♫
♫  You make me smile unknowingly  ♫
♫  That wonderful taste is the chemistry of love  ♫
♫  Lean on your shoulder  ♫
♫  My longing for you has left a beam of light in my heart  ♫
♫  Reminding me of the love you gave me  ♫
♫  I want to go somewhere far away with you  ♫
♫  Finding each other's sea  ♫
♫  Let the light of love heal the pain  ♫
♫  Make a wish under the starry sky  ♫
♫  After a long journey  ♫
♫  Our dreams have come true  ♫
♫  I want to go somewhere far away with you  ♫
♫  Finding each other's sea  ♫
♫  Let the light of love heal the pain  ♫
♫  Make a wish under the starry sky  ♫
♫  After a long journey  ♫
♫  Our dreams have come true  ♫