Do something! God damn it!
Pull yourselves together and listen up!
When I give the sign,
just take three steps forward!
Go forward? Are you crazy?
We have to make them trip!
That's bullshit!
Let's give it a shot!
No, I can't do it!
If you can't, you'll die!
On the count of three! One!
Two!
Three!
Pull!
Pull…
No!
EPISODE 5
A FAIR WORLD
Hey.
Who are you praying to right now?
To God?
Do you think you're alive thanks to God?
You're still breathing
and moving that tongue of yours
thanks to that old man
and that guy over there who pulled out
that awesome trick last-minute.
So if you're going to thank anyone,
thank them.
You poor lost lamb.
Can't you hear the cries of those
who were nailed to the cross today?
We lived to see another day
thanks to their blood and sacrifice.
On behalf of all us sinners,
I am thanking the Lord for his decision
and their sacrifice,
and saying a prayer.
Bullshit.
You killed them yourself.
So we all get to go to heaven
if we mumble a few prayers?
Shit, then I have to pray too.
Heavenly Father,
we worked together as a team today
to send many people to your side.
Please help us send
more people to your side from now on--
Be quiet.
Me?
Or that guy?
Both of you.
What's your name?
Why do you want to know?
So I can call you using your name.
Don't call me then.
Playing hard to get?
Do me a favor.
Just leave me alone.
You're the one who talked to me first.
Did you see that bald guy piss his pants?
After that,
all the wusses behind him kept…
He's not breathing.
Go get the doctor.
I seriously thought
we were all going to die.
But once I laid back,
I really felt so much stronger.
"What is this? This works?"
Sir, how did you come up with that?
When I was young, I just--
You copied that from a movie, right?
What's that movie?
You know, the one that goes like this.
The Matrix.
So, you slacked off at work
and just watched movies in Korea?
And you, babe.
"Just take three steps forward!"
I mean, that was way too cool.
How did you come up with that
in that situation?
You said that was bullshit.
I did?
What are you bullshitting about?
You were crying,
"Are you crazy? That's bullshit!"
That's what you said.
Hey! Which country are you from?
Do you even have a visa?
You're an illegal alien, right?
Gosh. Look, boys.
Should we really let
this strange foreign guy stay on our team?
I should take this chance
to sort this team out.
Who's the leader here?
Cool guy, are you the leader?
We don't have a leader.
We're all equal on this team.
Even better.
An egalitarian society!
Shit, it's totally different
to some damn thug
who thinks he's the king
and does whatever he wants.
But, why did you get kicked out, missus?
Babe.
I'm not a missus.
My name is Han Mi-nyeo.
Just call me Mi-nyeo.
And I wasn't kicked out.
I chose to leave the team.
Those thugs and I were
on completely different levels.
They only abandoned you
and then picked the big guys.
Right before the game at that.
It's as if they knew what game was next.
Lights out in 30 minutes.
Please get ready to sleep.
Another fight might break out
once the lights go out.
Let's prepare ourselves.
How so?
We have these women and an old man.
We're the weakest team here.
Let's pick a weak team
and attack them first.
The Lord's servant
is the vicious one here.
We're all sinners already.
Our hands are drenched in blood.
Offense is the best form of defense.
Let's attack first.
During the fight last night,
do you know
how the man in front of me died?
Someone he thought
was on his side broke his neck.
Do you all trust me?
I don't trust any of you.
All right.
We should focus on
protecting ourselves first.
Let's set up a barricade
before the lights go out.
It'll help to have some form of cover.
Hey, Mr. Ssangmun-dong.
So desperate to stay alive.
But…
you really think this will help?
It looks really drafty.
What about you?
Those scumbags on your so-called team.
Do you really trust them?
Try me.
Try it, bitch.
Go ahead. Bring it on.
If I were one of them,
once the fighting starts at night,
I'd take the chance to kill you first.
After all, you're the strongest one.
How's that?
Boss.
Which team should we crush first?
Let's take the night off.
Why?
Let's cut down the numbers--
I said we rest.
Okay.
Hey.
All of you, put those down
and get some rest.
Where's the doc?
He went out to the restroom a moment ago.
The lights will go out soon.
They won't be able to easily attack us,
but let's take turns
keeping watch just in case.
Let's do it in pairs.
There's a chance
one person might fall asleep
or side with another team to betray us.
I'll…
go first.
Old people don't get very sleepy.
Hey, how can we trust an old man
like you and fall asleep in peace?
I'll go first.
I'll join you.
I'm not sleepy right now.
Then I'll go next.
Wake me up when you get tired.
Then I'll join you
if you're okay with that.
Let's do that.
The day's work has been completed.
All workers,
please return to your quarters.
All workers, please
return to your quarters immediately.
Have this.
I saved it from dinner earlier.
To give it to you, sir.
Why would you do that?
You saved my life today, sir.
I wanted to thank you.
There's no need to thank me.
I did it to save myself.
You gave me the bus fare too.
I should return the favor.
Happy?
Your name is Ali, right?
How old are you?
Ali is 33 years old.
Then just call me Sang-woo.
May I do that…
Sang-woo?
How did you end up here?
I came to Korea to make money…
Sang-woo.
No, I don't mean Korea. Here.
This game.
I came because…
I had no money.
Any family?
My mom, dad, and younger siblings
are in Pakistan.
And I have a wife and baby in Korea.
You have a kid?
How old?
A one-year-old son.
You must miss them.
I do.
How did you end up
here?
Because I had no money.
To make money.
Number 29,
what happened yesterday?
Why didn't you show up?
Sorry.
"Sorry"?
I had to stop the others from killing you.
They don't trust you.
I owed you for saving my life
on our last dive. Now we're even.
One more strike and you're out.
Number 29. You're finally here.
I gave him a warning.
We couldn't make the delivery last night.
We can't let it slide with a warning!
Then you can deliver it yourself.
Do you think it's easy to find
divers like us in this place?
Make sure today's delivery
goes without a hitch.
What? You're not even done with one?
The doctor is
much slower than usual today.
Hey, quack. Hurry up.
This all goes to waste
if the ship leaves before we deliver.
Try doing this with no sleep
and only crappy food,
barely escaping death every day.
So we tell you what the game is
and give you extra food
to make sure you don't die.
Gi-hun.
Sang-woo.
Let's switch.
Okay, sure.
Will you be okay?
What?
Looks like you were having a nightmare.
No.
I'm fine.
Hey.
Why aren't you sleeping, boss?
Can't fall asleep for some reason.
I'm keeping everyone safe.
Don't worry and go to sleep.
I trust you, punk.
The doc's still not back?
No.
It's weird.
He went to the bathroom ages ago.
Hold it.
We're in a hurry.
Should I try working on those?
I think I can do it
if you teach me a few tricks.
You think this is easy
just because I'm here like this?
I saw on the news that nurses' aides
and office managers often perform surgery.
And some of them are better than doctors.
If you're so confident, do it yourself.
You have a lot of pride for a quack
who killed someone through negligence.
If you're so good,
how'd you ruin the eyeballs last time?
Got a ton of shit from the Chinese buyers!
It's because you put someone alive
on the operating table.
Everything went to shit
when he woke up and started struggling!
We have no time for this.
The ship will arrive soon.
Gi-hun.
Hey.
What are you so deep in thought about?
I thought you were sleeping
with your eyes open.
I was thinking about the past.
The past?
We once went on strike at my old company.
We set up a barricade like this.
What kind of company did you work for?
A car company.
Why were you on strike?
They fired us because
they were in financial trouble.
I'd worked there for over a decade.
It must've been tough.
I was just about to have a baby,
and I had a million things to pay for.
They suddenly told us to leave,
so I had no alternative.
They were the ones who ruined the company
but held us responsible.
It made me furious.
Just like now,
we kept watch while my colleagues
and I occupied the factory.
Scared the police might
barge in any minute,
we trembled every night.
I remember. About ten years ago or so,
there was a big strike at a car company.
It was big news back then.
Someone died there, right?
Yes.
Goodness.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't…
have mentioned it.
Sir.
Are you okay?
-You're burning up.
-It's okay.
I nearly wet my pants that night.
What I thought was a dead body
suddenly jumped up like a zombie,
and glared at me with one eye popping out.
I dreamed about it last night.
Everyone who failed Red Light, Green Light
was shot by a sniper rifle,
so we could hardly salvage anything.
That zombie was
the most decent looking of the bunch.
I almost died delivering that day,
but we didn't even get full price
because it only had one kidney.
Is it my fault
that the zombie only had one kidney?
This guy's organs are intact?
Most of the people here either signed
away their bodies or are terminally ill.
I don't feel great about this.
Lie down.
Wait here.
We need your fever to break.
Damn it.
Use this.
What happened…
to that zombie?
What do you think?
I just beat it to death
with that over there.
Why do you ask, though?
You saw it all.
What's wrong with you?
You don't remember?
I was just…
I was a bit out of it.
You were out of it?
You even got rid of the body
with your own hands.
Number 29.
-You--
-This is my operating room!
Cut the crap and hold this properly!
Focus on the work!
Or else, liver, kidney, whatever.
I'll cut through it all!
Thank you.
Get some rest.
You need to get better
and play another game with us tomorrow.
You should go back to sleep.
I can do this alone.
We agreed to do it in pairs.
I'm already awake anyway.
Thanks…
for the water.
It wasn't for free.
Pay me back tomorrow.
-Hurry.
-They're in great condition this time.
Make sure you get full price.
Hurry. The ship is already here.
Tell me now.
What's the next game?
We don't know yet.
What do you mean?
You don't know?
We haven't been told yet.
Then go ask your boss.
I know there's someone
pulling your strings.
If he knew, he would've told us already.
-I'm sure there's a reason.
-That's your problem.
I did everything you told me to.
Go tell him to find out now!
Go back and wait!
I'll tell you before the game begins.
Fucking bullshit!
What is it?
Pull.
Calm down.
If I don't find out what the game is,
they'll kill me in here tonight.
This isn't going to get you the answer.
Give us time.
You think I trust scumbags like you?
-What else are we supposed to do?
-You go and find out.
And you.
You're staying here with me
until he gets back.
It's more risky to stay here like this.
We have to return
before morning roll call.
That's none of my fucking business!
I'm not going back
until I find out what the game is.
Fine, okay. Calm down.
Go up there and find out what the game is.
Okay.
Wait!
You have to take the key.
I have the key to upstairs
in my right pocket.
Don't try to pull any shit.
I'm not.
He needs it to enter the control room.
If you don't trust me,
you can throw it to him yourself.
Don't touch it.
-It's a bomb.
-A bomb?
This passage was made
so the VIPs can escape in an emergency.
Once they leave,
the bombs go off
and this entire place gets buried.
What kind of people are the VIPs?
None of your business.
Number 29.
Emergency. The doc's escaped.
Fuck.
Damn it.
Why do you want to know who the VIPs are?
I'm just grateful.
The diving gear, this secret passage,
it's like they prepared it all for us.
Not only are you more curious,
your voice is different too.
Let me see your face.
Do you have to do this?
Should I kill you to find out?
Who are you?
Let me see your face.
Should I kill you to find out?
Don't come closer!
Calm down. We can still fix this.
Fix this how?
By killing me?
Think about it.
Why would I kill you?
That'll only complicate things.
Things are already complicated.
Your friend is dead.
He wasn't a friend.
I can throw his body
into the incinerator and burn it.
It won't leave a trace.
It's a huge problem
if a player goes missing,
but a missing soldier is
no problem at all.
Who am I?
Who I am isn't important.
What's important is
the identity of the man you did this to.
The man you called a zombie.
The man with one kidney
who woke up on the table.
Do you know where his other kidney is?
In here.
It's in here.
He gave it to me.
-That man is my brother!
-No!
It was a woman.
A woman.
It wasn't a man.
I'll make sure I find out
what the next game is.
If you make a bigger scene and get caught,
we'll both die like dogs.
Trust me.
-We still have another chance.
-How can I trust a scumbag like you?
See?
I'm just another human like you.
Yes.
Just go back in silence.
As long as you return
before bedtime's over,
we can both live.
Then what do I have to do?
Doctor.
Let's get you washed up first.
I'm telling the truth.
It was a woman.
How can I believe you?
Before we opened her up,
we took turns doing her.
We wouldn't have done that with a guy.
If you don't believe me, check the list.
-The list?
-There's a list of all the players.
It has all their personal information.
-It even includes their medical records.
-Where?
Above the ladderway.
In the captain's room.
The captain?
You've seen him.
The one with a different mask.
I'll help you find your brother.
And I'll give you all the money I got
from selling organs!
Once we become a team…
Whether you sell off organs from the dead
or devour them,
I don't give a damn.
However,
you've ruined
the most crucial element of this place.
Equality.
Everyone is equal in these games.
Players compete in a fair game
under the same conditions.
These people suffered from inequality
and discrimination out in the world,
and we offer them one last chance
to fight on equal footing and win.
But you have broken that principle.
I'm sorry.
Captain,
we found another one.
It's number 28.
There's one more,
the one who killed this one.
Maybe he already escaped into the sea?
The oxygen tanks are all here.
He's still here.
Find him.
LIST OF PLAYERS, 1999
LIST OF PLAYERS 1
Number 29 is gone too.
Find him.
He's not on the security cameras either.
He has to be in here.
All players, please
line up immediately in the center.
Let me repeat.
-All players…
-Everyone, come out into the center.
Please line up immediately in the center.
Move it.
Damn it. What's with all the fuss again?
Boss, that doctor…
Get up.
Now!
He's very sick right now.
OCCUPATION: CHAUFFEUR
LIST OF WINNERS
2015 28TH SQUID GAME
PLAYER 132, HWANG IN-HO
Hwang In-ho.
The year 2015…
LIST OF PLAYERS 1, 2015
Number 132…
Brother.
Subtitle translation by:
Eun-sook Yoon, Sharon Choi