But now
He no longer wants to cooperate with me.
I'm afraid I can't go on.
So, what can I help you with?
Are you really?
Want to do something for me?
I want you to go to work alongside him.
To work for him.
Yes.
Because with you by his side,
I can learn many of his secrets indirectly.
I can indirectly force him to continue cooperating with me.
In addition, with you,
You can be a softener for our relationship.
Are you sure I'll just go to work alongside him?
sure.
I promise you.
rest assured,
With me around, he wouldn't dare do anything to you.
I'll tell him
You are my cousin.
Good.
I am ready to do anything for you.
But don't cry now.
Aren't you really disgusted with me, are you?
I'm here with you.
Thanks.
Rest assured, I am here.
Everything will pass.
President Xiao.
The matters you ordered me to do last time have been dealt with.
Just a few security guards.
The quality this time is also very good.
Look.
Hard work.
Hard work, brothers.
Don't skimp on your comrades.
Rest assured, Boss Xiao.
Go.
Let's go.
How were you guarding?
So many of you couldn't guard a single mine.
What is the benefit to you?
Speak up.
They attacked us from behind.
We weren't really prepared.
Sorry, Chief Do.
Okay, get out, everyone.
Let's go.
Sorry, boss.
Xiao Tianman seemed to want to confront us face to face.
Good.
Then we will face him face to face.
My brother, my brother.
Get up quickly, brother.
Wake up, wake up.
Brother, brother, enough, don't scream.
Why all the fuss? I just fell asleep.
Our mine is about to be blown up.
To prevent Xiao Tianman from stealing the mine,
Situ Hong Tang decided to blow up all the abandoned mine caves.
And now the K26 mine is about to be blown up.
my brother.
Miss Seto.
Yang Gang.
Why are you here instead of at work?
I heard about the mine being blown up so I came to have a look.
Didn't you grow up in a mining area?
Haven't you had enough of seeing her?
Our brother Gang is the best at blasting mines in our village.
His skills are excellent.
We just came to have a look.
Yes, yes, that's true.
You on the security team know too
We are now in a period of restructuring.
Many people take advantage of this period to steal mines like crazy.
We have received approval from higher authorities.
I'm going to blow up all these abandoned mine caves
I will not give them any chance.
Why are you still standing?
Get back to work quickly.
And you, Yang Gang.
I heard you drank alcohol while working.
Don't do it again.
Just go.
Son Ke.
I know that I, Xiao Tianman,
I won't stay in this place long.
So I thought before I left,
To make the brothers earn more money.
But this is Situ Hongtang,
If you blow up the mine,
We will not be able to earn a single penny.
Old Xiao.
I know your situation well.
But this time I really have no help.
Situ Hongtang represents Shanshui Group.
As for the issue of renting the Dayang village mine,
It is one of the arrangements of higher officials.
All her actions are approved from above.
And I, old Sun, can't interfere.
Brother Sun.
All I said,
I understand him very well.
But don't forget,
We are friends.
We are in the same boat.
President Xiao.
What do you mean by this?
I don't mean anything.
I know that Sun Ke is a loyal and principled man.
You must not have forgotten Jiang Xiaomei, right?
President Xiao.
Do you dare threaten me?
I don't dare, I don't dare.
I'm just reminding President Sun.
If I miss Xiao Mi,
I have pictures of you together.
Xiao Tianman, you...
Son Ke.
There's no need to get so angry.
I...
I don't really have any other intentions.
We are friends.
I trust Sun Ke,
He will not abandon his friends.
Isn't it?
I will think of a way.
I will drop you off.
Take care of yourself.
President Xiao.
Why did you come?
Did you know that Situ Hongtang wants to blow up the mine?
In your opinion, do I know or not?
Do you have any solution?
Any solution I can have?
Situ Hongtang's takeover is legal and legitimate.
President Xiao, don't joke with me.
This is your place.
So how can you let Situ Hongtang take advantage of you?
Have you ever thought,
If you let her blow up the mine,
Your loss will be greater than my loss.
Did you see that car that just left?
Do you know who she is?
President Sun is in charge of this place.
Even he doesn't have a solution.
Get out of my face.
Come here.
In such a situation,
It's not like there's no solution at all, right?
If there was an accident in the mine or something like that...
Yang Gang, I have explosives in my warehouse.
After completing the mission, your mother's medical expenses,
I'll take care of it.
I didn't tell you anything.
Give me back my daughter! Xiao Tianman, release my daughter
Give me back my daughter! Give me back my daughter!
Give me back my daughter!
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Give me back my daughter!
Give me back my daughter!
It seems that this so-called Xiao Tianman is not an ordinary person
President Xiao, everything has been dealt with
What's up?
They come every day to make trouble about Jiang Xiaomei's case
It never ends
They come again, they come again
What is happening?
These two crazy people come here every day to talk nonsense
They oppress you, who can bear this?
Even if they wronged me, you can't treat people this way
How many times have I told you?
As the leaders of the mine
We must treat miners well
Isn't it? correct
Why don't you ever remember?
You taught me a lesson, President Xiao
I really didn't learn my lesson this time
I will definitely fix myself
Good management
faster
Go give them some money later
To calm these two old men
Don't worry, President Xiao, I've already made the arrangements
Rest assured
President Xiao
Don't let me see those two old men again
Did you hear?
They come every day, I have nothing to do, Boss Xiao
This is your problem
I want results, do you understand?
concept
And there's another thing
Let the brothers continue to cause trouble
They must cause trouble
If you don't cause problems, how will the waters get muddied?
Understood, President Xiao