And Fei, let me tell you.
Gang is very loyal.
He's the best ore washer in Dayang Village.
We don't need to discuss that, right?
And the price he gave me this time,
is just this much.
So Fei, I was thinking,
your price,
could be a bit lower too?
Mr. Xiao,
you're the boss.
It's up to you.
Come on.
I am the boss,
but I've always been democratic.
Everyone knows that, right?
So it's settled then, okay?
I have things to do.
I've got to go.
Don't be so uptight.
I'm off.
Hey, wait.
Liao Fei.
Yang Gang, what do you mean?
Calm down.
I can't calm down!
Believe it or not, I could kill you right now.
It's all Xiao Tianman's plot.
Xiao Tianman's plot.
Your family is in trouble.
I can help you.
But have you thought about it?
Don't I have a family?
Don't their families need to survive?
Listen to me.
I never thought about undercutting you.
I never thought about it.
I'll figure something out, okay?
I'll find a way.
I only earn enough for my mother's medical bills.
I'll give you the rest of what I earn, okay?
Let's do as you say.
Get back to work.
What is it?
Gold. It's gold.
For real?
It's gold.
We're washing sand from Mine K26.
That means Mine K26 has a gold vein.
I'm sure of it.
We found a gold vein.
Mr. Xiao.
Now every mine entrance is guarded by security.
Situ Hongtang wants to cut off our income.
Lao Er.
Can't you handle a few security guards?
Understood, Mr. Xiao.
I'm on it.
Come back.
Don't kill anyone.
Don't leave any evidence.
Don't worry, Mr. Xiao.
Gang, come take a look.
What's wrong?
It's gold ore.
Really.
You three in front!
What are you holding?
Who are you?
- Run!
- Stop!
After them!
Stop!
Go, go.
Stop right there!
Don't run!
You three.
Did you see three guys in security uniforms?
Why should I tell you?
What are you doing here so late?
A villager from Dayang Village taking a leak on Dayang Village's land.
Jing, they work for Liao Fei.
We probably won't catch anyone tonight.
Security squad, listen up.
All security personnel,
return to the dorms for roll call.
Alright, it's over.
Damn it.
Du Jing is doing a head count.
What's the rush?
Can you outrun a motorcycle?
Hold on tight. Brother Fei is taking you for a ride.
Security squad, fall in!
Yang Gang, Yang Gaoyong, Luo Zhengqiang.
Where are Yang Gang, Yang Gaoyong, and Luo Zhengqiang?
Yang Gang! Yang Gaoyong! Luo Zhengqiang!
Here! Here! Here!
Forgot! Forgot! Forgot!
Didn't hear you! Didn't hear you!
Why didn't you say something?
Drinking on the job?
Want some?
I'm docking your pay.
Dock it, then.
About last night,
thanks.
No big deal.
You know, we're both from Dayang Village.
We've actually known each other a long time, right?
But we've never been close.
I've always known you are a
generous,
manly,
and good person.
- Me?
- Yeah.
A good person.
Who'd believe that?
Let me ask you something.
I'm curious.
Tell me, why would someone like you
work for a dog like Xiao Tianman?
No.
You aren't working for Xiao Tianman.
I'm doing it for my mom's illness.
I'm just trying to make money.
I'm just making money, too.
My brother is sick as well.
Then we're the same.
Exactly the same.
Cheers.
What's wrong with you today?
You seem distracted.
Xiaomei.
Have you been happy lately?
Yes, I have.
Do I look unhappy?
No.
I'm happy whenever you're around.
As long as you're happy.
What is actually wrong?
What's up with you today?
Talk to me.
I'm always here.
I'm with you.
You're getting sweeter by the day.
What can you do?
Do you remember Section Chief Sun?
I remember.
The corrupt official.
Right, that corrupt official.
The factory actually does a lot of business with him.
A huge part of our profit comes from him.
But now,
he doesn't want to work with me anymore.
I'm afraid I can't keep this going.
Then... how can I help?