- Wow. This is amazing, Miss Freya.
- Thank you.
But, what is the show called?
It's called "Aerial Silk".
Actually, there are many equipment to use.
Including, silk
And hoop
- And straps.
- I see
Is this the show you've told everyone
That it's exclusive only at Deep Night Club?
LIVE: Unstoppable Influence After Opening of the Host Club
- Yes.
I'd say that at Deep Night Club, there are aerial shows every Friday night.
There are aerial-pole show,
Aerial-straps show,
And body balance too.
Once you come to our club, you'll be impressed for sure.
But I start to be confused.
At first, I thought that this place was like
An ordinary host club, isn't it?
It's both similar and not similar.
It's an ordinary host club, but
I want to make it to be an entertaining club as well.
I want everyone who comes here get the best service.
And great experiences back.
I want them to be the most impressed.
Actually, there are many equipment to use.
Including, hammoch,
Hoop,
And straps.
Damn.
Is this the host club?
Khemtid.
This is cookie.
I made it by myself.
Can you try it for me?
Try it?
Let's me try it when it's delicious.
This is the last box.
I took it from Engineer boys.
Good that you didn't get screw by them.
Oh
You're so good, Japan
Who the hell eating Durian French fries with red soda?
Is that delicious?
Can I try it?
Let me try it.
Please.
No.
You just cursed on me.
The past is just the past. So, let's me try it.
Khemtid, let me try it.
No.
Let me try it.
- I bought it for you.
- No.
Just one piece.
Just one.
Nope.
Don't be stingy.
Please me then.
No.
Shit!
Wela.
Thanks for a snack.
And thanks for making a loud noise.
Even though, I didn't ask for it.
(If you want to lay low, go to this place.)
(Tham Luang National Park, Khun Nam Nang Non)
You like this, don't you?
The peaceful place.
All students in the Faculty of Business Administration, attention please.
When you are on expressway,
Has anyone noticed the billboard advertisements on the expressway?
Which advertisement is the most abundant?
Alcohol.
Are you the alcohalic?
Do you know that
The billboard advertisements on the expressway
Are the best indicator.
To show us which business is at its the glorious days
Or which business
Has the high rate competition.
Who often go to the bar?
I know that you like to go there.
Alright.
As the students of the Faculty of Business Administration.
Who
Want to invest in the business about bar and club.
Garnwela.
Why you want to invest in the business about bar and club?
Even though
You know that there is the high rate competition
And it's the red ocean business.
I think that the bar and club business are still an interesting business, Professor.
Because they have received support from the government sector.
The opening hours are extended until 4 AM.
And they also support local liquor.
So, I think there is a chance to grow up in this business.
And based on
Consumer statistics in our country,
There is a high tendency of increasing demand for alcohol beverages.
About 2-4% per year.
67% of them tend to drink alcohol outside their house.
Around 8 PM-11 PM.
And another 50 like to drink around 11 PM-2 AM.
So, I think It's a proper number in doing business.
Give your friend a round of applause.
You're so good Garnwela.
I know that you're smart and you always pay attention to the class.
But I don't know that you are interesting in this kind of stuff.
Thank you, Professor.
Khemtid.
What's up?
But for me, I don't think it is an interested business.
Because the customers has high bargain power over us.
The presence of numerous service providers for the same product
Generates many alternatives for customers to choose.
And also diminishes their brand loyalty.
For an example,
When there is a new bar in town,
Is there anybody here
That always go to the same place?
No, right?
And if he's going to refer to statistical figures
Of consuming liquor statistic.
The increase of the rate is just 0-3% per year.
It's not that much.
Because producers are increasingly focusing on producing premium liquor.
This leads to limitations in consumption.
Give your friends hand clap.
Actually, if we need the customer to be brand loyalty.
So, we can solve by Set the key activity
And key proposition.
To find the unique selling point
In our business to be different from competitors.
But in this situation...
Enough.
Give your friends hand clap.
Both of you are so good.
Your ideas are so creative.
So,
I will give you guys
Bring this topic to do an assignment
With paper based and send me.
In the next class.
And we will have a discussion.
And the time's up, Thank you all
I know that you fucked with him.
Fucked what?
You are asking me?
You like to fuck with Wela.
Like when the boys like to tease his crush.
You are so funny.
(Why don't you pick up my phone call? I'll go to your mom's club.)
(I don't see any good thing in your mom's club. I don't understand why your mom opens a club of shame like this.
Why don't you pick up the phone call?
If I graduated,
I will be gone.
Hear me out buddy.
They will find you in everywhere you go.
Can you please drag the cloths rack smoothly?
Make it smooth.
It looks ugly.
It looks like shit.
Go.
What did he send to me?
Hurry up.
Where is another cloths rack?
Why there is less cloths?
Is it complete yet?
The shop told me that there are 2 left.
Tomorrow, the shop will deliver it to the club, Lucy.
Okayyyy.
Tomorrow, I will stand by at the club, waiting for  the delivery.
If your shop doesn't deliver it to the club,
I will leave my club and act madly at you at the shop.
Understand?
Why you're still standing? Just go!
I'm tired.
You're smiling big.
Come here.
Yes.
The cloths are arrived?
But still not complete yet. There are 2 cloths left.
I will catch up with them.
You will go again tonight?
I have to go. It's my club.
You don't go just one night, it doesn't make you club disappear.
You go the club for checking. Checking the club or checking what?
There are a lot of kind of the men.
Can you trust them?
Khem.
I'm your mother.
And I remember that I have never taught you to talk to the others like this.
Do not talk like this again, okay?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to talk like this.
I just don't want you to work at night.
It's not safe.
Why is it not safe?
There are a lot of people taking care of me.
And the employees at the club, they are so put in into their work.
If they heard you, how sad they will be? Understand?
And
In the future, this club will be yours anyway.
No.
If you give it to me
I will turn it into the Mu Kratha restaurant.
Well, Khemtid.
Why do you tease your mom like that?
I told you I promise
With the scout honor.
If someone does something to your mom,
I will ruin them.
Hi there.
How does my outfit look today?
Pretty, girl!
What's about mine?
Sooooo... Gorgeous!
Slay!
Let's go!
Go!
Wait.
Do you come here too?
What's about...
Your mother?
No need.
I can take you inside by myself.
Taking care of customers are the most important, you know?
They paid us a lot. It's not a little money.
Never mind. Go, Let's do our work...
Gosh! Khemtid!
Lower your voice!
Has anyone known me?
No.
Don't tell anyone then.
What?
Then why you come here?
It's because of Aunt Sroi-Nang.
Aunt Sroi-Nang...
Don't know why she came here.
She looks down on everywhere and everyone.
Oh my.
Since the front of the club to customers.
Gosh!
Where is she now?
There.
In the toilet.
Well.
Khemtid.
You wait me here for a moment.
Alright?
Right Here. Don't move to anywhere.
I'll be back.
I must do my duty on the stage now.
Okay?
Keep waiting me here.
Don't go anywhere.
Hello Hello, welcome.
Welcome to...
Deep Night Club
Where makes you not be able to sleep all night.
And of course for Friday Night,
We have a very special show by our top of the club.
And they are ready now.
Please welcome everyone to meet with...
Deep Night Party.
Let's go!
Hey.
I thought you should...
go back to the main house. It's gonna be better.
Better?
Yes.
If you go back,
I'll give you everything.
What do you want?
A car or a condominium.
Think about it.
It's not just like you chose to live with your mom. And that's it.
Because no matter what,
You're still the Ritpreecha.
I won't let you live in disgusting place like this.
Disgusting?
If it's that disgusting, just scream.
Scream.
No matter what, I'll stay here anyway.
If you can't stand this,
you should find yourself a husband and make your own baby.
Khemtid!
Mark my word.
Dirty money from dirty bar of dirty woman like this,
She can't raise you well.
One day,
You need to go back and live with me.
But not today.
Bye.
Is that the same person?
Do you fall asleep?
You seems not sleep enough.
A professor want us to find a pair for pair work.
You pair with me.
Do you have a pair?
You don't answer my question.
I have to pay you first?
To talk to me.
Done yet?
Done.
Thanks for last night.
Why you have to keep in touch with that family?
You should block them.
They drive me crazy.
Come on.
They're still your family.
Family?
I don't count.
They are so rude.
No manner.
They thought that they're in higher class than us.
Even though dad married with Fre,
They still have no respect to Fre.
Why Fre have to endure with them?
It has to endure, Khem.
Think about it, Khem.
If you are in a trouble, you have to let them help you
And depend on them.
If I stop keeping in touch with them, what can you do?
It's fine.
I used to it.
You're always being like this.
You went to a bar. How was it?
I really want to give to this bar.
What about
You intern here first.
Maybe you will like this bar one day.
I'll try it again.
Good.
You guys. You guys.
You need to hear this interested news.
Today,
We have a newbie here.
How is that interested?
People come and go everyday.
But you're still not quit yet.
I don't quit.
If I quit, I have nothing.
But believe me.
The new one is so handsome.
I don't know what position that he works.
If he's that handsome, he probably works as a host.
James
You need to hit your mouth.
He can be anything but host.
Why?
If he's a host,
you, you, you and I
Definitely lose our jobs.
It's the fact.
His skin
is tan like Weir.
His eyes are sharp like Pope.
And his smile
is precious like Mario.
Mario?
Yeah.
I want to meet him.
You are over acting.
I tell you the truth. He is so handsome...
Hi
Wela
Did you see that newbie when you walked in?
The handsome one.
I don't know. I didn't look.
Okay Okay.
That is just the way it is.
Why does Wela have to care about him.
He's still the number 1 here.
The rank can always change, bro.
How did you get in here?
You work here?
This is a private area.
If you're not out, I will report to a guard.
Report to a guard?
If you report to a guard,
I can also report to the university too.
About what you work here.
Up to you.
I do nothing wrong.
Really?
Okay.
Go ahead.
If you tell everyone about this,
They will know that you hang out in a place like this.
What do you like?
I can recommend you.
How about that?
Sorry.
I didn't come here to hang out.
But I work here.
Alright.
I'm going to introduce you our new one.
Khemtid.
This is the first day that he works here.
This is DJ James.
Great
Ken
Seiji
And Wela.
Everyone is the senior hosts of this bar.
If you have something,
you can consult with them.
And the position that Khemtid works for our bar,
it's the important position.
It's the first barrier that meet the customers.
It is...
Right here.
Park here, please.
That's right.
Over here.
Park here.
Hey.
Car is not allowed to park here.
What?
Then, where?
The parking is there.
There.
That side.
So, park there.
Alright, park there.
Let's go.
Go, please.
Park there.
Is that true?
Handsome like that, but traffic assistant?
Hey!
What?
Or is it our club's concept?
Every employee must be handsome.
Will he make it?
Look at him.
Don't pay too much attention to him.
He's just here for fun.
He probably won't show up tomorrow.
Do you know him?
Wait.
What's wrong with him?
That's it.
Is it weird?
Here.
Madam Freya.
Isn't it too much?
Like this is good enough.
If we let him start from the top
Without being overwhelmed by it,
how much do you think he can accomplish?
But if we let him start from small points
And gradually build up the connection
Until he loves it enough.
Then he'll ask for this club from me by himself.
Oh, this is your plan.
But I think...
Before he loves it,
You might have him go find a physical therapist.
Then give him massage vouchers as benefits.
Massage vouchers...
Oh my!
I want them too!
Come work!
Oh, I want it! I want it too!
Ouch...
Hey.
What did you do last night. You look sleepy.
Just played football.
All night.
For real.
Football?
Right.
All night?
For what?
Ouch...
Let's watch the table then.
I'll go to toilet.
Hey.
Don't talk with me?
Be careful, others might know about last night.
I go to work.
Not for fun.
Do whatever you want,
But don't mess me.
Hey.
Why are you standing here?
Aren't you sleepy?
I'm sleepy.
Better go to sleep.
You spray that perfume again.
- I just...
- How many times today?
I have to smell good all the time.
Wela...
Do you spray so much like him?
He's spraying all day long.
I have to keep charming all the time.
I'm not you, man.
You can chill. You're already handsome, you know?
(5 Golden Rules of the Deep Night Club)
(Rule 5: Employees are prohibited from being lovers)
Employees are prohibited from being lovers.
What?
Oh damn.
That traffic assistant.
You're here for work?
Of course.
I'm the one working.
Not here for fun.
Cool.
Yes, cool.
Need any help, let me know.
Hey, bro.
These gloden rules...
About that rule number 5.
What's that?
Well, we're not allowed to date each other.
Why not allowed?
That they don't allow, it's right.
Trust me...
Don't date anyone here.
But I want to date you.
So, let's go.
Let's shower with me.
Hey!
Are you serious?
I'm serious, man.
Wait up!
That's enough.
Ouch!
Sorry, really sorry.
Are you injured anywhere?
Oh gosh! My shoes!
This sucks.
You know, how much are my shoes? Do you have the wisdom to pay it back?
You just tell me how much is it.
I'll pay back to you.
Hm... using a new phone, huh?
I don't know if someone stole it or not.
Laborers!
Excuse me.
Is there any problem?
Are the shoes broken?
So...
I'll keep it for now.
Is there any injury?
Hurt...
It hurts here.
It's not too bad, right?
Anyway, I have to apologize again.
We'll take care of the shoe issue.
And don't worry that won't be less fun tonight.
I'll personally take care of you.
Alright, but...
The drinks fee... what about it?
The table opening fee, the club will handle it.
Oops!
Then let's go.
Let's go.
Smells like sweat.
What the hell?
Hey.
Khemtid.
Where are you going?
Toilet!
Go to the back of the club.
It's less crowded there.
I'll go inside.
What?
Up to you then.
Wherever you go, you go.
So damn dogged.
I don't wonder why you cannot be a host.
Hey.
Are you Ken, right?
Is there still going out with customers?
You mean Wela?
He didn't do it.
He gets paid a lot for a night.
No reason for him to go out.
It'll lose the balance.
Be careful to lose it by himself one day.
Walk carefully, Noeyhom.
Watch your step.
Sit here first, Noeyhom
Ummm. I don't want to go home.
Can I have your contact, Wela?
You want to leave now?
What.
He doesn't get fire yet?
Firing thing is for the club's owner only.
Not about the customer that didn't pay anything.
I pay nothing but I can walk in.
Not just being a stinky traffic assistant in here.
Have you ever taken a shower?
Ew. Stinky. Ew.
Before you leave, don't forget to check your car.
Goodbye.
- Let's go
- Why?
Go
What did you do to my car?
You stinky!
Why my car has a flat tire!
What did you do to my car?
That. Your car is arrived.
I'll make you pay for this.
Why do you come back?
The bar will lose the customer.
The bar needs to choose the customer.
You talk like you own this bar.
What about today's bill? Who will pay?
Don't worry.
I give a tip too.
How about that?
I target it since I do traffic assistant job.
Delicious?
Yes.
You look like a different person from the university.
You Look.
So sexy.
Moreover, you know the bar's golden rules,
You need to know my golden rule too.
I have only one golden rule.
I don't do things for free. I need to get a payback.
Okay.
About what I intimidated you in the afternoon,
I'm sorry.
I just want to tease you.
But I forget that you don't like it.
I'm sorry too.
About the thing I said that you just come here to fuck around.
You're serious about it more than I thought.
Not like when you are in the university.
If you want to know that I'm the same or not,
You have to look closer.
Why are you blushing?
Or you're just good when you get a payback?
Huh? Wela.
Khemtid.
You come?
You are here.
Bring more table. I will buy you meal.
Ken, help me carry the table.
Hey Seiji, you take chairs there.
Go Go Go Go
Come Come Come Come
You.
Hey You.
Hey you.
We arrived.
Arrived?
Where are we?
Deep Night Club.
The place that you told me.
No.
I told you to go to Danai alley.
You heard it wrong.
What.
I have driven for long time.
And you tell me that it's wrong?
Great.
You just forget your phone.
We all have to get in with you?
I'm scared of ghost.
I'm already hungry.
Just walk.
I'm about to eat.
Next time, I'll buy you, okay?
It's Khemtid and Wela.
Don't forget about our deal.
At the university, don't say hi to me, if it's not necessary.
We just live separate lives as always.
Understand?
Why do I have to do this?
I will get any payback?
What do you want?
I want you to kiss at my cheek.
Kiss it.
You're lame.
So naughty.
Have you ever heard about the story of the Multiverse?
You and someone might be really close to each other.
But in another Multiverse,
he might act like he doesn't know you at all.
Why do you get in there?
For applying a job.
You said that this club have the guards.
Why you let him drunk like this?
Are you drunk?
No.
If you have a new friend, I have to be your new friend's friend too.
If you want to know what real kiss look like, I'll show you.