I'm sorry that I didn't know anything at all.
I should've known sooner.
Others just don't know that
how much awesome you are.
But I know it.
If you have time,
I invite you to go to our club.
Thank you for inviting my mom.
Keep fighting!
Go!
fighting!
Hey.
Make it for me too.
Sure.
Oh, James.
Hey, are you ready?
I'm ready.
- Go.
- Let's go.
- Keep fighting tonight.
- Sure.
Thank you so much, Khemtid.
You know, this is the first time
that hold a big event like this.
First time of Deep Night?
Yes.
If there isn't you, it wouldn't happen.
Thanks for your dedication to Deep Night.
Change from the word thanks to...
give Deep Night to me?
Do you want it now?
- Let me think later.
- What?
Please Madam Freya.
Oh, Meji?
Well... I gotta go.
Hello.
For me?
Yes.
Thanks for coming.
The important event like this, I have to come.
Are you ready?
Maybe...
If I can help something, please tell me.
No matter how many times we fight,
I'm not running away from you.
I just think about it.
Both of us are old.
What you want me to be, where I can be,
Tell me then.
Just let me close to you is enough.
Do you think our age... can have a girlfriend?
I saw Khemtid and Wela, they're so happy.
I want one.
Shall we?
Be a girlfriend?
- Are you kidding me?
- I mean it.
- Girlfriend? We're a couple now!
- Easy.
- Yes or No?
- Yes for sure!
- Great.
- Hmm?
Did you see Wela?
Nope. He did it for me and then he's gone.
Where's he then?
Wela.
Oh?
Who tied it?
Wela.
Where are you?
Why do it yourself? It's dangerous, you know?
Next time, tell me.
Wela.
Three... two...
Are you okay?
Do you want to go to hospital?
Hey, Wela.
But you got hurt.
Please let me perform first.
How can you do this?
- Aren't you worried about yourself?
- Right.
Do you smell something burning?
- Shit, Seiji's shirt!
- Hey!
- Damn, such a good day!
- I'll handle it.
- Shit!
- Fuck!
How is it?
For a while.
If it's finished, you take it to him then.
Hey.
Why?
You fix it, take it to him by yourself.
He will be thankful.
No need.
You give it to him.
You're his boyfriend...
He will be happy more than I give it.
Please take care of him.
Try moving, Wela.
See? I told you can't stand it.
Don't perform it tonight.
Easy, it's just wrapped.
Why are you so stubborn?
Your leg got hurt like this, will you still perform?
I'm worried about you.
We're worried about you.
Everyone is worried about you now.
So why aren't you worried about yourself?
My mom came today.
I just want her to see what I'm doing here.
I'm sorry.
I forgot to think about it.
But no matter what, I'm still worried about you.
I promise...
I will save myself.
I'll save you myself.
- Welcome, madam.
- Thank you for coming. Welcome.
- Thank you very much.
- Welcome.
Is this the host club?
It's like a normal club, teacher.
Let's go. Let's take photos.
- Welcome.
Thank you.
Welcome. Hello.
Tat.
Long time no see. How're you doing?
I'm good.
Soi-Nang said that you held the event here.
I've never visited here, so I stopped by to have a look.
The event will start now.
Today, men can enter for free.
Please go inside.
Dai, please take care of Tat too.
Yes.
What's wrong? Hot? Do you want a fan?
No, it's not hot.
Are you hungry? I'll have someone
bring foods to you.
I'm not hungry. I'll go back.
Hey, how can you go back?
The event hasn't started yet.
Your real couple is here.
Let him do it for me.
Meji.
What do you mean?
He and I have been divorced for a long time.
How can he be my real one?
The real one is standing here.
Come on, don't be jealous.
Really?
Yes.
Don't be like this next time.
We'll be together for a long time.
You're crazy.
No one can see it.
I'm embarrassed.
Hello, test.
Hello esteemed guests!
First and foremost, I must say that everyone here
is an esteemed guest at our club.
Today's event is called 'The Real Deep Night'.
For anyone who doesn't know Deep Night,
today let's get to know us in depth.
But first of all,
let me introduce...
The Mother of Deep Night.
She is a beautiful and talented woman.
Let's give a round of applause
to our CEO, Madam Freya!
Thank you very much.
Hello.
I'm Freya.
I'm the one... who founded Deep Night.
Let me talk about my past.
I used to be a showgirl before.
It was a profession looked down upon.
They said it had no dignity.
No one knew how much effort we took for each show.
We had to work hard, practice rigorously,
and invest so much physically and mentally.
There are many talented hosts here
who excel in acrobatics,
so I wanted them to showcase their abilities.
That's why I opened Deep Night club
to let them do the showcase there.
I would like all of you to come here and have fun,
tell others by word of mouth,
and I'd like our hosts here are proud of yourself
and have the confidence to tell others
that you work here.
Just saying, everyone probably can't see the picture.
So... are you ready?
To meet the very special show of our Deep Night hosts.
It's time to see our show!
Hold it then.
Still hurt?
Are you okay?
I can do it one more time.
You did it so professionally.
Looking at the stage, I don't know you got hurt.
I got a good partner.
- Well.
So when did you learn to play straps?
It's been a while.
I used to ask Wela to teach me.
- And then you go with him?
- Right.
It's normal.
He's boyfriend.
Thank you.
Wela.
Does it hurt a lot?
Just a little bit, mom.
If it's too tight, tell me.
It's okay now.
Thank you, mom.
You really did great today.
I've never seen you do like this.
I didn't know you could do this.
I know that you're a talented one,
But I don't know what makes you happy.
When I see you're happy
I'm happy too.
Really happy.
Thank you, mom.
Wela.
Today was really fun. Thank you for inviting me.
Sorry for making you feel bad.
No problem. Thank you for coming today.
Thank you teacher too.
You did great, Wela.
I don't know how many more times I'll surprise with you.
For me,
I didn't worry anything about you at all.
You're a talented, dedicated, and hardworking person.
No matter what you do, you will definitely succeed.
Thank you very much, teacher.
Oh.
And also
From what I saw today,
The club looks safe,
clean,
and no vices.
I think the university would have no problems.
I'll go talk to them for you.
Thank you very much, teacher.
Working here, is it okay?
Okay, dad. Don't worry.
Sure?
I've heard that you work many positions here.
When you were with me,
have I ever made you tired, huh?
Well.
When I lived in the main house,
I didn't have to do anything.
But when I'm here,
I need to do many things.
I have to take responsibility for everything.
You might think it's tiring,
but I'm very happy.
I'm happy that I can take care of mom
and the club that she loves.
Even though, in the future, this club will go broke or not,
I'll be here.
Okay.
I promise
that no one will bother this club again.
But you've grown a lot.
We haven't seen each other in a long time.
Don't you miss me?
Dad, do you want to meet mom?
It's fine.
She's good, right?
Please take good care of your mom.
Thank you, dad.
- Good.
- Okay.
Now we've reached the end of the Real Deep Night.
I'd like to be a representative
to say thank you to everyone.
If there have been any mistakes, I must apologize here.
And our CEO, Madam Freya, may have something to say.
Thank you, Dai.
I'd like to thank everyone for coming today.
I believe that today will make
many people know more about Deep Night.
If from now on anyone feels lonely,
anyone who wants to have someone to talk to,
or anyone who wants to come see
our spectacular show,
Please come to Deep Night.
But if you want to book our number one host, Wela,
You might have to book a queue for a while
because it's very long.
Wela.
Let's say something to our guest for our hosts.
Sure.
Yes.
First of all, I'd like to thank all the honored guests
who came to our event tonight.
As a representative of my hosts friends,
It must be acknowledged that
our profession is often devalued.
Even though it's a profession that
brings joy and comfort to our guests,
we never give up.
We're still determined to continue to
provide happiness to our guests.
As everyone can see, there have many hosts in our club.
We have both expert hosts
who have been here for a long time
and trainee hosts.
For me, I've been here for a long time
that I want to move to another step.
Therefore, I'd like to announce that
I'll end my role as host
to pave the way for others to rise to this position.
As for me, I will go to be a behind
to transfer knowledges and push the new generation
to become quality hosts.
Anyways, I'd like all of you love Deep Night more.
Thank you.
Everyone wants to be 1st.
And someday...
I will be 1st.
And here,
Our club's next No.1 host.
Ah...
It was an unexpected farewell.
So I'd like to say that...
Our Deep Night No.1 right now is Seiji!.
Today, I'm shocked.
What you said on stage
Have you thought about it for a long time?
It's been a while.
Because of me?
Don't flatter yourself.
Oh?
Seriously.
It's okay, you can continue doing it. I don't stop you.
I'll understand you even more than this.
No.
I won't look after anyone anymore.
I only have you.
You're not allowed to have anyone else.
Please have only me.
I got it.
Actually, my debts are almost gone.
I just want to take a break.
We will have time for each other.
Like other couples.
You don't have to be like other couples,
I still love you anyway.
Don't be stubborn.
Don't want to do it?
Huh?
I'll do it for you.
Congratulations.
Finally,
you did it.
Thanks.
And also
Congrats to you about Japan.
Take good care of him.
Are you okay, Ken?
If you're okay, I'm okay.
Ken.
Thanks for today
about repairing his shirt.
But I won't give up.
I'll improve myself.
But the true love means...
making the people we love happy, right?
Seiji.
Actually... you love Ken, right?
Then
For your happiness,
What's about...
Shall we date together?
Since Seiji loves both of us
and I want you happy as well.
Why can't we be together as three people?
Also...
If you have only me,
there will have something that I can't take care of you.
But if you have Ken,
we can help to take care of you
and let you have max happiness.
Sure?
It depends on the decision of you two.
But for me,
Pan's okay.
I think he's right.
There are two people love you.
Two must be better than one, right?
Thank you guys.
I would like to thank everyone for tonight's event.
Everyone did a great job
And our guests loved it too.
Please clap your hands for yourself.
And I would like to apologize to everyone as well
that there was chaos in our club
until today's special event had to happen.
And then there's another thing
That I have to say it
Since we didn't solve it yet.
That is the 5th golden rule.
It is forbidden for people in the club to be lovers.
I didn't forget it,
but I just want to get through this period first.
Now, everything is perfect and...
I would like to announce the punishment.
I'll use the same measures as everyone.
It doesn't matter that Khemtid is my son.
If Khemtid and Wela were to be punished
for breaking rule number five,
Madam has to punish me too.
Because now...
Seiji and I are dating.
Me too.
Now, I'm dating Seiji.
Me too, Madam.
I'm about to break 5th rule.
Because... I like James
and I'm flirting with him as well.
Then, punish me too, Madam.
Because...
I'll probably break the rule as well.
Hey, is this true?
Actually...
I also has one.
My lover is like the people in the club as well.
If everyone has no problems,
I want to cancel the 5th golden rule.
Because I feel like it goes against
my own and everyone else's feelings.
We will have love, boyfriend or girlfriend, we can take responsibility for our work.
Personal matters must not be affected
by your work. Understand?
- Got it.
Madam Freya.
It's Dai?
Huh?
What are you guys thinking?
Oh, my dear. Gosh!
This is Deep Night club.
A place that made me encounter many stories.
- It's Meji!
- Meji!
It made me learn that...
We shouldn't judge the book from its cover.
While I'm not here, please take care of yourself.
Don't sleep late.
Take care my mom too, Meji.
Sure!
I'm out.
And it made me learn that...
In the dark night,
A single star cannot light it up.
But we need many stars
to help make the night dark
come back to light
With our unity.
And the important thing...
Good love always brings good things to us.
Here everyone. I'm with the new hosts of Deep Night!
Let's get to know each of them. What's your name?
Hello, I'm James.
Now, our Deep Night is once again
the number-one host club.
Because it is a source of male hosts who love service
and give happiness to everyone.
I told you to stretch my chest!
When talking to guests,
you must have a good personality.
Please be confident.
Slowly.
Take it easy and breathe.
Let's come and experience the Deep Night together.