Hey, get off!
Call me Big Bro.
Stop messing around.
Quick, call me.
Hey, get off!
Does this scent feel familiar?
What?
The laundry detergent you brought.
Why were you abandoned?
Was it because you were too lame?
Come, I'll teach you.
Hey, hey, you're so boring.
What about you then?
Why were you abandoned?
All these debts you carry...
...were they for him?
What else?
It doesn't matter.
Let's not talk about unhappy things today.
Why not talk about it?
He looks like...
...he didn't abandon you either.
Yes.
He didn't abandon me.
One day...
...he disappeared.
We were supposed to leave together.
Didn't we agree to leave together?
Why did you leave me alone?
Why?
Was it because you didn't want me to see you at your worst?
Can you hear me or not?
Speak!
Speak up!
Why?
He can hear you.
Are you trying to comfort me?
I don't know how to comfort you.
Damn it!
What are you doing?
Use your body.
Get off!
Don't move.
Don't rush.
He loved calling me "Big Bro."
Big Bro.
It's my boss.
Answer it.
How can I answer when you're like this?
Figure it out yourself.
You're crazy!
Not fun.
Not fun, huh?
Where are you going?
Going to buy some food.
So I'll have energy. Passion!
Hey.
Passion...
...is a brand of lubricant.
Boss!
I'm back!
Tonight, I'll let you experience the charm of Passion!
Why are you coughing so much?
You didn't even come out to greet me.
What the heck!
How did you get hurt so badly?
Chenxi!
Who hit you?
Did your boss come?
I'll go find him.
It's okay.
He already left.
Are you stupid?
If you had just let him find me, it would've been fine!
Idiot.
How could I bear to let you get hurt?
But I can't let you get hurt for me either!
That makes me even sadder.
Sorry, did I hurt you?
Does it still hurt?
With this yakuza friend around...
...I decided to move on from the past.
And start a new life together.
But this yakuza is a bit weak.
He might need my protection anytime.
Don't run!
Hahahahaha!
Hahahaha!