My name is Chenxi.
A year ago, I borrowed a lot of money from loan sharks to pay for his treatment.
But the treatment didn’t work.
He still left me.
The debt collectors keep coming.
Each one meaner than the last.
But this guy who showed up—
I never expected him to be like this.
I told you,
your organs
can all be turned into cash.
I just want to leave this world with some dignity.
Once I’m gone,
you can take this body, do whatever you want with it.
Dying is too easy.
If you don’t agree,
this place looks pretty nice to me.
Do whatever you want.
Hmph, do whatever I want, huh?
Do whatever I want.
Hey, only dogs pee on the floor like that!
Damn you!
Shut up!
Hey, boss!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
I’m about to get the money, I swear!
No, boss, don’t cut out my kidney!
I’m still useful, I promise!
Don’t worry, boss.
Alright, bye, boss!
Hey, can you get the money or not?
Don’t mess with me!
What, you mute now?
I’m asking if you can get the money!
What about your friends?
Your relatives?
Your parents?
Say something!
Can you keep it down?
Do I have to pull a knife to get you to talk?
What’s that?
Wanna fight?
What are you doing?
You’re bleeding!
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Damn it!
What did you do to me?
What could I do?
What’s so funny?
Didn’t want you dying in my house.
You faint at the sight of blood?
Fainting at blood and still playing gangster?
None of your business!
There’s sugar in the water.
Make sure you drink it.
Hey!
Just a heads-up,
the bank cut off my electricity to force me out.
No power at night here.
Wow!
Hahahahahahaha!
So dumb!
Still laughing? Come help me!
Hurry up!
Not bad, huh?
Pretty good, right?
Who asked you?
Hahaha!
Damn drunk!
Is this place for rats?
So messy and dark!
Haven’t cleaned in a while.
It’s a bit messy.
Get some light in here!
I need to use the bathroom!
Alright.
Where is it?
This light is way too dim!
Probably hasn’t been charged in a while.
Fine, come closer.
Hey, you’re standing too close!
Hey!
Why’d you take the light away? It’s dark again!
You’re so annoying!
Do you want me to stay or leave?
Fine, fine, fine!
Just stay here.
You said it.
You told me to stay!
Is your kidney failing or what?
You’re staring at me while I pee!
How am I not supposed to be nervous?
Who wants to watch you?
Stop saying “damn” all the time!
How many times have you actually done it?
Think that makes you cool?
You can barely pee, are you even capable?
Come on, I’ll help you!
Alright, alright, get lost!
Hey!
Let me tell you,
I’m plenty tough!
Don’t need your help!
And,
I’m not interested in you!
Hey, what are you doing?
Turn the light back on!
Turn it on yourself!
Damn it, give it to me!
Give it!
Come get it!
Give it to me!
Give it!
You giving it or not?
Not giving!
You giving it?
You’re way too confident!
I’m the one
who’s not interested!
Damn, you talk too much!
Can’t you just pay the electric bill?
No money.
You pay it!
Damn it!