He's dead. He's dead.
Zheng Ming killed him.
The map.
Hello, Director Fu.
Dai Dai.
I have something to tell you.
Several people from Myeonghwa City died unexpectedly.
What’s important is
on the feet of Pang Bei Yuan
It's the same as Pang Bei Yuan's. It's the same as Pang Bei Yuan's.
It’s a triangle mark.
Get ready. Okay.
Call Zheng Ming.
Let’s go to the morgue.
These three people died one after another and came from Myeonghwa City.
In their bodies,
the same poison in Pang Bei Yuan's body.
And they have
on their feet.
The special investigation team caught someone.
It’s related to Senbu’s organization.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
I think
the secret of this formula
is about to be solved.
This poison has an incubation period.
Some people died after a year.
Some people haven't died for many years.
Because there are many types of Voodoo Tower.
Each batch of people who tried the poison reacted differently.
An old man in the organization
found the antidote to the tower.
But...
that old man died soon.
And strangely,
the formula of the antidote
is gone too.
Eggplant.
I've basically done it.
Happiness
I can see you.
Tell me.
Zhi Xue.
The person we just caught
has some medical background.
Zhi Xue.
In the drug factory built by Senbu,
I used to work
I was
a researcher.
He mentioned the origin of the formula
the formula he mentioned.
According to the Senbu Organization,
the undercover Heo Haishan
took the formula of the antidote.
However,
As other provinces came,
there were also people who died in the tower.
So,
they gradually realized that
the police
haven't got the formula yet.
But
Pang Bei Yuan found me accurately.
This means
some of them believe
Haesan gave me the formula.
They believe it for a reason.
But Haesan gave you a glove.
I can't see anything wrong with the gloves.
Dai Dai.
What about Haesan's watch?
Is it hidden in the watch?
I checked the watch.
I found nothing.
By the way, Team Leader Eom,
What’s the number of people
How many people are there?
A lot.
They offered a high price to find someone.
Many people
are willing to go.
Let's go to Eggplant.
So we need to find the formula first.
Eggplant.
We can't let this thing
fall into the hands of criminals.
Zhi Xue.
to harm more innocent people.
But where
Where is it?
where it is.
How about this?
Zheng Ming,
You are familiar with Haesan.
Go to Myeonghwa again.
I'll apply for the police.
to cooperate with you, 39.
The place Haesan went before he died.
The people I met.
and find out.
I'll go tonight.
Zhi Xue.
Old Ruo Xue.
I want to join too.
Zhi Xue.
Gong, Xue.
You went to Myeonghwa before?
There are still people there.
And the organization thinks
you have the formula.
It's too dangerous for you to go.
But because I was imprisoned there,
No one knows that place better than me.
So I have to go.
No way.
Stay here with me.
Director Fu 26739.
Director Fu.
Pang Beiyuan tried so hard to lure me to the warehouse.
He asked me for the formula before he died.
So I thought
only I can get the formula.
The gloves Haesan left for me
must have an ulterior motive.
Since he told me 26739,
I can't let him down.
Zhi Xue.
How about this?
Eggplant Xue.
Tomato Xue.
I'll give you three days.
You must come back if you have any results.
If you find anything,
if you find anything.
Zheng Ming.
Protect Dai Dai.
If one hair is missing,
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Yes.
I can't get the formula.
You and him
and your
your half-brother.
disappear together.
Since I became an undercover,
I've predicted my ending.
I know you're not afraid of death.
for 11 years.
It's not easy.
But if they know your background,
can your glorious medal
can still be wiped?
You know the power of the tower.
I admire you.
I won't let you be a victim.
The last place
If we still can't find any clues,
we can only go back.
All the places
This is the only place
in Haesan.
Let's go in.
Welcome.
Have a seat.
What would you like to eat?
The menu is on the wall.
Boss.
I heard your restaurant has been running for years.
It tastes very good.
We
from another city.
I just want to try your cooking.
My small shop
to come here.
What would you like to eat?
Sweet and sour tenderloin.
Chili chicken feet.
Let's order fried rice first.
No spicy.
Boss.
Sichuan Restaurant.
Who doesn't eat spicy food?
I can't.
Okay, then you decide.
What would you like to eat?
What spicy food
It's easy to serve.
Okay.
Wait for me.
Boss.
Are you alone here?
My shop is small.
One person is enough.
Please sit down.
Okay.
Captain Zheng.
In the past three days,
he was the first one
reacted to my gloves.
He must know something.
Hello.
Please enjoy.
May I ask
come from?
Boss.
Didn't I tell you just now?
We came from another city
to eat your cooking.
How did you know
my shop?
A friend is on a business trip.
and ate your cooking.
and recommended us.
A friend recommended us.
Is he
Do I know him?
I think so.
Look at him.
This is a hat and glove
And a glove.
Interesting.
Speaking of dressing,
our friend
wearing black clothes.
And
the same gloves as me.
Yiu En.
Remember,
Trust me forever.
Guys,
If you want to eat,
I welcome you.
If there's anything else,
please.
There must be something wrong with that boss.
We've searched so many places in Ming Hua,
but only this boss.
When he sees this glove,
after seeing Haesan's glove.
That's right.
And I found his watch
was three minutes slower.
Haesan had this habit
in the police academy.
Late again.
Always three minutes slower than others.
Your watch is a decoration.
My watch.
3 minutes slower than others.
You don't even know that?
Take it off.
I'll adjust it for you.
Hurry.
It'll work if things are slow.
I think he must be related to Haesan.
That's why he reacted
when he saw your gloves.
He even came to test us.
But Haesan gloves never leave them.
Only the members
know about this.
In other words,
the boss is a member of the organization.
No.
If the boss is a member of the organization,
he should know who you are.
Do you remember
Pang Bei Yuan once asked you for the formula?
And if the boss is a member of the organization,
he won't let you go so easily.
He's not a member of the organization.
but he has a close relationship with Haesan.
Then he could be
before he died.
Haesan died
The formula might be with him.
But we haven't found
to make him trust us.
We don't have time.
We have to find the formula as soon as possible.
Where is this?
The least noticeable place
is the safest place.
I know where it is.
Boss.
Where is it?
What?
What is it?
Something that can be exchanged with those gloves.
Where are the eggs with cracks?
Where's the egg?
Someone took it.
Why did you hand it over?
Because he took the same gloves as you.
The facts and the results of sharing.
We speculate that
it must be someone from the organization.
I made a pair of identical gloves
and changed the formula.
After all,
only the organization knows the gloves.
And they can confirm the only quality of gloves.
When Haesan died,
one of the gloves
was picked up by Captain Zheng.
The other one
was given to me by Haesan.
So I think
that's why the organization
the formula is related to the missing gloves.
Besides,
we’ve talked to
and the special investigation team.
They're doing their best.
The person who took the formula.
Yiu En, the owner of Sichuan Cuisine Restaurant
has been handed over to Minghua Municipal Bureau.
Director Fu.
Ms. Um.
I'm sorry.
We couldn't bring the formula back.
This has nothing to do with you.
They've tried their best.
At least they've confirmed the existence of formula.
It's only a matter of time
It's just a matter of time.
The equation
the formula.
Eggplant.
It seems
Haesan's gloves
has a special meaning.
How about this?
You two go to rest first.
Thank you.
Eggplant.
It has to be in the mountains
Chen Yishi
Where's the picnic?
You asked me to pull the grass here.
Why don't you think of me?
Why don't you ask Gao Zhuang and Jin Jin Jin?
They were on duty.
Or they'll be dragged here too.
Work hard.
I'll take you to eat chicken later.
It's super delicious.
Everyone is working.
You?
You only know how to eat. You'll never grow up.
You'll never grow up.
Grandpa.
I have a lot of help.
Just finish your work.
Grandpa.
We're all kids in front of you.
You did a good job.
Grandpa.
I think you should live in the city with me.
We don't need to repair it.
What's so good about the city?
You don't even know the people living opposite the door.
There's no one to talk to all day.
Hurry.
Come down.
Take a break.
Have a peach.
Hurry up.
Here.
Sun Kwon.
Chen Yishi
Have some peaches.
Let's go.
Eat peaches.
Are you tired?
No.
Hurry.
Have some peaches.
Sun Quan.
Come on.
Have some peaches.
So sweet.
Let's go.
Let's drive to eat.
Okay.
Why are you driving?
I'll take you there
to take you there.
Sure.
Good.
Let's go.
Go!
Grandpa.
Let me turn it off.
Come on.
Let me do it.
Go ahead.
Grandpa.
Let me try.
You can do it.
Try it.
Okay.
Be careful.
Take care.
It's so cool.
Grandpa.
Your mirror is broken.
I'm free these days.
I'll fix it for you.
Okay.
Officer,
I've searched the village.
but I couldn't find him.
When did you lose it?
Yesterday.
Wang.
One night.
Captain Zheng.
Long time no see.
Are you busy?
I'm busy.
What is it?
Last night,
Her husband went missing.
According to her,
her husband Li Jun
received a WeChat message
called Huang Hankun.
to pay him back.
After Li Jun left,
he hasn’t come back yet.
He's completely missing.
Wang Hankun.
It's Huang Hankun.
Your ears are worse than mine.
I can't hear you.
Don't get involved.
Okay.
Get back to work.
Captain Zheng.
Let’s go.
Wang.
I'll leave you to it.
We're leaving.
Okay.
Let's go.
Officer,
I can take you to confront Wang Yu.
OK.
Let's go.
You're back.
Perfect.
Let's tear down the shed.
Secretary Ma,
Let us take a break first.
How far have we been?
I didn't even have a sip of water.
Chief.
Why aren't you here today?
I had a meeting in town today.
There's food behind.
Later,
Eat it.
Those are for the dead.
I'm afraid
he'll come to me tonight.
Just eat as much as you want.
That's how young people are.
Take a rest after eating.
Remove the shed.
OK, Secretary.
Come on, guys.
Let's take a break.
and tear down the studio.
Stop.
Where are you going?
Grandpa.
Who's holding a funeral?
Why didn't I know?
Wait here.
Grandpa.
Why do you still like to join in the fun?
You brat.
Wait.
What's there to see?
I'll go too.
This bastard
looks like his grandfather.
Secretary Ma.
Whose family is holding a funeral?
Huang Hankun.
Him?
He's so young.
This...
This is too simple.
People like him
It's fine if he's dead.
What a mess.
I've
treated him well.
Is this your grandson?
Yes.
Hello.
He's handsome.
We're here to eat chicken.
He heard everything.
He's just a foodie.
Yu Wang.
Over there.
Officer.
She is Huang Hankun's wife.
Yu Wang.
Have you seen my man recently?
Did he go to your house?
No.
Didn't he go to see you yesterday?
Didn't you say Huang Han Kun wanted to pay back the money?
I don't know.
I didn't see it anyway.
Where's Huang Han Kun?
Huang Hankun.
When did he die?
Last night.
Yesterday?
My husband disappeared yesterday.
He must have been to your house before he disappeared.
Now you tell me your husband died yesterday.
So you mean
my husband killed your husband
and ran away.
Stop slandering me.
My husband is buried today.
Stop arguing with me.
What does your husband have to do with me?
Calm down.
Yu Wang,
You go back first.
Okay.
I'll find out what happened to you.
Yan Hui.
Yu Wang.
Stop right there!
Yan Hui.
Go back.
Captain Zheng, I’m leaving.
Thank you.
Hey, man.
Don't you want to eat chicken?
I make chicken at home.
Is it good?
It's not bragging.
My home-made chicken is famous for its good food.
Don't lie to me.
No.
Trust him this time.
Okay.
Grandpa.
Let's go.
Lead the way.
All right.
Go and eat.
I'll have a chat with Secretary Ma.
Okay.
Go.
Let's go.
The rooster is here.
It looks good.
Guys, have a taste.
Boss.
Are you kidding me?
Did you raise it yourself?
It's not from the next village.
I raised it myself.
The next village.
You three look unfamiliar.
I see.
Are you from the city?
You must come back
Come back for a break.
You have good taste boss
Not at all.
Let me tell you.
This chicken
are all
by myself.
See that chicken farm?
I raised it.
If it's real, I'll pay for it.
Eat as much as you want.
And
if you think it's really delicious,
when you get to the city,
give me some publicity.
You can do that.
I'll eat first.
Delicious.
I'll promote it for you.
It must be delicious.
If not,
you'll ruin my reputation.
Okay.
Let's eat, guys.
This meal is on me.
Don't take it from me.
Go to the ball.
A little hand that brings wealth.