This is it.
Turn on the recorder.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
In the middle of the night,
I was passing by here
and saw Huang Hankun peeing here.
It scared the hell out of me.
I thought I saw a ghost.
When you were carrying the body,
did you see his face?
Do you think it was Huang Hankun?
I didn't dare to look either.
When we were carrying the body,
Wang Yu covered Huang Hankun with a blanket.
He said the dead
aren't presentable.
Take him away quickly.
Okay, Director.
Come on.
Easy.
Was Huang Hankun fat or thin?
Quite thin.
Then when you carried the body,
didn't it feel heavy?
Don't dead people get all bloated?
I didn't pay much attention at the time.
Buddy,
Huang Hankun
isn't actually still alive, is he?
The time of death was 10:30 PM.
According to Wang Yu's description,
the victim was fixing a light
when he was electrocuted,
and his head hit the transformer on the ground.
But the transformer the police confiscated
tested positive for pig blood.
Also,
my autopsy results show
that his head
was injured by the back of an axe,
which doesn't match the transformer at all.
In other words,
Wang Yu gave false testimony.
Why would Wang Yu give false testimony?
Does that mean
it's very likely
they committed murder?
Then where did her husband, Huang Hankun, go?
That means the two of them committed the murder together.
They staged the scene together
and disguised the body.
But that was six hours later,
around 4:30 AM.
Rigor mortis had already set in by then.
So,
when they were shaving him,
that's why they left scrape marks on his face.
They've watched too many dramas about swapping identities.
Let's go.
The toothbrush from Li Jun's home was tested,
and it matches the DNA of the body in the coffin.
It is Li Jun.
Every household in the village has a motorbike.
Plus, many people came back for the holiday.
One extra bike
would go unnoticed.
Bali Village isn't far from here, is it?
Has Li Jun been here before?
Li Jun
is from the neighboring village.
We don't know him well.
Huang Hankun from our village
isn't very popular.
A few years ago,
creditors often came
to collect debts.
Ever since
his daughter passed away,
the debt collectors
stopped coming.
Who is Huang Hankun's wife, Wang Yu,
close to?
She's quite close with my wife.
She doesn't interact much with others.
Since she came to the village,
I haven't seen her family visit.
Even when her child
passed away,
none of her family
showed up.
What exactly happened to their child?
That little girl
only started primary school last year.
On the first day of school,
when Huang Hankun took her to school.
Hurry up. You're going to be late for school.
Come and pick me up early after school.
Go to school now.
Study hard.
Don't be late.
Take this.
Read for a bit.
Mhm.
Dad.
I'll look for him for you.
Panpan.
For this child to be born into such a family,
it's really quite pitiful.
It was only after the incident
that we found out
about Huang Hankun's drug use.
Wang Yu didn't dare
tell the villagers anything either.
After the child's grandparents arrived,
they cried and cursed a bit.
The news about the drug use
just started spreading in the village.
The forensic report is out.
The person in the coffin is Li Jun.
Huang Hankun and Wang Yu are both missing now.
Their phones are unreachable too.
The surveillance at the village entrance
didn't capture them either.
These two have no phones,
and transportation is inconvenient.
Plus, right now,
they definitely wouldn't dare use their ID cards.
They probably didn't get far.
Could they have run off together?
It's possible.
They left in a hurry.
At Wang Yu's home,
there was no obvious vehicle.
So they most likely went on foot.
Wang Yu did lie to us.
So there is another possibility.
If Huang Hankun killed Li Jun,
it at least proves
that she knows the truth.
Given Huang Hankun's personality,
to someone who knows the truth,
it's hard to say what he'd do.
So,
Wang Yu might have left on her own,
or she might have been forced.
I learned during my visit to the village
that Huang Hankun often beat Wang Yu.
So it's possible Wang Yu was coerced.
After how Huang Hankun treated Wang Yu,
do you think she'd run away with him?
If they didn't run off together,
where would Wang Yu go?
As for the nearby villages,
we've sent police to investigate.
They'll let us know as soon as there are results.
Alright.
Let's not sit around.
Let's go to Wang Yu's parents' house.
Look at how we're living now.
What kind of life is this?
At least we had a home before.
But look at us now.
It's a good thing I met your parents.
They're the only ones who have ever been good to me.
My mom is half-paralyzed.
She needs constant care.
I have to carry her to the toilet now.
What about your two sisters?
Do they come back often?
My eldest sister
during the New Year,
came back once.
My second sister.
She never comes back.
What's the point of raising daughters?
They get married
or move away.
I still have to rely on my son.
If you'd treated Eldest Sister and Second Sister better,
you could have counted on them.
I want to go work out of town, too.
But with the state you're in,
how can I leave?
What year did Wang Yu leave?
I think...
2005.
She hasn't been back for thirteen years.
Does she usually contact you?
She must really hate us.
Second Sister.
Why aren't you eating the corn?
What are you doing?
I said I'm not eating it.
Your brother meant well.
Why are you yelling at him?
He burned me.
You complain even a drop of cold water burns.
Your hands are hurt.
Why are you still touching cold water?
You'll get chilblains.
Let me wash it for you.
I broke it again.
She's going to scold me again.
I really don't want to stay here anymore.
It's okay.
You...
just say I broke it.
Then you'll be fine.
Dry your hands first.
Not cold anymore, right?
Let me show you something.
This...
is from the city.
Smell it.
Does it smell good?
Smells good, right?
It's all our fault.
We let my sister down.
What is there to be sorry for?
Like a greedy cat with a bone,
she couldn't wait a single day.
I never said I wouldn't let her marry.
She just had to run off with that red-haired punk.
Huangjiazhuang is quite far from here.
How did they meet?
Huang Hankun's grandfather is from our village.
When he came here for New Year's,
he met my second sister.
They got together.
His family was better off
than ours.
So Mom wanted to ask
for a higher bride price.
But he couldn't afford that much.
So Mom wouldn't
let Second Sister be with him.
But your sister was only sixteen then.
Sixteen is practically a grown woman.
If a good family wants her,
as her mother,
how could I refuse?
You asked for so much back then.
He didn't even want to be with my sister anymore.
In the end,
didn't she run off with that man anyway?
That man didn't pay a single cent.
If your second sister hadn't left back then,
I'll find her another good family.
I want at least a cow, no matter what.
I'm doing all this for you.
So, how are things with her
and that guy now?
They're still together.
They had a child.
A boy or a girl?
A girl.
She died in a car accident.
Oh.
I don't think Huang Hankun and Wang Yu
will come back here.
I think so too.
Let's head back to the station.
I didn't expect a swim would turn into this.
It scared me to death.
The victim has multiple stab wounds on the back.
The body is severely decomposed.
It exhibits bloating,
and there is a lot of mucus on the skin surface.
And his hands,
the skin is sloughing off like gloves.
Captain Zheng,
ask Chen Yishi and Sun Quan to help me turn him over.
Okay.
Dr. Dai,
what should I do with this?
Take it to get prints.
The eyes are completely clouded.
The body has developed
marbling and blisters.
Preliminary time of death is over 48 hours.
Also,
this person likely had a history of drug abuse.
For the detailed autopsy,
help me take the body back.
Judging by the victim's physical features,
he is very likely
Huang Hankun, whom we've been looking for.
Sun Quan,
assist Dai Yu.
Confirm the identity of the deceased immediately.
Gao Zhuang.
Jin Jin.
Chen Yishi.
Our top priority right now
is to find Wang Yu.
Hello.
Have you seen this woman?
No, I haven't.
Thank you.
Sir.
Have you seen this person?
No.
Excuse me.
Have you seen this person?
No.
Forensic Doctor Chu Mitang called.
The identity of the body in the water is confirmed.
It's Huang Hankun.
Huang Hankun's time of death was
the day we went to Huangjiazhuang for the exhumation.
We previously speculated
that in the Li Jun case, Wang Yu
was a witness,
and Huang Hankun was the mastermind.
Now that Huang Hankun is dead,
Wang Yu's role is even harder to define.
She likely went from being an accomplice
to being the killer.
So, what was the couple's motive for killing Li Jun?
Money?
That doesn't make sense.
We've learned that Huang Hankun didn't owe Li Jun much money.
A crime of passion
doesn't make sense either.
The relationship between their families isn't that complicated.
The key is that Wang Yu took such a big risk
to cover up the truth using Huang Hankun's death.
There's only one possibility left.
Impulsive murder.
In Huangjiazhuang,
Wang Yu's parents' home,
and
her current residence,
we've arranged stakeouts.
But we haven't found any trace of her.
Also,
at Huang Hankun's parents' home,
we didn't get any useful information.
Tell me,
where could Wang Yu have gone?
On the roads leaving the city,
we've set up checkpoints.
She doesn't have a phone.
She shouldn't have gone far.
Your analysis makes sense.
Let me share my view.
Let's start with Huang Hankun's body.
It was found
by the Ba River.
Based on the current
and the motor on the body,
we can infer that
the dumping site
shouldn't be too far
from where the body was found.
Within a one-kilometer radius.
Let's get back to Wang Yu.
Assuming she is the killer,
could she have disposed of the body alone?
I don't think so.
Let's leave aside the transportation.
From her home to the Ba River,
it's about 20 kilometers.
She'd have to carry not only the body,
but also a motor weighing about 30 kilograms.
Obviously, a frail woman couldn't do that.
So, at the scene,
was there a second accomplice or killer?
We don't know any of this yet.
So finding Wang Yu
is our top priority.
Huang Hankun is a long-term drug user.
Could it be one of his
fellow drug users?
All your speculations are possible.
Jinjin,
you're a woman.
You should understand women particularly well.
If you were Wang Yu,
where would you go?
We went to Wang Yu's parents' home earlier.
Her mother strongly favors sons over daughters
and has no affection for Wang Yu.
So I feel
Wang Yu probably wouldn't go back there.
On the contrary,
according to what we know,
Wang Yu's in-laws
love her like their own daughter.
The ones Wang Yu
is most worried about
should be her in-laws.
Their home?
We just went there.
Just because she wasn't there before,
doesn't mean she didn't go back later.
Let's go.
Eat more.
Child.
It's rare for you to come by.
Whether the food is good or not,
eat up.
Look at you running around all day.
You've gotten so thin.
Yeah.
Thanks, Dad.
Thanks, Mom.
Let's eat.
Why did you bring all your melon seeds here?
You should have kept some for yourself.
Dad,
I want to do some other business.
It's a waste to leave the melon seeds sitting there.
You and Mom should sell them.
That works.
Yu'er,
did something happen?
The police came by a couple of days ago
asking about you and Kunzi.
The police?
What did they say?
They just asked
if you two had come back.
They said
if you came back,
we should give them a call.
I saw you come back yesterday,
and you were in a bad mood,
so I didn't bring it up.
I was afraid
Kunzi
got in trouble again
and it would affect you.
So I didn't tell the police.
It's okay, Mom.
It's always the same stuff with Kunzi.
I'm used to it.
He's a piece of trash.
It might be better if he gets locked up.
Then we can
have some peace and quiet.
Don't say that.
Dad.
Let's eat.