Yes.
That's the guy in the photo.
Come with me.
Officer.
Let me tell you,
that guy is bad news.
Ma Xiaoxi.
For what we're about to tell you,
you need to prepare yourself.
Your brother, Ma Xiaoquan,
has been killed.
My brother...
We're still investigating the cause of death.
The person I just showed you
was the only one your brother contacted.
If you have any leads,
please tell us.
Yang...
Yang Guang.
Where is he?
I'm sorry.
Regarding the case details,
we can't disclose them to you yet.
Did he leave with Yang Guang back then?
Why did he leave?
I don't know.
You never suspected anything?
Why leave when everything was fine?
I said I don't know.
Jin Jin,
calm down.
We're not trying to pressure you.
We know that
Ma Xiaoquan was your only family left.
We've asked around.
Your brother was very protective of you.
If it weren't for him,
who knows how Yang Shan would have bullied you.
He was such a good kid.
Can you bear to let him die in vain?
His death
must be related to Yang Guang.
I really don't know anything else.
Go.
Ma Xiaoxi.
Just go!
Go!
Captain Zheng,
where is Chen Yishi?
Chen Yishi helped the local police
take Yang Shan to the station.
Captain Zheng.
The identities of the two victims
have been reconfirmed.
Yang Guang and Ma Xiaoquan
are from the same village.
According to Ma Xiaoxi,
they both left Sheqi Village in 2007.
And judging by Ma Xiaoxi's reaction,
Ma Xiaoquan is definitely hiding something.
Gao,
what did you find?
We looked into Yang Guang's father, Yang Dayong.
Because for villagers to work in the city,
they have to go through him.
So Yang Guang
throws his weight around in the village.
As for that Yang Shan,
relying on his family ties with Yang Dayong,
he bullied Ma Xiaoxi constantly.
We also asked around.
Yang Dayong isn't home right now.
He's away on business
and will be back in a couple of days.
But we took down his contact info.
Gao.
Sun Quan.
Yan Jin, canvas the village again.
Dig up information on Yang Dayong.
Find out more details.
We'll go to Yang Dayong's house.
Yes, Captain Zheng.
This is Yang Dayong's house.
And who is this?
This is Yang Guang's brother, Yang Hao.
He's not quite right in the head.
Okay.
Thank you.
You can head back.
I'll leave you to it.
Hello.
Please,
have a seat.
Who are you looking for?
Thank you.
How old are you?
28.
Do you live here alone?
My mom,
and my dad.
With my brother,
and this.
Who are you looking for?
Mom,
my brother's friends are here
to see him.
Hello.
We're from the Criminal Investigation Detachment.
Hao.
Come inside and eat.
The food is ready.
Officer.
My son is out of town.
Is something wrong?
Is this your son, Yang Guang?
It looks a bit like him,
but not exactly.
This photo isn't clear.
Your son has a good job, right?
Has he contacted you recently?
He's an executive.
Do you need a favor from him?
Where does he work?
A big company.
He doesn't even get holidays.
Auntie.
Actually, your son
isn't an executive.
He worked at our local repair shop.
He didn't contact you
because he passed away.
What?
Gone just like that?
He was murdered.
Trash.
Get up.
What?
What is it now?
Where did you get the money for the tattoo?
None of your business.
None of my business?
I sent you to school,
and you dropped out.
How many times have you dropped out now?
I've only been gone for six months,
and you quit again.
So I quit. So what?
You quit.
Quit, quit, quit.
Just like that.
If the teachers didn't know me
and show me some respect,
do you think you'd still be in school?
Who the hell do you think you are?
Look at your bangs.
Longer than a girl's.
And that snake tattoo.
Are you trying to prove you're a man?
You spend all day
messing with that hair.
You don't look like a human.
You look like a freak.
What exactly do you want?
Nothing.
Are you going to school or not?
I can't.
You're rebelling now, huh?
You want to rebel?
Don't you dare stare at me.
Keep staring!
Go on, stare!
Why are you hitting the child?
You spoiled him rotten.
That Ma Xiaoquan you hang out with,
he got sentenced last week.
That hair of yours,
and that tattoo.
Where did you get the money?
Don't think I don't know.
Aren't you ashamed?
Have you no shame?
Spending stolen money.
If you'd robbed it yourself, I'd at least be impressed.
You've completely humiliated me.
The results from the samples you brought back are in.
The deceased, Liu Ping,
is actually Yang Dayong's son, Yang Guang.
I also looked into that theft case.
In 2005, Ma Xiaoquan
stole 10,000 yuan from a Tianwaitian locker.
He was sentenced to over a year.
He was released in 2007.
2007.
He was out a long time ago.
Why was he still running?
They must have done something else.
And that Yang Guang.
And that Yang Guang,
used to hang out with him all the time.
Ma Xiaoquan returned over two thousand.
Yang Guang probably got a cut of the rest.
If you calculate based on that,
running for eleven years,
it must be something big.
After Ma Xiaoquan got out,
he must have partnered with Yang Guang
to commit another crime.
The info Ma Xiaoxi provided was somewhat useful.
But Yang Guang's mother
didn't provide anything useful.
I think the most important thing is,
both families think the other is responsible for the deaths.
Chen Yishi.
Hurry up.
I had Sun Quan
pull up records from 2007 to now,
covering all the cold homicide cases.
Everyone, bear with me.
We need to work overtime.
Focus on murders for money,
especially cases in this city from 2007.
Why don't we go grab a bite first?
We'll continue investigating when we get back.
Bring Dr. Dai.
You guys go ahead.
I'm not going.
My wife brought me food.
Then I won't go either.
I'll mooch some of his food.
I already ate.
I'll help review the files.
Thanks for your hard work.
No problem.
Thanks for your hard work, Gao.
We're leaving now.
No problem.
Bye.
What's on your mind?
The place where Ma Xiaoquan stole things back then
was Tianwaitian Billiards Hall.
Coincidentally,
I used to play pool there often in college.
Wasn't Tianwaitian right around here?
Tianwaitian closed down years ago.
Dai Yu.
Are there any clues on the body?
There are clues on the body,
but not enough to solve the case.
Both cases are quite strange.
Look.
As for Ma Xiaoquan's death,
all we know now is
that it's related to those cloths.
But the problem is,
we don't know who tied the knots.
As for Yang Guang's death, it's even stranger.
We can't even find the weapon.
Based on Yang Guang and Ma Xiaoquan's living arrangements
and ticket information,
could it be that they committed a crime in the past,
and Ma Xiaoquan killed Yang Guang then committed suicide to escape punishment?
If Ma Xiaoquan killed Yang Guang,
we found no traces at the scene.
Why suicide?
What was the motive?
It doesn't make sense.
If it wasn't suicide,
let's consider homicide.
But these two were joined at the hip.
They didn't contact anyone but each other.
Who else could they have offended?
That's not necessarily true.
They've been living under false identities for eleven years.
It's possible that they really
offended someone eleven years ago.
To hide like this,
they must have been afraid of retaliation.
It wasn't a major crime like murder for money.
They shouldn't have to hide like this.
Alright.
Everyone's done eating, right?
Let's go back and check the files.
Okay.
Boss,
check, please.
Okay.
Dr. Xie.
Xie Tong.
What a coincidence.
Yeah, I just got off work.
I'm grabbing a bite with them.
Captain Zheng.
You've met him.
And they are?
Jin Jin.
She's a colleague.
And Chen Yishi.
He's a colleague.
Who is that?
An old flame.
Dr. Xie,
we're heading back.
I'll come for a psych evaluation another day.
Bye.
You like lilies.
I bought them for a patient.
Aren't you a med student too?
This is called humanistic care.
Learn from it.
First time I've seen such a thoughtful doctor.
But how can I learn?
I can only send chrysanthemums.
Lame.
Are you okay?
It hurts a little.
Should we go to the hospital?
Forget it.
I was mostly just scared.
But we really shouldn't come here.
I seem to get hurt every time I come.
Last time, I got hurt by accident.
This time, I got hit by a bottle.
Last time...
You still remember?
Stop fighting.
I'll call the police if you don't stop!
Do that again and I'll kill you.
Are you okay?
It hurts.
I don't know if there are glass shards in there.
It's too messy here.
I'll take a look inside.
Gently.
Bear with it.
It's so long.
Will it leave a scar?
Don't worry.
As long as you don't get it wet or scratch it,
you'll be fine.
It's a pity about our game.
We didn't even get to play.
It's all ruined.
We have plenty of time.
Let's do it another day.
But midterms are next week.
You should stay home and study.
Look at you.
What did your dad tell you?
He told you to treat me to good food and drinks.
But look at you.
If I hadn't called you,
you wouldn't even have sent a text.
Ice pop.
Here is the proof.
You only bought one ice pop.
I bought it for you.
I don't believe you.
You only bought one anyway.
What's that word again?
Selfish.
Inconsiderate.
Hogging food.
What else?
Stop it.
It's just that
I have classes every day from Monday to Friday.
My schedule is packed.
Isn't today Thursday?
Where did you find the time?
It's because at my house,
the water pipe broke.
My dad made me fix it.
You just got lucky.
I'm serious.
Lately, especially at night,
you shouldn't go out much.
It's so chaotic over there.
Don't worry about that.
I won't go out until my wound heals.
Okay.
I'll go return the medicine.
You,
stay right here.
Wait for me.
Don't move.
I won't move a muscle.
You remember everything now, right?
Back then,
I was just worried about your safety.
True.
That place was pretty dangerous.
Since I got hurt last time,
I haven't been back.
All these years,
you've been in Jianglin, right?
Why didn't you contact me?
You haven't contacted me either.
I...
I have things to do.
I'm leaving.
Captain Zheng,
you made me pay for the meal.
You also made me pay for the fruit.
I'm fine with paying,
but we only bought six in total.
Six apples and six peaches each.
Luckily we didn't buy just six grapes.
Enough.
When have I not transferred you the money?
You've been muttering all the way.
True.
Captain Zheng is too stingy.
He didn't even let me finish my meal.
He sent me off with just a bowl of hot and sour noodles.
And Chen Yishi paid for the meal.
Let's take a break.
Good work, everyone.
Come on.
Have some fruit
and recharge.
This fruit
is my treat,
but Captain Zheng paid.
Don't forget.
Come on.
Dr. Chu.
What good food did you have?
He just treated me to a bowl of hot and sour noodles.
He made me leave before I even finished.
Chen Yishi ended up paying the bill.
Rest a bit longer.
Have some fruit.
Take a look at this one.
I think I found it.
On June 1, 2007,
there was a kidnapping and murder case.
Two suspects are still at large.
The victim was Feng Youning
from Jianglin University.
She worked part-time at Tianwaitian Billiards Hall.
This is the ransom note.
The amount involved was 500,000.
As demanded by the suspects,
the ransom was left at Tianwaitian.
Captain Yan,
I asked the girl at the front desk.
Feng Youning
switched shifts last week.
Think carefully.
Are you sure you locked the money in this cabinet?
Did you see anyone come to take the money?
I really didn't see anyone.
Do you know where your daughter
usually goes?
Especially
on Thursdays.
If she's not in class
or working,
what would she be doing?
The suspect definitely
staked out the place beforehand
or followed you.
The more details you give us,
the faster we can find her.
Stop asking me.
I really don't know.
Aren't you the police?
Go find her!
He called and told me to leave it here and go.
I wanted to wait,
but
he must have been watching me.
He called again.
Told me to drop it and leave.
If I didn't, he would...
Calm down.
You should trust the police.
No call yet?
No.
Since the call yesterday,
until now,
there hasn't been another call.
Get ready to trace the call.
Once a call comes in,
start searching immediately.
Five hundred thousand
isn't a small amount.
Your family isn't rich. This money...
What do you mean?
Are you saying I stole the money?
Let me tell you,
to save my daughter,
I'd give my life.
Calm down first.
What we mean is,
in such a short time,
getting that much money
isn't easy.
Why didn't you call the police immediately?
I was scared.
You must have borrowed this money
from relatives and friends.
That's the money I saved half my life
to buy a house.
Let me in.
Calm down.
You can't go in.
Ningning.
Time of death was over 12 hours ago.
Her throat was slit.
Comfort the family.
Step up the investigation.
Yes.
This case...
It left a deep impression on me.
Like a knife
plunged deep into my chest.
Over the years,
we haven't stopped investigating
the suspects.
However it turns out now,
we can finally give the public and the family some closure.
I remember back then,
by the time we arrived at the scene,
five days had already passed.
The victim had already been killed.
It was pouring rain in the mountains.
The scene had been badly destroyed
by the rain.
The ransom had been taken by the suspects.
The only clue we found at the scene
was the ransom note
provided by the victim's family,
and
the location for the ransom drop,
Tianwaitian Billiards Hall.
Afterwards,
we investigated a large number of suspicious individuals,
but found no relevant leads.
What did that man look like?
That man...
was quite tall.
He was wearing a hat
and holding a bag.
What color were his clothes and shoes?
Do you remember?
It was too dark.
I don't remember clearly.
Do you remember the exact time?
Around nine or ten.
Chief Fu.
Have a seat.
Listen in.
According to the family's testimony,
the callers from 226739 were two men.
They estimated
they are between 20 and 30 years old.
One of them spoke
the Huishan dialect,
so he is likely an outsider.
Also,
based on the profile of the ransom note,
there are
two types of handwriting in it.
One of the writers
is impatient
and ruthless.
The other person
might be imitating handwriting.
He's not as bold,
but he's smarter.
The two of them
used
pieced-together handwriting
to write a ransom note
and sent it to the victim's home.
And the paper used for this ransom note...
It's from the victim's notebook.
It's her.