Come on.
[God of Post]
Okay.
Stop writing.
Give it back.
Give it back!
Give it back to me.
Stop crying.
Ruoxi, you're an idiot.
Idiot.
Ruoxi Zhang.
Today is the last day of our ten-year contract.
You still didn't show up.
I won't wait for you anymore.
Rammy.
I'm sorry for the mistake.
Sorry.
Cheers
Cheers.
[Hello, the number you have dialled is unavailable.]
Monitor.
What's wrong with her?
Rammy.
Today is the last day we agreed.
He's still not here.
Monitor.
Is she going to give up on the big shot?
Here, Xia Mi, I'll drink with you.
Just give up.
What's there to care about such a jerk?
There are plenty of girls in the world.
We should hang ourselves on the same tree.
Stop talking.
Boss must have his own reasons.
What reasons?
You men only protect men.
Why can't you tell me your difficulties?
Why do you have to hide?
You're right.
He can't tell me his difficulties.
Is he looking down on himself or me?
All men are cowards.
Coward
Monitor, what should we do?
Come on
If you want to drink,
I'll drink with you.
Let's get drunk.
Monitor, you're a good friend.
Let's get drunk!
Drink slowly, monitor
Drink slowly
Are you going to the hospital?
You're...
Ruoxi.
My fingertips appear in the sky
Your smile becomes gentle
Haze suddenly appears in the sky
Your smile has become
Stop drinking.
You appeared in front of me
in front of me
Monitor, I'll take him home first.
Okay.
Please take care of her.
No problem.
I'll send her home later. Don't worry.
Slow down.
Your smile blurs
Get up. Let me carry you.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
I want to go back with you.
Let me know when you arrive. Okay.
My dear.
I told you to drink less.
Xi.
Which room?
Room 305.
Did you see the fish?
Every moment
Xiammy.
I'll take you home if you're drunk. Stop singing.
I'm not going back.
Let me tell you.
Every time I sing this song, he will come out.
You don't believe me?
I'll show you a magic trick.
Ruoxi Zhang.
Come out.
Look.
He's out, right?
Xiammy.
Fan Yuan.
We'll talk about more later.
Since you're back,
take her home.
Ruoxi Zhang.
You're great.
You know you carried me on your back in your dream.
Like this.
I'll give you 90 points.
I'm afraid you'll be proud if I'm ten less.
Xiammy,
I'll carry you on my back every day.
Okay?
Really?
Pinky swear.
Forget it.
Pinky swear can never be realized.
I won't play with you.
Sorry, Xiammy.
It's all my fault.
Why did you say that?
You're good.
You're not always with me in my dreams.
It's either that bad Zhang Ruoxi's fault.
Rammy.
This is not a dream.
I'm really...
Ruoxi Zhang.
You never gave me flowers in your dreams.
If you give me one bouquet, I'll give you full marks.
Okay?
Which one do you want?
I want
This one.
Okay, I'll buy it for you.
What a beautiful flower.
[Jang Ruohee]
The meaning of roses
Love me every day.
Will you love me every day?
I will.
Liar.
You'll disappear tomorrow morning.
Xiammy.
Look at me.
I'm really back.
Look. Touch it.
Liar! Liar!
If you really come back,
why didn't you come back earlier?
Do you know how long I waited for you?
To repay the society with patriotism.
Come in.
Sir.
Could you please check
if there's a student
is there a student named Zhang Ruoxi?
Please.
FILM ACADEMY
[Job Recruitment Information Center]
Then you changed your phone number.
Everyone told me not to wait for him.
I don't want to listen to them either.
Maybe
you came to Beijing, I don't know.
Or you didn't come to Beijing at all.
or...
Or...
You're an actor, but I don't know.
I went to watch TV series.
I watched all kinds of dramas.
but I didn't see her name.
Zhang Ruoxi.
How can I trust you again?
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
What's the use of apologizing?
Don't come to my dream again.
I don't want to experience
I'm happy when I sleep every day.
When I wake up, everything will be in vain.
I won't
miss you
or wait for you.
Rammy.
I'm really back.
I will never leave you again.
Never.
The meaning of roses
Love me every day.
Will you love me every day?
I will.
You're dreaming again.
Hello, Xiao Yu.
Xia Mi, look at the hot search.
Ruoxi is on the hot search.
Change her name.
More.
Three minutes.
I want all the scenes he's done.
Let's watch his road show today.
Zhang is not a rookie.
He's a drama actor.
He's really good at acting.
He's handsome too.
I think he's handsome as a man.
Next,
I'd like to interview our leading actress, Ruoxi Zhang.
Mr. Zhang.
Hello, Mr. Zhang.
Hello.
I heard you've been in the drama troupe.
It's your first drama.
Why did you suddenly decide to be in a drama?
It wasn't a sudden decision.
I've been trying many different roles.
but I didn't have a good chance.
It's a great drama
such an excellent drama
thanks to Director Wu.
Thank you for giving me such a precious opportunity.
Don't mention it.
Ruoxi is a treasure actress.
I worked with him ten years ago.
At that time, I found
he was very talented.
So,
He deserves to be seen by more people.
Thank you.
I didn't expect you two to be so close.
The spring breeze ferry is still on air.
Your performance is also popular
Many audiences are very concerned about you.
Can you tell us
Can you tell us a little?
Actually,
I'm trying to get the lead role of a drama.
This drama
is a promise
in my life.
Let's make a ten-year promise.
What is it?
Ten years later,
you write our story.
I'll be the male lead.
Then we're a match made in heaven.
We promised to go to the film academy together.
to work hard for each other's dreams.
But I was absent for ten years.
In the past ten years,
she was very strong.
and came this far with our dream.
I want to take this opportunity to tell her
I didn't forget our promise.
I...
I'm back.
Hello, Susu.
Xia Mi, good news.
Our male lead has been decided.
Hello, Xiammy.
Are you listening?
Hello?
You're awake.
Mimi, you're finally awake.
Do you have a headache?
Do you want me to make you some hangover soup?
Hello, Susu. I have something to do. I'll talk to you later.
Mom, why did you come back with him?
I went to buy groceries.
I saw Ruoxi downstairs when I came back.
so he picked it up for me.
Ruoxi, thank you.
You're welcome.
Call me if you need anything.
I'll be there anytime.
Get out!
We don't need your help.
Get out! Go!
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Mimi.
Don't cry, Mimi.
I'm sorry.
I saw him drive you home yesterday.
I thought you two...
I'm fine, mom.
I don't feel well.
I'm going back to rest.
I know I can't change the past.
I don't expect you to forgive me now.
I just hope you can give me another chance to make up for it.
I will always wait for you.
You said you would wait for me.
It's all a lie.
Fan Yuan, she abandoned me.
Ruoxi Zhang.
This punch
for her.
Who promised me to take good care of her here?
Who promised me
that you won't give up easily.
You're just going to do that?
Look at me, Ruoxi.
You're just a jerk.
Luckily, you're fine.
If anything happens to you,
I will never forgive you.
The food abroad is so good.
You've become stronger.
You deserve it.
Who told you to disappear for so long?
Apply it yourself.
When she comes down,
she thought we colluded.
Don't worry.
She won't come down.
She doesn't want to see me now.
She waited for you for ten years.
It's reasonable to blame you and resent you.
You have to bear all this yourself.
I know.
Okay.
Don't be too discouraged.
She's angry because
because she loves you.
Find a chance to apologize to him.
and resolve the misunderstanding.
Sooner or later, she will forgive you.
No matter how long it takes,
no matter how long it takes.
I won't give up.
Stop fighting.
Forget it.
Why did you suddenly disappear?
How are your parents?
Where do you live recently?
Dr. Fan.
You asked so many questions at once.
Which one should I answer?
Talk nicely. I'm not joking.
Don't worry.
My parents are fine.
Me too.
Anyway, everything is fine.
Really.
I didn't.
You haven't watched the news recently?
Me?
a little red now.
Be good to her.
Don't let me down again.
and don't make her sad.
Okay?
I will.
Fan Yuan.
Thank you.
If you want to thank me,
live happily with her.
Don't make me worry about you abroad.
This place is as beautiful as before.
Good morning. I'm here for a breeze.
Why are you here?
Oh, me.
What happened to your face?
You care about me?
You think too much.
It has nothing to do with me.
Where are you going? I'll give you a ride.
I'm never the one who goes back on my word.
Stop following me.
Ruoxi, what are you doing? Are you kidnapping me?
It's not easy to get a taxi here.
Four wheels are faster than two legs.
No.
Stop! Stop!
Don't move.
I'll kiss you if you move.
Ruoxi, you...
You're a pervert.
I'm not the one who started it.
Upfist.
Ruoxi Zhang.
I was drunk and lost my mind.
Don't threaten me with this.
Rammy.
I'm also here to work.
Please cooperate.
Your job is to memorize the script at home.
What does it have to do with me?
To deepen my understanding of the character,
it's very necessary to communicate with the scriptwriter in advance.
For our
for our project.
If you're free these days,
help Ruoxi get familiar with the roles.
How did you know my schedule?
Which side is Sue from?
What?
You can't even talk about work?
Who said that?
Of course we can talk about work.
but not private matters.
Okay.
Where should we go next?
Mr. Han.
Let's go to the Ferris wheel park. I'm going to see the view.
Okay.
You sit next.
Why can't two people sit?
I just want to sit alone.
Sure.
But how do we talk about work later?
Sing a mountain song across the sedan.
You...
Whatever.
Do you remember
you asked me to buy some books for me at the wholesale market?
Then I have to go to the wholesale market to buy some notebook.
You'll write down "Zhang Ruoxi" on every notebook.
When you become a superstar,
I'll be rich lying down.
You money maniac.
You broke my brain.
What if I can't write in the future?
Some people are a big star now.
I didn't make any money.
If you're willing,
I'll go to the wholesale market to buy a book.
Let's set up a stall to sell autographs.
to make you rich.
No.
It was just a joke when I was young.
Don't take it seriously.
Ruoxi.
What are you doing?
Make a wish.
What wish?
Haven't you heard of a legend?
When the Ferris wheel reaches the top,
make a wish and be with the one you love,
we will never be apart.
How old are you?
how can you believe such a thing?
I don't care if it lies to adults or kids.
as long as it can come true,
I'm willing to make it 10,000 times.
Artistic common sense.
I hope I get good grades tomorrow.
I hope I can write a good script.
[Jang Ruohee.]
Will you really come to me?
There's no eternity in this world.
I don't believe in these.
Natmmy, we...
What's wrong?
It's going to rain.
Let's go.
Let me.
Should I take you to the hospital?
I'm fine.
Just take me home.
Sleep if you're tired.
Don't be afraid.
Are you okay?
Let's stop here.
Rammy.
Wait.
Where are you going tomorrow?
Should I pick you up?
Tomorrow?
tomorrow.
We can talk about work on WeChat.
Don't worry.
I'm a professional.
I'll cooperate if you're the male lead.
But outside of work,
I don't want to see you.
What can I do
to give me another chance?
Ruoxi Zhang.
I've given you a chance every day for the past ten years.
Have you given me a chance?
You ignored me for ten years.
Now that you're back, you want to start over without explaining.
Do you think I won't be sad or hurt?
I don't think so.
I just think
no matter how I explain it,
I can't make up for the trauma I caused you.
Is that the reason why you didn't say anything?
You left without saying a word ten years ago.
Now you're back without explaining.
Do you know
all these years,
what I fear the most is not that you forget our agreement.
but that you already...
Mom.
You don't have to cook for me for lunch.
I'm going out to write.
What about dinner?
Your grandma gave me a chicken.
Do you want some chicken soup?
Okay. Thank you, mom.
Hello.
One double espresso, please.
Okay.
Hello your Americano
Thank you.
Xiammy.
I just heard an explosion gossip.
So Lin Ruotear and Fan Yuan broke up long ago.
And because Lin Ruotear cheated on her.
No wonder they seemed strange
I thought they were weird.
She can even pretend to be affectionate for a whole year on Moments.
I have to say one word. Awesome.
Xia Mi.
Sorry, Ms Cheng.
I met a friend.
Can we talk?
Okay.
I heard that Ms. Jang is back.
and became an actress.
Are you going to keep working together?
Congratulations.
It's finally time to see the moon.
Now I can rest assured.
What are you trying to say?
Rammy.
Don't be so hostile to me.
I'm truly happy for you.
I hope you and Ruoxi can grow old together.
That's all I want to say.
I'll leave you alone.
Ruo tears.
I've never been your enemy.
If you really love the monitor,
I hope you can cherish it.
Don't blame it on others.
Agent Yang
to participate in the performance.
Gravity Audition Studio.
Xiangshan Yilu Culture and Communication Co., Ltd.
Beijing Pulan Yuxin Culture Development Co., Ltd.
August.
MingXie Group.
The Communist Party Hengyang City Committee
The PR Department of Hengyang Municipal Committee
The Committee of Political and Law of Hengyang Municipal Council
Hengyang City Culture Tourism and Guangdong Sports Bureau.
The Committee of Administration Committee of Hengyang
The government of Xianggu Committee in Hengyang.
The government of Zhuhui District, Hengyang City.
Hengyang Daily.
Hengyang City Radio Station.
Hengyang City Broadcasting Broadcast Media Center.
Hengyang No.1 High School.
No. 8 High School of Hengyang.
Hengyang Shiishan Experimental High School.
Libo Hotel, Hengyang.
Dajiang Technology Group Co., Ltd.
Yuhu Wanda Plaza, Hengyang.
Support units.
Chinese Literature Art Fund.
A product company.
Beijing Orange Guangli Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
[Beijing Guangli Cultural Media Co., Ltd.]