Come on.
Everyone's youth
may have a brilliant dream.
To chase our dreams,
We'll cry. Okay.
Okay. Okay.
You fall.
and stupid.
But no matter what happens,
we always have the courage
believed in miracles.
We were so cute
It's just yesterday.
Li.
Xia.
I don't want to cut my head.
No.
According to the admission letter of Yi Zhong High School,
girls can't cross their shoulders.
This is the rule.
Rules and rules.
Notice is not an imperial edict.
It's not the truth yet.
Natmmy.
You got into City No.1 High School.
You made it!
Yi Zhong High School is a key school in the city.
Many people can't get in even if they want to.
Listen to Uncle Li.
You have to follow the rules.
That's right.
Li,
Cut her head.
Okay.
Just cut it.
Just cut it like this
This is good.
We have our own rules.
The school has rules. I cut it.
TWBEAR
Lee
You're a good cook.
My daughter feels much better now.
That's good.
Hello.
When will you pick me up?
I've been waiting for half an hour.
I'm at the parking lot.
Brother.
Your wallet is so pretty. Where did you buy it?
I want one too.
Who are you?
I don't know you at all.
Give it to me.
You don't know who I am,
but I know who you are.
Your name is Thief.
You...
That's my wallet.
Help! Help!
Someone catch the thief!
Stop!
Little girl.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Confucius said
there's no courage to see justice.
This is what I should do.
You're quite brave.
Yes, you're not only brave,
but also smart.
It's really good.
You're the new era Little Mu Lan.
Thank you for your compliment.
Dismiss
Let's go.
Thank you.
Mimi.
Why are you so arrogant?
What if something happens?
What if you get hurt?
You should've called me.
Li, I'm leaving.
Next, before the final result comes out,
let's welcome our youth professional judges
to cheer for the two of us.
TWBEAR
NBEAR.
Your brain is very fresh.
Xia.
Mom.
You should have another child as soon as possible.
You'll lose your daughter from today on.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Xia.
What are you doing?
I told you to listen to her.
If you listen to her, you'll be useless.
Mimi, have some fruit.
Look how cute the fruit is.
It’s a pity if you don’t eat it.
Don't be upset.
Look at your mouth.
How about I help you?
I'm hopeless.
I was tricked by Tony too.
She's experienced.
Trust me.
I'll make you pretty.
Mom.
You said you were experienced and beautiful.
Don't worry, Mimi.
Since the admission notice has rules,
we'll do it together.
You won't be the only ugly one.
I'm going to cook.
Help!
I don't want to become popcorn.
We should get the materials.
How would I know?
We did it according to the school rules and regulations.
Mi.
Line up here.
Your mom and I will go get daily necessities.
Report to the register.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Excuse me.
11306127.
Please bless me to be possessed by a koi.
and be in a good class.
Excuse me.
Fan Yuan.
This class is so sharp.
With Fan Yuan as the ace,
won't win the first place in the future.
Liu Yifan.
Qin Zeyang is in Class 2.
It’s hard to say.
Hard to say?
Qin Zeyang is in Class 2.
There's also Ruoxi Zhang in that class.
In junior high,
he and Fan Yuan were a pair of superstars.
He's so good too.
I'm in the same class as him.
I'll be half the king then.
Humph.
Which class are you in?
I'm in the same class.
Class 1.
We know each other.
I'm in Class 1 too.
The boy in front.
Stop!
You can't ride your bike into the teaching area today.
Excuse me
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Why are you so careless?
Mi.
Dad, mom.
I have good news.
I'm assigned to Bomb Class.
Go to report.
Mi,
Do you want us to send you to the dorm?
No, I can do it myself.
I'm already in high school.
I'll do my own thing.
Oh no.
Xia must have forgotten to take the banquet before he left.
He said I was forgetful.
You are also forgetful.
It's him.
Cut.
ROCKETS
So handsome.
Handsome, are you still going to fight?
No.
I'm going back to class.
Let's play together next time.
Okay, bye.
Be careful
Happy
I'm sorry
KETS
RCKETS
I'm glad I ran fast.
I shouldn't have meddled.
He's a good player. He can definitely dodge it.
We're in the classroom. Let's go.
Let's talk after class.
I'm smart.
Strange.
There's nothing to block.
Could it be...
a legendary barrier?
You again?
Why are you laughing?
It's me.
Which sect are you from?
You can't break the barrier.
You're not good at learning.
It's none of your business.
You haven't paid for the hit-and-run.
I was just being brave.
I just made a little mistake.
I didn't mean it.
I haven't got even with you yet.
You're rude.
How dare you laugh at me?
I'll break the barrier for you.
Isn't it super simple?
Mind your own business.
I can come in myself, okay?
Smile.
The foolish sons of the landlord always laugh.
The hypothesis proposed by the German mathematician, Poynhad Leman.
It's an American Clay Mathematics Institute.
In the Millennium,
in the Millennium.
Fan Yuan.
I lost to you in the entrance exam.
That's because I didn't do well.
Do you dare to compete with me again?
You've lost to Fan Yuan
You've lost to Fan Yuan so many times.
Why don't you give up?
What?
The invincible Qiang.
You're not convinced?
Come on.
One on two.
Then tell me.
What?
Let's compete with Sudoku.
What do you think?
Anything.
Did you just provoke the top student in our class?
We have to watch it.
Let's go.
The top student.
One of the Bomb.
And...
The class meeting is in 15 minutes.
Whoever answers correctly wins.
OK?
It won't take 15 minutes.
I can finish it in ten minutes.
Fan Yuan.
I'll beat you today.
Okay.
Three.
Two.
The game begins.
So fast?
This Sudoku
can you write the answer directly
Just write the answer like this?
He can do it.
I didn't understand the question but they solved it.
A straight A student's brain is indeed different from ours.
Oh no.
Fan Yuan's distraction has fallen behind several planks.
Will he lose?
Fan Yuan.
I'm going to win this game.
Three, three, seven, nine, X.
29.
He won't lose.
Here he comes.
Fan Yuan won the national champion
in junior high.
You can easily catch up with this question.
Right?
You're right.
Look.
Fan Yuan caught up with Qin Zeyang.
What happened?
So unlucky.
Let God do the calculation.
After all, fate is better than fate.
Fan Yuan.
Game over.
The answers on both sides are correct.
Wow.
My little shrimp
I'm really swimming to the sea now.
Are we even in this round?
I don't accept a draw.
This round
you win.
If Fan Yuan hadn't dropped his chalk,
you would have won.
I don't want a tie like this.
Not bad. You even won.
But you have to give me half of the result.
Sure. Play two rounds with me this weekend.
You can have all the results.
OK. You can play all night.
Look.
The teacher is here.
Run!
Let's go.
What did you do this morning?
I was playing basketball.
Did you choose a seat?
It's in the back.
See you.
Ruo tears.
Yun Jin.
Dada.
Chae Ok.
Henqi.
Hello.
Excuse me.
for taking your seat.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Can I interrupt you?
Let's discuss something over there.
This is out of print.
I can't even borrow it from the library.
Where did you find it?
This is for you.
But I won't accept any reward without contributions.
This is too valuable.
I don't want it.
Don't be nervous.
I used to sit by the window when I was in junior high.
Let me discuss with you.
Change seats.
I'll change with you.
Thank you.
Hello. Hello.
I'll change my seat.
What's wrong with the king bomb?
Why did he suddenly change his seat?
Is he blaming me for disturbing him during the game
for bothering me during the game?
Hello.
My name is Fan Yuan.
Do you remember me?
Yes.
You were the top student in that grade.
Is there anything else?
Do you know how miserable I am?
Nine years of obligation education.
Nine years.
I haven't even met a female deskmate.
I swear
I will break this curse in high school.
Hello.
I have a seat here.
Please be quiet.
It's a class meeting.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Qiao Yun.
I’ll be your head teacher in the next year.
This is also my first time to lead a class.
I hope in the next year,
in the future.
These three pictures
represent three key words.
It represents that I teach Chinese.
Magazines and scenery photos
represent my hobbies.
I like traveling and writing articles.
What do you think?
Do you have a preliminary understanding of me?
Sir.
Did you publish all these magazines?
Yes.
Wow.
New literature is amazing.
Alright.
I'm not the lead of today's class meeting.
but you.
to get familiar with each other as soon as possible.
everyone needs to
with three key words.
What do you think?
Who comes first?
Looks like everyone is a little shy.
I'm quite shy.
How about this?
Next, let's play a dragon catching game.
I'll order a student first.
And then, this student
to pick the next trainee.
Fan Yuan.
Yes.
Come up.
Dust. Dust.
Hello, I'm Fan Yuan.
from Luxiang City.
As for the keyword,
I think...
I know.
You're the top student in that grade.
or the math industry?
Rukawa.
That topic was so cool.
Anyway, he's a straight A student.
Thank you for the keyword.
Rukawa from math.
I don't know if I'm good enough.
But I really like math.
I hope you can discuss math with me.
No, no.
We don't deserve it.
You don't have to be so serious.
As the saying goes,
"No noble, no lowly."
with no age or age.
The Tao exists.
The master exists.
Everyone is equal in front of knowledge.
Thank you.
Fan Yuan is right.
As the saying goes,
If you don't learn,
Everyone should learn from Fan Yuan.
Next one is...
The one in blue and white.
Hello.
My name is Zhang Ruoxi.
I only have one keyword.
Cool.
Very handsome.
OK.
Good. Everyone has good taste.
But let's keep a low profile.
This is the second king bomb.
So narcissistic.
Actually, my keyword is basketball.
If there's anyone who likes to play basketball with me,
That's Ruoxi Jang.
Is he good at basketball?
He's good at playing basketball.
or pray
or pray?
Anyway, we can
kill each other.
That's all for my introduction.
The next one I want is
The girl in green
The girl in green leaning on the window.
Natmmy.
This guy is so annoying.
Let's give him a round of applause.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Xiammy.
Summer of spring and summer.
Rice from the countryside of fish and rice.
In three words,
it should be writing.
I'm a TV fan.
And
Mushroom head.
He's also a mushroom head.
Okay, be quiet.
Stop laughing.
Miss Xiammy has strictly followed the image rules of admission notice.
Everyone should learn from her.
Let's give her a round of applause.
That's all.
Rammy.
I think your mushroom head is pretty.
Thank you.
I'm not comforted at all.
Hello, I'm Lin Ruotear.
I'm Yuhan.
My name is Siu Junyi.
I'm Wang Xiao Yu.
My name is Zhao Rui.
My name is Liu Dayou.
I'm Tian Jiarong.
My key word is my friend's study and travel.
The keyword is swimming.
My first keyword is Hong Kong film.
My idol is
Bruce Lee.
I like spicy food.
You can call me if you want spicy crayfish.
Besides milk,
there's one more word to describe me accurately.
That is...
Handsome.
My second keyword is basketball.
I've always been the class committee.
I hope I can have the honor
to continue to serve you.
I love math.
I like Sudoku too.
I hope I can
with Fan Yuan.
OK.
You all did very well just now.
Now I'll choose two monitors.
Fan Yuan will be the class monitor.
Tian Jiarong will be the monitor.
During the military training,
Can you two take care of the boys and girls?
Yes, sir.
Next is the class representative.
Our language class representative will be taken by Xiammy.
I...
I'm acknowledging you.
Okay.
Tomorrow at 6:30 a.m.,
at the central square tomorrow morning.
Remember to wear military uniform.
Especially the onlooker.
Remember.
Don't be late for the first time.
Got it?
Got it.
Class is over.
Goodbye.
I haven't been to the dorm yet. Why don't you take me there later?
It's totally fine.
I'll wait for you.
Okay.
Fan Yuan Fan.
Congratulations on becoming the monitor.
Thank you, Yuhan.
We seem to be in the same dorm.
You're so pretty.
Let's go recharge our campus card.
This is the canteen. I'll take you there.
Okay.
This is it.
We can put the card and money on the window later.
Xiao Yu.
You seem to know a lot about this place.
Of course. I came up from junior high.
You can ask me if you have any questions.
Wang Xiao Yu.
How much do you usually charge?
Whatever
I'm a parent anyway
I can use credit cards at the canteen, bathhouse and snack stores.
Just save some money to go home on weekends.
Lin Ruotear,
You may not have enough money to recharge.
Just call me Ruotear.
I don't eat much
I don't eat that much
And I don't like meat and fish.
This is enough.
No wonder you have such a nice body.
There's a reason why a beauty can become a beauty.
No.
You're pretty too.
Next.
It's our turn.
Walk faster
You're so slow.
Line up.
Everyone, gather around.
Line up by number.
Forward and back.
Hurry up.
Where are these students?
Is everyone in your dorm here?
Yes.
Okay.
You two are too slow.
I called you this morning.
I'm late.
I'm not late, am I?
No.
Fall in.
Follow the student number.
Hurry.
Fall in.
Yes.
All of you.
Attention!
Stand in position.
Half an hour.
Straighten your legs.
Look ahead.
What?
Are you trying to kill a mosquito?
It's moving around.
Isn't it a poverty
Shaking around
Stand still.
Bro, help me.
Sergeant.
What’s wrong?
I can’t.
You fainted already?
Do you still feel dizzy?
No, sir.
Stand still.
Every year,
I can cure some of you
And those with bad physique.
stand out at once.
I'll treat you all.
Xiammy.
Are you okay?
Yang Yin-yang.
and actors.
Shi Yunping, Chen Feiyan, Zhu Baohe, Wang Xiaoman Luo Qiuxia Lin
Audition team.
Gravity angle audition studio.
Late production company.
Xiangshan Yilu Culture and Communication Co., Ltd.
Visual effect production.
Beijing Renyan Co., Ltd.
Audio production.
Beijing Pulan Yuxin Culture Development Co., Ltd.
[Love Never Say]
Team Burning Youth.
Cocoon-Break.
17.
MingXie Group.
The People’s Government of Hengyang.
The People’s Political Consultation of China, Hengyang City Committee.
The PR Department of Hengyang Municipal Committee
Hengyang City Management and Comprehensive Law Service and the Gardening Bureau.
Hengyang City Education Bureau.
The Commission of Administration Committee of Hengyang
The government of Shi drum District Committee in Hengyang
The government of Yanfeng District Committee of Hengyang City.
Hengyang Daily.
Nanhua University and Affiliated Nanhua Hospital
Hunan High-speed railway Professional Technical School.
Hengyang No.1 High School.
Bowen High School in Hengyang.
Hengyang Branch of Hunan Bank.
Libo Hotel, Hengyang.
Hunan Bank.
Production Company.
Beijing Orange Guangli Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing New Film Film Co., Ltd.