[Meet Yourself]
[Episode 29]
Dad, your waist is frail. Don't squat there.
Let me do it. Stop for now.
I'm almost done.
- Stand up.
- Okay.
I'll do it. Sit over there.
Come on. Sit down.
I'm fine.
Here.
Have some rest. Drink some tea.
We've been living here for over 20 years.
Mi and you grew up in this house.
We spent ¥40,000 on this house.
Just ¥40,000?
It wasn't a small sum back then.
Really?
Dad, are we selling this house?
Nope. Your mom can't bear to sell it.
She wants to tidy up the rooms and rent it out.
There's a junior high school in front of our estate and a high school behind it.
it's an easy place to rent out.
You drew all those.
What did I draw?
Isn't it written there?
The beautiful and confident boss, Xu Hongdou.
The beggar, Xu Hongmi.
When did I draw that?
Was I that eager to be a boss when I was little?
We moved over here when you were in elementary school,
about seven years old.
Thinking back now,
you guys were such fascinating children.
When school was over, you'd rush over to my grocery store.
Xiao Zhang, who sold condiments next door, would ask why you came over.
You said you were there to pick up your dad.
Once you were a boss in the future,
you'd forbid me from selling rice.
Don't you still want to open a grocery store now?
That's right.
I've been busy working all my life.
It's boring to have fun all day long.
You can do housework, cook, and exercise with Mom.
That's quite enjoyable.
Your expenses aren't high either, and you have savings.
Sister and I can support you two.
Yes.
Days pass by.
We're just getting old... and useless.
How can you think this way?
Who said that?
Why are you useless just because you're old? Everyone gets old, right?
You're only sixty years old. You're still young.
Since I'm still young, why won't you let me set up a grocery store?
Setting up a grocery store is a business venture.
It's stressful to manage a new business.
Isn't that right?
Once you've made your decision, there's no turning back.
You may think it's easy to set up a grocery store.
All you need is a small shop front,
but the operations are complicated.
Firstly, you need to buy a shop front.
Then, there's the rental
and the renovation fees.
You still have to bring in goods.
The types of goods,
finding a cheap supplier, deciding on the retail prices,
figuring out the profits needed to cover your costs...
Dad, have you considered these?
It's not that I'm stopping you from working.
I just don't want you to set up a grocery store.
I've been the boss of a grocery store all my life.
What else can I do?
Our estate was recruiting security guards.
I went to inquire.
They said I was too old.
The parking lot of the company
that Kexin's husband works at needed a guard.
There weren't any age restrictions,
but there were night shifts.
I was worried that I couldn't stay up late.
Dad, my sister and I think...
you've been working all your life.
Now that you're over sixty years old,
we want you to lead a worry-free and happy life.
I'm happy. Of course, I'm happy.
We live in a peaceful age.
Your mom and I have a harmonious marriage, and we're healthy.
Our daughters are filial.
We don't have to worry about food or clothes.
How can I be unhappy? I'm extremely blessed.
But if I can find work and contribute to the family,
I'd be even more content.
All right.
I'll ponder over this for you.
[The beautiful and confident boss, Xu Hongdou. The beggar, Xu Hongmi]
At that time, you were so little.
In the blink of an eye...
Dad, what if I start a business and be the boss?
Enough.
It's a serious question.
Are you keen on setting up a grocery store, too?
I won't do that.
Why can't I set up a big hotel?
Of course, you can.
I'm serious.
I'm also serious.
I think you can pull off anything.
- Really?
- Yes.
Hello, Kexin. What do you want to eat?
How could you let Kexin pick up parcels on her own?
You're so careless.
What if she's hurt?
It's okay.
Please don't crowd at the door.
Save my wife first!
What did you say? There is no such rule here. We'll do our best to save them.
We'll do our best to save them.
What's the situation right now?
Doctor, save both of them.
- Don't worry.
- Doctor!
Don't worry. Sit down. Don't panic.
[Surgery]
The doctor is here.
Yang Kexin's family, here's the baby.
Is the mother all right?
Congratulations. Both of them are safe.
Thank you.
Second Sister, you can hug her.
Come on.
You'll be the first relative to carry her. Look at her.
She's so cute.
Your aunt and uncle went back to make nutritious meals for you.
Your husband and mother-in-law went to pack things.
Your parents went with the baby for checkups.
They're fine, don't worry.
Second Sister,
will the baby by injured because I fell?
The baby is doing well.
Even though this was an early birth, the baby is fully grown.
You underwent surgery once you got here, so she didn't lack oxygen.
Don't worry.
You scared me to death with your call.
You sounded like you were reciting your will.
I didn't know if I'd be fine.
If anything happened, I would've lost my chance to say my last words.
While I was waiting for the ambulance,
so many thoughts ran through my mind.
I didn't want anything else.
I just wanted to be alive.
Yesterday, I even quarreled with my mom.
I regretted that.
The baby isn't big,
and the position of the fetus was fine.
I even bought a constellation bracelet for her.
I wanted to have a normal childbirth,
but I bought that for nothing.
We didn't even make any preparations.
There are too many unexpected occurrences in one's life.
Don't harp on this.
Have some rest.
Is your cousin all right?
She's fine.
You didn't see how my relatives were.
This is the first time I saw them in such panic.
My aunt couldn't even stand.
You were terrified too, weren't you?
Of course.
She suddenly called me and said her last words.
She scared the hell out of me.
I can't even fall asleep now.
I'm scared.
How about... I fly over to you tomorrow?
Why do you want to come over?
I... I just want to see you.
I'm just kidding.
I just sent off the company you recommended to us for team bonding.
I've been busy selling potatoes lately as well.
I don't have any free time.
You were just kidding?
If I need you in Beijing, will you come over?
Of course.
I'm serious. I'm not kidding.
Get to work. Sleep early.
Okay.
Don't think too much.
You still need to care for your cousin at the hospital tomorrow.
By the way,
the plums you sent over turned sweeter after a few days.
They're delicious.
Your stomach will hurt if you eat too many. Don't eat too much.
I'm hanging up.
- Old Xie! Old Xie!
- Yeah?
Wake up! Come on!
What? What happened?
Calm down and tell me. What's wrong?
We made it!
What?
The bookstore. The bookstore just called me.
We made it!
- We made it?
- Yes!
- Really?
We made it!
I'll take these off first.
We must celebrate with good food tonight!
Really? Really?
That's great. You made it!
Yes. We finally sealed the deal.
Congratulations.
Shouldn't you share in our joy?
You contributed to this.
You contributed even more. You've done a wonderful job of building up Yunmiao Village.
- Xu Hongdou.
- Yeah.
If, and I mean if...
once the bookstore is built,
more prospects can be found here,
homestays and hotels will be established,
and the place will be more developed,
can you consider moving over and working here?
What can I even do there?
There's nothing here now, and developments aren't optimistic.
I'm talking about the future.
♫ There are stars in my journey ♫
Of course, it's fine if you don't want to come here.
You'll lead a better life in Beijing and more chances.
I'm just throwing out a question.
I'll think about it.
♫ Hidden spots make my heart flutter ♫
Really?
Unlike you, I don't make jokes all the time.
I don't just blabber jokes.
Don't say that.
Well, I have nothing else to say.
I haven't eaten my breakfast yet.
Okay. I'll go back to sleep.
Sorry to bother you. Enjoy your sleep.
Goodbye.
♫ Although the seasons go by ♫
♫ I'll still love passionately like a youth ♫
Heavens, please help me.
♫ Sometimes I find I fall in love ♫
♫ Make a little wish and pray ♫
♫ Maybe things will go your way ♫
Mom, five more minutes.
I'll skip breakfast.
Five minutes!
What are you doing?
Stop this nonsense!
Mom, she sleeps until noon every day.
Aren't you going to say something about this?
She's been accompanying Kexin at the hospital.
She slept late last night.
Just leave her be. Come on.
- Hongmi, have breakfast.
- When did you come back?
Why can't I be back?
I heard about Kexin's fall after we moved houses.
So, I came back during the weekend to lecture you.
- Where is Lingdang?
- She didn't come with me.
- Wake up!
- What are you doing?
Wake up!
Accompany me to the hospital to visit Kexin after breakfast.
Five minutes.
You won't even get five seconds.
Wake up! The noodles are clumping together!
Come on! Have breakfast!
Get moving! Wake up!
You lazy pig!
Mom, this pig is ready to be slaughtered.
Wake up.
On that day,
Dou and your dad went to the old house to clean.
Your aunt called me while wailing.
She said Kexin had a fall.
I was so shocked that my heart almost leapt out of my chest.
Kexin's husband was in utter panic.
He was like a fool in the hospital.
Luckily, Dou was there.
The whole family was panicking.
Dou was the only one helping out quietly.
She's useful now that she's grown up.
Yes, it's about time she grew sensible.
Your mom is a master chef.
It's a pity that you don't own a restaurant.
- Absolutely.
- Don't eat too fast.
Don't eat too much. It's bad for your blood sugar levels.
You can eat more.
I'll eat less, I'm on a diet.
Eat more.
She's smiling.
Did she fall asleep?
It has been a long time since I carried a baby.
Well done, Big Sister.
Second Sister doesn't dare to carry her.
She said the baby's too small and fragile.
She's afraid of hurting the baby.
What if your hotel guests need you to carry their babies?
I'll do it.
By the way, Big Sister,
have you watched the promotional video Second Sister helped with
during her trip to Yunnan?
Yes, what about it?
Did you meet the guy she was holding hands with at the seaside?
What do you think of him?
Just so-so.
I think he's pretty handsome.
He's too poor.
Poor?
He's starting a business. You know this.
His business is booming as well.
When you were there, he took good care of you, didn't he?
Now, you're complaining that he's poor.
There's something wrong with you.
I just said he's poor. Why are you so pissed off?
I just think you're wrong to say that.
Why can't I criticize him?
Why are you so pushy?
Am I pushy?
Am I pushy? I'll keep quiet.
Hilarious.
Can't you help me?
Do it yourself. I'm busy with work.
- The bookstore?
- Yeah.
They'll come over to select a site in a few days.
It's good to be busy with work.
Once you settled the deal with the bookstore, you've recovered.
Look at how you were a while back.
You were strange. I'm not used to that.
Well, get used to it.
Let me tell you this. I have a premonition.
With just another two years of hard work until the bookstore is built,
I'll get married.
What? After the bookstore is built,
will the village committee send you a wife?
That's right.
The heavens will give me a wife.
I just said you recovered.
Have you lost your marbles again?
Xu Hongdou has been gone for a long time.
You're still so insane.
- That's none of your business.
- I don't give a damn.
Uncle A'Yao. Brother Guanjun.
Am I pretty? My boyfriend gave it to me.
Another lunatic.
It's pretty.
Uncle A'Yao, will you treat us to a meal today?
Yeah, I will.
Xiao Qin, didn't you break up with Yang Zhinan?
No, I didn't.
Why not?
Lovers are bound to quarrel.
Without fights and separations,
a relationship will be uneventful and boring.
But you're just torturing yourself.
Love requires trials and obstacles.
Forget it. Why am I chatting with you about this?
You won't understand.
Don't you agree, Uncle A'Yao?
Yes. Love should be tested by hardships,
but these shouldn't be so frequent.
Don't threaten to break up with him all the time.
Weren't you the one who encouraged my breakup?
Well, will you do everything I say?
Why don't you listen to your dad's advice?
I suggested breaking up to drill the severity of this problem into his head.
Besides, I did that in a fit of anger. I didn't really mean to break up.
After all, Yang Zhinan is so handsome and honest.
I can't let others have him.
He's that great?
A'Yao, have you met him before?
Yes.
He looks... sprightly.
He's not just sprightly.
He's very dashing. He looks like a celebrity.
Which one?
That's none of your business.
Uncle A'Yao, don't give up.
Although you're old and tan, you have to believe
that even wild lilies have their springs.
You can have beautiful love just like me.
Beautiful love?
It's clear that he's gone mad.
He's gone crazy yearning for a woman.
He was fantasizing that the village committee will give him a wife
once the bookstore is built.
I have a strong hunch and absolute confidence about this.
After the bookstore is built, I'll be married.
See? Isn't he insane?
This has been put off for too long.
Hand it in to me tomorrow.
- What are you doing?
- Let go of me.
- Bring back my slippers.
- Nope.
You won't? Will you do it or not?
- Okay.
- Will you do it?
Okay. I'll do it.
Let go.
Xu Hongmi.
Xu Hongdou.
Before I decide on your burial spot, bring back my slippers.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Dumplings again?
Your sister is back.
Of course, we should eat dumplings.
I'll help you with them.
There's no need.
Hang out with your sister.
Her? She's planning to murder and bury me.
I'll bury you here.
Your ages add up to over 70 years old.
Why are you still acting like kids?
Your ages probably add up to over 100 years old.
You're the same as well.
Mom, what are you doing?
I can't live with your dad anymore.
You can choose one of us.
You got into another fight?
I choose my sister.
Get lost.
Dad, what's this argument about?
I said I won't set up a grocery store.
I just want to get a job.
She flared up.
Get a job?
Let's have a meeting.
I just want to work.
Okay. Here you go.
President, here is your tea.
Let's commence the meeting.
Xiao Liu, your disagreement is the strongest. You can start first.
What did you call me?
Be careful, it's hot.
Please share your opinions.
Fine, I'll start.
Xu Jianguo, we have a clear division of labor.
You work while I care for the family.
We have elders and children to care for.
We support the whole family together.
No, you support the family more than I do.
Don't be humble.
You've sacrificed a lot for this family.
We can see that.
You sold grains and oil, but how much can you earn from a bag of rice?
You just wanted to save money.
You never hired others.
You unloaded all the goods yourself.
You worked from day to night, and now what?
You have a problem with your lower back.
You're right.
My lower back...
Why are you praising me now?
Of course, I should praise you.
I should praise you if you do well.
You should be praised if you deserve it.
I'm just being honest.
I've always been fair, just, and...
- Gracious.
Your family was poor, and you didn't even graduate from junior high.
Why? You wanted to earn money, so you started working.
But I'm different.
I graduated from a technical school.
At that time, I was the most literate person in my family.
When the neighbors had conflicts,
they'd get me to mediate.
Mom is the best.
So, how can I possibly wrong you?
Yes, you're right.
I can understand your desire to get a job,
but I don't want to worry about you anymore.
Look at your lower back.
You can't sit or stand because of the pain.
I went to the hospital with you, didn't I?
I accompanied you for acupuncture and even collected your medicine.
When you were hospitalized, I rented a folding bed.
I lived in the hospital corridor.
It was winter. The wind was gusting.
I had a fever that lasted as long as your hospitalization.
You should've called us and told us!
That's useless!
All of you were working miles away!
Why would I bother you and make you come back?
Think about it, Xu Jianguo.
We're getting old now.
Aren't we supporting their careers just by being healthy and safe?
Yes. So, I'm not setting up a grocery store.
Dou broke it down for me and criticized me.
I admit that I was too naive with my assumptions.
You're so old now! What can you even do?
Even a security guard needs to be under 45 years old. You're too old for that.
What can you do now?
Being a warehouse guard or running a boiler?
All these are night shifts.
How can you do that with your condition?
The money you earn can't even cover your hospital bills.
Dad, you really can't get a job that'll harm your body,
but I support his desire to work.
Listen to what Dou just said.
I... I can rent some fields in the countryside and farm.
You think you can do that?
Look at the garlic you planted in the flower pot.
Did it grow? Did it?
I was born in a family of farmers.
You can't farm in the fields.
You need to bend over just to farm under the hot sun.
Your back will break.
But...
I know nothing else.
I've only sold grains for my whole life.
Don't be so humble. You also know how to eat grains.
We're having a meeting. Why are you dishing out insults?
You can't say that, Guiqin.
You're saying that I'm a pig.
You... I oppose that.
Opposition sustained. Mom, don't insult others.
Okay, fine. I'll stop with the nonsense.
You two, listen carefully.
- If you find an easy job, I'll give you my support.
- Okay.
But if it's harmful to your body, that's an absolute no.
Mom, let's work toward this target.
We should think of a solution.
Yes, think of a solution.
Dad, don't harbor too much hope.
Well, why did you even talk about it?
Dad, our estate's committee needs a volunteer.
That won't do.
I want to make money.
See? A money-grubber.
Enough, let's cook the dumplings.
Hold on.
Since my sister is here today, I have something to inform everyone.
What is it? Why are you so secretive?
I bet it's not good news.
Listen to Dou. Let her speak.
Dad, Mom, Sister.
I've made thorough considerations, and this isn't just a whim.
I've decided to seize the day.
This is also what I'm most keen on doing now.
I think it's meaningful,
a wonderful opportunity, and has great prospects.
Don't beat around the bush. Cut to the chase.
Just let me share my thoughts.
Okay, go on.
Dear family, I... don't want to return to Beijing to work for now.
I want to buy and run the homestay in Yunmiao Village.
According to reliable sources, the takeover price is cheap.
Moreover, Shaohua Bookstore will be built next to it.
It's the perfect time to buy the place now.
I work in hotel management, don't I?
This is my forte.
Moreover, I've found a partner who is willing to buy it with me.
We've discussed and made calculations.
We can pay the early expenses.
As for future plans, we still need some time to flesh that out.
I won't go into the details now.
Well, you mentioned a partner. Right?
My VIP customer, Sister Qiu, manages homestay brand building.
She's doing excellently.
She owns many homestays and even wants to rope me in.
I didn't agree. Why not?
That's because I want to build my own brand.
We have differing philosophies.
After that, I found another partner.
I won't elaborate on the philosophy.
Once I finish the proposal, I'll show you guys.
- Do you have enough money?
- Yes, for now.
- Come on, let's cook the dumplings.
- I'll peel the garlic.
Xu Hongdou.
As expected of someone who started dating with a Drift Bottle.
Mom, I want vegetable dumplings.
Okay.
Can we cook dumplings with the pot for steaming buns?
Look. I can distinguish the dumplings made by you two.
Dumplings are like people, aren't they?
Your dad is stingy, so he made small dumplings.
No way, I think he made this one. Look at this shelf he made.
How can I reach it?
He needs to reach every bowl himself. He deserves it.
I'll help you.
Where is the pepper and chili sauce I bought?
- It's here.
- Mom.
It's here.
So, do you guys approve?
Hey, you should make the sauce delicious.
Where is the chili sauce I bought?
I know where it is. It's here.
Add more chili sauce, that'll make it tasty.
It's a perfect balance of flavors.
Although your mom was angry, she didn't add more salt.
She deserves to be praised.
Who the heck was angry?
I just couldn't be bothered with you.
Mom, did you add dried shrimp with shells in the leek stuffing?
Prawns or dried shrimp won't bring out this taste.
- It tastes good.
- Eat more.
Well,
what do you think about my homestay venture?
Dou, don't talk during meals.
Eat more, here.
Have some spiced beef.
- Mom.
- Here you go. Delicious?
Yes.
So tasty. Your mom is a marvelous cook.
Chief, it's a pity that you don't own...
A restaurant!
Feels great.
You have to cover your whole face.
Only then will it be effective.
It's so refreshing and relaxing.
Do you want one?
She has them.
There's no way she'd buy such expensive facial masks.
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon,
and the starry sky ♫
♫ Disoriented footsteps will gradually be erased ♫
Mom, let her do it herself.
No one can beat her at this.
That's true. She majored in this.
Yeah.
I didn't major in making beds.
She's angry now.
All right, fine. Don't be angry.
Mom, what do you want to show me?
It's in my room. Take a look at my new bedside table.
Come here.
What's so nice about a bedside table?
Wh-What are you doing?
Why aren't you in bed?
I can't fall asleep.
It's 3:00 a.m.
What do you think?
What are you talking about?
The homestay.
Ask Mom.
What a nuisance!
What the heck?
Xu Jianguo, a ghost is grabbing my foot!
What's wrong?
What is it?
Oh my god!
Xu Hongdou!
You naughty girl.
Why are you squatting there?
You scared me.
Have some milk.
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
We ignored you on purpose to tease you and make you anxious.
Do you know what Mom told me over the phone?
She said...
Dou has become wild after leaving home.
She's so pleased when she talks about her friends there.
Who's the one who wants to start a business with her?
Xiao Xie!
- Yes, Xiao Xie.
They'll send peaches and plums to each other.
They're so clingy.
They're still so chummy?
So much time has passed.
Exactly. She even asked Li Yulin to send tourists there and drafted proposals.
They even stay up late to call each other.
I bet they'll start dating.
Really?
We can tell what she's going to do when she budges.
Will you approve?
Of course! We definitely do!
I'm fine with any guy she's fond of.
I just have one requirement. He needs to be alive.
Nan Nan...
Kexin also had a fall several days ago.
I still feel anxious thinking about it now.
Mi,
one of them is in Yunnan, and the other is in Beijing.
How can they even date?
Cyber dating. That's cyber dating.
That won't do!
They have to be together.
Didn't your aunt's daughter marry over to the northeast region?
Right now, they spend half a year in Sanya and the other half in Harbin.
They're enjoying their life.
That's right.
Aunty's daughter has already retired.
Dou needs to work.
They'll find a solution.
They can take flights to each other.
Planes are fast.
Flights? It'll cost a bomb to take flights all the time.
You don't get it.
Chairman Xie is a boss.
How can a boss be poor, right?
You're such a money-grubber.
He's rich with tons of loans to pay.
As long as he's nice and they adore each other,
we won't have any objections.
That's right.
Mi, when you were dating,
your mom and I didn't despise your partner either.
Why would you?
Would you complain that he has too many houses?
Look at you.
Why are you so brutally honest?
You're such a money-grubber, too.
You should've discussed this with the family first.
Instead, you mulled over this yourself,
and told us only at the very end.
So what if we ignored you for a bit?
But I needed to think this through alone.
I'm not a fresh college graduate.
Choosing a different path and starting anew
requires courage.
You're right.
I thought you were fond of your former job.
I was,
but perhaps I had a change of mentality.
I feel that I'm so puny and insignificant.
When I'm standing there,
people can see me.
Yet, I feel like not a single person sees me.
Do you know that when I see the hotel's clock,
I feel like I'm the spring on the clock's hands.
It keeps ticking and pushing me forward,
but I don't know where I'm headed.
I'm just walking in circles.
I feel that I'm losing sight of myself.
It's so meaningless.
It doesn't matter whether I'm standing there
or someone else takes my place.
It makes no difference to the hotel.
So,
I only feel like my existence in this city has meaning
when I'm before my best friend.
I'm treasured and respected by someone else.
Sister,
after Nan Nan passed away,
I...
I felt a void in my heart.
I feel...
it's like... my feet can't touch the ground.
I don't know...
which way to go anymore.
I don't know where I am either.
I don't want to do anything,
and I've lost interest in everything.
Don't cry.
So, I resigned.
Nan Nan told me she wanted me to follow my heart.
But I...
I don't know what my heart wants.
Most people don't.
You don't know either?
I... I'm not sure.
I'm pretty stressed now.
But I think my husband and my child are pretty nice.
So, I'm pretty content.
It's good.
That's living in the present.
That's pretty nice.
I've never thought about this.
Who can ever define what's good or bad?
Who can guarantee that their chosen path is a good one?
So, I just lived my life.
Working,
getting married, having a baby,
buying a house like others,
buying a car like others,
and following the crowd.
I'll always be with the majority
and in the safe zone.
Sister, this is the first time that I find you
so conventional yet peculiar.
I have no time for internal conflicts and contemplation.
That needs energy.
That's mental exhaustion, like what you're doing.
Mental exhaustion.
Yes. That's me.
That's really me.
So, just follow your heart.
Don't live in the past
or bank on the future.
Just don't regret your decisions.
All right.
I'm sleepy. I'm going to bed.
Don't leave.
Let's continue.
- Chat with me.
- Okay.
Speak your mind.
I'll listen.
Let me share my thoughts on the homestay with you.
You've been there.
Urban folks, especially those born in cities,
have never been to places so seeped in nature.
It's not that rural.
The transportation is convenient as well.
People who are stressed like me
get to watch the sky and clouds over there
and just think about my meals.
I feel healed in body and mind.
It's like a buffer between life and reality.
A buffer.
What else?
Xie Zhiyao also said this.
A good entrepreneur should be a good storyteller.
I think my experience is great.
It's a fabulous story.
I don't know what to say to that.
He's led you astray.
That only means
I have the mind of a boss.
You've packaged it so well,
but you're just doing it for a man.
He plays a very important part.
However, I want both the man and my career.
Excellent. Well done.
Seems like you've picked yourself up.
You have my support. Do your best.
Sister, you think...
it's risky to set up a homestay.
I don't have much money either.
Mom and Dad will think I'll starve again.
Your boyfriend can cook. You won't starve.
He isn't my boyfriend yet.
Sister, if my relationship
and business fails, what should I do?
Live in the moment.
Okay.
You have a weapon that others don't.
Your sister.
Let's go to bed.
I can't feel my legs. They're numb.
Be careful.
♫ Listen to the rain falling into the silent forest ♫
♫ Enjoy the mountainous landscape at sunset ♫
♫ The raindrops from the roof drip into my eyes quietly ♫
♫ The world is like a quiet island ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright without a sound ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for a ray of sunlight to shine across
the lake into my heart ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ Disoriented footsteps will gradually be erased ♫
♫ The light and shadows of the seasons ♫
♫  I've seen the meteor that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises, the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright without a sound ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for a ray of sunlight to shine across
the lake into my heart ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon,
and the starry sky ♫
♫ Disoriented footsteps will gradually be erased ♫
♫ The light and shadows of the seasons ♫
♫  I've seen the meteor that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises, the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ I'll head to a windy place to meet you ♫