[Meet Yourself]
[Episode 1]
Please come this way.
Manager Xu.
- Hello.
Hello. Here's your keycard.
Thank you.
Hello. Check out?
Could you tell me your room number, please?
701. Got it.
Okay.
Lisa, attend to this guest.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
- What's your room number?
- 328.
Okay, come with me.
Helen.
Madam, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Be careful of the glass shards.
Okay.
Don't worry. I can do it.
It's hard for you since you're in a short skirt.
- I'm really sorry.
- My apologies.
I'm really sorry.
The executive suites are fully booked this weekend.
Much as I want to, I cannot upgrade your room.
How about this?
I'll gift you two meal tickets when you check in tomorrow.
I'll definitely upgrade your room next time.
See you tomorrow, Mr. Liu.
[Female Restroom]
We have more guests during the holidays.
The receptionists must stay alert.
Make sure you don't miss out on any guests when they enter.
As for the luggage deposit, double-check the luggage tags.
We have to avoid the mix-up from yesterday.
Aunty!
Darling Lingdang!
Give Mommy the phone.
I already sent you a message two days ago.
- About what?
- She must've been too busy and forgotten.
- Give me the phone.
- Why do I hear Mom?
Did you head back from Shanghai?
Hongdou, it's your dad's birthday today.
You must've forgotten.
Not at all! I was about to call you!
- Where's Dad?
- Come over.
Have you eaten?
I'm eating now.
Happy birthday, Dad.
I told you to see a doctor for your stomach. Did you?
I'll get a gastroscopy tomorrow. Nan Nan's coming with me.
She's also taking a Doppler ultrasound.
It's an old ailment. Don't worry.
Okay, if Nan Nan's going with you,
I have nothing to worry about.
Why do you have to head to Beijing alone?
You could've gone to Shanghai.
Sure. How about working as a cleaner in our company?
How kind of you.
I'd rather not be a cleaner.
I'll be promoted next season
to be the associate director of the Housekeeping Department.
Have fun celebrating Dad's birthday.
Lingdang, kiss me goodbye.
- Bye-bye.
- Goodbye.
Bye.
[I've already bought Dad a leather coat. How about you buy him an electric shaver?]
Hongdou, why didn't you reply to my message?
I didn't get the time to reply.
The hot and sour soup today tastes great.
I'll get a bowl for you.
Cut to the chase.
I do have a favor to ask of you.
- My good friend's younger sister is an intern at the front desk.
- Hello.
She's capable, so guide her when you have the time.
Manager Xu, I'm Li Meiyu.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Are you graduating this year?
Do you have time after work?
I want to treat you to a meal.
Nope, I need to walk my dog.
You have time for a dog?
What about lunch tomorrow?
It's my day off tomorrow.
Hold on.
My VIP client is looking for me, so I'll get going.
Enjoy your meal.
Li Meiyu, I have two tips for you.
Firstly, avoid dishes with spring onion or garlic at work.
Secondly, don't drink too much water.
- Okay.
- I'm off.
Hongdou!
What's wrong?
My back has been hurting lately.
You have a gastroscopy tomorrow. Can you eat now?
Yeah, I just have to avoid food and drinks after 10:00 p.m.
What do you want to eat?
- Pizza!
- Sure.
Did you lose weight?
Is it obvious?
Are you on a diet?
Not at all.
It must be the business trip.
On my four-day business trip,
I inspected two hotels.
That included their environment and recreational facilities.
After I came back, I finished a report of 20,000 words.
I'm exhausted.
Our classmate, Li Jing, even commented on my post.
"I'm so envious! A free trip!"
What do you want to watch?
Anything's fine.
Your rich elder sister sent you tons of bird's nests again.
That's from last year.
Xu Hongdou!
It expired six months ago!
The chili sauce has expired, too!
I had it with cup noodles yesterday.
Is this the donkey-hide gelatin my mom made for you?
Yeah, I have some when I remember.
- What's wrong?
- Look at it yourself!
Why are you eating it? It's moldy!
I refrigerated that the moment you brought it over back then!
It hasn't been very long.
The last time I visited you was six months ago.
It's been that long?
Yeah.
We're not far off from the cowherd and the weaver fairy.
Even though we're both in Beijing,
we only meet up twice a year.
I'll help you clean your fridge after dinner.
We work so hard to make money.
But what for?
For a car!
Didn't you apply for the license lottery?
I won't get it in this life.
Take it easy.
Even if you buy a car, you'll still need the license first.
Besides, you'll be stuck during rush hours and frustrated from finding parking lots.
I used to think that I couldn't afford a house in Beijing,
so I might as well get a car.
Look at me now.
Even my simplest wish can't be fulfilled.
Forget about it then.
Who drove a car into a tree
when we headed home for the Chinese New Year?
Shut up about that and don't annoy me.
But that's the truth.
Drink less. It's bad for your stomach.
A little won't hurt.
This one is yours.
Delicious.
Look at my eyebags.
My eyebags appeared ages ago.
I even have dark eye circles and wrinkles.
It's the full package from staying up late.
Speaking of which, I'm starting to fear getting old.
It's time to find a boyfriend.
Go for it.
Didn't you say that your new colleague
is you type?
He's from an affluent family and he's handsome.
What's his name?
Sun Zhixin.
But he's six years younger than me.
Even if we date, I'm afraid we won't last for long.
I don't have time to waste.
Look at you. You're all talk.
You never take action.
But the age gap could be a real problem.
What about you? Any new suitors?
Yeah, a colleague. Poor chances though.
Why won't your colleague do?
Didn't your ex-boyfriend, Ke Ji, live too far from you?
One of you was in Yanjiao, and the other was in the East Fourth Ring.
You broke up because you met less than once a week.
[We hardly meet. Why don't we just break up?]
[Okay.]
So, we have to meet up.
However, meeting all the time is annoying.
He's just a colleague. There's no spark.
Life is so tough.
I want to retire.
Look at me.
I have no house, no car, and no boyfriend.
I feel so lost.
How's that so? You have clear goals.
Buy a house, buy a car, and get a boyfriend.
Then?
Then, you'll be happy.
Will I really be happy?
Probably.
Forget it. That's too idealistic.
How about we take our annual leaves
and travel to Yunnan?
I can't make it this year.
I'll be promoted soon, so I'll be busy.
You're so annoying!
You asked me to go with you,
but you're the busy one too.
You've stood me up for three years.
I'm really sorry... I promise to accompany you next year.
You can't be trusted anymore.
How about I buy you a birthday present this year?
I got a pay raise.
I want a handbag.
Sure.
I'm turning off the lights.
My back hurts. Massage it for me.
Sure.
- Here?
- Yeah.
[Happiness is the meaning and the purpose of life, the whole aim and end of human existence. - Aristotle]
Hongdou?
What's wrong? Having a stomachache?
They applied gel on my belly for the Doppler test.
It doesn't feel good.
Doesn't it itch?
Nope.
Are you allergic to it?
I have no idea.
This spot?
[Endoscopy Center]
- Xu Hongdou!
- Yes?
Room No. 2.
- Well...
- All the best! I'll wait for you.
All right.
Are you family?
The size of the tip of the pancreas
is abnormal.
What's the pancreas tip?
The front of the pancrease.
I suggest you head to the surgery department for a CT scan.
Don't waste any more time.
[CT Examination Room 2]
Chen Nanxing, it's your turn. Come on in.
It's on your right.
Thank you.
Chen Nanxing. Here are your results.
Come in.
Conservative treatment?
Is surgery out of the question?
It's advanced pancreatic cancer that has spread.
She can only take conservative treatment to ease her pain.
But she's so young! Why is this happening?
She's the only child of her family. How will they get by?
Thankfully, your examination results are okay.
I didn't hear you mention Nan Nan on the phone back then.
My heart was in my throat when I heard...
Mom...
I'm having dinner now. The dishes are getting cold.
Get on with your meal.
All right. Bye-bye.
[We sincerely apologize for the inconvenience.
Xu Hongdou, Waldorf Hotel.]
- Ouch.
- Kangkang.
Does your mom know you're here?
My mom's having a meal.
She asked me to play with Sister Nan Nan.
- That's good.
- I'm just babysitting.
Let me reply to a message from work.
Ouch.
I know it. Work is life until you're dead.
You should watch your health.
Your company will work you to death and get you replaced.
That's not appropriate to say here.
I'm trying to make a point.
Enough with this game. My hands hurt.
They're swollen from your hits. Let's play something else.
How about... Bumblebee?
Sure!
- Two bumblebees flying in the garden.
- Fly! Fly!
Fly!
Mom!
Are you okay, Mom?
- Kangkang, don't look.
- Doctor!
Nurse! Doctor!
There, there. I'm here.
Hongdou.
Mom!
I want some oden.
Mom...
Give me a few more eggs.
- Okay.
- Eggs.
Okay, eggs.
I want this one.
Give us more soup.
This reminds me of our college days.
I'd always get hungry after lights out.
I'd pester you to buy spicy hotpot for me.
Yeah, that restaurant closed down from your gorging.
No, they didn't!
They made enough money and bought a house in their hometown.
They went back to take care of their middle school children.
Really?
Of course! They told me!
You sure are great with small talk.
You're way too busy.
Right now, you should live a good life.
Eat and drink well.
Interact more with others.
Make more friends.
Otherwise, why are you working for money?
Enjoy life?
I used to tell myself
I should get a boyfriend soon, get married, and have children.
I'm scared of being a lonely old woman.
Now, I understand.
That was nonsense.
I never knew what I really wanted.
Isn't it happiness that you want?
Right now, health is happiness to me.
Do you remember our classmate, Li Ruiyuan?
She already has two children.
Really?
She has two children?
I had no idea!
Look at me.
I don't even have a single child.
Yeah, that's because you're single.
Why are you so mean?
Here you go.
Take this radish.
Radish tastes amazing.
It's all right.
[Symposium on Asian Biotechnology and Medicine]
Why is 1603 unavailable?
It smells like hotpot?
Try using air freshener.
The executive suites are overbooked today.
Okay.
Thanks, Sister Hongdou.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
What's happening?
That was really loud.
Manager Xu!
Sorry.
This doesn't match.
[Nanxing's Mom]
Give me a minute.
Hello, Aunty?
I'm on my way.
Help me apply for leave.
Manager Xu?
You have stomach problems, so you should eat slowly.
Don't be negligent because you're busy.
You need balanced nutrition.
Mister, you dropped a gear.
I don't need it anymore. It's chipped.
The gear is worn out after longterm use.
The clock won't be precise with it.
I'm swapping it out with a new one.
You can leave after taking the IV drip.
Doctor, am I dying?
I've given you an examination. You're fine.
You fainted, so it might be a little shocking.
It's just temporary ischemia and hypoxia
due to excessive stress or anxiety.
Just relax.
Don't be too anxious.
So, I'm not ill?
You're suffering from slight anemia and malnutrition.
You need iron supplements. Be sure to eat on time.
Have more eggs and meat. Don't skip meals just to diet.
- Thank you, Doctor.
- No problem.
You're free to go after taking the IV drip.
Okay.
Manager Xu, I've paid the bills.
I'll leave the receipt here.
Okay.
Thank you.
I... I have something urgent to attend to.
It's my boyfriend's birthday today.
He flew over from Guangzhou to meet me.
Hurry over to him. I'm fine.
I... I'll wait until your IV drip is done.
I'm feeling fine. You can go.
Don't make him wait.
Okay, I-I'll head off.
Manager Xu, call me immediately if you need anything.
- See you tomorrow.
Hongdou.
I don't know how to say this to you in person.
So, I'm sorry about this.
I have to speak to you like this.
You won't get a chance to answer me.
This might just be my last words.
When I'm gone,
I think my parents will be the most miserable.
Please give them a call during the holidays.
Check in on them for me.
A call is enough.
There's no need for anything else.
I know the two of them...
will never ask others for favors.
I'm sure they'll be ecstatic just to receive a call from you.
When I'm gone,
don't drown in sadness for too long.
Cry for a bit
and show that you're upset.
That's enough.
Anyway, I didn't do anything evil
in this life.
Right?
I'll go to a great place after death.
Don't worry.
Besides, I won't feel pain by then.
I'll be free.
You should be happy for me.
Don't you agree?
Actually, I really regret this.
Why didn't I confess my feelings to Sun Zhixin?
When it comes to romance,
one more day of happiness counts.
Isn't that so?
Right now,
there's still a world that I yearn to see...
but can no longer do so.
I'll leave this to you.
All the food, drinks, and experiences I want to try.
Everything I can't do.
I'll let you
eat, drink, and experience on my behalf.
But listen up.
Make sure to check the expiry dates before you eat anything.
Don't stuff everything into the fridge
and forget about them.
One more thing.
You have to take proper meals.
Sleep well.
Live a good life.
You have to be happy.
You have to go out more often.
Open your heart to others.
Make some friends.
After all,
someone has to
take my place.
Right?
If you meet someone you fancy,
take the initiative and go after them.
Don't wait for others to woo you
just because you're pretty.
Get into a romance.
Seize the day.
That's my assignment for you.
Do you hear me?
When I'm gone, grasp happiness for both of us
and enjoy life.
Stop wasting your time.
Lead the life...
you really want.
I'll keep you safe,
but on one condition.
Make sure you burn paper money for me.
The more the better.
I'm too tired to continue.
That's all for now.
This is a segment of my will.
If I think of more,
I'll add on to this.
By the way,
I'm glad I didn't confess my feelings to Sun Zhixin.
Otherwise, I'll be ruining his life.
All right, that's it.
I'll stop.
That's all.
I'm feeling...
pretty energetic today.
I can probably march on for another 500 years.
Can you believe that?
Will you drop by after work?
I want some steamed meat rolls.
Buy me some.
Okay.
♫ Listen to the rain falling into the silent forest ♫
♫ Enjoy the mountainous landscape at sunset ♫
♫ The raindrops from the roof drip into my eyes quietly ♫
♫ The world is like a quiet island ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright without a sound ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for a ray of sunlight to shine across
the lake into my heart ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon,
and the starry sky ♫
♫ Disoriented footsteps will gradually be erased ♫
♫ The light and shadows of the seasons ♫
♫  I've seen the meteor that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises, the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ I'll head to a windy place to meet you ♫
[Resignation Letter]
Yeah, Mom.
I got three months of paid leave.
I haven't taken any vacation for years.
I won't go home for now.
I want to spend a few months in Yunnan
and take a breather.
I want to travel.
♫ Listen to the rain falling into the silent forest ♫
♫ Enjoy the mountainous landscape at sunset ♫
♫ The raindrops from the roof drip into my eyes quietly ♫
♫ The world is like a quiet island ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright without a sound ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for a ray of sunlight to shine across
the lake into my heart ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon,
and the starry sky ♫
♫ Disoriented footsteps will gradually be erased ♫
♫ The light and shadows of the seasons ♫
♫  I've seen the meteor that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises, the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright without a sound ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for a ray of sunlight to shine across
the lake into my heart ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon,
and the starry sky ♫
♫ Disoriented footsteps will gradually be erased ♫
♫ The light and shadows of the seasons ♫
♫  I've seen the meteor that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises, the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ I'll head to a windy place to meet you ♫