I would love to do this again.
But do you wanna try something else
next time?
Like what?
A date?
No.
No, I didn't say date.
We can talk. Like, normal conversations
between two regular people.
Why? Do you want to go on a date?
No.
Not at all.
Talking sounds good.
-When? Today?
-Hmm.
-And, no Maharaja talk, no CEO talk.
-Not at all.
Just normal conversations
between two regular people. Right?
Stop it.
Stop it! Our main launch is in three days.
So what--
I'll show you the carpet samples tomorrow.
-Yeah, sounds good.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. Okay.
-Okay.
Girdhari ji?
Rani-sa would like to see you.
-Right now?
-Yes.
Okay.
Welcome back, Kunal sir.
Sorry for being late.
We'll have to postpone
The Royal B&B's launch.
-What?
-Why?
Rani-sa, the launch is in three days.
And the preparations are done.
Akshaya Tritiya is in three days.
This is the most auspicious time
in the last 15 years.
And that's why Aviraaj
will be crowned in three days.
What about our launch, Rani-sa?
The invites have been sent out.
We're ready to go. We're ready.
And I don't think you understand how big
of a problem it is for us, Rani-sa.
We really need your help.
You don't understand, Sophia…
that a Maharaja gets crowned
only once in a lifetime.
And so does our launch.
But a lot happens with the coronation.
Ideally, more than
40 royal families come over.
People from far and wide attend it.
But unfortunately, the situation is such
that Fizzy's coronation won't be as grand.
Even so, it should be memorable.
Rani-sa, what if we organize the launch
and Aviraaj's coronation on the same day?
-Okay.
-No, no!
I think it's a great idea.
-Yeah.
Right? And you know what?
The Royal B&B will take care
of half the expenses.
Invite everyone you want.
Make it grand.
This date is auspicious
for start a new business too.
It's great!
So, what kind of launch is it going to be?
One befitting Morpur's grandeur.
-That's right.
-Fifty biggest hospitality influencers
and top media reporters will be there.
If we give front row seats
to the influencers,
Aviraaj's name will become
a household name.
This is gonna be big. We will make it big.
Just trust us.
Okay.
-Great.
-And Sophia…
-Yes?
When will you tell Aviraaj?
What?
Kunal.
Hi.
I know I shouldn't have taken such
a big decision without consulting you,
but at that moment, it felt right and…
You know how I am and…
I'm really sorry.
Soph, your decision was absolutely right.
It's a great idea.
-Really?
-Yeah.
And… Zubin?
I'll handle him.
Focus on the launch.
Kunal, we haven't spoken in a while.
I really miss us.
Shall we go out for dinner?
Yeah.
I was thinking about it too.
After the launch?
Yeah. Sure.
Thank you.
I'll see you.
Kunal, funders are really excited.
They want to meet you. So, dress sharp.
I can't make it.
You haven't told her yet.
Kunal, why don't you be upfront with her?
She'll respect you more for it.
You like Sophia, so it--
I don't like Sophia.
Yeah, right, and I'm the Queen of England.
We can't meet again.
-We made a mistake once--
-Twice.
Twice.
Don't call those
love-filled moments a mistake.
We've made a mistake twice.
But not anymore.
The way…
you're getting prettier by the day…
It's not because of overthinking.
Don't try to butter me up.
I don't want to hurt Aviraaj.
And who's gonna make my heart happy?
It's already crazy about you…
Fine.
If you…
really want to crush my heart,
I won't say anything.
If not…
I'll wait for you in my suite.
Are you here for a date or to talk?
Your dress is definitely here for a date.
Aviraaj, I want to talk to you.
Yeah, I know. Normal conversations
between two regular people.
Let's start with school.
So, I used to be a backbencher.
-But I was totally--
-Actually, it's about work. You…
You think we could stop the music?
Your coronation is in three days.
-I'm not joking.
-Okay.
No, really, I'm serious.
That's why Rani-sa asked for me today--
Whoa, absolutely the fuck not.
Look,
I know this makes you
really uncomfortable, Aviraaj,
and I promise you only our launch
was planned on that day.
But Rani-sa insisted
-that it's auspicious--
-Don't listen to my mother.
Please.
Okay? Focus on your launch.
Forget about the coronation.
But, Aviraaj, think about it.
This could be…
This could be so great for us.
You're already the Maharaja.
So, honestly, it's just a formality.
This is not just a formality.
This formality can change lives.
I need time.
I'm not ready.
Okay.
If you're not ready, I'll…
I'll find a solution.
Okay?
So…
Where were we? School.
-Sadly, I was a topper at school.
-Wait a second.
Why did you agree so easily?
If you're insisting, it must be important.
And honestly, Aviraaj…
I don't wanna push you.
No, clearly, this coronation ceremony
happening on launch day
is important for you.
Isn't it?
Then wait for some time.
I can't push the launch date, Aviraaj.
It was decided months in advance and…
honestly, I don't want to either.
Why? Why does it have to be in three days?
So, I don't want you
to get weird about this…
Aviraaj, it's my parents'
death anniversary in three days.
It took me years to gather the courage…
to do something new on that day.
It's probably really silly, but…
I want to do it.
So…
I can't change the date.
Look, I…
I told you don't get weird about it,
because if you do…
-I'll feel weird too--
-In three days, huh?
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's do it.
-No.
-Yeah.
-The whole thing, let's do it.
The coronation and all.
Aviraaj, you don't want to, and I…
don't want you to do anything
that you don't feel like.
It's fine.
I wanna do it.
You're right. It's just a formality.
Okay.
Sorry, I messed up the date--
-What did you mess up?
-What did I mess up?
-You said "date."
-Date, huh?
We've been paired up
for the next round of Gastronautics.
That's why I'm letting you
practice, Dilip. Okay?
-Wait a second. What are you doing?
-What?
-Is this a wrestling ring?
-Then--
You're wrestling with it. Move!
Hey.
Knead it gently, man. Massage it.
-Okay, I'll do it. I will.
-Do it then.
Like this.
Like this…
Are you getting late?
No, I just need to get to Morpur.
Are you from Morpur?
-Yes.
-Where in Morpur?
Moti…
bagh.
Motibagh.
Palace?
Yes.
You sneak!
Do you work there?
I'm a dishwasher there, that's all.
Can you take me there some day?
Even my mother is not allowed there.
Then you're not allowed here. Move.
-What happened?
-Move!
-Move.
Fine.
It's difficult,
but I'll try.
I am not promising anything. I'll ask.
Massage it.
-Massage it.
-Yeah.
In 1870, the jewelers of Lucknow
made this head ornament.
It's not just a piece of jewelry,
it represents Morpur's history.
The diamonds and the lotus flowers
engraved on it
represent the power and glory
of the Maharaja.
It was last adorned
by Maharaja Yuvanath Singh himself.
The peacock engraved on this ornament
represents the arrival of the new Maharaja
who will always be there
for Morpur and its citizens.
Our last Maharaja Yuvanath Singh's
elder son, Aviraaj Singh…
Be careful, Hukum.
Sorry. Sorry.
Mom, can we do the rest tomorrow? Please.
Is everything okay between you two?
Yes.
Excuse me.
-Pankaj-sa.
-Yes.
Hukum, your achkan looks great.
It's not an achkan, it's a problem.
Hukum, after the ceremony tomorrow,
this sword and case
will also be handed over to you.
Besides that,
the Maharaja will bathe 108 times.
If you wish, you may use
this sword on me right now.
-What are you saying, Hukum!
-Hukum.
Yes?
What is it, Rafiq chacha?
He's not eating and he's vomiting.
-Since when?
-This morning, Hukum.
And you're telling me now?
It started out of nowhere, Hukum.
Khan must get the best treatment.
-Sure.
-Am I making myself clear?
-I don't care about the expenses.
-Sure, Hukum.
You'll be fine, Khan.
A HISTORICAL MOMENT FOR MORPUR,
MAHARAJA AVIRAAJ SINGH TO BE CROWNED SOON!
TO GRACE THE THRONE,
COMES MAHARAJA AVIRAAJ
Today, Rajasthan's Morpur city
will reverberate with loud cheers
for the Maharaja
Late Maharaja Yuvanath Singh's elder son,
Prince Aviraaj Singh,
will receive the honor
of wearing the crown of Morpur.
Darling,
are you okay?
I'm okay.
All the best, darling.
It's a very important day of your life.
Yeah.
Fizzy, the position of a Maharaja
comes with loneliness.
Does it mean
you must push your family away?
It's an age-old tradition of Morpur
that all the royal families of the region
and the citizens of Morpur
gather here to witness
the coronation of the Maharaja.
This time, The Royal B&B
has added to the grandeur of this ceremony
by inviting social media influencers
and the guests.
-All hail the Maharaja!
The Royal B&B is a dream
my co-Founder Kunal Mehta and I
dreamt of together.
Today, all of you,
the hospitality influencers
will witness a spectacle here.
A once-in-a-lifetime event.
The coronation of Morpur's Maharaja.
-Wow!
-Great.
And along with that,
you'll witness our dream come true.
From today, The Royal B&B is yours.
And now, we're open for bookings.
I do want to bore you
with the business details,
but Kunal is worried
that you will all disappear in no time.
Until then, enjoy Morpur's fresh air.
Enjoy this special experience.
And, please, Gram the hell out of us.
Yeah!
Lot of stories, lot of boomerangs please.
Please enjoy this royal experience.
And please tag The Royal B&B.
I'll check.
Oh, my God!
Sophia has outdone herself.
It's so beautiful.
Diggy, let's go find Fizzy.
Enjoy your life, Paddy.
But make sure
to always keep up the appearances.
Greetings, Dhondi Maharaja.
Greetings. How are you?
I'm fine. Glad to meet you.
What's the matter, Dhondi Sahab?
Your eye seems to be
twitching a lot today.
No. It's…
Greetings, Rani-sa.
…just…
expressing its desires.
You seem to have forgotten…
that you don't wink at a Maharani,
but lower your gaze.
Please forgive my folly.
But my Paddy was singing a different tune
when we were making those two mistakes.
Stay in your limits.
Limits?
Now you're gonna teach me my limits?
You seem to be forgetting, Rani-sa,
I'll own this palace soon.
Have you lost your mind?
This is Morpur's Maharaja's palace.
Who is my daughter's fiancé.
That's where you're mistaken.
Why?
I see.
So, they found out about us.
Or should I tell them?
-Are you trying to threaten me?
-How can I dare to?
I'm just making a deal.
Rani-sa,
I'm so sorry to interrupt
but do you know where Aviraaj is?
I've given the medicine to Khan, Hukum.
It may take…
an hour to take effect, Hukum.
But…
But?
But if there's no improvement,
-we may have to let Khan go--
-You may leave.
-But, Hukum…
-Didn't you hear me?
Hukum.
Rafiq chacha,
-no one is allowed to touch Khan.
-Yes, Hukum.
Aviraaj, I know a really good vet.
We'll call him.
Everything will be fine. Okay?
I told you…
everything changes.
Coronation is not just a formality.
I said it.
You didn't pay heed to it.
That's not fair, Aviraaj.
I only requested you.
This was completely your decision.
-This is not okay--
-He died.
Aviraaj…
Khan is alive.
Listen to me.
-I'm listening.
-You're not.
-I am listening to you, Aviraaj.
-Listen…
-Will you listen to me for a second?
-Okay.
Okay, calm down. I'm listening to you.
He died.
And I couldn't do anything.
He left without meeting me.
Aviraaj.
Aviraaj…
He's… He's with you, Aviraaj.
He's in you. You are him.
How's he in me?
He's dead!
When he was alive, I left!
What's the point now?
You get it now, Aviraaj.
Finally, you've understood everything.
You're here, you didn't run away, did you?
You didn't, did you?
You did not do what's easy.
I didn't do what's easy!
I have the biggest launch of my career
planned today, Aviraaj!
It's tough for me to do this on this day.
And I'm only doing it for them.
I'm doing it for my Mom and Dad.
Just like you are!
You're doing this for yourself,
not for them!
You…
really think
that I'm doing this for myself?
You know what's funny?
I was doing this for you.
Fizzy?
Did you run away again? Fizzy!
Hello?
Cement this traitor into the wall!
Stop! Even the traitors in Morpur
are treated with kindness under my rule.
Kindness?
All hail Maharaja Digvijay!
All hail King Digvijay!
All hail Emperor Digvijay!
Fizzy!
What's wrong, Fizzy?
Oh, God.
What happened, Fizzy?
Huh? Did you eat something wrong?
What happened?
Okay, okay. Relax.
Relax.
I can't do it.
What?
-I can't do it.
-What?
Dad died, Diggy.
-This crown killed him!
-Fizzy.
The crown is worn
just on the outside, Fizzy.
Something was eating up Dad on the inside.
You own it.
-No, I can't. You stop this!
-Get up!
I can't do it.
-Get up.
-I can't do it, Diggy!
I can't--
What the fuck, dude?
That felt really good.
Okay, now that you're awake…
Come on.
I can't do it. I can't.
-I can't do it.
-You can.
And you will, because you have to.
Fizzy, you were born for this.
You're the eldest son of this family.
Everyone loves you.
I've seen it.
There are thousands gathered outside
from every corner of Morpur,
and they are here only for you.
For the Maharaja.
That's you.
So, believe me when I say, you got this.
Come on now.
Okay?
-And I'm here for you.
-Okay.
Don't stress.
And I know without a shadow of a doubt,
Dad would've been so proud of you today.
Okay?
Okay.
Go, wash your face. You look silly.
Hello?
How would I know the name on his ID?
-Please…
-How long have you worked here?
There he is.
Dilip, tell them that you know me!
Hukum.
Hukum?
-Hukum, do you know her?
-Yes.
Molshri, you didn't give me a heads-up.
Look, Dilip, or whatever your name is,
don't ever call me,
or I'll tell the Gastronautics officials.
-that you're a fraud.
-Hold on.
-You're mistaken.
-And I don't want to get disqualified!
Maharaj. Maharaja!
I'll drop you back home.
Please come inside.
I'll manage!
-Hukum.
-I'm not the Maharaja!
-What?
This achkan belongs to Maharaja Aviraaj.
I know!
-Sophia.
-Hi.
-Nandini, hi.
-Congratulations.
Thank you so much. I hope
Keertana is taking care of you.
-Of course. Don't worry about it.
-I'm glad.
-Okay, listen.
-Yes?
Can I get an exclusive interview
with you after the ceremony?
Sorry, Nandini, not today.
Kunal and I are really busy,
but I promise you, tomorrow.
Greetings, sir.
What happened? Did I say something wrong?
No, you didn't, but you lied.
What?
I mean, how can Kunal
give an interview with you
when he's quitting your company?
Okay, I'm getting a call.
I'll talk to you later. Okay?
So, you're alive.
Then why aren't you answering my calls?
Sorry to disappoint.
Ayesha, we should…
We should talk.
We will.
But after the coronation ceremony.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Come with me.
Hang on.
Ayesha…
Sophia and I…
hooked up.
It's fine.
Come on.
One second.
Doesn't it bother you?
You guys hooked up.
Big deal.
Affairs don't have a future.
But we do.
Therefore, we need to move on.
Let's go.
Why did you attend the ball that night?
Are you all right?
Are you scared of adulting?
Do you need help?
Don't worry about me.
Just answer my question please.
Why did you come that night?
Because if I have to be a queen,
I'd better find a king
who will live happily in New York.
So I can run Dhondi Hospitality
the way I want.
You don't have any attachment
to Motibagh anyway.
Then what's the problem?
Your ideology.
We don't have a future, Ayesha.
And you do with Sophia?
She knows that you always run from Morpur,
from the people…
From yourself.
-Or is she as screwed up as you?
-You don't know Sophia.
And don't even try to figure her out.
She is nothing like you.
She can't be like me even if she tries to.
She's just a commoner…
Maharaja.
Please leave, Ayesha.
Pankaj-sa!
Hukum.
Please escort her to her car.
Thank you, Pankaj-sa.
I will manage.
Greetings, Maharaja.
I see.
So these are Morpur's etiquettes.
Maharaja has a message for you.
Princess Ayesha
is ready to leave with you.
So the son has decided
to act up like his mother.
Dhondi Sahab,
you are talking
about the Maharaja of Morpur.
Watch your words.
Say another wrong word,
and you'll be kicked out
in a very wrong way.
You better think again, Rani-sa.
Messing with me will cost you dearly.
Then I'll manage with something cheap.
I don't have money anyway.
Shall we?
Kunal,
are you joining Sameera?
-Just give us a minute.
-Oh, my God, Kunal.
When were you going to tell me?
I was going to. Trust me.
When, Kunal? I heard it from Nandini.
This is not the place or the time.
-I'll talk to you--
-Then when?
After the launch? Or were you waiting
for a press conference?
What is she offering you?
Sellout bonus? She's doubling your stocks?
Or a private jet? What is it?
She values me.
And I don't value you, right?
Fuck you, Kunal.
Fuck you!
Zubin's asking me to stay back too.
Zubin what?
You should know that I turned him down.
But Zubin also wants me to be the CEO.
The heir to Morpur throne,
late Maharaja Yuvanath Singh's son,
Prince Aviraaj Singh is here
at his grand coronation ceremony
to ascend the throne
with his people as his witness.
Welcome, O our King
You rule this land
Amidst the drums and trumpets
We welcome you
All hail our King
Welcome, O our King
You rule this land
Amidst the drums and trumpets
All hail our King
-All hail the Maharaja!
All hail Maharaja Aviraaj!
All hail our King
The pride and prestige of our King
Our King is our pride
Our King is loved by all
The pride and prestige of our King
Our King is our pride
Our King is loved by all
The pride and prestige of our King
Our King is our pride
Our King is loved by all
The pride and prestige of our King
Our King is our pride
Our King is loved by all
Hi, Sophia. How's the launch going?
Zubin, did you offer
the CEO's position to Kunal?
It was the board's decision, Sophia.
I can't do anything on my own.
Bullshit, Zubin.
You've always been trying to kick me out.
Why would I kick you out
of your own company?
Unless you're unable to run the company.
How is that, Zubin?
Everything is fine. See it for yourself!
What is the fucking problem?
What exactly is your definition
of "fine," Sophia?
Your deliverables, timelines
keep changing.
You don't get along with your clients.
Your team is unhappy with you.
I already told you, Sophia…
Not every founder can be a good CEO.
But the CEO of your choice is leaving.
What are you gonna do now?
I'll find someone else.
Zubin, we had a deal.
I told you that if I failed, I'd quit.
Then why are you doing this?
Why wait till you fail
when we can save our investment?
Zubin, this is my company,
and I'm going to fight tooth and nail
to make sure the votes swing towards me.
-You wait and--
-The board wants you to resign.
We have a majority.
Six to three.
-All hail…
-The Maharaja!
Hukum.
Hukum. Greetings, Hukum.
We couldn't find Ms. Shekhar anywhere.
But Khan is much better now.
You can visit him.
Fizzy,
Morpur is yours from today.
And I wanted you to get this letter
after you become the Maharaja,
because I've taught you
how a Maharaja must conduct himself.
I told you that being a Maharaja
comes with loneliness.
But today, I must tell you
that because of that,
you must choose your own path.
You must find your love.
Without love, we are weak.
Even a King.
I listened to people
and forgot to listen to my heart.
I lived a fake life.
But one day, out of the blue,
life lead me to my strength, my love.
I was wrong, Fizzy.
A Maharaja can also have desires,
and the name of your father's love is…
Maurice.
Subtitle translation by:
Sheela Sijin Mathews