=My Name is Zhao Chuxi=
=Episode 7=
Shaoqing.
Sorry, am I late?
Not at all.
You're right on time.
Did you pick out this outfit yourself today?
It's elegant and suits you perfectly.
I remember you said
that you want to create
a private haute couture brand named Xiluo.
Still interested?
- What's private haute couture?
- I'll invest in you.
You wouldn't understand high society matters.
Not interested for now.
Let's talk when there's a chance.
Alright.
Then let's head inside.
Let's go.
I need to go in and work for Ms. Su.
I'm her personal assistant.
Personal assistant, huh?
Assistants can only wait outside.
From Luoshen Group?
How... How do you know?
I've read your profile.
Zhao Chuxi, right?
Yes.
My name is Zhao Chuxi.
I'm Ms. Su's driver at Luoshen Group.
If I'm not mistaken,
you and Xu Shaoqing don't get along.
There's hostility between you two.
His hostility toward you
is because you're too close to Su Xiluo.
And your hostility toward him,
first,
you just can't stand his attitude;
second,
it's also because of Su Xiluo.
Don't you think this woman is a bit sly?
Using you as a pawn.
With your current strength,
what benefit is there
in opposing Xu Shaoqing?
You're here to gather intel, aren't you?
Smart.
Let me ask you one question.
Make your choice.
If I told you to stay neutral,
to advance or withdraw,
holding onto Su Xiluo tightly,
or distancing yourself from her,
what would you choose?
Do I have to answer?
If I tell you,
your answer will decide
whether the cooperation is successful.
Dare to bet?
I don't dare.
I don't have the leverage.
But,
I must tightly hold onto Su Xiluo.
She's my stepping stone.
If I leave her,
I'll definitely fall back to square one.
Smart,
bold, and ambitious.
But let me tell you this,
it's good for a man to have ambition.
But you must learn to keep it hidden.
Being too rigid can lead to failure.
I understand your desire
to rise above.
I fear poverty.
I lack money.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Xu Lin.
You really match my vibe.
Would you like to be friends?
Sure.
Absolutely.
Xu, this...
This scene...
This is so-called high society, huh?
This is life.
Life is full of pretenses everywhere.
That's why so many people
will do anything to enter high society.
Those with no money or little money,
come here to make a living.
As for the wealthy ones,
they come here to prove their worth.
Remember this:
shallow waters, plenty of wannabes.
You'll only know,
who's swimming naked when the tide recedes.
Xu,
you must have seen a lot
to say that, huh?
How about I work with you?
(This guy is so shameless)
(that reminds me of my younger self.)
Get your footing first.
Then we'll talk when you're stronger.
At first, they were still on the fence.
But after your negotiation,
they're scrambling to invest in you
and afraid you'd run away.
Xiluo, you always manage to give me
unexpected surprises.
Not really.
Of course,
sometimes, there are tiny shocks too.
Like
that person.
Didn't you promise me
not to let him be your assistant anymore?
I almost forgot about this.
Shaoqing, I think you're absolutely right.
He's not suited to be an assistant.
So now,
he's my driver and bodyguard.
Fancy wine parties? Not even filling.
Driver and bodyguard,
you're still not full?
That's all what you've got.
How does me eating a sausage bother you?
Talking all day long.
Zhao Chuxi,
you made a new friend?
I just met a guy, and he's quite interesting.
Quite interesting?
You know, he's not as simple as he seems.
He's officially an assistant at his company,
but he's actually the one
making all the decisions.
Zhao Chuxi,
if you can become friends with him,
I'll owe you big time.
Alright, I got it.
Alright?
Alright, Fusheng BBQ.
Let's go!
Driver and bodyguard,
you just got your license.
It's time to test your skills.
Just don't press the brake and gas together!
You're always so talkative all day.
My driving skills are top-notch now.
- Cheers.
I have a few words to say.
First of all,
Lu Yao,
I want to thank you.
Because of you,
I found the courage to face my heart.
Absolutely right.
Also, without her, you wouldn't drive.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- And also,
I need to thank you, Chuxi.
Ms. Su, no need to be so formal with me.
Thank you for coming back.
Come on, cheers.
Here we go.
Cheers!
Just go!
Ms. Su,
I've always admired you.
Why?
You know,
you're the one in this world,
aside from my sister,
that I admire the most.
Wait a second.
You have a sister?
She's my adoptive father's daughter.
Is your sister pretty?
Much prettier than you.
You...
Me what?
Is your sister prettier,
or is Ms. Su prettier?
Each has their charm.
Wrong answer.
- Punish you.
- Punish you!
Go ahead.
Zhao Chuxi,
you're a good person
in every way,
but you have one shortcoming
that you're too honest.
Drink up!
Is being honest bad?
Just drink!
People in the village are all honest.
- Come on!
- You're really good at it.
I respond really fast.
Faster than you.
Cheers.
(Shui She Suite Hotel)
Can you walk by yourself?
I...
I can't.
My legs feel weak. I can't move.
Let me help you. Come on.
Take it slow, okay?
Oh dear, you're quite heavy.
Ms. Su,
is this your friend?
Yes.
Why did he drink so much?
Come on, let me help you.
No need.
It's fine.
Don't be polite, buddy.
We security guards are really professional.
- Come on.
- I don't need you.
I've got Ms. Su.
Ms. Su is just a young lady.
Look, you've already overwhelmed her.
No need to be so formal.
It's... it's fine.
Come on, buddy.
Ms. Su, you go ahead.
Alright.
- I'll get the door.
- Alright then.
Your arm...
Arm... Let's go.
Why are you so clueless?
Can't you figure this out?
People never ruin a marriage.
Don't mess up my plans.
Ms. Su.
Did I ruin a marriage?
This city is indeed full of tricks.
Such a deep scar.
That must've hurt a lot.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
Don't get me wrong.
I bring my brother to you. This is my robe.
No.
My brother asked me to bring you a robe.
Your brother?
It's not that.
This is my brother's robe.
I... I bring it to you.
You get changed first, alright?
Ms. Su,
you always keep such a stern face,
isn't that uncomfortable?
You should smile more.
Smiling makes the world a better place.
I'll go prepare your bed.
The sheets and covers have all been changed.
They're clean.
Rest easy and sleep well.
Call me if you need anything.
Or just send me a message.
Go to bed early.
Why aren't you asleep yet?
You're not sleeping either.
What are you looking at?
You look so good.
Do I look good?
Great.
Do you like me?
Who wouldn't like you?
You dress like this.
Aren't you afraid I might
take things further?
You're playing with fire here.
Where's my room?
Over there.
I'm tired, going to sleep.
Playing with fire?
He got the desire but not the guts, huh?
Come here, come here.
What are you hiding for?
Hey.
I'm awkward to face you.
I almost ruined your big moment last night.
You know, huh?
Next time, be more perceptive
and use your brain, got it?
Got it.
I spent all night thinking.
I was wondering if I ruined ten temples,
or broke up a marriage.
The conclusion is,
I might've messed up your marriage.
It's not that serious.
I pushed you away, didn't I?
Think before you act next time.
Show some emotional intelligence.
- Got it?
- Got it.
Where are you from?
Hua County.
Really? I'm from Wanjing Mountain.
Is that so?
Are you serious?
It's true. My name is Zhao Chuxi.
I might be a few years older than you.
I'll call you Zhao from now on.
My name is Zhang Maodun.
Maodun?
Your name doesn't sound right.
It's a contradiction in itself.
My dad came up with this name randomly.
Zhao, to be honest,
I really admire you.
Since Ms. Su moved into this neighborhood,
aside from the pesky flies,
no man has ever stepped into her room.
Really?
Impressive.
I'll treat you to dinner sometime.
You know,
keep an eye on Ms. Su for me.
I'm currently her assistant and bodyguard.
I'm responsible for her safety.
Take more care of her, alright?
Got it.
Let me leave you a phone number.
If there's anything with Ms. Su,
I'll call you immediately.
Got it.
Zhao, I promise,
even if it's a male fly,
it won't get into her room.
Okay.
You're my idol.
Well...
The overnight stay...
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Mr. Xu,
I saw Zhao Chuxi left Ms. Su's place
this morning.
- Get out.
- Mr. Xu...
Xiluo,
I really don't understand you anymore.
Don't tell me you're into Zhao Chuxi.
Zhao Chuxi!
Guan Yue.
Here.
Earlier,
I asked you to investigate Zhao Chuxi.
How's it going?
Everything is clear.
Besides working at Ms. Su's company,
Zhao Chuxi is also the security captain
at Langtaosha Bathhouse.
That's all?
That's all.
Three things.
First,
find someone to clean this up;
second,
don't let more people know about this;
third,
you personally lead a team
to teach Zhao Chuxi a serious lesson.
Alright.
I'm on it.
Can you do me a favor?
Go ahead.
I'm feeling a bit embarrassed.
No need for that. Just say it.
My brother asks me if I have a boyfriend.
He keeps asking and I feel annoying.
I said I do.
That's what I'm thinking.
Once his school starts,
come with me to meet him, okay?
Want me to pretend to be your boyfriend?
Alright, I agree.
But the specific details,
like family situation, tell me clearly,
to avoid making a mistake later.
Thank you, Chuxi.
Why so polite with me?
Look at this snow.
Come on.
Cheers.
Sanqiang.
Can you get me a car?
I already have one.
My van.
Here.
To get a more fancy car.
You know, one that looks impressive.
What do you need it for?
Just helping Qin Ran.
Oh my gosh.
Chuxi, something's going on with you, huh?
Nothing is going on.
Her family's press her to get married.
I'm just pretending to be her boyfriend
to deal with her brother.
Pretend?
What? Why are you pretending?
Why not just make it real?
Exactly, why bother pretending?
Don't talk nonsense.
She's a decent young lady.
We have a pure friendship.
- Pure friendship?
- Pure, you say?
A pure friendship.
Here's to friendship!
Be serious.
Cheers to friendship!
It's pure.
It's a serious matter.
No problem.
I'll take care of the car.
Don't you need a driver?
Don't you need a bodyguard?
Forget it.
You're scaring her.
What are you talking about?
Actually,
it's just to show off.
One driver, one bodyguard.
That will be absolutely impressive.
Yeah.
Correct.
Erpang,
you have to learn from Chuxi.
Look at how considerate
he is towards a girl.
You really should learn.
- Absolutely.
- Learn it.
Don't make fun of me anymore.
- Hurry up.
- Learn from him.
Here, I propose a toast to you, Chuxi.
Why this toast, though?
Is it for friendship or for status?
For the status of friendship.
Drink it.
Come on, come on.
How's that? Feel proud yet?
Sure.
Whose car?
Sanqiang handled it.
Today, I'm the professional driver.
Today, I'm the personal bodyguard.
I've arranged everything for later.
Isn't this a bit too flashy?
My brother doesn't believe it.
No way, I'm a big boss now.
Making it too plain wouldn't convince him.
Alright.
- Mr. Zhao, please.
Ying, right?
Bro.
You've grown so tall.
But you're way too thin.
You need to focus on nutrition.
It's my place.
You can eat whatever you want.
Beer or liquor?
He's a kid.
Let's get some beer then.
Sure, bro.
Then let's go with some beer.
A pack of beer.
Got it!
Sis,
are you sure
this is your boyfriend?
Well...
How could this be fake?
This is nothing
like what I imagined.
Is it higher
or lower
than expected?
It's definitely higher!
See, Ying knows what to say.
I like it.
I'll give you a big red envelope later.
Learn from Chuxi.
Watch how he handles the conversation.
You'll treat your girlfriend like that later.
Why would I need that?
Why don't you get yourself a girlfriend?
I'd love to, but I need one first.
Bro, what line of work are you in?
During New Year, I asked my sister,
but she didn't say a word.
I've been holding back until now.
Real estate.
People in real estate are always rich.
Private enterprise or state-owned one?
Private enterprise.
Luoshen Group.
Do you know about it?
I've heard of it.
These year, the group's branch...
Whose car is parked at the entrance? Move it.
The car.
Mine, it's mine.
The car is mine.
These years, the company's business
has been expanding into Jia City.
Do you know the International Mansion?
That's actually managed by our group.
Over there...
You're asking too much.
Don't worry.
I came here under the order of our parents.
You're already at this age,
and you still don't have a boyfriend.
They're also concerned.
- Here.
- Ying's got a point.
She finally got a boyfriend.
I had to come over to check things out.
Come on, bro.
Bro, I'll make a toast to you.
No way.
As the elder, I should fill my glass.
- Cheers, Ying.
- Cheers, bro.
Bottoms up.
What about me?
Here, let me.
Sis.
Are you taking the bus back or a taxi?
Look. His driver is picking us up.
Hello.
Qin Ying.
How about having my driver take you back?
No, no need.
Taking the bus back is fine for me.
Alright.
I let my driver send your sister home first.
Sis.
Bro.
I'll head back now.
- Alright.
Take care.
Take care, Qin Ying.
What should we do now?
Head back to work.
Work is so boring.
How long can we borrow this car?
Until tomorrow.
I want to drive too.
Then let's go.
Let's take a drive.
Mr. Guan, we've remembered what you said.
Go ahead.
Be mindful of your actions.
(Langtaosha Business Club)
Sir, please check the water temperature
and see if it's hot.
Are you trying to burn me?
What kind of service is this?
Apologies, sir.
What are you staring at? Hurry up!
- Could you blow-dry for me?
- Sir.
Serve me well and I'll let it go.
Sir, show some respect.
Sir, please.
What are you pretending for?
- Sir, don't do this!
- Help! Help!
- Come here!
- Someone help!
Mao, help!
Sir!
Mao!
Sir! Sir!
Don't get handsy.
It's a legitimate business.
What if I do get handsy?
Could you both step outside with me?
Alright?
We're out here. What's the matter?
Zhao.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
There's no need for this tension, right?
So many people.
Let me count.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11.
What, trying to threaten me?
Not possible.
We're in the service industry.
- You look respectable.
- Are you okay?
How about this?
If you're not satisfied,
I'll cover the bill today, alright?
Please, calm down.
No, I can't.
Do you see the surveillance footage?
How about I call the police now?
Let the officers come over
and help you calm down.
You're ruthless.
We'll just wait and see.
Are you two okay?
We're fine.
You two head back now.
Take the day off from work.
Go home and get some rest.
It's really nothing.
Listen to me. Go back and rest.
What exactly happened?
I don't know.
They stirred trouble on purpose.
See you, sir.
Sir,
Zhao Chuxi is finishing work early tonight.
He must pass through Xiaokang Alley.
Got it.
Don't worry, sir.
I've already taken care of everything.
I reassigned all of Zhao Chuxi's men.
No one will help him tonight.
Take care.
- We're going.
- Take care.
Zhao Chuxi,
let's see how you'll handle this.
Captain Qiao, what are you looking?
Where have you been?
I'm heading to the restroom.
Why do you need to go so often?
Nature calls, you know.
Take care, Captain Qiao.
(Langtaosha Business Club)
See you, Zhao.
Bye.
Zhao! Zhao!
Teach me how to do this.
After you leave, I can practice.
Not today, feeling a bit tired.
Can't handle it today.
I'll teach you another day.
Uh...
Take care.
Yeah.
Stay safe.
I'm in.
Two Qs.
Two Jokers.
Go ahead, then.
I can't. Just go.
- Hello? Chuxi.
- Erpang,
I'm off work now.
Call Sanqiang and let's grab breakfast.
Sounds good.
Qiang and I will join you soon.
Alright.
♪I'm just a nameless person
on this road♪
♪I have no news or comments from anyone♪
♪I'm struggling for an ordinary script♪
♪Despite the twists and turns,
it's just to survive♪
♪I'm the one who left the small town♪
♪The one who ate
while crying or laughing♪
♪The one on the road,
and the one feeding the family♪
♪The silent one in the city background♪
♪I just want to touch it with my hands♪
♪Every moment I bend down♪
♪Are the wet footprints
I leave worth it♪
♪If you're also choking♪
♪Then we're friends on the same road♪
♪To all those who stand tall
but are ordinary♪
♪I come from the spring in the north
and every step I take♪
♪Behind me, there's a parting road,
warming every sunset♪
♪When my hometown enters winter,
after the train stops♪
♪The wind from childhood blows again♪
♪Reminiscing the simple happiness♪
♪On the familiar street♪
♪Someone will use all their tenderness♪
♪To shout your name♪
♪Those who left home, cheers to you♪
♪To your silence and every scream♪
♪To your bent back and walking uphill♪
♪Striving to live under the vast sky♪
♪The nameless people, cheers to you♪
♪Listen to your silence
and every scream♪
♪To your bent back and walking uphill♪
♪Striving to live under the vast sky♪
♪Nameless people♪
♪Nameless people, the car is here♪
♪Don't look back with so many worries♪