- Mr. Ho Woo!
- Well, the thing is...
I...
What's this?
Well...
do you normally not have any boundaries with other people?
People could get distracted at times.
Who cares, right?
Is it something that embarrassing?
I've never done anything to be embarrassed about.
Then include me too.
I don't usually meddle in other people's work, but
I also don't want new staff to struggle.
Shall we...
do it properly this time?
Cooperation.
Do you even know what this is?
I have an inkling of what it is.
There are things that are important
to a person's life, such as wealth, fame, power, and love.
There are many things.
You're not the type to chase after power or fame, Mr. Ho Woo,
but money...
you are having other thoughts because of money, right?
Maybe it's because of his educational background...
You can't understand the way Jang Ho Woo acts, right?
You know how those who lack a proper education think they're so great.
That's what I mean.
Does he think the company is a place for self-actualization?
Who does he think he is to mess up a deal?
In an age where even the chairman would be called a kkondae (old fogey) for self-actualization...
What a hero.
Don't you think he'll get fired?
We'll have to wait and see about that.
Even if that is true,
you talk about someone else's business too easily.
I didn't say this easily.
My heart is beating so fast right now.
No.
It looks easy for you.
Me?
I only did this because you seemed to be having a hard time, Mr. Ho Woo.
Does it really look easy for me?
Yes.
I don't know exactly why you're so serious like this.
All I can do is take a guess.
But...
even if you may be going through a hard time, you shouldn't
trivialize someone else's sincerity.
I wasn't trivializing it.
This is why I say a blind (anonymous) hire is useless.
What's the point of giving him a chance?
He does whatever he wants, thinking he is so talented.
I don't think they'll hire any more high school graduates due to Mr. Jang Ho Woo.
Of course not. Common sense is part of intelligence.
Getting good scores on the exam isn't everything.
I know.
I wonder if he has any friends.
Even if he does, they're probably all high school graduates like him.
They probably all live full of themselves.
Why do you look down on high school graduates?
- Ms. Yeon Ah?
- I asked why you look down on high school graduates.
I mean, tell him what he's doing wrong.
Is it right for educated people like you to discriminate by education level and stereotypes?
I mean, why would you get involved, Ms. Yeon Ah?
My father is a high school graduate, too.
I just got a bit upset.
Sorry.
In any case, Mr. Ho Woo being a high school graduate isn't a problem.
He's capable and has convictions.
But yes... well...
even from what I can see, he does seem a bit timid.
And he does seem a bit narrow-minded...
I'm sorry.
What was that?
Isn't this V.P. Han Je Gyun?
To think I'll see you here...
How long has it been?
Have you been well, Chairman Lee Seong Joo?
I've been well, thanks to you, V.P. Han.
But what brings you here?
He's here for an appreciation banquet hosted by the Taeil Scholarship Association.
By Taeil Scholarship Association,
I assume you mean those you've supported for the past 20 years.
To those in the Taeil Scholarship Association, you would be
someone they should be grateful to for the rest of their lives.
Well, then take care of your business
and get home safely.
I'll come by to see you soon.
I have something to discuss with you.
I have something for which I need your discernment and insight, V.P. Han.
I'll contact you and visit you at Taeil Accounting.
So what is it that you want from me?
You must want something from me, to be doing this.
Please let me pass the confirmation hearing
for the chairman of the Financial Services Commission.
With your position on the State Affairs Committee,
I think that should be possible for you.
"Financial Services"?
If you would just do that for me,
I will find a reporter who will publish only what you want.
"A bipartisan (two parties) agreement between the ruling and opposition parties"
"that puts life stability first."
Don't you like the title?
Here's the file you asked for.
Why do you think the patent grants were all under the children's names?
If one wants to pass on their wealth to their children, they would need to pay taxes.
So they set it up so the children could make the money themselves.
It's not teaching them how to fish.
But rather, they are giving them a fish farm full of fish.
People without parents would be so sad.
They believe that's their right.
If they have patents...
They would have a way
without paying a won in taxes.
What are they trying to do after gathering people like this?
Are you crazy?
I should be the one to say that!
You're Project Manager of Deals, yet you go to the airport and break up the deal?
Do you think this is right?
Tell me properly why you did that.
They're nothing but a shell.
How could I make a deal like that? So embarrassing.
Good for you.
You're so smart.
Thanks to Han Seung Jo and Jang Ho Woo, the future of our Taeil Accounting is bright.
Which one is how you really feel?
- Your words or your facial expression?
- Both.
A deep consideration and compromise between professional honor and human greed.
Can't you tell?
I don't want to know.
Since this bus has already passed,
Jang Ho Woo is quite the character.
You know.
Only those like us who have gained some experience think to doubt the financial statement numbers,
examine more and check the sales.
Did we even imagine doing such things as a new staff?
The financial statements were our religion and the truth.
But Jang Ho Woo doesn't get scared.
How is he able to be like that?
He doesn't believe the numbers to start.
An accountant doesn't believe the numbers?
Then what does he believe?
Hey... what is that facial expression?
What are you up to this time?
I like presents,
but I was a bit surprised because it was unexpected.
So could you explain it to me?
Wouldn't the deal need to fall through in order for you
to take the external audit of Jisan Bank?
Even if it's not right this instant.
What would that mean for you?
I also suffered losses.
"Losses"?
From our accounting firm?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You will soon learn about it, too...
V.P. An.
You're saying that person is also a problem for me.
Right?
Probably.
All right.
Then what's next?
The sales deal is over now.
I'm thinking of gathering more people,
like someone else is doing.
This is Deals Department 309.
Mr. Jang Ho Woo.
I heard you went all the way to the airport
to tell Chairman Lee Chan Joo not to buy Cake Bean.
Let's hear your reasons.
Not your thoughts right now,
but your thoughts at that moment.
You probably didn't do that with no conviction.
Right before the contract agreement,
I found out about how the head office of Cake Bean manipulated sales by force.
I determined this would be a decisive factor impacting cash flow.
So?
I thought if Sangah Group found out later that we pushed forward with the deal, despite internal defects,
greater losses and risks would be involved
than to lose this current contract.
So that's why
you stopped this contract deal.
Okay.
Okay. We'll have it like that on the written apology.
All right, then how about you tell me now the real reason
for messing with me?
You told me to sell Cake Bean to Sangah Group,
but you told Chairman Lee Chan Joo not to buy it.
If you didn't think to sabotage both Chairman Lee Chan Joo and me from the start and divide us,
it would mean you were just toying with us.
This is the last time I let you off easy  because I like your talents.
If you naively overstep your bounds again without fear,
I will teach you how cruel a person, who loses
his equanimity and rationality, can become.
Are you threatening me?
Let's say it's a forewarning.
Yes, V.P. Han?
Please remove Mr. Jang Ho Woo from major tasks
starting from his current assignment immediately.
Yes, Sir.
I thought he would get fired, but our V.P. really held himself back.
Is it because he didn't have a legit reason to fire him?
Why do you think company records employees clock in and out?
Being tardy or leaving early isn't a big deal.
It's all so they can use it against you to fire you in the future.
There should be a reason why he's only going this far...
What are you guys doing?
Could I ask you something before I tell you?
Why me?
You could have asked for other things for lending me your name.
So why would you ask that while telling me you will retake Sangah Group?
I heard you weren't on good terms with V.P. Han Je Gyun.
I think that explains everything.
The enemy of my enemy is my ally.
He toyed with a large corporation's head and an accounting firm's V.P.
If we use him well...
What should we do about Chairman Lee Chan Joo?
He probably lost faith in us through this ordeal.
We should give Chairman Lee Chan Joo something he needs.
It appears there was an oversight with regards to the Cake Bean deal.
I will make sure to oversee things carefully in the future
so mistakes like this don't happen again.
We're sorry, Chairman.
Well...
all right.
What are you doing? Come inside.
Honestly, I would be lying if I said I wasn't upset.
Since you've apologized this way, V.P. Han,
and more importantly, thanks to this accountant running all the way to the airport,
I have no ill sentiment against Taeil Accounting.
I met him in front of here.
It was so nice to see him, and I was so grateful.
V.P. Han, you know him, too, right?
Our accountant, Mr. Jang Ho Woo.
Of course, I do.
He's a great asset to our Deals Department
so I have high expectations
for Mr. Jang Ho Woo as well.
All I did was fulfill the calling and duties of an accountant
that you've often emphasized, V.P. Han.
Now that I think about it,
I think you two resemble each other.
Succession of management rights?
The stock prices are at their lowest right now,
and it is great timing for a succession.
We should also take into account Bo Sung's age.
I mean, that's true,
but the atmosphere these days are just...
The bad rumors swirling about Sangah Group can be taken advantage of.
Take advantage of it?
I will explain the details separately in my office in private.
No more being opportunistic.
Make sure to keep in mind what I've told you.
Hey, Lee Seong Joo.
Why are you here?
Well, then I'll await your call.
You rude b*stard! You don't even respond when your older brother asks you a question!
You would ignore me like that?
Gosh, goodness.
Investment is putting it nicely.
It's basically just lending money for interest!
Is Taeil Accounting doing any sort of background checks?
How could they let a loan shark like him in here?
Chairman.
What do you mean, loan shark?
I think in terms of corruption,
I'm nothing compared to you.
What did you say, B*stard?
This b*stard, I'll just...
You're done for, Man!
You should know my relationship with Chairman Lee Seong Joo better than anyone.
I do.
As soon as you placed Lee Chan Joo as Chairman, you had Lee Seong Joo kicked out of his position.
Was it Sangah Mill? The flour factory.
Demoting someone, who graduated abroad with a business management degree, to run a flour factory...
that was going a bit too far.
If you know that so well...
He who hires and doesn't pay is the problem, not those who pay workers.
That's what you've always said, Father.
This rude b*stard! He didn't even respond when I asked him a question!
Yes.
How would I know?
Does he still not understand that the Heavens choose the firstborn by birth?
Should I just get rid of him, or what?
Why won't I be able to? Of course, I can.
You're saying these things without even thinking.
- Get rid of me?
- What the heck? Let go of me!
I was going to run Sangah Group due to an incompetent firstborn.
But you used Han Je Gyun to push me out to a flour factory just as I'd take control!
So how are you any good as the firstborn?
Lee Chan Joo. You're only respected outside as a chaebol family firstborn.
What do you know to do by yourself?
Don't you see your son, who is exactly the same as you, only obtaining his bachelor's degree
thanks to his parents and wasting his family's wealth?
F*** you, you b*stard!
I should have just killed you then.
You little...
Since Han Je Gyun took it all away from me,
Accountant Han Je Gyun will also return what's rightfully mine,
not an incompetent one like you.
That son of a b*tch...
I won't let you get away with this.
Where did he go?
Hey, where's my car?
I asked you where my car is, you f***ing b*stard!
Hang up!
You're dead today, you son of a b*tch!
Gosh, that b*stard.
I won't let you get away with this.
Step on it.
I told you not to stop, and step on it!
Gosh, you son of a b*tch!
Hey, you punk.
Is this what you should be doing right now?
Getting into fights.
What am I supposed to do when they hit me first?
I told you to stand up for yourself, not beat them up!
They started it with Yeo Jin and Hee Sam!
So how many times did you hit them?
Just once.
- How many times did you get hit?
- I got hit once, too.
You should have hit him more.
Yesterday's enemy can become your friend today.
Whatever you guys do, we'll gain anyway
and hold many cards.
Goodness.
A day will come when you'll get in big trouble due to your temper.
Why don't you just curse me?
Why not a shaman ritual while you're at it?
Hey, you think I did that to Jang Ho Woo for myself?
It's because you were so worried about the performance review–
Are you so good at knowing how I feel?
Then I wonder why you did nothing when Mother-in-law was being mean to me.
Are you a selective idiot?
Why would you bring that up again?
I still feel it's unfair that she thinks only her son is an accountant
and endures struggles by himself.
Just wait until I get promoted.
I will move out.
You said we shouldn't leave work in opposite directions since people think we live together.
Oh, Ha Eun. Let's go with Mommy.
Careful.
Come here, my baby.
You got scared?
Acute methanol poisoning?
Yes.
Why would I have something like that?
What about treatment?
I can recover if I do surgery, right?
Right?
I won't go blind or something like that, right?
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Chairman Lee Chan Joo of Sangah Group crashed his car into the car of Chairman Lee Seong Joo of SA Investment,
and the police investigated the incident.
Chairman Lee Seong Joo is the second son of the Sangah Group family,
and it was revealed that he and Chairman Lee Chan Joo fought often over the inheritance.
Here is Reporter Ha Ji Min.
Is this what you call a "War of Brothers"?
They haven't announced their official position on the matter yet.
Currently, Chairman Lee Chan Joo is...
You surprise me every time I see you ever since I came to Korea.
Are you close enough with Chairman Lee Chan Joo that you'd visit him in hospital?
He's my client.
But you're a mere new staff.
What about you then?
It's also because he's my client.
Tell me the reason next time we meet.
I came  just to leave this here.
- Don't drink too much now.
- Wait, no.
What are you stopping me for?
Why would I stay here where the youngsters are partying?
Yeo Jin should be here any minute now.
- Hurry and put this on.
- No–
- There.
- Aigoo, this brat.
- How pretty.
- Aigoo, what is this?
Do you know how wicked a false alarm is?
What a fool. You have no idea it's your birthday tomorrow.
But look at how short-tempered you are.
No one knows what will happen tomorrow.
So how could she know anything about tomorrow?
Grandma...
- Congrats.
- Hey, congrats!
All right. Let's go.
Aigoo, she's so happy.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I like it a lot.
When did you have time to get these?
They're very expensive.
I got advice from Ms. Yeon Ah.
Did Ms. Yeon Ah also choose this for you?
I knew something was going on between you two.
No, she said to give this to Grandma.
What is it?
Wow, hey, this is awesome.
You already have enough supplements.
What good will managing blood sugar levels do for you?
- Please have this.
- I need it, too!
Hey, I-I...
I'm not in a great condition lately.
Always scolding me about food...
-  Mr. Ho Woo!
- Yes.
What's the meaning of this?
That's what I want to ask.
How did you know I needed all those books and files?
I guess I was being needlessly nosy again.
Also, sorry for looking easy again.
Why are you doing this to me, seriously?
I want to help you.
Do I need a reason?
V.P. Han Je Gyun is being too harsh.
I thought better of him.
What did you think of him?
"Noblesse oblige (noble duty),"
every accountant's role model.
Help yourself. It will get soggy.
When you met Chairman Lee Chan Joo, why didn't you ask who's managing HK Private Equity Fund?
You should have just taken a blind shot.
I did.
You did?
Just stay right behind me.
If he has a sense of conscience, V.P. Han shouldn't be able to say anything to me.
Let's go.
Could I ask you for one more favor?
What is it?
Who is A.N., the actual manager of
HK Private Equity Fund?
Why are you curious about that?
Because it's an important matter for me.
It's not like you're going to make me money.
Why ask who the manager is?
Just ask me to sell the country instead.
Even I don't know what my money is doing and where.
If Chairman Lee Chan Joo said that...
it means the money is transferred at the company level.
It also means the fund manager has actual power, not the deep pocket (wealthy).
The person you called A.N. before?
I thought I was almost there.
You still found out something, thanks to Chairman Lee.
And V.P. Han can't harass you anymore because he has to be wary of Chairman Lee.
That's true.
For now, let's dig into Sangah Group's data.
If we look at how the money got put into the fund,
we'll also be able to find a clue about HK Private Equity Fund's manager.
Okay.
(Property, plant, and equipment: physical assets)
Oh, I got that.
Couldn't it have been out of loans from companies abroad?
"Loans"?
I found Sangah Group's subsidiaries frequently trade among themselves,
like paying off a credit card with another.
It is possible, but loans are money that leaves a mark in the books.
So they're hard to be dispensed freely.
They also need to show they have that money during each year's audit.
Be it slush funds or whatever else, I'm sure they sent it overseas.
So let's first check money sent overseas from Sangah Group in the last ten years
that didn't get returned yet.
For a sum large enough to move a private equity fund across borders,
they can't help but leave a trace in the books.
We can save time if we prioritize companies with many fixed assets or foreign stock purchases.
Look into big purchases: foreign real estate, stocks, airplanes, or ships.
Yes.
What's up? Did you find something?
Accountant Han...
Let's first check the bond distribution status of Sangah Group.
We need to first see who has enough to develop a plan to buy their stock.
In the report, I'll include who holds each bond.
What got you all worked up now?
Are you collecting Sangah Group's bonds?
Just leave if you plan to give me another pointless lecture.
There's something you must see.
What's so weird about a shipping company buying a ship?
The process.
"The process"?
Even if we forget they didn't buy during their ordinary ship replacement period,
they especially registered only this ship in Hong Kong.
Sangah Shipping's other ships are all registered in Korea.
People do that to cut costs sometimes.
Long before they purchased that ship,
Sangah Shipping has been using it.
What do you mean?
They were actually using the ship they supposedly bought on a monthly rent basis.
Just like a rental car or a lease.
But one day, they suddenly bought the rental car, no...
- they bought the ship?
- Yes.
Saying they can be trusted since the registration was done abroad.
Though the ship is still floating around and what can be seen hasn't changed at all,
more than 200 billion won was sent to Hong Kong for the purchase of the ship.
So you're saying that money is...
the slush fund Chairman Lee sent to Sangah Group?
It's impossible without the case manager's silent agreement and approval.
It could also be she acted like one body with A.N.
A.N.?
The person who manages HK Private Equity Fund's capital.
But I don't know his full name.
Who's the case manager?
It's V.P. An Seung Yeon.
I was in for nothing.
- Why?
- It's probably an actual purchase,
not a slush fund.
How can you be sure?
There's no reason.
The reason V.P. An would help Sangah Group form its slush fund,
you have only circumstantial evidence.
Moreover, it's HK Private Equity Fund.
She'd never do that.
You also didn't know V.P. Han Je Gyun would do that to Haebit Construction...
causing Ahjussi to pass away like that.
What did you say?
You have no idea what kind of person An Seung Yeon really is.
What do you know anyway?
I know the ship's price is the same amount written on the cash receipt Noona Ji Soo saw in HK Private Equity Fund.
What?
Do you know the saying,
"Profit beats conviction"?
Whom do you think is really the one in the dark?
Mr. Jang Ho Woo.
In France,
this darkness where you can only make out the silhouette,
is called the hour between dog and wolf, I heard.
Because it's vague whether what's coming toward me is
the dog I'm raising or the wolf chasing me.
Which one are you,
Mr. Jang Ho Woo?
Looks like I'm not the dog.
Is it because of Sangah Shipping?
It's probably an actual purchase, not a slush fund.
How can you be sure?
There's no reason.
The reason V.P. An would help Sangah Group form its slush fund,
you have only circumstantial evidence.
Moreover, it's HK Private Equity Fund.
She'd never do that. I know her.
You have no idea what kind of person An Seung Yeon really is.
Just a while back, Sangah Shipping had another expense again,
apparently for insurance expenses.
It might be disappointing,
but Sangah Shipping made a normal ship purchase and no such thing as a slush fund was found.
For the two years I've been the auditor, there were no problems.
I've no interest in whether you made a mistake or not,
nor does it matter.
Why is it that you're obsessed with Sangah Group's slush fund?
That's how I'll be able to approach...
the actual manager of HK Private Equity Fund.
After that?
Since that's where all misfortune and ill fate began...
I'll bite and tear it apart.
I looked into it, but documents such as arrival and departure were flawless.
We can see it in person if it's stationed at a dock.
But it feels like this is a ghost ship.
You said it's hard to see even at docks since it crosses borders.
We need to prove the ship purchase was fake to show
the money used for the purchase was for the slush fund.
That's how we can catch the private equity fund manager.
Mr. Jang Ho Woo, you're not too busy right now, are you?
I'm quite sure V.P. Han told you to take a break.
O-Oh, yes. That's right.
Well, then come outside with us for a minute.
It's because the job will end quicker with more people.
What's the job?
Do you want to come as well, Ms. Yeon Ah?
Let's all take a breather!
"A breather"?
I should have known when they asked if the company had any padded jackets.
All right.
Our new staff somehow ended up together.
A perfect chance to get to know each other.
You can introduce yourselves.
What's all that?
Collaterals.
A savings bank loaned 12 billion won with fishery products as their collateral.
It seems the fishermen colluded and gave overlapping items as collateral.
They also lied about having them in a freezer when they didn't have them.
And to file a damages suit based on faulty collateral, we must find out
the extent of damage and detailed value of remaining collateral.
Wait. Does that mean you want us to investigate all those items individually?
Yes, that's right.
That's why we brought all of you.
Well, Ms. Jin Yeon Ah, I leave our new staff in your hands.
Gosh, it's freezing. Let's go.
Wait, aren't you two doing it with us?
Mr. Woo Sang Hyun and I need to go to the savings bank.
I'll call you later.
Good luck.
Ms. Si Young. Mr. Woo Sang Hyun!
My head was all jumbled up.
So this is actually for the better.
Are you telling me to believe that?
It was clearly here until you printed the list of inventory to hand over to the bank,
but you moved them to another warehouse this morning?
Wait.
If it's a warehouse in Ohsung...
don't we have to go more than 200 km from here?
It's already so late.
You're messing with the wrong person.
Did you expect us to just accept whatever story you throw at us?
You're wrong!
Let's go, everyone.
Let's go to that warehouse and see if they're there or not.
Ms. Yeon Ah, one second, please.
Gosh, let's see.
You moved this much to another warehouse?
A 3.5 ton refrigerated truck loads about 320 to 350 boxes.
You must have called at least 10 trucks for this list.
Your payment receipts for the transport.
What?
Let me see the payment receipts for transport.
Oh, the thing is, well...
Wait, didn't the freight company give you a receipt for your payment?
Those guys need to get the flame from the National Tax Service to wake up.
You know reporting tax evasion comes with rewards, right?
N-No! Wait a second.
Hold on.
All right.
Female and male crabs are all mixed up here.
Those two differ a lot in price.
On the list, you used the high price, which is that of a ripe female crab.
Do they differ in price?
I'm not sure. I don't know, either.
The yield is different too.
You mixed in jumbo and large crabs when they differ in price like this
and used the jumbo crabs' prices.
What are jumbo and large crabs?
You think I'd know?
What do you say?
Should we have the accountants check the inventory in the other warehouse
while I check the prices of all the items in these boxes?
- Or else...
- N-No, no.
It was my mistake.
Your car's not one of the fastest ones today.
We're on our way to work so what's the hurry?
You were awesome earlier.
We would have wasted so much time if not for you.
How do you know all that stuff?
It's hard for a restaurant owner's grandson not to know all that.
Still, I didn't think you'd catch false inventory by the lack of payment receipt for shipping.
Moving assets and people require money.
True. They say affairs are caught using toll expenses.
CFS charges? (Container Freight Station loading)
Even when you buy a ship and arrive at a dock,
you'd have to pay CFS charges, right?
That's probably the case.
Please pull over.
Thank you.
Mr. Ho Woo!
Mr. Jang Ho Woo, what kind of rude–
I thought my explanation was sufficient for you to understand.
What is this?
If Sangah Shipping really purchased a ship in Hong Kong as you said,
they had to report it
as imported goods to the customs.
But you didn't do so, V.P. An,
since there was no need...
or a means to do so.
Which is because
that ship wasn't purchased but borrowed
from the very start.
- Mr. Jang Ho Woo...
- The 200 billion won slush fund
you sent to HK Private Equity Fund, didn't you?
- I...
- A.N.!
Will you...
Will you still deny the fact that you're HK Private Equity Fund's...
fund manager?
Sure.
The ship...
It's true that it wasn't purchased.
It's also true that I formed...
a 200 billion won slush fund.
However, I'm not the person you're seeking.
If I was,  how would you explain the recent transfer of funds out of Sangah Shipping?
I no longer have any relation to Sangah.
- Then why did the 200 billion won...
- That is...
You said an accountant also takes responsibility for the process, not just the result!
What's the meaning of all this?
I said I'll come down to you.
Mr. Jang Ho Woo, let's discuss the rest later–
Why isn't she coming?
Hey, what's the matter?
I'll...
bring you the evidence.
You two can...
talk about the rest.
It seems, we'll have to watch today's performance on a different date, right?
So who is it? This person called A.N.
I've got nothing to tell you,
Han Seung Jo.
However, I'm not the person you're seeking.
If I was, how would you explain the recent transfer of funds out of Sangah Shipping?
I no longer have any relation to Sangah.
The best end to a stressful day is a can of beer.
How did you get this in here?
Hurry and drink it.
Come on.
Are you allowed to leave these at work?
Isn't it against the rules?
I'll gladly get fired if I get caught. It's their loss.
It's like a first aid kit.
Some days you need bandages, and
there are days when you need to let go.
Each symptom calls for a different treatment.
Many other things are in my locker besides this.
What about when you want to just drop everything because you're overwhelmed?
When it feels you're walking in circles.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
No.
This is an old case.
Refer to the contents of this document...
and find out who has each patent type owned by HK Private Equity Fund.
By MRG,
the government will guarantee a minimum revenue for private investors,
when they're constructing stuff like roads and railroads?
Yes, since they're doing the government's work for them.
They're allowed to collect tolls, and the rest is covered with tax money.
And the lower the percentage,
the better it is for our client.
Of course, since our client is the government.
That's how the tolls will be cheaper for people,
and there will be less burden on taxes.
Why? Is something wrong?
Why is the arrow going up, not down?
That's weird.
Just like what you said...
if I really was AN,
wouldn't I have developed a long-lasting, secretive income system, using the immense power
of Taeil Accounting, instead of purchasing a ship?
Ever so strangely, people are able to
take on losses
if they're cut into many small parts.
I don't know which fund it is, but they must have collected big tax money.
It's a 30-year contract so they're probably still collecting.
Gosh, this is infuriating.
Who the heck made such a horrendous mistake?
It wasn't a mistake,
since the private investor must be HK Private Equity Fund.
How did you know that?
Blue.
Yes.
Because we're hit with recession and higher interest rates,
there will be tons of businesses in financial crisis
for sale in the market.
It wasn't A.N.
It was Han.
Should HK Private Equity Fund ever miss a great opportunity
like this one?
Han Je Gyun.
♫  Please tell me why, find out the truth you wanted  ♫
♫  Find again the dreams that you've forgotten  ♫
♫  Focus your mind, see deep inside  ♫
♫  I will call out in the midst of it for all to see  ♫
Now both need to risk everything to stop Han Je Gyun.
Is Han Seung Jo helping as well?
Don't let them know that we know.
I believe you owe me something, A.N.
Are you threatening me?
You should stop now. I'll stop him this time.
I believe Accountant Han Seung Jo is different.
You know there's something between the two.
I will consider this as my payment for using your name.
There's a limit to patience.
Mandate is what we make, isn't it?
Could you burn one more bad inventory?
Which one?
Nothing is more definite than burning the whole thing down.
♫  I will show you from now on  ♫
♫  Please tell me why  ♫