Director Shim Hyung Woo!
- Director Shim Hyung Woo!
- Jang Ho Woo!
Here! Hurry!
Here! Jang Ho Woo!
Hey, you b*stard!
Mr. Yang!
Help Yang Jae Hwan first.
What is this? What about Shim Hyung Woo?
He's inside the warehouse.
We found him.
How does this make any sense, Sunbae?
I've seen all sorts of things while working at Taeil for 10 years
so I thought nothing would surprise me now.
How could a person die?
Hey, Han Seung Jo. Say something.
How can someone die like this?
And what about you, Mr. Jang Ho Woo?
You know something, right?
- Why aren't you saying anything?
- Sung Min...
You saw him a few days ago, too, Sunbae.
Something was definitely up with Shim Hyung Woo!
I should have forced him to tell me then
and stopped him...
I'm sorry.
Why is it for you to be sorry about?
But...
think about it.
You guys could have died on the site.
All the accountants here could be
over there instead of Shim Hyung Woo.
Still many accountants don't care that a colleague died
because they're so focused on their own performance.
See how many colleagues didn't even show up.
No matter how much we try to find out,
it will be buried away quickly.
Ms. Hye Won, you should go to Mr. Jae Hwan now.
He's probably in the hospital by himself.
I'll go in a bit.
I just feel so sorry.
No, you should go right now.
I'll walk you to the front.
- Hello.
- Great work.
- You guys are going through a lot.
- Thank you.
It appears V.P. Han Je Gyun is coming.
It's about time.
- And he even brought his minions with him.
- Pardon?
The people from Taeil Scholarship Association. Don't you know?
Quite a few accountants in our firm are from there.
Some are in Financial Services Commission, Ministry of Economy and Finance, and the media.
Taeil Accounting paid for their scholarships.
It's funny how they're only loyal to V.P. Han Je Gyun.
Who... is that?
Here!
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Only burn the warehouse.
Leave this behind.
- The order was...
- I'll take care of it so do as I say.
There wasn't anything special, but we got the laptop.
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry about what happened during the Special Shareholders Meeting.
If you wait for the right time as the second major shareholder
of Sangah Group, I will–
If it was undercover, maybe.
But it's too boring to wait without doing anything.
What are you planning?
A plan?
Will a plan be needed for the idiotic father and son,
Lee Chan Joo and Lee Bo Sung?
The customer is not answering the phone. You'll be connected to voicemail.
Is he really busy?
Is it a date?
Unfortunately, not yet.
Who is it?
You should tell me now and confess.
Not yet, I'll tell you later.
Aigoo, goodness.
What I know for sure is he's very capable and righteous.
What?
"R-Righteous"?
Isn't being good at his work enough? He also has to be righteous?
Wow, my daughter, you've got high standards.
By chance, is he the love
that involved that request before?
Yes.
I like this one.
Isn't this one too tacky?
This looks a lot more righteous.
Come on, Dad.
It wouldn't be good if you're righteous but look tacky.
Well, then how about you just give up on righteousness?
Geez.
Hey, Jang Ho Woo.
I realize you're not feeling well, but get up for a sec.
What time is it?
You're dating, right?
"Ho Woo, can I see you before you come into work?"
"I have something I want to ask you."
"I just miss you!"
What is this? When did you guys start?
The losses of this online loan company are significant.
It's like a time bomb.
I was told you don't need to worry about those companies.
He said Taeil Accounting will take care of that.
HK Private Equity Fund's Han Je Gyun
is commissioning Taeil Accounting's Han Je Gyun, I see...
What is he trying to do with this?
When I came in today,
I saw that the vibe of the firm is definitely different.
I'm sorry about what happened with Accountant Shim Hyung Woo.
Oh, yes. I think it's a shame as well.
This is a P2P online loan company
that HK Private Equity Fund is selling.
I thought that Jisan Bank would be the best business partner to sell it to.
Thank you for your kind words,
but will Jisan Bank need an online loan company?
I don't know about that.
Well, won't you need it, President Jin?
Your term is coming to a close soon
so another major accomplishment would make it easier for you to extend your presidency.
There's no better accomplishment than raising the stock prices.
"Stock prices."
Even if the business profits stay the same, if you own an IT company,
you can promote your bank as the next generation of financial technology,
have a higher performance, and your stock prices will quickly rise.
Why don't you wrap up and take home this good opportunity?
Do an M and A of an online loan company
and raise the bank's stock price...
Has our Taeil Accounting ever let you down?
Ms. Yeon Ah.
Mr. Ho Woo.
Well...
I...
Do you know you and I share something in common, Ms. Yeon Ah?
"Something in common"?
Our situations are different, but we both
can't hide in the safety of being average.
Ms. Yeon Ah, our company's biggest client,
Jisan Bank President, Jin Tae Soo's daughter.
And I am the son of someone
whose whereabouts are unknown.
I was going to tell you first, Mr. Ho Woo,
but I was scared.
We had just started getting close,
and I worried we might grow apart again.
It doesn't matter to me
who you are, Ms. Yeon Ah.
Then...
you're not going to distance me, right?
I won't distance you,
not even one step.
I'll make sure to guarantee
Accountant Son Hye Won's career.
And you'll receive compensation for work-related damages.
I will...
gratefully accept your offer, V.P.
- But...
- "But"?
I want to keep working
at Taeil as long as I can see.
Are you thinking of reporting it to the police?
To tell them to punish V.P. Han Je Gyun since he tried to kill someone?
You think I can't? I am a living witness to it.
You know better than anyone that you can't go against him like that.
Do I just sit still and do nothing?
If he steps on me, just take it.
If he kills me, then just die?
No.
You should go to work.
Jang Ho Woo... What is this?
Beside this guy who is nothing, I...
Gosh.
"Jang In Ho"?
The Jang In Ho of Haebit Construction from way back when?
This is suddenly getting interesting.
Let's raise our glasses!
Cheers!
Congrats.
If you've gained management rights in the succession process,
you should have many Sangah Group shares in your name, 4%?
What's the point? I've on such a short leash.
It's better than being an accountant and salaryman like me.
I had to buy stocks with a stock-backed loan so it's hard enough to pay interest.
Then how about you switch to a place with low interest?
You would have 2% less interest if you go through me.
Two percent?
So many people around me saved money through lower interest like that.
Why mention this just now?
I was going to open it anyway.
I guess he liked basketball shoes.
You know the dream of guys
to buy all these things to feel successful in life.
What is it?
Someone searched Shim Hyung Woo's office. His laptop has disappeared.
Do you think V.P. Han Je Gyun ordered it?
How are things going with the inspection of the online loan company?
If we want Jisan Bank to desire it,
it seems we'll have to pay extra attention.
Yes.
It appears to be the orders of V.P. Han Je Gyun.
I took a glance at the meeting files in the copying room,
and it seemed to be a Jisan Bank case.
"Jisan Bank"?
Hyung Woo came to see me not long before he died.
He said he lived diligently,
but that he's lived wrong.
I forgot about it from the shock of sending Hyung Woo off like that.
I finally looked at it yesterday,
and I thought you guys should see it, too.
"People's Entertainment"?
The plan strategized to suck the goods out of People's Ent.
Then all the companies here...
They're all companies that ended up bankrupt after V.P. Han Je Gyun used them.
Just like Haebit Construction, Shim Hyung Woo likely handled them all.
So this is a record of Han Je Gyun's wrongs.
Proving this would be another story,
but based on the circumstances, it's correct.
But...
would he have sent this to only you?
How many people did they bribe?
"National Forensic Service"?
Why would Han Je Gyun get involved with National Forensic Service?
Find someone for me.
Hwang In Beom.
The files are all ready.
Let's take a look.
Is it 120%?
If my stock price reaches the minimum limit,
my stocks could be taken; I'd be forced to sell to save money.
How could Sangah Group's stock prices drop below minimum and force you to sell?
Maybe I should ask my dad.
I heard your chairman is overseas on business.
I'm an accountant at Taeil Accounting.
So?
It means even our old fogey approved my smarts.
You dare fearlessly harass a minor?
- You don't fear public authority, do you?
- "Harass"?
I don't even remember it!
I don't even know who she is!
Drink, drink!
Cheers.
Are you okay?
Drink, drink.
Cheers.
Exactly.
Technology needs to advance quickly so we can scan your brain, and you'll shut up.
Call my dad!
Is this a school that I call your dad for you?
Come here! Come here, you b*stard!
Darn it, you b*stard!
Dang it! Hey!
Did anyone ask you to bring in money?
All I asked was for you to do nothing! Is that so hard?
How could you cause trouble like this and create this mess?
All due to you, it appears our stock prices will be cut in half!
Dad. This is really unfair!
You know my friend, Gyeong Il, right?
- He works at Taeil Accounting and–
- You b*stard!
This is a criminal case!
There's a limit to what I can do to get you out!
You b*stard! It's not like I can just kill you, geez!
But Dad,
there's one more thing.
You didn't... Did she get pregnant?
Geez, that'd be awful!
Actually, I...
changed my stock-collateral loan...
B-But?
Because our stocks dropped,
I ended up getting liquidated.
You...
Are you saying you got... all of those stocks taken away?
Dad, just give me one more chance.
I will really do well from now on.
I really wanted to do well this time.
Hey, you b*stard!
You b*stard!
Do you know how I amassed those stocks?
That was like my blood!
And of all situations, why now?
No. No, no, no, no!
No. J-J-Jang Ho Woo, Jang Ho Woo.
I need to call Jang Ho Woo.
Aigoo, my nephew.
I wondered when you would grow up and act like a human being,
but you gave me such a great gift!
Hey, I'm not in the mood to play with you right now. Just leave.
I told you to leave!
I guess your stocks got forcibly sold so you're busy trying to deal with that situation?
How did you know that?
You b*stard! No way...
He is Mr. Choi Gyeong Il of the audit team.
He's very close to Bo Sung.
Say hello.
All you have to do is encourage Bo Sung
to change his stock-collateral loan while Chairman Lee Chan Joo is away on a business trip.
Yes, Sir.
You should know that you're benefiting due to me.
Okay, I got it.
Those stocks would have been liquidated anyway if it weren't for your son.
Who are you?
Since your son, who does no proper work or economic activity,
bought all those stocks with money that had unclear sources,
the financial authorities can order a liquidation for illegal acquisition.
- You think that's easy to do?
- It's not easy.
However, it's not difficult for our accounting firm.
Even if you hold a shareholders' meeting again and appeal, you'll clearly lose to me.
So don't make more work for yourself.
Just exit on your own while I'm offering you generous severance pay.
Lee Seong Joo...
Lee Seong Joo, you b*stard!
You son of a b*tch!
How could you do that to Bo Sung, who knows nothing?
That's what I mean!
Would it be good for you guys, who don't know anything, to act as Chairman? Darn it!
Thanks to your stupid son, I became the major shareholder
so should I thank him?
Hey, I'm Lee Chan Joo.
Lee Chan Joo!
You think I'll come to an end like this?
Of course, it shouldn't end like this.
I'm Prosecutor Lee Soo Young of the Economic Crime Investigation Dept. of Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office.
Lee Chan Joo, you are under arrest for aggravated specific economic crimes,
since there is the risk of destruction of evidence or fleeing.
What... what did I do wrong?
Wrongful subsidizing of affiliates,
internal transactions, manipulation of stock prices,
embezzlement, breach of trust, and tax evasion.
Lee Seong Joo, you b*stard!
You can't get away with this!
I see you quite often these days.
Dad! Hey!
You've regained your position,
and everything is done now.
There's still...
one more interesting thing.
Hey, Kong Hee Sam, don't you hear that?
You go get it.
You should hurry and go.
- You should go!
- It's your house!
You should go!
You can't even face off against me.
Go.
Hey, Ho Woo.
Jang Ho Woo.
I'm not expecting anything at home...
- What is that?
- Hey.
That...
looks like a card key.
Hey, maybe it's something like a safe key.
You sure it's not like an act of terrorism where it explodes if you open it?
What an imagination for one who deals mostly with drunks.
Excuse me, could you check the CCTV to see who sent this?
Oh, that would be difficult.
The CCTVs are off-limits as per company rules.
I really need it. If I had any other way, I wouldn't be doing this.
Here, the person who sent this is dead.
- I just need to find out who sent it–
- I told you it's not possible!
Please leave before I call the police.
Hello.
I'm Officer Song Yeo Jin from Dongin Police Station.
I know it's a hassle for you, but can I take a look at your CCTV?
Which overseas destination would take about a week for a package sent from Korea to be returned?
"To be returned"? Not sent?
Yes, so it would return due to an unidentified recipient.
The recipient's name is Jang Ho Woo.
I'll report to you after it's burnt completely.
I think he earned some time by using returns on international shipping.
He probably knew better than anyone that V.P. Han would order someone to rummage through his stuff.
I think it's a card key.
Would it be for the rental safe at a bank?
Probably not.
If he had borrowed a safe from a bank on credit...
there's no way V.P. Han wouldn't know about it.
He'd have searched for it and his home first thing.
Why did Director Shim Hyung Woo give me a riddle like this?
He could've just sent the data over.
While he wanted you to find it, don't you think...
he also didn't want you to find it?
Either way, he probably wanted you to understand his actions.
Since that's what comes first to find the answer.
It was arson, not an accident?
It seems Shim Hyung Woo expected it.
A few days before the incident, he handed info about V.P. Han to Sunbae Kang Hyun.
To me, too.
Taeil Scholarship Association... Politicians, prosecutors, and police.
He's got all sorts of people, right?
"National Forensic Service"?
I'm also looking into him because it's odd.
What you ordered for Ilseong Baby Formula, my father-in-law's company–
Mr. Yang Jae Hwan...
Mr. Yang Jae Hwan seems to be quite mistaken about something.
I've never given orders before.
All I've done was give appropriate opinions.
All of this is...
The one who heard my opinion and acted
was by all means done of your own accord.
Mr. Yang, aren't you an expert?
V.P. Han.
- That's an inappropriate–
- Mr. Yang.
Have you ever seen an ambulance keep the speed limit?
He lacks flexibility.
Whether they're my guys or not,
no one knows to keep a secret.
Director Shim Hyung Woo.
Yes, V.P. Han.
While burning those, could you burn one more bad inventory?
You *sshole!
Will you be able to handle it?
Yes.
The cabinet Shim Hyung Woo used when he was a new staff?
You're saying it was right under our noses.
Since no one cares about a new staff's cabinet,
his cabinet number was 23.
So he couldn't help but do those things for success?
What the heck is in there anyway?
We fabricated the ledger by importing raw materials from overseas and increasing inventory prices.
If we cover up with a warehouse fire, there should be no problem.
Nothing is more definite than burning the whole thing down.
While you're burning those, could you burn one more bad inventory?
Which one...
I'll promise you a partner position once you take care of it.
The decision is up to you.
Very slowly, take your time to think over my offer.
Get out!
Ahjussi?
I stand before the gates of hell numerous times, even in one day.
You think I wouldn't have prepared for the worst?
"A stab wound"?
"A knife"?
Why would it be there?
Are you Dr. Hwang In Beom, who used to work at NFS?
Who are you?
I have some questions for you.
Is that so?
Are you saying you fabricated the autopsy report for money...
when it was a murder and not a suicide?
Rather than for the money...
I did it out of fear.
I guess you don't fear Han Je Gyun anymore, right?
The fact that I didn't recognize the one...
who did that to Ahjussi when he was right next to me...
I only resented him for leaving me behind alone.
He's the one who must bow his head to Ahjussi.
I'm going to make him beg.
Who are you?
Have you gone crazy? Are you insane?
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
I don't think you should stay here.
This might happen again.
- There's something I must tell you.
- Save it for later.
I have to tell you right now–
Even to Noona Ji Soo's hotel now?
We can't leave Ji Soo alone like that.
I don't think you'll make her safe just by going to V.P. Han right now.
I must do whatever I can.
What were you going to tell me?
Come in.
V.P. Han knows something regarding the Jisan Bank matter...
but you can't really tell what he knows?
Even if I ask my dad, he says it's nothing.
I wouldn't be this worried if I could at least know what it's about.
It's a business where they sell online lending companies to Jisan Bank.
Pardon?
You checked the work Mr. Woo's assigned to... right now on his time report?
Because it's the fastest, most accurate way.
But why would they have to be so discreet about selling online lending companies to Jisan Bank?
They wouldn't be if it was a normal deal.
And they wouldn't have told only Jisan Bank to be the buyer.
Would there be a real reason... why they have to sell those goods to Jisan Bank
without people knowing?
Hee Sam, lend me a hand.
Help yourself.
Stop looking. You'll give me indigestion.
Unnie, you know I'm the police, right?
My house is the safest.
Well, Noona, I also have a free room in my house...
although it's not as nice as a hotel.
Why go to a hotel when she has a home?
Have you got money rotting away?
Grandma, that's not the point here.
- There was an intruder–
- I'm sure she will see to it herself.
Everyone, just stay put.
Anyhow... I'm also against you staying in a hotel.
What's the use even if we know V.P. Han's plan?
Without his approval, we can do nothing.
Since he's the Deals Department leader,
we lack a reason to ask to hand over info irrelevant to our work.
So we just sit and watch like this?
Is there no other way?
Competitive bidding?
Oh, I forgot about that. Competitive bidding.
By competitive bidding, you mean...
We'll bring someone other than Jisan Bank who wants to buy online lending companies... on paper.
In that case, V.P. Han wouldn't have a reason to stop us.
Since it's official participation.
To V.P. Han, who wants to sell it to Jisan Bank...
having another buyer appear will be confusing.
Because some random person might buy them instead.
However, we can't celebrate just yet.
Because we need to find a company to hire us to enter the bid. That's our homework.
That homework of yours...
I'll help you out.
Sunbae!
What about you? Are you okay, Hyung?
I'm sure your company doesn't really plan to buy an online lending company.
You'll be paying quite a sum to Taeil for hiring us.
I also feel the same way you guys do.
Coming here reminds me of Hyung Woo.
We can't lose anyone else.
That shouldn't happen.
To prevent it, we must stop...
V.P. Han so he can't cross the line anymore.
"Financial Services Commission"?
What can Han Je Gyun do with them?
Regarding the insolvency (failure) of this P2P lending company...
let's just leave them as they are.
No need to bother to solve this one.
Yes, I understand.
It'll be marked as unnoticed on our end.
I think you need to come and see this.
Han Seung Jo, if you sold this without knowing, Jisan Bank would have a mountain of debt overnight.
There's a mountain of debt, but they switched out the papers.
They hid the problem by using a program where they loan the amount of interest
the borrowers fail to pay on time.
What does that mean?
As time passes, debts Jisan Bank needs to repay in the
online lending company's stead will arise left and right... just like a time bomb.
Cornering Jisan Bank on purpose?
For what? What does V.P. Han gain from doing that?
What are you talking about?
Is Han Je Gyun cornering Jisan Bank on purpose?
If loan failures happen so suddenly like this...
there will be issues with the BIS rate.
"BIS"?
If something goes wrong with that, it means the bank will falter.
What does decreasing BIS rates and...
Financial Services Commission have to do with each other?
"Financial Services Commission"?
How do you know that, Jang Ho Woo?
Han Je Gyun is colluding with the Financial Services Commission.
"Financial Services Commission"?
Aren't they the people HK Private Equity Fund invited to join their side by handing out patent certificates?
Yes, you're right.
What is it?
What can Han Je Gyun do by making the Financial Services Commission follow his orders?
What is Han Je Gyun trying to do?
The banks...
Yes, it's the banks.
V.P. Han was after Jisan Bank in the first place.
Is he after the bank?
It's on a different scale from taking over a company.
It's a lot more dangerous for an unqualified individual to take over a bank.
If he wants to, he'll start drawing blood out of individuals and companies alike.
Once that starts...
he can adjust the books as he pleases.
Once that happens...
it's only a matter of time before V.P. Han starts...
meddling with the national economy.
If Jisan Bank purchased that online lending company without even knowing these inner workings...
How fortunate are we to have realized it now?
Dad... are you listening to me?
Yes, yes.
I heard you.
I'm at a meeting offsite right now.
Yes, yes.
I'm sorry about this.
According to our analysis...
the online lending company's status is very good.
I wasn't going to bother telling you.
But I thought you should know...
about the person we must fight in the end.
I stand before the gates of hell numerous times, even in one day.
You think I wouldn't have prepared for the worst?
Yes.
Shim Hyung Woo killed CEO Jang In Ho of Haebit Construction
and Han Je Gyun ordered it.
Does Ji Soo know this, too?
Yes.
I had so many thoughts about what I should say to you.
But I couldn't really think of anything.
Though I can't...
ever express it with these words...
I'm really sorry.
It's not your fault.
Having such a father is my fault.
I hope you won't act rashly.
You know your father.
I'm busy right now. Let's talk next time.
There won't be a "next time." Come take a seat.
Sure. What's the matter?
Let me ask you this one thing for the first and last time.
Is that position...
really that important for you, Dad?
Enough to take away someone's life?
What are you trying to say?
Dad, I'm asking if being the chairman of Taeil Accounting and owning Jisan Bank
hold enough value to you that it's worth killing people.
Of course not.
What proof do you have that it was me?
I'm quite sure you heard it, too.
The police's announcement on the fire at the warehouse.
Do I look like I'm doing all of this out of greed...
just so I can make a fortune for myself?
That seat you just mentioned...
I'm going to seat you there after me, no matter what.
And when I become the chairman, you'll again
take that seat after me. I'm sure you know all this.
Did I ever say I wanted it?
Ever since I was young, I was always...
thinking in front of your room's door that you closed on me.
What on Earth could he be thinking in there?
An ordinary life...
Do you even know what it looks like?
You eat together at mealtimes, and
you ask me if I'm sick or having a hard time with anything,
consoling each other with a word.
A family is like that.
Have you ever thought about these things, even just once?
You've never done any of that, Dad.
If I'm sick anywhere, taking my medicine or not...
whether I want to live or die...
and how much pain I'm in...
I fully understand what you mean. However...
Mr. Han Seung Jo...
I'm sure you're too old to be a baby now.
What conversation could I have with a man who calls that childish?
But it doesn't matter anymore,
since I can no longer live as a murderer's son.
You'd better watch out.
Did you know? The greatest fortune in your life...
is that you're my son.
And the worst misfortune in my life...
is again that you're my son.
I lived my whole life at its worst.
Your son, Han Seung Jo, is no more.
Dad said... I mean...
Jisan Bank apparently purchased the online lending company.
What do we do now about Jisan Bank?
Wait, why?
Calm down for now.
Where is Jang Ho Woo right now?
I thought you weren't too fond of me due to what happened at the last stockholders' meeting.
That's right.
However... it's as you can see.
Why did you ask for me?
Because I like competent people.
Want to hear an interesting story?
Of course, you'd want to stay at Taeil Accounting to get back at Han Je Gyun.
Because the dead CEO, Jang In Ho of Haebit Construction, was your father figure.
What about this then?
What if your birth parents were also killed by Han Je Gyun?
What kind of nonsense is that?
I told you before. I like an interesting story.
Let me tell you how your birth parents died.
Cut your bullsh*t.
How the heck do you know...
my parents, whom I don't even know?
♫  I still hope you're coming  ♫
♫  I still hope you're coming home  ♫
♫  Can hide away, at the end of my tears  ♫
-  Hey. Will you apologize?
-  Have you two seen Mr. Ho Woo?
You'd surpass your dad if I waited a little longer?
I can't wait very long.
Are you planning to quit work?
Forget your emotions right now and face reality.
When people can't trust a bank...
what do you think their first action will be?
I told you not to buy it. I said the deal seemed off.
-  Have you been well?
- What made you decide to return?
I must find out everything Han Je Gyun owns and how much.
How daring of you, not knowing your place.
So only I can take you down.
If it's the president who's above the vice president...
I think you were looking for me.