[English subtitles are available]
[Bazaar Beloved Birds]
[Episode 1]
This person is Yu Zhao,
the only son of the Yu family.
He is also the manager of Huixian Restaurant.
and has gained great prominence in Xianyun City.
Objectively speaking, he can be considered talented and good-looking.
Moreover, he often puts on airs and graces.
Many young ladies in the city
wish to marry him.
If they could really marry him, it would be great.
He wouldn't have to pester me then.
I'm not bragging.
Being pursued by him is not a good thing.
Besides, that day is getting closer.
What should I do?
What's wrong with you?
Today it's your turn to treat, and you're sighing.
Are you reluctant to spend money?
Let's go over there and drink.
Let's go.
Come on, Miss.
Let's raise our glasses together,
to Miss Xixi.
Thanks for treating us.
Xixi.
How has
your manager Yu been lately?
Is it time for him to get married?
What are you talking about?
Manager Yu? Getting married?
Why are you asking about this?
Tell me the truth.
What's going on? Something is wrong.
Nothing.
I'm not feeling well.
-Miss.
-Xixi.
Miss, don't go.
It's Manager Yu!
Speak of the devil.
Young... Young Master.
Marvelous! Manager Yu!
No, I have to go.
No.
-You can’t leave.
-Let me go!
Let me go!
Manager.
Uncle San.
Where is Xixi?
She is in the pavilion upstairs.
Let me go!
No!
Li Yun, let go of me!
He’s coming up. Let me go!
Let me go!
Go!
Miss...
Come on, let's drink.
Drink up. Pretend nothing happened.
Hurry up.
Young Master, please have a seat.
You're here. Join us and eat together.
Did you forget something?
What did I forget?
Tomorrow is the wedding.
Wedding?
-Wedding? -Wedding?
What's going on? Are't they siblings?
Yes. What's going on?
Ladies and gentlemen,
everyone here is a good friend of Xixi.
I have an announcement to make.
Before my mother passed away, she arranged for Xixi to be engaged to me.
Tomorrow,
I hope you all can join us for our wedding ceremony.
What?
Yu Zhao, what are you doing?
I've already helped you throw away your garbage.
That's my hobby.
Just find a new hobby.
Are you crazy?
Beyond cure.
You...
Yu Zhao.
Stop!
By the way.
This is for you.
I...
Isn't this the jade pendant that Young Master has always treasured?
How did you know?
Last time when Xiang was cleaning Young Master's room,
she happened to see it.
Young Master was holding the jade pendant, lost in thought.
As soon as he saw me coming in,
he immediately hid it.
So Xiang remembers it very clearly.
Miss.
Young Master is really good to you.
I...
Give it to me.
Miss.
This jade pendant looks quite expensive.
Why waste money?
I'm asking you a serious question.
Aren't you and that Yu Zhao siblings?
How can you get married?
Let's talk over there.
Let's go.
What's going on? Tell me.
Miss.
This...
is a long story.
[Yu Mansion]
[A decade or so ago]
In childhood, he came riding a bamboo horse,
playing with green plums around the bed.
I've known Yu Zhao since we were little.
You could say we were childhood sweethearts.
Back then, my mother didn't allow me to leave the mansion much.
But luckily, I could climb the mansion walls
to take a peek outside.
Everything outside deeply attracted me.
However, every time I tried,
Yu Zhao would always find a way to block me.
What are you doing?
Go back to study.
You're so annoying!
My mother also didn't like me
tinkering with mechanical balls and such.
Whenever I picked up a mechanical ball,
Yu Zhao would bring mother to interrupt me.
Afterward,
there would be a sycophantic smile on his face.
Fortunately,
not long after, he was sent by mother to various branches
for inspection and training.
Young Master.
The day he left,
I thought I would be happy.
But in reality,
there was a strange feeling in my heart,
definitely not joy.
But finally, I had peace.
Then, 8 years later,
during the general meeting of all branches of Huixian Restaurant,
Yu Zhao returned to Yu Mansion.
At that time, I didn't know
this person was my nightmare, Yu Zhao.
I was even captivated by him.
I must have been blind.
And so, 2 more years passed.
My mother fell ill with a strange disease
and was going to pass on soon.
It was at that time
that he appeared in front of me again.
My heart raced when I saw him.
But mother quickly dealt me a heavy blow.
Xixi, look at him.
He is Yu Zhao.
When I heard that the person
I had been infatuated with for two years was Yu Zhao,
I was devastated.
What?
That's impossible!
Mother, mother! Mother!
Mother.
Xixi.
You're not my biological child.
I found you and adopted you.
What happened?
It's not...
Mother!
I'm dying.
After I die,
you two
should get married.
Mother!
What exactly happened?
Stop.
There is too much information.
So you're not your mother's daughter.
You're your mother's...
daughter-in-law?
That's not wrong.
Didn't Her Ladyship pass away 3 years ago?
Why now...
Yu Zhao said
he has to mourn for her mother for 3 years.
In fact, it's just another way to torment me for 3 more years.
You have no idea how I've endured these past 3 years.
Today is the first day after the mourning period ended.
It's so annoying.
This Yu Zhao,
he actually dared to throw away my things.
He seemed strange today.
He even gave me a jade pendant.
Something must have gone wrong.
There must be a trap.
There isn't.
Who is it?
Miss, it's me.
What happened?
Young Master asked me to check on you.
He told you to go to bed early.
-Then the wedding will…
-Got it. He's so annoying.
This ball, I don't know why,
has been with me since I was little.
But I've never opened it.
[Xiao]
[Yu Mansion]
Thank you.
Young Master.
Young Master!
How is it?
Is Xixi ready?
The auspicious moment is approaching.
Young Master,
I've called Miss several times.
But she's been standing still in the room.
I haven't dared to call her again.
-After all, Miss…
-No.
I'm not a puppet
to be manipulated at will.
There's no need to look for me.
Anyway, you won't find me.
But don't worry.
Once the auspicious moment passes, I will come back.
Wonderful! The feeling of freedom is amazing.
From now on, the sky is high and the birds can fly,
the sea is vast and the fish can leap.
But where should I begin with all of this?
Good.
Why do I feel
it looks so much like Yu Zhao?
Everything was ready.
The next step was disguise.
The uniform of the Yu Mansion's servants
was the best disguise.
Perfect.
Then, the most crucial step:
escape.
The backyard was the most challenging step
because Jin Gang would be there.
Jin Gang is Yu Zhao's loyal dog,
and he's cautious.
Whether I could get past him
might require some luck.
Brother Jin Gang, where should I put this batch of goods?
Inside, that room.
Obviously,
I was very lucky.
Then, I just needed to improvise freely.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
The feeling of freedom is really nice.
As for this marriage, whoever wants to get married, go ahead.
Seriously.
Uncle San.
What happened?
Miss ran away from the wedding.
What should we do?
The guests have all arrived.
And the auspicious moment is approaching.
If the wedding cannot take place,
our Yu Mansion
will become the biggest joke in the world.
We still have time.
No big deal.
Young Master will soon bring Yu Xixi back.
Who gave you such confidence?
The key lies
in the jade pendant Young Master gave to Yu Xixi.
The jade pendant?
Yes.
For that jade pendant,
Young Master used four kinds of spices:
chicken tongue incense, tangerine peel, mugwort,
and Suhe incense to smoke it for 49 days.
The scents of these spices
have deeply permeated the jade pendant.
That Wealth that Young Master trained
is very familiar with this scent.
So, as long as Yu Xixi is wearing that jade pendant,
Wealth can follow the scent.
and find her.
Young Master is indeed Young Master.
Of course.
Young Master even gave a special name to this jade pendant.
What is the name?
It's called GPS.
-Impressive!
-Let's wait and see.
Young Master, come back with me.
If Master finds out,
you'll inevitably face punishment.
I'll just play for a few days.
I'll go back before he comes out of seclusion.
Don't worry. No one will know.
It's so hot wearing this.
You mustn't.
The martial world is treacherous.
After all, you are the son of the Sword Master.
If there's any danger...
Who in the martial world still recognizes the Sword Master?
Mo,
isn't it hot wearing this?
Take it off.
It's better to be careful.
Okay.
Mo, give me some money.
What do you want it for?
For ordering things.
Don't be fooled by the quietness here.
The sliced lamb here
is famously delicious.
We should definitely give it a try.
I...
have no money.
Mo, you're good at everything
except for lying.
Young Master,
you already owe me a substantial 50 taels of silver.
So stingy.
My dad only gives me a little allowance every month, and it's never enough.
Besides, Lu Ming Manor isn't doing well now,
and I can't keep spending the manor's money.
So, you're using my money?
Of course.
You worked so hard to earn the money.
How can I live up to your expectations if I don't spend it?
Okay.
Don’t worry.
I'll pay you back once I become the Master.
Boss lady, serve the dishes.
Who are you?
We're going to be rich this time.
Look at how this girl is dressed,
she's obviously a young lady from a wealthy family.
Let go of me!
Don't think about letting her go without 500 taels. Retreat!
What's going on?
How dare you commit a crime in front of me?
Mind your own business!
Young Master!
Let go of that girl!
Let go of me!
What is that?
Did he go the wrong way?
He scared me.
Let go of me!
Young Master, pull the reins!
What's going on?
If I say I don't know,
would you believe me?
You don't know?
Should you be here now?
Where should I be?
Where do you think you should be?
I don't know.
Excuse me.
Get us a doctor.
-Young Master.
-Miss.
Arrange for Yu Xixi
to freshen up and change clothes, and prepare for the wedding.
Also, have someone keep a close eye on her
to prevent any further mistakes.
Yes, Young Master.
Miss.
It's the auspicious moment.
The wedding ceremony begins.
Welcome the bride.
♫Your hair wraps around my finger♫
♫I'm lost in my dream and I don't know anything♫
♫After having a drink, you left♫
♫I wanted you to stay♫
♫Silly, sentimental lover in this mortal realm♫
First, bow to heaven and earth.
♫Drizzling raindrops in the coolness of an autumn night♫
Second, bow to parents.
♫Mountains have trees, and trees have branches♫
[Memorial Tablet of Zang Muxiang]
Bride and groom exchange bows.
♫I love you, but you are unaware♫
The ritual is accomplished!
♫How many partings and reunions on the divine mountain♫
♫Though reluctant to part, what matters most is not being together every day♫
How about we unveil the cover now?
Wait.
I haven't decided yet.
At this point, what are you thinking about?
Now is the time to think even more.
I won't marry you.
What?
I've had enough of you.
Everything has to be done according to your will.
After Mother's death,
it has become more critical.
What else can I do?
Letting you have your way?
What's wrong with letting me have my way?
I am a living person,
and of course, I have my own thoughts.
Moreover, I don't even know
who my biological parents are.
In the Yu Mansion, I am just a dependent.
Now I have to marry you in this way.
Have you considered my feelings?
Your feelings?
Then tell me.
I want to study mechanical arts.
I feel that it's related to my identity.
It's all your imagination.
Besides, as a young lady,
you expose yourself too much, and if word gets out...
Must a young lady always be gentle and agreeable?
Besides, I don't want to marry someone
I don't love.
Parental arrangements are someone else's rules,
not mine.
Wait.
What?
Before Mother passed away, she wanted me to marry you
because she was concerned about your future
and wanted me to take care of you.
You have to prove to me
that you can take care of yourself.
So that
I can fulfill my promise to Mother.
How do you want me to prove it?
It's up to you. I'll follow your lead.
How about this?
In 3 months,
if I can earn enough money,
the engagement will be completely canceled.
And if you don't earn enough?
Then we get married, and I'll be devoted to you.
Earning money is too easy.
Even a single copper coin counts as earnings.
Let's set a target.
How much do you want to set?
Your monthly expenses,
including all the miscellaneous things,
are at least 50 taels.
So, for 3 months, it's at least 150 taels.
I'll cut you some slack
and make it 100 taels for 3 months.
100 taels.
100 taels?
How about 80 taels?
150 taels.
100 taels. Deal.
It's a deal.
♫Autumn is coming and the wind ripples the pond♫
♫I don't know♫
It's a deal.
♫I know, the water flows east, and the moon rises in the west♫
Enjoy yourselves.
♫All remains the same♫
Drink up.
♫Your hair wraps around my finger♫
♫I'm lost in my dream and I don't know anything♫
What's going on?
♫After having a drink, you left♫
♫I wanted you to stay♫
♫Silly, sentimental lover in this mortal realm♫
Distinguished guests,
The wedding ceremony between Yu Xixi and me
has been decided to be postponed
♫Drizzling raindrops in the coolness of an autumn night♫
after our discussion.
As for when it will be rescheduled or completely canceled,
♫Mountains have trees, and trees have branches♫
we cannot provide an answer today.
I would like to extend my apologies at this moment.
Uncle San,
♫I love you, but you are unaware♫
Refund the monetary gifts in full.
♫How many partings and reunions on the divine mountain♫