[A Moment But Forever]
[Episode 12]
You're awake.
Are you feeling uncomfortable anywhere?
No.
You were severely injured.
It's better for you to rest in bed.
I'm fine now.
This is my friend Mei Shan's residence.
He was the one who underwent the lightning tribulation.
Lightning tribulation?
Are you alright then?
A tribulation's force is immense
and you were sealed away for so long.
Your essence blood has been severely depleted.
How could you disregard yourself
and take on someone else's calamity?
Do you have a death wish?
Apart from creating things,
what other skills do you have?
And how dare you
block a lightning strike for me?
I'm different.
How are you different?
I made a promise
to protect you well.
Of course, I can't let you
lose your life right before my eyes.
However,
you need to learn
to protect yourself well.
I can't save you again.
If you encounter such a problem again,
I won't be able to intervene.
Who did you promise?
When did you promise them?
And why can't you intervene again?
I can't tell you.
You...
Is this Baitou Mountain?
You've been here before?
Yes, I have.
But before,
this wasn't the name.
Something's not right.
What's not right?
I used divination
to calculate Tanyin's fortune for this journey.
The result shows it's still a mix of good and bad luck,
unclear and obscure.
It's exactly the same as the previous result,
with no changes.
How could that be?
Then how do you explain Tanyin's dream?
We are gods.
We don't simply have
insignificant dreams.
What do you think?
Didn't Tanyin say
the High Priest
almost killed her in her dream?
Isn't it obvious?
This person stole the Divine Hand
and killed countless people.
He must have learned Tanyin's identity
and decided to strike first to kill the god and seize the Divine Hand.
It's not impossible.
How can you interpret it
so simplistically and crudely?
In Tanyin's dream,
there was also Deity Taihe.
If it's what you said,
then how do you explain Taihe's presence?
Hannv,
I know you're worried about Taihe,
but the five Preceptors of Discipline
of the Discipline Hall
have already made their decision.
We can only obey.
This... this...
May I ask where you're from
and which clan you belong to?
I'm from Pingzhou. I'm of the human race.
Pingzhou?
Pingzhou...
Are there any... any immortal caves there?
Did your ancestors
also have this kind of
talent for resurrection?
I see that you have extraordinary potential
and you're not afraid of the harm from heavenly lightning.
I wonder if you've had any
extraordinary encounters?
No, I haven't.
Then, then, then...
Is it
related to the techniques you've practiced?
Can't you ask something useful?
Haven't...
Haven't you been suspicious of her all along?
I was just asking on your behalf, wasn't I?
Mind your own business.
Hey, you're so ungrateful.
I'm thinking for you.
She took
such a big risk for you,
suffering the lightning,
and saved your life.
Yet you're still here,
questioning her.
Where are your manners?
I didn't ask.
You didn't ask?
Even just thinking about it
is impolite.
What's your relationship with her now?
This is a life-and-death relationship.
Yet you keep suspecting her.
You're utterly heartless.
Utterly heartless.
Mei Shan,
I called you here to check her legs.
If you're not going to treat her,
then get out.
Understood, understood.
How is it?
Pardon my frankness,
but the nerves and muscles in her legs are severely damaged.
I'm afraid
there's no possibility of recovery.
Even you can't do anything?
I can make her a pair of crutches.
Does that count?
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
It's okay.
If he can't cure you,
I'll find someone else to treat you.
There must be a way.
I believe you.
Excuse me, you two,
could you please respect
my diagnosis?
If I say
these legs can't be cured,
no one can make it happen.
Didn't you say yesterday
that if she could come back to life,
you'd take off your head
and use it as a stool?
Go on.
Children should be seen but not heard.
If you don't speak, no one will miss you.
Thank you,
but I still prefer to believe
what Yuanzhong said.
Young lady,
I have a question
I'd like to discuss with you.
This selfless spirit of yours,
this noble quality of sacrificing yourself for others,
is it innate
or acquired later in life?
To be honest,
I'd like to be friends with you.
The kind that can withstand heavenly thunder for me.
Zi Fei.
Young lady, listen to me.
To be frank…
Go, go, go.
When I saw your brave act
of facing the thunder,
I developed
a deep admiration for you!
Young lady, let's be friends!
Let's go.
Young lady!
Go out!
That's just how Mei Shan is.
He's a bit crazy.
Don't take it to heart.
Wh-Why are you staring at me?
I just have a lot of questions I want to ask you.
But I also know
that even if I ask,
there won't be any answers.
Are you hungry?
A little.
I'll go get you something to eat.
Reporting to the deity,
I have dispatched the elites of our clan.
We vow to reclaim the God-Slaying Dagger.
Please
give my clan one more chance.
You don't even know
if your clansmen are alive or dead.
How will you find them
and reclaim the God-Slaying Dagger?
The mortal realm is vast,
with countless living beings.
With your current
manpower and abilities,
trying to find the dagger
is like searching for a needle in the haystack.
How can I trust you?
If I may speak,
although our clan is in a difficult situation now,
we are not without allies.
I have sent people to contact them
and ask for their assistance.
There's no time.
We must prepare for both possibilities.
I've heard that the War Demon Clan
has a secret technique
called Possessing.
It's said that if certain conditions are met,
one can control someone's body
from thousands of miles away,
making them live
or die at will.
Is this true?
Yes.
What are those necessary conditions
that must be met?
War Demons?
Do you really want to use them
to perform the possessing technique against Yuanzhong?
If they were capable of succeeding,
they wouldn't have been chased
for so many years,
unable to see the light of day.
I have my own considerations in what I do.
There's no need for you to worry.
Still don't feel anything?
But you don't need to worry.
I'm just too badly injured.
It will take some time
to recover.
I'm not worried.
It's just that if you don't get better,
I don't want to have a cripple
as a handmaiden.
Look, what a nice girl.
Her legs are so badly injured,
yet she's still putting on a brave façade.
If I can't be friends with her,
it must be against the will of heaven
and I deserve to be struck by lightning.
Are you really trying to
befriend her?
I'm almost embarrassed to expose your true intentions.
Why wouldn't I be?
Don't doubt my sincerity in making friends.
You have ulterior motives.
You just want her to help you bear the lightning.
I don't like what you're saying.
Let me ask you,
when making friends,
shouldn't we be open and honest with each other?
When a friend encounters difficulties,
shouldn't we be willing to go through thick and thin for them?
In the end,
you just want her
to help you bear the tribulation.
Young man,
you need to have a longer-term perspective.
If she encounters any difficulties in the future,
I will certainly rush to her aid without hesitation.
I'd even hold up
the sky for her if it fell, let alone bearing lightning,
Anyone can make empty promises.
I could even give my life for Yuanzhong.
What are you thinking about?
When do you plan to break the seal?
In the next few days.
You're ready?
Alright, then in the future,
if there's anything
you need me for,
just let me know.
I will.
Can't you show some courtesy?
I did it in my head.
I almost made myself sick.
What are
your plans for that girl?
I haven't decided yet.
Well, it seems
she has no future with you.
How about she stay and help me bear the lightning instead?
See?
You're reluctant to let her go, aren't you?
I can't figure her out.
Who doesn't have some secrets?
Don't you have any?
Don't I have any?
I mean, I don't know
what she's after.
She's after you, of course.
It's such a simple matter.
I think the girl
has fallen for you.
To protect you,
she's even willing to give up her life.
Where else would you find
such a devoted and good girl like her?
If it weren't for the fact that
my heart already belongs to someone else,
even I would be moved.
I'm telling you,
you should trust the judgment of someone who has experience.
Yuanzhong, you're still young.
You haven't seen such a situation before,
so it's understandable.
Don't take yourself
too seriously.
Of course,
you can't disregard
others' feelings either.
Feelings are something
that can disappear in an instant.
When that happens,
you won't even know who to cry to.
Seriously.
♫Too many old dreams♫
♫Where did the snow fall to?♫
♫Going to face a catastrophe♫
♫No one is irrelevant♫
She's likes me?
What does that have to do with me?
♫A slight ripple in my gaze♫
♫Who knows the warmth and cold of my fleeting life?♫
Ji Tanyin.
♫If staying together is difficult, it's not worth it♫
Ji Tanyin?
♫I'll return what's left of my life♫
♫Falling into the mortal world♫
♫Wandering through the clouds and rivers♫
♫Being by your side is like finding the shore♫
Ji Tanyin?
♫If between oaths♫
♫I hold onto the longing for just one more glance♫
Ji Tanyin!
♫Unwilling to bid farewell for good♫
♫Tears grow cold in a single cup♫
♫Longing fades in half♫
♫Like flowers in a mirror, or the moon in the water♫
♫A thousand years of long nights, yearning from dawn to dusk♫
♫A slight ripple in my gaze♫
♫Who knows the warmth and cold of my fleeting life?♫
♫If staying together is difficult, it's not worth it♫
♫I'll return what's left of my life♫
♫Falling into the mortal world♫
♫Wandering through the clouds and rivers♫
♫Being by your side is like finding the shore♫
♫The moon falls by the riverbank♫
♫The light finally dims♫
♫How can my heart be at ease?♫
♫Tears grow cold in a single cup♫
♫Longing fades in half♫
♫Like flowers in a mirror, or the moon in the water♫
♫The lonely guest can't sleep, destiny can't be undone; speechless♫
♫Falling into the mortal world♫
♫Wandering through the clouds and rivers♫
♫Being by your side is like finding the shore♫
♫The moon falls by the riverbank♫
♫The light finally dims♫
♫How can my heart be at ease?♫
♫Tears grow cold in a single cup♫
♫Longing fades in half♫
♫Like flowers in a mirror, or the moon in the water♫
♫The lonely guest can't sleep, destiny can't be undone; speechless♫
Why didn't you stay in your room?
Why did you go there?
I-I was just
taking a bath.
After being unconscious for so long,
I must have smelled awful.
As for you,
as the High Priest of the Youhu Clan,
don't you know it's improper to peek?
How dare you stand there and watch?
I wasn't peeking.
I was just passing by.
Your legs are injured so badly.
How could you go so far?
A mechanical bird carried me there.
Hold on tight.
Here, have some water.
Thank you.
Here you go.
I'm fine.
Well then, you should rest.
I'll be going now.
Do you have something
you want to say to me?
No.
Then I have something to tell you.
Sit here.
Don't you have something to say?
What are you laughing about?
You don't want to send me away anymore,
do you?
Who told you that?
I can see it
in your eyes.
That's good.
At least that strike wasn't for nothing.
You have no idea
how painful that purple lightning was.
If there had been another strike,
I might have been reduced to ashes.
If you're afraid,
you should stay far away.
That won't do.
I have to follow you
and be with you.
Ji Tanyin.
You don't know me.
I do know you.
I think I'm the person in this world
who knows you best.
Why do you always say that?
Because I've seen it.
I don't even know what you're talking about.
You're so weird.
Anyway, even if you follow me,
you won't gain anything.
You can't change anything either.
When this matter is over,
I'll find someone to heal your legs.
Then, whether you stay or leave
will be entirely up to you.
I won't leave.
If you follow me,
you'll still be a handmaiden.
That's already good enough for me.
Silly.
A new store has opened over there.
Really?
Let's go check it out sometime.
Okay.
They have a complete selection of items inside.
Is that so?
Miss, there's a gentleman
who invites you to dine with him.
Friends have come from afar.
Naturally, I'm delighted.
I've specially prepared a table of food and drinks
to welcome the three of you.
May our friendship stay evergreen,
as enduring as heaven and earth,
and as eternal as the sun and moon.
Come, eat up.
Please start eating.
No need to be so polite with me.
Excuse me, everyone.
Could someone please settle the bill for the food and drinks first?
Why are you looking at me?
Don't forget,
I still owe you half a year's worth of drink tabs.
You...
I don't have money either.
No way.
How long the light
of our friendship can last
all depends on you now.
Surely you won't
heartlessly
extinguish it over the cost of one meal, would you?
You should know
that in my heart,
I've always believed you to be a good person.
Does being a good person mean you must have money?
Besides,
wasn't this meal
supposed to be your treat for everyone?
Why must
someone else pay for you?
That's right, Mei Shan.
You're an immortal,
yet you've ended up like this.
Aren't you ashamed?
I don't want to be like this either.
Every 49 days,
I get struck by lightning once.
All my time is spent
enduring lightning, cultivating, and recovering from injuries.
How can I find time to make money?
How about we continue to put it on the tab?
Listen, you all,
you're immortals after all.
Surely you can't be unable
to scrape together the price of a meal, right?
Look.
What's so special about this?
You know me, don't you?
There are indeed immortals
so poor they can't even afford a meal.
Zi Fei.
Thank you, immortal.
Alright.
Then, this first cup of wine
is to toast me for surviving the tribulation.
Surely good fortune will follow.
The next tribulation is approaching soon.
For such matters,
we do our best and leave the rest to fate.
If all else fails, to hell with it.
Drink some wine, gaze at the sky,
and live one day at a time, right?
Come, let's drink.
Cheers!
Miss Ji is not good at drinking.
I usually do drink a little,
but this wine is really too strong.
That's because you haven't drunk enough.
Drink some more
and you'll even find it bland.
Don't listen to his nonsense.
Baitou Mountain is covered in snow year-round.
The local mountain dwellers brew this wine
specially to ward off the cold.
It's easy to get drunk if you have too much.
Then I won't drink anymore.
Eat more.
Thank you.
Why do you two
look sneaky?
Do we?
No.
It didn't break?
The material seems quite ordinary.
This is something you don't know.
Nothing on Baitou Mountain
can be damaged by external forces.
You won't be able to
pluck a single leaf
from the ordinary plants
in this room,
unless it falls down naturally.
Is that so?
Try it.
It seems there's an invisible force
protecting this place.
It's fortunate that it is so.
Otherwise, with me experiencing tribulations here year after year,
this mountain would have been struck by lightning and destroyed long ago.
Eat quickly. The food is getting cold.
Don't you like it?
I suddenly have a craving for roast goose.
You like roast goose?
Earlier on the tower ship,
I saw others eating roast goose
and thought it smelled delicious.
Are your legs better?
A little better.
But I feel
I can barely stand up.
However, I believe it will heal soon.
How can such a severe injury
heal?
What's wrong?
Perhaps when I stood up earlier,
I put too much strain on it,
so it's a bit painful now.
I'm only doing this because
you took a hit for me.
Don't overthink it.
By the way,
you and Mr. Mei Shan
seem to be good friends.
I guess.
Besides me,
no one else wants to be his friend.
I heard earlier
that you destroyed his cave dwelling
and had a fight with him.
How come
you're now good friends?
Because I showed mercy
and spared his miserable life.
He was grateful to me, worshipped me,
and kowtowed to me.
He shamelessly
insisted on being my friend.
I had no choice but to give in.
I don't believe that.
Having no choice but to give in
is actually true.
This guy
is reckless when he goes crazy.
But after all, I was in the wrong first.
I destroyed his cave dwelling,
so it wouldn't be right to go all out against him.
So you apologized to him?
It was a strategic compromise.
What happened after that?
After that...
After that, something happened
in the clan.
My Divine Hand power was sealed.
Kai Shan and the others
were also sealed in different places.
This Baitou Mountain
is where Kai Shan is sealed.
After that,
Mei Shan helped me guard this place.
Does it hurt?
A little bit.
Bear with it. It helps with recovery.
Why are you looking at me?
It's nothing.
Am I not massaging well?
It's fine.
Just feels a bit tingly.
That means it's almost healed.
That's enough for today.
You should rest now.
Please.
Esteemed guest,
are you satisfied with this fish?
Thank you, waiter.
You're welcome, you're welcome.
Enjoy your meal.
This is bream from the Min River.
The taste is exquisite.
If we hadn't passed by here,
we wouldn't have had such a delicacy.
We're just passing acquaintances, Sir.
I don't know why
you've invited me here.
We're not just passing acquaintances.
Although it's a bit late,
I still remembered you.
This is liquor from the Min River.
Though not a fine wine,
it has its own unique flavor.
Please.
How does it taste?
When did you remember me?
You felt familiar when I first saw you.
After thinking carefully,
I remembered.
Do you have something to tell me?
This sword is quite special.
The blade is a bit shorter.
The hilt is also thinner.
May I take a look?
The hilt fits well in my hand.
The blade is sharp enough too.
It's a good sword.
Does this sword have a name?
You don't recognize it?
Should I recognize it?
Then why
did you say you recognized me?
You're a handmaiden from Xiaoxiang Peak.
When I was confined by the Elders
in Jinxia Palace,
you came to clean the room.
What? Did I remember wrong?
No.
You remembered correctly, Sir.
I was indeed a handmaiden from Xiaoxiang Peak.
We've met a few times.
My status is humble.
I'm flattered that you remember.
Don't worry.
Over these decades,
it's not unheard of for human handmaidens
to quietly slip away.
I've come down the mountain this time
for other important matters to attend to.
I won't give you any trouble.
You're so generous.
Thank you so much, Sir.
Judging by your physique,
you must be trained in martial arts.
Did you learn it before coming to the mountain?
As a human, my status is lowly.
Would anyone
from Fangwai Mountain teach me martial arts there?
Perhaps you think
I learned it secretly?
You seem to dislike me.
I wouldn't dare.
I'm just curious.
Since you're trained in martial arts,
why did you go to the mountain as a handmaiden?
If you don't want to,
you don't have to tell me.
I'm just curious, that's all.
I was looking for an answer.
An answer?
When I was young,
I accidentally entered a spiritual mountain.
All traces of life had vanished on the mountain.
There was only the light of snow everywhere,
as if blessed by the gods.
I...
I encountered a deer.
It stood majestically
in the wind and snow.
I looked into its eyes
and felt
an unprecedented stirring in my heart.
It was as if it were
the only color in the world.
I thought at the time
that all things have spirits
and our meeting was no coincidence.
For many years after that,
I searched for this deer.
I heard
it was a divine deer from the spiritual mountain.
It was extremely rare.
Perhaps...
Perhaps something belonging to the divine race
might be on Fangwai Mountain.
I went up the mountain to serve as a handmaiden
and searched for it for many years.
Did you find it?
Later, I did indeed see it again.
Isn't that good?
It's both good and not so good, I suppose.
Its appearance hadn't changed,
but it was completely different
from the clear and transparent,
ethereal,
almost otherworldly feeling
I remembered.
So you were disappointed?
I wouldn't say disappointed.
So many years have passed.
I can barely remember
what it originally looked like.
It was nothing more than
an illusion
that I had beautified
many times in my mind.
To judge the present version
against an imagined one
isn't fair to him.
Perhaps the one I met
back then
wasn't his true self to begin with,
but rather who I thought he was.
Moreover,
he had long forgotten about me.
You seem to have deep insights.
Not exactly.
I've been trapped in my obsession for too many years.
It's time to let go.
How old are you?
You're too young to talk about "too many years."
But that's good.
Wasting your life for a deer
is truly unwise.
You're right to admonish me, Sir.
This sword seems destined for you, Sir.
Please accept it as a gift.
♫I gaze into your deep eyes♫
What do you mean?
♫For whom do you take apart the word "love"?♫
Consider it a thank you for the wine you offered.
♫Turning around, it's like a dream♫
♫I have betrayed deep love♫
♫Unable to get what I yearn for, I sink in sadness♫
♫When I brush past love fate is set♫
♫I've used up my brush and ink♫
♫But I can't describe♫
♫This lovesick path♫
Kai Shan is right here.
So you're saying
he sealed himself
in the hot spring?
He found a good place, right?
According to what the Divine Hand has detected,
he's in an even deeper place
below the hot spring.
It's surrounded by scorching energy.
What should we do? Let's fish him out.
Kai Shan, return.
Yuanzhong, up there.
Tell me about the restrictions on this mountain
and its original owner.
Well, you're asking the wrong person.
It's my first time seeing
the full extent of the restrictions.
As for this place
and its former owner,
I've never even met him.
That's not right.
This person set up
such extensive restrictions.
He couldn't have done it overnight.
Surely their intention
was to maintain the mountain's appearance
and prevent others from damaging
even a blade of grass and leaf on this mountain.
How could he allow you
to leisurely undergo your tribulations here?
Well, if you put it that way,
there is indeed something strange.
When I first arrived here,
there was always this old fellow
who came to give me trouble
and tried to drive me away.
And then?
Then I fought with him
for several years.
When he saw he couldn't do anything about me,
he never came back.
Divine artifacts have spirits.
They wouldn't choose
to seal themselves here without reason.
Could it be because
this place has restrictions
that it's
the safest for him?
But the problem is it's too safe.
Even I can't do anything about it.
Don't tell me
that you, the mighty host of the Divine Hand,
can't break
the restrictions here.
You really can't break them?
Forget about breaking the restrictions.
I just tried to deduce it,
but I couldn't even determine
the direction of the formation's eye.
What should we do then?
Take care, Sir. Please come again.
The Juque Sword?
What did you say?
This is the Juque Sword?
Sir, you don't
recognize this sword?
It is said that this sword
was the fifth sword
forged by Ouye Zi.
On the day it was completed,
its aura pierced the sky, emitting a brilliant light.
Today, I've truly seen something great.
Are you sure this is the Juque Sword?
I specifically searched for this sword in the past.
The Juque Sword in the sword diagram
doesn't look like this.
You said it yourself.
It's just a diagram.
After so many years,
people have passed on inaccurate information,
drawing based on imagination.
It can't be very accurate.
Now, you have obtained the precious sword,
yet you fail to recognize it.
This is truly...
I came out this time
just to find it.
Since you want to find it,
I will surely find it for you.
Innkeeper,
where is the young lady
who dined with me yesterday?
That young lady
checked out and left early this morning.
She left?
Do you know where she went?
I have no idea about that.
Are all these for me?
Yes, they're all for you.
They look quite nice.
They're not just nice-looking.
If you wind it up,
it can even move.
Give it a try.
Can I ask you a favor?
Go ahead.
Can you go down the mountain
and buy a roast goose for me?
No problem. Just wait here.
Thanks.
No problem.