(Dear Mom)
Ever since I was child,
everyone praised how I looked.
That I'm pretty and cute.
My mom was a model
who was proud and confident
in her own beauty.
But after she'd taken me to England
because of my dad's job,
her pride was destroyed.
Even though she wanted to
keep working as a model there,
no one paid her any attention.
Mom?
Asami.
I've told you many times
when you smile,
don't show your teeth.
You were born
with a beautiful face.
Understood?
Mm.
(Thank you, Mom)
To my mom,
what mattered most was
her son must be beautiful.
The secret to living with
someone sensitive like my mom
was to make myself numb,
to keep everything inside,
to never reveal how I felt.
Hayama,
the film study club invited you?
Mm.
Sekimizu begged you, didn't he?
He's been saying behind your back
you can be used to bring people in.
Eh? Is that so?
Just "Eh?"?
Aren't you mad?
Mihara?
Mm?
I trust you're well.
No, that's not the answer.
Mm. Let's do this.
Great.
Ah! Sorry for the wait.
Can you go over there?
Thank you for helping out.
Have you ever acted, Hayama?
No, I haven't.
Ah, you see.
Just having you
stand there will help a lot.
You don't need to try hard.
- Got it.
- Mm.
Okay.
- Explain the lines to him.
- Yes.
Uh, these are your lines.
You just have to yell at him.
Your lines are...
- Uh...
- There?
Oh, yes. There.
Okay. Thank you.
Oh, mm.
Uh, do your best.
Is everyone in place?
- Rolling.
- Yes.
Scene five, take one!
All right. Start!
(Film Study Club)
Acting was more fun than I thought.
After the filming,
I started watching more films.
When we're sad, happy, angry,
(Citizen Kane)
how do we move?
I researched that a lot.
(Welcome, newcomers!
Screening)
(by Film Study Club)
So you lied.
Did you mean it?
I'm sorry. It was my fault.
It's unforgivable!
For me, you're...
my first love.
(Aoyama: Hayama Asami
Yohe: Nishiguchi Shota)
(Manami: Asakawa Mire)
The Hayama-kun guy is very cool.
- Yes. He's very good-looking.
- Right?
I might join this club.
Everyone praises how I look.
Thank you for coming.
- So...
- The film study club...
I just have to
accept the compliments.
"It's fine even if
they don't watch my acting."
That was I thought.
"At 25:00, in Akasaka"
(Episode 7)
(Film Study Club's
Equipment Loan Logbook)
The first time I saw that name.
(Shirasaki Yuki)
in the club's loan logbook...
Someone else besides me...
actually takes them out.
(Welcome, newcomers!
Screening Survey)
The next time I saw that name
was on the club's
screening survey form.
"Hayama-san is so handsome."
"Hayama-san's still just as handsome."
Listen to that.
Such unhelpful feedback.
It's good. They're compliments.
Jeez.
(Welcome, newcomers!
Screening Survey)
So long.
Shirasaki Yuki...
Why are you making that face?
Anything interesting?
No.
Jeez.
"The character Hayama-san plays"
"seems like a gentleman
at first glance,"
"but I can feel
his unmistakable loneliness"
"hidden deep in his eyes."
"I'd love to see Hayama-san
in different roles more often."
Listen to that.
This one's crazy about you.
That was the first time
my acting received
such high praise.
That's so nice.
Hayama Asami's true number one fan.
- Are you making fun of me?
- No.
His name is Shirasaki Yuki.
Do you know him?
No, I don't.
Mm.
(I love Hayama-san's
acting the most.)
All right, rolling.
Mm. Go on.
Scene ten, take two.
All right! Action!
That's why I didn't think
to hurt someone
with my personal feelings.
Those people are pitiful...
having to lie to themselves...
and pretending to
not know how they feel.
If they keep doing that,
one day they won't
know who they are.
"Who's the actor in that role?"
It was the first time
I had that thought.
(Shirasaki Yuki)
I'm gonna tell the police
you're the culprit.
Do whatever you want.
Great. Something like that.
Let's do it.
Senior!
The original lines
are already good.
The changes you suggested
will make the story inorganic.
Jeez, that kid doesn't know
how to read the room.
He must feel alienated
in a group setting.
- I see. Go with the original lines.
- How nice.
- Use the original lines in scene ten.
- Being like that might feel nice.
He's the opposite of you, Hayama.
I wonder if someone like that...
will become an actor someday.
Since then,
the next thing I knew,
I couldn't take my eyes off of you.
- Are you going to Tokyo?
- Who?
No, I'm not.
You must be going there.
Tokyo?
(What I don't know is my own path.
To the bigger world.)
Here's what I've learned
about Shirasaki-kun.
He's always by himself.
He has a sweet tooth
so he always puts
sugar and milk in his coffee.
- Right?
- Why did you improvise just now?
It doesn't go with
the important dialogue later.
No matter who it was,
he faced them with candidness.
- The dialogue here is crucial.
- I get it now.
Shirasaki-kun and I
were completely different.
We would never see eye to eye.
The dialogue after this
is crucial too.
Eh?
That kid.
Look.
The kid who can't read the room
from the film study club.
Oh.
That's Shirasaki-kun.
Whoa, that's weird.
You remember
a junior's face and name.
Well.
I said that kid
was the opposite of you, right?
But you're actually alike.
Eh?
Well, he's...
the type without a shell.
The way he talks, behaves,
his social etiquette,
or his ability to read people.
He's like, "Yes, go ahead."
He's like that.
- Mm.
- But you, Hayama,
are the type with
a many-layered shell...
people can't tell
what you're really thinking.
So we have nothing in common.
I guess not
but it must be hard to live
both for you and that kid.
Hayama,
you have so many walls
you don't know
what you're thinking.
You're scouted by
a model agency from Tokyo.
Isn't that wonderful?
A handsome guy like you
is different from us.
- Mm.
- Yes, it's wonderful.
No way.
You won't work
as an actor, Hayama-san?
That's not right.
Ah, that's right.
Shirasaki-kun's still the same.
- So inconsiderate.
- I actually want to act.
I know.
I didn't realize that.
And the one who made me realize
was Shirasaki-kun.
Sorry, please give me
a different pose.
To me, he's my most
beautiful memory
and a special person.
You won't work
as an actor, Hayama-san?
That's not right.
But memories are memories.
My world and Shirasaki-kun's world
would never meet
no matter what I think.
(Hiru no Yume)
(Shirasaki Yuki)
But Shirasaki Yuki
appeared before me again.
(Shirasaki Yuki)
Hayama-san's here.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
I was so anxious to see you again
after so many years.
Nervous?
Oh, yes.
(Sugar)
Delicious.
No matter the genre,
or what type of scene or role,
creating is always difficult.
I felt incredibly happy.
Since then he...
You haven't changed, Shirasaki-kun.
Eh?
I'm looking forward to
being your boyfriend.
Eh? Have we met before?
- Uh, I don't think so.
- First time here?
Yes.
Oh. The film study club.
That kid from the film study club
called Shirasaki-kun
is at the bar I work right now.
The next thing I knew,
I was running.
I already kissed you.
Until the filming's over,
Shirasaki-kun and I
would be a couple.
Why couldn't I leave
Shirasaki-kun alone?
Oh, Asami-san.
Hello.
Should I stay over tonight?
Huh?
I wish the filming would never end.
So that's what...
the word "like" is all about.
I'm looking forward
to our sensual kiss scene.
Yuki, let's check out
the onsen together.
Eh?
The onsen here is famous.
Uh...
Going to the onsen with Yamase-kun?
No.
When I'm with Shirasaki-kun,
I feel like my shell
is being pried off.
What I've got hidden,
covered up,
and stored away
is about to be revealed.
You two were wonderful.
Shall we rehearse?
Our kiss scene tomorrow.
I finally understood...
I don't wanna give Shirasaki-kun...
to anyone.
Hey, about the person
you still can't get over.
You said, "There's someone
I can't get over."
Mm.
So... you like that person?
I do.
It really felt like a dream.
I'm gonna stop...
being your boyfriend, Hayama-san.
I don't need to rely on you
anymore, Hayama-san.
But eventually
I have to wake up from this dream.
The script for the last episode.
Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
Ryouji and Takumi
press their lips together
as if to affirm their feelings.
And they...
become one for the first time.
I have no idea...
how to touch Shirasaki-kun
who's keeping me at arm's length.
I have no idea.
(Next episode)
It's been fun
acting in my first drama.
I won't force you
to stay in character anymore.
Why do I keep
thinking about Hayama-san?
Can you hold me?
It sounds fun.