‪SPOOKY IN LOVE
‪CEO CHEON YEO-RI
‪EPISODE 2
‪Why do you run away
‪whenever we meet, Ms. Cheon?
‪I wasn't running away. I was avoiding you.
‪Why avoid me like I'm some kind of virus?
‪Okay, fine. So you avoided me.
‪Why do that
‪if you're not guilty of anything?
‪People who aren't guilty
‪can avoid others if they want.
‪Oh, so you ignore everyone to start with?
‪To be honest, I couldn't stand you.
‪You left a terrible first impression.
‪I'd say you're just as bad in that aspect.
‪So what is it that you want to know?
‪You reported the body on Mt. Haewang,
‪didn't you?
‪You caught the culprit and found the body.
‪Does it matter who reported it?
‪There could be more than one culprit,
‪and it's too suspicious
‪that you knew where the body was.
‪Are you saying
‪that I'm the accomplice?
‪If something feels off,
‪isn't it best to cover all bases?
‪Delusion must come
‪with being a prosecutor.
‪Let's say I'm here to check facts.
‪How did you know the body was there?
‪You seem to have asked
‪all you wanted to know.
‪Please leave.
‪What's the point of asking
‪when you didn't answer a single one?
‪Tell me just one thing.
‪How did you know the body was there?
‪I was told.
‪By whom?
‪-By a ghost.
‪-What?
‪Are you kidding me right now?
‪Why ask if you won't believe me?
‪Are you a psychic medium or a shaman
‪-for a ghost to tell you that?
‪-Ms. Cheon.
‪Did I hit the nail on the head?
‪Now I feel bad for no reason.
‪Hey!
‪I can't believe I'm seeing this.
‪What are you doing in a place like this?
‪I come to such places often,
‪to enforce search warrants.
‪What do you think?
‪Totally luxurious, right?
‪The owner of this hotel
‪is my future cousin-in-law.
‪Want me to pull some strings
‪and get you a membership?
‪You really must have a thing for hotels.
‪Jang Eun-ju disappeared from a hotel too,
‪didn't she?
‪Why would you bring her up?
‪Just you wait.
‪I'll find Jang Eun-ju's body,
‪no matter how well you hid it.
‪You have quite the imagination.
‪Nice jacket. Looks good on you.
‪Ghosts tell you stuff?
‪Like what?
‪It's nothing.
‪I was just joking.
‪Shaman Baek's suppression ritual
‪to stop you from seeing things.
‪Did it fail?
‪Of course not.
‪Don't you act rash.
‪There are eyes and ears everywhere.
‪A strange rumor has been
‪going around already.
‪What kind of rumor?
‪That you were ordained as a shaman.
‪I assume it was your ex-fiancé's family
‪who started it.
‪Just make sure
‪you don't get caught up in gossip.
‪I'll be careful.
‪Oh, right.
‪About the Competitiveness
‪Improvement Strategy.
‪I thought you'd suggest
‪we drive Reina forward with an upgrade,
‪just as luxury brands
‪have their high-end tier.
‪Reina Seoul will stick to the strategy
‪to upgrade and improve.
‪The same goes
‪for the Busan and Gyeongju branches.
‪But if we consider the brand as a whole,
‪we need a strategic revamp
‪to change our structure.
‪It's not a decision
‪to make here and now,
‪but I thought of CL Raymond Hotel.
‪I find their brand strategy
‪quite appealing.
‪When CL Group opened their first hotel,
‪they collaborated with Raymond,
‪the global hotel chain, to succeed.
‪It's true that global hotel chains
‪are entering not only Seoul,
‪but other larger cities as well.
‪Still, I'm against it.
‪Why bother paying a fee to use a name?
‪They opened last year
‪and you know how much they grew.
‪It's not a bad idea.
‪Give it some thought.
‪It's me. Where about are you?
‪Where else?
‪I'm on my way back to the office.
‪Didn't you take the day off?
‪Why would I take the day off?
‪People like me don't have the time
‪to take days off.
‪I've reminded you so many times
‪since last month.
‪You must do a good deed today
‪during the Hour of the Monkey.
‪I'm not some high schooler
‪collecting good deed miles for university.
‪Good deeds only work out
‪if they come from the heart.
‪What's the point in doing good
‪on an auspicious day just to avoid evil…
‪My goodness.
‪My one and only grandson
‪doesn't listen to a word I say.
‪If you think that little of me,
‪I don't see the point
‪in living any longer.
‪I've outlived my welcome.
‪Come on, don't say that.
‪You're breaking your grandson's heart.
‪I'm on my way, okay?
‪I'll take the afternoon off.
‪Careful, kids.
‪You said you wanted this last time.
‪-Be careful, guys.
‪-It's mine!
‪-One, two, three, let's go!
‪-Let's go!
‪Pass it forward.
‪We lost the ball!
‪Oh, no.
‪-No, don't lose it!
‪-Get it!
‪Hey, no.
‪Foul! That's a foul!
‪-You couldn't block that?
‪-He aimed too well.
‪-No, it's just that…
‪-How did you miss it?
‪-That is bad.
‪-Oh, no.
‪We replaced that window
‪just three days ago.
‪The director's away on business, right?
‪Yes, that's true.
‪I'll destroy the evidence.
‪The director's office is locked
‪and we don't have the key.
‪There's always a way.
‪A way?
‪I found the ball!
‪People who stayed in the rooms near Jang's
‪around the time of her disappearance?
‪Yes, those who stayed in the rooms
‪next to, above, and below hers,
‪the times they checked in and out,
‪and their alibis for that period.
‪Got it.
‪Okay.
‪Park Seung-jae sunk thrilling shot
‪after shot at the championship
‪and is now top of the leaderboard
‪in the third round.
‪Wow, you ripped the green
‪like you were shredding a stage.
‪This is embarrassing. Let's just drink.
‪Mr. Park. You're pretty cool.
‪This is just between us,
‪but isn't that score a miracle
‪compared to your previous games?
‪I mean, data is science,
‪but what beats science is luck.
‪I guess I got a lucky break.
‪-That's it.
‪-Yeah, nice.
‪-Mom.
‪-Yes?
‪Should we ask Shaman Baek
‪to write him a talisman
‪so his luck doesn't run out?
‪Well…
‪Why not? They say ghosts control luck.
‪Shaman Baek is best at handling spirits,
‪like what he did for Yeo-ri.
‪Ha-ri.
‪Was Ms. Cheon ever possessed by a ghost?
‪Gosh, no.
‪She wasn't possessed.
‪She's a ghost herself,
‪the type that drags others down.
‪She totally badmouthed you last time.
‪Me? What did she say?
‪What was it again?
‪That you dumped your ex for my money
‪and that you're a parasite.
‪Hey, don't.
‪What? She did say that.
‪You can't just barge in like that.
‪What do you want?
‪Ms. Cheon,
‪I hear you've been talking reckless.
‪That I'm a parasite who dumped my ex
‪for Ha-ri's money.
‪What was that smirk about?
‪Cheon Yeo-ri. Do you hate me that much?
‪Am I not good enough for your cousin?
‪Not good enough doesn't even cover it.
‪The truth is, Jang Eun-ju
‪came to our hotel before she went missing.
‪Hello, ma'am.
‪I'll speak with her. Can you excuse us?
‪Yes, of course.
‪You want to reserve Siena Hall?
‪Yes.
‪Is there a problem
‪for you to come see me in person?
‪No, there's no problem.
‪It's just that the name of your groom
‪made me wonder if it's the person
‪I happen to know.
‪Yes, it's him.
‪You see, there's nothing else I can do,
‪so I had no choice but to come here.
‪He asked me to marry him
‪and put this ring on my finger,
‪but then he broke up with me
‪and started dating someone else.
‪I'm pregnant.
‪I can't live without Seung-jae.
‪Will you please help me?
‪What stupid crap is this?
‪You think she got pregnant
‪just from holding hands?
‪-You're saying it wasn't you?
‪-Of course not!
‪She's a professional
‪when it comes to bluffing and lying.
‪You don't believe what she said, do you?
‪I guess the only way to find out
‪is to set up a three-way encounter.
‪A three-way encounter?
‪You, me, and who else?
‪Jang Eun-ju.
‪Just how would you sit
‪face-to-face with the dead?
‪You said she wasn't dead, but in hiding.
‪Wasn't that the story you told?
‪Well, yes. She disappeared.
‪If something feels off,
‪isn't it best to cover all bases?
‪Let's go for a three-way encounter.
‪So you're saying
‪Jang Eun-ju is coming here?
‪She could be here already.
‪Come on in.
‪Is there anything that seems off?
‪Not yet.
‪What about the call history?
‪I didn't find much from that either,
‪other than what we mentioned
‪in the previous trial.
‪I don't think we'll find anything new.
‪Evil is thorough and meticulous,
‪so it stays well-hidden.
‪We must find something
‪we might have overlooked.
‪Something to overturn the verdict
‪in the second trial.
‪A smoking gun.
‪Well, the best smoking gun would be…
‪Jang Eun-ju's discarded body.
‪You asked for me?
‪Mr. Park will be on his way out.
‪Make sure to give him
‪some free merchandise.
‪Yes, ma'am.
‪Your secretary is Jang Eun-ju?
‪You already knew
‪there was no way Jang Eun-ju
‪would walk through that door.
‪You have a way of cornering someone.
‪We'll be in-laws soon, you know.
‪By the way,
‪Eun-ju asked me to tell you this.
‪She hopes you win this championship.
‪-What?
‪-She says
‪the higher you are, the harder the fall.
‪I'm rooting for you
‪and your most monumental fall.
‪Monumental fall, my ass.
‪-Wait.
‪-What?
‪-I've seen her somewhere.
‪-Where?
‪There.
‪The woman in the photo
‪on Park Seung-jae's phone.
‪We suspected that he was dating her too.
‪I think that's her.
‪She stayed in the suite
‪right next to Jang Eun-ju?
‪Could this be a coincidence?
‪Yes, this is me.
‪But who took this photo?
‪Do you know Park Seung-jae, the golfer?
‪-I do know him.
‪-You do?
‪How do you know him?
‪I had a job interview
‪with another airline.
‪My flight schedule got messed up,
‪and I had to rush as soon as I landed.
‪You seem to be in a hurry.
‪I'll give you a ride
‪if we're going the same way.
‪He was a first-class passenger
‪I'd seen a few times,
‪and he was pretty polite.
‪I got in the car
‪thinking he was being nice.
‪Thanks to him,
‪I got to the interview in time.
‪Did you see him again after that?
‪No.
‪Then were you ever at Lavo…
‪-Laviem.
‪-Yes, Laviem Hotel.
‪Did you ever stay there?
‪Never.
‪Isn't this you?
‪You say you've never been there,
‪but when you checked in,
‪they confirmed your ID card.
‪They checked my ID card?
‪Yes.
‪Come to think of it,
‪I must've left my wallet
‪in Mr. Park's car that day.
‪It was delivered to my airline office
‪by courier a few days later.
‪Right, I see.
‪Thanks for cooperating.
‪We need your signature
‪to confirm your statement.
‪Please sign right here.
‪You're right-handed.
‪Yes.
‪Park Seung-jae is a leftie.
‪The story seems to be coming together,
‪doesn't it?
‪-Good shot!
‪He's playing so well today.
‪He's so good.
‪-You're doing great!
‪-Good shot!
‪I got Park Seung-jae's receipt
‪from the wig store.
‪Where are you right now, Mr. Ma?
‪I'm putting
‪the final puzzle pieces together.
‪See you back at the office.
‪The time the flight attendant
‪entered the room next to Jang Eun-ju's
‪was 10:17 p.m.
‪If the two suites
‪share an outdoor terrace‪…
‪he could've easily gotten into Jang's room
‪avoiding the cameras outside.
‪If…
‪Park Seung-jae,
‪disguised as the flight attendant,
‪checked into the room next door
‪to get into Jang's room…
‪The time the flight attendant
‪left her suite
‪was 10:40 p.m.
‪The lobby camera caught her at 11:05 p.m.
‪It took her 25 minutes
‪to get from the suite to the lobby.
‪The white sheet
‪peeking from the suitcase in the corridor
‪was no longer visible
‪in ‪the ‪lobby ‪footage.
‪The only place
‪Park ‪Seung-jae ‪could've ‪gone ‪to
‪in the missing 25 minutes is…
‪PENTHOUSE FLOOR
‪Oh, my back…
‪What was that for?
‪What are you doing here?
‪I should ask you that.
‪I'm working a case.
‪I'm handling a private complaint.
‪Does that mean
‪the reason you're here is…
‪-It's going in.
‪-It went in.
‪What's going on, Seung-jae?
‪Will you give it more thought?
‪What is there to think about? We're done.
‪I'm pregnant.
‪Hey.
‪Don't lie to me. I'm off.
‪-I'm serious. Just wait.
‪-What's wrong with you?
‪-Please think it over.
‪-Let go of me.
‪I said, let go of me!
‪Hey.
‪Jang Eun-ju.
‪Hey. Wake up.
‪The winner of the Astra Championship.
‪With a total of 270 strokes, 18 under par,
‪the winner of this championship
‪is Park Seung-jae.
‪Over the past four days,
‪he scored 66 strokes, 69 strokes,
‪then 68 strokes,
‪and 67 strokes on each day.
‪A shocking score
‪of 270 strokes, 18 under par
‪has made him the new champion
‪of the Astra Championship.
‪The hosting chairman
‪is now awarding him the trophy.
‪Please give him a warm hand of applause.
‪Ha-ri.
‪This is for you.
‪Can you come and take some photos?
‪-Look over here, please.
‪-Gosh, what are you doing?
‪Over here, please.
‪-Can you tell us how you feel?
‪-Look over here too, please.
‪-Over here.
‪-This way. Yes.
‪-Over here, guys.
‪-Look over there too.
‪-How about a winning pose?
‪-One, two, three.
‪Look over here.
‪-What is that?
‪-What's going on?
‪-Hold on.
‪-Who are they?
‪-What's that?
‪-What's this?
‪-Who is that?
‪-Who's that?
‪Hey!
‪You happy, man?
‪What's that punk doing here?
‪Stop.
‪Gosh. What killer weather.
‪What's going on?
‪Gosh, what brings you all the way here?
‪Are you here for a search and seizure?
‪Yes, but it's you and you alone.
‪Take a look.
‪PRO GOLFER PARK'S EX JANG FOUND DEAD
‪PARK WANTED AS LIKELY SUSPECT
‪BODY FOUND ON HOTEL ROOF,
‪PARK SEUNG-JAE TO BE QUESTIONED
‪POLICE INVESTIGATE PARK AS MAIN SUSPECT
‪What are you up to?
‪What do you think?
‪I'm up to official business.
‪SEARCH AND SEIZURE WARRANT
‪Why you…
‪Escort him away.
‪Park Seung-jae, you're under arrest
‪for suspected murder and body dumping.
‪-Stay still.
‪-What?
‪It wasn't me.
‪Didn't Jang Eun-ju go into hiding?
‪Did you really kill her?
‪I didn't kill her.
‪Let go of me!
‪-Come quietly.
‪-It wasn't me!
‪Hey, you. Hold on a minute.
‪Ms. Cheon had a message for you.
‪"Congratulations
‪on your most monumental fall."
‪Get going.
‪-Let's go.
‪-It wasn't me!
‪I didn't do it!
‪We should go.
‪Hey! It wasn't me!
‪-This is Ma Gang-uk.
‪-I know.
‪I passed on the message
‪about his monumental fall.
‪You didn't have to report back to me.
‪Bye then.
‪No, wait.
‪I was too preoccupied earlier
‪to hear your answer.
‪How did you know the body was there?
‪Cheon Yeo-ri.
‪I have to go.
‪She has zero manners.
‪How could you do this to me?
‪What were you doing at the place
‪that woman's body was found?
‪PRO GOLFER PARK'S EX JANG FOUND DEAD
‪It's not even one of our branches.
‪You reported it, didn't you?
‪Are you ruining my engagement
‪because yours fell through?
‪Watch what you say in my hotel.
‪Do you think I'm in the mood
‪to watch what I say?
‪Don't you see the big picture?
‪The man you almost married
‪killed someone.
‪Do you think
‪you could live with a murderer?
‪I could if I didn't know.
‪I could if nothing came to light.
‪-Have you lost your mind?
‪-How dare you do this out here?
‪What's the point in fighting Ha-ri?
‪You have my full support,
‪but Ha-ri, Dong-jun,
‪their mom Director Ok,
‪and the executives who favor them
‪will fight hard for the equity.
‪Yes, I'll be more careful.
‪The PR Team will release a statement
‪on Ha-ri's engagement.
‪She's already upset as it is,
‪so don't do anything to provoke her.
‪As for the CL Raymond Hotel business
‪I mentioned last time,
‪at least get in touch with them
‪before rejecting it outright.
‪You didn't bring it up again,
‪so I thought that matter was closed.
‪Actually…
‪Well…
‪Their CEO approached me with an offer.
‪He seems quite eager too.
‪Why don't you hear what he has to say?
‪CORRECTIONAL SERVICES
‪ADVANCING ORDER AND HUMAN RIGHTS
‪He wants me to lie low?
‪He won't help me out then?
‪That's the best we can do for now.
‪So this is what my dad's like.
‪He milked me for all I'm worth
‪with the arranged marriage,
‪but now that he's at a loss,
‪he'll cut ties with me?
‪I've done as he said,
‪and now he thinks I'm some livestock
‪that he grazes, doesn't he?
‪Pardon?
‪Give my dad a message.
‪The cub of a tiger is still a tiger,
‪not some livestock that crawls on command.
‪Don't say that.
‪The assemblyman cares a lot about--
‪Come on.
‪You're his lawyer,
‪so you know what my dad has been up to.
‪Illegal favors, bribery,
‪even trading shares in borrowed names.
‪Getting a freeway to curve
‪right through his land was a work of art.
‪I saved every bit of evidence
‪of his deeds onto a flash drive.
‪Pass him a message.
‪Tell him I'll see what his next move is
‪before I decide what mine will be.
‪According to medical records,
‪the late Jang Eun-ju
‪had psychological issues
‪including symptoms of delusion.
‪EMERGENCY PRESS CONFERENCE:
‪ASSEMBLYMAN PARK, PARK SEUNG-JAE'S FATHER
‪The deceased falsified her background,
‪education, and work experience,
‪practically everything.
‪She approached my naive son
‪with an ulterior motive,
‪and spread groundless rumors
‪to tarnish his reputation.
‪Not only did she use them for blackmail,
‪-she took large sums of money…
‪-We found her body
‪and found clear evidence of her murder.
‪This is how the powerful
‪use the media to change the narrative.
‪At the rate of how this is going,
‪the appeal might not go as planned.
‪He's digging up the victim's past
‪to tarnish her character
‪and change the public's mind.
‪I have to say, he's a pretty great actor.
‪Let's see how powerful your dad is.
‪I won't just sit around myself.
‪Hey, Park.
‪You never called
‪since you got transferred to Jeju Island.
‪I have been in touch.
‪My wedding's this weekend
‪and only you haven't RSVPed yet.
‪-What kind of friend are you?
‪-A wedding?
‪What wedding?
‪I sent an invite ages ago.
‪You didn't even pick up my calls.
‪Oh, my bad. I'll check right away.
‪PARK DO-JUN & YOO HYE-WON,
‪SATURDAY, FEBRUARY 7, 2026
‪CL RAYMOND HOTEL
‪3RD FLOOR, FORÊT NOIRE BALLROOM
‪What even is life?
‪I almost missed my best friend's wedding.
‪-It's in Jeju Island?
‪-Yes.
‪Good for you.
‪Treat it like a special holiday.
‪If you're going to Jeju,
‪you should try Grandma Chun-hui's.
‪Go and try the abalone, steamed conch,
‪sea urchin roe, and fresh sea squirts.
‪Eat all you can and even more for me.
‪Hello, ma'am.
‪This way, please.
‪HOUSE OF HAENA
‪A HAENYEO'S DREAM TAKES FLIGHT
‪AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
‪Hello.
‪Your recent New York collection
‪was a great success.
‪The dress you collaborated on
‪with celebrity Heidi Markle
‪was especially a massive hit.
‪Yes, it was inspired by
‪Korean folk paintings.
‪It's a perfect mix of Asian sensibilities
‪and modern values,
‪and it represents everything
‪that I'm known for.
‪Could you give us a bit more info
‪on the concept of this show?
‪Yes, about that.
‪Why don't you
‪see it for yourself at the show?
‪You'll write lots of nice things
‪about it, right?
‪Thank you. Hae-na Jung is incredibly busy.
‪Shall we head to the show venue now?
‪Thank you for coming.
‪Enjoy the meal as well.
‪Hey, Do-jun.
‪-Gang-uk, you made it.
‪-Hey, man.
‪You got here on time.
‪I'm sorry, work has been crazy lately.
‪You should take it slow, you know.
‪-Congratulations.
‪-Hello, thank you.
‪You can let go now.
‪Yeah, sorry. I'm just nervous.
‪Why don't you spend the night
‪while you're here?
‪I can't. I have to get back.
‪I got a free night at a suite here
‪in the wedding package.
‪I can't use it
‪because I'm leaving for my honeymoon.
‪-Just take the room.
‪-No way. That's too much.
‪-Mr. Park?
‪-Yes. I'm coming.
‪-The room is yours, okay?
‪-Hey.
‪-I put it in your name.
‪-Hey, Do-jun.
‪Spend the night.
‪Congratulations, Do-jun!
‪That punk.
‪Please wait a moment.
‪She's here.
‪Kang Min-hwan?
‪-It's been a really long time.
‪-You recognized me.
‪I was worried you wouldn't.
‪You're the one
‪my grandma wanted me to meet?
‪Yes. I contacted her.
‪Come on.
‪Friends don't have to shake hands.
‪When did you come back to Korea?
‪Last year.
‪I was pretty busy getting things on track.
‪I'm not surprised.
‪How are you doing?
‪I wanted to reach out to you sooner,
‪but I was worried
‪that if I contacted you too often…
‪I'd be reminded of Ji-hwan?
‪That wasn't all it was,
‪but it was part of it.
‪I don't see why either of us
‪should keep mentioning him.
‪What was that my grandma told me about?
‪Was it your idea?
‪Yeah.
‪As you know, our main businesses
‪are leisure and resorts.
‪We may lack in management capabilities
‪when we first branch into hotels.
‪You learn by gaining experience,
‪and that's how you become competitive.
‪That's true.
‪But if we get some help
‪from a global hotel chain,
‪we'd become better known
‪in a shorter period.
‪We started off with a partnership,
‪and we're doing pretty well so far.
‪Once we're sure we're well-recognized
‪and that we have
‪a competitive edge within the market,
‪that's when we end the contract.
‪What do you think?
‪Isn't it a pretty sound deal?
‪That's the choice CL Group made.
‪I'm going to run Reina Hotel my way.
‪It's a flat-out rejection.
‪How about this then?
‪Think of it as visiting a friend's home
‪and spend a night at our hotel.
‪If you head right back to Seoul,
‪your grandmother will think
‪I'm incompetent.
‪We have a deal.
‪"House of Haena"?
‪Hae-na Jung?
‪Do you want to meet her?
‪Her designs aren't my style.
‪Isn't she the best in her field?
‪Hello, sir.
‪Oh, hello.
‪Can we see the dresses for the show today?
‪Oh, the dresses?
‪They're not open to the public.
‪But for you, we can make an exception.
‪This way, please.
‪Sorry, I have to take this.
‪Hello, Kang Min-hwan speaking.
‪Yes.
‪Oh, right.
‪You're drawn to that one?
‪I'm Hae-na Jung.
‪You're CEO Cheon Yeo-ri, right?
‪I wondered about you
‪because you're rarely in the public eye.
‪So this is what you look like.
‪This is a mermaid-style dress
‪inspired by ‪haenyeo,‪ Korean female divers.
‪Haenyeo‪ and the Little Mermaid.
‪That sounds a bit sad,
‪but also nice.
‪"Sad, but also nice."
‪What combination is that?
‪The Little Mermaid was
‪a sad bride who had no choice
‪but to turn to bubbles.
‪I like that it has a story.
‪It feels different from the previous works
‪by House of Haena.
‪The seafood here
‪really is on a different level.
‪By the way, where's Grandma Chun-hui?
‪Pil-dong told me to say hi for him.
‪She comes in sparingly these days.
‪She's been acting strange
‪since her granddaughter lost her job.
‪Maybe that's why.
‪She hasn't been able to dive much either.
‪Why talk about it when it's not good news?
‪Why don't you join me?
‪You eat all you want.
‪MA GANG-UK
‪Why won't anything come up?
‪-Excuse me.
‪-Sure.
‪Yes, this is the front desk.
‪Oh, yes, sir.
‪The Royal Suite?
‪Yes, sir.
‪-Okay, I can confirm your booking.
‪-Great.
‪-I'm sorry you had to wait.
‪-That's fine.
‪Thank you.
‪Yeah, I just checked in.
‪No, I didn't run away. I'm here.
‪Hey, thanks for this.
‪All right. Enjoy your honeymoon.
‪Bye.
‪Am I allowed to stay here on my own?
‪I'm sorry to bother you
‪when I could manage on my own.
‪Not at all.
‪Mr. Kang told me many times
‪to provide you with the best service.
‪Please enjoy your stay.
‪What was that?
‪Do five-star hotels like this
‪get broken into?
‪No, wait.
‪Maybe five-star hotels
‪are more likely targets.
‪Am I being too sensitive?
‪"Seoul, Daejeon, Daegu, Busan,"
‪"Gwanghwamun Love Song,"
‪"Busan Vacance‪…"
‪This just isn't fair.
‪How could they follow me
‪all the way to Jeju Island?
‪Or is it a local ghost?
‪All right.
‪It's so exhausting.
‪What the hell?
‪Who are you?
‪Are you a stalker, not a prosecutor?
‪You're the one who broke into my room!
‪What are you on about?
‪I'm so sorry. It was our mistake.
‪It was all my fault.
‪When you checked in yesterday…
‪The Royal Suite?
‪The CEO called and I just…
‪MA GANG-UK
‪I'm sorry.
‪-I'm really sorry.
‪-It's fine.
‪Did I graze him
‪while moving about in bed last night?
‪Did we make contact?
‪What then? That would be a disaster.
‪Should I ask?
‪Excuse me.
‪Did you and I…
‪-I mean, was there anything physical or…
‪-Why?
‪Are you going to sue me
‪for coming onto you or something?
‪Why would you put it like that?
‪I'm only asking if my hand touched you--
‪Back then, on the mountain that night.
‪You claimed aggravated assault
‪when I grabbed your sleeve.
‪If I say you touched me,
‪you'll accuse me for coming onto you.
‪Besides, what do you take me for?
‪You're not at all my type.
‪I'm asking out of concern.
‪I don't even care what your type is.
‪Sure.
‪I asked out of concern for his well-being.
‪Who cares if he sees ghosts or not?
‪Watch your step when you get on.
‪Oh, no!
‪Watch out!
‪My goodness.
‪Oh, gosh.
‪Yeo-ri!
‪Yeo-ri, are you all right?
‪Oh, yes, I'm fine.
‪-Are you hurt?
‪-I'm okay.
‪-Do you need to see a doctor?
‪-No.
‪-I think he needs…
‪-Why is he taking all the credit?
‪I'm so sorry.
‪I let go of the suitcase
‪to look after my son. I'm sorry.
‪It's fine.
‪-Were you hurt?
‪-No.
‪I'm really sorry.
‪You must've been scared too.
‪-Yes.
‪-It's okay now.
‪-Thank you.
‪-Sure.
‪Say thank you before we go.
‪-Hey--
‪-Good job.
‪Good job with what?
‪I'm thanking you.
‪Yeo-ri could've been badly hurt.
‪Here's a voucher for a free stay.
‪It's a token of my gratitude.
‪You're going way overboard for nothing.
‪I'm not saying this
‪because I want recognition,
‪but I threw myself in harm's way
‪for Ms. Cheon.
‪So why are you going overboard about it?
‪If Yeo-ri gets hurt,
‪it's the same as me getting hurt.
‪If you need anything,
‪call me at any time.
‪CEO KANG MIN-HWAN
‪Hey.
‪I really could've gotten hurt.
‪Thank you.
‪Well, sure.
‪You don't need to thank me anymore.
‪But I would've done the same for anyone.
‪Let's go.
‪Okay.
‪"If Yeo-ri gets hurt,
‪it's the same as me getting hurt."
‪Sir, it was a terrible mistake
‪to check a guest into the wrong suite,
‪but firing someone over it
‪is too harsh a penalty.
‪Both I and this young man
‪will make sure it never happens again.
‪-Please don't fire him--
‪-"Young man"?
‪He's your subordinate.
‪A team has joint responsibility,
‪so when a staff member messes up,
‪-the superior also pays.
‪-Yes, sir.
‪This incident made me see you
‪in a different light.
‪Our company has
‪a fairly high bar for promotions,
‪but this has made me start to have doubts.
‪What if this wasn't a mistake,
‪but your limit?
‪That was the first friend I invited
‪since opening the hotel.
‪How incompetent do you think I looked?
‪You see, that actually hurt my pride.
‪I'm sorry, sir.
‪Could you find it within yourself
‪to show some mercy and lenience?
‪Let's do this then.
‪Resign from our hotel,
‪and I'll find you a job at another one.
‪The same goes for the young man.
‪I'm here to see my granddaughter.
‪She used to work at this company,
‪and she said she'd be here today.
‪-Da-mi, where are you?
‪-Take a seat, ma'am.
‪-We should get someone.
‪-Your grandma's here.
‪Da-mi!
‪We need you to leave.
‪-Da-mi, where are you?
‪-Excuse me.
‪-Where…
‪-Give me a minute.
‪You're Grandma Chun-hui, right?
‪My goodness, aren't you Prosecutor Ma?
‪I was afraid I wouldn't get to see you.
‪What's the matter?
‪Prosecutor Ma.
‪You reported that your granddaughter Da-mi
‪didn't come home last night,
‪but the police thinks
‪she ran away from home?
‪But you remembered her saying
‪before she left
‪that she'd attend the fashion show
‪being held at this hotel,
‪-so you came to look for her?
‪-That's right.
‪She won't answer her phone.
‪I'm dead worried
‪something happened to her.
‪She'd been acting strange
‪the past few days.
‪Did she say anything about meeting anyone?
‪She only said
‪she was going to the hotel
‪to see someone's event.
‪Prosecutor Ma.
‪Will you please find Da-mi for me?
‪Could I take a look around her room?
‪Come on in.
‪Take all the time you need.
‪I'll get you something to eat.
‪Gosh, why did the car brake
‪all of a sudden?
‪I'm sorry, ma'am.
‪It's fine.
‪I have a favor to ask.
‪Skim through it fast. Thanks.
‪Can I see the footage
‪from that camera too?
‪You've been at it for an hour.
‪Didn't you say you wouldn't be long?
‪You acted so magnanimous earlier,
‪that I could call at any time.
‪Can we go forward from here?
‪A bit more.
‪More.
‪Go further.
‪Stop!
‪Right there.
‪Rewind just a bit from here.
‪Just a bit. A bit more.
‪That's it. Now skim right ahead.
‪Keep going. Keep on going.
‪More. A bit more.
‪A bit more.
‪Right there.
‪Zoom into that shot.
‪Our cameras don't have that function.
‪They don't?
‪This isn't one of your offices.
‪Can you please leave now?
‪I saw all I needed. Thank you.
‪Sure.
‪I located the taxi
‪and emailed you the details.
‪I asked the local police
‪for assistance too.
‪Can you tell me what's going on?
‪All right.
‪I'll call you back in a bit.
‪This is where the taxi dropped her off.
‪What is that woman doing down there?
‪-Excuse me?
‪-Oh, shoot.
‪Life is very precious
‪if you think about it.
‪Huh?
‪What are you doing here this time?
‪Did you have to make me jump like that?
‪What are you doing here on your own,
‪looking all gloomy?
‪It's nothing.
‪Don't mind me.
‪Just go on your way.
‪SPOOKY IN LOVE
‪I just can't seem to make sense of it.
‪How did you know where to go?
‪It wasn't a coincidence, was it?
‪Do you still see ghosts or something?
‪You know that when it comes to succession,
‪it's not just about blood.
‪You want me to step down
‪when I indicted him?
‪I swear on my life
‪that I'll help you take over Reina.
‪If I reveal the truth about that,
‪Grandma will give up the idea
‪of letting you take over.
‪I don't plan to wait for long.
‪Dispel the rumor yourself,
‪with a marriage.
‪It's Prosecutor Ma Gang-uk.
‪-Ms. Cheon?
‪-Who are you?
‪We shared a bed.
‪-They must have a thing.
‪-They're playing hard to get.
‪Why does he have my gloves?
‪I did that without my gloves?
‪Do you happen to see things
‪you weren't able to before?
‪He's in my home right now.
‪He came all the way to my home.
‪Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim