So it's Sister Nuoyi.
What brings you here today?
To play at my little casino.
I'm not here for you.
I'm here for him.
Sister Nuoyi.
How about this?
This truckload of cash
is a gift from our casino to you.
Why don't we leave it at that for today?
I heard Miss Sun's fiancé
is the God of Gambling's disciple.
I'm here to challenge him.
How about this:
Let's have a gamble.
If I win,
I'll trouble Miss Sun
to transfer this casino to Mo Panbi's name.
If you happen to win,
I can give you a casino too.
Or is there something else you want?
Let me thank my Sister Nuoyi first.
But Sister Nuoyi,
compared to a casino,
I'd rather you help my fiancée
expose this fraud who claims to be the God of Gambling's disciple.
If you're not really the God of Gambling's disciple,
then you're deceiving my fiancée.
I'll have to rip your tongue out.
Wait, why am I being dragged into this again?
Don't go.
Mo Panbi.
Who is your fiancée?
Aren't you just trying to
get our Sun family's casino?
Fine.
Let's have a bet today.
But if you lose this time,
from now on,
don't ever bring up that so-called engagement again.
Hurry, go, I—
What are you doing?
If you help me win today,
I'll agree to any condition you want.
I told you,
I'm fine with running errands or odd jobs,
but I won't gamble.
If you help me win today,
I'll give you the entire Golden Street.
I really can't.
Good luck.
I've heard
that your Hao Jinjin hates gambling the most.
You probably don't want her to know
that you're at the casino today, right?
Look,
Mo Panbi's people
will definitely send out all the photos tonight.
They'll spread them everywhere.
Tomorrow, all of Laiwan will know you were at the casino.
Including Hao Jinjin.
Miss Sun,
you're setting a trap for me.
What those reporters will write
is out of my control.
But,
if you help me win this round,
I can make all the reporters keep quiet.
Dad
There are still survivors from the previous cruise ship explosion.
Didn't they say everything had been taken care of?
This wasn't supposed to happen.
But a few bodies were eaten by fish in the sea.
It's normal that they couldn't be found.
I didn't expect this.
I didn't expect it.
No matter what method you use,
this person
cannot be allowed to live in Laiwan.
Yes.
Get up.
Sign this.
Then you can leave.
Okay.
This...
This is an agreement to sell my organs!
Since you refuse to sign,
Guards!
Take him back to the death cell.
I'll sign!
I'll sign, I'll go!
Go ahead, what do you want to play?
You just won so much money with the dice.
Let's play dice, then.
Are you looking down on me?
Alright.
Then let's play dice, highest number wins.
Miss.
It won't be easy for us to win this time.
You just returned to Laiwan.
If we lose the casino,
it'll be hard to explain to the board.
What do you mean?
Nuo Yi is all about skill.
I'm afraid things don't look good this time.
He's the one I chose.
Win or lose, I'll accept it.
We'll figure something out later.
Yes.
Turns out it's six sixes.
Your turn.
Reveal it, go ahead.
He really pulled it off.
Yes.
What a pity, Sister Nuo Yi.
Sister Nuo Yi didn't get to keep winning this round.
Uncle Pacha, prepare the car.
Take Sister Nuo Yi back.
Yes.
Wait.
What is it?
Sister Nuo Yi, are you going back on your word?
Qian Qian, don't be hasty.
I remember Sister Nuo Yi just said
the loser leaves.
But Sister Nuo Yi didn't lose.
So no one is leaving.
Good luck.
I haven't lost yet.
Some people already want to send me away.
You just got lucky earlier.
When we played for the highest, you rolled six sixes.
How about we play for the lowest this round?
Is Nuo Yi going to use the "Dragon Spits Pearl" move?
"Dragon Spits Pearl" is Nuo Yi's signature skill.
Hardly anyone in Laiwan can do it.
Looks like Lucky is going to lose.
What is "Dragon Spits Pearl"?
"Dragon Spits Pearl" uses centrifugal force
to stack all the dice in a straight line.
This...
That doesn't sound too hard.
Stacking them in a line isn't hard.
The hard part is
the second die from the top.
The second die must show one dot.
Because only the pit for one dot
can support the top die to hang in the air.
So that none of its faces are facing up.
Which means it shows no number.
No number.
Right.
That's why Nuo Yi
chose to play for the lowest.
Because no matter how lucky you are,
it's impossible to get no number.
It's over.
Please.
Why aren't you rolling?
Are you afraid you can't do it?
Let me go.
Let Lucky go.
Jin Jin, why are you here?
They didn't do anything to you, did they?
I'm fine.
I'll be able to go back soon.
You are
gambling.
Jinjin, let me explain.
I...
I was so foolish.
I even asked you to persuade my dad not to gamble.
Jinjin.
But you’re gambling too.
Please, let me explain.
Give me back my glasses.
You want your glasses?
Finish this round with me.
You’re forcing me.
That’s better. Good.
You lost.
How is that possible?
Even with good luck, you still rolled "Dragon Spitting Pearl."
Not only is the top die still spinning,
but all the ones below have one facing up.
At best, it's just a tie.
Really?
How could this happen?