Manman
Jinjin, hurry and come with me.
Quick, quick, quick!
Let go of me.
Why are you following me?
Go find your Miss Sun.
No time to explain, just come with me.
You're in danger right now.
I just saw him slip you something.
I told you,
my business is none of your concern.
What's wrong?
Jinjin, let's go!
What are you doing?
Take your dirty hands off me.
Remove your dirty hands.
Is he bothering you again?
Now get out of here.
Did you hear me?
Someone, come here!
Why should I leave?
Can't I spend money here?
Spend money?
Did I hear that right? You came to spend money?
Here, even a single bottle of wine—
It costs over ten thousand dollars.
Even if you work hard for a whole month,
could you even afford half a bottle?
Besides,
this club is members-only.
How did you get in?
I remember now.
Our working-class friend here
is best at sneaky, shady things.
Isn't that right?
Let me tell you,
get out of here.
Otherwise,
I'll have security take you to the police station.
You can stay there for a few days.
Who ends up in the station isn't certain yet.
Jinjin,
I just saw him have someone drug you.
He wants to hurt you.
That's not true.
Jinjin, don't listen to his nonsense.
Impossible.
I'll drink it right now to show you.
Let's see if he really put something in it.
If I pass out in a bit
or if anything happens to me,
don't worry about me, just run.
How is that possible?
I clearly saw it just now.
Do you think I'm like you,
someone with a filthy mind?
I think you just came here to mooch some drinks.
Am I right?
Let me tell you, Jinjin,
this person is rotten to the core.
I'll help you kick him out.
Throw him out for me.
Jinjin, trust me.
I really saw it just now.
He drugged you.
Jinjin, hurry and leave!
You can serve the drinks now.
What should we do with this guy?
Should I just dig a hole and bury him?
Go ahead and dig, aren't you tired?
Why not just throw him into the sea?
Hurry up.
That's true.
Wait.
Miss Sun.
I want this person.
Boss Peng Sai told us to handle this.
I said I want this person.
Which word didn't you understand?
I wouldn't dare.
I'll leave right away.
Miss Sun, untie me quickly.
I need to find Jinjin.
I...
You want me to let you go?
Fine.
But you owe me a favor.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Come out.
Thank you.
Jinjin, please be safe.
Jinjin, please don't let anything happen to you.
Hey, Sister Nuoyi,
your underground casino is really hard to find.
Let me tell you,
that guy needs to disappear from Laiwan for me.
I don't care if he ends up feeding the fish in the sea
or getting fat in the mountains,
either way is fine.
Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about that worker named Haoyun.
No.
Are you playing dumb with me?
You were the one who wanted to protect him before.
You wouldn't let me touch him.
Now he's getting close with Sun Yiqian.
If this keeps up,
I'll be kicked out of the Sun Group.
Sister, look,
once I take over the Sun Group,
I'll keep my promise as I said before
and let you run the casino.
Since you want to protect him,
then help me become friends with him.
That's fine too.
Right.
That guy is now with Sun Yiqian
developing a relationship at the club.
As long as you help me win him over,
the promise I made to you before
will still be fulfilled.
Young Master Mo Panbi,
I always thought we were just business partners.
Are you telling me how to do things?
No, no, Sister,
I wouldn't dare.
Well then...
Well, sis,
Well then,
You, you drink first.
I won't bother you anymore.
Why did you tear it up?
Boss, didn't you say you didn't want to go?
Now even you want to tell me what to do?
No.
Okay.
Come on, come on.
President Peng Sai,
I really can't drink anymore.
It's okay, this wine tastes terrible.
Just one last small glass.
Just the last small glass.
Alright, here we go.
Come on, Jin Jin, you can do it!
Well done.
That's great.
How do you feel?