KAMEN RIDER
There's no night that never ends.
I thought it was a beautiful thing.
Will you accept this?
But...
I want to believe that beautiful thing.
You promised not to call me.
You shouldn't have come so suddenly.
It's the same as always.
You shouldn't do something that's useless.
What?
That's what you mean?
I'm sorry.
Is that what you mean?
That's what I meant.
You should go home.
I see.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Haruka Kiba, Ren's childhood friend.
I'm Makoto Sugawara.
Sorry for the sudden visit.
Please introduce me again.
Sorry.
Please let me do that.
I forget about the guests.
Good night.
Sugawara, see you.
I'm sorry for the time.
I was going to introduce you properly.
Yes.
I want to talk to you slowly.
Are you going to sleep?
I don't care.
Then let's go to the bedroom.
Yes.
Good night.
See you tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
The End
Makoto-san, did you find anything?
No, nothing.
If it's a love problem, I'll ask you.
What's that?
Even if I did, I wouldn't tell Matsumoto-kun.
What?
You should have told me earlier.
Makoto.
Yes.
There are too many cases of this kind.
I can't suggest anything.
What?
With this system, the vanguard doesn't trust us.
I'm sorry.
I'll ask them right away.
Will you support Matsumoto?
The reason you noticed here is because you put it on the wall just in case.
Yes, I understand.
I'll come back early today.
I have something to tell you.
Just the two of us.
If you have something to say,
go and be my friend.
Are you sure you want to be my friend?
I said be my friend.
Do you know
that Chief Odagiri is the real Gokudo?
Chief Odagiri is the real Gokudo?
Yes?
You're being so hasty.
Or are you in a hurry?
Ta-da!
I can't believe my boss was a Yakuza.
I'm scared I can't work under him.
Makoto-senpai,
even if you know that I'm the real Gokudo boss,
will you understand?
Is this a threat?
No!
This is a sincere request from my subordinate.
Chief Odagiri,
please stop working.
I understand your request.
But I need some time.
Time?
I want a week of internal investigation.
I'm bored of being so calm.
Please let me finish this quickly.
Otherwise,
I wonder what Makoto-senpai will think of me.
Makoto-senpai,
you're a bad guy.
What?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Welcome back.
I made you dinner.
I won't be back for a while.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
I can't tell you now.
But I'll explain it to you someday.
So,
please wait.
I understand.
It's okay.
I believe in you.
Thank you.
I see.
You're brave enough to threaten me.
I want to get away from Sugawara
and turn my attention to you.
Ren,
you've changed.
The Odagiri I know,
you're rational, cold-hearted,
and you're good at business.
I'm glad you're happy.
You're rational, cold-hearted,
and you're good at business.
I see.
I'll see what I can do.
I have to do something about this.
Hey,
do you have any photos of your opponent?
I'm Aina Kawata from the same club.
This girl?
I'm sorry.
I was a little lost.
Did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
Thank you.
I want to protect
Sugawara
and only her.
Are you ready?
Let's start the meeting.
Yes.
Kawatari,
can you get the time for the meeting ready by tomorrow?
Hey, answer.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Will you take it?
The next day
Thank you.
It's all thanks to you.
Are you really going to quit?
What?
Did you say something?
It's nothing.
Kawatari,
I have something important to tell you.
What?
Just the two of you?
I thought you forgot
the promise you made.
The manager is not as usual,
but I thought you were too desperate to be honest.
If you don't do anything, you'll be fired.
What?
You'll be in full investigation.
The company will ask you for a hearing.
Wait.
What's going on?
You can't just fire me.
You're right.
That's right.
As long as there's no reason to fire me.
This is the reason.
This is the evidence of the information you posted on social media.
You used your account to post information and photos of your company's expenses repeatedly.
In addition,
you've also confirmed many other employees' death threats.
No.
This is strange.
It's not me.
From now on, you'll be contacted by the company.
You'll be waiting at home until then.
Wait a minute.
You won't admit this?
It's not over yet!
What?
You were attacked by a red glasses?
By me?
You're giving yourself a reward?
This is the earring I was looking for.
This project is made for you.
No!
I was fooled by the director.
The director is useless.
I knew who he was.
I'm going to be erased.
Don't be fooled by everyone!
I have evidence!
Are you serious?
You can't do that.
Why don't you believe me?
I'm not guilty.
You're a useless man with no technique.
I didn't mean to steal it.
I want to throw it away.
Is this your true self?
The picture of the earring is also a fake.
No.
This is real.
You're a fuxxing fuxxing bitch.
You only think of yourself as a tool by looking down on others.
You're breaking the law.
Kawatani.
Pack your things and go home.
Right now.
Go back to your business.
I'm home.
It's all over.
Sugawara.
I'm going to be a good son to you.
I'm sorry.
Will you stay with me from now on?
I'm sorry I turned you around.
It's okay.
It's not right now.
Please tell me...
...about Nagiri.
No matter what happens...
...I love you.
Welcome home.
I don't think...
...it's possible for me to live without you.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I can stand it tonight.
I've always wanted to touch you like this.
I'm sorry.
I was just a little worried.
I wonder if we're dating.
I like you.
I've always been more than I thought.
Yes.
I'm relieved.
I'm happy.
I like you.
Makoto.
I love you too.
I'm saved this time.
I've been able to collect that much evidence.
It seems that she was very resentful.
She was self-pitying.
Haruka.
Thank you very much.
However, you can't avoid the fact that you're in the house.
Yes.
I'm going to tell you everything soon.
I'm sorry.
Makoto?
Did something happen?
No.
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Makoto?
I finally got out.
I'm sorry.
Mom is next to Makoto.
When I was a kid.
I'm called Tora.
I'm here.
If you're close to him.
I don't want to be taken away by him.
Please help me.