[Deep Lurk]
[Episode 10]
My dad will be fine.
He's fine in Shanghai.
Why would anything happen to him?
You are bad guys.
You're lying to me.
You must be lying to me.
My father...
My father is definitely okay.
It can't be true.
You're lying to me.
Mi Lan.
You have to stay strong.
If your father knew
you were like this, he wouldn't
be at peace even in the afterlife.
That mole works fast.
We just found out Myna's real identity
and Yun Hongshen's whereabouts,
and the Japanese already sent assassins.
Sometimes it's not that the mole is too skilled;
it's that our confidentiality measures are lacking.
I'm sorry, Sir.
That was my oversight.
But judging by how eager
the Japanese are to eliminate Yun Hongshen,
it seems he's not our enemy.
But why are the Japanese
so desperate to take him out?
Does he have something
that could threaten them?
He said he could
find the person who killed Myna.
He has some leads.
No wonder.
When will he contact you again?
Once we lift the pursuit orders against him
and stop the surveillance of the Yun family.
Right now, we're under
immense pressure from all sides.
In the end, we'll probably have to compromise.
But if we surrender
every time someone threatens us,
it'll ruin the reputation
of the NBIS.
Don't worry, Sir.
I'll figure out a way to force Yun Hongshen to reveal himself.
[Morgue]
Dad...
From now on,
I'll be all alone.
I'm scared.
Wake up.
Please wake up.
Dad,
wake up.
Please wake up.
Wake up.
Wake up, Dad.
Wake up!
Li Liang disappeared for about twenty minutes,
Liu Chengdong for 15 minutes,
and Yu Peng for half an hour.
During that time,
Yun Hongshen and Yun Hongqi
were ambushed near Deyang Road.
But we still can't determine who the mole is.
I'm sorry, Chief.
I failed my duties.
It's not that you failed;
you were just too impatient.
Ever since you started suspecting those three,
you've been pressuring them.
Of course, they noticed.
And once they noticed, you lost the upper hand.
Your criticism is fair.
I know I've been feeling guilty
over Qu Wenzhi's defection,
but this can't all be pinned on me—
I bear some responsibility too.
The more critical the situation,
the calmer we need to remain.
It seems this mole
is far more cunning than we anticipated.
You sent her home?
Well, that's just great.
Now we've lost our hiding place.
We can't go back home either.
So, where should we go now?
There's only one place left we can go.
Come in.
Uncle Yang.
Alright.
Get some rest early.
Young Masters,
this way, please.
Okay.
This way, please.
[Skynet Operation]
Muzhi,
I really don't know how to bring this up.
Come in.
Uncle Yang,
Hongshen.
Come, have a seat.
What's wrong?
Why aren't you asleep yet?
I couldn't sleep.
Uncle Yang, did my father
ever mention someone called "the Viscount" to you?
I know of him.
The night the Viscount died,
I found something in a locker
at the train station.
A very strange family letter?
How did you know?
Your father and I made a pact:
if anything happened
to either of us,
we would entrust everything to the other.
Your father had everything planned,
so he told me everything in advance.
My father was always thorough.
If I hadn't been so arrogant back then,
thinking I could handle everything myself...
Hongshen,
you're still young.
Your father once
walked the same path you're on now.
But Uncle Yang,
there's one thing
I can't understand.
Why did my father reveal
Myna's situation to the French?
Your father had been tracking Kunwu
for five years, yet he had no leads.
Then suddenly,
Kunwu reappeared.
Your father suspected that
Kunwu was orchestrating
a massive conspiracy.
But everything happened so quickly,
and your father had very limited information.
He wasn't sure what this conspiracy was.
So he shared what he knew
to the French.
hoping to use them
to probe the Japanese reaction.
Based on the Japanese response,
my father could adjust his next move.
If I hadn't acted impulsively,
my father wouldn't have died.
Maybe that conspiracy would have already been thwarted by now.
Hongshen,
the real culprits behind Muzhi's death
were Japanese and Kunwu.
You shouldn't blame yourself anymore.
Uncle Yang, I understand.
Regret won't change anything.
What I need to do now
is finishing my father's mission
and walking the path he couldn't complete.
Earlier, you seemed hesitant to tell me something.
Is there something difficult
that you don't know how to bring up?
Could it be that
you've already deduced that
Kunwu might be hiding in the NBIS?
Uncle Yang,
the best course of action right now
is for me to infiltrate the NBIS
and find the real culprit.
Uncle Yang,
I know you're worried about my safety.
but the situation is dire,
and I am currently the most suitable candidate.
That's why you hesitated, isn't it?
You're already caught in this web,
and you've obtained the codebook,
which means that person has been watching you closely.
You're right.
You're indeed the best fit for this mission.
But you've just returned to Changsha,
and in such a short time,
there have already been two assassination attempts on your life.
I... I just
can't bear to put you in more danger.
But no matter how dangerous,
someone has to do it.
I've made up my mind.
Hongshen.
On behalf of the hundreds of thousands of people in Changsha,
thank you.
Uncle Yang,
I am Chinese.
Good boy.
Now, sit down.
This is what your father entrusted to me.
If you have time, take a look.
All the information your father
wanted to give me is in here.
By the way, have there been any breakthroughs
in cracking Myna's codebook?
Not yet.
But don't worry,
I'll try to speed up the process.
I know this is difficult for you,
but the situation is urgent.
you must give it your all.
Yes.
Dad,
I need to decipher Myna's intelligence.
Please help me.
It's just a maze he built.
Once you figure out the direction,
you'll find your way out.
But Dad,
I'm already lost.
I can't find the way.
Then think differently.
For example,
if you want to hide a leaf,
what's the best way to do it?
To hide a leaf?
The best way to hide a leaf
is to hide it in a forest.
The book you have in your hands is the forest.
The code is the hidden leaf.
You just have to find it.
You don't need to rush back to work.
Take a good rest at home.
Come back when you're feeling better.
I don't want to be alone at home.
When everything quiets down,
I just start thinking about Dad, Mom, Grandma,
and my little brother.
Alright, alright.
If you don't want to be alone,
come to the hospital.
There are so many people here to keep you company.
You'll be okay.
Thank you.
Miss Mi Lan,
we meet again.
Ms. Wen,
what can I do for you?
Please come with us.
Miss.
This is a military hospital.
If you want to take anyone,
you need the approval of our director.
We are investigating the cause of Mi Lan's father's death.
There are many things we need to clarify with her.
You can't just do as you...
It's okay.
I am willing to cooperate with the investigation.
Yun Hongqi said,
my father was murdered.
I want to find his killer
and avenge him.
Ms. Wen.
I'm willing to cooperate with the investigation.
As long as we can find my father's killer
and avenge him,
I'll do whatever it takes.
Take her away.
Wen Yeming's car?
Yun Hongshen knows that
investigating Mi Lan is just a normal procedure.
If it were him,
he would do the same.
Mi Lan seems perfectly innocent,
without any flaws.
But the biggest point of suspicion
is that she just happened to
be right by his side at the right time.
And, coincidentally, she's Myna's daughter.
For this,
Yun Hongshen had suspected Mi Lan before.
So, he decided to give Wen Yeming two hours.
Because he's sure that
if Mi Lan was innocent,
then the man who shed tears for orphans
Wen Yeming, who once cried for the orphans in the shelter,
would never make things difficult for her.
Call Yun Hongqi's lackey
and tell him
we've arrested Mi Lan.
Okay.
Dao.
You're here.
Gangzi,
How's that thing I asked you to take care of?
-It's done.
-Okay.
Don't worry.
Thanks for your hard work.
We're at Uncle Yang's place.
The NBIS doesn't dare to openly cause trouble here.
If you have any issues, you can speak to us directly.
What?
The NBIS took Mi Lan away?
Those bastards!
They're crazy!
Wen Yeming deliberately had Dao inform me.
She's pressuring me.
She wants to know who killed Myna.
Shen,
when did they take Mi Lan?
How long has it been?
She was taken away when we went to the hospital.
You...
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you looking at me?
Young Master, please don't be so anxious.
Shen,
did you just stand by and watch Wen Yeming
take Mi Lan away?
The NBIS
is a monstrous organization!
Dao,
go wait downstairs.
Young Masters,
if there's any issue,
you can negotiate.
Please don't argue.
Don't worry, we won't!
-Hongqi, let me explain.
-Stop.
If you're still going to
talk about your conspiracy theories,
just stop.
Mi Lan is such a kind girl.
What does she have to do
with your ridiculous schemes?
She helped us before.
She risked her life for us.
It's one thing for you to suspect her,
but now you're just watching her die without lifting a finger!
This is just a normal investigation procedure.
She won't be in any danger.
No danger?
What do you mean by no danger?
Is it no danger
as long as she's alive?
Hongqi, be rational.
I am being rational!
But you've really let me down.
Hongqi, where are you going?
I'm going to save her.
You can't go.
Why?
If you want to get me killed,
then go ahead.
Why did you hide Yun Hongshen and Yun Hongqi
at your place?
I...
They had nowhere to go,
so I let them stay with me.
When did you find out your father had died?
Yesterday.
Someone tried to kill Yun Hongshen and Yun Hongqi.
We escaped together.
It was Yun Hongqi who told me.
After your father returned to Changsha,
did he contact you?
No.
When was the last time
you saw your father?
Last year.
Around March.
Explain yourself.
What do you mean by saving Mi Lan is killing you?
Hongqi, calm down.
Listen to me.
Wen Yeming has a reason to suspect Mi Lan.
If you don't let her clear things up,
and just rush to save her without thinking,
that's just a temporary fix.
As long as they're suspicious of Mi Lan,
they can keep investigating her.
If this time doesn't work, there'll be another time.
And if that doesn't work, there'll be the next time.
Unless you hide her somewhere
where they'll never find her.
Go on.
If Mi Lan is innocent,
this is just a routine inquiry.
She'll be out soon.
Wen Yeming is the one who took her.
I believe Wen Yeming won't use torture on her,
so you don't have to worry about that.
I noticed that
since you came back,
your attitude toward Wen Yeming
has changed.
What makes you so sure
that Wen Yeming won't do those things?
Even if you don't believe me,
you should believe Uncle Yang.
He's already looked into Wen Yeming.
Uncle Yang investigated Wen Yeming?
Actually, I didn't want you to get involved,
but I have my reasons too.
I don't want to
sour the relationship with the NBIS.
It would be very bad for my next steps.
The Japanese are determined to kill me,
and if I offend the NBIS
at this crucial moment,
I'd be surrounded on all sides,
not knowing what to do.
I really can't understand it.
What has Mi Lan done to deserve this?
To me, Mi Lan's just a poor soul.
She's got an information trafficker for a father,
and on top of that, she helped you and me out of kindness.
So why is everyone suspecting her?
That day near the Boya Tea House,
you were late because you were saving
Yun Hongshen and Yun Hongqi, right?
I really didn't know someone would die.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I'm sorry.
Mi Lan's reactions and behavior
make perfect sense for who she is.
She suddenly lost her father,
and then for some reason, was brought into the NBIS.
She was sad,
angry,
scared,
desperate,
and on the verge of breaking down.
Yet, for some reason that she doesn't want to talk about,
she's trying to be strong.
Her expression, her tone,
and even her breathing
were all so spot on.
Just like how she appeared
right next to Yun Hongshen.
It's like she was perfect,
and yet something didn't add up.
Why did you save them?
Yun Hongqi saved me.
I don't think they're bad people.
When did he save you?
Just a few days ago.
You've known them for such a short time,
and yet you're calling them by name?
That means your relationship is more than just casual.
Tell me,
what's your relationship with them?
Answer my question!
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
Just kill me.
I don't want to live anymore.
Treat her wound.
Watch her closely.
Don't let her kill herself.
Yes, Madam.
Actually, Wen Yeming took Mi Lan
for another reason.
She's trying to force me to hand over the killer of Myna.
So,
Mi Lan is suffering
because of us.
So what do you plan to do?
I'll have to speak up eventually,
but not today.
Hongqi, don't worry.
I can handle this.
How is Mi Lan?
Don't worry.
I won't let her die.
You really don't need to do this.
I genuinely want to cooperate with you.
So, you've been following me and Director Ling
to lay the groundwork for future cooperation?
We don't need to keep obsessing over past matters.
What's important is the future.
I don't trust you.
How could you possibly know
who killed Myna?
You don't need to trick me.
I'll tell you eventually,
but not today.
To be honest,
I not only know who killed Myna,
I also have what once was his.
I have the codebook.
Hand it over.
That's impossible.
Then you're not leaving here today.
Even if I'm willing to hand it over, would you dare take it?
Your organization isn't safe.
I've already survived two assassination attempts
by the Japanese.
Those were orchestrated by the traitor in your ranks.
Don't think I don't know.
Chief.
Yun Hongshen.
This is Chief Ke.
Hello, Chief Ke.
I am Yun Hongshen.
I've heard about you from my father.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Please, have a seat.
Your father
was once quite a famous figure.
What a pity.
Fate's cruel.
I overheard outside
that you were talking about Myna's codebook.
How can I believe you have it?
Before Myna died,
he was staying in Room 302 in Shengxing Inn.
You can take my portrait to the owner
and have them confirm it.
You say you have the codebook,
but what about the cipher key?
The Japanese took it.
Have you seen that person?
Chief Ke,
you should be well aware
cooperating with me will be a win-win situation.
You're hesitating to agree
because you think I'm a threat.
Both the NBIS and you
are concerned about losing face.
So,
I'm here today to show some humility.
Let's take a step back.
We don't necessarily have to cooperate with you.
Even without you,
I can still retrieve the intelligence.
Of course.
I strongly believe that.
But it will
waste more of your time.
So, what's your purpose for coming back to Changsha?
About that,
even if I tell you, you won't believe me.
Just investigate it yourself.
Once you get to the bottom of it,
you'll see my sincerity.
Don't get too arrogant.
Even if this ends up going to the Chairman,
you still have to hand over the codebook.
If you don't hand it over,
it proves you're hiding something.
How about this?
Here's my offer of sincerity.
Lift the surveillance on the Yun family
and cancel the warrants for the two brothers.
How's that?
That's very sincere.
However,
Mi Lan has to be released as well.
Myna's codebook is encrypted.
She'll be a big help in cracking the code for me.
No problem.
My sincerity is on the table.
I hope to see your sincerity soon.
[Bureau of Investigation and Statistics]
You tortured her?
That's a stupid, disgraceful tactic.
I would never stoop that low.
Then why is she in this state?
She refused to say anything.
Maybe she was afraid she wouldn't hold out and tried to end it herself.
Thank you for sparing her.
Goodbye.
Master,
good news.
Your chance to get even is here.
What are you talking about?
Yun Hongqi.
Look,
The ship transporting goods to Shanghai is back.
This is from the Shanghai Daily a few days ago.
[The Bank of France transferred its reserve funds to the China Reserve Committee in support of the Greater East Asia Co-Prosperity Sphere]
I've waited so long for this day.
That's what
they call karma—
it always comes back around.
[Military Hospital]
Hongqi.
Don't worry.
Mi Lan's colleagues will take good care of her.
She doesn't need care right now.
What she needs is a sense of security.
She's terrified.
Hongqi.
Now that the NBIS has lifted the warrants against us,
we can't delay Dad's funeral any longer.
Yes.
[Yun Residence]
Muzhi.
You're back home.
My son.
Look at this.
Yun Muzhi—selling out his country for glory.
You'd all better watch your backs from now on.
Give me one. I want a copy.
He colluded with the Japanese.
A total traitor.
-Give me one.
-What's this?
Here.
Folks!
Come and take a look!
Here.
You'd better be careful from now on, alright?
Yun Muzhi was a big traitor.
[Xiangjiang Girls' School]
Listen up, everyone!
Everyone in Changsha!
Yun Muzhi sold out his country,
colluding with the Japanese.
He was a big traitor!
Listen, everyone in Changsha!
Yun Muzhi was a traitor!
Take a look,
see it for yourselves!
Everyone, listen!
Fellow citizens of Changsha, listen up!
I'm warning you,
this is a school.
Don't spread nonsense here.
Yun Muzhi colluded with the Japanese,
selling out his country.
He was a traitor!
Everyone, look at the newspapers you're holding—
Yun Muzhi's betrayal is all over it.
Stick more posters over there.
Alright.
Folks,
come take a look!
[Stone Tablet Shop]
Yun Muzhi sold out his country.
You'd better be careful from now on.
Yun Muzhi,
that traitor!
What are you saying?
What are you talking about?
Who's this?
Isn't he one of Yun Muzhi's family members?
What did you say?
They say bad apples spoil the bunch.
Are you a traitor too?
Of course he is!
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
Stop talking nonsense.
Are you looking for a beating?
I'll knock your teeth out!
Go ahead, read the papers.
Your Yun family sold gold to the Japanese.
If that's not treason, what is it?
Watch your mouth!
Let me tell you,
Listen up—
tear all of this down right now.
Got it?
If I catch you again,
your mother won't even recognize you when I'm done with you!
I won't tear it.
Tear it right now.
I just won't tear it.
Will you tear it down or not?
No way!
In broad daylight,
you want to kill me to silence me?
All the evil things your family did
will come back to haunt Yun Hongqi sooner or later!
Get him!
Beat him up!
You just wait!
I will!
Let's go.
Aunt.
Trust me.
One day,
Muzhi will receive the recognition he deserves.
Muzhi never cared about that.
Look at this tree.
Muzhi planted it
the day he left home.
But now,
the tree remains...
But he's gone.
[Family Ancestral Hall of the Yun Clan]
[Tomb of the Late Yun Muzhi and Du Jiayan]
Dad,
I hope you can go to a new world,
one without war.
There,
you can be a poet,
wandering the world freely.
Uncle Yang,
where is that batch of gold?
I can only tell you this—
the gold has gone to where it should be,
and it will eventually serve the war effort.
But for now, I can't say more,
because too many people are involved.
If it gets exposed,
many lives will be at risk.
But Hongshen, you must know that
before your father did this,
he had already set aside his name and fortune.
History will give him
a fair judgment in the end.
By the way,
how are things going with the NBIS?
Although they've
lifted the manhunt and surveillance on me,
it won't be easy
to earn their true trust.
I think it's time
to give them a little gift to break the ice.
You mean
the person who killed Myna?
You must have some idea in your mind.
He smokes Punch cigars—
those are very expensive,
not something just anyone can afford.
So,
he must be from the upper class,
someone with a good social standing.
Uncle Yang.
Qi.
Have a seat.
How's your grandma?
Is she asleep?
She's become so much
thinner all of a sudden.
You two should
spend more time with her
and try to comfort her a bit.
Oh, by the way,
tomorrow night,
there's a fundraising gala at the Changsha Hotel.
Do you two want to go?
Of course we should go.
The killer
might be invited too.
Uncle Yang,
I want to find him.
But
rumors about your father are flying everywhere now.
I'm afraid that if you two go,
you'll be mocked by many people.
Our Yun family
has never been afraid of rumors.
The more they spread,
the more we should go.
Good,
now that's the spirit of the Yun family.
I'll send someone with the invitation
over to you this afternoon.
Come in.
[Folder]
Sir,
Yun Hongshen contacted me.
He said
he found the killer of Myna.
He's someone from the upper class
who smokes Punch cigars.
He suggests
we attend tomorrow night's fundraiser
to take a chance.
You should go for me.
Me?
That doesn't seem appropriate.
If someone has to go,
it should be the deputy station chief going on your behalf.
You're going there on official business,
so there's nothing wrong with that.
Zhu won't mind.
Alright then.
I'll go.
There's something I need to talk to you about.
What is it?
I want Yun Hongshen to join the NBIS.
But there are still many doubts about him.
How can people like us
be totally clean?
If you stay in the dark for too long,
you're bound to get some dust on you.
I know what you're thinking.
He always got ahead of you,
making you lose face.
But right now, during the Anti-Japanese War,
we really need someone like him.
He's not only smart
but also unconventional.
He's a perfect candidate for an undercover agent.
I understand.
Don't worry.
I'll get along with him.
Of course,
smart people like him are never going to stay put.
Keep an eye on him for me.
Yes, Sir.
Everyone's code
has traces of their past selves.
What are you doing,
up so late with a suitcase?
I'm having trouble cracking Myna's code.
I want to check out his things
and see if I can get some inspiration.
Those are someone else's things.
It's impolite to look through them
without permission.
Well,
desperate times call for desperate measures.
Just don't break anything.
Don't worry, I'll be careful.
How's Mi Lan?
Is she feeling better?
It's been so chaotic these past couple of days.
I almost forgot about her.
Here's what we'll do:
After you've looked through this tonight,
I'll return it to Mi Lan tomorrow.
After all, this is the last thing
her father left for her.
Don't worry.