[Deep Lurk]
[Episode 18]
I have a friend.
She's a fan of Miss Li.
Miss Li?
You mean Li Miaohan, right?
Exactly.
So,
Chairman Zong, I was hoping you could help me
to meet her.
Hongshen,
if I may be so bold to ask,
is the friend of yours
a man or a woman?
A woman.
She's simply a fan of Miss Li, nothing more.
I see.
It's your girlfriend, isn't it?
Chairman,
she's a friend of my brother.
I've heard it.
Young Master Yun has been quite taken with a certain young lady recently.
I suppose you're trying to help your brother out, hmm?
Let's not talk about that.
My brother
happens to be busy tonight.
Since I'm free anyway,
I was wondering if you might be available.
Of course.
I'll give Miss Li a call right away.
-Please wait here for a while.
-Okay.
Please, help yourself.
Alright, thank you.
Hello?
Is that Miss Li?
This is Zong Fang.
Oh, come on.
Can't I contact you without having a specific reason?
It's like this.
Young Master Yun's girlfriend
is actually a fan of yours, Miss Li.
She was hoping...
Miss Li, you're certainly quick to respond.
Chairman,
if Miss Li would do me the honor,
I would like to treat her to a meal.
Miss Li,
if you'd be willing to grace us with your presence,
would you join us for dinner tonight?
Good.
Then it's settled.
See you tonight.
Chairman Zong,
thank you so much.
Please, don't mention it.
If you keep being so formal, we'll start feeling like strangers.
Hongshen.
I won't take up any more of your time then.
Please, carry on with your work.
Alright, let me see you out.
No need.
Let's have a drink together tonight.
Alright.
-See you tonight.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Police business.
Everyone out!
Out! Out! Out!
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
What are you doing?
Quickly! Get out! Hurry, hurry!
Quick! Quick! Quick!
What's going on?
Hurry up, hurry up! Get out quickly!
Let's go!
Mr. Bai.
Captain Tang.
What do you mean by this?
Director Lu's son was just here yesterday.
How can you turn on us so quickly?
Take them away.
You...
He's already got his eyes on us.
He might have also found out
about your relationship with Kawashima.
This dinner tonight
is just to use you to draw out Kawashima.
I'll notify Kawashima right away
and tell him not to show up.
No.
He needs to appear.
You mean to
turn the tables on them?
Rather than letting a venomous snake
watch you intently,
it’s better to pull out its fangs
so it never has the chance to bite you.
Didn't Onitetsu tell us
not to target Yun Hongshen?
After completing tonight's mission,
you and Kawashima
can safely return to Japan.
Really?
[Changsha Hotel]
Here we are.
-Come on.
-Come on, Hongshen.
Not bad.
Then let's have a few more drinks.
No problem. Wait till I drink you under the table.
Miss Li,
you're even more dazzling in person than on screen.
I feel the same way.
I've always felt that making movies
is a waste of my beauty.
Miss Li, you're really too funny.
Miss Mi, you're quite a beauty yourself.
You're a good match for Young Master Yun.
Miss Li, you'd better watch what you say.
Miss Mi Lan isn't used to
such jokes in public.
It's alright.
Miss Li meant no harm.
Okay.
-Come on.
Come on, let's drink.
It's been a while since I climbed a wall.
I'm not sure if I can still do it.
You'll get this.
Come on.
[Seal of Changsha Police Station in Hunan Province]
Young Master.
Young Master,
there are just some ordinary books and ledgers over there.
I didn't find anything special.
Do you think
Bai Qingkui would put something so important
in a place like this?
It's not safe with all these people coming and going.
If you can think of this,
don't you think others would too?
There's an old Chinese saying,
the most dangerous place
is also the safest place.
I see.
This is called "doing the opposite,"
right?
You'd better hurry and search.
I'm waiting to use it.
I'll find it now.
[Ledger]
Miss Li.
I'm so happy to have met you today.
Me too, Miss Mi.
It's been a really pleasant conversation today.
Let's meet again next time.
Thank you both for your generous hospitality.
We'll be taking our leave now.
Alright, let's get together again next time.
Bye-bye.
Let's go,
Miss Mi Lan.
I have some urgent matters to attend to.
I won't be able to take you home.
Let me call a rickshaw for you.
No need.
It's alright.
Wait here.
I'll go call one for you.
Rickshaw.
Mi Lan!
Sir,
could you help me?
Please call an ambulance.
Come here and take care of her.
Thank you.
What's going on here?
Why haven't they caught up yet?
Captain,
that's Second Young Master Yun's car.
It's going so fast.
Has something happened?
Let's go. Follow him.
This sudden accident,
and the hit-and-run vehicle that disappeared in an instant,
made Yun Hongshen realize
that he and Wen Yeming
might have fallen into someone else's trap.
They wanted to lure and capture the assassin,
little did they know
that in others' eyes,
they are also
their prey for a long time.
Thinking about Wen Yeming
going alone to chase after the mysterious killer,
Yun Hongshen
couldn't help but feel anxious.
Hurry!
Catch Wen Yeming,
and you and Keiko can go home.
Are you alright?
What took you so long?
I'm sorry.
I was held up by something.
We heard gunshots from far away.
So it was you.
What's wrong?
Leader Wen,
you're injured.
Captain Tang,
arrest Li Miaohan now.
Call the station
to block all docks and stations.
Don't let Li Miaohan
or that assassin escape.
Do as he says.
Go!
Alright, alright.
Let's go.
Commander,
urgent telegram from Kunwu.
[Yun Hongshen has known the agents' dispatch plan. Please identify the leaks.]
Miss Kudo.
Doctor!
Someone is injured.
Quick, take her to surgery.
Dad!
[Supervision Division]
Next.
ID, please.
Wait a moment.
Next.
Go.
Thank you.
Yes.
I've executed Keiko.
Kawashima is missing.
I think Yun Hongshen's next plan
must be to get the cipher key
from Zong Fang.
Yes.
Who gave you permission to act on your own?
Who?
Speak up!
I'm sorry, Chief.
I was careless.
I'm willing to take full responsibility.
How are you going to take responsibility?
Li Miaohan is dead.
The assassin has disappeared.
Can you bring Li Miaohan back to life,
or can you find that assassin for me?
It was such an important operation.
But you didn't even apply or report it.
You think you're the only capable and skilled one
in the entire Hunan Station, huh?
If you're so capable,
go find the cipher key for me right now.
I promise it won't happen again.
What use is your worthless promise to me?
Tell me,
how are you going to make up for today's losses?
Speak up!
I've discovered a more valuable lead.
But I can't disclose it yet.
Fine.
Yun Hongshen, let me tell you this.
The next time I hear
the words "I can't disclose it,"
I want to see your results immediately.
Do you understand?
Also,
Hunan Station
is not a place for you to show off.
If you don't follow my rules,
you leave immediately.
I can still get the cipher key without you.
Is that clear?
Understood.
What's your opinion on this matter?
This afternoon,
Deputy Chief Zhu was out of my sight
for about half an hour.
You mean the surveillance on Li Miaohan
happened during this half-hour?
Regarding your speculation,
I neither confirm nor deny it.
I can only say that I don't have evidence yet.
Investigate quickly.
Clearly, this mole has gone mad.
He's risking exposure
just to kill those two.
It seems that what they were investigating
has touched a sensitive nerve.
Understood.
And what's the deal with this Zong Fang?
What role does he play in all this?
Don't worry about that.
I'll investigate it thoroughly.
Master,
how was it?
You didn't suffer in there, did you?
He wouldn't dare.
When I have the time,
I'll make Yun Hongqi pay.
Please, just calm down.
You all go ahead first.
Someone broke into your room last night.
Was anything stolen?
Nothing was taken,
but a page is missing.
The shipping record for July 2nd.
Extra! Extra!
Local socialite Li Miaohan mysteriously murdered late at night!
[Li Miaohan was killed late at night. A famous lady falls.]
There's no name of the shipper on this.
It's practically useless.
So we've been working for nothing?
Don't tell Shen yet.
We can't let this be for nothing.
We need to make it useful somehow.
Then, Young Master,
do you have any good ideas?
I was calm when facing him.
I wasn't afraid.
But whenever I think of
the person I'm looking for,
my whole body turns cold.
Shen has always been very brave.
Someone who can scare him
must be an extremely dangerous person.
We need to catch him as soon as possible.
This way, Shen
can get out of this situation.
Will this work?
If that person knows Zong Fang has been exposed,
he will definitely take action.
Then his true colors will be revealed.
Go find Huang for me.
Ask him to find an informant from the NBIS
and let that informant spread a message.
Alright.
Captain,
this is Liu.
When I cast my net,
it was quite heavy.
I was hoping for something good.
Thought today's catch would be decent.
Didn't expect it to be a dead body.
What bad luck.
When was the body
discovered?
[Taichang Restaurant]
Today,
that unfortunate guy fished out of the river
was Bai Qingkui's follower, Liu.
They're really bold,
daring to mess with Bai Qingkui's people.
Has the killer been found?
Come closer.
I heard
someone bribed Liu
to take Bai Qingkui's life.
But Bai Qingkui turned the tables and killed him.
Recently,
Bai Qingkui tried to kidnap the Old Madam of the Yun family.
Although he didn't succeed,
a grudge was formed.
The Yun family can't just let it go.
The Happy House was shut down for rectification.
It was the Eldest Young Master of the Yun family who pulled the strings.
Could Liu have been bribed by him?
It has nothing to do with the Eldest Young Master of the Yun family.
Bai Qingkui has done plenty of despicable things.
I heard
Bai Qingkui got dirt on an old client.
He pushed them too far.
Now they want to silence him.
Come on.
Hello.
Don't say it over the phone.
I'll be right there.
Ling Han?
Just leave.
You can speak here.
If you feel this place isn't suitable,
I can also take you to the NBIS's interrogation room
for a little tour.
No.
I'm not going to the NBIS.
I'll talk.
What should I say?
Why did Bai Qingkui kill Liu?
Liu was disloyal.
He was bought off.
He wanted to kill Boss Bai.
Who bought him off?
I think it was...
Zong Fang.
Yes,
Zong Fang bought him off.
[Zong ships goods via waterway, July 2nd]
Hello.
Shen,
it's me.
I have something important to tell you.
Come out right now.
I'm outside.
Okay.
Give me two minutes.
Hongqi.
Go ahead.
I've found that person.
Who?
The person you've been looking for.
How did you find him?
I've already got Bai Qingkui's ledger.
But that old fox is too cunning.
It only recorded the shipping times and prices.
There were no names of the owners.
Hongqi,
what have you done?
Nothing much.
I just added the character "Zong" to it.
And then?
Then,
I had NBIS informants spread a rumor.
It said that
this Bai Qingkui
had dirt on one of his old clients.
This old client, to protect himself,
had no choice but to silence him.
Ling Han went to Happy House.
He's probably already got
what he wanted.
I never thought
that person would be Ling Han.
No wonder when you were tailing him before,
you were targeted for assassination by the Japanese.
I heard this guy has made quite a few achievements.
He's really good at hiding.
He's hidden himself very well.
What's wrong with you?
After this is over,
do you have any plans?
Are you still going to stay with NBIS?
Who told you to do that?
Who gave you permission?
Who are you to act on your own?
I...
How am I acting on my own?
Isn't this all for you?
The sooner we expose this person,
the earlier you can get out.
Hongqi,
do you think you can fool Ling Han?
Do you know who he is?
Even Ke Jingping has to respect him.
You're no match for him when it comes to mind games.
If you don't want to get me killed,
don't meddle in this anymore.
I...
Hello, Chief.
This is Yun Hongshen.
I have some information
that I need to report to you in person.
Wait a moment.
Director Ling and I have important matters to discuss.
Okay.
It's too late.
Ling Han has already started to act.
Yun Hongshen knew
the only thing he could do now
was to find loopholes in Ling Han's actions.
Fortunately, he had already told Yun Hongqi to back off.
As long as he doesn't act rashly again,
he won't fall into Ling Han's trap.
July 2nd,
the day Qu Wenzhi defected.
Through this record,
it seems we can draw a conclusion.
Zong Fang is the person behind Li Miaohan.
In that case,
Zong Fang's rank in the Japanese spy network in Changsha
must be quite high.
It can even be said to be very high.
However, this character "Zong"
was clearly added afterwards.
It is possible that someone may have framed him.
It's that mole again, right?
Yes.
Our investigation is progressing step by step.
That mole must have sensed danger.
So he bribed Liu to assassinate Bai Qingkui
and then framed Zong Fang for it.
Of course,
the possibility that Zong Fang is a Japanese spy is still high.
Do you have any plans?
My plan is divided into two steps.
They will be carried out simultaneously.
We can verify two people separately.
Step one,
I will find Bai Qingkui's hiding place
and have someone secretly monitor him.
Since the assassination of Bai Qingkui failed,
the mole will definitely try again
to eliminate any future trouble.
Step two,
I will find a way to make Li Miaohan come back to life.
She's not dead.
She was revived.
I believe
Zong Fang
and her lover
will both be very interested in this news.
Very good.
Killing two birds with one stone.
Let's proceed with your plan.
Chief,
I have a request.
Go ahead.
For this operation,
I want to complete it independently.
Actually, there's no need for that.
We just need to let as few as people
know about this action.
You have to leave space
for the mole to take actions.
If we hide it from him,
how can he take actions?
Yeming
is still in the hospital.
Have Yun Hongshen assist you.
This operation is crucial.
We can't be careless.
I know Yun Hongshen
has some issues of his own,
but his abilities are still very strong.
As you know,
people with strong abilities
usually have a bit of a temper.
You should understand this.
I will obey the order.
The operation has two objectives.
First,
to verify Zong Fang's identity.
Second,
to lure and capture Li Miaohan's accomplices.
The entire operation is divided into three phases.
Phase one,
draw the snake out of its hole.
I will find a way
to spread the news that Li Miaohan is still alive.
Phase two,
I will personally go to a private clinic
to pick up a person
and take her to safe house number three.
Phase three, which is also the most important phase,
those interested in Li Miaohan will take action.
And our task is
to capture them alive.
I have a question.
Go ahead.
If Li Miaohan's handler
is absolutely certain that Li Miaohan is dead,
then they won't take any action.
Is there any point in us doing this then?
Even if her handler is certain,
her lover may not necessarily be certain.
Because of Li Miaohan's death,
her lover and her handler
have completely fallen out.
If we can't kill two birds with one stone,
we can at least draw out that assassin.
I hope this operation
can make up for our previous passivity.
I need an accurate name
and a precise lead.
In short, we need to regain the initiative as soon as possible.
-Yes, Sir.
Although Yun Hongqi has been told to back off,
Yun Hongshen still dares not
to be optimistic
that their inaction
will allow them to escape unscathed.
If Ling Han is really the mole,
he wouldn't
give the opponent a chance to fight back.
He must have a backup plan.
Yun Hongshen decides to stir things up.
He needs someone
to distract Ling Han's attention.
Liu Chao.
I've got some good cigarettes.
They're in that drawer.
Go distribute them to the guys.
Yes, Sir.
[Spy Psychology]
Here they are.
Come on, guys.
-Thank you, Sir.
-Thank you.
Quick, thank Leader Yun.
-Thank you, Sir.
Thanks, Sir.
Ling Han's investigation has led to Bai Qingkui.
This fact makes Zhu He very anxious.
It's time to sever ties with Bai Qingkui.
But how to cut it off and when to cut it off
became a difficult problem.
Under the current circumstances,
if he acts rashly,
it will certainly give others ammunition against him.
But it's impossible for him to remain inactive.
Because Bai Qingkui holds
a secret that could cost Zhu He his life.
Come in.
Deputy Chief.
I have something to report to you.
Speak.
In our leader's drawer,
I found a photo.
It's about you.
About me?
Director Ling is monitoring you.
Our leader took a picture of it.
Alright.
I understand.
Yes, Deputy Chief.
Zhu He is not surprised
that Ling Han is investigating him.
What frustrates him is
that Ling Han is following so closely
while he himself was completely unaware.
Perhaps Ling Han has already
uncovered many of his secrets.
He can't hesitate any longer.
He must take the risk to eliminate Bai Qingkui.
There was a heavy rainstorm recently.
The half-built office building of the girls' school
was washed away.
Principal Wei is raising funds everywhere.
It seems there's still a significant funding gap.
The reconstruction of Xiangjiang Girls' School
is not only of great significance to the education sector
but will also be a boost
to the morale of the entire city of Changsha.
This is what I'm thinking.
We in the business community should take the lead
and contribute to Changsha's educational cause.
What do you think?
Great.
It's what we should do.
I think this proposal is excellent.
As they say, contribute money if you have money, and contribute effort if you have strength.
It's about making more contributions to the local education sector.
Indeed.
Hello, it's me.
There's an emergency action.
Captain!
Li Miaohan's body is missing.
What?
[Changsha Police Station]
What kind of people are you all?
You're drawing a public salary but not doing your job.
I'm going to expose your shameless behavior.
Despicable.
Shameless!
Director Liu.
May I ask what you encountered at the police station?
What shameless behavior of the police do you want to expose?
Are you here to handle Miss Li's funeral arrangements?
Could there really be more to Miss Li's death?
Listen to me, everyone.
They say Miss Li's body has disappeared.
Isn't this nonsense?
Who would be idle enough to come and steal a body?
And they were stealing right under the bright sunlight,
right under the noses of the police?
There must be something fishy going on here.
Fishy?
How could this be?
How could the body be stolen?
This...
After Miss Li was killed,
as her best friend when she was alive,
I am deeply saddened.
I've been running around trying to sort out this matter.
Even the movie I was just preparing to shoot, "Tales of Love and Dreams,"
has been temporarily put on hold.
Director Liu,
about Miss Li's body being stolen,
what did the police say?
They said
it might have been done by Miss Li's crazy fans.
This is absolute nonsense!
Miss Li was the designated lead actress
of my project, "Tales of Love and Dreams."
How could this happen?
If Miss Li were still alive,
there might indeed be crazy fans
who would do something crazy.
But she has already passed away.
How could something like this still happen?
Could it be that the so-called murder
was just a cover-up?
Thank you all for your concern and efforts.
You're welcome.
We're leaving.
These are all the documents
you need to sign and approve today.
-You can leave now.
-Okay.
[Changsha Chamber of Commerce
Dock Revenue Report]
[No. 12 Youpu Street]