[Deep Lurk]
[Episode 4]
My leg...
Let's go.
Check on the girls' school.
Alright.
Give me a hand.
Take it slow.
How is it?
It hurts.
Young Master Yun.
How's it going?
Principal Wei,
what's the situation?
Several students didn't make it out during the air raid.
They're trapped underneath.
Is she alright?
Careful!
Got it.
Watch out!
Are you okay?
Stay back!
Slowly, gently.
Don't crush her.
Miss.
How is she?
How... how is she?
She... She didn't make it.
I hope you can still smell
the fragrance of flowers in heaven.
Miss,
are you okay?
Do you need to go to the hospital for a check-up?
I'm fine.
No need.
I still have to tend to other wounded.
I'll get going now.
Alright.
Miss,
may I know your name?
Our young master feels terribly guilty
about your injury.
He'd like to visit and apologize personally.
That's not necessary.
Don't trouble yourselves over my injury.
My name is Mi Lan.
I really have to go now.
Thank you.
Miss Mi Lan,
our young master is Yun Hongqi from the Yun family.
Hey, stop!
What's going on?
Don't ask so many questions.
Your ID.
Qin Tian?
You can leave now.
Idiot!
Go search
every corner!
I don't think
he'll just leave you here.
I'll wait right here
and trap him like a turtle in a jar.
Hello?
It's me.
What?
The train station?
You saw it with your own eyes?
Seal it off immediately.
I'm heading there now!
We've searched
every inch inside and out,
but there's no sign of Yun Hongshen.
You told me on the phone that it was locked down tight.
So where is he now?
He grew wings and flew away?
We all saw him.
I'm absolutely certain.
So, he made it to the station and then escaped again?
But where could he go?
[Changsha]
Madam, we're here.
Madam.
For the past few days, the students have been protesting.
Did the girls' school join in?
Yes, they did.
But out of respect for the Yun family,
our people held back.
That's why we couldn't
fully suppress the protests.
The deputy station chief is furious.
He personally planned tomorrow's operation.
Yun Hongqi is known
for his integrity
and extensive connections.
He has friends everywhere.
If he finds out about tomorrow's operation,
he won't be pleased.
If a conflict breaks out,
it'll be embarrassing for everyone.
The deputy station chief has ordered absolute secrecy.
It might not
reach Yun Hongqi's ears,
so we could still have the upper hand.
Most of the guys here are locals from Changsha.
Many owe a debt of gratitude to the Yun family.
It's almost impossible
to keep this under wraps.
You're absolutely right.
Who knows, someone might tip off
the Yun family if they disagree with us.
[Yun Residence]
Grandma, you shouldn't
go out to distribute porridge tomorrow.
The Japanese are bombing us
every single day.
It's too dangerous.
Grandma,
you
should just stay at home.
It's safer.
Our house isn't a fortress.
[Madam Yun]
Air raids are dangerous no matter where you are.
Jingyu and I
are tired of being cooped up all day.
A walk outside would be a nice change.
Let's eat.
Old Madam.
Young Master,
-I'm back.
-Join us for dinner.
Don't worry.
-It's been taken care of.
-Okay.
I sent those items
to Miss Mi Lan.
But she was busy,
so her head nurse received them on her behalf.
Dao,
you can keep talking.
I promise I won't hit you.
No.
Let me see your ticket.
Okay.
The Special Operations Division and No. 76 were fully mobilized,
and yet Yun Hongshen still slipped away.
Useless fools!
Worthless!
A bunch of idiots!
Go ahead.
Young Master.
What's the matter?
Look.
Someone slipped an envelope through the door.
NBIS really has nothing better to do.
Instead of catching Japanese spies,
they keep pestering these students.
Now what are they up to?
Shameless.
Here's the plan:
inform everyone
that today's porridge distribution location is changing.
Okay.
[Changsha Station]
-Brother.
Keep your eyes peeled.
The guy standing to the left
of our sworn enemy—that's him.
We're here.
Okay, thank you.
Don't let him get away.
If he escapes today,
your heads are on the line!
-Got it?
-Yes.
Did you get that?
Got it!
Dismissed.
[Pay Phone]
Yes.
I've settled in.
When can I see my daughter?
I've done everything you asked...
Can't you release her first?
Then...
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Quick, Zhang and Wang, over there!
Let me see.
Are you feeling any discomfort?
No.
Are you alright?
Here. Hold this.
Okay.
[Changsha Station]
Here.
Lady,
let me help you.
Thank you, thank you.
Take it slow, take it slow.
You're finally here.
Come on, let's go!
I'll carry the luggage.
We're finally here.
Over here, over here!
Quick, chase him!
What's going on here?
Chase him!
Cigarettes for sale!
Cigarettes!
[Exit]
Excuse me, coming through!
You can't go in.
Slow down.
Step back!
My family's in there.
Get out of the way.
Step back! Step back!
Sir!
Zhang, Wang, come help quickly!
-Help him get in the car.
-Okay.
What are you...
What's going on here?
Make way! Make way! Make way!
[Renji Hospital]
Hurry!
Quick!
Slow down, slow down.
Hurry!
This way!
Be careful!
Take him to the medical room.
You're safe now.
Thank you.
You...
You've offended the Bai Clan, huh?
Those were Bai Qingkui's men?
You don't know them,
No, I don't.
yet you know Bai Qingkui?
I've been away from Changsha for years.
By now, Bai Qingkui's men
have probably changed multiple times.
I didn't recognize any of them.
You're not a bad guy, are you?
You don't even know if I'm a bad guy,
yet you're covering for me?
I don't know what kind of person you are,
but there's not a single good person in the Bai Clan.
If they're after you,
you can't be all bad.
Thanks.
Goodbye.
What a strange person.
[Happy House]
Five sets.
Fifty-eight.
Twenty-five.
Is that correct?
Go.
You go, you go.
You go.
You didn't catch him?
That guy ran like he had wings—
disappeared in a blink.
Once he left the train station,
it's like he vanished into thin air.
I think he must've had help.
[Bai Qingkui, the Bai Clan]
You two are all talk, huh?
Slap each other for me!
Go on, slap!
Sir. This way.
Chief,
these Communists really think they're something.
They're meddling right under our noses.
If it weren't wartime, none of them would've escaped.
And they still have the nerve to protest here.
It's a special period, after all.
We still have to pay attention to public opinion.
I'll leave these people to you;
I can't be bothered.
Don't worry, I'll handle it.
These people will always lose because of their soft-heartedness.
We killed their men.
And the only thing they can do is protest.
They just talk about the bigger picture
and united resistance against Japan.
But have you thought about it?
That's exactly why they win over people's hearts.
-But, Chief...
-Enough.
This isn't our concern.
We still haven't figured out what happened with Qu Wenzhi's defection.
Yes.
[Yun Family's Porridge Distribution Site]
Here.
Don't rush, one at a time!
Slow down, ma'am.
Everyone, please don't rush.
-Everyone has a share.
-One by one.
Don't rush.
One at a time.
Here, please take this.
Thank you.
Here, auntie.
Hurry up and leave!
Didn't you hear me?
Give the villagers extra rations.
Get up now.
[Fight Resolutely—Defend Our Nation till the End]
Go home right away.
What are you doing?
Causing trouble, huh?
What's all this commotion about?
Look at yourselves!
Let me tell you,
we've been more than patient.
Don't push us, or we'll handle you all!
-You hear me?
-There's enough for everyone.
Do you hear me?
Still not moving?
Get going, get going now.
Don't push us too far.
Young Master,
let me show you how to deal with these scoundrels.
Bro,
we're on duty.
Well, it's a coincidence.
I've got orders too—
from my Young Master.
My task today is to protect these students from the girls' school.
You—don't get cocky!
Push me too far, and I'll arrest even you!
I said, if you push us too far, we'll arrest you too!
You want to arrest me?
Oh, really? Go ahead!
Hey, everyone, come take a look!
NBIS is arresting people!
They're arresting the Yuns without reason!
Why are you arresting us?
The government doesn't
care about the homeless;
all you do is arrest people!
If it weren't for the Yun family,
we'd have starved long ago!
If they dare arrest Yun family members,
let's fight back!
Yeah, fight back!
Enough!
Are you trying to start a riot?
Why aren't you arresting me?
Go ahead, arrest me.
We're just following orders.
Let's all take a step back.
If the students behave,
we won't make any arrests.
Then let me ask you—
if it weren't for you people
committing all those immoral acts,
why would these citizens be out here protesting?
Who would give up a good life
to come out here and cause trouble?
Step aside.
Alright, break it up.
You can go now.
Alright.
It's over.
Everyone, let's go eat.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Let's eat.
How was that, Young Master?
That's how you deal with these troublemakers.
Gangzi.
You're here.
-How's it going?
-Are you busy?
Yeah.
I just came from the train station.
Really?
Okay, okay, okay.
Carry on with your work.
Young Master.
Gangzi ran into Rat on his way here.
He asked Gangzi to pass along a message.
Last night, Wu Tong and Cong Hu
went to some little shops that collect old newspapers.
They asked the owner to sell them newspapers from years ago.
What kind of old newspapers?
It seems to be
the issue covering the 15th anniversary of the girls' school.
The 15th-anniversary issue?
Yes.
What's going on?
They're looking for Shen.
[Guli Mountain Temple]
That issue had photos of our whole family.
Now they're searching for a young man...
Who else could it be but Shen?
But isn't the second young master in Shanghai?
He would've told you if he came back to Changsha!
Something's definitely wrong.
This is the Bank of France.
Whom may I direct you to?
Hello,
I'd like to speak with Bank Manager Yun Muzhi.
I'm sorry, sir,
but Mr. Yun passed away from a heart attack a few days ago.
Young Master, what's wrong?
What's the matter?
What's wrong, Young Master?
Has something happened?
It's impossible.
This can't be true...
Something's not right.
If anything had happened to Father,
Shen would've told us.
No way...
Some-something's happened.
No.
Did something happen to Master Yun?
Secretary Liu said
Uncle Yang came back a few days ago, right?
Yes.
Minister Yang just returned from Shanghai.
Let's go to the city hall.
I don't want to see another report
like this again—it's far too sloppy.
Yes, Minister Yang.
I'll be more careful in the future.
Call Chen Si and tell him
this is from me: I want to see
an exact account of every penny spent.
If even one cent is unaccounted for,
he won't get another dollar
from me.
Understood.
Minister Yang,
here's a document
that requires your signature.
Building an official residence?
At a time like this,
when the nation is in crisis?
Tell him
I won't sign it.
If he insists, he can come to see me personally.
Minister,
you have a visitor.
You can get back to work.
In half an hour,
we'll have a meeting in my office.
Yes, sir.
Qi,
you really live up to your reputation
—you've got ears everywhere.
I just got back, and here you are already.
Secretary Wu,
you can go attend to other matters.
Don't let anyone disturb us.
Here.
Sit down, sit down.
Have a seat.
Uncle Yang.
Qi.
You don't look well.
What's wrong?
Uncle Yang, did something happen to my father?
Who told you that?
I called the bank at noon.
They said
my father had a sudden heart attack...
And passed away.
Is that true, Uncle Yang?
Your father is fine.
Not a scratch on him.
But he's run into some trouble,
so he had to fake his death to get out of a tight spot.
During this period,
he might not be able to contact you,
so you'll need to be mentally prepared.
But remember,
in front of others,
you need to act like it's real.
Is that true, Uncle Yang?
Don't you trust me?
I do.
Uncle Yang, I trust you.
Uncle Yang,
but why didn't Shen contact us
after coming back?
If this is all about
making the fake death seem real,
wouldn't it be better to spread the news widely,
so everyone believes my father...
There's no reason to keep it hidden from me, is there?
How did you know Shen is back?
Uncle Yang, here's what happened:
The new school campus land for the girls' school—
Bai Qingkui was after that land too,
but in the end, I secured it.
He's been holding a grudge ever since
and has been sending people to cause trouble.
I anticipated this,
so I had someone keeping an eye on things.
I heard
he's been looking for the report
on the girls' school's 15th anniversary.
That newspaper had a group photo of our entire family.
And just this morning,
he sent someone to the train station
to search for a young man.
So, I'm guessing…
They're looking for Shen.
That Bai Qingkui...
He's got quite the reach.
He even found out in advance that Shen was back.
Uncle Yang, you might not know this,
but Bai Qingkui
runs all sorts of shady businesses.
Plus, his ships frequently go to Shanghai.
So, I was thinking…
Maybe he got wind of something.
And now he wants to capture Shen,
using him as leverage
to force me into negotiations.
It's very likely that Shen noticed
something was off at the train station
and decided to hide himself.
He'll reach out to you
once he's safe.
Don't worry.
Oh, Qi,
about your father's situation...
Don't tell your grandmother yet.
Wait until Shen comes back,
and he can
explain everything clearly.
Only then should you inform her.
I understand.
I won't say anything
until I get the full picture.
Good.
Dao.
Starting today,
you need to learn to act.
Act?
Act sad.
Sad?
But Second Young Master hasn't returned yet.
I'll act sad once he's back, okay?
I'm driving now.
Also,
no one outside of our family
can know about my father's situation.
Got it, Young Master.
Yang Ziming felt very uneasy.
According to their original plan,
Yun Hongshen should have arrived in Changsha
yesterday morning by ship, accompanying the casket.
By now, he should have been here.
But just now, Yun Hongqi mentioned
that Yun Hongshen came back by train.
Clearly, something unexpected must have happened.
Minister Yang.
[Pay Phone]
Hello, brother?
It's your seventh cousin here.
Seventh cousin!
I heard you went down to Southeast Asia?
Southeast Asia? No way!
I was tricked into going up to the northeast.
Just managed to get back now.
So, how are you now?
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Everything's good.
It's like this,
my fifth uncle
wanted me to ask—
Why haven't you contacted the family lately?
The phone line at my home
has been faulty for days.
I see.
Oriole had completely lost contact with Yun Muzhi.
This confirms that something has indeed happened to Yun Muzhi.
What exactly transpired during this period?
Perhaps Yun Hongshen
is the only one who knows the truth.
Contact Nighthawk immediately.
Have him find out
if Hongshen has indeed returned to Changsha.
In my study, on the second shelf of the bookcase, there's an album.
It has photos of me, Hongshen, and Hongqi together.
Show him the photos
so he can recognize Hongshen.
Yes.
I'll get on it right away.
[Supervision Department]
When did he come back?
Last night.
I heard he went straight to his office after arriving,
didn't even report to the Station Chief.
That's inappropriate, isn't it?
Watch your mouth.
You know better than anyone
that he's the last person here you'd want to offend.
Right, right...
[Loyalty to the Party, Love for the Nation, Uphold Confidentiality]
Come in.
Chief.
Deputy Chief.
You go ahead.
I have a meeting to attend.
Good work.
Thanks for your hard work.
You must be exhausted.
You don't look well—
how many hours did you even sleep?
It's fine.
Chief,
is Wen Yeming coming back?
I have a few questions to ask her.
Chief,
I'm back.
You're back just in time.
Director Ling has some questions for you.
How did Qu Wenzhi die?
He was taken out by a sniper.
Three shots,
killed on the spot.
I had colleagues in Shanghai investigate.
The assassin was highly skilled—
left no trace to follow.
Based on your experience,
those three shots…
How many shooters were involved?
Judging by the timing and angles of the shots that hit Qu Wenzhi,
there were likely three shooters.
Did he say anything
before he died?
I asked him
who arranged for his release,
but he was too scared to say.
His wife and child have vanished—
they're likely in the hands of the Japanese.
No wonder.
Chief,
I suspect we have a mole in our upper ranks.
The Chief is really playing favorites.
Both of us went to Shanghai for the mission,
but he only sees Wen Yeming.
He's clearly
planning to give all the credit to her alone.
Alright, that's enough.
This time, getting through
having no merit or fault is already the best outcome.
Qu Wenzhi's case has reached the higher-ups—
it needs to be dealt with.
Wen Yeming went solo to Shanghai to capture the traitor—
that was her own cunning.
If she succeeds, we all share the glory,
and we together might get a reprieve.
If she fails,
having someone to share the blame with
would at least make her punishment less severe.
That's me?
The Chief sure puts a lot of thought
into Wen Yeming.
I agree with Director Ling.
All the commanders in the Ninth War Zone
are under our surveillance.
Every independent operation
goes through layers of approval.
Routes, security plans—
they're all set by us.
Under such circumstances,
for Qu Wenzhi to not only defect
but successfully escape,
it would've been impossible without inside help.
-I suggest...
-Director Ling.
You're in charge of investigating the mole.
I'm entrusting this to you.
If you need anything,
get Wen Yeming to assist.
Yes, sir.
You should go rest soon.
Anything else?
The communists who disrupted the assassination of Qu Wenzhi...
We've eliminated them.
Sir,
those communists
shouldn't have been killed.
That's not your place to question.
Putting aside political allegiances,
repaying kindness is the most basic principle of being human.
Wen Yeming.
How can one allow others to sleep soundly beside one's own bed?
The communists have already infiltrated
even the inner circle of the Ninth War Zone Commander.
The Principal is furious.
You know that's his bottom line—
he won't let anyone touch it.
I don't understand.
We are all Chinese.
With the enemy at our doorstep, we should unite against them.
These internal conflicts are just a waste of time and resources.
Doesn't he worry about breaking the nation's spirit?
Sir...
Enough! Don't bring this up again!
If even I can't do anything about it,
what can you do?
Sometimes, I even question
whether I chose the right path back then.
I don't want to hear you say things like that again!
Do you hear me?
I know you're in pain,
and I know what's going on in your mind.
Because I was once your age.
But understand this:
Sometimes, to achieve your goals,
you have to make compromises. Got it?
-But...
-No buts.
Finding the mole, uncovering who was behind Qu Wenzhi's defection,
and fighting the Japanese—it's all the same.
It's just a matter of perspective.
Understood.
[Yun Residence]
I'll get it.
Hello,
Secretary Liu?
That's great.
Okay.
I'll be sure to thank you in person another day.
Alright, alright.
Goodbye.
It's been an entire day,
and that rascal Shen still hasn't reached out to me.
Grandma,
it was Secretary Liu.
He told me that the paperwork
for the girls' school land has been finalized.
That's wonderful.
One less thing to worry about.
Exactly.
That's why knowing how to deal with people is key.
If you cater to their needs,
things get done quickly.
But it seems like you have something else on your mind.
Do I?
Don't you think he seems a bit distracted?
This person.
Keep an eye on his movements
and protect him as much as possible.
[Chinese Communist Underground, Changsha Police Bureau, Captain Tang]
Understood.
She's been very cautious along the way,
using various methods
to check if anyone is tailing her.
She didn't come here
just for a meal.
On the day Qu Wenzhi defected,
the intersection he used for his escape
was passed by a bus
that arrived on schedule,
without any incidents.
We can rule out any issues there.
However, the license plate of the truck
that blocked our view was clearly switched—
the original vehicle was out of town at the time.
The ambulance that collided with the truck
was from the Military Hospital.
They had received a notification from the frontlines,
requesting them to pick up wounded soldiers.
That part checks out,
but the timing of the call was just too perfect.
I suspect both the truck and the ambulance were involved.
But now that several days have passed,
the people involved and any evidence
are likely destroyed.
We'll have to backtrack
and investigate Qu Wenzhi himself.
There's another lead—
the route Qu Wenzhi took to leave Changsha.
You really didn't have to escort me back;
I can take care of myself.
Hurry upstairs
and rest.
See you tomorrow.
He is following Director Ling.
He's simply courting death.