[Deep Lurk]
[Episode 33]
We'll need your help
to draw firepower for us.
Pleasure.
But you only have 10 minutes.
10 minutes later,
I will fulfill the promise I once made.
By then,
it's just a matter of who has better luck.
After 10 minutes,
I will still fulfill my original promise.
What does he mean by 10 minutes?
Do it in 10 minutes
or something will happen in 10 minutes?
10 minutes?
Forget about Mi Lan.
The safe house is ahead.
Let's get the gun there.
Save the Deputy Chief first.
Deputy Chief.
I've called the station.
Director Xu is at home.
He will send someone to pick you up
in 10 minutes.
Okay.
You can leave now.
Get back to your work.
Deputy Chief.
Leave me a gun.
If they come again,
three or five people is fine with me.
It would be better if Ling Han came here.
I'll kill him myself.
Alright.
Stop dawdling and go.
Be careful.
Shall we go straight to the church?
Yun Hongshen.
Wen Yeming.
We need to think.
Ling Han has been out of our sight for a long time.
What will he do?
Also, according to Director Xu,
Chief has sent everyone out
and isn't at the station either.
We haven't seen
anyone on the way here.
What will they do?
With Chief's style,
he won't have all the people
near the church.
He'll count all possibilities in,
including what Ling Han will do.
Also,
if Ling Han chose to give up the codebook
and escape,
which route would he take?
Chief would consider all the factors
and arrange people to block them
at different points based on that.
[Changsha Station]
[Waiting Room]
Ke Jingping, that old fox,
fooled us all.
Ke Jingping is definitely no ordinary person.
The spy network
we've been working so hard on in Changsha
was destroyed by him in the end.
Judging from Ke Jingping's layout,
this is an interlocking,
interactive
hunt with timely support.
At all important points in the church,
people have been arranged.
As long as something goes wrong in one link,
the other sections will respond immediately
and remedy in time.
And he's got snipers at all the high
points along the street.
It's almost impossible to escape from this
well-designed web.
The phone booths on this road
must have been bugged,
including the cafe at the intersection
and Changsha Theatre.
[Changsha Theatre]
Tell your people:
From the moment you step into Chaozong Street,
you have to give up outward contact.
Don't do anything unnecessary,
and don't talk to unrelated people.
Because there's always someone
observing the strangers entering Chaozong Street.
It is only possible to complete the task
by treating yourself as a passerby
without any purpose.
[Changsha Station]
Captain said
you need to pay more attention
to those ticket sellers with wide connections.
Understand?
Yes.
If Ling Han wants to escape,
they're likely to get tickets through these sellers.
Understand?
Yes.
Isn't that the head of those ticket sellers?
You go in first.
I'll take a look.
Madam.
I got the ticket you asked for.
Thank you.
Hold it properly.
Mi Lan?
Stop!
[Yun Residence]
I caught the ticket dealer and interrogated him.
He just confessed.
He said Mi Lan bought three train tickets
to Shanghai from him.
What time is the train?
At 6:48 p.m. this evening.
Okay.
Go ahead.
I'll call you if I need anything.
Okay.
I'll go back now.
Thank you.
Let me see you off.
Okay.
Let's go.
We're about to close the net.
You need to get out of here.
It would be detrimental to our work.
Madam.
Madam,
are you okay?
Director Gong said you were taken away by Ling Han,
which scared us.
He wouldn't let us save you.
He did the right thing.
You think you guys can save me?
You'd put yourself in trouble.
Pass the message to everyone later.
Next, we'll search for the target in stages.
At the first stage,
keep an eye out for anyone
similar to Ling Han, Zong Fang, and Mi Lan.
Yes.
Oh no!
The church in Chaozong Street is on fire.
Come and put out the fire!
Who called the fire truck?
No one called a fire truck.
Oh no! Something's wrong!
Stop it!
Yes.
Stop the fire truck!
What's going on?
Who asked you to come?
Officer,
I just got a call,
saying the church is on fire.
When did you answer it?
Seven or eight minutes ago.
Was it from a man or a woman?
A woman.
She sound young.
Go block the intersection
and search carefully!
Yes.
Director Gong.
What's going on?
Why is the fire truck here?
Someone called them just now,
saying there was a fire near the church.
I'll check it.
Chief.
Has they arrived at Chaozong Street?
Yes.
After Director Gong finishes asking,
let the fire truck go back
in case it affects traffic.
Some small characters haven't come in yet.
Go get Liu Chao.
Yes.
Chief.
You want to see me?
-Sir...
-Quiet.
Stay here.
Move the manhole cover.
[Changsha Station]
You mean
letting Ling Han die in today's operation?
This is Chief's order,
as well as Director's.
If one day
I had a conflict with Chief,
which side would you take?
Stop!
ID.
Go.
Young Master.
How is it?
Everyone is here.
Let's go.
No reinforcements for now; wait for my order.
Yes.
What do you think?
They're trying to confuse us,
making it hard for us to judge
what Ling Han will do next.
I can guarantee that
he's hiding around here
and will come out when it gets dark.
It's getting dark soon.
Chief,
why don't you go back to the station first?
I'll take care of things here.
Ling Han has been cornered by now.
We don't know what he'll do next.
I'm afraid he'll harm you.
I want to see how he will harm me.
Do you remember what I told you?
If we find out he is the mole,
I'm gonna give you justice.
Now that we've found out,
then there's no need for him to live.
I want to see him die in front of me.
And when you went to save those kids,
you clearly knew that it was Ling Han's trap.
Why did you jump in?
The key is with you.
Why didn't you take it back to the station first?
If you and Wen Yeming
fall into his hands,
the safe won't be safe.
Aren't you afraid that Ling Han will get this codebook?
If Ling Han
can't get the key,
he won't jump into the net we set.
I want to use the key as bait.
You're quite bold.
Because I know
Chief won't let Ling Han get the codebook.
Why is Young Master Yun here?
When you see them later,
show no mercy.
Ling Han won't appear again.
Why?
Since they've made so many fake Ling Han,
they must be trying to cover the real Ling Han.
The more coverup they have,
the more it means that Ling Han won't come here.
This place
should be a battlefield for Mi Lan and Zong Fang.
They purposely lured Yun Hongqi here
to mess up the situation
so they could take the cipherkey and escape.
This is bad.
Young Master Yun wants to kill Mi Lan and Zong Fang
to avenge Madam Yun.
It's not that easy to
catch her alive.
I don't think he's here to make trouble.
Prepare to fight.
Yes.
Let's go!
If anyone sees Mi Lan,
don't hold back.
Beat her to death.
You hear me?
Why are you here?
Mi Lan deliberately leaked her whereabouts to me.
I have to show her respect.
Deliberately?
Dao.
Young Master.
Someone like Mi Lan
came yo buy tickets at the train station in person.
She wants everyone to know her whereabouts.
She's trying to fool us
with this little trick?
I guess I was right.
The train station is just a smoke screen.
They knew you were eager for revenge,
so they lured you here
and caused a conflict between us.
Then they can get
more time, and maybe
a few more can escape.
We're going to put on a good show later
and make them believe it.
Yun Hongqi!
You're obstructing my work!
Wen Yeming!
You can arrest me now!
But let me tell you,
if you arrest me, it's exactly what Mi Lan wants.
My guys are not easy to deal with.
They could raise a rumpus
and escape in chaos,
leaving you nothing.
You're a smart person.
Instead of going back empty-handed,
why don't you bring a body back to report?
Isn't it better?
Don't think I dare not arrest you!
What are you doing?
All you NBIS do
is fighting with your own people.
What?
Fght?
What are you doing?
Don't ask for trouble.
You're the bullies here.
-Shoot.
-Always blaming on others.
Go ahead.
Retreat.
You are really capable,
pointing a gun at your own people.
The Japanese are over there.
Go shoot them!
Are you bullying people here?
Let's go.
It must be a fake alarm.
Keep chasing.
Thank you for your cooperation.
But still, as I said,
you've never been trained.
You're no match for them.
As for the rest,
you won't be able to help.
Go back now.
Okay.
Call me if you need help.
Gangzi,
let's go.
Be careful.
If anything happens to you,
he won't stand it.
Search the station carefully,
front and back!
-Yes!
Let's go.
It's almost over.
Young Master.
What's almost over?
Everything is almost over.
Shen said they are going to close the net.
Great.
That Mi Lan,
-what will happen to her?
-Die!
She will die!
Either die in her own people's hands,
or die in the hands of the NBIS,
or die in Shen’s hands.
Anyway,
she will be punished.
Get the chair.
This place must have just been trampled.
A woman indeed.
Keep a close eye on it.
Team A, go over there. Restore the electricity quickly.
Team B, guard the front door.
Team C, guard the back door.
Hurry up!
You two come with me.
The rest of you stay here.
Don't leave no matter what happens!
-Yes, sir.
Ling Han.
You were careless.
You wouldn't have made such a stupid mistake before.
He's here.
He must be waiting for the mess outside
and jump in through the window.
Even you can think of it.
He would never take the way.
I guess
he'd blow up the switchboard
and then ccme down
to distract the people behind us
and make them panic.
Then he'd come in to get the codebook.
How about this?
What's the point of saying it now?
Protect the Chief!
The Organization has found out about
Ling Han's background.
Your father was an official in the former Qing Dynasty.
You're not Japanese.
Chief.
Are you okay?
I've lived to death
for nine years.
Flowers in the Mirror.
Yun Hongshen knows that
he could only make Ling Han
believe that he's not Japanese,
and he would hand over the cipher key.
Since Ling Han is not Japanese,
but Ke Jingping must
let him die.
This action
made Yun Hongshen begin to suspect
Ke Jingping's identity.
He's a good agent.
What a pity.
We've found the car.
It's parked at two blocks away from the train station,
in a very remote alley.
Unfortunately,
we couldn't find
any valuable witness.
I've checked this car.
It was stolen this morning.
The owner has a clean background.
Nothing suspicious.
The car thief and the person who set off the air alert
should be the same one.
By the way, ask around.
There should be a lot of rickshaws going
toward the train station at that time.
After Mi Lan abandoned the car,
they probably left in a rickshaw.
Go have a try.
Yes.
Leader Wen,
Chief is back.
He wants you in the meeting room for a meeting.
If it wasn't for Yun Hongqi,
we'd have Mi Lan and Zong Fang by now.
He didn't behave. What about you?
The sooner we get the cipher key,
the less our soldiers will die
on the battlefield.
Didn't you tell him about the stakes?
I'm sorry, Chief.
And you, Wen Yeming.
Yun Hongqi obstructed official duties,
resulting in the injury of our secret service personnel.
Didn't you know what to do?
Chief,
I had a conflict with Yun Hongqi
because we agreed on it.
We're going to put on a good show later
and make them believe it.
Only by turning the trick against them
can we lure Mi Lan and Zong Fang out.
I don't want to hear this nonsense.
I just want to know where the cipher key is.
Who can tell me?
Which one of you?
I suggest we re-investigate
the passengers on the same ship as Mister.
I suspect the two dead Misters
were just a cover.
The real Mister has lurked in Changsha
and made contact with Mi Lan and Zong Fang.
The operation this morning
proves my deduction.
Obviously,
Mi Lan and Zong Fang have got new help.
As long as we find the real Mister
and follow the clues,
we can find Mi Lan and Zong Fang.
They must know where the cipher key is.
Chief,
I don't think it's necessary to investigate further.
You know, after today's mission,
the trick of the real and fake Mister
has been exposed.
I think
Mi Lan and Zong Fang know it too.
This Mister must have
moved after the mission was completed.
There's no need to investigate further.
But we can't let go this clue.
This is the only way
we can make a move right now.
Even if Mister has moved,
I'm sure he's in touch with the Mi Lan and Zong Fang.
We've been through the manifest for
the last batch of passengers.
This time, let's do it more specifically.
I believe the result will come out soon.
Keep investigating.
Find this guy
before you go to work tomorrow.
Besides,
when can you give me the cipher key?
Well,
I'm not sure.
Not sure?
Interesting.
Your biggest rival, Ling Han, is dead.
Now the rest are just some small fry.
But now you're not sure.
Didn't you just say that
as long as we find Mister,
we can find Zong Fang and Mi Lan?
It's not hard to find Mister.
It's hard to find Mi Lan and Zong Fang.
And I always feel
Ling Han couldn't have died so easily.
It seems that he
had some backup plan.
So?
So when he was alive,
you two were equal rivals.
Now he's dead,
but you become a coward.
No, I...
I don't want to hear your explanation.
I only give you three days.
Everyone,
three days later,
I want all this to finish.
Understand?
Yes.
Everyone, I have something to say.
Although we have paid
a heavy price for this operation,
after all, we've taken back the codebook.
For someone as capable as Ling Han,
who is absolutely loyal to the KMT,
losing him is a huge loss to Hunan Station.
I hope you all to restrain yourselves
and your subordinates.
Regarding Ling Han,
this is the only one statement,
no matter to whom,
internally and externally.
Got it.
Dismiss.
Chief,
this bag
was found at the place where Ling Han
kidnapped the deputy chief.
How did you find this bag?
There was a mark engraved on the spot
where the bag was found that is unique to our station.
Maybe it was left by Leader Yun.
You may leave.
Yes.
According to the situation,
the person who set off the air alarm
is the same one who drove the car and saved
Mi Lan and Zong Fang.
This means this person knows
the backup plan if the operation fails.
Normally,
the person who knows
the backup plan must be trusted.
So I think
we can assume that this person is Mister.
I've just talked to Wen Yeming.
According to her analysis at the crime scene,
we can infer that this woman's
height is probably
between 1.6 to 1.7 meters.
Not too thin.
Is it possible that it's a thin man and his
weight and height
is within this range you mentioned?
It's not likely.
Because the power of men and women
is still very different.
People of the same height and weight
leave very different marks
when they exert themselves.
Especially a long curly hair found
under a window at the crime scene.
I'm sure Mister is a woman.
I see.
Director Gong.
The day you caught the fake Mister,
our people were there too.
After your people do the preliminary screening,
have my team cross-reference with yours.
That's more efficient, right?
Thank you.
It's my duty.
What did Yun Hongshen give you?
You disobeyed my order again and again.
And now you dare come here
and doubt my decision.
Wen Yeming,
you've really let me down.
It has nothing to do with others.
I can't accept it myself.
Letting Ling Han die as a hero
and be admired
by those who know nothing.
It's not fair.
I can't face those people
who died because of Ling Han
and their family.
I feel guilty.
I can't tell them without conscience
that their sacrifice was worth it.
Sir,
you told me before
that our job
might not be understood
or fair and square.
But everything we've done
is for the future of this country, isn't it?
Is a false peace,
making a traitor a hero,
part of tomorrow too?
That would be horrible.
For the sake of someone,
the truth is buried,
and the right and wrong are confused.
Is such a tomorrow worth looking forward to?
Fine, you wanna talk about the truth?
I'll tell you what the truth is.
The truth is a compromise
between the various forces!
There is no real fairness or justice in this world.
It's not black or white.
It has its grey zone.
There are some things you have to compromise on.
You know?
Even if there is no absolute fairness,
you can't distort the truth.
The truth?
If I tell you the truth,
do you think you can handle it?
Now, let me ask you.
Have you ever suspected that Yun Hongshen is a Communist?
Tell me!
Yes.
Yang Ziming cleared him of suspicion.
But there's still something suspicious about him.
Do you dare say you've never suspected him?
You've suspected.
But you don't dare look into it.
Because you just can't
face the fact.
Go back.
Don't hold on to Ling Han.
There are many things that you may not like,
but you have to accept it.
Looking at these files,
Yun Hongshen's more certain that
Kunwu is not Ling Han,
but someone else.
As more and more
information in the files
is presented in front of Yun Hongshen,
all his doubts
now point to Ke Jingping.
He is the most likely
Kunwu.