[English subtitles are available]
[Fireworks of my heart]
[Episode 27]
You are way better than his son,
but his son is better
at buttering people up.
You know he's not as good as me,
but Mum still arranged Qin
to go on a blind date with him.
He's not as capable as you,
but he's not a bad person.
If we have to find her someone as good as you,
[Erudite and discerning]
how many men in Yancheng can qualify?
If we just keep on looking,
how can your sister
get married?
It's okay if she doesn't.
It's not like we can't provide for her.
What are you even talking about?
I really can't understand
young people like you nowadays.
Uncle Gu's daughter is great.
But you don't like her either.
What have you been up to lately?
Why haven't you come home on weekends?
It's almost the end of the year.
I'm a little busy.
So is Qin.
She hasn't been home
since she came back from the disaster area.
Every time I called her,
she said she was busy.
I don't know what you're busy with.
She didn't come home last weekend either?
No.
Dr. Xu, we're leaving.
Bye.
Are you off work?
I'm on my way.
It'll be a bit late today.
I'll leave in ten minutes.
Okay.
[Director Liu] [Secretary Wang]
[Xu Qin]
[QR code name card]
[Recent activities]
[Xu Qin]
Brother.
Go up.
Come home with me.
Meng Yanchen.
You are her brother.
You two can't be together.
As long as our parents don't agree,
you two can't get married.
Since you got together,
she's never come home.
She's just avoiding the problem.
Don't you understand?
Don't you worry about it.
Whether I can keep her or not
depends on how good I am.
Right.
Keep her.
Then what?
Asking her to give up everything for you
just to satisfy your own desire?
Will you be at ease?
Song Yan.
Ask yourself.
Do you deserve her?
Check out the environment of this neighborhood.
Weigh yourself.
Can't you see clearly?
You were dumped back then
because our parents didn't approve.
If you still have any
dignity and guts,
you'd do anything you can
to make yourself
presentable
so that you can deserve her.
But look at yourself.
What do you have?
What can you give her?
Asking her to stand on the opposite side
of everything she has just for you?
Song Yan.
Who do you think you are?
Meng Yanchen.
Do you know her?
Besides knowing that she is sensitive
and dull,
what else do you know?
You don't know her at all.
Yes.
You've hated me since ten years ago.
You hated me for teaching her to smoke,
drink,
and fight.
But what really happened?
She was the one
who asked me to take her to a bar.
I don't fight.
She just picked fights with others herself.
Do you know why?
She wanted to play.
She wanted to act wildly.
She wanted to go crazy.
She wanted freedom.
She had been suppressed for too long,
so the way she did it was extreme.
At that time,
at least she was vivid.
So,
you ask me why I deserve her?
Just for her laughter just now.
At least she was full of life back then.
What about now?
Ten years have passed,
and she's been suppressed to be completely numb.
Don't you know her personality?
She seems cold
and unconcerned about anything on the outside.
But in fact,
she's just a coward.
No matter how well she disguises herself,
she's just a pushover.
Even if she's suppressed to death,
she wouldn't say a word of complaint to you.
She treats you as her next of kin.
But what do you take her for?
You treat her as a pawn,
making her marry for business
to pave the way
for your family enterprise?
I won't use her to pave the way.
Can you protect her?
You can't even protect yourself.
Meng Yanchen.
My parents
are not as bad as you said.
They do have
their own set of
rules.
This set of rules does suppress me
and Qin.
But...
Qin is her daughter.
They treat her as their own daughter.
Meng Yanchen.
You know very well
she's not only Meng Qin,
but also Xu Qin.
Go back.
You and your family.
Please don't make things difficult for her anymore.
She has had insomnia for a long time.
She needs sleeping pills to fall asleep.
Do you know that?
You said this neighborhood is good.
It really is.
The floor is good too.
It's very high.
Meng Yanchen.
Look up.
Given her previous state,
do you think one day,
she'd jump
from above?
None of your family
has the right
to say I don't deserve her.
You two didn't fight, did you?
Go.
Check downstairs.
What's wrong with you recently?
Nothing.
Do you think I believe you?
What do you want me to say?
This is not how you should drink wine.
Wine is supposed to be tasted,
and bring happiness to people.
It's not for drinking your problems away.
Who is it this time?
It has nothing to do with others.
I just want to drink.
Seriously?
Torture yourself like this?
There are two caterpillars
living in a dark cave.
There's no light.
It's very depressing.
They're just caterpillars.
Neither of them can escape.
But luckily, there are two of them.
They can depend on each other.
Although it's dark,
they have each other's company.
But one day,
one of them comes out of the cocoon,
turns into a butterfly, and flies away.
The other caterpillar
is still in the cave.
Still in the endless darkness.
The other caterpillar
will turn into a butterfly too.
There are too many butterflies outside.
No matter how hard it searches,
it can't find
that caterpillar from before.
You two used to
bear the suppression of your mum together.
Now, Qin
is pursuing her own happiness.
The pressure she and Song Yan will face
will only be 1,000 times greater than you.
In comparison,
they are braver than you.
No matter what,
as long as they fly out,
there'll be a vast world out there.
It's obviously better than
staying in the dark forever.
He's always a decent man.
I'm also surprised
about today.
I know.
I knew it long ago.
What do you know?
I know it's not been easy
for you to be in that family.
It's not about how difficult it is.
It's just that when we are with family,
it's not that easy
to tell
who's right and who's wrong.
You think my mum is tough, right?
Indeed.
She's very controlling.
But you know what?
When I had a fever
in my childhood,
she was the one
who kept me company all night.
When someone bullied me,
she was also the one who stood up for me.
Surprised?
It's just my mum's personality is like that.
She treats Meng Yanchen
and me in the same way.
My brother is very much like me.
We are like caterpillars.
We spinned ourselves in a cocoon,
thinking that we were hiding in a safe zone.
Once anything
changes in this zone,
we'd suddenly lose our sense of security.
My brother thinks
the other caterpillar ran away.
He has no companion now,
and he's abandoned.
That's why he feels uneasy.
From now on, your safe zone
will be me.
Warm water.
Where is the wine?
The wine was the boss's.
I'll buy one bottle.
What do you want?
Anything.
Okay.
I'm in the bar.
Okay, got it.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Who is the wine for?
Mr. Meng.
Who allowed you to open the wine for him?
He paid the bill.
Why can't I open it?
Will you be responsible if he gets drunk?
Yes.
Yes?
Ye'zi.
I remember you are from a pretty good college.
It's already graduation season.
Why haven't you been looking for a proper job
instead of working part-time here?
It's hard to find a job.
Aren't you an internet celebrity?
Why are you so keen
about this part-time job?
Isn't it good to work hard?
Listen.
Young lady.
You're still young.
Don't think about
unrealistic things.
You look like that person,
but you don't really.
You are alike in appearance but not in essence.
You're nothing like her.
After you finish your work today,
go collect your salary at the finance department.
Don't come tomorrow.
Zhou.
Take this.
Give me a bottle of water
and hand me the clothes.
I'll leave early
because I have things to do.
Call a designated driver for Mr. Meng.
Okay.
Okay, Boss.
What's going on?
Why is he so tough today?
Saying things like
"alike in appearance but not in essence"
and "nothing like her".
Who was he talking about?
The purest vodka.
Try it.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Take a break.
Drink some water.
My dad just
called me
and asked me to go home.
I'm leaving.
Don't drink any more.
Don't let me see you here
when I come back later.
I'll tell on you.
Hello, Mr. Meng.
Kaming Designated Driving is at your service.
Please fasten your seat belt.
I thought you already quit this.
No one would complain about
how many ways there are to make money.
You haven't fastened your seat belt yet.
Are you drunk?
Turn left in front.
Change the lane in advance.
Looks like you're really not drunk.
People like you
never get drunk, do you?
What kind of person am I?
Extremely self-disciplined.
Still self-disciplined even when you're drinking your problems away.
Then it's an exception today.
Cold wind is the worst for the drunk.
Are you okay?
Tissues. Wipe your mouth.
It'll be extra work for the cleaning lady.
I'm sorry.
Is something
bothering you?
No.
You look like you are lying.
I'm not.
I just don't have
anything happy in my life.
So what can make you happy?
Never.
Never again.
[BWZ Vintage]
We're here.
This shop, right?
Hello.
Anyone here?
Hello, who called the police?
Where are they?
It's me!
Hello, what's wrong?
I...
There's a spider
upstairs.
It's massive.
But...
But I dare not catch it.
Please help me catch it.
Don't worry. We're on it.
Dapeng.
Are you afraid of spiders?
Hide behind me if you're scared.
Lady.
Where did you find the spider exactly?
Over there.
Pipi, Dapeng, Ge. Go!
OK.
Be careful.
That is expensive.
Ge.
Be careful with it.
Okay.
Be careful.
This is more expensive.
Hello.
Are you sure it's over here?
I've searched for a long time but I didn't see it.
I'm sure it's there.
I saw it with my own eyes. It was right there.
Miss.
Is that spider really this big?
It's big anyway.
Chi. Yi.
I really didn't find any spiders.
We didn't either.
Not here either.
Did it run downstairs?
It's here.
It's on your back.
Don't move.
Dapeng, don't move.
It's only this big.
Pipi.
Catch the spider.
Miss, is this the one?
Yes.
Lady.
The problem has been solved.
We'll leave now.
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
This is what we should do.
Back to the station.
Let's go.
The spider is really huge.
Thank you.
Wait.
Well...
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work then.
Thank you.
Bye.
-Problem solved./N-OK.
Dismiss.
Ge Zheng, you have a girlfriend?
No.
You deserve it.
Catching spiders for someone at night.
Amazing.
Last time, Class 2
helped someone catch a gecko.
Exactly.
[Police]
[Rescue]
Ge.
What's wrong, brother?
Is that your girlfriend?
Yes.
[Public Security]
Say hi.
There's so much traffic.
Are you shy?
It's not easy for you to run into her.
Why don't you say hi?
Lu Xiaoqiu!
She's working.
[Public Security]
Is there anything to eat or drink?
Li.
Give her a drink.
Are you cold?
No.
What's your mission today?
Catching a spider.
Catching a spider?
Right, this is for you.
How long before you get off work?
About an hour.
Another hour?
Keep warm.
Okay.
Wear more.
This mission is worth it, right?
It's not worth it for me.
I even lost two bottles of drinks, Yi.
I'll return them to you.
I'm like a lonely dog
walking on the street,
but suddenly got kicked by someone for no reason.
It's not like it. You are that dog.
You're awake.
Why are you here?
This is my home.
Why am I here?
Did you forget?
You were drunk last night.
I'm asking you.
Why am I here?
I did put in my address
on the order page.
Just because you are a rich young man,
you think
I have some ulterior motives towards you?
It was you who refused to get off yesterday.
You refused to go home
even after we arrived at the underground parking lot.
You said you'd like to be anywhere
but not home.
I really didn't know
where I could send you.
I'm sorry.
I don't remember anything.
You said you are sorry,
but you're actually suspecting that I was lying.
It was my first time blacking out for drinking too much.
You should
have left me
at my apartment's underground parking lot.
Where's my jacket?
I should go back.
Wait.
I bought breakfast for two.
Don't waste food.
You even apologized to the cleaner
for throwing up on the ground,
yet you don't show any respect
for me, a part-timer at a bar.
Mr. Meng.
You are a very interesting person.
Did you sleep in the dorm
last night?
Or what?
I bought
this toothpaste and toothbrush for you.
You'll only use them once,
so I bought the cheapest ones.
Bathroom.
Thank you.
[Peace and Joy]
Did you rent
this place alone?
I share it with a classmate.
She didn't come back
because she had classes last night.
So,
have you paid off your student loan?
Almost.
You want to ask about the rent, right?
Last month,
we gained a lot of fans.
Also, many people came to me for collaboration.
I received way too many packages, and it was too crowded in the dorm.
I'm about to graduate anyway.
It's better that I rented a house in advance,
so I don't have to find a place later.
Why do college students today
all want to be internet celebrities?
Even in such a good college,
you still want to do that.
Or what?
Should I live on air?
Dreams
require material foundation.
It's not for me
to pursue at the current stage.
I won't comment
on your opinion.
Smells good.
You're up so early.
Done.
Here. Have some breakfast.
It's Monday the day after tomorrow.
Are you going back to work?
I've taken a sick leave long enough.
Here.
So,
I won't be able to see you in a while, right?
Do you feel like you won't be used to
living alone?
No.
All these years,
I've always been living alone.
What I'm not used to
is you being here these days.
I'll be back next weekend.
A week actually passes quite quickly.
Your management
is quite humane now.
There's something more humane.
What is it?
Come closer.
Local
married staff
can have more holidays.
Really?
Do you want to consider it?
Just eat.
[Mum]
I need to take this.
Hello?
Qin.
Mum.
Where are you?
Mum, I'm at home.
I'm about to go to work.
Work on weekends too?
I asked you to come back last weekend,
but you didn't.
I've been busy lately.
So busy that you can't even come home
or go on blind dates?
You won't have time
to get married in the future either, right?
Mum, I'll take care of
my own business.
Come home
tonight.
You haven't been home for over a month.
Maybe tomorrow.
I'm off tomorrow.
I'll go back early in the morning.
If you are so busy that
you can't come home for over a month,
I'll call
your senior
and ask for a leave for you.
Got it.
Here.
It's getting cold.
My mum just called me
and urged me to go home.
Go.
I...
I won't come back
tonight.
I'll come back and see you tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
Here.
Chief Song, eat up.
[Fire]
[Rescue]
[Emergency]
Doctor!
Hurry! Someone is injured over here!
Hurry!
Look. Her hands are bleeding a lot.
It's okay. She's not badly injured.
Such a big fire.
I'm still horrified that this happened.
Exactly.
What a relief.
Luckily,
no one's severely injured.
There was a girl in the bus.
She's amazing.
She smashed
the window with a hammer
and brought us out.
Otherwise,
we'd be in big trouble.
Yes. At such a young age,
she's so calm and decisive.
She's over there.
That girl
who's talking to the driver.
Yes, that's her.
She saved us.
If there's nothing else, I'm leaving.
You can go now.
She saved us.
It's her.
Thanks to her.
Sister-in-law.
Zhai Miao.
You were in the bus too?
She saved all of us.
She's great.
So brave at such a young age.
So smart.
I'm a firefighter's family.
If I couldn't handle
such a trivial matter,
it would be a disgrace to my brother.
Am I right, Sister-in-law?
Just call me Xu Qin.
No way.
My brother said
I should't be disrespectful.
Otherwise,
he'll hit me back home.
What did he say to his family...
Sister-in-law.
We did have
some bad memories before.
But that's because
I treated you as an outsider.
Now,
we are a family.
I will treat you well.
Let's
move on, okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Don't worry, Sister-in-law.
The fire burnt a hole in your clothes.
I have spare clothes.
I'll get you one.
No need.
Get back to work.
I won't bother you.
Bye.
[Emergency]
When you go back,
don't get any water on this wound.
[Debridement Room 04]
Avoid certain foods.
Sleep well.
[Debridement Room 04]
Do you want to go shopping
after work?
I'll pass.
My mum is coming to see me.
I'll pick her up at the airport.
I'll pass too.
I have something to do later.
You are not
going on a date
with that firefighter from last time, are you?
What's his name again?
Zhan Dapeng.
Right.
Do you have
any progress?
I was just answering
the question she asked.
I didn't say
I have anything to do with him.
[Demonstrate the Morality of the Hospital and Create Life Miracles]
Listen.
Don't spread rumors.
I'm going to a school reunion.
I really think
that young man is quite nice.
Forget it no matter what.
I can't.
What?
You are a doctor that people call at 120, and he's a firefighter with the phone number of 119.
Even your number is bigger.
You are better than him no matter what.
I'm also a lot
older than him.
[Demonstrate the Morality of the Hospital and Create Life Miracles]
It's good that you are older than him.
A younger man
is both positive...
And childish.
You haven't spent time with him yet.
How do you know if he's childish?
Exactly.
You should try everything.
You are always timid.
You think too much.
Right.
If you don't choose to start,
how can you know
what the ending will be like?
Besides,
choosing to start
can help you push things forward
in a good direction.
If you don't choose to start,
surely you can avoid a bad ending,
but
there won't be a happy ending either.
Dr. Xu, you don't talk much.
But when you talk, it makes great sense.
Dr. Li.
Watch and learn.
But,
if
all signs indicate that
there's probably not going to be a good result,
why would I want to go through it at all?
Even if there's no result,
at least there's a process.
No matter what, if you've experienced it,
there wouldn't be any regrets.
I'm leaving.
[Demonstrate the Morality of the Hospital and Create Life Miracles]
Bye, Leader.
Leader even
gossips with us now.
Did I hear it right?
Watch and learn.
-I'm leaving./N-I'm leaving. Bye.