[English subtitles are available]
[Chief Director]
[Li Muge]
[Fireworks of My Heart]
[Episode 3]
The door is open.
Please come in.
You go first.
I'll follow you.
Mom.
Mom, dad, I'm back.
Why did you come back together?
We met at the door.
Where is dad?
He went to Xiao's house.
Maybe he'll have dinner at his home.
I was sweating in the car.
I'll go upstairs and get changed.
I'll go upstairs, too.
[China Fire and Rescue]
[The Vanguard of Party Members: Red Truck]
[Rescue]
Hurry up.
[Firefighting]
Mom.
Where's my wooden sculpture?
I asked the housemaid to throw it away.
Why?
I told you
I don't like you doing those things.
The sawdust on the ground is so dirty.
You're a girl.
Why can't you learn something good?
Mom, Qin...
I don't like
you studying medicine, either.
It's a thankless job,
and you have to work overtime.
When you have a family,
how can you take care of it?
Mom.
Auntie.
Xiao, you're here.
I'm here for a meal.
All right, you young people talk.
This is...
Who got scolded again?
It's time to eat.
Okay.
Jiang.
Chief.
Who is responsible for taking out the trash today?
Da Peng is on duty today.
I saw him
go downstairs to take out the trash.
Have you lost
something important?
I'll find it for you.
I'm just asking.
All right, it's nothing.
Go ahead.
If you don't need your chef anymore,
please tell me and I'll hire him to my place.
My mom is here.
Are you trying to scare me?
Aren't you the one who is most afraid of her?
I have recently opened a new bar.
Come to my place tomorrow.
You can relax there.
Mom.
Again?
Are you addicted to scaring me?
Although my aunt is a devil,
she's still very cute.
Right?
Auntie, I just told them
I haven't seen you for days. I miss you.
Here.
You can't read social cues at all.
Have a seat.
Yanchen,
you should learn from Xiao.
Find a girlfriend as soon as possible.
You grew up together.
You should give him some advice.
Auntie, what if he takes my advice
and finds someone you don't like?
If the girl is not good, of course I won't like her.
Whether she's good or not,
I don't really know your standards.
First,
if they're not equal
in social status,
this won't do.
Here.
This is yours.
You take this.
Auntie, you've prepared red envelopes.
I want one too.
You don't need it.
This is the information
about the girls I've selected for you.
And this is the information
about the boys I've selected for you.
Take a look.
Choose the one
you like.
Tell me then.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's eat.
I'm not blaming you.
If you're free,
you can come back home more often.
It's such a big house.
It would be too empty if you don't live here.
Right?
Also, Qin,
you work hard
in the hospital.
Come to my bar when you're available.
I'll get you a bottle of good wine.
And you.
You should come too.
Auntie wants you
to find a girlfriend.
In my bar,
there are many beautiful girls.
Let me give you some advice.
Xiao.
Don't talk
when eating.
[Be loyal to the Party; strict in discipline; go through fire and water; and serve the people wholeheartedly]
What are you looking for?
A lighter.
She gave it to you?
For the past ten years,
you've always taken it with you.
You still love her.
Why did you break up?
[Be ready to come at the first call]
Our families
have a huge gap.
Her parents take the social status
very seriously.
They don't think I'm good enough for her.
Actually, I can understand a little bit.
All these years,
you've been pushing yourself.
You want to be the first in everything.
You care so much
about the honor and mission on your shoulders.
It's partly
because of her, right?
I want to
narrow the gap between us.
I once imagined
if one day
we meet again,
I want to stand in front of her,
dignified and imposing.
I'm fine.
For the past ten years,
I've kept it well.
Isn't that strange?
She's here.
But I've lost it.
I suddenly feel
my heart is empty.
Although I don't know
what happened between you two,
I can see
you were deeply hurt
in this relationship.
You've seen her.
Since you don't want to bring up the past,
let bygones
be bygones.
If you lose something,
you don't have to look for it.
If you miss someone,
you don't need to look back either.
We can't always live in the past.
Maybe this is what God wants to tell you.
Forget the past
and start a new life.
Give me some advice.
They all look good.
Don't you think
the three of them are like triplets?
They've all altered their faces.
They're nothing like you.
Jiang Yu.
He's a nice guy.
He's reliable.
Much better
than Song.
What?
I'm not allowed to ask.
And now I can't even talk?
I'm not afraid you'll get angry.
He is not suitable for you,
and it's impossible for you to be together.
We tend to look on the bright side
about the past.
Actually,
you don't like him at all.
You just have regrets about the past.
The best thing
is what we can never get!
Where are you going at this hour?
Bar.
Welcome, my beautiful doctor.
I'm here
waiting for you.
Save your time
to coax your girlfriend.
You're my only girlfriend.
Get lost!
You hit too hard.
You're getting far too cheeky!
You need to teach her to be polite.
Stop it.
Show us around.
OK.
Mr. Meng, please come in.
Here.
How is it?
Is it good?
Boss.
The Yamazaki 25. Three glasses.
Okay.
Sit here.
Here, Qin.
Have a seat.
I bought two floors.
It's noisy upstairs.
This floor is quiet.
Isn't the view nice?
Yes.
I didn't expect
you have a good taste.
I learned it from you.
Qin.
Just come here if you're free.
What's wrong with you?
Are you new here?
Didn't the foreman train you before?
Boss.
She is new here.
I'm sorry.
Apologize.
It's okay.
She works part-time.
I'll talk to her later.
You need to train
these part-time workers well.
Listen.
This is all your mistake.
You know?
Yes.
I will be careful.
The firefighters will come for inspection later.
Please receive them.
Be polite.
Okay.
I'll go down first.
You're quite strict.
Are you pretending in front of me?
I'm serious
when I work.
I'll make a call.
It's not easy to recruit people now.
Sorry.
Do you think
she looks a bit like Qin?
Does she?
I think so.
Have you checked the fire-fighting equipment
in time?
Yes.
If there's any problem,
remember to change it in time.
OK.
Don't worry.
We will strictly
follow the rules.
Hello.
Are you from the fire station?
Yes.
Shouldn't the firefighters
come for the fire safety inspection?
The inspection is under the control of the detachment.
The firefighters belong to the fire rescue station.
They are not in charge of this task.
Go to the emergency exit.
Okay, this way please.
What are you thinking?
I met Song Yan
the other day.
What is he doing now?
Let me guess.
Could he be a boss
just like me?
A firefighter.
And then?
You had a chat?
How did it go?
He ignored me.
You feel regret?
Whether I feel regret or not,
what can I do about it?
There are always regrets in life.
Even if people
try their best
and go crazy,
in the end,
they can't escape.
After so many years,
you still like him?
I thought I wouldn't.
You couldn't control yourself when you met.
Your love for him grew again from the bottom of your heart.
It means you haven't forgotten him.
Qin.
The most torturing thing in the world
is to stand still and think
we can go back.
I've heard about you two.
With all due respect,
it's impossible in the past,
let alone
the future.
Cheer up. Don't think about it.
Let's go.
Let's go back for a drink.
You go first.
I'm going to wash my hands.
Don't look.
Qin.
Where are you going?
Something came up at the hospital.
I have to go.
You're leaving?
Qin left,
and she lied.
What?
Do you know
what Qin told me?
She said there are always regrets in life.
Even if people
try their best,
they can't escape.
Is this what a normal person would say?
Life is short.
It is a great blessing
to be able to have fun.
Giving up what you have
and pursuing the illusory
is not worth it.
[Guards are sacred. Do not invade]
[Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station, Yanbei District]
Hello.
Excuse me.
Does Song Yan work here?
[Fire and Rescue]
Who are you?
I'm
his old classmate.
Can you contact him for me?
Please wait a moment.
Thank you.
Hello, Chief Song.
Someone is looking for you.
She said she's your classmate.
[Fire and Rescue]
Your name...
Xu Qin.
Her name is Xu Qin. Chief.
Okay.
Sorry.
Our chief is not here today.
Where did he go?
Maybe he went outside
for training.
Thank you.
[Fire and Rescue]
[119]
[Guards are sacred. Do not invade]
[Official Business]
Li Cheng.
Officer Li.
I have a meeting
with the division leader later.
Please send the dog food
to Chief Song.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay, go ahead.
Take care.
[Official Business]
[Guards are sacred. Do not invade]
Go out if you want to see her.
Meng.
Be good.
There's a close bond
between you and Meng.
Of course.
I raised it.
Dogs are affectionate.
It takes after its owner.
Why do I feel
you're implying something?
I'm saying you're affectionate.
Get lost.
[Please register]
[Please show your ID]
You're not going to see her?
Why?
She's not that important to me.
[Zhai’s]
It's very delicious.
Delicious.
I'll give it to you later.
Yan, you're off work?
Brother Yan.
When are you taking us
to see and take
the fire truck?
When you grow up,
I'll take you there.
No.
Now we're
grown up.
Come here.
Don't pester him.
Hurry.
Uncle Zhao.
Are you off work?
You're pestering him again.
Let's play Chinese chess.
One for each.
Say thank you.
Thank you, Brother Yan.
Brother Yan is the best.
Uncle Zhao.
This...
You're losing.
Yeah. Hurry up.
Help me. Come on.
Do it yourself.
Brother Yan, keep your word.
[Zhai’s]
OK.
Aunt.
I'm back.
Yan, you're back.
You haven't eaten, have you?
Beef noodles.
No problem. Come on.
Why are you carrying so many things?
I bought some fruits.
Come on.
Okay.
Here.
Have some pickles.
This is more tasty.
Here.
Is it good?
I just want this.
Xu Qin
came here to see you.
You met her?
You still like her?
I'd say I hate her more.
If you don't have feelings for her, how can you hate her?
I really don't like her.
I'm annoyed when I see her.
You swear?
I'm relieved then.
Listen.
A good man doesn't backtrack.
You know?
You suffered so much
because of her.
I'm still angry when I think about it.
She went too far.
Why did she go so far?
She even came to you.
Shame on her!
Aunt.
Do you have garlic?
Aren't these pickles enough?
Do you want garlic?
My uncle said
it'll get more tasty
when eating noodles with garlic.
Okay.
I'll bring some for you.
Relax.
Don't be nervous.
Come on.
Have some fruits
to replenish vitamins.
Thank you, aunt.
You're welcome.
Why is this girl
so pretty?
Well,
take good care of her. Eat more fruits.
Make yourself at home.
Eat more.
You're so beautiful.
Is it sweet?
Enjoy yourself.
My uncle and aunt
are very nice.
They won't eat you.
Are you following me to the toilet?
Let me show you how to shave flowers.
Here we go.
One more.
Song Yan, I love your house.
It's useless to just talk.
Do you dare to marry me and move to my house?
I promise
I will only love you
in this life.
You
should think about
how to study well.
Qin
has got into such a good university,
yet you have to prepare again for the college entrance exam.
Be careful. She might not like you then.
You don't like me?
You don't?
She might not like you then.
Uncle and aunt are really nice.
Yeah.
This yard is so beautiful.
I wish I had a beautiful yard
like yours.
I would stay at home every day
and never go out.
Eat it. It'll melt soon.
I don't like this ice lolly.
It's not hygienic at all.
Don't get too picky.
You'll be fine.
Here.
Why is your car there?
Let's go.
Song Yan.
Don't come to me again.
I used to play with you
because I felt fresh.
Now I've figured it out.
We are not
from the same world.
We won't have any connections in the future.
If you keep living like this,
you won't have any chance of achieving
when you grow up.
Xu Qin.
Is your family against it?
No.
I don't want to lie to you anymore.
Once the freshness is over,
it'll be boring.
Tell me the truth.
Did your parents
force you to say that?
No one forced me.
Your house is a mess.
I don't like your house at all.
Don't contact me again.
♫I still have a lot to say♫
♫I've missed too much♫
♫Without your company♫
♫The fallen leaves have no choice but to fall from the branches♫
♫I will stay for you♫
♫It rained heavily outside the window all night and who shed tears♫
Xu Qin.
Xu Qin!
Stop, Xu Qin.
♫I'm sorry I didn't protect you and me back then♫
♫I shed tears and I can't bear to let you go♫
♫Who drew a beautiful scar in my heart that I can't wipe it away♫
♫I still remember we burst into tears the day we parted♫
♫I still remember the nameless flower you put in my hand♫
♫Who made a promise in the midsummer♫
[I want to talk to you. I'm waiting for you in the forest.]
♫It rained heavily outside the window and I shed tears all night♫
♫Even if I have to wait for you in my youth♫
♫I shed tears and I can't bear to let you go♫
♫The wish I made in the midsummer is you♫
Vice-president Liu.
[Emergency] [First floor]
Xu.
Are you off work?
How are you?
Have you adapted to the hospital?
Yes, I'm fine.
Okay.
If you have any problem,
just come to me. I'll solve it for you.
No, everything is fine.
Okay.
The other day,
I met your mother.
Send my regards to her.
[Emergency] [First floor]
Okay.
If you're off work...
Xu.
Director Xu.
He's always pulling a long face
like someone owes him money.
This man.
Vice-president Liu.
I'll go first.
Okay.
Be careful.
[Emergency] [First floor]
The city has launched a rainstorm red warning.
From tonight to tomorrow morning,
there will be a heavy downpour
in the city.
Please be careful.
[The red boats lead; dedicate ourselves to Yancheng City; strict in discipline; fight with courage and wisdom]
All production units
should take precautions
[Train in actual combat to win]
[Be strict and hard in training the best soldiers]
to avoid any property loss.
Ge, come down.
It's pouring.
Today's training
is over.
Tong Ming, take away the ladder.
Check the safety equipment.
Check the equipment carefully.
We can pack up
and load the car later.
Okay.
Pull the canoe here
and check it.
Instructor,
there would be no fire
on rainy days, right?
Why are you so nervous?
Sometimes rain
is more troublesome than fire.
Go get changed.
Don't catch a cold.
OK.
OK. Instructor.
Hello.
I think your vacation might be...
I know.
I have returned to the team.
I didn't expect
your vacation to be over
just as it started.
It just started tonight.
[Ambulance]
[Take regular physical examination. Pay attention to your health]
Hello. Leader.
There are many emergency patients because of the rainstorm.
Director Xu said everyone must be on duty.
OK, got it.
Hello, is this 119?
Hello, this is 119. Please speak.
My car is flooded.
I can't open the doors now.
There's no emergency hammer in the car.
I can't get out.
Don't panic.
Can you tell me your exact location?
The sunken passage under the Songmen Bridge.
Okay.
We have firefighters
near your location.
We've informed them.
Please keep your phone open.
Help!
Here! Here!
Here!
Help me!
I'm here.
Chief, the water is too deep here.
Slow down.
Chief, I'll get the car from the back.
Come out.
Let go!
I'll throw you into the water.
Bring me some clothes.
Do you know how many cars
are involved in accidents
in a radius of five kilometers within an hour?
There is a rainstorm red warning.
Why did you come out
instead of staying at home?
The hospital called us back on short notice.
Chief.
Find a shelter for yourself.
Did you know it was me
in the car just now?
It was so dangerous.
Even if a dog is trapped in the car,
I will save it too.