[English subtitles are available]
[Fireworks of my heart]
[Episode 10]
I heard from your mother
that she's recently been arranging blind dates for you.
How has it been?
Any progress?
Dad.
Can't I find
someone I like?
So
you already
have someone you like.
I don't want
to spend a life planned out for me.
I also don't want
to spend days that are predictable.
This is how parents are like.
They don't want their children
to go down the wrong path.
Our generation
had suffered a lot.
That's why we have some bad habits.
Whatever we do,
we like to
calculate the gains and losses.
That's why we have a narrow outlook.
We always think love and marriage
involves being on similar standings in all aspects,
including one's economic situation.
Your mother is doing this for your own good.
There's nothing wrong.
I don't mean
to go against Mom on purpose.
I just want to
have freedom and my say
in my own business.
Qin.
Can you be
honest with me?
Do you
still like
the boy with the surname Song?
No wonder your mother is so angry.
She will definitely not agree to that.
Well,
what about you?
Are you against it too?
To be honest,
I'm a little worried.
You know
your mother's temper.
She would do anything
to stop you two from being together.
Qin.
I really don't want
our family
to be in shambles because of this.
I was wondering why you applied for
a local school.
So it was because that hooligan
didn't get into college,
and you want to stay with him
and date secretly here.
You've really disappointed me.
Because of this hooligan,
this rascal,
you lied to your parents.
You even gave up on your future.
Mom.
He's not like what you said.
He skips classes, fights,
and couldn't even make it to college.
What can he do?
Qin.
Listen.
I will never allow you two
to be together.
If you won't listen to me,
and you think this person
is more important than your family,
then you have to make a choice.
Either you choose this family
or
follow that hooligan.
Mom.
When eating,
there are table manners.
First,
you need to sit upright
and hold onto the bowl.
Don't make a noise when you scoop.
After you finish the soup,
put the rice in place.
For each dish,
stick out your chopsticks
no more than three times in a row.
Grab the ones near you.
Don't stir the food around.
Got it?
Yes.
What did I tell you?
Girls should be dignified
and steady.
Listen to your parents.
Be good.
Understand?
It's windy.
Why didn't you wait inside?
It's okay.
I just arrived too.
Let's go.
Usually, when you apply for leave,
you have to return to work
within two hours?
More or less.
Before, every time I asked you out,
you'd find excuses.
This time, you agreed to it straightforwardly.
Xu Qin.
Just cut to the chase.
You...
you...
saved me a few times before.
This time,
we're even.
Even?
Fine.
We're even.
Let's not talk about this first.
Let's eat.
Xu Qin.
Just say it
These days,
you wanted to make up with me.
Now you regret it and are scared.
Is that
so hard for you to say?
I...
Say no more.
I know.
I'll accept whatever you say.
We're even now.
Fine.
I deserve it for taking a glance at you by the hallway
in the past.
What?
♫Tears, I cannot let go of you♫
[Electrical Hazard]
♫You've carved a beautiful and indelible scar in my heart♫
♫The heavy rain all day outside the window are my tears♫
♫The journey of time, please give me the answer I have been waiting for♫
♫Is that promise you made in the middle of summer still valid♫
[Electrical Hazard]
♫You're the wish I made in the middle of summer♫
Is there a fire?
Fire!
There's really a fire!
Hurry up!
Fire!
[Jiu Tian House]
The people are already evacuating.
Fire!
Step back.
Step back. Step back.
Step back, everyone!
[Jiu Tian House]
Be careful and step back!
I'm a firefighter.
Is anyone still inside?
The head chef is still inside!
Please save him.
Everyone, step back!
Back off! Back off!
Get down! Get down first!
Get down!
Come on.
Help! Anyone there?
Get out first.
Anyone there? Help!
There's one more.
He's out.
Head chef!
[Jiu Tian House]
Hurry, send him to the hospital.
Hurry up!
Help!
Here, come with me!
Come with me!
Come on!
[Jiu Tian House]
The fire rescue team will be here soon.
Everyone, please disperse.
Move out of the way of the fire exit.
Anyone else?
Anyone else inside?
[Jiu Tian House]
Turn on the water!
Open the tap!
Xu Qin, are you guys close?
Tell me.
Tell me, Xu Qin.
Actually, we're not that close.
It's okay. I can do it myself.
Give me his number.
His WeChat ID is fine too.
What do you want?
He's such a handsome firefighter
and he saved my life.
Of course I have to pursue him.
Quick, give me his number.
Please.
Please, please, please.
The last one on my Contacts list.
I love you the most. When I get him,
I'll treat you to a big meal.
Where? Where?
Here, here.
[Contacts]
The last one on the Contacts list.
Hang on.
Let me call him now.
Hello?
Hello? Nice to meet you.
I'm the girl you just saved,
with long hair and in a black skirt.
Do you remember me?
No.
It's okay. We'll meet again next time,
and then you'll remember me.
You saved my life,
so I want to treat you to a meal.
No need.
Let's have a drink then.
This man is quite interesting.
Are you still going to pursue him?
Of course.
I have a hunch that
he must be a good man.
I was interested in a scum
like Xiao Yixiao because I was blind
when I was young.
Wait and see.
I'll definitely get him.
Go.
Ready?
Spread out the water hose.
Pay attention to the nozzle.
Don't make any mistakes.
Jiang.
Chief.
Where is Yang Chi?
Yang Chi is...
in the gym.
Okay.
Carry on with your work.
Come on, let's do it again.
Insomnia?
[A middle-aged man committed suicide by jumping off a building]
Look at him.
His son
was abducted
when he was four.
His wife got sick two months ago
and died of illness.
This couple
starts work early and ends late just for a meagre amount of money.
They saved up just a meagre amount of money from selling buns.
And then the Peer-to-Peer Lending Crash happened
and they lost everything.
Sometimes,
perhaps for him,
death is easier than living.
Brother, do you think...
I...
Everyone's definition of life
is different.
We also make different choices.
You just fulfilled your duty.
So, in your heart,
there shouldn't be guilt.
Some people
are just trapped
in the moment.
What we need to do
is to give these trapped victims
one more choice.
The choice to live.
After all, some people
will choose to live
after overcoming the difficult situation.
Right?
I really envy you.
You never get lost.
I also have my moments.
No one is a piece of steel.
How can I never be lost
or troubled?
Song Yan.
Let's make up.
This time,
we're even.
[Song Yan]
Qin, what's wrong?
He's not here.
You want to talk about life with me, right?
Come here quickly.
I'll accompany you tonight.
Okay.
Ye'zi.
Take these two bottles over.
Give me this room.
When my friend arrives,
bring them here directly.
Why are you here?
Ms. Zhan.
It doesn't seem suitable
for just one person like you
to be occupying such a big room.
Let me get you another room.
I'll get you some guys
to get your party started.
Get lost.
Can you get
the guy I want?
Are you looking down on me?
There are no guys that
I can't get for you.
Are you trying to do
an indecent business with me?
What's so indecent about
finding you a partner?
Why did you come here today
without telling me?
Why are you also here
I didn't know you'd be here too.
Fine.
Two great gods, please don't leave.
Waiter, get me a glass of water.
Where's Qin?
I saw her car downstairs.
She didn't come up.
I don't think she's here yet.
What a day...
Let me explain.
This is really a coincidence.
I didn't ask them to come.
Qin, you're here.
Have a seat.
Rao, what are you doing?
I'm meeting someone.
You've been on your phone all night.
Who're you talking to?
You're so clingy.
It's a one-sided chat.
I asked him out for supper,
but he actually refused me.
Then, I sent many more messages,
but he didn't even reply.
This man is so cruel.
Do you know how hard it was for me
to find out
when he's not at work?
If I miss this chance, I have to wait.
Who is this man
giving you the cold shoulder despite your passion?
I'm happy.
I'm chasing him because I like him. What's wrong?
Isn't this what men do all the time?
Why can't women do it?
Right?
Of course you can.
I didn't say you can't.
He has agreed to see me!
Why are you freaking out?
What are you doing?
I have to go on a date.
I don't have time for you.
Who is he?
Why are you so interested in him?
A firefighter
who saved my life.
And he has
a very nice name,
Song Yan.
I'm leaving.
I need to wash my hands.
Are you okay?
What's this smell?
Come here.
What are you doing?
-It stinks.
-Come on.
It's said online that
it has to be pickled for a week.
It's been less than a week.
Why is it already so stinky?
Did you put too little
salt?
Cover it.
Cover it. Cover it. Cover it.
Is the fish originally this smelly?
Nonsense.
This mandarin fish is quite expensive.
You've wasted it.
Anyway, you'll have to eat it. I'll definitely not eat it.
It's too smelly.
Too smelly?
Who was the one who initially said durians
are too smelly and that she wouldn't eat them for the rest of her life,
and then later said that
it's addictive and that the smellier the better?
Why are you
so annoying?
You're annoying.
Okay, I'll stop.
Well, what is Yan'er doing?
He's upstairs.
He went to look for
Qin yesterday, right?
Why is he so...
It seems like this won't do.
We must be stricter with him.
What do you mean?
He should be reprimanded for his mistakes.
Make strict rules for him.
From now on, he's not allowed to see
Qin again.
If he's always sad after seeing her,
why should he see her?
You're right.
Let's talk to him now.
Let's go. I'll go with you.
Okay.
Yan'er.
Are you going out?
Is anything the matter?
Your uncle has something to tell you.
Go ahead.
Wait...
What is it?
What's stinking up the place?
Yes, that's what I want to talk about.
This stinky mandarin fish
is indeed very stinky.
It's so stinky that it's fragrant, don't you think so?
That's it?
W-Where are you going?
To take a walk.
Yes, go get some fresh air.
The night is very beautiful.
The air is good too.
Uncle.
Did you drink?
A little.
Come back early.
Why didn't you say it?
How can a man like me talk about such matters?
Commander Miao, you do it yourself.
I’ve already taught you everything.
What do you mean?
We agreed that you'll be the one saying it.
What's wrong with you?
I disguised it well, didn't I?
Come on.
You're useless.
Come in.
I don't want to go in. It stinks.
I'll get changed and take you for a walk
and let the smell in the house dissipate.
One more.
Give Boss' bottle
of Ardbeg Scorch to me.
Another one.
Boss, here's your wine.
Okay.
I bought this bottle of scorch
from an auction.
Try it.
Drink it yourself.
Why isn't Qin back yet?
Don't tell me she left again?
Let's go have a look.
Ye'zi.
What's wrong, Boss?
Go to the women's bathroom
to see if our friend is there.
She was at the bar counter just down
drinking alone.
She has left.
She just left.
[The Bar of Charm Color]
Qin.
Let me send you home.
No, I can go on my own.
Sir, Lanxuan Apartment.
Drive slowly.
Did Qin
drink to drown her sorrows?
No.
It was to strengthen her courage.
Come with me.
Sir, Wufang Street.
Didn't that gentleman say
to head to Lanxuan Apartment?
Wufang Street.
I want to go there. Thank you.
Okay.
She's not going home.
You were right.
[Tea]
Song Yan!
Who is it?
It's you?
What are you doing?
Do you know what time it is?
Stop right there!
Do you know what time
it is now?
Song Yan.
Song Yan, are you asleep?
It's me.
Stop knocking.
My brother is not here.
Where did he go?
He went on a date with someone else.
He's not coming back tonight.
You should go.
I feel like I'm going to die.
There's no point in living.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Why don't you have a seat?
These are my brother's shoes.
He forgot to take them in.
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
You...
Brother, look at her!
Why is she throwing a drunken tantrum at our home?
Why did you come here?
I'm sorry.
She's drunk and throwing a drunken tantrum.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Stop right there!
Where have you been?
I went out with a lady.
You know her.
Her name is... oh,
her surname is Zhan,
and her name is Xiaorao.
Xu Qin.
What are you doing?
Who are you to make a scene here?
Let's go.
What's there to say to someone like him?
I don't know if he's good enough for you.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
Yes.
You're not good enough for me.
You're definitely not good enough for me!
Because I like you
more than you like me.
I'm not good at socializing.
I don't like making friends.
Finance,
Law,
and Management.
Many professions don't suit me.
Only as a doctor,
where I just have to focus on my studies,
do I not have to worry about losing my job.
I can support myself.
After I came back from abroad,
I moved out from home.
I was planning to
gradually
stop taking money and things
from my family.
I was thinking of
how I could
appease my mom and dad so that they wouldn't be angry,
wouldn't go against me,
and wouldn't disown me as their daughter.
Maybe if I focused on my studies
and quickly became
a famous surgeon,
they would approve of me
in other aspects,
be proud of me,
and indulge me a little.
But what about you?
Song Yan, what did you do?
What did you do for me?
Let me ask you.
Yes.
I keep approaching,
and hesitating.
I keep going back and forth,
and I'm hesitant and weak.
I don't see any hope and I'm scared.
You've never
done anything
for our relationship.
Never.
Am I right?
Song Yan.
You don't like me that much, do you?
Do you not like me enough?
Otherwise, how could you
have never tried anything?
You never thought of getting close to me.
Why should I
go towards someone like you?
You always stay where you are
and wait for me to go to you.
Even if you saw me fall,
you wouldn't come and help me.
For someone like you,
Why should I...
Why should I go to you?
Yes.
I'm selfish.
I'm very selfish.
I'm selfish to the person I like too.
I only want to see you put in some effort
before I go towards you.
Otherwise, I'll lose everything,
while you stay where you are.
Then, what will become of me?
I'm not pure.
I'm the one who wants to argue.
I also want to see you put in some effort.
I also want you
to take a step towards me.
But why won't you come?
Song Yan, why won't you come?
Why won't you come?
I can't feel
your love for me at all.
You definitely don't like me that much.
You don't like me that much, do you?
You don't like me that much.
Why did you say that?
Why did you say
you like me to death?
I took it seriously.
I took it seriously, Song Yan!
-I took it seriously!
-Let's go home!
Get up.
Listen.
I won't go towards you ever again.
I won't.
It's not what you think!
Zhai Miao!
Brother.
♫Watch the sun go down slowly♫
♫It falls into your eyes and my heart♫
♫Stars are struggling to chase the rays of the setting sun♫
♫They don't want the radiance to be wasted♫
Brother.
♫Thank you for traveling through time and living in my heart♫
Brother!
♫I've never been afraid even though I have many scars♫
♫When I take a firm step towards you♫
♫Please answer me♫
♫Many houses are ablaze with lights, is there one that belongs to me?♫