[English subtitles are available]
[Fireworks of my heart]
[Episode 35]
Someone was trying to bribe you.
When did this happen?
[China Fire and Rescue]
Just now.
Have you ever seen
this person?
No.
You weren't involved in the investigation.
Someone was trying to frame you
and get you involved.
This tactic is so low.
[China Fire and Rescue]
Am I that stupid?
This is not simple.
This afternoon,
the investigation team went to the construction site.
According to them, the thermal insulation materials
stored on site
are all of Level B1.
They perfectly met the standard.
It's impossible.
First, they substituted the materials
and fished in troubled waters.
Then, they gave you this money.
There must be something
behind this.
You should
first submit the money
to the Commission for Discipline Inspection.
[Emergency]
[Nurse Station Work Code]
Has the CT scan result
of Bed No.15, Li Dalong,
come out?
His family refused to do it.
They said he had done it before.
They wouldn't listen to me.
The hospital is urging us to pay again.
The compensation we got
is running out,
but you still haven't recovered.
If it weren't your boss,
who cut corners
to save money,
you wouldn't have been so seriously burnt.
Stop nagging.
We've taken the money
and got fingerprinted.
What's the point of saying this?
Doctor.
Why haven't you done
CT scan yet?
We're not doing it.
I'll get him discharged
and let him recuperate back at home.
Discharged?
No.
He can't be discharged now.
There are rales in his lungs.
I suspect it's a complication of burns.
It may be pulmonary edema, or even sepsis.
If not treated in time,
it may be life-threatening.
Doctor.
You can't say things like that
to scare us
just because we are uneducated.
It's the truth.
Whether you'll do the test or not
is your call.
I've made myself clear.
Think about it.
How are you feeling?
[Red Boat Leading the Way, Dedication to Yancheng, Ironclad Discipline, Being Wise and Courageous]
[Fire]
The team has decided
to suspend him temporarily.
You'll have to take care of
the station affairs for now.
Is there really
no room for negotiation?
This is already the best solution
after comprehensive consideration.
The best solution?
What a joke!
[Improve Road Civility]
[Enhance Safe-driving Concept]
That video
is obviously edited.
Isn't that framing?
If you still decided to suspend him,
I'll quit.
We'll quit too.
[Enhance Safe-driving Concept]
[Improve Road Civility]
Supervisor.
Why is he suspended?
The Detachment has its own arrangements.
We can only wait for further news.
Why wait?
Let's just quit.
If we can still wait for further news, then...
Shut up!
Do what you should do.
Don't worry about me.
Get to work.
Go.
Yes.
Get to work.
You're suspended?
Keep it down.
Are you afraid that your parents can't hear you?
Just tell them I'm taking some time off.
What happened exactly?
I saw on the news that
Zhan Dapeng sacrificed his life,
and the cause of the fire
is still under investigation.
It's quite complicated.
Why did they suspend you?
This is completely unreasonable.
I think
you should change your job.
This way, we won't have to worry about you like this.
Even if I get fired,
I will
get to the bottom of this incident.
Do you think
the Meng family is behind this?
Don't talk nonsense.
That wasn't nonsense.
Have you forgotten
about what happened back then?
Not to mention the physical examination.
When you tried to join the army,
you finally managed to
be recommended for admission to the military academy
as an excellent soldier.
In the end,
it got messed up
right before the appraisal meeting.
And now,
this kind of thing happened again.
Don't you think
it's too similar?
Zhai Miao.
Don't bring that up again.
I didn't want to.
But is the Meng family willing to
let you go?
Besides,
as for what happened back then,
are you really willing to let it go?
I've told you
not to bring up
the past events anymore.
Although
this incident is related to Guokun,
it has no direct connection
with the Meng family.
They have no reason to mess with me.
Zhai Miao.
The past
is in the past.
As for now,
the truth is still unclear.
Why do you have to
trouble yourself with a bunch of assumptions?
Justice will be delivered
sooner or later.
I believe.
[Zhai's]
Why are you here?
Wufang Street is about to be relocated.
I want to see it more.
I can see you through.
Aren't you not allowed to drink
by company rules?
What happened?
I'm suspended
for now.
Suspended?
What? Why?
Is it because of the Junguang incident?
You didn't do anything wrong.
First, someone tried to give me
a bribe of 200,000 yuan.
Then, the Detachment
received a report letter,
saying that I took the money
and slandered Junguang Square,
because I said that something was wrong with their thermal insulation materials.
[China Fire and Rescue]
Pipi.
How many have you had?
Brother.
Don't you feel cold?
Every time we came back after putting out a fire,
Chief would buy me
a popsicle.
I feel it's burning inside
now that he's not here.
When do you think
Chief will get his job back?
We don't know that, either.
Brother.
These days,
I've always dreamed of Dapeng.
Dapeng has always been
telling me one thing.
But why can't I remember?
Alright.
We all
miss Dapeng very much.
Let's call it a day.
Wash up.
Have a good rest.
Look how dirty your face is.
Don't think too much.
Brother.
I remember now.
Dapeng said
17.48 seconds.
17.48 seconds?
What does that mean?
He said he
beat Chief at 100-meter obstacle course race.
He even outran Chief.
Why couldn't he outrun the fire?
Have you considered to
change your job?
To be honest,
I did think about it at first.
But then...
I didn't think too much at first.
I just took it as a job.
I trained hard every day.
When a fire took place,
I'd do my best.
I thought this kind of life
was quite simple.
There wasn't much to worry about.
But gradually,
being a firefighter became
more than a job to me.
It also became half of my life.
The fireman suit
became a part of me as well.
I can't leave it either.
Hope the truth
can be found out soon,
so that your name can be cleared,
and there will be a satisfactory explanation for Dapeng's death.
I also hope
you can go work in the Detachment soon,
so that you can
go to work at 9 a.m. and come home at 5 p.m. every day,
safe and sound.
The balance in the card is insufficient.
How much am I short?
More than 20,000.
[Cashier]
Another 20,000?
Come back when you have the money.
There are many people waiting in line.
Sorry.
I won't pay now.
[Cashier]
Next, please.
[Women]
Mum.
It's not that I don't want him to be treated.
I really have no choice.
Why is Li Dalong's life
so hard?
The compensation
has been used up.
The money I saved up
also ran out.
When I went to pay the bill,
the doctor said we are still 20,000 yuan short.
Where can I get that money?
I shouldn't have signed
the agreement
and accepted the hush money.
Now Dalong hasn't recovered,
but they don't want to be involved anymore.
I'm really cornered.
Mum.
There's really nothing I can do.
Mum, what are you doing?
Why are you packing your clothes?
We have no money for further treatment.
Let's transfer your dad back to our hometown.
The nurse said
the fee had been paid.
We can proceed with further treatment.
Look.
Who paid it?
Dr. Xu.
Our family can be saved.
Your dad can be saved.
[During the Operation]
[Preoperative diagnosis: Complications of burns]
[Type of anesthesia: General anesthesia]
[Surgical site: Chest]
[Operation Time]
[Family please wait outside]
Li Dalong's family.
Coming.
The operation went well.
You can rest assured.
Thank you.
By the way,
where is Dr. Xu?
Dr. Xu?
Dr. Xu has left.
Thank you.
Dalong.
Dr. Xu.
How is everything today?
All good.
It's just he woke up once due to the pain
last night.
Don't worry.
Post-operative pain won't last long.
It's a common phenomenon.
Feng Bei.
If he hurts badly,
give him an injection to relieve the pain.
Thank you, Dr. Xu.
It's my duty.
Who you should thank
are those firefighters.
They saved his life.
By the way, Dr. Xu.
How's the fireman
who saved Dalong's life?
Is he okay?
He sacrificed his life.
He sacrificed his life?
That fireman
was still so young.
Rest well.
Ring the bell if anything happens.
Let's go.
[Emergency Ward]
Dr. Xu.
You go ahead.
I heard
you know someone in the fire brigade?
I have something
to tell you.
Open the door!
Open it!
Clean and sharp!
Load the trucks and get them transferred.
Hurry up.
Police!
[Police]
Get off!
[Public Security]
Stand still.
[Guokun Group]
The cause of the fire at Junguang Square
has been preliminarily identified.
Project manager Zhao
set off fireworks illegally.
The sparks ignited
the thermal insulation materials stacked on the 12th floor
and caused a major fire.
Wang,
Secretary of Director's Office of Guokun Group,
colluded with Zhao
and substituted inferior thermal insulation materials
[Guokun Group]
for the original ones
to make profit from it.
And they used illegal means
to avoid fire safety inspections.
The two have been criminally detained
by the police.
The case is under
further investigation.
Please stay tuned to our channel
for more updates.
[China Fire and Rescue]
Your report
was highly recognized
by the investigation team.
Junguang Square
did resort to deceit
on the fire safety matter.
We
must strengthen
fire safety supervision and inspection.
[China Fire and Rescue]
The bribery
was totally a frame-up.
It's all clear now.
In this fire rescue,
you not only
made contributions to firefighting,
but also got wronged.
If you have any difficulties,
you can tell us.
[China Fire and Rescue]
I only have one request.
I hope the Detachment
can take care of Zhan Dapeng's parents.
He was their only son.
[China Fire and Rescue]
Don't worry.
No problem.
The organization will
do its best to take care of this matter.
Thank you, Dr. Li.
Why haven't you been cooperating
with the treatment actively?
No.
It's just I've been too busy lately.
You know that.
Besides,
we thought the treatment had been completed.
Right.
Those who were not badly injured
have been cured.
But you are badly injured.
Didn't I ask you
to come a few more times?
How could you not understand it?
I was wrong.
I'll come on time.
I'm sorry.
Enough. Stop talking.
Are you inhaling it?
Are you?
Say something.
I am.
You asked me not to talk.
Don't be angry.
I'll go see you later
after I'm done.
[Emergency Department]
Dr. Li.
Thank you.
[The Bravest]
Mum.
Dad.
I've done something y'all
can be proud of this time.
Well,
the Panpan you put up is cute.
Did you feel any different?
Not much.
It's all for serving the people.
I see you've lost weight.
You haven't been resting well lately, have you?
You care so much about me.
I just don't want you to trouble me.
Thank you, Nan.
Take care.
OK.
I accept the test.
I'll wait for your good news.
I will win.
The rest of you,
stand by.
If your teammates in the front fail,
those in the back,
fill the places even if you have to risk your life.
Yes!
We'll complete the mission.
[China Fire and Rescue]
Yang Chi!
Here!
Jiang Yi!
Tong Ming!
Here!
Zhang Wanzhang!
Wang Lin!
Here!
Li Chengshuo!
Wang Bin!
Here!
Fu Lei!
Shao Qiang!
Here!
Li Cheng!
Wang Hanxiang!
Here!
Wu Yongxin!
Liu Junkai!
Here!
Li Xinming!
[China Fire and Rescue]
Liu Junping!
Here!
Pi Shaojie!
Ge Zheng!
Here!
Zhan Dapeng!
[China Fire and Rescue]
Here!
Zhan Dapeng!
[China Fire and Rescue]
Thank you.
Mr. Meng.
You're back.
Qin isn't back?
No.
She's on emergency shift tonight.
It's so busy in the hospital.
We take her
as apple of our eye.
But what about her?
This matter
ended up like this.
It must be Song Yan
who's been stirring up the trouble.
Mum.
I agree with
Qin on this.
That's his duty.
Judging by this matter,
we can see
that person
has absolutely no sentiment
for our family.
If Qin
insists on being with him,
doesn't this mean
she doesn't want our family?
Don't say that.
She won't.
This incident was
caused by Gu's men,
who didn't do their work well
and caused such a major disaster.
We must admit it,
no matter it's punishment or chastisement.
The punishment has been done.
Fortunately,
the company
didn't suffer much.
After this,
Gu won't have
much say
in the company in the future, right?
He's responsible
for not managing his men well.
Yanchen.
When can you
take over from your father?
Look.
The situation is getting more and more complicated.
Your father is no longer as healthy as before.
Now the situation
is not under our control like before either.
How much longer do you want
to waste in that small company?
And Qin.
You should
discipline her.
For real.
These two kids
are both so troublesome.
We'll leave now, Dr. Xu.
[Contacts][Dad]
Hello?
Hello, Dad.
Qin.
Are you
off work?
Have you eaten?
Yes.
And I'm off work.
I just wanted to call you.
How have you been?
I'm good.
How about you?
How's your health?
Do you have antihypertensive drugs
with you all the time?
Don't worry too much
about company affairs.
I know.
Don't worry.
I...
I'm all right.
The company incident
didn't affect you much, right?
How should I put it?
It didn't affect me much, actually.
Don't worry.
You.
Just work hard
and take care of yourself.
Come home and visit us more.
Got it.
I'll hang up now, Dad.
As for your future work arrangements,
[China Fire and Rescue]
the Party Committee
has had our discussion.
But we still want to hear
your own opinion.
There are two options.
One is
to transfer to the Detachment.
The other one...
See for yourself.
You don't have to decide right away.
Think about it for a few days.
[Fire and Rescue]
Considering
Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station
[Unified command. Specialization and normalization. Highly responsive. Joint efforts at all levels. Peacetime and wartime alike.]
under Yanbei Fire and Rescue Team
fully demonstrates
its advanced and exemplary role,
takes protecting the life and property safety
of the people of Yancheng as its responsibility,
and stays true to its belief
and mission.
They effectively put out
a major fire accident,
and made great contributions to
securing the economic development of our city,
and the life and property safety of the people.
After discussion,
we hereby submit this report for approval
for establishing
Shilitai Fire and Rescue SWAT Station.
[Daily alert response] [Alert response]
Your instructions, please.
Commissar.
Mr. Gao.
I've made up my mind.
I'll stay at Shilitai
and accept this challenge.
Am I right?
[China Fire and Rescue]
[30th Anniversary of the Establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station]
Today
is the 30th anniversary
of the establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station.
Thank you for coming, leaders.
Please welcome
the Commissar, Lian Jie,
to address us.
[30th Anniversary of the Establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station]
Today
is a big day.
It's the 30th anniversary of the establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station.
The past 30 years
has been the 30 years of
growth and honor
for Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station.
[30th Anniversary of the Establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station]
In the past 30 years,
Shilitai
responded and took action
for over 35,000 times.
We rescued
and evacuated
over 170,000 people.
The people's properties that we protected
are worth over one billion yuan.
The commanders and firefighters of Shilitai
advanced wave upon wave, stayed true to their mission,
and had no fear of difficulties.
You didn't fail
the fire services badges on your hats
or the people's expectations.
[30th Anniversary of the Establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station]
Down.
[Always Loyal to the Party and People]
Please welcome
the leader from the Municipal Party Committee to address us.
[Fire and Rescue]
[30th Anniversary of the Establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station]
Comrades.
The commanders and firefighters
of Shilitai
have been guarding
our city
[30th Anniversary of the Establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station]
[Bestowal Ceremony of the Title "Guardian of Yancheng"]
with their flesh and blood, and their spirit as strong as steel.
You deserve the name
of
guardian of the city.
In order to inherit
and carry forward
the spirit of rescue
and the spirit of enterprise
of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station
for 30 years,
[30th Anniversary of the Establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station]
as well as to
express our gratitude
to the firefighters here
who have been serving our city
quietly and devotedly.
The Municipal Party Committee
and the Municipal Government
decided to
bestow the title
of "Guardian of Yancheng"
on
Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station.
Comrades.
In the new period
[30th Anniversary of the Establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station]
[Bestowal Ceremony of the Title "Guardian of Yancheng"]
and new era,
we are faced with
new tasks
and new challenges.
Next,
under the leadership
of the Municipal Party Committee,
the Municipal Government, and the Corps,
we'll further optimize
our fire and rescue team,
so that we can
turn
Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station
to
a SWAT station.
We will
upgrade our team
with the aim of
becoming the
national and main force of emergency rescue.
[Always Loyal to the Party and People]
We'll become a sharp knife
among the rescue teams.
Do we all have confidence in that?
Yes!
Good!
Song Yan!
Here!
Get on the stage!
[30th Anniversary of the Establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station]
Yes!
Song Yan.
This is not only a military award,
[Guardian of Yancheng]
but also a military order.
Take it.
And guard it.
Yes!
Please.
[Guardian of Yancheng]
Thank you.
Loyal to the Party!
Be Disciplined!
Go Through Fire and Water!
Serve the People!
Loyal to the Party!
Be Disciplined!
[Always Loyal to the Party and People]
Go Through Fire and Water!
Serve the People!
Loyal to the Party!
[Fire and Rescue]
Be Disciplined!
[30th Anniversary of the Establishment of Shilitai Fire and Rescue Station]
[Bestowal Ceremony of the Title "Guardian of Yancheng"]
Go through fire and water!
Serve the people!
[Guardian of Yancheng]
[Miss a city for someone in the city]
You're back.
Aren't you working the night shift?
I switched shifts.
Perfect timing.
You must be craving Sauerkraut fish.
I'll cook it right away.
When will you
start working in the Detachment?
The transfer order has been issued, right?
Yes.
So, are you going or not?
I've decided to
stay at Shilitai.
At first,
I did want to go work in the Detachment.
But now, Shilitai
has been fully upgraded.
Our equipment and staff
have all been improved.
In the future,
it'll get better and better.
Actually, I've been struggling.
I thought about it for days
before I made this decision.
Why did you struggle?
Was it because of me?
Were you afraid that
I'd hold you back?
No.
Why didn't you discuss with me
before making such an important decision?
I...
I didn't want to put you under pressure.
I was also afraid that you'd choose to support me
because you're sensible,
and you'd be wronged.
So, every time, you chose
not to tell me.
I'm sorry.
I was thoughtless.
I'm not saying this
to defend myself.
But...
I don't know why,
but when I'm faced with pressure,
I always tend to handle it myself.
I don't want to transfer it to you.
Indeed.
When you feel pressured,
the first thing you think of
is not to share it with me,
but to hide it from me.
You think it's for my own good,
to make me worry less.
You're always like this.
You didn't tell me when you were suspended,
and you didn't let me know that you wouldn't work in the Detachment.
What do you take me for?
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
I have nothing to hide.
What about your gunshot wound?
Tell me.
What about
your failing the repetition?
What about your joining the army?
What about your
becoming a firefighter?
Why do Zhai Miao,
Uncle, and Aunt all know about everything,
but I'm the only one who can't know?
I just want to know the truth.
Or give me an explanation.
There's no truth
or explanation for many things.
So this is your attitude?
I...
Xu Qin.
For real.
I've
never lied to you.
Trust me.
I will never hurt you.
You've already hurt me.
There shouldn't be
any secret between us.
Now I feel like
you've been keeping me
out of many things.
I feel like
you've never treated me as your family.
How could I not treat you as my family?
I treat you
as the most important family to me in this world.
Don't you know?
Then tell me
what's going on.
Fine.
Even if you don't want to say it now,
you have to give me a reason
why you don't want to tell me.
I don't know how.