♪In rain or shine♪
♪When you're around,
the sun shines through♪
♪Spare ourselves the endless thoughts
and guessing games♪
♪Let's just meet
and escape these frames♪
♪I stand within the shadows deep♪
♪My hand outstretched,
your rescue I keep♪
♪Even if the world falls apart♪
♪No distance is too far♪
♪To stop us from coming together♪
♪Through the night,
you're at the end of the line♪
♪To protect you is my humble wish♪
♪Farewell, to the timid soul I knew♪
♪It was you who made me brave and new♪
=Always Home=
(Adapted from Xiao Ge's novel, Always Home)
=Episode 29=
(Love Is The Only Answer)
(Huandao Technology)
Jing.
Hello? What's the matter?
What are you doing?
I just got back to the dorm.
How are you after joining a big company?
I'm alright.
Why does your tone
sound a little down?
I just have a small problem.
Currently,
the company wants Yangwu to transform.
Transform?
That's not their attitude
when they recruited you.
Why the sudden transformation?
From the company's perspective,
projects are about making money.
I can understand that,
but
I don't want to compromise.
Don't compromise then.
I believe in you.
Got it.
How about you? How are you?
Me?
I'm fine.
I ran into Tian Chi just now.
We're under the same supervisor.
Maybe we'll do experiments together
in the future.
Do your experiments then.
Would you mind?
If you mind,
then...
I'm not that stingy.
As long as it's good for your studies,
I support it.
Okay.
Alright.
I'll go back to work now.
Take care of yourself.
Don't exhaust yourself.
You too.
I love you.
Love you too.
Bye.
Senior Gao.
I've sorted out the data you want.
I'll leave it here.
Okay.
By the way, Chen,
did you collect the packages?
They're here.
Here.
Check this out.
Help me check
the thesis data.
Give me as soon as possible.
Also, help me organize my petri dish
observation records
in the next two weeks.
Sure.
And
help me write
two research reports.
Make sure
there are no typos.
Senior Gao.
That's inappropriate.
You have to write it yourself.
Just write it when you're told to.
But this is against the rules.
I'll do everything else
you ask me to do.
But if this matter
is discovered,
we'll all get criticized.
What do you want then?
Sorry, Senior Gao.
I can't help you with this.
I'm really sorry.
Senior Gao.
Huan'er
didn't mean to offend you.
She just speaks her mind.
Don't take it to heart.
Tian Chi.
What's your business here?
How about this?
I'll help you
when I'm done.
You'll help me do it?
Is the work I assigned her
appropriate
for a first-year graduate student?
Why can others do it
but she can't?
She's a girl.
Take extra care of her.
So what if she's a girl?
If you think the work
I arranged is unreasonable,
you can talk to the professor.
Senior Gao.
That's not what I meant.
Enough.
You don't need to attend
the clinical pharmacy forum
at the end of the year.
Why?
You tell me.
Because you have to
take care of your junior!
Take good care of her.
(I still remember)
(how ambitious we were)
(when we first entered the campus,)
(until we lost our shelter)
(and really embarked on the journey.)
I'm leaving.
(Facing the reality of life,)
(I realized how naive I was)
(at that time.)
(There's no other place)
(that can tolerate us
as unconditionally)
(Second-Hand Books Market and Trends)
(as home and school.)
(We stumble)
(as we experience
the inevitable path of growth.)
(Not only work,)
(but also relationships.)
What is it?
You're acting all mysterious.
You can find out when you open it.
What's all this?
Why did you send these to me?
I'm afraid that you'll miss me.
All's good now.
You can see me around you
when you open your eyes.
♪You are my blue♪
♪Blue♪
♪Coke in the bottle♪
♪Nowhere to sew myself together♪
♪The transparent packaging♪
♪Hates being exposed like this♪
♪The world♪
♪Has so many colors♪
♪I don't like many of them♪
♪It's rare to find one that I like♪
♪I like it but it's not suitable♪
(Huan'er)
♪You are my blue♪
(Babe)
(User Experience, Service Quality)
(Sorry, I was in a meeting just now.)
♪Blue♪
♪You are my blue♪
(Babe, Call Cancelled)
♪The sorrow under the neon lights♪
♪I don't quite understand
how to get through♪
♪The flood of neon lights♪
♪Red, yellow, white and blue♪
♪You're every frame of the picture♪
Hello?
Is this Du Man?
Yes.
This is Jing City's
Tinghu District Police Station.
Do you know Zhang Wanfang?
Thank you.
Don't you think I'm stupid?
She deceived me with just a few words.
I even gave her
all my savings.
It's her fault,
not yours.
That's why
people should be more rational.
Do you want to try again?
Try again.
Yes!
(Only after growing up)
(do we understand)
(that we're just
ordinary people in life.)
(Right and wrong)
(sometimes become blurred.)
(And some answers)
(don't seem that important.)
(What are you doing? I'm going to bed.)
Thank you for telling me so many things.
Do you think
there's anything
that can be improved on our website?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you see what time it is?
Sorry.
(Babe:
What are you doing? I'm going to bed.)
(Sorry, I was busy
and didn't see the notification.)
Xichi.
We only
have this left to call.
Let's stop here today.
It's too late.
We'll disturb people.
Besides,
we've basically
gone through all the users.
Most of them are owners
of second-hand bookstores.
They have no real value.
I have an interesting one here.
Highly active,
but doesn't have a lot of transactions.
They mostly buy niche books.
I'll send it to the group for you
to take a look.
The final decision-making meeting
is just around the corner.
We haven't gotten any idea yet.
Are we packing up
and leaving just after joining?
It's late.
Let's take a break first.
Goodbye, Fu Ying.
Light Messenger?
What a pretentious name.
Xichi, are you not leaving?
(User Data, User ID: Light Messenger)
Hello?
Good morning.
Well...
I was too busy yesterday.
I didn't see your message in time.
You won't be mad at me, right?
I'm mad.
Just kidding.
By the way,
how have you been these past two days?
Have you solved it?
Not yet.
What about you?
You called me yesterday.
What do you need?
Nothing.
I just wanted to hear your voice.
You missed me?
How about I
record
a wake-up call
or a phone ringtone for you?
Forget it.
(Backend Homepage, User Data)
If I hear your voice,
I won't be able to get out of bed.
These two days,
I somehow...
Huan'er.
Sorry.
(User Data)
I have another meeting here.
I'll go to the meeting first.
Can I call you back?
Get to work then.
I'm going to the lab soon.
Okay.
Bye.
What's wrong?
Do you have a stomachache?
Maybe I'm hungry.
I'll just go back and eat something.
Why don't you go back and rest?
I'll take care of the rest.
I'm fine. I also need this data.
Huan'er.
Huan'er!
Fu Ying.
You haven't found Light Messenger?
No, I contacted them.
They're always out of the service area.
It's time for lunch.
Eat first.
I'm so busy that I forget.
I'll go eat first.
Go ahead.
The number you dialed is unanswered.
Please call again later.
Sorry.
The number you dialed is unanswered.
You finally picked up.
What are you doing? Why did you keep...
Are you in the hospital?
You're not feeling well?
My gastroenteritis has flared up.
I feel much better
after getting an IV drip.
Gastroenteritis?
Why did you suddenly
get gastroenteritis?
Did you eat something
that upset your stomach?
My stomach was upset yesterday.
I thought I'd be fine
after a good night's sleep.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't think it was a big deal.
How are you feeling now?
If I could be by your side...
Huan'er.
I just bought you some porridge.
Eat it while it's hot.
Thank you.
Tian Chi.
I thought you left.
No.
Was it Jing Xichi?
Yes.
Eat it while it's hot.
Eating it
will make your stomach feel better.
You can't faint again.
Thank you, Tian Chi.
I've troubled you enough today.
You should go back and rest.
Sure.
You should rest early too.
Thank you.
You fainted?
In the lab today.
Tian Chi happened to see me
and sent me to the hospital.
Which hospital are you in?
I'll ask Yan Mu to accompany you.
No.
I can take care of myself.
You should handle Yangwu's affairs.
Rest
a bit longer then.
Call me if anything happens.
Bye.
Why are you back so early today?
What's wrong?
Chen Huan'er fainted
due to gastroenteritis.
Tian Chi sent her to the hospital.
Why were they together?
No.
I'm really worried.
I have to go back to see her.
Isn't your decision-making meeting
the day after tomorrow?
Are you going back now?
Chen Huan'er
needs me the most right now.
I have to go back to see her.
Well...
It's late, and there's no train.
How are you going to go back?
Driving license.
I'll rent a car back.
Okay, go ahead.
You have my support.
I'll go now.
Take your time.
Press it.
Thank you.
Huan'er.
Tian Chi.
Why are you still here?
I'm worried about you being here alone.
Let me send you back.
I feel much better now.
I can walk on my own.
Let's go.
We're here.
Sorry for bothering you today.
I'll go upstairs first.
Okay.
If you don't feel well again,
remember to tell me.
Thank you
for taking care of my girlfriend.
Sorry to bother you.
Huan'er is my junior.
It's my job to take care of her.
I will take good care of Chen Huan'er.
Next time this happens,
you don't need to worry.
Are you sure?
If Chen Huan'er
faints in front of me again,
you want me to ignore her?
Jing Xichi.
If you really love Chen Huan'er,
how come you didn't even know
she was sick?
You weren't by her side
during her most difficult times.
You have no right
to stop others from being nice to her.
Hello? Senior Gao.
What's wrong?
Hurry and pack your things.
Follow me to Tonglin City tomorrow
for a growth survey
of medicinal plants in the wild.
We'll be staying over,
so bring some change of clothes.
Why so sudden?
Can I not go first?
No.
It's been arranged.
Here's the thing, Senior Gao.
I just got back from the hospital.
I'm not feeling well.
Can I go in two days?
Our experiment
can't be postponed
just because you want to rest.
Senior Gao.
What do you mean by that?
Even if it's delayed,
it's because
you didn't plan
and notify in advance.
Fine. Chen Huan'er.
If you really don't want to go,
I'll find someone else.
But I'm not sure
whether you can
get the credit for this project.
No.
I did everything I should have done
and things I shouldn't have done
in this experiment.
Who are you to deny my credit?
Just because I'm the person in charge
of this project.
Okay.
Got it.
(I'm downstairs.)
Why are you here?
When did you come?
You're sick.
I want to come back to see you.
How are you?
Still feeling unwell?
I'm fine now.
By the way,
how's your proposal going?
I haven't finished writing it yet.
Well...
Why don't you hurry back to work?
So you don't want me
to come back and see you?
No.
That's not what I meant.
What I mean
is that I don't want you to miss work
because of me.
Chen Huan'er.
I don't want to be
the last one to know that you're sick.
I don't want Tian Chi to be the one
to take you to the hospital
and accompany you back to the dorm
instead of me.
I didn't let him send me.
He was waiting at the hospital.
What do you mean by that?
You don't trust me?
I trust you.
I think you just don't trust me.
What are you agitated about?
I'm not agitated.
Didn't you say it yourself?
If it weren't for Tian Chi,
would you have come?
I'll come, of course.
With you being so busy,
will you usually come?
When I said I miss you,
did you come?
So do you think I came back
because of Tian Chi?
Yes!
Do you know we haven't
had a good talk for a long time?
I also don't want
to have to see your updates
through Fu Ying's social media.
Chen Huan'er.
I've tried very hard.
I'm under great pressure every day
just to finish it quickly
and come back to see you.
And then what?
As soon as I came back,
I saw Tian Chi
sending you back to the dorm!
I've tried very hard
to control my emotions.
And then what?
When I came back
and we met,
the first thing you said
was to let me leave!
That's not what I meant!
Can you be more mature?
Jing Xichi.
Are you the only one
who's tired every day?
I'm tired too.
I attend classes
and do experiments every day.
I also have to go to the mountains
for research tomorrow.
I'm really tired.
Answer it.
Hello?
We found Light Messenger.
They're in Wu'an.
Send me the address.
I'll go find them.
Okay, I'll send you the address.
Alright.
Bye.
Huan'er.
I don't want to argue with you.
You should hurry back.
I know that Yangwu's project
is important to you.
Don't delay your work because of me.
I'll go back to pack my things.
♪You're silent in the midst of the lies♪
♪You're also indifferent
to tortuous speculation♪
♪After going through
the story's separations and reunions♪
♪Deprived of regret♪
♪You obviously miss me too♪
♪Why didn't you tell me?♪
♪Gentleness descends from the eyes♪
♪Wrapping up time with me♪
♪You obviously love me too♪
♪Don't miss it again♪
♪Gather roses and fireworks♪
♪I'll watch the sun rise
and the moon set with you♪
Excuse me.
Are you Light Messenger?
Hello?
Hello.
Light Messenger?
My name is Jing Xichi.
The founder of Yangwu.
Sorry
to bother you.
My colleague
should have told you
why I'm here, right?
It's mainly because
Yangwu encountered
some difficulties recently.
We're facing transformation.
You've been a regular user
of our website.
Among all users,
your login rate
and activity level
have always been very high.
That's why I want to see
if you
can give us any advice.
Actually,
I want to see you too.
Meet me?
Why?
I want to thank you.
I'm
not very good
at dealing with others.
I used to stay at home every day.
I'm not talkative either.
I'm either reading a book
or looking at the stars
with a telescope.
I first registered Yangwu
because
I lacked money.
Astronomy books are quite expensive.
I can't afford it.
I can only look for old books
that are sold at a discount.
I didn't expect
to meet a group of like-minded buddies
on Yangwu
by accident.
I used to like astronomy very much
because I think
every star is far away.
The stars are lonely.
The same goes for people.
But Yangwu gave me friends.
It made me realize
that as long as each star
illuminates one other,
they can gather
into the brightest galaxy
in the dark night.
(The Meteorological Observatory
issues an orange warning.)
(There will be typhoons and heavy rains
in some areas.)
(Please stay safe when you're out.)
Sorry.
The user you're calling
is temporarily unavailable.
Please call again later.
Sorry.
The user you're calling
is temporarily unavailable.
Please call again later.
Hello?
Do you have Tian Chi's phone number?
Yes. What's the matter?
Send it to me.
I can't get in touch with Chen Huan'er.
Okay, I'll send it to you.
Hello?
Hello? Tian Chi?
I'm Jing Xichi.
Do you know where Chen Huan'er is?
She went to Tonglin Village
to do research.
Tonglin Village?
(Soil Fertilizer
Nutrient Level Rapid Tester)
By the way, Chen Huan'er,
take a work photo for me.
Three,
two,
one.
All done.
Okay.
Take a look.
Not bad.
Okay.
Keep an eye on it here.
Wait.
What about you?
I'll go to the village and hand out
the questionnaires.
Handle this first.
I'll come find you later.
Okay?
Lu.
No...
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Hello? Jing.
I have Yangwu's proposal
for the meeting,
but I can't go back.
Go to the meeting with Zhou Ye.
Me?
Where did you go?
Something happened to Huan'er.
I'm going to find her.
But you're the one in charge of Yangwu.
Is it appropriate
for me to take your place?
It's okay.
We're all a team.
Besides, you've done no less for Yangwu
than I have.
If it weren't for you,
Yangwu wouldn't be where it is today.
What should I say then?
It's raining so hard,
but you're going up
for scientific research?
It's too dangerous.
The weather was good just now.
Who knew the weather on this mountain
would change so quickly?
Yeah.
The mountains around Tonglin Village
are too dangerous.
There was a wildfire here
many years ago.
A firefighter
was trapped in the mountains
and never came out.
He never came out?
Who is it?
Where's Chen Huan'er?
She went up the mountain
to collect samples.
No news of her after that.
I can't reach her.
Letting her go alone today?
The weather was fine this morning.
Who knew
it would suddenly start to rain?
Don't worry.
Maybe her phone
just doesn't have a signal.
Do you even have a heart?
You...
Jerk.
Chen Huan'er!
(Retreat first.)
(Retreat.)
(Hurry up!)
(Catch up.)
(Hurry.)
(Hurry and retreat!)
(Xichi.)
(Thank you for your hard work
over the years.)
(You're really a grown-up now.)
Drink something hot.
Warm yourself up.
Thank you.
There's no signal here.
I just tried.
It's late now. It's dangerous
to descend the mountain.
Let's wait till dawn.
What is this place?
This is our supply stop
for sample collection.
Why did you come here suddenly?
I couldn't get in touch with you.
So I called Tian Chi.
He said you went to Tonglin Village.
I heard
and couldn't care about anything else.
Are you okay?
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm fine.
What happened to you
just now?
I'm fine.
Wait here.
Take this.
What's this?
This is the vegetation soil
after the fire.
After the fire,
the vegetation restoration period
can be as short as a dozen years
or as long as several decades.
It's a very long process,
but
it continues to grow
even if it looks barren.
One day,
it will return
to its original lush appearance.
Huan'er.
Sorry.
I shouldn't have
lost my temper with you yesterday.
It's all over now.
Let's not mention it anymore.
This is nice.
It seems like
we haven't sat together
quietly like this
for a long time.
In these past few days,
I've been thinking
whether my decision to leave Wu'an
for Jing City
was right or wrong.
It's true
that I've been busy this month,
but it's also true
that my heart feels empty.
When I was in Wu'an,
my favorite thing of the day
was to take the subway for half an hour
at 6:30 PM
and change buses three times
so that I could go across the city
to see you.
But after arriving in Jing City,
there's no bus
or subway
that can take me to you.
I feel the same way.
I've already regarded
Wu'an as my other home.
But since you left,
I just feel
that even the most familiar places
have become unfamiliar.
Chen Huan'er.
Will you regret
being with me?
Have you lost your mind?
Do you know
why I'm called Chen Huan'er?
Because I was always hospitalized
when I was a kid.
The nurses wouldn't
call patients' names.
They only called the patient in bed 3
or the patient in bed 5.
Whenever my mom
heard these words,
she would be frightened.
But my mom said
since we're stuck with it,
we'll try to turn the bad
into good.
That's why
those words
became my name.
[*Patient sounds like Huan'er in Chinese]
She hopes I can
grow up happily
amidst laughter and joy.
I've been thinking about it
over the years.
Am I happy?
I didn't know before,
but now I know.
I'm quite happy.
Especially after meeting you.
You never reject
my weird ideas
and always
support me silently behind me.
(Maybe you're a little unreliable)
(in the eyes of outsiders.)
(But in my eyes,)
(your unreliability)
(is exactly what I need.)
That's why
I'm grateful to have met you.
I also cherish our relationship.
I don't regret it.
Chen Huan'er.
I love you.
Why so sentimental?
Jing Xichi.
I love you too.
♪Fallen leaves flutter past your gaze♪
♪I dream of worlds within your days♪
♪Countless times,
I write your name in my heart♪
♪Wishes whispered to the stars above♪
♪How many faces in the glass I see♪
♪Time's gentle hand
pulling me out of my cocoon♪
♪Under the sun,
a rainbow butterfly takes flight♪
♪To rest upon your left shoulder bright♪
♪I still hear your promise in my ears♪
♪Before we said goodbye,
your spirit free♪
♪And full of life♪
♪If summer could last a little longer♪
♪Would regrets rewrite
where we'd gone wrong?♪
♪And let me be there with you
at the end of the story♪
♪Watching your silhouette from behind♪
♪My footsteps slow, we were too young♪
♪To know right from wrong♪
♪Your sweat-kissed face
I hold in my memory♪
♪Glows as bright as ever♪
♪I hope one day we'll meet again♪
♪At just the right time♪