♪In rain or shine♪
♪When you're around,
the sun shines through♪
♪Spare ourselves the endless thoughts
and guessing games♪
♪Let's just meet
and escape these frames♪
♪I stand within the shadows deep♪
♪My hand outstretched,
your rescue I keep♪
♪Even if the world falls apart♪
♪No distance is too far♪
♪To stop us from coming together♪
♪Through the night,
you're at the end of the line♪
♪To protect you is my humble wish♪
♪Farewell, to the timid soul I knew♪
♪It was you who made me brave and new♪
=Always Home=
(Adapted from Xiao Ge's novel, Always Home)
=Episode 18=
(Going Separate Ways)
Zhang Yang!
That was a nice kick!
Zhang Yang.
This is our new roommate,
Jing Xichi.
Hello.
Come on, let's play a match.
I haven't played in a long time.
Come on.
You must know how to play.
Let's go!
We're just short of one person.
Come on.
Let's go.
Okay.
I'll try.
Let's go.
Huan'er,
which course is your friend studying?
Computer Science.
Computer Science?
So he's going to be a programmer, right?
I don't know what he'll do
in the future.
Aren't programmers
all those
nerdy types,
wearing black-rimmed glasses,
checkered shirts,
and always looking serious?
Is he nerdy?
I don't know.
However,
he's very childish.
He's so handsome!
Take a picture for me!
Exactly!
- Nice!
Over here! Over here!
Run, quick!
Nice shot!
Great!
- Nice shot!
- Defend!
Wow, impressive!
You're Beckham in China.
Chen Huan'er!
I sent you so many messages,
why didn't you reply?
I didn't see them.
I knew it.
Song even thought you were mad at me.
Come on, we're so close.
Why would you be mad?
Oh, right.
My mother let me
bring you some medicine.
Here, take it.
Bye.
Let's go.
Huan'er.
So is this
your programmer friend?
So is this your little sister, Huan'er?
We're high school classmates
who live in the same compound.
Dude,
if you keep gossiping,
I'll kick you so hard
you'll call me Dad.
You're so fierce!
That's the spirit!
You can't play football
without a bit of aggression.
Stop staring and let's continue.
Stop looking.
Don't be so reluctant.
Come on.
Pass it to me!
I squeezed too much. Take some.
Thank you.
(Not bad, but I think Tian Chi
from pharmacy course is more handsome.)
Huan'er.
Look.
This.
Is this your handsome friend
from Computer Science?
(Not bad, but I think Tian Chi from
the pharmacy course is more handsome.)
(Within three minutes,)
(I want all the information)
(on this football guy.)
(I declare)
(he is the new
heartthrob of Wuan University.)
(He's just okay.)
(I think Tian Chi
from the pharmacy course)
(is more handsome.)
Yes.
Was he very popular
at your high school?
Do you think he's handsome?
Of course!
Honestly,
he's pretty good-looking.
Just be honest,
during the three years as his classmate,
did you ever have
any thoughts about him?
Yes.
Every day I wanted to shoot him,
especially today.
A famous psychologist
once said:
The essence
of avoiding your true feelings
is guilt.
That makes so much sense.
Which psychologist said that?
I did.
The student council senior
invited me to a social barbecue.
Why don't you
come with me?
Sure.
Would that be okay, though?
She invited you, not us.
If we go, wouldn't it be...
It's fine.
It's a welcome event, after all.
The more, the merrier.
In that case, I need to sleep early.
So it's settled then.
Where's Dong Huixin?
I haven't seen her all day.
She's really over the top.
Forget it, let's sleep.
Let's sleep.
Good night.
(Are you still mad?)
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Hope we can get along well.
It's late now.
Let's get to know
each other better tomorrow.
Good night.
Um...
Do you think it's warm?
Not really.
Left.
Is Yan Mu out again?
He thinks we're
too loud when we play games.
He says it affects his karma.
So he went to the lake
to chant scriptures.
Fine.
Tonight, the student councils
from various faculties
are hosting a big social event.
They're having a barbecue.
Are you coming?
Yes!
Jing, what about you?
No.
Jing.
I heard you've been trending
on the school forum.
Shouldn't you take this chance
to meet more people?
Expanding your network
is just as important
as studying seriously.
No need.
Jing.
Just go.
A senior specifically asked me
to bring you over.
If you don't go,
how am I supposed to explain?
Catch.
Then I'm definitely not going.
Come on, Jing.
Do me a favor.
No.
Are you really not going?
Then we're heading out.
Let's go.
What a pity.
(Have you packed? Our dorm doesn't
have air conditioning. Does yours?)
(Also, let's have dinner tonight.)
(Are you still mad?)
What are you doing?
Chen Huan'er.
Hurry up and pack.
I'm done.
What did you pack?
What's wrong?
She means
you should put on some makeup
and change clothes.
Is this not okay?
Chen Huan'er.
Are you really planning
to just show up like this for dinner?
Isn't it just
a casual gathering?
This isn't an ordinary dinner.
It's your first time
meeting the seniors.
You need to make a good impression.
Even if you don't want
to join the student council,
you should
at least tidy up a bit.
Look up.
Lipstick too?
Press your lips together.
Put this on as well.
Fine, you both...
Hurry up.
Let me see.
Are you satisfied?
Yes.
Let's go.
We're running late!
Well.
First of all,
welcome
to today's gathering!
I'll say
a few words.
I really hope you all
consider joining our art department.
Our department
is full of handsome guys
and beautiful girls,
and it's the most popular department
of the student council.
Right.
Since you've spoken,
I'll say a few words
for the sports department.
We are pretty straightforward.
Tonight, I just want everyone
to eat well, drink well,
and have a great time!
Nice!
Great! Great!
Good!
Tian Chi.
Cheers.
Nice to meet you.
Don't drink alone.
I'll drink with you.
All right.
Watch your manners.
Be ladylike.
Look at the good stuff I bought.
Here.
Be ladylike.
Try this.
Thanks.
Huan'er?
Senior Tian Chi?
Why are you here?
I'm in the student council.
I was busy earlier,
but I came over once I was done.
Do you want a skewer?
Here.
Thanks.
Would you like some beer?
I'll pass.
Thanks.
I saw you're studying pharmacy.
Was that your choice?
Do you plan to go
into drug research
or some other field?
I haven't thought that far ahead.
I'll just take it one step at a time.
The semester hasn't even started yet.
What if I can't keep up?
Your answers
are always unexpected.
This beer is pretty good.
It tastes just like juice.
Are you sure you don't want to try?
I...
I'll pass.
Um...
Is Jing really not coming?
I texted him.
He said he's not coming.
I'll text him again.
Okay.
(Everyone's waiting for you.)
(Hurry and come!)
(I'm not coming.)
You can really hold your liquor.
Drink up!
Drink more!
Come on.
More!
You should slow down.
What's going on with this kid?
She's not answering the phone.
Come on, pick up!
She's...
Still can't get through?
This kid
just won't pick up. I've called
several times.
Could it be
because you and Xichi lied to Huan'er
and upset her?
That kid is so stubborn.
Who does she take after?
Goodness.
Call Xichi and ask him.
She's probably fine.
Right, good idea.
I'll call Xichi.
(Aunt Lina)
Hello, Aunt Lina.
Xichi.
Is Huan'er with you?
No.
Didn't she contact you?
She hasn't messaged me all day.
Could something have happened to her?
What's wrong?
Is Chen Huan'er unreachable?
I've been calling,
but she won't pick up.
Xichi, can you find her?
Okay.
Don't panic.
I'll ask around.
Okay.
What's going on?
Huan'er.
Are you all right?
Do you want some water?
These...
Did she drink all of these?
This alcohol has a strong aftereffect.
Is she all right?
Huan'er.
What should we do?
Let her drink some water.
Huan'er.
I feel dizzy.
Chen Huan'er.
Your mother called you.
Where's your phone?
My phone...
It's in
my bag.
Right. It's here.
It's here.
It's in the bag.
I found it.
Sorry.
Her alcohol tolerance isn't great.
We'll leave first.
No battery.
My phone's dead.
Charge it when we get back.
Let's go.
We're heading off too, Qiu Li.
We'll leave now.
We're going back to the girls' dorm.
Goodbye.
Hey, pass me the bag.
Keep up!
Be careful.
Watch out.
I'll help her.
Slow down.
- Watch the stairs.
- Is she okay?
How did she get this drunk so fast?
Slow down.
Be careful.
Let's take her there
to rest for a bit
before heading back.
Slow down.
Let's go there.
All right.
Don't touch me.
- I'm all right.
- Be careful.
Other than feeling dizzy,
do you feel unwell anywhere else?
I'm okay.
Really?
Yes.
Lu.
I want to go back to use the bathroom.
Number one or number two?
You could go back first.
I'll sit here with her
until she sobers up,
then send her back.
Okay.
Wait.
Leaving her alone here
doesn't seem right.
I really can't hold it anymore.
I really can't.
Aunt Lina.
Don't worry, I found Huan'er.
Her parents know him.
Okay.
I'll take her back first.
Please take care of her.
Okay.
All right.
Huan'er, we're heading off now.
I need to go to the bathroom.
It's fine.
Just go back.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Okay. Please take care of her.
I'll leave her to you.
Call me when you're back.
It's okay. I can go back myself.
Can you walk by yourself?
Yes.
Isn't that the dorm right there?
I can make it.
Can you? Are you sure?
Get on.
Just get on.
You're poking me. It hurts.
I feel like throwing up.
Just don't throw up on me!
Jing Xichi.
What now?
Take this punch from me.
Can you stop making people
worry about you?
Chen Huan'er!
Drinking with strangers
and getting this drunk,
are you careless
or just stupid?
Yes, I'm just stupid.
I'm an idiot.
That's why I let
you fool me for so long.
I just wanted to joke with you
and give you
a surprise.
A joke is only a joke
when both people
find it funny.
Do you get that?
Fine.
I'll apologize.
I'm sorry.
Okay?
Can you stop being
so childish,
Jing Xichi?
Are you saying I'm childish?
Does going to that social event
and getting drunk
the first time you drink
make you mature?
We're not in high school anymore.
We're in university.
I can't just stay by your side
all the time like before.
Can you stop caring about me?
If I don't, who will?
If Aunt Lina
hadn't called me,
I...
I wouldn't have bothered.
Fine!
From now on,
we'll go
our separate ways.
Don't care about me anymore.
I'll go back myself.
How are you going to walk like this?
Why wouldn't I be able to walk?
I can walk! I...
I can walk.
I... I can walk.
You seem to be on a shaky bridge.
Didn't you say you don't care about me?
Were you drinking fake alcohol?
Hello.
Today is the first class
of Medical Psychology.
I won't be taking attendance.
There's no need
for these formalities.
Everyone
seated in this hall today,
I trust you all
have a certain level
of self-discipline.
Those who chose clinical medicine
aren't here
to enjoy life.
Do we all agree on that?
Enough talk,
let's get straight to class.
My stomach hurts.
You're awake.
Drink some honey water.
You drank too much last night.
Li, thanks for saving
my life.
Next time, don't be so foolish.
If you can't drink, don't.
Anyway, you were pretty impressive.
You could get upstairs on your own.
Last night,
wasn't it you both who brought me back?
Don't you remember?
Chen Huan'er, what are you doing?
This is my bed!
Huang Lu!
Come get her off my bed!
Chen Huan'er!
Tonight,
you're staying with me.
Thanks.
Seriously,
Huan'er,
you're really strong.
Last night, Qiu Li and I
couldn't move you
no matter how hard we tried.
I'm really sorry.
I had no idea
I get this strong
when I'm drunk.
By the way,
last night,
did I do anything
I shouldn't have?
For that,
you'll have to ask Jing.
Why would I ask him?
He's the one who brought you back.
Was he...
Was he there last night?
What did you two do last night?
Did he do something to you,
or did you do something to him?
No way!
What could possibly happen between us?
Don't overthink it.
As expected,
buddies
can never become a couple.
It's so warm.
Who turned off the aircon again?
Who else?
It was the top student.
I woke up at midnight from the heat
and didn't fall back
asleep until after five.
Every time she
comes back, she turns it off.
If she doesn't like
air-conditioned rooms,
why doesn't she move
to the old dorms in the east?
Oh, right, Huan'er.
Tian Chi
called last night to ask
how you were.
You were already asleep,
so I didn't wake you up.
I charged your phone.
Check your message.
Thanks, Lu.
(Are you okay?)
(Huan'er, did you make it back?)
(Thanks, Tian Chi.)
(I'm fine.)
(Classes officially start today.)
(Wishing you all the best.)
(Where are you?)
(Aunt Lina is looking for you.)
(Recent calls: Mom - 5)
Oh no.
No, no, no.
(After a ridiculous drunken night,)
(my university life)
(has officially begun.)
(Honestly, university life isn't)
(very different from high school.)
(I still rush to class
at the last minute every day.)
(The only difference is)
(the lecturer doesn't
know every student by name.)
Today is a general course.
Let's do a random
roll call.
Wang Tao.
Yes.
Yang Tao.
Sun Changhe.
Yes.
Zhou Haitao.
Zhou Ye.
Yes.
Jing Xichi.
He's so handsome.
Dong Huixin.
Yes.
Qiu Li.
Huang Lu.
Yes.
Chen Huan'er.
Sir,
I'm here.
Chen Huan'er.
Are you
attending class
on behalf of three people?
You answered
three times consecutively.
I can't even pretend
not to notice anymore.
All three of you
are marked absent.
I...
Next.
Tang Song.
Yes.
Today, we're covering Chapter One,
Marxist Philosophy.
(It's not a great start.)
It has a long history.
The emergence
of Marxist philosophy
brought about a great revolution
in the history of thought.
In the history of human thought,
in terms of scientific validity,
truth,
influence,
and reach...
(What does this have to do with you?)
The significance of Marxism...
Class dismissed.
Um...
Last night,
how did I get back to the dorm?
Don't tell me you
don't remember anything.
You...
You didn't do
anything crazy to me, did you?
I didn't,
but you did plenty.
Jing Xichi.
Take this punch from me.
You owe me medical expenses,
Chen Huan'er.
I didn't ask for your help.
Besides,
weren't my roommates there?
That's exactly what you said last night.
From now on,
we're going
our separate ways.
Don't care about me anymore.
You're really heartless, aren't you?
Are you still mad?
It's unnecessary.
Huan'er.
Hello,
I'm Zhou Ye,
Jing's roommate.
Look.
It looks like we were meant to be
classmates in this general course.
How about
we add each other?
If you ever need anything,
just call me.
Who said you could call her Huan'er?
Aren't we all one big family?
No need to be so distant.
If she needs anything,
she can come to me.
What's it got to do with you?
Look at you.
There's a club
recruitment this afternoon.
Let's check it out.
No need to trouble yourself.
Well, don't be mad anymore.
This semester just starts.
Are you planning to be mad throughout?
Who would dare be mad at you?
You're a campus celebrity now.
That football video
is viral.
Well, that just proves
talent shines eventually.
Don't get cocky.
Let's go check out the club recruitment.
Is it this way?
Which club do you like?
Not sure yet.
Let's take a look.
Zhou Ye!
Du Wei.
Hello, Du Wei.
Jing,
this is our third-year senior,
Du Wei.
She's also from our course
and incredibly skilled.
She's also the head of the art
department in the student council.
She was there yesterday
too, don't you remember?
With so many people, how could I?
Hello, Du Wei.
Jing Xichi,
I've been wanting to meet you.
I'd like to invite you to join
our Computer Competition Team.
Are you
interested?
Of course!
We're definitely interested!
Jing. I've heard a lot
about this competition team.
Everyone in it is a top student.
That's perfect.
We're having a gathering later,
and many people
are curious about your current project.
Come along.
It'll be a great
chance to exchange ideas.
Okay.
I can go to the club recruitment alone.
Then I'll meet you
once I'm done.
Okay.
Sure, go ahead.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
I have to tell you,
the Marxist Philosophy professor
took attendance today.
I answered for both of you,
but guess what?
We all got marked absent.
What?
That's so unlucky.
Well.
You two owe me a hotpot meal now.
That's settled. I'm hanging up.
Are you craving for a hotpot?
Tian Chi.
I was just joking with my roommate.
Did you just finish class?
Yes.
I thought I'd check
out the club recruitment.
What a coincidence.
I'm going too.
Let's go.
I'll introduce you
to the different clubs.
Thank you.
No problem.
There are so many clubs.
University clubs
can be a mixed bag.
If you pick the wrong one,
it's a waste of time
and energy.
Do you have
any hobbies?
If you're interested, check us out.
Thanks.
I feel like
I like everything,
but at the same time,
nothing in particular.
You once told me
that you have to try things
to know whether you like them
or not.
Do you remember that?
Of course.
Do you have any special skills?
I know martial arts.
Does our university
have a martial arts club?
Martial arts?
Why are you laughing?
Do you think I'm making it up
or that I can't do it?
No.
I believe you.
Unfortunately,
our university doesn't
have a martial arts club,
but you could consider joining
the Student Union's Sports Department.
It's easy to get in.
All right, everyone,
that's all for this week.
Same time, same place
next week,
don't be late.
(I'm done here.)
(Are you still
at the club recruitment area?)
Here's the application form.
Welcome aboard.
I don't think I've agreed yet.
Joining the competition team
not only improves
your professional skills
but also earns you extra credits.
Why wouldn't you want to?
I'll think about it.
Can I borrow your phone for a moment?
I've already
saved my number for you.
If you make up your mind,
feel free to contact me.
(Du Wei)
I've heard
this senior is quite the tough one.
Well, seeing is believing.
Let's go.
Where to?
Check out the club recruitment.
Class dismissed.
First,
lower his psychological guard.
Then?
Never admit that you like him.
You're both in Jing City.
You two are wanderers away from home.
There will always be times
when you study together.
That's your chance, isn't it?
Jing.
Is there any club you're interested in?
I haven't decided yet.
I'll take a look first.
Zhou Ye!
Here.
Lin.
You're done.
I sent you a message just now.
Why didn't you reply?
I was busy filling out the form
and didn't see it.
Your friend joined
the sports department.
Consider it.
You can put down that you're good
at martial arts.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Also,
you're a sports lover.
Sports lover.
Write that you want
to use this opportunity
to make new friends.
Sports department?
What's in it for you?
Do you want to lead
the charge during Sports Day,
starting with a 1,500m run?
No.
Tian Chi told me the sports department
is pretty chill.
I think you're just
blinded by attraction.
Not again.
Li.
Which club did you join?
The student council's art department.
The arts department?
Nice choice.
Don't even try to leave.
Lu.
I have a feeling
that Tian Chi
likes you.
Tian Chi is the most handsome guy
in our faculty.
He's top three in his major
and has published in a core journal
with his supervisor.
He's even recommended
by a professor for a postgraduate spot.
He's such a perfect guy.
What a catch!
Stop talking nonsense.
Who's talking nonsense?
At the start of the semester,
didn't he help you carry your luggage
and give you his contact?
That's just because we went
to the same high school.
We're alumni.
Then why did he
accompany you
to the club recruitment today?
He didn't accompany me.
We just ran into each other.
He ran into so many people,
but why did he only
accompany you?
Li.
Am I right?
Yes.
Look.
People pursuing Qiu Li
are lining up
from the West Campus to the East Campus.
Even she thinks I have a point.
What do you have to say now?
According to
your logic,
shouldn't he
like Qiu Li instead?
Stop right there!
He's not my type.
Why are you turning off the aircon?
It's not that hot.
I think we should just turn on the fan.
Why use a fan
when we have an aircon?
With the aircon on,
the temperature inside gets too low,
but outside it's hot.
If we keep going in and out,
we'll catch a cold.
Plus, it wastes electricity.
Well.
If you don't want
to split the aircon bill
because you're not here often,
I'll pay for it myself.
However, I get to decide
when it's on.
Why do you
always boss people around?
Just because you have money?
What does this
have to do with money?
Can you stop making all of us suffer
just because of you?
It's fine.
It's not that hot.
We don't have to turn it on.
Yes.
We can wait until it gets hotter.
Here, eat something.
Don't be angry.
Go ahead
and sweat if you like.
Li.
You...
Your phone.
Let me take this call.
Hello? Qi Qi.
You finally remembered me.
How's your new life?
It's hard to explain.
I thought university
would be pretty chill,
but I didn't expect
so many frustrating things.
What about Jing Xichi?
He's something else.
He actually tricked us for so long.
Exactly.
Even Song...
Let's not talk about him anymore.
Let's stop.
It's okay.
I've let it go.
By the way,
what are you doing?
I...
I'm waiting for a classmate to eat.
I need to stop.
He just finished class.
He?
Who is he?
Why are you here?
You've been in Jing City for so long
and never contacted me.
I'm just joking.
I'm over
all that.
Since it's just the two of us
studying in Jing City,
shouldn't we look out
for each other
as old classmates?
Are you free later?
I'm free.
Then come with me
to your university's
screening hall for a movie.
A movie?
Why not?
I rarely visit your campus.
Won't you even show me around?
Okay.
Let's go.
Who's that?
Why didn't you reply?
It's Du Wei.
She asked if I filled
out that application form.
Speaking of this, I'm curious.
Isn't that competition team pretty good?
Why are you so against joining?
It's too much hassle.
Not joining is more hassle, okay?
Du Wei
is famous for never giving up
until she gets what she wants.
What's that got to do with me?
Haven't you noticed
she's got her eye on you?
Keep going.
What exactly has she set her sights on?
Even if I'm the top student,
that's only among freshmen.
Even if we actually
join that competition,
we'll just end up
doing the hardest work.
That's it?
That's it.
Well.
Should I call you naive
or just plain dumb?
Haven't you noticed
the way she looks at you?
It's like she's about to
see right through you!
So by your logic,
since you pay
so much attention to her,
do you like her?
Can you not say things like that?
It'll bring bad luck.
What are you doing?
I'm working out now.
I have to strictly control
my daily fat intake.
It can only be 30%
of my total daily calories.
Okay.
I'll have some more of this then.
What exactly are you trying to do?
Let me educate you.
Based on my fitness plan,
not only do I need
to control my fat intake,
but I also have to consume
exactly 120 grams of protein a day.
I've already had
quite a bit.
I think I'm still short
by 15 or 16 grams.
What "15 grams"?
I need protein too!
Do you think
only you need protein?
Don't I?
I put in so much effort...
If I don't gain muscle, it's on you.
♪Fallen leaves flutter past your gaze♪
♪I dream of worlds within your days♪
♪Countless times,
I write your name in my heart♪
♪Wishes whispered to the stars above♪
♪How many faces in the glass I see♪
♪Time's gentle hand
pulling me out of my cocoon♪
♪Under the sun,
a rainbow butterfly takes flight♪
♪To rest upon your left shoulder bright♪
♪I still hear your promise in my ears♪
♪Before we said goodbye,
your spirit free♪
♪And full of life♪
♪If summer could last a little longer♪
♪Would regrets rewrite
where we'd gone wrong?♪
♪And let me be there with you
at the end of the story♪
♪Watching your silhouette from behind♪
♪My footsteps slow, we were too young♪
♪To know right from wrong♪
♪Your sweat-kissed face
I hold in my memory♪
♪Glows as bright as ever♪
♪I hope one day we'll meet again♪
♪At just the right time♪