♪In rain or shine♪
♪When you're around,
the sun shines through♪
♪Spare ourselves the endless thoughts
and guessing games♪
♪Let's just meet
and escape these frames♪
♪I stand within the shadows deep♪
♪My hand outstretched,
your rescue I keep♪
♪Even if the world falls apart♪
♪No distance is too far♪
♪To stop us from coming together♪
♪Through the night,
you're at the end of the line♪
♪To protect you is my humble wish♪
♪Farewell, to the timid soul I knew♪
♪It was you who made me brave and new♪
=Always Home=
(Adapted from Xiao Ge's novel, Always Home)
=Episode 27=
(Practice of Farewell)
Here's the toothpaste.
Use this toothbrush.
Bath towel and face towel are here.
Wait a minute.
After you take a shower,
you can wear this.
I washed it two days ago.
It's clean.
Thank you.
Well, I will
go out first.
Call me if you need anything.
Well, I'll shower first.
Okay.
I...
I didn't mean that.
Don't worry.
Just take a shower.
Jing Xichi.
I can't sleep.
Is
my typing noise too loud
and bothering you?
No.
I think I have got used
to my own bed.
When I couldn't sleep,
I used to think
of something happy and relaxing,
and then I'd fall asleep.
Did it work?
It worked for me.
What should I think about?
Do you want
to think
about what our home
will be like in the future?
Our home?
I'd like to have lots
and lots of pictures,
all over the wall.
Pictures of us
in the family housing compound,
pictures of us now,
and
pictures of us when we're old.
It hurts.
Chen Huan'er, what's wrong with you?
♪As you nap
on my shoulder in the afternoon♪
(I'd like to have a garden)
(where I can grow vegetables)
(and flowers.)
(And I'd like to have a)
(puppy like Xiaodi.)
(And I want)
(a big fridge.)
The fridge is full
(of fridge magnets of all the places)
(we've been.)
♪Pain♪
♪Life troubles me year after year♪
I also want
a kitchen...
The kitchen is...
♪But the sky is clear♪
♪Hope shines
like light across the prairie♪
♪Your kindness♪
♪I long for it,
yet the wind chills me again♪
♪Give me a brief taste of sweetness♪
♪May our love last long♪
♪My baby♪
♪I think of you in my mad dash♪
♪My daze of boredom
is also about you♪
♪My baby♪
You're all
I need.
Let's learn this today.
(Advanced Math,
Linear Algebra for Engineering Math)
These
are university courses.
I'm done with high school,
so I'll advance to university.
Actually,
you don't need to learn this now.
No,
I have to learn.
There are other students in our class
who are learning too.
Why do you
have to compare yourself with others?
I can't accept that others
are better than me.
I just want to be number one.
Why do you just want to be number one?
I have no idea.
I'm just used to being first.
You've never been second?
No.
You're a lot
like the old me.
The old you?
From primary school to high school,
I never came second.
At that time,
I was a genius in the eyes
of both students
and parents.
Studying gave me a sense
of achievement.
As time went by,
I felt
I was born to be better than others.
But then I went to Yenching University
and I realized
that it wasn't like that at all.
Because you couldn't easily
be number one anymore?
That was the first time I found
studying to be painful.
(Then, I)
(studied day and night.)
(Finally, on one exam,)
(I came in second.)
(That's good.)
(You can be number one)
(after that.)
(I gave up.)
Why?
Because I found out
that the top student in our class
is a 15-year-old kid
who doesn't usually come to class.
A whiz-kid?
(End-of-term Results for Clinical
Medicine, Professional Ranking 2)
(Professional Ranking 2)
(That was the moment)
(I realized)
(that a lot of things
I had to work very hard for)
(were as easy as drinking water)
(for some people.)
From that moment on,
I gave up
my obsession with being number one
and accepted the fact
that I was just
an ordinary person.
Are you happy now?
All I can say is
that I'm a lot more relaxed.
Song Cong, wait a minute.
Here's the last tuition
for makeup lessons.
They asked for a new teacher.
Thank you.
Sorry to trouble you.
Aren't you surprised?
I could guess.
Can I ask why?
It's certainly not a matter
of professionalism.
If you can't teach them,
I don't know who to recommend.
I probably
can't satisfy their demands.
He wants to be number one forever,
but who can be number one forever?
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Let me buy you a meal.
It's payday.
I'm buying.
Okay.
I told you I'd buy you a meal.
Why don't you let me
buy you a nice meal?
I think this is nice.
There's no need for formality.
Actually, you...
You didn't have to talk so much
to that kid.
If you hadn't talked
to him about life,
you wouldn't have lost your job.
I saw him
and thought of my old self.
I was also afraid
that he'd lose his self-confidence
if he entered an environment
like Yenching University.
But there are some things
you can't understand
until you've experienced them yourself.
I remember
you were always in the top three
in high school, right?
How did you adjust your mindset?
Do you know
how much I wanted to be number one?
But as long as you're around,
I'd never get it.
So, thanks to you,
I'm used to it.
Shouldn't you thank me?
I found you a job.
And I grew up knowing
that I don't always get
what I want.
This dish is quite tasty.
Eat more.
Hello, guys.
You're here.
What took you so long?
Sorry,
we're late.
You have no sense of time.
It's only five minutes late, Xinyan.
Did you order the food?
Yes. I thought I'd wait for you
before they serve the food.
Start with some appetizers.
Sure.
Okay.
Huan'er,
you and Jing Xichi
will stay in Wu'an from now on?
Highly probable.
I applied for graduate school
at my school.
He's handed over his person
and his website
to the company.
He'll be working for them.
Not bad, Jing Xichi.
Whether or not
the next Bill Gates
or Zuckerberg appears
in my circle depends on you.
I'll try my best.
Do well in university.
Don't think of dropping out.
Of course not.
Time flies.
A rebellious teenager
becomes a henpecked man.
Who says otherwise?
You two are better.
Pursuing master's
and doctoral degrees consecutively.
You've seen the pigs getting fed,
but not them getting slaughtered.
I wish I could have graduated earlier.
Hello, everyone!
You're so late.
You're finally here.
Isn't this Mr. Li?
I heard you're going back
to Tianhe No.3 Central Hospital
for your internship.
Yes, that's the plan.
You're the most obedient.
What's wrong?
He's doing good.
He lives and eats at home,
and his immediate superior is his dad.
Unlike us,
we work hard every day for our future.
He's lying
on the finish line now.
He's a life winner.
Don't say that.
A life winner?
I haven't even had
a girlfriend.
Liao Xinyan, stop chatting on the phone.
It's a class reunion.
You can chat until you get home.
He's clingy.
No, no.
I suspect
my recent toothache
must be due to seeing too many
of your affectionate displays.
Pissed me off.
What? You want to fall in love?
You don't?
I don't.
You and Song go to the same university.
Why don't you two try to fall in love?
Why are you still such a talker?
What's wrong?
If you criticize me again,
I'll sing the alphabet song
for everyone.
What alphabet song?
A, B, C, D...
Come here.
E, F, G.
Keep singing.
What?
You still want to sing?
Don't touch me!
Are you singing or not?
Sing loudly. Come on.
Come in.
Hi,
we got a call from a Mr. Bai.
He asked us
to give this to Ms. Liao Xinyan.
My tooth hurts even more.
It's been almost two and a half years.
Why is he still so sweet?
What?
Singles don't get to talk,
huh?
The one she's chatting with isn't this.
(My baby, I don't want
to break up with you)
No wonder they say
graduation season is break-up season.
Anyway, Xinyan,
we're in the second half
of our third year.
Isn't it a bit early for you
to break up?
I... I'm really fine.
I just want to graduate and take
the civil service exam back to Tianhe.
He's an only child.
His home is near our school,
and I can't come back.
I thought
I'd let go and be free.
I'm looking for my next romance.
If that's the case,
we'll wish you good luck
on your civil service exam.
Okay?
Sure.
Come on.
Wait.
We're drinking
before the food is served?
Jing Xichi,
we didn't decide
on a winner last time, did we?
Come on.
This time,
do you want to fight me again?
Put that drink down.
You can't get drunk today,
even if everyone else does.
Then let's cut the cake
to celebrate my happy breakup.
Cut the cake.
Come on.
Waitress.
Knife.
I'll get her.
Miss.
What do you need?
Knife.
Waitress.
Here it is.
The knife is here.
I'm so speechless of you.
Xinyan, you're making a fool of us...
Be careful.
Cut the ties of love.
This knife is so big.
But I really didn't expect
Xinyan to take the civil service exam.
Maybe she's the one who knows
what she wants the most among us.
Jing Xichi,
do you think we'll change?
No matter how you change,
my love for you
will never change.
Be serious.
I'll go back now.
I'm very serious.
You're just leaving like that.
Where is my kiss?
Stop it.
What if my dad sees it?
There's no one here.
Don't.
Your dad already knew.
What are you afraid of?
Don't be late.
I'm leaving.
Go back now.
Get up early.
Got it.
(Second semester of third year)
(arrives in a rush.)
(Youth comes to a screeching halt)
(when it stumbles.)
(The note of parting is played.)
(We've reached)
(the point where we're facing society
and the future.)
(But life)
(is always full of surprises.)
I'll raise a toast.
There's a message from the counselor.
Let me see.
It's this late in the day
and he's still sending out
internship questionnaires.
The third year isn't over yet,
and we're already looking forward
to the future.
Right,
Lu,
I thought you said
you were looking for a job in advance.
How is it?
I've been thinking about it,
and I've got maybe
30 or 40 years of time
to work in the future.
But I only have
a year or so left to fall in love
in university.
So I've decided
not to rush into finding a job.
I'm going to have
a good love affair
in university.
To be honest,
what are your plans?
It's senior year.
It's the norm for couples to break up
and go their separate ways.
Huan'er,
you've got to be careful.
Jing Xichi's work
is on track now.
I think I'll stay in Wu'an too.
You're going to graduate school?
I can't help it.
My grades aren't good.
Huixin is number one,
and I'm number five.
There are only four spots available.
Huixin,
the future of pharmacy
depends on you.
Don't talk about me.
Li,
what's your plan?
My parents found me a
pharmaceutical company.
Is it Guangfeng?
It's a dream place
for pharmacy graduates.
Their branch
has business with my parents,
so they helped me get in.
Don't forget us when you're doing great.
Researchers
depend on you.
Let's raise a toast?
Come on.
- Cheers!
I'll take a call.
Are the exam questions hard?
Not too hard.
Come on, let's drink.
Bottoms up.
Cheers.
Huixin.
Huixin,
what took you so long?
Come here.
Come sit with me for a while.
I haven't had a good chat with you.
Huan'er,
do you still want
to go to graduate school?
What's wrong?
I
am not going to graduate school.
I'm going back to my hometown
to look for a job after graduation.
No.
Why do you want
to go back to your hometown?
Isn't it your ambition
to go to graduate school
since you entered university?
You work so hard every day.
You're just giving up like this?
My brother scored very well
in his senior year
of high school.
As an elder sister,
I have to do my part.
No.
What decade are we living in?
Do things like this still happen?
Don't you have a scholarship
and a grant?
You are not dependent
on your family.
How come your family
won't let you study?
My parents called me before.
They're getting old.
They can't afford to support
another university student.
So they want me to go home early
and help out,
and start working early.
Besides,
if I go home early,
I can take care of them
if anything happens to them.
As you know,
I had to repeat a year
to get in here.
Compared to my brother,
I don't have much talent for studying.
Huixin.
I now realize
that studying is the happiest thing
in the world.
There will be one more spot
for graduate school if I quit.
If you have made up your mind,
I can help you prepare the documents.
I don't want it.
Consider it
a way to repay you
for taking care of me
these past three years.
Huan'er,
actually, I know what you
and the girls did.
Like Li,
she's a rich girl,
but she asked for samples
when she bought things.
Lu is so lazy,
but she always got a part-time job
at the student union.
When she got back to the dorm,
she told me she was going home
and asked me to go in her place.
As for you,
you're afraid I won't
get enough to eat,
so you always buy an extra dish.
No...
Huixin...
Think about it again.
Huixin,
are you alright?
Why are you back?
Qiu Li sent me a message.
Dong Huixin,
are you willing to do that?
Yeah.
You don't get
to choose your background,
but you do get to choose
what kind of life you want to live.
Huixin, even if you don't go
to graduate school,
what can you do back home?
Why don't you stay in Wu'an
and prove yourself?
Yes, just stay.
Think about it.
Give me your parents' phone number.
I'll talk to them.
Stop it.
How do you know if you don't try?
Try it.
You're so young.
Okay.
I'll reconsider.
Let me think about it.
Stop drinking.
Come on.
We'll drink with you.
- Qiu Li, get down.
- Qiu Li.
- Let's drink.
Let's drink.
You girls...
Cheers!
Don't go back.
Forget the unhappy things.
Let's drink. Come on, cheers!
Cheers!
Huixin.
Let's stay together, Huixin.
We love you.
Jing,
come on.
I'll talk to HR tomorrow.
You can work here for now.
Okay.
Mr. Jiang.
Jing, let me introduce them to you.
Cai Wenlong, Mr. Cai.
He's your senior.
I've sent you someone
this time.
These are the pillars
of our company's technical department.
Cherish the chance
and learn from them.
That's great.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Hi, Mr. Cai.
Excuse me.
(The closer we get to graduation,)
(the more we feel that the previous
four years of university life)
(were like a party
with the purpose of saying goodbye.)
(Because once we step out
of the campus,)
(all the privileges and
advantages of being a student)
(will disappear.)
(Time)
(is like a whirlpool of great force,)
(silently)
(pushing us into the vastness
of mankind.)
(There are those
who wear out their feet)
(for a salary,)
(and those who run for the moon)
(in the sky.)
(No one knows)
(what will become of themselves
in the future,)
(only occasionally stopping)
(to see the ignorant)
(and happy)
(new students of the campus,)
(and vaguely remembering)
(that we were)
(also like this.)
(Huandao Technology)
Mr. Jiang asked me to remind you
that the project's go-live date
is confirmed.
The 31st.
It's set by the headquarters.
Didn't we agree on the middle
of next month?
Why is it half a month earlier?
What Mr. Jiang means is
that we have enough manpower now,
so he'd like to move it forward
as much as possible.
Enough manpower?
I'd like to ask Mr. Jiang
where he got
these men.
Do they count as manpower?
Alright,
I got it.
These men
were sent here to help,
but they didn't do anything to help.
They even treat me like a waiter
and make me grind coffee for them.
Why didn't they let me do latte art?
Mr. Cai,
I'd like to have a word with you.
Surprise!
Huan'er is here.
What brings you here?
Well,
I'm here to buy you a meal.
Let's go.
You haven't had dinner, right?
Go now.
I'm not going.
Just buy some food for me.
Zhou Ye,
you should hurry back too.
Huixin hasn't had much luck
in finding a job lately,
so she's not in a good mood.
Really?
I... I'll get going now.
Go, hurry up.
Don't talk to her directly.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
What are you waiting for?
Let's go.
Eat it while it's hot.
Your favorite
Stir-fried Pork with Chili.
Okay.
Thanks.
Come on.
Eat slowly.
Hello.
Mr. Jiang.
Are you having
any problems on your end?
The go-live date
has suddenly been moved up.
The workload's just too much.
So far, it's just me and Zhou Ye...
Why did you let Mr. Cai
and others leave the team?
They're not working anyway.
Why stay?
You want me
to serve them every day?
I'm sorry, Mr. Jiang,
I can't do it.
I am obliged to provide you
with manpower.
It's your freedom to use them or not.
Anyway,
you must accomplish the task
within the time limit.
I know.
By the end of the month.
Well,
I'll hang up if there's nothing else.
Come on.
Eat it while it's hot.
I got rid of all those men
sent by Jiang Sen.
I think
if you think
they're not convinced of you,
then you need
to show them what you can do
to convince them.
You want them to be convinced of me?
It's not easy.
So you'd rather
get rid of them
than try?
Or do you think
you can't handle it?
No matter
how hard you try,
you can't
change their minds?
Jing Xichi,
do you remember
what you were like in high school?
The one who wouldn't
give up and move on,
no matter what?
Mr. Cai, Mr. Qian,
I bought your favorite
roast goose with crispy skin.
Is that so?
You've praised this place
out of all the restaurants in Wu'an.
Come on, eat it while it's hot.
Fu, thank you.
We're in for a treat today.
Come on.
This...
Mr. Cai,
is this roast goose
to your liking?
They're the real hosts
of today's meal.
For this meal,
my junior has traveled
across the city to bring it back
from the restaurant himself.
It's full of sincerity.
I remember
when Mr. Jiang proposed
the Yangwu Website,
Mr. Cai,
you voted for it.
Why don't you listen to him
for the sake of the Yangwu Website?
The first order from the Yangwu Website
was for me
and my two other best friends
to review for our three years
in high school.
(In bed, he watches the beam and writes)
Inside those materials
are not only the knowledge
we learned in high school,
but also the time we spent
with each other.
I think every old book
carries the memories and ideals
of many people.
I don't want these things
to be eroded by the passage of time.
Young man,
your story is interesting.
Unfortunately,
we don't
buy your story.
Let's go.
I know
it's naive
to ask you to fulfill
my wish with me.
Anyway, Mr. Cai,
don't you want to do something
for yourself?
What do you mean?
Hello,
Fu Ying.
Can you help me find out
about Mr. Cai's preferences
and the projects
he's worked on
over the years?
Okay.
Only his alone?
Yes.
Only his.
As I know,
Mr. Cai, you've been working in Huandao
for seven years.
But you've only been promoted once.
In recent years,
you haven't even successfully
financed any of the projects
you're directly responsible for,
right?
I wonder
if it's your judgment
in selecting a project
or your ability that's at fault.
Young man,
mind your words.
I've seen all the projects
you've worked on in Huandao.
I don't question
your expertise.
Your expertise
is far superior to mine.
It's just that in recent years,
you've been discouraged by failure.
I also know
that in your mind,
you feel aggrieved
that the company sent you,
such an experienced senior,
to give me a hand.
But you need a project
that will go live quickly.
The Yangwu Website
needs your technical support.
Only if we work together can we win.
Mr. Cai,
please give me a chance
and give the Yangwu Website a chance.
At the same time,
give yourself a chance.
Do you live far from the hospital?
Not far.
It's only a five-minute walk.
I'm about the same.
Is there anything else you want
to see me about?
Boys must be careful
when they're out.
But don't be too nervous
or too self-absorbed.
(Inquiry about The Results
of Master's Examination Candidates)
(Congratulations, you have
been accepted by your first choice.)
How's it?
I...
I've been accepted.
(Congratulations, you have
been accepted by your first choice.)
That's great.
Your efforts have not been in vain.
Tonight,
I'm buying dinner.
(I just found out)
(that Dong Huixin
didn't keep looking for a job.)
(If you don't go on)
(to study pharmacy,)
(you can't do anything)
(as a pharmacist,)
(doctor,)
(or researcher in Wu'an.)
(Later,)
(Dong Huixin returned home)
(and found an ordinary job)
(to pay for her brother's
university education.)
(I didn't expect fate)
(to be so unfair.)
(In the blink of an eye,)
(my roommates and I)
(are going our separate ways.)
(I wonder)
(when we'll meet again.)
Plug in oxygen.
One milligram of adrenaline.
Three minutes once.
Time of death,
20:37.
Take the family
to get a death certificate.
Remember to calm the family down.
Who's it?
Your food delivery has arrived.
What?
I didn't order any food.
It's not my name.
I ordered it.
Thank you.
Have you eaten?
Just eat.
Okay.
Your house has
the same floor plan as mine.
How much did you rent it for?
2,500 yuan.
What?
What about you?
3,000 yuan.
The landlord told me
I got a great deal,
saying it was the lowest price
in the neighborhood.
It turns out
that a top student gets tricked too.
I've actually imagined countless times
a patient dying
in front of me.
I thought I was ready for it.
But when it came to that moment,
I realized I had overestimated myself.
Maybe
one day you'll get used to it.
Get used to facing death?
Get used to accepting
the cycle of life more openly
and face up to your responsibilities
as a doctor.
♪Fallen leaves flutter past your gaze♪
♪I dream of worlds within your days♪
♪Countless times,
I write your name in my heart♪
♪Wishes whispered to the stars above♪
♪How many faces in the glass I see♪
♪Time's gentle hand
pulling me out of my cocoon♪
♪Under the sun,
a rainbow butterfly takes flight♪
♪To rest upon your left shoulder bright♪
♪I still hear your promise in my ears♪
♪Before we said goodbye,
your spirit free♪
♪And full of life♪
♪If summer could last a little longer♪
♪Would regrets rewrite
where we'd gone wrong?♪
♪And let me be there with you
at the end of the story♪
♪Watching your silhouette from behind♪
♪My footsteps slow, we were too young♪
♪To know right from wrong♪
♪Your sweat-kissed face
I hold in my memory♪
♪Glows as bright as ever♪
♪I hope one day we'll meet again♪
♪At just the right time♪