♪In rain or shine♪
♪When you're around,
the sun shines through♪
♪Spare ourselves the endless thoughts
and guessing games♪
♪Let's just meet
and escape these frames♪
♪I stand within the shadows deep♪
♪My hand outstretched,
your rescue I keep♪
♪Even if the world falls apart♪
♪No distance is too far♪
♪To stop us from coming together♪
♪Through the night,
you're at the end of the line♪
♪To protect you is my humble wish♪
♪Farewell, to the timid soul I knew♪
♪It was you who made me brave and new♪
=Always Home=
(Adapted from Xiao Ge's novel, Always Home)
=Episode 24=
(Unable to Hide)
Dad,
you're still up?
I was sorting out
your mom's medication.
Is Mom asleep?
Yeah, she's asleep.
Huan'er,
I've decided
to retreat to the back line.
I won't be going anywhere anymore.
I'll stay in Tianhe,
do some grocery shopping,
cook some meals,
be a stay-at-home husband,
and spend time with you and your mom.
Do you know
what the happiest thing
in life is?
What?
A false alarm.
I think your mom's illness
is most probably
caused by me stressing her out.
How could that be?
Back then, I was always
busy making money,
and your mom
handled everything at home.
Sometimes,
I even made her angry
and added to her troubles.
Do you know?
She talked about
divorcing me quite a few times,
but in the end,
she couldn't go through with it
because she's softhearted.
Now that I think about it,
I really owe her a lot.
When we got married,
there was no proposal,
no romance,
nothing at all.
We just muddled through the wedding,
and then
we had you.
At the time, I thought,
there's plenty of time.
So, I'll make it up to her later.
But now, looking back,
half a lifetime has passed.
How time flies!
Why are we here?
I want to
help my dad
to buy a diamond ring for my mom.
Consider it making up
for the wedding gift
when they were young.
Do you bring enough money?
I still have my scholarship
from last semester.
Ones, Tens, Hundreds, Thousands,
Ten Thousand...
Wait.
Why is a tiny rock so expensive?
Huan'er,
how much money do you have?
Not much.
How much exactly?
3,000.
Can I try this one?
Sure.
You have great taste, Miss.
This is our store's latest design.
The price
is 94,800 yuan.
This is pretty nice.
I'll take this one.
Okay, I'll use a credit card.
Okay, please come over here.
It's not that nice.
Let's look around a bit more.
94,800...
She didn't even blink
before buying it.
Maybe for her,
it's just like buying a couple
of expensive outfits.
Jing Xichi,
how many cups of milk tea
can 90,000 yuan buy?
90,000...
If we assume
10 yuan per cup,
that is 9,000 cups.
If you drink one a day,
you can drink at least 24 years.
24 years...
What would you like to drink?
Just three glasses of water for now,
thanks.
Alright.
I was too naive.
I thought by gathering all
my Chinese New Year's money
from the past few years,
I could get that ring.
But, it turns out
that I can't even afford
the prong to hold the diamond.
It seems that the power
of adults in this world
has nothing to do
with the grades in school.
Qi Qi invited me to dinner.
I get to go now.
Bye.
By the way,
Happy Valentine's Day to you two.
Thank you.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Guess who I am.
Stop it.
Happy Valentine's Day.
I got you a present.
What is it?
I made it myself.
It's beautiful!
Do you want to try it on?
Yeah.
I can't find it.
Here.
Pretty?
Yes.
I'll wear the other one.
Is it done?
Yeah.
Thank you.
I got you something too.
This is...
Check it out when you get home.
I'm meeting my friends for a meal.
Let's go. Otherwise, we will be late.
Alright.
Let's go.
Are you hungry?
I'm okay.
What about you?
I'm okay too.
Qi Qi,
you are finally here!
Long time no see.
Wenwen.
Song Cong,
this is Wen Wen.
And, that's Dazhao.
Nice to meet you.
I heard you're studying medicine
at Yenching University.
Much respect.
If you open a private clinic abroad,
you'll make good money.
Public hospitals in China are great too.
You can only earn a little
in a public hospital here.
What are you saying?
Let's sit.
I know you like this.
I saw it at a boutique overseas.
What is it?
Take a look.
It's this!
How did you know I like it?
It's gorgeous.
Put it on now.
Looks good.
Put this one on too.
Waiter,
we'd like to order.
Song Cong, over the years,
many people pursued Qi Qi,
but she never agreed to anyone.
- He'll pay the bill.
- You managed to win her over.
No matter what,
you have to treat us
to this meal today.
Aren't you embarrassed?
You invited them to eat,
and now you're making them pay?
Pay the bill.
It's my first time meeting everyone,
so I should treat you.
I'll pay the bill.
Cash or card?
Cash.
Alright, here's your bill.
I'll use my card.
Okay, one moment, please.
Yeah.
Where are you guys heading afterward?
We've got something to do later,
so we won't be joining you.
Oh, come on.
What a killjoy you are!
I hardly come back here,
yet you prioritize
your boyfriend over me.
Nothing I can do about it.
Alright,
let's go.
Let's grab something warm to drink.
Hello.
Hey!
It's you!
You still remember me?
Of course!
We're selling our cakes
by the slice now.
Do you want to try some?
No, thanks.
Just two hot chocolates, please.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
What's up?
Are you acting serious now?
Nothing.
I'm just thinking
that back in school,
we were taught that if we study hard
and get into a good university,
we'll definitely have a good life.
But now,
it doesn't seem that simple.
Maybe the school
just protected us too well.
Hold on.
Are you just
making excuses to avoid studying?
Aunt Lin told me specifically
to keep an eye on you.
If you dare skip class,
she won't let you off the hook!
You're so evil!
Here's your hot chocolate.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Wait.
Thank you.
I tell you, you better be kinder.
Or every Valentine's Day from now on,
you'll be spending it alone.
I won't keep you company.
What do you mean, you keep me company?
Obviously, I'm the one
keeping you company, okay?
Aren't you alone too?
Since
we're both alone...
Why...
Don't we...
Just go to McDonald's?
They have a buy-one-get-one
ice cream deal for today.
It's your treat.
Hey, you haven't paid
for your hot chocolate.
Oh, right!
How much?
Twenty.
Is there a Valentine's Day discount?
No.
Hao!
Why did you come here alone?
I mainly came
to drop off some documents for you.
Your recovery seems to be going well.
Yeah, pretty good.
Let me take a look...
You haven't reached retirement age yet.
But, it's a work-related injury.
The hospital said
I can take early retirement.
Alright, let me check the documents...
(Internal Employee Early Retirement/
Pre-Retirement Leave Approval Form)
Why hasn't
the finance department signed it?
Finance said
HR can sign first.
That is not allowed.
They have to sign it first
before we can process it.
Finance said HR could go first.
But, Director Zhang
is out on a business trip.
He said he'll be back in two days,
then he'll sign for me.
Then, you can wait two more days.
Once they sign it,
you can come again.
It's just that...
I'm not very mobile right now.
How about this?
I'll leave it with you for now.
Once Director Zhang returns,
could you help get it signed
and stamped for me?
Then,
I'll come pick it up.
Would that be okay?
Definitely not.
Look at my place.
How messy it is!
If I lose it,
I can't take responsibility.
Zhou, we've known each other for years.
It's just a small favor,
and this doesn't break any rules.
I've got all the documents ready.
This isn't standard procedure.
It puts me in a difficult condition.
Yan!
What brings you here?
You could have just called,
and I would have come to you.
This early retirement was
personally approved by the director.
Now, you check
if it can be processed now.
Alright.
Here you go, take it.
Thank you.
(Name: Hao Mei, Retirement Application
Unit: Tianhe No.3 Central Hospital)
Be careful.
I'm fine.
You're back.
Mom.
What are you holding?
This is
a Valentine's Day gift
from Qi Qi.
It looks nice.
Wash your hands first.
Dinner is ready.
It looks expensive.
What did you get for Qi Qi?
I gave her a pair of earrings
which I made them myself.
You can make earrings?
I think you should have
bought her
a standard gift.
Later,
you check how much this costs
(Retirement Certificate)
and buy something of a similar price
so we don't look too low-standard.
Did you hear me?
Alright.
Hurry up and eat.
Mom.
Did you go to handle
your retirement today?
Yeah, it's done.
Didn't you
want to continue...
Forget it.
I don't want to push myself anymore.
Is Qi Qi's family very wealthy?
What does her mom do?
Her mom
owns a law firm.
That's much better
than our family's situation.
Does her mom
know about
your relationship?
Qi Qi
hasn't had the chance to tell her yet.
Does Qi Qi
mind my current situation?
I know you young people
don't like hearing
about "matching social status",
but given our circumstances,
does it put a lot of pressure on you?
Mom, what are you talking about?
Alright.
I won't say anything.
Can you stop bringing this up again?
Fine, fine.
Let's eat.
(Men's Shirt: 8000 yuan)
Huan'er, you've been wearing
this shirt for so long.
I'll bring it for washing.
Huan'er,
I want to talk to you about something.
What's up, Dad?
I know that university life
is full of temptations,
but academics
should always come first.
Right?
I was young once too
and I know young people
are always impulsive,
acting without thinking things through.
But, I have to remind you,
don't get confused by your emotions.
Don't make rash decisions
without careful thought.
Who's confused by emotions?
Hold on,
Dad.
What exactly are you trying to say?
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend!
Stop making things up!
I really don't have a boyfriend!
Look yourself. What is this?
You've come to a stage of marriage
and need to buy a diamond ring?
No,
Dad.
I was planning
to buy you a diamond ring.
Buy me a diamond ring?
What?
Didn't you once tell me
that Mom didn't get a diamond ring
when you two got married?
And, you feel regret.
So, I thought
I'd buy one for you
to make Mom happy.
(True love is eternal.
Shining with light.)
Dad,
what do you think?
It's unnecessary.
This is an adult matter.
You little kid just stay out of it.
You should prioritize
your study.
Stop thinking
about buying diamond rings.
Go study in your room.
I wasn't meddling!
Mom has always said
she wanted a diamond ring!
Do you have money
for buying a diamond ring?
I have no money.
Why are you meeting me?
What's up?
Missing me already?
I came to return this to you.
I checked the price,
and it's too expensive.
I can't accept it.
It's just a gift.
Moreover,
didn't you also give me earrings?
The price is just a number.
What matters is the thought.
Price is price.
Thoughtfulness is thoughtfulness.
I appreciate your gesture,
but I really can't accept this.
Do you have to be like this?
Fine.
You won't accept it, right?
Then, I'll just throw it away.
Qi Qi!
Stop messing around, okay?
Then, just accept it this time.
I promise I won't gift this
to you again next time.
Okay?
Alright.
Let's order some drinks then.
Waiter, we'd like to order.
Don't stay up too late. Go to sleep.
Take a shower and go to bed.
Mom, can you slow down your voice?
You scared me.
I have to go shower and sleep.
I know.
You're going back
to university tomorrow.
And, you're still playing it.
Go to bed early.
(Hello, can I take
a moment of your time?)
(I'm Jiang Sen, head
of Wu'an Huan Dao Technology)
Hello.
Where is Mr. Jiang's office?
Thank you.
Please come in.
Hello.
I'm...
You're Jing Xichi, right?
Yes.
I'm Jiang Sen,
head of Huan Dao Technology
in Wu'an Branch.
Nice to meet you.
Have a seat.
I heard you're still in university.
Yes, I'm Year 1 student.
Just Year 1?
That's impressive.
Your second-hand book
trading website has great potential
and a decent user base.
However,
your platform has been
operating as a non-profit.
If you upgrade it,
the future possibilities are limitless.
Thank you.
Alright.
I'll get straight to the point.
I have two proposals for you.
First,
we create
an identical platform.
With Huan Dao's team and technology,
we can launch quickly.
But when that happens,
we'll be competitors.
Second,
we provide you
with funding and technical support,
and you continue running the platform.
You'll receive dividends later on,
and if it does well,
it could be quite lucrative.
So,
you mean...
What I mean is that,
while your team is still inexperienced
in terms of technical part,
Huan Dao values your potential.
Alright.
I'll think about it.
Sure.
I'll wait for your response.
See you.
Alright.
Hello,
Jing Xichi.
Are you free these next few days?
I have my last final exam tonight.
After that, I'm free.
Why?
Let's head back together
after your finals.
What happened?
(A semester passed quickly.)
(Mom has fully recovered.)
(It's time to make)
(the surprise plan happen.)
Mom, let's go inside
and pick out some clothes.
Yeah.
We don't even have a photo together.
Let's go.
It's so pretty, Mom.
Come on, let's check inside.
Wow, it is beautiful!
Mom.
This is a bridal shop. Wearing this?
Dad!
It's not appropriate.
Why not?
Other people have wedding photos,
but we don't.
When I think about it...
I get jealous. Right?
Yeah, Mom.
I've never seen you in a wedding dress!
You must be very beautiful.
Our daughter is an adult now.
What's the wedding photo for?
Mom, Mom!
It's not a problem.
Besides, who says wedding dresses
can only be worn at weddings?
Exactly!
If you're willing,
we can take a photo every year
until Huan'er is as old as we are now.
We'll take them until we're 90!
Yeah!
I agree with Dad!
Mom,
when you're 90,
Dad will be the most handsome old man
in Tianhe!
And, you'll be
the most stunning beauty!
Come on!
Come on.
Wearing a wedding dress at 90
would be ridiculous.
People will laugh at us.
Stop messing around.
Just pick one.
We're already here.
This one looks nice.
No. The breast has reached the stomach.
What about this one? It's puffy.
The back...
No, no, no.
Dad, hurry up and pick one.
How about this one?
It even has a ribbon here.
- It's not nice.
- Too old-fashioned.
Fine. Let's see another one.
So many styles...
Why don't you pick one yourself?
You choose, okay?
Choose from these.
I think these look pretty good.
This one looks great, Mom!
You'll look absolutely stunning in it.
See?
My mom has such a great taste.
Isn't it beautiful?
It's so beautiful!
Here she comes!
I've never worn anything
like this in my life.
Snow White!
Be careful.
You guys...?
So beautiful!
Why are you all here?
You see, wearing a wedding dress
at this age is quite embarrassing.
Mom!
I tell you,
you look stunning in this dress.
Just like twenty years ago.
Hey.
Come on!
Why are you here too?
Your leg...
It doesn't hinder me
from joining in on the fun.
Exactly.
See what you have done.
You look amazing.
So handsome!
Since you're all here,
let's take it together.
No, you two first.
You two stand in the center.
Okay, here we go.
Here.
Look over here.
Three, two, one.
Okay?
Great!
Get a little closer.
We'll take another one.
Take one photo with you holding her.
Wait a second.
What's wrong?
You know,
I've always been a straightforward guy.
I don't know romance,
and I don't know
how to make people happy.
When you got sick,
I felt really guilty.
I felt guilty for not
taking good care of you.
In these past few days,
I've been thinking
about how I can do better,
and how I can be a good husband.
In the end,
it was Huan'er who reminded me.
Even our kid could think of it,
but I couldn't.
After all these years,
we've stumbled our way
to today.
And, there's always been
a regret in my heart,
in which I never
properly proposed to you.
So today,
in front of everyone,
I want to ask you
the question I should've asked
twenty years ago.
Lina,
will you marry me?
Yes, I do.
Don't cry.
Dad!
Put the ring on!
Oh, right! Put the ring on!
This is for you.
Purple roses.
So beautiful.
Purple roses mean
eternal love.
Eternal love.
Mom,
watching television?
Thank you.
Thank me for what?
Thank you for giving me
everything you could.
So, don't ever think our family
is any less than others.
In my eyes,
you've always been
the best mom in the world.
What's wrong with this kid?
Why are you grinning like that?
Why?
Can't I smile now?
My dad just proposed to my mom.
I'm really happy!
Uncle Chen and Aunt Lina's love
is deeper than I imagined.
Yeah.
My mom doesn't
care about material things.
She cares about two hearts
that truly love each other.
But, this is such an important event.
Why didn't you even tell me in advance?
Only my dad and I knew.
No one else did.
What's wrong?
Are you upset?
No.
Don't be mad.
I didn't mean to keep it from you.
I'm not mad.
What's wrong?
What's that smell?
What smell?
Did you put on perfume?
No.
You put on perfume?
♪A snack bar by the lake♪
I...
♪I stared straight at you♪
♪I wish that you will stay♪
♪I don't remember what I said♪
♪I treated you to a cake♪
♪And maybe ice cream♪
♪Like you're as sweet as it♪
♪Fantastic date♪
♪It happened in my fate♪
♪While you're counting to three♪
♪I'll tell you a tale♪
♪No matter how late♪
♪I haven't complained♪
♪You used to cheat to win the game♪
(What you just smelled)
(is probably the scent of pheromones.)
I'm sweating.
I've arrived.
What a coincidence.
My house is here, too.
Yeah.
Just now...
Was that your first kiss?
Of course, it was my first kiss.
I've never been
in a relationship before.
But, you seemed
pretty skilled just now.
I thought
it wasn't your first time...
Stop it!
Maybe it's just
that I watch too many movies...
And I just...
Couldn't hold myself back...
So I...
Chen Huan'er.
So, does
this mean
we're a couple now?
How does that make us a couple?
But, we just...
Yet, you haven't even
properly
confessed to me.
Chen Huan'er,
I like you.
Will you
be my girlfriend?
Xichi,
what are you two
still doing out so late?
Dad.
I go in first.
You guys have a lot
of topics to talk, huh?
Your mom's been looking for you.
She called me just now.
Get home now.
Really?
What's up?
Anything else?
No, nothing at all.
I...
I walk you home.
No need, Uncle.
My home is upstairs.
Go on, hurry up.
Bye, Uncle.
Why hasn't he called me yet?
Jing Xichi.
(Piggy Jing)
Hello?
Just now...
Why does my mobile plan...
Hello?
What's going on?
How dare he hang up on me!
How do I cancel this? Help me check it.
How to cancel it?
Why isn't it working?
Mom, it's just easy.
You go to sleep first.
I'll fix it for you tomorrow.
It's late now.
Go to sleep.
It keeps deducting money!
Go ahead, Mom.
Fine. Don't forget to help me tomorrow.
Don't worry.
What's going on?
(I just wanted to tell you that...)
(I just wanted to tell you)
(that I was serious just now.)
(Will you be)
(my girlfriend?)
(Silly.)
(What does that mean?)
(Goodnight,)
(my boyfriend.)
(Good night, my girlfriend.)
Boyfriend! I have a boyfriend!
What was that sound?
Mom!
The bed collapsed.
You...
This...
Be careful.
What's going on?
I just turned over...
Gosh...
The quality of this bed is terrible.
So weird...
♪Fallen leaves flutter past your gaze♪
♪I dream of worlds within your days♪
♪Countless times,
I write your name in my heart♪
♪Wishes whispered to the stars above♪
♪How many faces in the glass I see♪
♪Time's gentle hand
pulling me out of my cocoon♪
♪Under the sun,
a rainbow butterfly takes flight♪
♪To rest upon your left shoulder bright♪
♪I still hear your promise in my ears♪
♪Before we said goodbye,
your spirit free♪
♪And full of life♪
♪If summer could last a little longer♪
♪Would regrets rewrite
where we'd gone wrong?♪
♪And let me be there with you
at the end of the story♪
♪Watching your silhouette from behind♪
♪My footsteps slow, we were too young♪
♪To know right from wrong♪
♪Your sweat-kissed face
I hold in my memory♪
♪Glows as bright as ever♪
♪I hope one day we'll meet again♪
♪At just the right time♪