♪In rain or shine♪
♪When you're around,
the sun shines through♪
♪Spare ourselves the endless thoughts
and guessing games♪
♪Let's just meet
and escape these frames♪
♪I stand within the shadows deep♪
♪My hand outstretched,
your rescue I keep♪
♪Even if the world falls apart♪
♪No distance is too far♪
♪To stop us from coming together♪
♪Through the night,
you're at the end of the line♪
♪To protect you is my humble wish♪
♪Farewell, to the timid soul I knew♪
♪It was you who made me brave and new♪
=Always Home=
(Adapted from Xiao Ge's novel, Always Home)
=Episode 30=
(Always Home)
(I dreamed of these woods.)
(In my dreams,)
(I ask these trees over and over again)
(if they've seen my dad.)
(But none of them answered me.)
(If only the trees could talk...)
(Because you're the only ones)
(who saw him for the last time.)
(Now,)
(I realize)
(that perhaps the rustling)
(of every leaf as the wind blows)
(is a goodbye)
(you didn't get to say.)
(They will come together)
(as the gentlest force)
(to keep me from being afraid
of the road ahead,)
(from dwelling on the past.)
(Market Status and Trends
of Second-hand Books)
(Yangwu is
a Secondhand Book Trading Website.)
This concept
was born out of a bookcrossing event
I did in high school.
That long-ago event
proved the simplicity and sincerity
of human feelings.
But when we enter the society,
in this multi-dimensional world
of convenient transport
and communication,
we find that the distance between people
is getting further and further away.
I've always believed
that people are not isolated islands.
We spend our lives
searching for a family to snuggle with,
to warm up to,
as well as companions
to reflect our souls.
They are the stars of the night sky,
(the lighthouse of the sea,)
(and the everlasting sun.)
(They are the proof that we are alive,)
(and the meaning of our existence.)
(It's when we start)
(to burn for each other)
that the world becomes so bright
and colorful.
(Yangwu's Proposal)
Therefore,
a book is not just a book.
It's the port
of communication between people.
It is a shelter for the lonely,
a haven for the wandering,
a home where warm lights
are always on
and the door is open
for the return of the wanderer.
Fu Ying,
I don't need this anymore.
For you.
You...
How is it?
Have you got the results
from the meeting?
What
are you doing?
I'm moving
to the 10th floor.
The 10th floor?
So our plan is approved?
To be precise,
she'll go to the 10th floor,
and I'll go to the ground floor.
What are you doing on the ground floor?
Take a cab and go home.
The plan
didn't get approved.
You don't have to blame yourself.
It's not our problem
that the plan didn't get approved.
A long time ago,
I wanted to tell you.
No matter how well
our plan is done,
it will still be rejected
by the company.
Huandao is a
very mature organization.
Every project that is incorporated
into the company's territory
and every piece of content
that is produced
is closely related to the company's
future development.
It's never going to shift
at the will of some of us newcomers
to the company.
So,
they've been making us
waste our time from the beginning?
The company already gave us
a one percent chance.
It's just
that we're all ordinary people.
And miracles
don't always happen to ordinary people.
I still don't quite get it.
And you...
Want to ask me why I got to stay?
And got a promotion?
Well, actually, I got an offer letter
from headquarters before you got here.
I was offered the position
of department manager.
So,
Fu Ying, you're the spy.
You're such a good actress.
But I don't understand
why you've been working hard
with us for a month,
doing...
Doing this for nothing.
I have no idea.
Maybe I was still harboring illusions.
That we're
the one percent that survived.
It's not for nothing.
I'm just trying
to pull off one last
silly romance
with my companions.
Fu Ying,
thank you.
What about you?
Do you want
to fight to stay again?
Xichi, I'm sorry.
It's impossible for me to stay.
Why?
To sum up,
in the future, Yangwu
will not only be able
to trade second-hand books,
but will also be able
to build a community
based on interests
and meet more
like-minded people.
After all this time,
this is what
you've come up with?
Huandao is not a charity organization.
According to your plan,
we need to invest
a lot of time
and manpower to manage the website.
If the cost-effectiveness
of the website is so low,
what is the use of keeping it?
Young man,
having an idea and trying it out
is a good thing.
How about this?
I'm giving you one more chance.
You can follow the original...
No need.
What did you say?
I said,
I don't need it.
I'm quitting.
You're all about money.
Doctor?
Engineer?
Technician?
To put it bluntly,
you're just a capitalist.
You are a wolf in sheep's clothing.
Zhou Ye,
do you know what you're talking about?
Young man,
I'd advise you to hold back your temper.
Don't think too highly of yourself.
You're just nothing.
Calm down.
I...
Let go!
You...
Go away!
I'll beat you to death!
Come back here!
Starting today,
I am the first person
to straighten out the workplace.
I'm the man
Huandao can never have.
Do I stand by you?
Bring me the box.
This one?
What do you need this for?
I'm leaving with you.
Actually, the boss
doesn't necessarily want you to leave.
It's me who can't stay any longer.
After all, it's just that Huandao and I
don't share the same philosophy.
Then I wish you both the best of luck
in finding your own paths.
Thank you, Fu Ying.
Fu Ying,
take good care of yourself.
Pack up.
The following
are some of the data produced
by our team.
The treated cells
were stained
and the percentage of apoptosis
was detected by flow cytometry.
Among them,
A and B
represent the reference
of control group and treated group...
Is there anything wrong with these data?
No.
I did it all by myself.
Nothing can go wrong.
Look at it carefully.
Are you sure nothing's wrong?
Senior Gao...
What's the matter?
Chen Huan'er,
what's going wrong?
The data should be the old version.
He must have opened the wrong file.
Even if you opened the wrong one,
can't you tell
if your own experimental data
is correct or not?
Tell me.
How much
did you participate in this experiment?
I...
Well...
Chen Huan'er,
tell me.
Professor Qiu,
the data was prepared
by me and Tian Chi.
Senior Gao Ang
usually just gives guidance.
You can't even understand
the basics,
so how can you mentor
your juniors?
Get down.
Chen Huan'er, present it.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Let me correct
our experimental data for you.
You have no idea
how embarrassing it was today.
So many people were in the hall.
Anyway,
Gao Ang
got what he deserved.
That's good.
I don't need to teach him
a lesson for you?
Don't bother
to do that for me.
I can still handle it.
I'm going to have a feast today.
I'm going to treat myself.
Can you add a pair of chopsticks?
Add a pair of chopsticks?
What do you mean?
Look to the right.
Piggy Jing!
Why are you here?
Zhou Ye and I
left Huandao together.
From now on, we
won't need to be separated anymore.
What do you mean?
That means
I'm now
unemployed.
I'll have to rely on you
to support me from now on.
Okay.
Then you have
to be good to me from now on.
No problem.
Right,
where are you staying tonight?
I'm still renting
the same house as before.
The owner never got round
to renting it out,
so I got it.
Okay.
Wait here for me for a while.
Where are you going?
I'll pack.
What are you packing for?
Why?
You don't want to live with me?
Go now.
I'll wait for you here.
Wait for me.
Okay.
We're back.
We're all back.
It's pretty clean this time.
Of course.
Your little sheep slippers.
Let me unpack your things.
I can do it myself.
Listen.
During the day,
I'll go to school,
and you and Zhou Ye will work here.
I need to get Zhou Ye
a punch card machine.
He likes slacking off.
He's very motivated now.
He's determined to humiliate Huandao.
Really?
Give it to me.
You even bring this?
Don't look at it.
You let me set it up
in the dormitory...
So I brought it all back.
Alright. Get me a glass of water.
Okay.
Quick.
Why is the power out?
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
There are candles in the house.
I'll look for the candles
and light them.
Coming.
The candles are lit.
I'm coming in.
Come... Come in.
Well,
I'll leave the candle here.
I'm going out now.
You...
Can you
not go yet?
I'm scared.
Okay.
Jing Xichi.
Yes?
Nothing.
I just want to say your name.
Jing Xichi.
Is "Xi" a polyphonic word?
It can also be pronounced as "Qi".
Qichi.
I'm poor and drifting, and I've got
to drink to drown my sorrows.
Doesn't "Qichi"
mean adrift?
In addition to what you said,
there's actually another saying.
Under Heng Gate,
you can have fun and rest.
Have you ever heard of it?
No.
It's from the Classic of Poetry.
It means
that as long as your heart is calm,
no matter how bad
the situation is,
you can use it
as a shelter from the wind and rain.
I see.
Why does everyone call you
Xichi instead of Qichi?
When people see
the word "Qichi",
they think of adrift.
My mom thought it was bad luck,
so she said she'd call me
Xichi instead.
I got it.
Aunt Lin wants you
to be able to find a home
wherever you go,
right?
So...
Have you found it now?
Jing Xichi.
We...
We went through a long detour.
We're finally back together.
They haven't arrived yet, have they?
It's been a while.
Go over there and take a look.
Year of the Monkey.
We have the same one.
It hasn't changed much
since we were here.
Huan'er.
Huan'er, Jing Xichi.
Feifan.
Bei.
It's been a long time.
- Why do you two...
- You two...
We've been together for a long time.
- Not that long.
- More than two years.
That's quite long.
When can we
attend your wedding reception?
Yes.
Soon.
Okay.
I've missed you so much.
Mee too.
It's been a long time.
Let's get together
with old classmates sometime.
We've got to go.
Okay.
Keep in touch in the group chat.
Keep in touch.
Bye.
What a coincidence.
Yeah.
We ran into our classmates.
They haven't changed much.
Top Student.
What a coincidence.
We're here.
Huan'er.
We've got to go now. Bye.
Okay.
- Bye.
- See you next time.
Bye.
What a coincidence.
Xinyan.
You're all dressed so beautifully.
It's been a long time.
Wait, it's not that.
We can see you every day.
Jing Xichi displays affection
on social media every day.
Xinyan, where do you work
in that outfit?
I've passed
the civil service exam this year.
They sent me to the countryside
for training.
I got back from the county,
and had time to get changed.
Xinyan has a stable job from now on,
okay?
Come in.
We're all inside.
Come on, let's go sit down.
Let's go.
Sorry I'm late.
I was delayed by something.
It's alright.
What is it?
Why don't you tell me?
It's been a long time.
- It's been a long time.
- It's been a long time, Tian.
What would you like to drink?
I'll order.
Let me do it.
Let me order.
No, let me do it.
I'd like to have some tea.
Song, we'd like to have hot drinks.
Okay.
I thought you didn't like hot drinks.
You want a hot drink, right?
You two are so sweet.
How is it?
Just like that.
We're good together.
So sweet. Nice.
Don't you watch
my social media everyday?
Didn't you say you wanted
to collect all the zodiac signs?
I didn't know better
when I was a kid.
Here you go.
My heart's locked up now.
No time for love,
and even no time to eat.
You're really busy.
Independent woman.
Let me do it.
Li Tian,
what are you wearing?
Are you married?
This is
an engagement.
When did you get engaged?
Why didn't you tell us?
Who said back then
that wise men don't fall in love?
Have you got your
relationship figured out yet?
You're engaged?
Shouldn't he wear the ring
on this finger for marriage?
It's an engagement.
With my dad's status,
he didn't want to announce it,
so I didn't tell you.
I'll give you invitations
to the wedding,
so you have to come.
Who's the bride?
Someone from your hospital?
Yes, who is it?
Secret.
- Secret?
To protect her.
It's like hiding a beauty in his place.
What about you two?
We're both doing internships.
Doing internships.
You two are in the same hospital
and there's no chemistry
between the two of you?
Yeah.
We are comrades in arms.
Colleagues.
Neighbors.
Okay.
Sorry I'm late.
Qi Qi.
You didn't reply to my messages.
I thought you weren't coming.
It's a class reunion, isn't it?
I'll come. I just wanted
to surprise you.
This is Du Man.
Hi. I'm Du Man.
Qi Qi.
Hi,
I'm Qi Qi.
The one who switched classes.
Yes, we met in school before.
I know.
Du Man was my deskmate.
Yes, Du Man.
How are you doing abroad?
Not bad.
Are you still writing now?
I'm publishing
my first book next year.
We'll definitely support you.
I'll ask my juniors to get one.
Okay.
We'll give you a boost in sales.
Don't spend the money.
I'll give you as much as you want.
Generous.
You're Princess Qi Qi indeed.
I'll give a copy to everyone
in my office.
Okay.
You go ahead and chat.
Well,
do you have a boyfriend now?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
Didn't I come back here to tell you?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Where did you meet
your boyfriend?
I met him
at an art exhibition abroad.
He's a music student.
Then...
What? You're envious again?
I want to fall in love too.
I want to fall in love.
Go ahead.
Come on.
Look.
Are these our books
from the Bookcrossing Event?
They look familiar.
"The Fountainhead"?
(I wish I could...)
It really is.
Look.
At that time,
after I broke up with Song Cong,
I donated this book
through Yangwu.
Song Cong,
I remember you said the other night
that you wrote this line
for a friend.
Now, can you tell me
who this friend is?
Sure.
Who?
He's sitting here.
He's sitting here?
Seriously?
I wrote it.
You wrote it?
You're something, huh?
I didn't write it.
I let him write it for me.
Yes, I wrote it for him.
Then whose
"Catcher in the Rye" do I have?
You're the one who took it?
This is Song Cong's.
This is Song Cong's?
Yes.
So, at that time,
I thought you liked Song Cong.
Who liked him?
How come I didn't know anything?
That's why I was so annoyed
with you.
I wasn't looking for him because...
To argue?
That means
she stole your book.
And he said I had no character.
You do have no character.
Do you want to look
for your own book, Bro?
What's wrong with mine? I...
Who did he give that book to?
He gave... He gave it to Huan'er.
Yes. I'm so pissed off.
It's because of your spell
that I'm still studying.
You could not have studied so well
without my Five-years of Past Exams
and Three-year of Mock Questions.
Knowledge brings wealth.
It brings me a handsome guy.
I got him.
Gosh.
I can't stand it.
And we even had a falling out.
That's because of Du Man.
What's it got to do with me?
You don't know, do you?
It's been so long.
And we were kids.
We didn't know that much.
Do you remember
when we went boating?
We shared a boat.
You had your own boat then.
Jing Xichi.
It's all your fault, Jing Xichi.
It was very cold that day.
You had to race.
It was cold that day.
He even ran her over in the water.
Yeah, he chased me and ran me over.
I fell into the water.
Do you remember
the sports day?
That day, you ran...
1,500 meters.
I felt my heart
pounding,
and then I fainted.
At that time, I
was going around the whole class,
and begging everyone
to help me run for me,
but no one participated.
At that time...
It's me.
Only me.
Then, I asked you...
I asked you to go.
And the Class 6 next door.
Yes.
The Class 6.
Fight with them.
You're even holding a
small hand flower.
How can you remember so much?
I remember it very well.
On the sports day.
I was so touched.
At that moment,
I had just come back from a run,
and then I saw you guys
standing up for me,
and I
knew
these were my sisters, and besties.
Do you remember
the blackout when we were about
to graduate?
Yes, the night of the blackout.
Right?
And there was Xu.
Xu.
Xu said something.
When I went back to my room, I cried!
Did you go back and cry?
Really, Jing Xichi?
You cried?
I... I didn't cry.
Wait.
I switched classes then.
So what did Mr. Xu
say that day?
What Xu means is
that, actually,
there's no standard in life.
Grades don't matter.
Yeah.
There are no standard answers in life.
Yes.
So is your life now
what you want it to be?
Yes, it's what I want.
Yes.
Me too.
For me,
yes.
I think so.
Yes.
The present is the best.
It's all good to look ahead.
As long as you don't regret it.
Yes.
Life is like a blank sheet of paper.
The paper is blank.
Fill it in with whatever colors you want
and it becomes your own painting.
Right?
You're not busy these two days, are you?
In a couple of days,
come to my house.
What's up?
You'll know it by then.
What's it?
Good or bad?
We won't go to help you move house.
(Wealth and peace)
Hello, future Li Tian.
Have you gone
to university in Cambridge by now?
If not,
don't blame current me too much
because I've done my best.
Got it.
I have a good news
and a bad news.
Let me start with the bad news first.
I didn't go
to Cambridge,
and I gave up on English Literature.
But I don't blame you
because the good news is
I'm still in love
with my life.
I've realized
that there's more
to life
than what I imagined
when I was a kid.
Hello, future Qi Qi.
I'd like to ask you,
have you become your mother's pride?
Have you gained
your mother's approval?
Whether you have or not,
it doesn't matter.
You should be
in charge of your own life now, right?
You...
Are you happy now?
I don't know if I have become
my mother's pride,
but
it doesn't matter now.
I think
she must have approved of me
because I can understand her now.
Of course
I'm in charge of my own life.
As for me being happy now...
Yes.
At least happier than when I was a kid.
Hello, future Du Man.
Are you making new friends now?
It's normal if you don't.
People are lonely.
The world changes all the time.
Remember to look ahead.
Speaking of friends,
I've found a lot of new friends
among my old classmates.
Every day of my internship
at the hospital is so busy
that I seem
to be able to ignore the loneliness.
That's good, actually.
The world is still changing,
and so am I.
Life
is all about
being bored and persevering
at the same time.
Play the claw machine when you're free.
You'll get a surprise once in a while.
Hello, future Liao Xinyan.
I want to ask you a question.
Are you in love?
Are you in love with a handsome man?
If he changes his mind first,
will you break up with him?
Remember,
always be the strongest in love.
Don't lose.
If it's possible,
collect all the signs of the zodiac.
That's it.
Liao Xinyan,
I were in love.
That's a handsome man.
Every breakup,
it's me who dumps them.
Don't worry.
I've tried
everything I wanted to try.
Now,
I can finally focus
on my career.
Besides,
you must not
confess to Jing Xichi.
It's really awkward.
Hello, future Song Cong,
You should have accomplished
your own goal by now.
Don't think too much.
You can definitely become
what you want to be.
The more precious something is,
the less you can get it
just by working for it.
Growing up for me means
accepting that I'm ordinary and common.
I'm sorry I failed the wonderful person
you were back then.
And I've suffered for it.
However,
I'm finally ready
to say goodbye to you now.
I'm so lucky to have met you.
Leave the rest of your life to me.
I'll walk the path for you.
Hello.
Hello, future Chen Huan'er.
I don't know how you're doing
in the future
or
if you've found your dreams
and goals.
But I
haven't yet.
In fact, I'm quite anxious
to see that everyone
has their own goals
and dreams.
Do you think
life is meaningless
if you don't find
your dream and what you want
to do
in life?
That's it.
Bye.
Hello,
little Huan'er.
I know you're probably
panicking about not being able
to find your goal
and meaning in life.
But Jing Xichi is right.
Let's play it by ear.
Life is not a test.
There are no standard answers.
Everyone will answer differently.
I have
my dad
and mom
around me.
The people I love
and the people who love me
are all here.
I'm very happy.
(Song Cong,)
(I remember you used to say)
(that friends are meant
to be in certain phases.)
(Do you still think so?)
(Maybe some of our friends)
(can only accompany us
on a short journey.)
(But our lives )
(are complete because
of this little journey.)
(Those)
(who have been in our lives)
(will be part of our souls)
(for the rest of our lives.)
(Xichi.)
(Huan'er, come out now.)
(It's time to make dumplings.)
(Let's go.)
(Coming.)
Let's go. Let's make dumplings.
It's no use running.
I'll be sure to get you on tape.
None of you will escape.
It's 3 PM today,
17 September 2008.
It's a beautiful day.
The sun is shining.
It's quiet outside the family
housing compound again.
I wonder what everyone is doing.
Li Tian
must be studying.
He's been trying to surpass Song.
I sometimes want to tell him
to let himself go,
to stop being so hard on himself.
Song.
Song must be thinking about life.
I'm really puzzled too.
What on earth
does he have to think about
all the time every day?
Chen Huan'er
is carefree.
She must be either sleeping
or having a good time
because of something.
Silly girl.
If I could,
I'd like time to stop right now.
They always say
that change is a constant in life.
So
houses get torn down,
friends get separated,
and even
the closest people leave.
But I always think
that even if that day comes,
the traces
of those people
and things
will follow me,
and accompany me
all the way to a faraway place.
Even if I've already forgotten
this afternoon
many years from now.
Anyway,
some things will change
and some things
will never change.
♪I remember there's a place
I used to know♪
♪Where the sun always shined♪
♪The nights were warm♪
♪Where we were living wild and free♪
♪Hearts were bold♪
♪But now I lost my way♪
♪To get back home♪
♪And I heard these echoes of my soul♪
♪In the crowds♪
♪It's been so long♪
♪That I miss those days♪
♪When dreams felt close♪
♪In that place we called home♪
=Always Home=
♪Fallen leaves flutter past your gaze♪
♪I dream of worlds within your days♪
♪Countless times,
I write your name in my heart♪
♪Wishes whispered to the stars above♪
♪How many faces in the glass I see♪
♪Time's gentle hand
pulling me out of my cocoon♪
♪Under the sun,
a rainbow butterfly takes flight♪
♪To rest upon your left shoulder bright♪
♪I still hear your promise in my ears♪
♪Before we said goodbye,
your spirit free♪
♪And full of life♪
♪If summer could last a little longer♪
♪Would regrets rewrite
where we'd gone wrong?♪
♪And let me be there with you
at the end of the story♪
♪Watching your silhouette from behind♪
♪My footsteps slow, we were too young♪
♪To know right from wrong♪
♪Your sweat-kissed face
I hold in my memory♪
♪Glows as bright as ever♪
♪I hope one day we'll meet again♪
♪At just the right time♪