♫  No matter if it's a rainy day or a sunny day  ♫
♫  As long as you are by my side  ♫
♫  Even the sunlight becomes dazzling  ♫
♫  Thinking too much, blindly guessing  ♫
♫  Why not find a day to meet  ♫
♫  Saying too much, there's no "what if"  ♫
♫  Might as well go on an adventure  ♫
♫  I stand in the shadows  ♫
♫  Reaching out, waiting for your rescue  ♫
♫  Between you and me  ♫
♫  Even if the world collapses  ♫
♫  No matter how far the distance  ♫
♫  Nothing can stop our meeting  ♫
♫  Stepping through the long dark night  ♫
♫  You are standing at the finish line  ♫
♫  Protecting you is my tiny wish  ♫
♫  Goodbye to the shy me of the past  ♫
♫  Because of you, I have become a little braver  ♫
For all these shampoos and other items, I let Huan Er bring them.
- Buy two more bottles later.
- Close it tightly so they don't leak.
- Dad, Mom, I'm home!
- My dear, you're back.
You're back.
My dear girl, you've become slimmer.
- Have you been too tired lately?
- No, I haven't.
- Why do I think she...
- Mom, what are you doing?
See, your mom is so forgetful.
Your admission letter already arrived, and I just remembered to get things ready for you.
Oh, right. You have to report on the 28th.
So soon?
Here, you see.
Jing Xi Chi, how about you?
I'm the same as Cong.
What about your second choice?
I didn't fill out a second choice.
You didn't? How bold you are!
What if you don't get in?
What else? I'll just retake it.
What are you talking about?
You know how hard this year has been.
What's wrong?
Not happy?
Do you think the stuff Dad bought is old-fashioned?
He doesn't have an eye for fashion.
Doesn't look good? I can get you something else.
No, Dad.
I just feel that... I'm going to university.
Leaving home for another city, being away from friends and parents... I feel a bit reluctant.
Tianhe isn't far from Wuan.
That's less than an hour away by high-speed rail.
- If you're homesick, come back every week.
- Yeah.
When I have time, I'll visit you whenever I can.
Huan Er, your mom is right.
Just come back if you miss home.
If it gets too hard, it's fine not to go to university.
Dad! Can you wish me something good for once?
Oh, yeah, Mom.
Has Jing Xi Chi received his admission letter yet?
- I don't know.
- I do.
How do you know?
I saw it. A delivery man went to their house a few days ago and delivered a letter.
You've got sharp eyes.
What do you mean?
Congratulations on getting into your dream university.
I also received the offer letter from Anhui-Wuan University.
Want to meet up?
I think celebrating in person is more meaningful.
Why are you here?
I was bored at home with nothing to do, so I came to find you.
How was your graduation trip?
It was fine.
I can tell from your response that it wasn't fine.
Luckily, I decided not to go.
I knew it would have been a waste of money and suffering.
All of you are too complicated.
With that money, I'd rather study.
Yeah, it's so complicated.
I...
Never mind.
You should go home. I'm closing up.
Fine.
All right. I'll come by tomorrow.
Don't come here tomorrow.
I won't be here tomorrow.
I have a tutoring job tomorrow.
Huan Er.
Song Cong.
Why are you here?
I just stepped out to get some air.
Congratulations on getting into Yenching University.
Thanks.
Congratulations to you too.
Thank you.
I was just watering the plants.
I'll get going now.
Huan Er.
Stop avoiding me.
I think there are things I need to clarify with you.
I want to apologize.
What I said that day must have made things awkward for you.
I... I drank too much that day and got a little carried away.
It's fine.
You don't have to apologize for that.
Just pretend I never said it.
Well...
Can we...
still be friends after this?
Honestly... It's hard for now.
Please give me some time to process.
All right.
It's okay.
If you feel it's awkward, you can just think of me as a neighbor.
I'm leaving.
I'm at our secret base.
Do you want to come?
I'm working on the website. I'm not going.
- Sit here.
- All right.
I'll go and order some drinks.
- What do you want?
- Anything is fine.
Hello, waiter.
- Hi.
- Three orange juices, please.
Thank you.
Huan Er, how do you resist buying all those pretty dresses?
I feel like none of the stores have one that suits me.
Which one do you think looks better? The gray one or the white one that I didn't buy?
White...
I think they both look nice.
They look the same to me.
I think white is more elegant.
And I feel like my boyfriend likes that style more too.
You have a boyfriend?
- Xin Yan!
- Babe!
I'm sorry. There was a long line at the ice cream store when I bought this.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
- Thank you.
Oops, sorry. You have a friend with you here.
I only bought one.
I'll go and get another for your friend.
That's so sweet of you. It's so hot outside.
It's fine. Not a big deal.
Just wait for me a while.
Wait a minute.
Help me pick. Which dress looks better?
Gray or white?
I love them both, and I can't decide.
They both look great.
If you like them both, just buy them both.
- I'll pay for it.
- I'm not that greedy.
They are similar. One is enough.
You go and buy the ice cream.
I have another friend coming later. Get one more.
All right.
Chen Huan Er! What's with that face?
Nothing.
Huan Er! Xin Yan!
Why are you so late?
I just finished my piano lesson and came straight here.
Did you see my boyfriend just now?
- What?
- Is he handsome?
- She has a boyfriend now.
- The one who just walked out.
Boyfriend?
Why that expression? Is it strange for me to have a boyfriend?
Not strange.
Just...
Just a little too fast.
I got rejected three days ago.
Just three days?
Are you upset because you got rejected by Jing Xi Chi
and you want to get back at him?
How is that possible?
I like my boyfriend very much.
Then... When did you meet your boyfriend?
- Yesterday.
- Yesterday?
On a soccer field.
It was love at first sight.
Soccer field?
So...
He's a substitute?
How should I put it... not exactly.
I thought about it, and I just like this kind of athletic guy.
So, do you still like Jing Xi Chi?
Yes, I do.
You like them both?
It's just like with these dresses.
I like them both, just in different colors.
If circumstances allowed, I'd want them both.
That sounds...
reasonable...
How can this be reasonable?
Dresses and people aren't the same.
Why not?
Are you planning to be hung up on Song Cong forever?
You... How did you...
You're way too obvious about Song Cong.
I don't know.
But, Song Cong doesn't like me.
There's nothing between us.
Qi Qi, I already made things clear with him that day.
I knew something was going on between you two.
I could tell from the agriculture study lesson.
No, there's nothing!
Qi Qi, don't misunderstand me.
I made it clear to him.
Don't worry.
Whether Song Cong likes or doesn't like you, or whoever he likes,
you will always be my most important friend.
So, since there's nothing between you and Song Cong...
Doesn't that mean you have a chance?
Me?
Think about it. For four years of university life,
you two will be far away from home with no parents around to watch over you,
and there will be plenty of chances for you to study together.
Isn't that your opportunity?
Tell me more.
First, you have to take the initiative.
In Year 1, you need to seize the moment.
Well, how does she take the initiative?
Make sure he knows you like him.
He already knows.
Then you're halfway there.
That's already halfway?
So, what about the other half?
Since you two are serious about learning this,
I'll share my unbeatable dating strategies with you.
Xin Yan, stop keeping us in suspense. Just tell us.
No desire means strength.
The ice cream is here.
Thanks, babe. This is my boyfriend.
This is my friend Qi Qi, and this is Huan Er. You just saw her.
Nice to meet you.
Don't just sit there. Try it.
Let me feed you.
Is it sweet?
Sweet?
Want another bite?
Dad, Mom.
- You're back, my dear.
- You're back.
I'm hungry. What did you guys make?
We thought you wouldn't be eating at home, so your dad and I just mixed everything
and made a cold dish along with some Zhajiangmian.
Come, let's eat together.
- Is this enough?
- It smells so good.
Is it okay?
How could this not be okay, Mom?
I was planning to eat out with my classmates,
but then I thought that since university is starting soon,
I should enjoy more of my mom's homemade food.
What a liar!
Your classmates must have had other plans and didn't invite you.
- How did you know?
- Is it that they had a date
and didn't want you to be a third wheel?
Dad! Mom must have put a GPS on me.
I just guessed.
Wait, wait. What does it mean, Huan Er?
Your classmates started dating?
- Yeah.
- No need to act so shocked.
They'll be university students soon. What's wrong with dating?
No. What do you mean by "what's wrong with it"?
Huan Er is still a young lady.
Huan Er, listen to your dad.
In university, the most important thing is to focus on your studies,
not on starting dating. I absolutely won't allow it.
Don't listen to him. I tell you, it's your university life.
It lasts four years. Why not enjoy your youth?
Hold on, don't fill her head with all that, okay?
What do you mean by "enjoy your youth"?
What do you mean by that?
When I was in medical school,
weren't you the one who always appeared at my school and chased after me?
- During your postgraduate years!
- Don't mess around.
She's just in her freshman year.
- You're unbelievable.
- Absolutely no dating!
Let me ask you something.
Someone likes your classmate.
Does anyone in your class like you?
Chen Huan Er, I like you.
No one...
How could anyone like me?
It makes sense. Slurping noodles like that.
You're not ladylike at all. It'd be weird if someone liked you.
Just like you.
Well.
Jing Xi Chi and Song Cong are around you all the time.
Why don't they like you?
That makes sense.
They must not see you as a girl.
Dad.
Mom says I'm not even a girl.
Can't you stop talking? My daughter is wonderful!
- She's beautiful and nice.
- Look at the way you eat.
She learned it from you.
Still, no dating!
Don't listen to him.
Dad.
Are you done eating?
It's all yours.
Take this big bowl.
Have some vitamin C after your meal.
- Mom, I can't eat anymore.
- Eat slowly.
Oh, right. Since it's back-to-school season, book your ticket soon or it'll be too late.
Got it.
By the way, Aunt Hao Mei told me Song Cong is heading to school early.
Is Jing Xi Chi going with him?
I don't know.
Aren't you always hanging out with him?
He's been disappearing lately. I have no idea what he's up to.
Huan Er, I have something to discuss with you.
It's your first time going to university.
What about us going with you?
- Yeah, yeah.
- No way!
- Why not?
- Dad, Mom,
none of my classmates go with their parents.
That's fine, we can.
How do you know no one's parents are going?
Xin Yan isn't going with her parents.
- Dad, Mom.
- We can go.
At least let me spend time with you.
I'm going to university to learn to live independently. Really!
Help me!
It's almost time to enter university. When are you leaving?
Not decided yet.
Are you free? Come and meet me at our secret base.
He finally remembered me.
What's up?
I have something to tell you.
Let's talk about it when we meet.
Mom, I'm going out for a while.
Jing Xi Chi, I sent you so many messages, but you didn't reply.
And you're finally willing to contact me.
What happened?
What is this?
The money from selling our books.
Qi Qi, Xin Yan, and Song Cong have already taken theirs.
You're the last one.
That much?
Did you call me here just to give me money?
Yeah.
We're going to university soon.
Don't you have anything else to say?
I mean, I haven't seen you these past few days.
I have no idea what you've been up to.
I was selling books, working on my website, and handling all sorts of random things.
It's fine.
Anyway, we'll see each other during school breaks.
If you need anything, just call me.
Honestly, when I got my admission letter, I was really happy.
But the moment I realized we were all going our separate ways
and living in different cities...
I couldn't feel happy anymore.
Do you think...
we will slowly lose touch?
Why?
You'll... miss me?
Yeah. I'll miss you.
All right. I'll get going.
Oh, yeah.
Well... Before we part, can I give you a hug?
- I'm leaving.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Not a big deal.
We're not that far apart.
I'll come back soon.
Driver, can you open the trunk?
Make sure to keep your ID safe.
Keep your wallet secure.
And as soon as you get off the train, call me. Got it?
Yes, I'll text you.
Huan Er, do you have enough phone credit?
If not, I can top it up.
You just topped it up with a hundred yuan yesterday.
Remember, when you get there, eat well and buy whatever you need.
Don't worry, I won't let myself go hungry.
- Oh yeah—
- Stop nagging.
She still has to catch the train. If you hold her up, she'll miss it.
Wait a second. I want a hug.
- Dad.
- Take care of yourself.
One more hug for me.
All right, didn't you say she was in a hurry? Go on, go on.
I'm off. Bye, Mom.
By the way, there's a pack of medicine in your bag.
And remember to wear more layers when it gets cold.
- Drink less cold beverages.
- Got it.
- Go on. Driver, please drive carefully.
- Be safe.
- Bye, Mom.
- Take care of yourself!
- Stay safe. You hear me?
- Got it.
Bye!
Dad, take care of Mom.
Don't worry.
I'm just as worried as you.
How about I apply to be a security guard at her school?
- Even if I'm just watching the gates...
- Forget it.
You're always traveling abroad, and I never feel that you're worried about her.
She's just going to Wuan now. It's not far away.
And you became so worried about her.
It's different. She was at home before. You were here to keep an eye on her.
Now, someone else will be watching out for her.
Who? Did you arrange something?
See, you're totally out of the loop.
What?
What are you talking about?
­
Did you check in yet?
Thank you.
What do you think?
When it matters, you can always count on me to show up, right?
Jing Xi Chi!
Wait, why are you here?
Wuan University. Computer Science.
Student ID: 110101.
Chen Huan Er, we're schoolmates again.
Surprised?
Didn't you apply to Yenching University?
I missed the mark by a few points.
Didn't you tell me you only put down one school?
You think I'm silly? I put down more than one!
I lied to you.
What's wrong? Too happy to speak?
Let's go.
I'll take you to your dorm. Are the girls' dorms over there?
I can handle it myself.
It's fine, I can help you.
I said, I can handle it.
Are you mad?
I just wanted to mess with you because I wanted to surprise you.
Can you be more mature?
I was worried about you all summer.
It wasn't necessary.
Are you really mad?
Chen Huan Er.
- I didn't mean to.
- Are you Chen Huan Er?
- Yes, I am?
- Hi, I'm Tian Chi,
a senior in the School of Pharmacy.
I'm helping with freshman orientation today.
Are you from Tianhe No.1 High School?
Yes, I am.
I'm from Tianhe No.1 High School too. I'm two years ahead of you.
Nice to meet you, Senior!
- And you are?
- I'm from Tianhe No.1 High School as well.
I just got into Wuan University's Computer Science.
I'm Jing Xi Chi.
Welcome to Anhui-Wuan University.
Are you heading to the dorms?
Yeah, I am.
I also had to go to the dorm supervisor to check students' information.
- I can take you there.
- Thank you, but no need.
- We'll go ourselves.
- Thanks, Tian Chi.
Let me help you.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
We met at the library back then.
I don't know if you still remember.
Really? When was that?
I remember there was a Book Exchange Event.
It left quite an impression on me.
I borrowed a book back then and never returned it.
The book I put in the exchange also never came back.
Could it be that you took it?
The book you put in... Was it...
Neuropsychology?
So, it was you!
What a coincidence! I'll return it to you.
- Sorry about that.
- It's fine.
Since it's fate that we meet again, I will just give it to you.
Really?
Let's go.
Aunt, don't worry. Huan Er has arrived at the dorm.
You didn't get into Yenching University?
Why?
I missed it by two points.
Then, what was your second choice?
- Anhui-Wuan.
- Wuan University?
Wuan University is pretty good too. You'll be at the same school as Huan Er.
Yeah.
Can you do me a little favor?
Aunt, I got it.
Chen Huan Er. I'll definitely take good care of her.
But, Aunt, can you keep this a secret for me?
A guy's got to have some pride. I understand.
- Who are you?
- Hello.
You're also in the Computer Science department?
How do you know?
I just overheard it earlier.
You could hear that from there?
I have sharp ears. I'm a freshman too.
Which room are you in?
- 258.
- 258?
- Really 258?
- Yes, 258.
- That's destiny, buddy.
- What? What destiny?
- Let's go.
- My suitcase.
- Just come with me.
- Who are you?
- I'll take you there.
- Wait...
- Come with me.
- Give me my suitcase first.
- Just come with me.
- Who are you?
Did you come with that guy from earlier?
No, I came alone.
I saw him drop you off downstairs, so I thought you two were close.
We were high school classmates.
Let's go.
- That's it.
- I'll help you bring it inside.
It's fine. I can do it myself.
Hello. I'm Huang Lu.
You can call me Huanghuang or Lulu.
Hi. I'm Chen Huan Er.
Huan Er.
Well... And this is?
This is our direct senior.
Hi, I'm Tian Chi.
Hi, Tian Chi.
Hi.
Well, if there's nothing else, I'll get going.
All right, thank you, Tian Chi. Thanks.
- Bye, Tian Chi.
- Bye!
Wow, such a handsome senior.
Is he your boyfriend?
No, no.
We just met downstairs.
He's from my high school.
A potential boyfriend, then?
No, don't simply say that.
Don't be shy.
What's the big deal? Or do you have a boyfriend from high school?
- So, you can't make him yours.
- No!
- Really?
- Really.
- Really no?
- Look into my eyes. Really no?
- No, no.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Hi, juniors.
- Hello, senior.
Qiu Li, we left your luggage here.
- Thank you.
- Well,
if there's nothing else, we'll head out. Feel free to contact us anytime.
We're in the same major, so we should help each other out.
- All right.
- We'll get going.
- We're leaving.
- Bye, seniors.
We'll keep in touch.
Hello, I'm Qiu Li.
Hi. I'm Chen Huan Er.
I'm Huang Lu.
We're all roommates now. Let's take care of each other.
Of course!
Oh, right! My roommates, since we're all here,
I brought some specialty snacks from my hometown. Take whatever you like.
That's a lot!
Take a look.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Wait... Aren't we missing one person?
Oh, her? She arrived early.
Where is she now?
She went to the library early in the morning.
That early?
It's only the first day.
All right, I'll go unpack. Help yourselves.
Thanks!
Come on!
From today on, we'll be living under the same roof.
He's Yan Mu.
He doesn't talk much.
This is your place.
Are you the one who obtained the highest score in our major?
My student ID is 02.
You scored even higher than me. Why did you come to Wuan University?
I didn't get into my first choice.
Was your first choice...
Wow, we're really in the same boat. Such a coincidence! I...
Come on!
What a coincidence!
Come on, take this.
Since we're so similar, just take this with you.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it. We're too similar!
Buddy, your gear is really something.
It's pretty nice.
Listen, Jing, as guys, we need to be delicate too.
I think you also have a good base.
But you shouldn't slack off, or you won't be able to get a girlfriend here either.
Thank you.
Wait.
You didn't disinfect it.
Are you... a Virgo?
I'm tough on the outside and soft on the inside.
I'm a meticulous person.
It's done.
What did you mean just now?
In other words, I'm a "hidden gem" type of guy with rich emotions.
- All right. You, carry on.
- Okay.
And our other roommate?
He is Zhang Yang. He went out to play soccer.
You unpack first.
Come on.
Such a coincidence.
Thanks.
Disinfectant. Disinfectant.
- Thanks.
- Not a big deal.
­
Song Cong, do you know whose bed is opposite?
- Who?
- Lin Jing Yi.
Our school's top scorer.
I really want to see what kind of person can achieve such a crazy high score.
Hello, Cong. What's up?
When are you coming to register?
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
I didn't get into Yenching University.
I'm at Wuan University now.
You applied for a second choice?
Then, why didn't you tell me when I asked if you wanted to come with me?
Because I was afraid that if I told you, you'd tell Aunt Hao,
and then the whole family housing compound would know.
How would I surprise Chen Huan Er then?
Are you sure it's a surprise and not a shock?
You're right.
It probably was a shock.
She's mad at me.
You're so bad, Jing Xi Chi.
I suggest you properly apologize to her.
All right, I got it.
Anything else? If not, I'm hanging up.
Fighting with your girlfriend?
No. It's just my childhood friend.
It's childhood sweethearts then.
Have you finished unpacking?
Our dorm doesn't have air conditioning.
Do you have one in your dorm?
And what about having dinner together tonight?
Who wants to have dinner with you?
What's this?
Huan Er, this is a medicine kit I prepared for you to prevent acclimatization issues.
One pack for you, one pack for Xi Chi.
So, I was the only one who didn't know? Everyone kept this from me?
I'm Tian Chi. This is my phone number.
If you need any help, feel free to ask.
Senior Tian Chi, how did you get my phone number?
I'm in charge of freshman registration.
Your personal information is in the student handbook.
Thank you for your help this morning.
Don't mention it.
How bad!
They are too bad!
OST:
­"Yesterday’s Clear Sky" by Yang Xizi
♫  The falling leaves outside the window gently glide past your sight  ♫
♫  Imagining how special your world must be  ♫
♫  How many times have I written your name in my heart?  ♫
♫  The wishes made upon the stars, how I hope they come true  ♫
♫  Looking at myself in the mirror, how many sides do I truly have?  ♫
♫  Quietly changing with time, breaking free from the cocoon  ♫
♫  A rainbow butterfly dancing under the sunlight  ♫
♫  When will it finally land on your left shoulder?  ♫
♫  Before saying goodbye  ♫
♫  The you from back then  ♫
♫  Still free and passionate  ♫
♫  If only this summer could last a little longer  ♫
♫  Will regrets ever be rewritten?  ♫
♫  The end of the story  ♫
♫  Has me standing by your side  ♫
♫  Watching your silhouette  ♫
♫  I am behind you  ♫
♫  Walk a little slower  ♫
♫  The us from back then  ♫
♫  Still didn't know how to tell things apart  ♫
♫  In my memories, sweat dampened your face  ♫
♫  Still shining just as brightly  ♫
♫  Looking forward to the day  ♫
♫  When we meet again  ♫
♫  At the right time  ♫