♫  No matter if it's a rainy day or a sunny day  ♫
♫  As long as you are by my side  ♫
♫  Even the sunlight becomes dazzling  ♫
♫  Thinking too much, blindly guessing  ♫
♫  Why not find a day to meet  ♫
♫  Saying too much, there's no "what if"  ♫
♫  Might as well go on an adventure  ♫
♫  I stand in the shadows  ♫
♫  Reaching out, waiting for your rescue  ♫
♫  Between you and me  ♫
♫  Even if the world collapses  ♫
♫  No matter how far the distance  ♫
♫  Nothing can stop our meeting  ♫
♫  Stepping through the long dark night  ♫
♫  You are standing at the finish line  ♫
♫  Protecting you is my tiny wish  ♫
♫  Goodbye to the shy me of the past  ♫
♫  Because of you, I have become a little braver  ♫
The best mom.
I love you.
I'll use this one.
Mom, aren't you on the night shift? Why are you back so early?
Are you sure it's your mom?
Dad! Dad!
Weren't you coming back? Why did you suddenly come back?
It's your mom's birthday. I wanted to surprise her. How could I not come?
Dad! Listen. I've got everything ready.
That's great!
- Hurry, give it to me!
- Let me wash my hands first.
You have no idea how hard it is for me to take time off.
What happened, Dad?
Huan Er.
Why are my mouth-rinsing cup, toothbrush, and towel gone from the washroom?
Where did they go?
Mom said the washroom was too crowded there, so she put them away.
- Let me call and ask her.
- Don't!
Don't call her. If you do, the surprise will be ruined.
Yeah, you're right!
You see, I hardly ever come home, and now I feel like this isn't even my house.
Dad, I'll go and buy you a new set.
- Don't! Forget it.
- It's just downstairs.
It's late now. It's not safe.
I have a solution.
What is it?
I'll rub my teeth with my fingers; that'll do.
Dad, don't be disgusting.
Your mom is unreasonable for putting all my stuff away.
Luckily, no one noticed.
Oh my god.
Huan Er, is there any milk left?
This milk expired days ago.
Dad, try looking for it again.
Doesn't your mom cook for you?
I've just found five or six bottles of expired stuff here.
Also, this spatula wasn't cleaned properly after being used.
Is your mom mistreating you at home or what?
How am I abusing her?
Wherever you came from, go back there!
Mistreating her? If you're not happy, take her away!
- Look, this is expired.
- I'm playing both the mom and dad roles.
- It's not easy for me.
- Do you think it's easy for me?
Please, come back to the topic. This milk is expired.
So what? I'll use it as fertilizer for the plants! I didn't give it to her to drink!
- Are you just arguing for the sake of it?
- You're barely ever home all year,
and you have the nerve to lecture me?
What do you mean? Why am I never home?
I work hard all year. I raise the kid and take care of her.
I live like a widow. Is it easy for me?
You've gone overboard. A widow? Then, who am I here?
- I'm just like a widow.
- Aren't I out there earning money?
Earning money? Give it to me.
- I gave you all the money!
- That little bit?
I gave you money and you bought such a thing?
- Why can't I buy this?
- This could poison someone.
What's wrong with you?
All you buy is expired stuff.
How was I supposed to know it was expired?
I don't want to argue with you anymore. I just got off my night shift.
I'll sleep first, then I'll argue with you later.
Stay or leave, it's up to you.
You scared me half to death!
Morning. You wake up so early.
Morning.
Why are you up so early?
What else?
Taking out the trash.
Oh yeah. You have to take out the trash.
It's still early. Why are you in your pajamas
and standing in front of my house?
I...
I woke up early too.
Go on. Keep making things up.
Hold on, Chen Huan Er. That look on your face...
You really see me as just a brother, right?
I...
I just...
wanted to ask you for tutoring.
You...
want me... to tutor you?
You're talking nonsense in the morning. Are you sleepwalking?
- Are you...
- Ouch! It's painful.
My parents had a fight.
I just wanted to come here and hide for a bit.
Is that okay?
Cong, come to my house! Chen Huan Er needs you.
Wait, should I change my outfits too?
Otherwise, I'm going to look out of place with you two.
Are you okay?
I'm fine now.
What's so funny?
Nothing, go on.
Sorry for waking you both up so early.
I just don't understand why my parents suddenly started fighting.
They used to argue, but never this bad.
Why are they fighting?
I don't know.
When I woke up and started washing up,
my dad was making breakfast and my mom returned from her night shift.
Then suddenly they started fighting.
It feels like they argue because of me.
Didn't you ask them why they were fighting?
How am I supposed to ask?
Fair point...
What about your parents?
What do they usually fight about?
My parents?
My parents...
Anything from international wars to the most trivial things.
As long as they breathe the same air, they'll find a reason to argue.
Usually, within a minute, my dad finds a way to coax my mom.
And soon after he calms her down, within another minute, they'll start fighting again.
Sometimes, it gets really dramatic.
In our house, there's no fighting.
Never?
Never.
Every day, it's just my dad who gets scolded.
Now that you mention it, I think my family isn't so bad after all.
But what I really don't get is...
if they can't stand each other so much,
why did they choose to be together when they were young?
Haven't you heard the saying?
Many people say that before having kids, parents have a good relationship.
Who told you this nonsense?
So, according to you, why did our parents have us?
To suffer?
Who knows?
All beings endure suffering.
Oh, right. Let me show you something I found last night.
- Where is it?
- What is it?
This and this.
Do you get it?
So basically, your dad and your mom are actually fine.
Wait, does that mean...
Your dad, and your mom?
Are you crazy?
My mom?
How could that possibly be my mom?
All right, move a little this way.
- This way?
- Yeah, this background.
All right.
One, two...
No more film.
Sorry about that. Let me check if I have a spare roll.
Hold on.
No rush. Take your time.
Yi Fan, why do I feel he has other intentions toward you?
Xi Chi.
Good morning, Mom.
- Morning, Aunt Lin.
- Morning.
You three slept in this room last night?
Mom, what are you thinking?
How could it be possible to fit three of us on my bed?
They just got here.
Just got here? Then you probably haven't had breakfast yet.
What do you want to eat? I'll make it for you.
- Mom.
- What's wrong?
Can I ask you a question?
Uncle Song... back when he was younger, did he... ever like you?
What?
You're back for B and C again?
What a special style you have!
Why are you here?
Delivering photos to Jing Xi Chi.
I have something for you.
Regarding the last math problem, I thought about it.
I think that not everything needs an answer.
What if the answer isn't what you want?
Study it carefully.
This is all I can do to help.
Jing Xi Chi.
I'm here. Open the door.
­
Dad, Mom doesn't like surprises.
If you do this, will she take it seriously?
You don't get it.
Your mom's been in the hospital for a year. She's seen all kinds of chaos and drama.
Ordinary surprises don't work on her.
I tell you, you must follow my orders later.
As soon as your mom comes home in a sorrowful mood,
we rush up and give her a big hug.
That's what we call a surprise. What do you think?
- All right.
- Let's do it.
Let's go.
Didn't you say she went to the hospital for a quick visit?
We've been waiting for so long. Why isn't she back yet?
I don't know.
My back hurts. Keep an eye out for me. I need a break.
All right. Go ahead, Dad.
Dad! She's here! She's here!
Hurry!
Move!
Hide! Hide! Hide!
Chen Lei! Give me back my daughter!
What's happening?
- Oh no, we messed up.
- Oh my goodness.
- Mom! Mom!
- Li Na! Li Na! Li Na!
Chen Lei!
Huan Er!
Li Na!
- Mom! Mom!
- Li Na!
Mom!
Why did you come back? Why did you even come back?
Get your filthy hands off me! I tell you...
Take this!
You two are too much! You scared me a lot.
- What is this?
- Look!
Why don't you hang a banner for me too?
- Oh, right, Dad!
- We forgot the banner.
I'll get a banner next time!
- Hurry up!
- Sit down!
You two are too much!
- Mom, don't be angry.
- We were just joking.
Huan Er, put this on your mom. Come on, come on.
- I'm not wearing that!
- Come on, put it on!
So pretty! How beautiful!
Look here. Ready?
- I don't want!
- Just take a look. Just take a look.
One, two, three.
Sister, after thinking about it, I want to change back to the previous cake. Can I?
Sure!
Honey, happy birthday!
Dad picked this one out himself.
This looks pretty nice.
Look.
Come on, let's celebrate the birthday.
Look at you. How could you take it seriously?
Wasn't it just a joke?
What joke? That was a scare, okay?
Fine, a scare. Sorry, sorry.
Light the candles.
♪  Happy birthday to you  ♪
♪  Happy birthday to me  ♪
Make a wish, make a wish.
Make a wish. Mom, make a wish.
Blow out the candles.
All right.
- Mom.
- Look how nice it is.
I prepared a birthday present for you.
- Look. This is the one I prepared.
- There's even a birthday gift!
Mom, open it and see.
Inside... you're the star of every photo.
You learned this from Jing Xi Chi, right?
Not very original.
- Yeah.
- I went through our family photos,
but I couldn't find many pictures of you both.
You were always busy taking pictures of me.
From now on, I'll take more pictures of you both.
Oh, you're mistaken.
Your mom used to have more than a dozen photo albums. They were all lost when we moved.
All that's left is...
♪  Happy birthday!  ♪
Mom, do you like it?
- Does it look nice?
- How about this one?
Isn't it nice?
Come on, let's eat cake.
Don't just eat cake.
I'll cook some noodles.
Let me do it. You don't have to.
You just stay and cut the cake. Let me do it. I'll do it.
Just as I expected, my parents' argument ended without any danger this time.
Now I finally understand that only when love is deep enough can one argue
with such confidence.
That's their unique kind of romance.
- Why did you call me here?
- You'll know when you see it.
I'm full. I don't feel like moving.
- Hurry up.
- I feel bloated.
Go up there! Sit there.
Here. Sit here.
What are you doing?
Close your eyes.
Have you already closed your eyes?
Don't open your eyes unless I tell you to.
Don't open your eyes. You must not open your eyes.
- Are you cheating?
- No.
No peeking! Close your eyes.
- I got it.
- No peeking.
Chen Huan Er!
No peeking!
I'm watching you. Don't try to peek.
I'm watching you. Don't open your eyes yet. I'm still watching you.
- What exactly are you up to?
- You'll find out soon.
Stop talking.
Don't open your eyes.
Stretch out your hand.
No peeking. You still can't open your eyes yet.
- Wait a while.
- I didn't peek.
Don't open your eyes.
What's that sound?
Open your eyes.
This...
Didn't they say they don't sell this cake in slices?
This is just a small problem that won't defeat me.
Look at you. You wanted to eat it, didn't you?
Since you want to eat it, of course you should have it.
How did you settle this?
Hi.
Could you get me the cake from the display rack and cut it into three pieces?
Okay, wait a moment.
- What's the big deal?
- Why did you call me over?
What are you doing?
Back at Sishui, didn't Aunt Hao like eating cake?
Take this cake back for her. She'd be so happy.
But you guys didn’t invite me there. Why drag me into this?
I'm not accepting your bribe.
Buddy, I'm not bribing you.
I was just thinking of you.
Look, Dr. Li worries about you every day.
Shouldn't you do something to show your filial piety?
Am I right?
I've finished packing.
Thank you.
- You two, remember to pay.
- What?
158 yuan.
Do you have...
How much do you have?
38 yuan.
Not enough.
Still 20 yuan short.
Just 20 yuan more.
I have no more left.
- We'll just take one.
- Can we pay next time?
Why do you ask so many questions? Just eat it.
There's even a candle.
It's not my birthday today.
Who cares if it's your birthday or not?
I say it's your birthday, so it is.
Happy birthday.
Don't cry.
Close your eyes.
Make a wish.
Blow out the candle after making a wish.
Thank you.
It must be very delicious.
Eat it.
Why is there only one?
I bought this for you. I'm not eating. You eat it.
Here, hold it. Eat it.
How is it?
- This is delicious, right?
- It's so good.
- You try a bite too.
- I don't want to.
- Just try one.
- I find you gross.
I don't even mind you, and you mind me?
Try it, it's really good.
Is it good?
- It's really delicious!
- Yummy, right?
No wonder it's so expensive.
Is this pricey?
Not really. I got it covered. Eat up.
Then, take another bite.
Mom, I got you a cake. Try it.
Son, you finally know how to care for your mom.
All right, I'll go and cut it. We'll eat it together.
- You're back.
- Mom.
What did you buy?
The cake shop had a discount, so I bought some for you.
We just ate. Isn't that a waste of money?
- Look.
- Let me see.
Song Hang.
- This is nice.
- Dad, come and have some.
Are you done taking photos?
Yeah, it's done.
Your camera is nice. It's made in Germany, right?
- Let's go dancing.
- Hurry.
This is nice.
Let's go.
Just loosen up a bit when we're there, okay?
There he is.
You came so early.
I came a bit earlier to save a seat for you.
You're here, Yi Fan.
He's calling you Yi Fan now?
Don't just stand there. Let's go dance.
Come on! Come on!
I'll go and buy something to drink.
Song Hang, what do you want?
- I'll go with you.
- All right.
You usually dress like a gangster.
Why are you dressed so properly today?
Didn't you say that running around playing soccer doesn't lead to much of a future?
So, I decided to apply to the fire department.
I was joking.
Why did you take it seriously?
I wasn't joking.
Yi Fan, if I get into the fire department, will you seriously consider me then?
The photos from last time are done.
I brought the ones with you in them.
You even carried them along with you?
That day, when I went to your workplace to drop off photos for the juniors,
I actually brought yours too.
But it looked like you had swapped shifts.
You weren't there.
So...
The pictures are so nice.
You university students take photos differently.
It's nothing.
Thank you.
♫  Love ya love  ♫
♫  What really is love  ♫
♫  Maybe after a long time, she finally understands  ♫
♫  Love ya love  ♫
♫  Maybe one day she forgets love  ♫
♫  Until she suddenly wakes up and learns to love  ♫
How are you doing at your workplace? Is your stomach still hurting?
Listen to me, drink some warm water when you're free.
Listen to the doctor's advice.
I may be your wife, but I'm also a doctor.
All right, I got it.
♫  Maybe she never left  ♫
♫  I think it is love  ♫
♫  That makes her brave  ♫
Hey... what do you think love was like for our parents back then?
Maybe we'll understand it someday.
♫  Maybe you are still waiting  ♫
♫  Wandering in a deep night  ♫
♫  Those past memories feel like a dream but cannot be let go  ♫
♫  That young girl  ♫
♫  Maybe she never left  ♫
♫  I think it is love  ♫
♫  That makes her brave  ♫
♫  The umbrella held tight in the rain  ♫
♫  Is the faith she believes in  ♫
♫  Remembering his silhouette still makes her heart race  ♫
♫  The blank space in her heart  ♫
♫  The expectations he once gave her  ♫
♫  Some things can never be defeated by time  ♫
♫  So what is love  ♫
♫  What is love  ♫
- Huan Er.
- Dad!
You're back. Did you get wet in the rain?
- Not really.
- Really? Your clothes are soaked.
- Go home and change.
- Uncle Chen.
- Hello. Go home and get changed.
- Bye, Uncle Chen.
Don't catch a cold.
All tidied up? The rain stopped.
- Didn't I tell you to change? Aren't you cold?
- It's fine, Dad. I didn't get too wet.
Huan Er, I want to ask you something.
It's so late already. What were you doing with that boy from the Jing family?
He brought me something to eat.
Dad, I've eaten so much.
I feel like my stomach is going to explode.
I can't take it, Dad. I need to go to the washroom.
Mom, are you done yet?
Mom, hurry up!
My stomach hurts.
I can't hold it, Mom.
Li Qiang, bring a bed sheet.
I just washed it. It's clean and dry now.
There's definitely one over there. No need to bring that.
Just listen to me.
The bed sheets over there are always worn out and not as good as the ones at home.
What if you have an allergic reaction?
Dad, where are you going?
I'm going on a work trip.
Nonsense.
Your dad has been transferred.
Look how bad your department is.
They just transferred you without prior notice. It was so sudden!
I don't even know what to pack now.
You got transferred, Dad?
To Tonglin.
Uncle Yang got promoted to deputy director,
so they transferred me over there.
If I do well, I might get promoted to deputy director too.
I heard the sports university in Tonglin is quite good.
I'm near the place. Let me check it out for you first.
Got it.
Li Qiang, I told you to bring more sweaters, but you didn't.
It's just a quick check-in. No need to bring so much!
You're always so stubborn with me. How stubborn you are.
- Take care of your mom for me.
- Don't worry.
I'm getting older now.
I won't be going out to the field as much anymore.
Once you start college, I'll transfer back,
and we can all be together more often.
- Oh, about your soccer—
- I know.
Keep doing it until the end.
I have to go now.
You've grown taller.
- Really?
- You look like an adult now.
I'm off.
Bye.
Where is Uncle Jing going?
My dad was temporarily assigned out of town.
When will he be back?
Don't know.
Where did you go?
I bought a set of practice questions.
Let's go.
I used to think I was the only one afraid to ask when Dad would come back.
But I realized it's not just fear of the answer being too far away.
I'm home!
Huan Er, you're back.
Dad.
Oh, right. Don't touch the kitchen door just yet.
I just fixed it and put some oil on it.
Why did you suddenly fix the door?
Whenever you push this door, it creaks.
If your mom comes home from a night shift for a nap,
the creak will definitely wake her up.
I guess I was also worried that Dad, who already had so much on his mind,
might hear it and feel even worse.
I'm leaving tomorrow, so I better get this done quickly.
Oh yeah, I bought you some oranges.
They're really sweet. Try one now.
I'll try it.
- It's so sweet.
- Right?
- Try one. Try one.
- I'll have one.
Sweet or not?
- Sweet.
- Sweeter than me?
Nothing's sweeter than my precious daughter.
Dad, you're sweating so much.
It's fine.
Let me wipe it off for you.
I'm getting VIP treatment. I have a little helper while working.
All done.
Look, this is too loose.
I told Mom she doesn't need to put your stuff away next time.
It's okay, whatever is convenient for you two.
Dad.
Let's take a photo together.
Why the sudden idea to take a picture?
Well, I'm an adult now.
I just want to keep a memory.
- Can we?
- Sure, we'll take one later.
Wait a moment. Your neck is covered in sweat.
I've realized I'll never ask that question aloud.
Parents choose their dream careers and live the lives they want. It's their freedom.
I can't choose my parents, but I can choose what kind of child to be.
I choose to let them feel at ease.
My memory of senior year is simple: silence.
A sudden, overwhelming silence.
No more noise during breaks.
No more whispering during self-study sessions.
Everyone is working hard toward their future.
No one wants to attend PE class.
I'll go by myself then.
Xi Chi!
I passed my physical test.
Congratulations.
Your future is promising now.
Honestly, if I hadn't been competing with you all this time,
I might not have been able to go through it.
Let's have another battle someday.
After all, there aren't many opponents I actually respect.
Look at you bragging.
All right.
I got it.
Don't give up.
I'm leaving.
I've been looking for you two for a long time. It turns out you're sitting here.
Come on.
Recently, I had someone bring me some supplements from New Zealand.
Kids are under a lot of academic stress lately. These are good for the brain.
Each of you, take one.
Sister Li, you do know that supplements shouldn't be taken care of carelessly.
Even medicine is three parts poison.
For kids, just some basic vitamins will do. Understand?
Am I right, Yi Fan?
What's wrong with you? Something on your mind?
It's nothing. I'm just hesitating over whether I should ask you for
a good tutoring school recommendation.
Of course. Any level, any price range, you name it.
Feel free to ask me. What happened? Are you thinking of getting Xi Chi a tutor?
It's just...
A while ago, I went to ask the sports university professors.
With Xi Chi's current level, if he doesn't pass the sports university assessment,
his only options would be schools for sports management or other related fields.
In that case, it would limit his career choices.
So, I've been thinking it might be better for him to aim for a comprehensive university.
- What do you all think?
- That's true.
- It makes sense.
- The entrance exam is a big deal in life.
As parents, we should plan for our kids.
- Exactly.
- I'll help you ask around.
Thanks so much.
I see you should take two more boxes.
Give them to your kid to boost their brain power.
He needs more.
Since your kid is not that intelligent, he should eat more of this.
- You...
- You just take one box first.
I'm saving this last one for my kid.
Anyway, I'll head off now.
I'll save it for Dr. Li, then.
"Yesterday's Clear Sky" by Yang Xizi
♫  The falling leaves outside the window gently glide past your sight  ♫
♫  Imagining how special your world must be  ♫
♫  How many times have I written your name in my heart?  ♫
♫  The wishes made upon the stars, how I hope they come true  ♫
♫  Looking at myself in the mirror, how many sides do I truly have?  ♫
♫  Quietly changing with time, breaking free from the cocoon  ♫
♫  A rainbow butterfly dancing under the sunlight  ♫
♫  When will it finally land on your left shoulder?  ♫
♫  Your promise still echoes in my ears  ♫
♫  Before saying goodbye  ♫
♫  The you from back then  ♫
♫  Still free and passionate  ♫
♫  If only this summer could last a little longer  ♫
♫  Will regrets ever be rewritten?  ♫
♫  The end of the story  ♫
♫  Has me standing by your side  ♫
♫  Watching your silhouette  ♫
♫  I am behind you  ♫
♫  Walk a little slower  ♫
♫  The us from back then  ♫
♫  Still didn't know how to tell things apart  ♫
♫  In my memories, sweat dampened your face  ♫
♫  Still shining just as brightly  ♫
♫  Looking forward to the day  ♫
♫  When we meet again  ♫
♫  At the right time  ♫