Hey, hey, ha, ha, ha
Ha, ha, hey, hey
Hey, ha, ha, ha
Ha, ha, hey, ha, ha
I am a good man
I grew up on the border
I thought he was on the horse
Follow me to the room
Pity
His mother died early
Can't see this day
Marquis
Mengyao's mother растine
the thing's
Do you feel Shekhovsky didn't punish her?
Yes
Do you think someone in His Majesty's residence
who killed Su solely
will be punished?
How?
and not her
What are you doing here?
Go back now
Take her back
Go away
I'm the daughter of the minister
Shen Wan is from a low-ranking family
She's a low-ranking woman
Why did she die for so many years?
She can still be the daughter of the Zhuang family
I'm your wife
Zhixing is the son of the Crown Prince
Her mother's rank can be the daughter of the Zhuang family
Who dares to doubt it?
She's the son of the Crown Prince
What's the position of the Crown Prince?
That bitch is the wife
What am I?
Even if Zhuang Zhixing is the son of the Crown Prince
she's the son of the Crown Prince
She's also the son of my Jiang Xiang
I'm the only master of the House of Marquis
You're not a master
Take her back
Madam, please go back
Madam
I know what you're thinking
The House of Marquis will depend on her
So she must be the rightful heir
But my family can't stand up anymore
Do you think the House of Marquis can stand up again?
You're deeply in love with Shen Wan
Don't forget how she died
Take her away
Get away
Let's talk
Please
Madam
You lost your importante ground
I'll toast you
Come on
Casey is arrested, yelling at you flower.
It's just a Mr. Xi's wish.
You're welcome.
Eat.
Madam.
I'll do it.
Here, eat another one.
Mother, what's wrong?
Is it sweet?
Open your mouth.
It's okay.
Is it sweet?
Here, eat another one.
Madam.
Madam, the Marquis said
that the eldest son has this disease and needs to rest.
He asked us to send the eldest son and the young madam
to the Yongzhou residence tomorrow morning.
Why?
The Marquis said that the second son will be in the court in the future.
There are many people in the house.
The eldest son's mother is not well.
I'm here.
Who dares to...
Madam, the Marquis said
that you are allowed to go with the Marquis
to take care of the eldest son.
Get out.
Get out!
Madam, pack up quickly.
We'll leave tomorrow morning.
Mother, why are you like this?
Mother.
Go to my room.
Bring me a high-quality, high-quality, Madam's coffin.
Mother.
Go and get it.
Don't push hard.
If you can't do something,
you won't be able to put up with how your husband is.
That's right.
Bear it.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
After all
I always expected money
There is both money and respect
But who will be the one to keep your dagger?
Mom
Father
Your father
He really abandoned us
It's
It's too late
At the very end, you even
lost the minimum использ of relationships
Good
Very good
Sir.
Today, everyone is celebrating for me.
This is the first time in my life
that so many people praise and praise me.
Is this the feeling of power?
Many people have always been pursuing
this thing.
Once you taste this taste,
you will never let go.
As you expected,
tonight,
my father called me to the study
and told me everything.
When I met him,
I suddenly found that
he had a lot of white hairs.
He had already returned the military power
and now he has lost his position.
He is no longer the
handsome and handsome Pingjing Duke.
I even felt that
he was a bit short
in front of me.
Zang Hai,
that day, on the fire field,
my father helped you get out.
Actually, I was very jealous.
However, he didn't even know
that you were the one who wanted to take over his position.
Your goal has been achieved.
My father has already lost.
His heart is full of pain.
He is already a late-dead old man.
Can't you let him go?
You care about your father.
You even want to kill him in the hands of your enemy.
Then you should understand me more.
I was indeed thinking too much.
You are like a rock.
You don't move at all.
If it was you,
I wouldn't have gone against you.
Finish
Nobody can three things good
shareholders must not five.
Hopefully, you have appeared tonight prepared.
Wait for it,
I am just going to chew on the air.
Does it hurt or not?
Zhao Jun.
His Highness used the
This is Jaguar paper idol.
panel.
It's about the Eastern Xia.
So my father
asked Chu Huai Ming to pay attention to the situation.
Three years later,
my father was ordered to escort the child back to the capital.
When he was about to arrive in the capital,
my father received a secret report from Chu Huai Ming.
The secret report said
Feng Shan Tai was leaving the capital.
Feng Shan Tai is here!
Save him!
Hurry! Save him!
But the Guaido under the camp
took something mysterious
and rushed back to the camp.
Hurry! Save him!
Hurry!
Over there!
Find more people!
Hurry!
Sir, something happened.
Go over there.
Help save him!
Hurry!
Go!
On the night we went back to the capital,
the day you took me away,
my father went out to meet two people.
They guessed
Kuai Duo wanted to take the poison after he found the ghost.
Later, they found out his secret route back to the capital.
They were sure
he would leave the capital with his wife and children.
They and my father
waited for your father
outside the Kuai family.
You already know one of them.
It's Cao Jingxian.
Who is the other one?
Dong Xia lost his treasure
and was taken away by an outsider.
They will definitely find a way to get it back.
You mean
the other one is from the Dong Xia Royal Court?
He is not only from the Dong Xia Royal Court.
He himself
represents the Dong Xia Royal Court.
It's the Queen of Dong Xia.
You are really smart.
You have thought of all the possibilities.
I think
they must have used each other
with the Queen of Dong Xia.
In order to take the ghost away from your father,
they conspired to destroy the Kuai family.
Even if she is the Queen of Dong Xia,
I will never let her go.
I know that I have to find you today.
No matter what you want to do to the Queen,
I can help you.
But I need to make it clear to you.
I have already made up my mind.
I will definitely find a way
to get the ghost away from you.
I have already fulfilled the agreement
and told you everything.
You can take revenge on the other two enemies,
but you can't hurt my father.
Thank you.
I will never let you go.
Today,
Zhuang Zhi ascended the throne of the Crown Prince.
Marquis Pingjing told him
all the secrets.
So the third enemy of your family
is the one who killed your father.
You are right.
I will never let you go.
Who is it?
Your mother.
Impossible.
It can't be my mother.
Marquis Pingjing must have framed her.
You have been in the capital for ten years.
Has your mother
been asking you to find the ghost?
Before the banquet at the Marquis Mansion,
you and Cao Jinxian met.
It was your mother who took the night, right?
My mother told me
Cao Jinxian was a sinister and cunning man.
We were just pretending to be friends.
Once we find the ghost,
I will try to send it back to the Eastern Xia.
I will never share it with her.
Of course she won't share it with him.
Marquis Pingjing,
Cao Jinxian,
the Queen of the Eastern Xia,
is just trying to get the ghost blood for the time being.
In fact, they are all evil.
It's not like that.
Ghost blood is your treasure.
The Queen of the Eastern Xia will definitely
find it at all costs.
If so,
my family has more than ten lives in her eyes.
What does it count?
You're talking nonsense.
When your family was killed,
I was just sent here.
My mother was in the Eastern Xia.
She didn't come to Dayong.
How could she show up in your house?
How do you know she didn't come secretly?
My mother is the Queen of the Eastern Xia.
Do you think it's easy to come to Dayong?
Zang Hai,
you can't just listen to one side of the story.
When the house is full of smoke and dust,
I asked the frost and the cold.
You can't even listen to what I'm saying.
You hate me now,
right?
Qingzhou is surrounded by mountains.
The sky is dark and the moon is clear.
Let's write another night.
I want to follow the light of the night
and wait for the night to come.
The past days are brighter than the past.
How many dreams are on my mind
until dawn?
Call Zhuang Zhixing to the hall.
You are here!
This way,하겠습니다.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
dismissed the first- photographs of
Gao Zhenyang to be the commanding officer of K banquets
andt меся least of the minister of radius.
Thank you, your Majesty.
We've failed.
You don't like the drink, and you sent it here instead?
Tell me about this.
Ask the pueda-pay the bill.
Father!
If you want the fairest drink,
I can give you this tears- собственно.
But if we can't get it ourselves,
I will ask the conch release final intention.
I won't meet you.
If Youyang doesn't go to18thcompress for business check,
public holy
Pete's father will be harmed.
I just kalo ed once for Interest.
After meeting Heungu Aphor я,
I finally thought to drive him out of the golden field.
years later creative yin questão
baipeng
but my state affairs.
I want to see
what he has to report
on this good day
and what he has to explain.
Summon
Zhang Jiangshi to the court.
Since my father directs me to come here,
I have to refer to him
since it is saying one day
after I become the emperor.
I want to know
Feng Xi's
Your Majesty.
Lady Zhuang.
Do you know what this Deng Wengu is?
I know.
Today is the day of the crown prince's
golden title ceremony.
I specially changed the
pre-ordained high-quality
Lady Gaoming's etiquette
to remember Deng Wengu.
I have something
to report to you in person.
Tell me.
I want to ask you
if the great warriors of Dayong
should be
fair and dignified
and have high martial arts.
Of course.
But if these warriors
are not wise
and have bad reputation,
and even involve
the reputation of being a prostitute,
what should we do?
I am here today
to report to you.
This man is a traitor
and deceives the emperor.
He is the father
of the five great warriors, Zhuang Zhixing.
Marquis Pingjing, Zhuang Luyin.
Zhuang Luyin
became the five great warriors
to protect his son, Zhuang Zhixing.
He bribed all the examiners.
Your Majesty is wise.
There is no such thing.
But recently,
my eldest son
has been in a bad situation
and has no medicine.
He is too worried
and has a strange disease.
That's why he said such things.
I will take him back.
Go.
Let him finish.
Zhang Jiangshi,
do you know that
in front of the officials,
you slandered the high-ranking general
who has made great achievements
for our Yong Dynasty.
What a big crime!
Since I dare to
take the throne today,
and I dare to testify for my husband
in front of His Majesty,
it is not an empty talk.
I have the evidence
of Zhuang Luyin in my hand.
Your Majesty.
What's wrong?
The examination of the five main examinations
of the military and military departments
was held by the deputy minister of the Ministry of War,
Feng Zhang,
and the same examination.
The former deputy minister of the Ministry of War,
Wang Renliang,
and the former assistant minister of the Ministry of Government,
all three of them
were bribed by Zhuang Luyin.
This account book
is the evidence of his bribery.
In order to help Zhuang Zhixing
to take the crown,
Zhuang Luyin spent a lot of money.
He is not willing to
spend a lot of money
to bribe the examiners.
I'm afraid that
the money is not enough
to buy flowers in their house.
Your Majesty, please investigate it.
Did you three hear it?
Feng Zhang,
I ask you,
if you have such a thing,
I would never dare to do such a thing.
What about you two?
To be honest,
I won't spare you.
I was indeed
instructed by Zhuang Luyin.
I was confused for a moment
and made a mistake
in the five subjects.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Zhuang Luyin,
do you have anything to say?
Your Majesty, please be honest.
I don't know
what they said.
I don't want to do
anything that would
manipulate the imperial examination.
I'm dedicated to the country,
to help Dayong guard the border,
and to help Your Majesty
break the East Xia.
I'm completely
devoted to Your Majesty.
I can do anything.
I'm asking
what you've done now,
not what you did in the past.
I, He Ziqing, the deputy minister of the Ministry of Rites,
have a report.
Go ahead.
Your Majesty,
Zhuang Luyin used his own money
to get into the Grand Office
and protect the eldest son,
Zhuang Zhifu, from the Central Security Department.
In the past years,
he has been involved in
countless money transactions.
Is that true?
Zhuang Luyin is not only guilty of this,
he is also in the imperial mausoleum
and is forced to
bury the dead under his command.
People in the imperial court
are all angry but dare not speak.
I beg Your Majesty
to investigate and ask for justice,
and to return justice to the people.
Zhuang Luyin,
do you
admit these things or not?
Your Majesty,
I didn't kill the innocent.
I did this
to avenge the dead.
Where is the Department of Law?
I'm here.
I order you to investigate this matter thoroughly.
I obey your order.
From today on,
Zhuang Luyin will be taken into the Imperial Court.
After the trial of the three departments,
the whole Zhuang family
will be sentenced to death.
Yes.
I'm here.
To be honest
I'm still worried about Yuzheng
She has the meeting in two days
She reported her pearl
We have to
What's the matter?
The Three Judicial Offices have found out
that you are very clever
and you are in the army
and you control the border
What's the emperor's attitude?
No one can guess the emperor's mind
But no official in the court
pleaded for you
Cao Jinxian also told the emperor many times
to kill you
This bastard
wants to kill me
in his dream
I'm afraid the emperor
won't spare you this time
This is a death sentence for others
For me, it's nothing
My family has led troops to fight for generations
and guarded the country for more than a hundred years
The emperor won't do anything to me
As for this bastard
Zang Hai
You go to find Xie Houguang of the Ministry of War
and Huang Shen of the Ministry of Rites
They know what to do
I want to see
who can laugh till the end
Go
My lord
Don't you think
you can walk out alive?
You talk about Cao Jinxian
I think
I want you dead.
What do you want to say?
Ten years ago,
you killed the spy of the New Heaven Sword,
Kuai Tuo and his family.
And you set a fire.
Wei Zhuang Cheng killed the bandits
and avoided the court's investigation.
You thought you could kill them all.
But
their son survived.
Kuai Tuo's son?
Kuai Tuo?
You are Kuai Tuo's son?
I've killed too many bandits in my life.
Your father
is just one of thousands.
You want to get the ghost blood.
There are many ways.
Why do you have to kill my family?
Why do you want so many innocent people
to die because of you?
People will die.
It doesn't matter
who will die.
Is it important?
I see.
There is such a kind of people in the world.
For a little selfish desire,
people's lives are like a grass.
But don't forget
the good and evil
are all retribution.
Ridiculous.
I've been fighting in the battlefield for so many years.
I've been blooded by so many people.
I never believe in retribution.
Here I am at your side.
This is your final wish.
If you pretend to surrender to me and
stoop to mygrad.
You don't have to sacrifice my meaning to you.
You even planned to harm me.
You are really smart.
But Zang Hai,
I will win.
You think you have won?
You think I will die here?
I will win this time.
I won't die.
Till then,
I will kill you first.
My lord,
you should think about it.
You are a man of your own.
Although you are the commander of the Ninth Division,
your confidant
is still in charge of the Muji Camp.
His majesty is a man of your own.
He won't kill
a general from the whole of Dayong
who is a man of your own.
But if there is a hand
who kills you for him,
even if the court is unstable
and the army is unstable,
he will only kill this man.
If he kills you,
he can give an explanation to everyone.
Tell me,
what will his majesty do?
So all the misunderstandings between Cao Jingxian and me
started because of you.
Then you should know
that he is your enemy, right?
As long as I tell Cao Jingxian
your real identity,
he will kill you.
If you can pass this level,
will I tell you my identity
right now?
After the fierce battle at the Marquis's mansion,
you and Cao Jingxian
have completely broken off the alliance
because of the ghost.
You are his confidant
when you are alive.
The person he wants to kill the most
is you.
But who am I?
He will only know it
when you are alive.
He knows everything
but he can't do anything.
Pretending to be a wolf.
The feeling of being lost
is not suitable.
If you have the ability,
you should fight with me.
You are plotting against the people behind my back.
What are you?
I am no longer a human.
I have been living in hell
since I was alive ten years ago.
For me,
the process is not important.
I only look at the result.
Besides,
I already know
who are the three people who killed my family.
This is the only way
for me to live.
And you,
you only have the way to hell.
I know it all.
Do you think
I should do my best
to protect the family?
Do you think I really
want to protect the family
and my family?
Do you think
you can keep
the cause of his mother's death?
His eldest son has passed away.
Your youngest son
is obedient to me now.
is密ically involved for the cultivation
and ripped off every part of me
all without any preparation or freedoing.
i I'll make sure
no one else in the Imperial Court
will suspect.
All of you
will be together.
Nobody's done anything
except mother's death but you.
You all
are running against your father
before you know it.
placed County Marshal
Good son.
Zhuang Zhixing,
you are really my good son.
Hurry and hide! Hurry and hide!
If you see
that I am hiding,
you will be in trouble.
Look at your son now.
Should you laugh
or cry?
Look at my eyes.
The shadow is my life-saving armor.
The eyes are my ultimate weapon.
The light is always on.
The knife is not black.
It's just because my heart is boiling.
The rain is my
fortune and my disappointment.
If I am too willful,
someone will eventually make a move.
The life is mine.
The rain is mine.
When the sun rises,
I sing with the army.
In my dream,
I am the leader.
The world is me.
You are also me.