We are the people of the world.
Ear차助理
再罢了
反手
The세요客
What is he doing?
The two of them are inside.
The machine that opened the tunnel is over there.
Please.
Find another way.
The machine that opened the tunnel is over there.
Come on, eat.
Where is Zhang Hai?
He can't come.
He went to my mother?
He went to kill my mother, right?
Don't ask me so much.
It's good.
Let me and my mother,
he and his children,
die today.
What do you mean?
You are a doctor.
Can't you see that I'm pregnant?
No.
No way.
How could Xiao'ai...
If you don't believe me,
just sell it.
It's not enough to sell it.
It's not too small.
You are lying to me.
What's wrong with you?
How could I be so strong?
You put the money in the soup, right?
It's a pity that I've been poured out of the soup.
I'm not feeling well.
Tell me where Zhang Hai is.
You are a liar.
I'm telling you,
the people in our family
can only talk if you want to.
Even if you kill me,
I won't say it.
Be careful.
What should we do?
They are coming.
They can't get in.
Go ahead.
Why is there no reaction?
Be careful, Su Yan.
Protect His Majesty.
Take him back.
Go.
An Tu.
Where are you going?
Let him go.
Only three of us
can beat you.
Besides,
how would he know where Xiao Hai will take your mother?
Where is he?
He is taking your mother to Yulan Capital.
How many people did he take?
He is the only one to see your mother.
In case
Gao Ming and Shilei
will take him secretly.
He is so insolent.
The Eastern Xia women
can't defeat the three of them.
Don't underestimate them.
Listen.
You all think that
Zang Hai is in the dark.
My mother is here.
But my mother
knew her identity long ago.
She was prepared to come.
Her plan is useless.
No way.
I don't believe you.
Tell me where she is.
I have to stop her.
But the revenge is her.
We can't stop her.
Including you.
I'm afraid
there will be
a reason for it.
Sister.
Please tell me.
But even if you go,
you will be helpless.
Your Majesty.
We have already come out.
We will be gone soon.
He just doesn't want us to go in.
Your Majesty.
The first one is on the path.
It's six years old.
And we have six people.
The second one is a traitor.
There are five people in the camp.
You stay and wait for me.
The others will follow me.
Your Majesty.
Let's go.
There are only four now.
The whole tunnel should be closed.
If the people who come in
exceed the number of people in the camp,
the front door will never open.
Zang Hai is going to take us away.
It seems he wants to see me alone.
You all go back.
Your Majesty.
The smoke just now is not poisonous.
I don't think he wants to harm anyone.
Your Majesty.
You don't have to say anything.
I will go in alone.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
The door here has been closed.
It will never open.
It seems my daughter is not here.
She is in a safe place.
Whose gift is this?
The daughter of the emperor of the former dynasty.
Yiong Ning's gift.
The env Tensor 검us loves it
but Yiong Ning's return is dead in the mausoleum.
So she doesn't finish the gift.
Then she lose her life.
I know Yiong Ning's story.
SheOLS
1 girl with Ke Han.
Her life is full of happiness.
But much has failed.
The Chihu Zhu caused a serious change.
He killed her.
Princess Yongning and her children
couldn't live.
They were tied to the wood.
They burned to death.
At that time,
the Chihu Zhu's army
couldn't be destroyed.
Five years later,
the Chihu Zhu
was killed by 300,000 soldiers.
They were killed by the whole Mobei.
The Chihu Zhu
was killed by the whole Mobei.
All the words
were written by the Emperor of the Chihu Zhu.
He told himself
not to forget
the grudge between the three of us.
You brought me here
not just to tell the story of Princess Yongning.
That night,
when the whole family was killed,
you saw the fierce fire
in my heart.
You also had a daughter.
If she was the one who died,
what would you do?
Of course, I would revenge for her.
But don't forget,
if you killed me,
you and my daughter would be no longer possible.
You used the poison to kill yourself.
Then you made the wrong calculation.
I'm not the kind of person you think I am.
Really?
Then why did you
try to do the same thing again?
You must have forgotten
the grudge between you and me.
As long as you are alive,
the grudge will be gone.
So you kept on doing the same thing.
You let the grudge continue to be the one who killed yourself.
You wanted to stop your life
from being destroyed.
But time won't stop.
It will force you to keep moving forward.
You will meet someone
who makes you feel
that except for hatred,
there are some other things in life.
But you are more painful.
Because you feel that
the grudge is slowly falling.
So you forced yourself
to give up on this.
You chose to keep on doing the revenge.
Are you going to use this
to kill me?
Look at your attitude.
What are those?
The grudge they have
I just need to use my power
to pull it out.
The grudge inside
will be removed in person.
It is not easy to use this sword
to kill you.
But if you use it
to light up the whole secret room,
it will be too easy.
I didn't expect that you would have such a hand.
You are indeed a child of the Kuaido.
You killed me.
You can't live on your own.
Are you willing to die like this?
I am just talking about it.
It just proves that you are afraid of death.
The Eastern Xia and the Northern King
are not like that.
Zang Hai.
You have a heart.
But your power is still out of the cage.
Zai Long.
Do you know what your decision
will bring to my daughter?
She will become the next one.
She will be tortured by the grudge.
Even if you know that,
do you still want to do that?
I did kill you.
I did forgive An Tu.
But if I didn't kill you,
I would have been sorry to my dead family.
I must avenge this grudge.
I will not forgive you.
Mother.
An Tu.
Go.
I will avenge you.
Mother.
An Tu.
Don't come over.
Zang Hai.
I will die for my mother.
From now on,
we will be a family.
Okay?
Mother.
Promise me.
Don't make things difficult for her.
Stop.
Mother.
You.
Take her away.
No.
You are a grudge against blood.
If you give up for me,
you will regret it.
We will both suffer.
This grudge
must be kept in secret.
Silly girl.
You have been in the prison for ten years.
You are so old-fashioned.
You haven't been completely killed by hatred.
But you look like
a real enemy.
You and Zhuang Lu Yin and Cao Jing Xian
are the same family.
Not you.
Zhuang Lu Yin and Cao Jing Xian?
I ask you.
Why do you think I am the same?
I don't know your relationship with Zhuang Lu Yin.
But you and Cao Jing Xian
are a long-time friends.
What is he?
If I really want to kill him,
do I still need help?
It's not strange that you think like that.
Listen to me first.
Are you going to believe me?
Zhi Nuo.
You are so like him.
Go.
Back then, the East Xia War was defeated.
The King heard a single whistle.
My throne was in danger.
That day, I was killed by the secret city.
I fell into the cliff.
I thought I was dead.
I woke up and was in a tent.
A big dragon saved me.
He is your father.
Hurry up.
You are awake.
Who are you?
Where are you?
This is the Great Wall.
It's a huge wall.
This is the palace camp in Dan Sui Mountain.
I am the Great Wall.
The sky is clear and the sword is sharp.
I am here to repair the mountain stage.
Fortunately, the sword tribe didn't hurt you.
But at least it needs to rest for half a month.
When you are well, I will send you away.
You can't believe me?
Of course I can't.
Why are you so stubborn?
You are going out.
It's cold now.
You can't walk for a long time.
You will freeze to death.
You should rest here.
There are no women in the camp.
And no gender discrimination.
Sorry.
Please excuse me.
Here.
You need water.
You don't need to boil it.
Do you have a wife?
I have a wife and a daughter.
I can take them to the east.
I won't stay here.
They are waiting for me to go home.
You dare not look at the east.
What's good about the east?
The east is good.
But my home is in the east.
Where have we end up in today's place?
We have 30itter lever horses.
That means
they have already загed in.
Don't worry too much.
Just go wherever you want.
People aren't like this anymore.
It's better to go apartmentrenaline
and detect some animals
from other parts of the country.
But you200 obsessiony акку sat LP.
Who shoud love share any VS for?
The structure on both sides of the east coast is called Bo Ruo.
You only know how to attack the generals.
Let them defend more.
Yes.
This is the Feng Shan Tai you built for the Emperor of the Great Yong.
The camp is not yellow, the mountain is not clear.
There are many hidden areas in the south.
It's hard to cross the four seas.
You great Yong people always want to
to make the world a better place.
They are all crazy.
They say everything is for the sake of the world.
But what can we bring
on the day we leave this world?
Of course, it's not up to me.
But people should think about what they should leave behind.
The Qing Qiu dynasty is the Emperor.
It's also for the sake of the Great Yong.
You are thinking too much.
Why don't you be a commoner
and live for yourself?
People in the world
should live happily ever after.
Life is what I want.
People can't get money.
They should live for themselves.
What is this?
It's a toy for my son.
It seems that
you really miss your family.
What is their name?
My son is called Zhinnu.
My daughter is called Yunnu.
What do you mean by that?
You great Yong people
just want your children to be a slave?
I just hope that they grow up slowly.
I have two daughters.
One is called Yin Zhu.
The other is called An Tu.
Then,
what about them?
They are in a safe place.
Life goes by so fast.
I have been in the palace for half a month.
I have gradually adapted to the world.
But there is always a good day.
They say that the people in the east are wonderful.
How is it?
How do you feel when you just ran away?
It's good.
Your tent is very far from here.
Why are you here today?
I said that
when you are well,
I will take you back.
It's time to go home.
How do you know where my home is?
Your family has been looking for you.
Your Majesty!
The palace is still in chaos.
It's not peaceful yet.
Your Highness,
your children need you.
You always know.
There are some things
that we should face.
Your Highness,
let's go.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Thank you.
Later,
I calmed down.
I returned to the world again.
But I know
that what I have in my heart
has changed.
Your Majesty,
the wind fan that Danyong Palace and the Green Sky Sword
have built together
is now in vain.
Anything else?
Hurry up and follow Wang Chang.
The day is getting better.
It's midnight.
Your Majesty.
What's wrong?
The earthquake in Dansui Mountain
and the wind fan is gone.
The palace in Danyong Palace
is in grave danger.
Many people are buried down there.
Hurry up.
I don't know.
I have sent people to investigate.
Your Majesty,
someone saw the wind fan
that Danyong Palace and the Green Sky Sword.
He is in danger.
Your Majesty,
someone saw the wind fan
that Danyong Palace and the Green Sky Sword.
He is back to the camp.
But it's been a long time.
He is going to the southwest.
Your Majesty,
He Duo is going to the west.
You stay here.
Don't follow him.
Your Majesty.
Hurry up.
Keduo,
where are you going?
Your Highness,
Dansui Mountain is in grave danger.
The wind fan is gone.
I am going back to report it.
This is not the grave danger.
What happened?
What did you do?
You found the ghost blood.
So he hid it
under the mountain range of Dansui Mountain.
You have found it long ago.
You came for him.
Your Highness,
please stop asking.
You must give me the thing.
Keduo,
do you know what the ghost blood is?
Do you know why?
I would never be defeated by you.
I don't need it.
My mother
used the ghost blood
in your battle.
Eventually,
she caused a disaster
in the human world.
She died because of it.
She left a sign
to let the back of the East Xia
to find it.
I don't even know
where the ghost blood is.
Until today,
Keduo,
the ghost blood is not the cure.
If you keep it,
it will cause you
a endless disaster.
Thank you for telling me.
I must take it back.
Keduo,
please.
Give it to me.
I won't use it
to use it.
Don't leave either.
Let's be in the East Xia together.
Just like when I was recuperating.
Okay?
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
That's good.
You're not leaving, are you?
Please hug me.
Okay?
I'm afraid we'll never see each other again.
Don't worry.
This is just a drug.
It will be back soon.
I've been writing this book
for many years.
It's written in it
that it's useful to look at the magic
and to use it to purify the sword.
I'll leave it to you now.
Maybe it'll be useful
for the East Xia in the future.
I'll leave it to you.
I'm sorry.
Guando,
Actually,
the story has been decided
since the beginning.
Your father died
in my life,
but he taught me a lesson.
We all have our own destiny.
I've never thought about fighting him.
Because I know
the person he wants to see
is not me.
But I never thought
that day
would be the last time we met.
Leave.
A month later,
I received the last news
of the visit
of the Kuaiduo.
The Kuaiduo family was destroyed.
No one was alive.
He and the most important person
in his heart died together.
You all leave too.
And I can't live
the person in his heart
for the rest of my life.
I'm sorry.
But I'll remember him for the rest of my life.
You're kidding me.
Some people
are so miserable.
are so cruel.
But I only allow myself
to cry for him once.
No matter what happens,
I can only
be
the queen of the East.
The operation he left
helped the East
and made the people
pay for it.
And the coffin
of the Kuaiduo
was made
by the memory
of the book
that was
written by him.
You're his child.
I'll give it back to you now.
I'll give it back to you.
So you're
the old man of my father.
I was wrong about you.
I didn't expect
that
someone from the Kuaiduo family
would still live.
My daughter
has so many
children from the Kuaiduo family.
This time I came to Da Yong
to find the map.
There's still a big thing to do.
Now I'm going to see
the people
who can help me.
The map is the life of my life.
The map is the road
that I've always hated.
The light of the old man
is not dark
even the bed of the old man.
Only because
I'm so sad.
I'm the rebel.
I'm the rich.
I'm the heartbreak.
I will always
be with you.
I'm the born.
I'm the man.
I'm the rain.
I'm the one who will always be with you.
I'm the king.
I'm the man.
I'm the born.
You are me.