Li Xia.
I got a big melon today.
Qingge is so handsome.
Li Xia,
your eyelids are open,
I took it off for you.
What are you looking at?
Get lost!
Li Xia
My eyelids are open. I'll remove them for you, okay?
Li Xia,
let's go too.
Let's go,
let's go,
You want to run away?
Xu Yinuo,
do you know the way or not?
From day to night,
if you don't know the way, don't take it with you.
Why are you yelling at me?
Besides,
I'm not from here,
You know the way?
Show me the way.
Point
You're being unreasonable.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's easy for me to find them.
May I ask,
who is your Excellency?
I'm the sixty-eighth generation leader
of the Beggar Sect,
Hong Bagong is also.
Sorry,
it's Master Hong.
Excuse Me
What can I do for you?
Do you want to
treat us to a meal?
Nonsense!
Pay for my doggy stick.
Didn't you say it in the novel?
The dog stick is indestructible.
Are you blackmailing me?
Silly girl,
the glory of my beggar for a hundred years,
Destroyed.
Losing money?
Is it,
Let me do it.
It seems that you really did it.
So annoying.
How much?
One price,
fifty taels of silver,
Isn't this one or two?
That's right.
It's a one-off price.
How about this?
How about one or two lines?
One or two will do.
There's not much bargaining
for silver
It's a loss.
What are you doing?
Give us the money Wu Yaoyang gave us.
It's gone.
Where's the money?
I took it to fortune-telling.
Fortune telling,
What?
I can't even get a silver or two.
Guards!
Arrest him!
Run!
Stop running!
Don't run!
Stop right there!
Go after him!
You go this way.
Go over there.
Okay,
There's a hole next to it.
What are you doing?
If you want to get in,
you can get in.
Xu Yinuo, you,
Zhou Luochen,
Where are you?
Who?
Who touched my butt?
You even broke my bracelet.
Smelly rascal.
You guys,
I'm sorry,
He looks pretty watery.
just now
You touched my butt.
Annoying.
Why don't you admit it?
I'm the proprietress of this inn,
and you broke my bracelet.
It cost hundreds of taels of silver.
You're losing money
again. Do you want money?
It's killing me,
I don't have money.
I don't have money to pay for it.
I'll pay off my debts with my work.
Let's talk about it after losing my bracelet.
I don't agree.
Who knows if your bracelet
is worth hundreds of taels?
The landlady
is working here,
Do you want food and shelter?
Bag,
Deal.
No way.
I don't agree.
If you don't tell the truth, I'll just … He'll say
yes,
Deal.
I'll arrange for you to stay in a room later.
Then have dinner.
Okay.
Madam.
Why?
Pretty boy,
wait a minute.
Come to my room first.
No problem.
Why?
We
… Enough, enough.
Wake up.
It's midnight.
Let's get to work.
Ghost.
Madam,
it's not dawn yet.
Drink
If it's not enough,
keep drinking.
It tastes awful.