Follow them
and monitor their every move.
Yes.
If they can't take out the sword,
I'll ask them to bury my beloved chicken with them.
Yes, sir.
Wait a minute.
Sir,
Then.
The travelling expenses.
Hold on.
Just now, in order to make up for the Sword Saint couple,
there was no money left in the account.
This one hundred coins is my private money,
and the rest,
Figure it out on your own.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Xiaowu,
I hope you didn't choose the wrong master.
Hurry up.
Excuse me,
handsome guy.
Call me?
I can tell from the sound of your footsteps
that
you are very energetic,
His eyes are bright,
like stars in the sky,
He must not be an ordinary person.
A star?
No,
Not a star,
but a superstar.
Yes.
That's right,
Young Master Lai,
Sit down. Let me
tell you the divination.
Master,
how is it?
Well,
Young Master,
It's really not an ordinary child.
The future is bright.
It's just...
It's just what?
This one.
But,
Love,
It's a little hard to figure out,
love,
May I ask what love is?
It's love.
Master,
do you dare to ask me when my love will come into being?
Young Master's love has already appeared.
As long as you close your eyes,
you can see her face.
Young Master,
you can close your eyes and try.
Silly girl,
you believe that.
Someone jumped off the building.
Hurry up
Go,
go, go.
What are you waiting for?
Let's go and watch the fun.
Really?
Is it her?
Excuse me.
They've been standing there all day.
As long as you close your eyes,
you can see her face.
Young Master,
you can close your eyes and try.
Let's go.
What are you waiting for?
Let's go and watch the fun.
Here we go.
What color do I like?
Pink,
what weather do I like,
From sunny to cloudy to light rain,
Then.
How many hairs do I have?
Before going up to the city wall,
you had 112, 365?
But you just dropped one.
There are only 112, 364 of them now.
Amazing.
This man is so sincere.
Okay.
Then.
Who is my idol?
Tang Mufeng of Imperial Sword Villa,
Wrong
General Shen Ce, Leng Wuyou,
you said Tang Mu Feng last week,
Last week was last week.
I had a lot of idols. Do you know?
Li Xia,
I'm sorry,
Don't stand there.
It's dangerous.
I'm sorry.
I can only say sorry.
Don't you know what else to say?
I've told Senior Sister long ago,
don't look for men from Everlasting Sect.
She wouldn't listen.
Exactly
How nice would it be to find someone from Imperial Sword Villa?
Forget it.
According to Senior Sister's plan,
She's about to jump.
Let's get ready.
Come on,
Come and eat melons.
Su Qi,
why are you here?
Me,
Why can't I be here?
Aren't you from the Five Poison Sect?
Why are you in the Beggars'Sect, a
versatile person like me,
To promote cultural exchange among all sects, of course.
To build a bridge of peace,
I think,
You must be poor.
I'm not poor.
This one hundred coins
is my private money,
As for the rest,
you can figure it out yourself.
Okay, sir,
this is mine,
Exactly
Careful consumption.
Yes,
One minute has passed.
Why don't you say anything?
Do you want to give me a cold shoulder?
Li Xia, that's not what I meant.
I don't care.
You must give me an explanation today.
Otherwise,
Me,
I'll jump from here.
Li Xia,
No
I dropped it.
Something big is going to happen.
Let me do it.
Woman.
What a beauty to save heroes.
Saving people is a beautiful thing.
Are you okay?
Gu Qingge
is also here.
Who are you?
Why did you touch
a scumbag like me?
-I'll save her. -Save
her.