(Pearl Hotel)
=Pearl Hotel=
=Episode 19=
- Let's go.
- Duan?
Duan.
What happened to Duan?
It's enough!
Go to hell.
Auntie Mei, hurry up!
Find the chute!
Hurry up! Come in!
Hold the door!
Come on!
Let's go!
Hurry!
Hurry up!
Hurry up! Come on!
Hurry!
Hold this!
You should be responsible.
You kissed me. I want another apartment.
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
What?
Are you okay?
Where are we? It stinks!
This is the garbage room!
How can it smell good?
Where are we?
The basement.
The basement?
I've never been here before.
We didn't know this place until now.
Go away.
Where's Xiaodao?
Xiaodao...
Xiaodao?
Xiaodao is lying on the floor.
He can't move.
What do you mean?
What does he mean?
It stinks. Let's get out first.
Something's wrong.
It smells like
corpse.
Corpse!
That's what spoiled pork smells like.
I knew it.
I saw someone chopping things in Room 404.
So, it was pork, wasn't it?
Oh, no.
At that time, Jian was on the 2nd floor,
and Xiaodao and Duan
were on the 3rd floor.
Who was chopping pork?
I got it. It was Hu.
She knew we'd go down,
so she wanted to make us sick.
- Hu?
Yes.
The girl who jumped?
Didn't she die?
No.
She didn't die.
It was she who kidnapped me and Bao!
I don't remember.
She must've drugged Bao.
He forgot everything.
Forgot it?
Mom!
Let's get out. Don't stay here.
Why are you still collecting trash?
Wait!
I remember now.
Before I passed out,
in Room 404,
I...
I saw a woman in white,
and she...
tucked her head. I saw it!
Yes, yes.
That ghost forced us to come here.
Hu is that ghost!
That's right.
A real ghost wouldn't smash the door.
So, it's also a human.
On the Ghost Festival,
four groups of people
posed as ghosts in Pearl Hotel.
So ridiculous.
It means Xiaodao was right.
There are no ghosts in this world.
When I get out,
I won't go easy on Hu!
Stop saying that!
Shouldn't we get out first?
She wants to kill us.
Listen,
she believes
we killed her grandma.
What? I don't even know her!
How can she blame me?
You cut off the power,
and she fell from the roof!
How's that possible?
- She'll kill you first, understand?
- Stop!
You'll be the first to die, understand?
Stop! Stop!
Can't you smell it now?
Let's get out first!
Let's go.
The door is locked.
Open the door!
- She really wants to kill us all.
- What?
She'll kill us all.
What's the smell?
It's gas.
Gas...
Where's Xiaodao?
Where is Xiaodao?
How could he leave
at this point?
We pushed him down.
We didn't mean to do that.
Xiaodao was right.
There are no ghosts.
Humans are much worse than ghosts.
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)