(Pearl Hotel)
=Pearl Hotel=
=Episode 21=
Brother Xiaodao.
Bro,
why are you here?
They said you died.
Nezha can be revived.
However, some people
don't deserve to live.
I wish I could leave you here to die.
However, when I went down,
I saw the gas valve was turned on.
You must've touched it
when you went down.
I said I didn't do it!
Do you believe me now?
Move.
Move!
Wait! Wait!
How dense is the gas in there?
It's bad. Can't you smell it?
In that case,
the iron gate is well-sealed.
So?
So...
If the door opens, the air will go in...
And?
You need to be prepared.
When you open the door, it will explode.
We're running out of time!
Go!
Hurry!
- Let's go.
- Go!
Bro!
You...
Go to the hospital.
I'll save her.
Don't leave her behind this time.
Get her out.
Hurry!
Xiaodao!
Brother Xiaodao!
He's alive!
- Xiaodao is alive!
- He's alive!
(Pearl Road)
(Real-life Escape Room)
- Hello.
Show me your Health Code.
You can read the flyer.
Next.
Here, take a look.
Hello, hello.
Can you please show me your Health Code?
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Show me your ticket.
No problem.
- The number is 151517.
- How many?
- Two.
- Two tickets.
- Okay.
- Read this.
You should go this way.
Okay. Have a good time.
Welcome.
- Come on.
- Excuse me, what is...?
How many tickets?
Can I jump the queue? Take this.
Can I jump the queue?
Hey! No cutting, man.
What are you doing?
Stop, don't cut in.
Do you have a VVVVIP membership?
What VIP?
A lot of money.
No IP. You can get an Annual Pass.
3888, do you want it?
38 million yuan?
3888 yuan.
Oh, no!
I spend tens of millions of yuan
every day.
It's too cheap.
Are you crazy?
I'm not crazy.
I have to spend all my money.
I have to spend it all
to become a billionaire.
And this is...
Xiaodao, do you hear me?
Copy that.
Xiaodao,
there's a psychopath.
Repeat, there's a psychopath.
I'm not a psycho.
We've found the target.
Take him away right now.
Do you accept oil?
Over.
- Over.
- Do you accept oil? I have oil.
- Go!
I'll give you a can of oil.
Please let me spend money!
Help!
What IP? Psycho.
I want your lollipop!
(Pearl Hotel)
(Da by Vinida)
(Bao by Lu Yuhao)
(Landi by Yang Ziyu)
(Frank by Shen Yuan)
(Auntie Mei by Peng Jianghua)
(Tang Yuanbao by Wang Xiaolong)
(Tiezui by Pan Yucheng)
(Jian by Wu Guobao)
(Hu by Zhuang Dingxin)
(Dabao by Mai Jiaxin)
(Xiaodao by Ban Majia)
(Duan by Song Muzi)
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)