It's so cold!
What's so funny?
My dress is new, and so are my shoes.
It took an hour to style my hair this way.
I'm really unlucky.
What kind of first date is this?
Date?
Two people who like each other
are hanging out. That's a date.
I don't have any interest in you.
Then why are you hanging out with me
on your precious weekend?
That's because…
you won't bother me for a while
if I let you hang out with me.
You've hurt my feelings.
Let's go.
The owner
of the chicken restaurant told me
that you always stare at me
whenever I pass by.
Seon-u, a fifth-grader,
asked me while buying a Popsicle
whether you and I were dating.
Are you sure
you aren't the only one
who doesn't know that you like me?
Gosh, this is so suffocating.
Play rock-paper-scissors, and the loser
stands in the rain for 30 seconds.
No.
I don't play such useless games.
Ready-or-not, rock-paper-scissors.
You lost!
Come on, go stand in the rain.
Hee-seong.
What's wrong?
Do you realize how weird you are?
Why do you like me? Why?
I don't understand.
How could you like me?
Never mind.
There's no point in talking to you.
I'm leaving.
Why did you have to insist
on getting married and cause all this?
How many times did I tell you
to go live abroad?
You want to get married?
You want to live a normal life?
If you want to die, do it alone.
If the world finds out about us…
Just thinking about it gives me chills.
If that ever happens,
I'll kill myself in front of you.
Calm down.
Nothing has happened.
Drink this.
His name is Nam Sun-gil,
and we knew each other.
And I had some history with him.
I think that's complicated some things.
I'm sorry for hitting you.
Did that hurt?
I'm okay.
I can't seem to fix
this bad habit of mine.
If I ever get worked up again,
tie my hands first.
Your wife doesn't know anything, does she?
She's in charge of this case.
What? Didn't I tell you?
I warned you that she'd be the end of us!
If need be, I can cope
with the situation faster this way.
I never liked her.
You better watch out. She's two-faced.
How could you marry someone like her?
The killer was caught on CCTV,
and his blood was found at the scene.
The case will be solved.
You know
that chasing after Do Hyeon-su
won't lead them to Baek Hee-seong.
That is, as long as you continue
to be on my side, Mother.
Leave.
Okay.
The house is too big.
It's too big for just your dad and me.
Come have dinner
every now and then if you want.
It's not just you two.
Goodbye.
-It's time to feed your son.
-Let me do it.
13TH ELEMENTARY MATH CONTEST
21ST CHILDREN'S MATH COMPETITION
GOLD
AWARDS
BAEK HEE-SEONG
Hee-seong.
Here is Do Min-seok's family certificate
and Do Hyeon-su's relation certificate.
Do Min-seok had a daughter.
-Yes, she's older than Do Hyeon-su.
-She's the same age as you.
Ji-won, you should meet with her.
I've already met with the victim's family.
I'll leave the suspect's family to you.
I'm truly jealous of how soft you look.
People feel uncomfortable around me
because of my charismatic looks.
Simply put, they dislike you.
-Don't move.
-Enough with the chit-chat.
Find Do Hae-su's number and address first.
Yes, sir.
How is it?
You're not in pain anymore, are you?
It doesn't sting anymore.
But it smells a bit off.
It's slightly pungent.
It's not a problem, right?
That's the smell of liquid latex.
It's hardly harmful.
All good, then.
Ms. Do.
I want him
to look like he just died.
Can he look fresher?
Have you ever seen
an actual murdered body?
What?
Nan-hui, the blood.
Here.
Ms. Do, you've got a call.
-Hello?
-Is this Ms. Do Hae-su?
I'm Detective Cha Ji-won
from Gangsu Police Station.
Ms. Do Hae-su?
I'm Detective Cha Ji-won,
the one who called.
How did you know it was me?
Do I take after Do Min-seok?
No, I just took a guess.
You came here quickly.
Your workplace was quite nearby.
-Here's my card.
-I don't know.
CHA JI-WON
GANGSU POLICE STATION
-Pardon?
-I don't know anything.
I haven't seen Hyeon-su
ever since he disappeared in 2002.
This is what I've been telling
all the detectives for the past 18 years.
May I leave now?
That wasn't my question.
We've found out that about
900 million won of Do Min-seok's assets
hasn't been registered
on any certificate of inheritance.
A house in Paju,
a workshop in Gagyeong-ri,
and a villa in Taean.
Why did you leave the buildings there
when you'd sold the land?
It feels like you left them
for your brother to take shelter there.
Do detectives nowadays
use their imagination to investigate?
I sold the land to compensate
the bereaved families.
Other than that, I'm not interested
in any of that monster's money.
I haven't seen our Hyeon-su in 18 years.
How many times do I have to tell you?
"Our Hyeon-su"?
The police and the media
have been pestering you for 18 years,
so you must resent your brother a lot.
But you look…
sad.
I've been gone for too long.
And it doesn't seem like
I can help you anyway.
BAEK HEE-SEONG
Where did the real Baek Hee-seong go?
BAEK HEE-SEONG'S CONCERT TICKETS SOLD OUT
METAL CRAFTSMAN BAEK HEE-SEONG
ILSIN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL DIRECTOR
BAEK MAN-U EXPANDS MEDICAL CARE
ILSIN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL DIRECTOR EXPANDS
MEDICAL CARE TO LOW-INCOME FAMILIES
His father is a hospital director?
YOUR SON IS THE GIFTED MATH PRODIGY,
BAEK HEE-SEONG
"Gifted math prodigy, Baek Hee-seong"?
The son of a serial killer
disguised himself really well.
-What are you up to?
-My God.
You startled me.
It's your fault for not noticing me.
Bosses that watch over their employee's
shoulders are the worst, you know.
But a good employee isn't afraid
to show what's on their monitor.
I picked these up for you.
This is the father's case.
This is the son's case.
It wasn't easy to get them.
I expect a scoop.
BAEK HEE-SEONG
How's the police investigation going?
-Honey, here.
-What?
Can you try it on?
-Why?
-Hurry up.
Okay.
What is this about?
The Chinese restaurant case.
You came home looking like this.
So?
This is a common raincoat.
Do you think I went out late at night
and killed someone?
Don't be absurd.
I couldn't recognize you at first,
and it startled me.
So how did Nam Sun-gil
recognize the murderer at once?
The killer was even wearing a mask.
Maybe he mistook the killer
for someone else.
No. It has to be Do Hyeon-su.
Why?
That way, I can get a special promotion.
I'll be solving
a long-term cold case as well.
Go to bed first. I have a lot to work on.
GAGYEONG-RI VILLAGE HEAD MURDER
YEONJU SERIAL MURDER CASE
I'm going to sleep here tonight.
I don't want to sleep alone.
Do as you please.
YEONJU SERIAL MURDER CASE
Did they really not know?
What do you mean?
Did they really not know
that their father was a serial killer?
Do Hyeon-su's antisocial personality was
probably greatly affected by his father.
Anyway, this is a good case.
What do you mean?
This case will help find the genetic cause
of antisocial personality disorder.
So? Do you think
you'll catch the killer soon?
We already have his DNA,
so we just need to find out how he looks.
But it's not easy.
As an alternative,
we'll draw a facial composite.
We've found someone
who can confirm his face.
And who is that?
The owner of the Chinese restaurant
where he used to work.
Where in the world
did he go after he left there?
How could he just vanish into thin air?
Honey, you should take a rest for a bit.
I can't. I won't be able to get back up.
Stop staring at the documents
and stare at my face instead.
-Come here.
-Gosh.
Goodness.
I didn't know my husband
was this handsome.
What? Have you forgotten how I looked?
Of course not.
I can even recognize your shadow.
Goodness, look at the dark circles
under your eyes.
This won't do. I should tuck you in.
I shouldn't sleep.
I really shouldn't.
Then should I nap for just five minutes?
-Ji-won.
-Yes?
For the facial composite,
Mr. Kim will be there too, right?
Oh, right. I forgot about him.
I should cross-check
with the restaurant owner.
By the way, did I mention that
Mr. Kim knew Do Hyeon-su?
Yes.
When you were changing,
you said they went to the same school.
I can't believe I even told you that.
You shouldn't tell anyone
about the things I tell you.
Of course not.
GAGYEONG-RI VILLAGE HEAD MURDER CASE
Six bodies were found buried
in that tiny, rural village.
And the victims' thumbnails and photos
were found in Do Min-seok's workshop.
It was truly a shock.
It's been 18 years
since the Yeonju Serial Murder Case.
The killer's son was
in high school back then.
-Why has his name come up again?
-What is that?
A horrendous murder occurred
early this morning
at a Chinese restaurant in Seoul,
And the police believe
that it was Do Min-seok's son's doing.
Oh, dear. They say the apple
doesn't fall far from the tree.
-Goodness.
-This is Do Hyeon-su's photo.
But isn't the photo too old?
The police can't confirm
his current appearance,
and this has hindered the investigation.
So they're desperately waiting
for citizens' help.
That's wrong.
He was more manly. More robust.
Right?
Well… Right.
But in high school,
he grew about 20cm taller.
That's when
his appearance changed drastically.
Interfere with the facial composite.
I have something else to do.
He has a scar
on the left side of his forehead.
It's about 3cm long
and not very noticeable.
-He does?
-I guess you don't remember.
When you become old like me,
you remember less and less.
Are you sure?
Things like a scar
make quite a difference.
It's so vivid in my mind.
While I was
giving Hyeon-su a ride in a tractor,
I made a sharp turn, and he fell.
That's when he hit his forehead
and got about seven stitches.
Please add a scar over here.
Your eyes play a big role in looking sad.
Let's take a look at a sad expression.
The ends of your lips
should face downward.
Your eyes should be out of focus.
I know it's really hard for you.
Thank you so much for agreeing
to be interviewed.
I've covered many cases as a reporter.
But this one in particular
breaks my heart.
I heard that the last person
my husband looked for
was you.
If only I had picked up my phone then…
I'm truly sorry.
No. It wasn't your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
I feel responsible.
Thank you for thinking that way.
Speaking of which…
your husband was attacked
at around 3:00 a.m.
Why do you think he remained
at the restaurant until that hour?
Had it been around two months?
Once a week, he'd stay up late,
coming up with a new menu.
The killer must've known that.
Who could it have been?
Other than me, I'm not sure.
You must find out.
I'm certain
there was someone else who knew.
I'm sure it's somewhere in here.
This isn't it.
Not this one either.
Here it is.
Yes, it's him. I'm sure of it.
Pardon? You have a photo
of Do Hyeon-su from five years ago?
Ma'am, hold on.
Could you elaborate on that?
My daughter, who lives in Seoul,
gave me a tour of the city that day.
So we went
from place to place taking photos.
And that's when Do Hyeon-su
was caught on my camera.
Are you positive that it's him?
My neighbor and I had different opinions.
But if you ask me,
I'm pretty sure it's him.
I've watched him grow up
ever since he was an infant.
There's someone here who can confirm it,
so I'd like you to send us the photo.
Of course, I will.
Goodness,
he looks exactly like his dad
when he was young.
Can you take a photo
with your phone and send it right now?
That's not right.
No, he looks totally different.
Take a look.
You think this looks like him?
Well…
I can't say it looks exactly like him.
But I can say it could be
Do Hyeon-su's half-brother.
Mr. Kim, are you sure
you even remember how he looked?
Of course.
I vividly remember his face
as if I met him yesterday.
Didn't you say
your memory was failing you?
Since he's young, he must be right.
Let's start with this
and touch it up as we go.
FORENSIC SCIENCE
Yes, Captain Lee.
Pardon? Okay, I'm on my way.
Thank you for today. You may leave now.
Are we done with that?
Yes. There's no need for one anymore.
I'm sorry I couldn't be of any help.
It doesn't matter how trivial it may be.
Call me if you remember anything.
I will.
-Goodbye.
The taxi.
Sir, the taxi.
Sorry?
Homi Village, Gagyeong-ri,
Namchon-myeon, Yeonju.
Ms. Oh Bok-ja, right?
I'll go to the post office
and send it by express delivery.
You don't have to come all the way here.
This is quite urgent.
You must not show that photo
to anyone until we get there.
Don't you worry about that.
Thank you.
I'll go with Detective Im.
Is something bothering you?
Pardon?
Your face is telling me
that something's not right.
It doesn't feel like
we're chasing Do Hyeon-su.
Rather, it feels like
he's dragging us around.
Is that guy not picking up his tumbler?
Sir, why aren't you picking up
your tumbler?
We'll discard it at the end of the day.
Goodness, I'm sorry, sir.
I've been busy working.
I'll make sure to drop by today.
Okay. Please keep it safe for me.
Okay. Thank you. Goodbye.
GANGSU POLICE STATION
Detective Choi,
did you check the dashcam footage
from the cars near New Sun Villa?
The ones I received this morning
were of no use.
I need to go out and search for more.
Smile, will you?
Everything will go smoothly
once we get our hands on his photo.
Do Hyeon-su.
Your phone.
Give me your phone.
Let me just make one call.
Mine's out of battery.
My wife is waiting, you know?
Do Hyeon-su.
Why are you so old-fashioned?
Here. This is a 256mb MP3 player.
You can keep it.
Throw away that piece of junk already.
I can't listen to this tape with that.
Do Hyeon-su?
You're him, aren't you?
Did you just say "Do Hyeon-su," sir?
Something doesn't feel right today.
Maybe it's because I didn't go with them.
They're just picking up a photo.
Nothing will happen.
Every time my husband
came home late, he'd take a taxi.
And it was the same one every time.
I'm glad you called.
You need to look into something.
-It's Igang Taxi Service.
-Hey, now is not the time.
I have good news and bad news.
What do you want to hear first?
Bad news? What is it?
You know Ms. Oh Bok-ja, right?
She has a photo of you
from five years ago.
Do you want to know what's worse?
What? What is it?
The police are on their way
to get that photo. Detective Cha is on it.
-What?
-Your wife is going to catch you.
Then what's the good news?
That I'm on your side.
Where are you right now?
How did the sketch go?
They remembered him differently,
so it didn't work out well.
We'll know once we get the photo.
Let's go.
GANGSU POLICE STATION
-Step on it.
-Hey.
Will we be able to get there
before they do?
-Yes, for sure.
-How so?
Because they'll follow traffic laws.
UNPROTECTED LEFT TURN
I can't believe we're visiting
the crime scene of a serial murderer.
Me neither.
Seven bodies were buried
in that tiny village.
How did none of the villagers know that?
They only found six bodies.
Right. The seventh victim's body
has yet to be found.
Maybe he found
a different place to bury it.
Where could that be?
They should at least find the body.
But why did Do Min-seok commit suicide?
If he hadn't, his crimes
wouldn't have been revealed.
This case came to light while the police
were investigating his suicide.
Beats me. It's impossible for humans
to understand a monster.
Did he even commit suicide?
Have you come up with a conspiracy theory?
Only the victims' right fingernails
were found at his workshop.
Where did the left fingernails go?
Did he split them with someone else?
For example…
with his son.
You're approaching a speed trap.
Please drive within the speed limit.
It'll be awesome
if we catch the killer first.
Both the police and the media
are only after Do Hyeon-su.
If a weekly reporter like me
ends up catching the culprit
and writes up an article about it…
Doesn't it sound amazing?
You're not listening, are you?
Why do you have my sister's necklace?
What?
My sister's necklace.
Oh, that?
I just…
It just happened to…
Hey, why is that hers?
I bought it for her, so it's mine.
She gave it back
when we broke up. So what?
I found it in one of my drawers.
I was going to fix it and sell it.
You got a problem?
-I threw it away.
-What?
-You have no right to--
-It's too cheap to sell anyway.
Hyeon-su.
By the way,
how did Do Hyeon-su
turn into Baek Hee-seong?
Is this an interview?
Forget about everyone else.
How did you fool your wife?
-Hey, Moo-jin.
-Yes? I'm listening.
I won't judge.
Ji-won doesn't know anything about me.
About my past
or how I'm not normal.
Do you really have no feelings for her?
They say couples develop a stronger bond
once they have a baby together.
Ji-won is someone that I absolutely need.
Because my father…
is afraid of her.
He can't get close to me
if she's nearby.
What are you on about?
You're scaring me.
I'll promise you one thing.
What? Hold on.
Why was that in my pocket?
Wait a minute. What are you doing?
Let me. Hold on.
You can't just delete all of them.
I have so many important interviews
in there. Don't erase them.
Damn it.
If you tell her what you know…
I may actually kill you.
Gosh, stop joking around.
That wasn't even funny.
I meant it.
GAGYEONG-RI
Now, there are more vacant houses
than occupied ones.
Come here! I said, come here!
Move!
Come here!
DO HYEON-SU
You're approaching your destination.
Turn right after 300m.
Here. Get ready.
OH BOK-JA
All right. We'll follow our plan.
You remember everything, right?
This is my last time explaining,
so listen up.
Okay.
First, I'll distract her.
-Ms. Oh!
-My goodness.
-Ms. Oh! It's been ages!
-Goodness.
-Here.
-Goodness, it's okay.
I'll tell her that I'm covering the case
and ask to see your photo.
Goodness. So this is it.
After that,
I'll text you the location of the photo.
IN THE DRAWER UNDERNEATH THE FLOWERS
Then I'll lure her out of the house
under the pretense
of welcoming the detectives from Seoul.
We should wait outside
since they're coming from Seoul.
Of course, we should.
In the meantime, you'll steal the photo.
No, you'll go fetch it in peace.
I'll prevent them from going inside.
While I buy some time,
you can…
get out of there easily.
Then we'll rendezvous as planned.
So? Simple, right?
What if she doesn't show you the photo?
What if you can't lure her out?
What if the detectives come in?
Do you have another idea?
If not, be quiet.
Hide in there.
Ma'am.
Ms. Oh.
It's me, Moo-jin. I'm a reporter in Seoul.
Kim Moo-jin.
Are you not in?
Ms. Oh.
Watch out…
-What?
-Watch out…
-You need to pee?
-Watch your back.
What's taking him so long?
Who are you?
-Do Hyeon-su.
-I don't know you.
Why are you doing this to me?
You may not know me,
but I'm sure you know Jung Mi-suk.
What?
Where is Jung Mi-suk?
-Jung Mi-suk?
-The police will be here soon.
We don't have time to waste.
Both you and I aren't fond of the police.
Doesn't that car look familiar?
-I think it's Mr. Kim's.
-How did he know about this place?
Let's meet without the police
getting involved. What do you say?
There's a nice bed and breakfast
near the fishing area.
I'll pick you up tonight in a taxi.
I've been looking forward
to our first date.
We should give each other
some time to get dolled up.
Don't you agree?
What do you want?
Ms. Oh Bok-ja, are you in?
Ms. Oh.
Do Hyeon-su!
-Mr. Kim!
-Detective Im.
-Sir.
-She's in there.
Let go!
I said, let go!
Let go! I said, let go!
Let go!
Do Hyeon-su! Stop right there!
Uncuff me!
Hello? Hey, where are you?
I almost died in there.
What happened?
Jung Mi-suk. Find out who she is.
He mentioned her name.
Jung Mi-suk?
That name rings a bell.
He asked me where she was.
She and I must have a connection.
Hello?
What a bastard.
Jung Mi-suk?
Jung Mi-suk…
Are you serious?
Do you know how worried sick I was?
Just uncuff me. I'm so humiliated.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Look at the mess around you.
Are you sure you're not injured?
You didn't break any bones?
I'm fine.
-Just uncuff me.
-Geez.
Right. Is Ms. Oh okay?
Yes. She's just a bit shook up.
-She's not injured.
-Damn it.
But the photo was stolen.
I should've caught him.
How did he know about the photo?
Who the hell is Do Hyeon-su?
It wasn't Do Hyeon-su.
What?
Which one's Do Hyeon-su?
I said, which one is he?
He didn't know how he looked?
One thing is certain.
The culprit is after Do Hyeon-su.
And in the most extreme way possible.
I don't think the culprit behind this…
It's not Do Hyeon-su.
There's a nice bed and breakfast
near the fishing area.
I'll pick you up tonight in a taxi.
Come on in.
-Let me know if you need anything.
-Okay.
Rest up, then.
GAGYEONG-RI VILLAGE HALL
Thank you so much for gathering here
at this late hour.
-It's fine.
-Of course, we should.
After what happened to Bok-ja?
Gosh, it's so terrifying.
How can we live here?
Is Do Hyeon-su really back?
See? I told you.
He's been possessed by a ghost
just like his father was.
What ghost?
We should've performed
more exorcisms back then.
-Ghost, my foot.
-You're right.
What kind of grudge
does he have against this village?
The person we're looking for
isn't Do Hyeon-su.
-What do you mean?
-What?
We're actually looking for someone
who's determined to find him.
Did anyone visit this village
and inquire
about Do Hyeon-su's whereabouts?
-Gosh.
-There were too many.
Everyone from the city looked for him.
-Right.
-What kinds of people?
-There were some TV producers.
-Right.
-Reporters.
And writers as well.
-There were also your kind of people.
-Police.
-I mean, there were police officers too.
-Right.
Please think hard.
The culprit we're after
has deep resentment towards Do Hyeon-su.
How would we know something you don't?
That… That man.
-Who?
-Who are you talking about?
-That man!
-Who?
-That taxi driver.
-Goodness.
Taxi driver?
I found him.
Detective Oh worked hard to get
the dashcam footage, and it paid off.
I caught you.
What? No one got out.
He said he dropped him off
around New Sun Villa.
IM HO-JUN
-Yes?
-Sir.
It wasn't Do Hyeon-su. We were wrong.
What? What do you mean?
So…
-Is that Captain Lee?
-Yes.
Captain Lee, one of Do Min-seok's victims
hasn't been found yet.
Please look into her husband.
-I believe he's a taxi driver.
-A taxi driver?
IM HO-JUN
Elaborate.
They had found six out of
the seven victims and closed the case.
But the victim's husband didn't give up
and visited the village regularly.
He dug up all the areas
where the other bodies were found.
Mi-suk, I'll find you soon.
Please just wait a little while.
-Don't do that!
-Goodness!
-What are you doing right now?
-Let go!
-He looked very unstable.
-I need to find her!
He believed that Do Hyeon-su
was an accomplice and obsessed over him.
He believes Do Hyeon-su
knows where his wife is buried.
And Captain Lee.
I have no idea how he knew
about the photo Ms. Oh had.
I'm afraid our information
has been leaking.
And Nam Sun-gil feared Do Hyeon-su
until the moment he got killed.
But what's this photo of Do Hyeon-su?
This is his middle school
graduation photo.
In 2002, when Do Hyeon-su was 18,
he murdered the village head and fled.
And he set his house on fire.
VACANT
EXCLUSIVE: CHINESE RESTAURANT
OWNER NAM DIES…
MISSING PERSON
JUNG MI-SUK
27, FEMALE
VICTIM IDENTIFICATION REPORT
JUNG MI-SUK
HUSBAND: PARK GYEONG-CHUN
OCCUPATION: TAXI DRIVER
Taxi driver.
So Do Hyeon-su was an accomplice
in the serial killing?
With his father, at that?
Mi-suk and I each had this made
as a couple item.
At Do Min-seok's workshop,
they found her phone but not this.
But according to what you said,
Do Hyeon-su had this.
-Leave this to the police--
-The police…
are not willing to catch Do Hyeon-su.
Unless he commits a heinous crime
that becomes the center of attention.
Wake up, will you?
To be blunt, what's the point
of digging up a rotten body?
What difference will it make?
Anyway, I truly appreciate
your help today.
-What did I help you with?
-You told me about Do Hyeon-su.
And I think it'll help me greatly.
MOTHER
Eun-ha, why are you crying?
All right. Dad's on the phone,
so stop crying now.
Why did you leave me while I was asleep?
Come pick up your daddy's girl!
Eun-ha.
Something came up, so I had no choice.
Will you be here soon?
Yes, I will.
Is Mom coming with you?
Dad, hurry up.
I miss you.
Okay, I'll be there as soon as I can.
Eun-ha.
I'll see you soon.
Ma'am.
Please take a look at this.
We found this in the warehouse back there.
We were wondering if it was yours.
GAGYEONG HAEOREUM BED AND BREAKFAST
And this is my gift for you.
I love it. Thank you.
I had your initials engraved on it.
I think my husband is the one
who was abducted.
You saw how Park Gyeong-chun
murdered Nam Sun-gil.
Jae-seop, what am I supposed to do?
Park Gyeong-chun
is still near the village.
Take the road along the reservoir.
You can catch up with him.
Killing me won't fill the holes
in your imagination.
I can't prove something I don't know.
Where is Jung Mi-suk?
Help!