Bride, please smile more naturally.
Okay.
The groom is really good at this.
You could be a model.
Do you want to take a break?
Yes, it's tiring.
I'm sorry, but can we take ten?
Sure.
Sit down.
Is this really your first photoshoot?
Why are you so good?
It's all about your stamina.
What is it?
Are you worried about something?
Are your parents really not coming?
No. They won't come.
You only get married once.
I don't want you to regret--
Then let's do it twice.
We can have another wedding.
Are you going to gloss it over again?
Weddings are just a formality.
Don't take it to heart.
But you're going to feel sad
if your family doesn't come.
You're the only family I need.
It's true.
Have you been well?
We met for the last time two weeks ago
at Lawyer Song's office.
Time flies, doesn't it?
It's already been four months.
Im Ho-jun.
He's alive.
Breathe. He's breathing.
-Stay still.
-He's breathing.
I'll call an ambulance.
He's still unconscious, but both
his breathing and pulse are stable.
How's Baek Hee-seong?
He's dead.
How badly is he injured?
By the looks of it,
they think the bullet grazed him.
It didn't penetrate his head.
All right. I'll go to the hospital
once I settle everything here.
I know it's tough right now,
but hang in there.
The bullet grazed his head
and ripped his scalp.
And his skull is fractured.
It's a linear fracture.
Simply put,
there's a fracture in his skull.
It's not fatal, right?
No. And judging by the CT scans,
this is the only injury he has.
We've treated him for infections.
Then when will he regain consciousness?
As of now, he's unconscious
due to a concussion.
But he should wake up in a day or so.
My God.
The reporters are gathering outside.
How is he?
As long as there's no coagulation
in his brain, he'll be okay.
How's Ho-jun?
Captain is taking care of him.
He's not himself right now.
He'll be questioned for the entire month.
He did nothing wrong
while shooting, did he?
Captain will take care of that.
Just worry about yourself.
A tsunami will come to you
as soon as he wakes up.
You better brace yourself.
That's all right.
There's nothing
we can't overcome together.
Geez.
Back then, I had no idea
that I'd never
get to see him again.
Say something.
Anything is fine.
Do I…
make you feel very uncomfortable?
You don't have to be.
I hope you don't feel too uncomfortable.
Hee-seong, you and I…
can slowly get to know each other again.
It's Do Hyeon-su.
Sorry?
You called me Hee-seong again just now.
I'm sorry.
People tell me…
that I was in a coma
for a month before I woke up.
But I don't feel that way.
Come here! Come and hug me!
I broke your heart.
I hurt you.
I wish you could live
as me for just one day.
Then you'd know how much I love you.
Goodness, I didn't know
my husband was this handsome.
Call Detective Im and tell him that
you're dealing with a more urgent case.
Forget it. Stop that.
Eun-ha, I'm coming to get you.
Here I come.
When I woke up in the hospital,
I thought I was hospitalized
due to a car accident.
I really…
thought it was still 2005.
Hey, Mom.
He didn't injure his brain,
and his vitals are normal as well.
So I don't get why he's still in a coma.
Okay. I'll stop by later.
Honey.
CHA JI-WON
POLICE AGENCY
What's wrong?
Honey!
-It's Do Hyeon-su!
-Mr. Do!
-You're Mr. Do, right?
Have you fully recovered?
You're the one who helped end
the Yeonju Serial Murder Case.
Not only had I skipped
15 years of my life…
-Please say a word or two!
-When did you start…
…but I'd also become very famous.
In 2005, Baek Man-u and Gong Mi-ja,
Baek Hee-seong's parents,
put Do Hyeon-su
up to living as Baek Hee-seong.
Through our investigation, we've found out
that Detective Cha Ji-won
had nothing to do with this.
After she found out
about it in May this year,
she convinced Do to help the police
with the investigation.
Thanks to his active cooperation,
we were able to swiftly
carry out the investigation.
As a result, we have
successfully uncovered the truth
regarding the Yeonju Serial Murder Case.
Some people say that
I'm a hero who caught a serial killer.
And some people say…
that I'm a poor guy who's taken
the blame for my sister's crime
and lived in hiding.
And some say…
that I'm a psychopath
who hid my real identity
and deceived and used a woman
to my advantage.
But…
the only person
who should never forgive me…
doesn't resent me for it at all.
That's because…
you don't know how close we were.
What I'm trying to say is…
it's already too much
for me to accept everything…
that's been going on.
So…
I'm afraid I can't give you
the words you want to hear.
There's nothing I want to hear from you.
However,
I do have one question.
Sure, ask me.
Why…
are you…
still wearing that?
Sorry?
Never mind.
I apologize.
I know today's an important day
for you, Hee-seong…
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I came here to give you my support.
But I think I've made you
even more uncomfortable.
I don't know…
if I'll do a good job.
Just do as you've practiced.
Okay.
Goodbye, then.
SUPREME COURT OF KOREA
WITNESS WAITING ROOM
All rise.
JURY BOX
The first trial for Ms. Do Hae-su,
who has been indicted for the murder
of the Gagyeong-ri village head
18 years ago, takes place today.
In this jury trial,
the prosecution will accuse her of murder
and the defendant will claim self-defense.
It's expected to be a neck and neck trial.
Also, the defendant's brother,
Do Hyeon-su,
who has been in the spotlight recently,
will appear as a witness for the defense.
This has sparked
more interest among the public.
JUDGE BENCH
"I swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth
and nothing but the truth."
"If I commit perjury,
I swear to be punished."
WITNESS
DO HYEON-SU
Mr. Do, you were the first one to arrive
at the scene after the incident occurred.
Is this true?
Yes.
Did you do this?
I came here…
to tell him not to perform
exorcisms on you anymore.
But he suddenly…
He suddenly tried to…
I took the scissors from her.
Then I wiped her fingerprints
with my clothes.
Mr. Do fully knew that the village head
Kwon Seong-bok's violence
was the cause of the accident.
Is that true?
Yes.
Then why didn't you ask
the judicial system for help?
I never thought someone else
could help us at that time.
Since our father
turned out to be a serial killer,
I was sure
that we'd never win the case.
Had Mr. Kwon…
always terrified Ms. Do?
On the days when
I was dragged away by him,
she was unable to sleep all night
and often vomited anything she ate.
That'll be all.
Isn't Hyeon-su doing
much better than we expected?
I think he has almost
completely won over the jury.
The prosecution
may cross-examine the witness.
I hope he answers their questions well.
God, I'm dying to know.
How do you think the trial will pan out?
Since she used a weapon,
I doubt the judge will acknowledge it
as self-defense.
Her lawyer is planning to use
the public's sympathy for Do Hyeon-su
for a unanimous verdict from the jury.
In other words,
they have no decisive card they can play
to claim that it was self-defense.
Everyone at that village
is on the same side.
All their statements
were practically the same.
Hold on.
The same side?
WITNESS STATEMENT
You changed your identity
to live a more comfortable life
and even deceived
those around you for 15 years.
On top of that, you completely
deceived your own wife, a detective.
Is that true?
Yes.
JURY BOX
How were you able
to deceive everyone so perfectly?
People have testified that you
cannot feel emotions like most people do.
Does this mean
you're not capable of feeling guilt?
I love you.
I…
love you, Ji-won.
Do
you…
love her?
No.
I've never loved her.
Not even for a moment.
Witness?
Please answer me.
Are you unable to feel any guilt?
Objection, Your Honor.
That'll be all.
She pretty much informed the jury
that Hyeon-su is good at lying.
That way, all his previous
statements will seem fake.
The trial is adjourned
until 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
Thank you, everyone.
Why did you do that?
You knew she'd ask you that question.
You even rehearsed.
"Back then, there was
nothing else that I could do."
"I am filled with remorse
for what I've done."
How could you forget that?
What is it?
It was because of that woman.
The moment I met her eyes,
my mind went blank.
JAE-SEOP
Hey.
It just ended.
Things aren't looking up.
We have no witness to summon.
Would it hurt to be a bit more friendly
to Detective Cha? What a jerk.
I don't want to get her hopes up.
Hopes? What hopes?
I deceived and used her
for 14 years for my own sake.
I think she's refusing
to acknowledge the fact
that I'm that kind of asshole.
I should keep my distance from her.
You genuinely loved her.
How do you know that?
I could see it.
You read me wrong.
Had I really loved her,
how could I have married her
as someone else?
Forget it. Don't think too much.
Tell me. Is she on your mind
right now or not?
-She makes me feel uncomfortable.
-Hey, she's here.
So she is on your mind.
What?
Are you going to punch me or what?
Let's just go.
Hey, it's her.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
But…
Quit joking around about her.
Just thinking about her
makes my heart feel stuffy.
Mr. Do, we need to go somewhere.
We've found a witness
who could perhaps turn the tables.
I was looking through
the witness statements again
and found someone who could be helpful.
It's Yang Jin-tae,
the village head's nephew.
He said that his uncle had spent
Do Min-seok's money on the exorcisms.
Whenever the exorcisms were performed,
the money that was taken
from your father's account
and the money paid
to the exorcist weren't the same.
The money taken from his account
was three to five times more.
Through the exorcisms, the village head
wanted to take your father's money.
That's why he intentionally
made you the scapegoat.
Honey, do you know Yang Jin-tae,
the village head's nephew?
Jin…
I'm sorry. I was too busy talking.
Yang Jin-tae?
Yes, the college student.
He always came by during the breaks.
And he agreed to be our witness?
He hasn't agreed yet.
Detective Cha and Hyeon-su
went to persuade him.
-Just the two of them?
-Yes.
How are they doing with each other?
God, Detective Cha
is pretty much Mother Teresa.
If I were her,
I would've grabbed him by the collar,
asked how he could forget me,
and hurled him down.
She's trying to seduce
Hyeon-su again with endless patience.
I mean, she's waiting.
What about Hyeon-su?
Has he been opening his heart?
But more importantly,
don't you think he has changed
since he lost his memory?
I mean, he still has
that obnoxious side to him,
but it feels like he's blended
with someone else.
Sometimes, I think
it's not that he's changed.
Maybe that's his true self.
I thought this was a horror genre, but
you looked at it in a humanistic aspect.
I guess blood is
indeed thicker than water.
Is it not uncomfortable
to live with Hyeon-su?
He pretty much thinks he owns the house.
It's such an inconvenience.
I guess this is one downside.
Moo-jin, you don't have
to come here this often.
Why not? I like coming here.
I have the most fun
when I'm chatting with you.
I just feel a bit embarrassed.
About what?
-I'm in this uniform and--
-You look good in that.
What?
What I meant was,
you look good in that pastel color.
I enjoy chatting with you as well.
I hope Hyeon-su,
Ji-won, Eun-ha, you, and I
can eat together under the same roof soon.
We agreed to meet at his house.
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the beep.
His phone is off as well.
Did something happen to him?
He's just avoiding us.
He gave it some thought
and decided not to do it.
I'm sure that's not the case.
When we spoke on the phone earlier,
he was willing to talk about it.
I'm sorry, but I don't think
I can testify for you.
I apologize.
He refused…
to testify.
Let's leave, then.
Let's wait.
He's bound to come home anyway.
Let's try to convince him.
It's raining.
Do you like the rain?
Ji-won only believes what she sees.
So I find it very easy to deal with her.
GRANDMA, MOM, EUN-HA
-Eun-ha.
-Yes?
Do you hate your dad?
No.
Then why isn't he in your drawing?
If I draw him,
Mom will cry.
I feel sorry
when she cries.
Goodness, you sweet thing.
You even worry about your mom.
Gosh, you're all grown up now.
I hate Dad.
He went on a trip by himself.
He should've taken Mom and me with him.
It stopped raining,
so you should get going.
Why don't you head back without me?
I'll wait for him by myself.
Detective?
Yes?
I'll wait for him by myself.
You should go.
Why
are you still wearing that?
Sorry?
That ring.
I've been going to the workshop lately
to brush up on my skills.
And I keep making mistakes
whenever I take this off.
I apologize.
I was being thoughtless.
I should've given this back to you.
Here.
Don't worry about me.
I can wear another ring
that weighs around the same as this one.
Take it.
Yang Jin-tae?
Did you do something wrong to me,
Mr. Yang?
I'm sorry, Hyeon-su.
Are you
Mr. Yang Jin-tae?
Yes.
Please testify for us,
Mr. Yang.
VOICE RECORDING
Do you mind if I record this?
No.
What were the village head
Kwon Seong-bok's intentions?
My uncle was determined to take as much
of their father's money as possible
before they found a temporary guardian
for Hae-su and Hyeon-su.
What did you do to me that made you
avoid me so much?
He offered to pay
for my college tuition if I helped him.
KWON SEONG-BOK'S INTENTIONS
YANG JIN-TAE'S ROLE
So I spread
a fake rumor about you.
What was it?
I killed a chicken, cut it open,
and left it on the streets.
The next day, people gathered around it.
I told them that it was Hyeon-su
and that he was possessed
by his father's evil spirit.
You made everyone terrified
and encouraged them
to carry out exorcisms on him.
That's right.
Please repeat what you just said
in court.
I'll make an anonymous report, but…
Hyeon-su.
I'm really sorry.
I know it's the right thing to do,
but I teach elementary kids.
If people find out about this,
my life will be ruined.
I really don't think I can't do it.
FAKE RUMOR
REFUSES TO TESTIFY IN COURT
Mr. Yang.
Follow your heart
and decide whether to testify in court.
I would like you
to make a decision for yourself,
not for anyone else.
That way, you won't resent yourself.
Also,
I am going
to forgive you here and now.
So…
you can stop feeling guilty about me now.
What you said back there
about forgiving him…
I'm sure that wasn't easy to say.
It was hard, wasn't it?
No, it was easy.
Sorry?
Because I lied, of course.
Forgiveness?
I really wanted to just
snap his neck if I could.
I'm sorry.
He looked like
he was suffering from a lot of guilt,
so I thought I'd win him over
if I nudged him a little.
See?
YANG JIN-TAE
Yes, Mr. Yang.
Hyeon-su, I'll testify.
It's the right thing to do.
Thank you.
My lawyer will call you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow, then.
We should summon him to turn
the tables at the final trial, right?
Detective Cha,
you should see your face right now.
I can tell what you're thinking,
and it's a bit embarrassing.
What do you think
I'm thinking about right now?
"He's not the man I knew."
"He's not the man I was looking for."
Am I wrong?
You're doing this on purpose, aren't you?
Why are you being so mean?
I am…
capable of lying
without feeling any guilt
or being emotionally stirred.
I don't think you realize that.
Do you believe
you can tell if I'm lying
or telling the truth?
Hyeon-su. Do Hyeon-su.
Hyeon-su, you crazy bastard.
When I regained
consciousness at the hospital,
I didn't remember anything.
So it felt like
I had woken up after 15 years.
But I was wrong.
Habits from the past 15 years
that I don't remember
are deeply engraved in my body.
I can cook dishes
I've never seen or eaten.
When I'm working,
I become unbelievably dexterous.
And…
I can instinctively read
other people's emotions
and I know how to use it to my advantage
very well.
That's why…
I know exactly what you want to hear…
from me.
There's nothing I want to hear from you.
You're wrong. There is.
You long to hear those words
from me.
"I may have lost all memories of you,
but my feelings still remain."
Lies like this.
I never…
I never wanted to hear that from you.
How could you forget me?
How could you?
We loved each other so much.
We went through a lot together.
So how am I…
the only one you can't remember?
Detective Cha.
Sometimes, I doubt myself.
I doubt if I even have
a genuine side to me.
I can't trust myself.
Never once in my lifetime…
have I shown unfaltering
emotions towards someone.
So…
how long do you think these feelings
I feel for you right now will last?
Why do you doubt yourself so much?
Do you know what you're doing?
You keep
searching for that man inside of me.
You become hopeful
whenever you find a similarity.
You become dispirited
when you find a difference.
But you know what?
I hate him.
I don't want to know about him.
It feels like…
we're wearing a pair of shackles…
and running around in circles.
You're chasing me from behind.
And I'm running away from you
because I don't want to show you my face.
In the end,
there is no way for us
to take a step forward.
BEHIND THE YEONJU SERIAL MURDER CASE
A LARGE SACK WAS RUSTLING IN THE CORNER
THOSE WITH EVIL INTENTIONS TEND
TO BLEND IN WITH THE CROWD
HE'S ONLY SAYING THIS BECAUSE
DO HYEON-SU CAUGHT THE KILLER
I PITY DO HYEON-SU
Hey, are you out of your mind?
What did I do?
Come here.
Do you know how aghast I was?
They're for you.
Just looking at them makes me nauseous.
Why do you keep buying food you don't eat?
I can't help but buy them
whenever I see them.
That's an illness, okay?
What? Did you cry?
No. Why would I?
What's going on?
Did Yang Jin-tae refuse to testify?
No, he's going to.
Seriously? Then it's all working out.
But why the long face?
Ms. Cha must've finally punched you.
I wish she did.
Once the trial is over,
we'll have to talk about our daughter.
To think that I'll be seeing her again…
makes me feel suffocated.
Are you going to meet with Eun-ha?
No.
I don't want her to see me.
What's the point?
I can't even remember her.
Then what's your plan?
Moo-jin.
If I tell her that I want to give Eun-ha
all my inheritance
that hasn't been disposed of yet
and…
settle everything,
do you think…
it'll break her heart?
YANG JIN-TAE'S RECORDING
KWON SEONG-BOK'S INTENTIONS
REFUSES TO TESTIFY IN COURT
I killed a chicken, cut it open,
and left it on the streets.
The next day, people gathered around it.
Mr. Yang.
Follow your heart
and decide whether to testify in court.
I would like you
to make a decision for yourself,
not for anyone else.
That way, you won't resent yourself.
Mom.
Yes?
Did you
and Dad
get a divorce?
What?
When I told everyone…
that my name was Cha Eun-ha now…
they said
it meant you two got a divorce.
That's not true.
Then why isn't Dad coming home?
Come here.
I want…
your dad to be happy.
What about you?
Me too.
Your dad…
has never lived
as his true self in his life.
So…
I want your dad…
to live freely for once.
I heard you were of great help.
Thank you.
I can't even dare
to tell you
that I'm grateful or sorry.
Because you made a huge sacrifice for me.
At that time,
I truly wanted to protect you and Eun-ha
at all costs.
Thanks to the sacrifice I made,
I have come to like myself a little.
I know Hyeon-su is
giving you a lot of pain.
I'm going to let him go.
I've finally realized that letting him go…
is the best thing to do
for both of us.
Since I met you,
I've come to believe something.
That the pain we're experiencing right now
is just a step we need to go through
to accept more things later on in life.
But still, I hope you feel less pain.
The jury has made a unanimous decision.
I will read it out loud.
"Taking into consideration
the circumstances
and the unusual upbringing
the defendant experienced,
the defendant's behavior can be considered
acceptable according to social norms."
"Therefore,
this is our unanimous decision."
"We acknowledge
defendant Do Hae-su's actions
as an act of self-defense."
Before giving out the ruling,
I would like you to know
that the judicial department's decision
isn't limited to that of the jury.
I will give out the ruling.
The judicial department's decision
was different from that of the jury.
The judicial department didn't acknowledge
defendant Do Hae-su's actions
as self-defense.
But due to the fact that
she was a minor at that time
and that the incident
occurred at nighttime,
they decided it could be exempted
as excessive self-defense
and declared her innocent.
You're so loud.
I'm sorry. God, I saw that coming.
I told you so.
Why did you come?
It must be true that you lost your memory.
If you remembered me,
you would've never come here.
I thought you would
know me better than anyone.
Did you
visit him too?
Mr. Baek Man-u?
Hee-seong.
What took you so long?
I've been waiting for a very long time.
Dad.
Have you been waiting for me?
Yes.
Every single day.
I've missed you too.
Why are you so handsome?
Were you always this handsome?
I kept them for you.
Don't share them with anyone else.
You don't need to worry about him.
He's going further into the past…
as a way of escaping from reality.
So?
What did you want to ask me?
It's about Detective Cha.
What…
did she mean to me?
You really hated it
every time my husband and I met her.
At first,
I thought you were just
being careful not to get caught.
That's what I thought.
But later…
I realized…
that you…
cherished her very much.
You should leave. I'm getting tired.
We're done.
You're studying abroad?
I've never lived my own life.
But must you really
go so far away to do so?
Seoul, Daejeon, Daegu, and Busan.
We live in a big country.
As a senior in high school,
I stumbled upon Antoni Gaudí's work on TV.
And my heart began to thump.
I was reminded of that day.
I want to start afresh there.
I'm happy for you.
I'm glad you finally found
something you want to do.
I support you.
I'm not sure
how important Gaudí is to you,
but I'll always support you.
Thanks.
Don't expect me
to wait for you, because I won't.
Right, I forgot about an interview I had.
I can't believe it's already this late.
I'll get going, then.
Hae-su, we should
meet up before you leave.
Have fun.
Hyeon-su.
Yes?
Okay.
Hey, you should console me
if you came out here, you bastard.
Damn it.
Should I wait for her?
Do what you want.
I shouldn't.
I'm going to forget everything.
I'm going to forget
every little thing about her.
How do you lose your memory?
You must have some tips.
In order to do that,
you need to crack your head open.
So? Should I help you do that?
Hey, Hae-su. I didn't expect
a call from you at this hour.
What?
Right. We promised to chat today.
I've been so busy lately,
so I forgot about it.
Are you sad to hear that?
Really?
It's still morning there, right?
What did you have for breakfast?
Gosh, isn't that too greasy?
Should I send over some kimchi?
Oh, they sell them there?
I was going to send you some
if you wanted.
Hyeon-su.
You and I
have lost our true selves
somewhere down the line.
I'm sure we'll often
feel lost and confused.
So we need a starting point
if we don't want to get lost.
You won't be here anymore.
So who will give me the answers?
You are the only one…
who knows the answers.
I'm really unlucky.
What kind of first date is this?
Are you sure
you aren't the only one
who doesn't know that you like me?
REAL ESTATE AGENCY
We've found a perfect place
that fits what you wanted.
WHERE THE RISING STAR STAYS
Hello, you found it.
This is it. Let's go inside.
What do you think?
I was really surprised too.
From the neighborhood
to the interior, structure, and space,
everything perfectly matches
your requirements.
May I take a look around by myself?
Take your time and give me a call later.
I'll tell the landlord that you're here.
Thank you.
WHERE THE RISING STAR STAYS
SHE ABHORS MOTHS
WHY DOES SHE ABHOR THEM
WHEN SHE LOVES BUTTERFLIES?
WHAT IF I TOLD HER THAT
TINKER BELL WAS A MOTH?
MOVIE POSTERS ON HER SOCIAL MEDIA
LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL, TITANIC
SHE LIKES THE RAIN
She likes rain.
When it rains, her pitch goes up
and she laughs so easily.
Does she like how the cold rain feels?
Or is it because the sound of rain
muffles other noises?
You shouldn't read those.
I was cleaning out the place.
Feel free to take whatever you need.
They were yours anyway.
Those notebooks are yours too,
but they're all about me,
so I'm afraid I can't give them to you.
WHERE THE RISING STAR STAYS
Did I
name this workshop…
myself?
Yes.
Do you know what it means?
You always refused to tell me.
Now that I think of it,
it'll remain a mystery forever.
In the Greek and Roman mythology,
there's a god of blacksmiths
named Hephaestus.
He had the ugliest face in Olympus.
And due to his horrible temper,
everyone hated him.
So
he always spent time in his workshop.
Even he
had a wife he loved very much.
In English, her name was Venus.
It's the morning star.
And the "rising star" is its nickname.
I…
always thought about you
in this space where I spent
most of my time.
I requested to be transferred
to the TF team in Busan.
They're in need of more workers,
so it'll be decided soon.
So…
are you telling me…
that you'll be leaving?
I want to start over
in a new place.
I don't want
to run into you, even by chance.
How could you?
I've finally managed
to take one step towards you.
So how could you run away?
I got my hopes up and was dispirited.
And then, it happened again.
I just can't do this anymore.
Could you please…
change your mind?
I will be really good to you.
I'll genuinely love you.
I'll love you even more from now on.
I will be really good to you.
Let's find that man…
you've been searching for.
I've become…
curious about him as well.
I want to know him.
What happened
to your hand?
I keep getting injured
whenever I take off the ring.
I'm still not used to it.
Whenever I'm in front of you…
I can't help but tense up.
I'm also scared
that I'll make a mistake.
I feel the same way.
I'm going to pick up Eun-ha.
Would you like to come with me?
Do you think
she'll like me?
Why are you laughing?
Because you are.
Dad!
Dad.
Dad, I really missed you.
Dad, did you bring me any gifts?
What?
I'm sorry. I forgot.
It's okay. You are my gift.
You're my favorite person
in this entire world.
Me…
Me too.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING FLOWER OF EVIL