SPRING 2008
POLICE
KOREAN HISTORY
POLICE OFFICER ENTRANCE EXAM
Hee-seong!
-I passed it!
-What?
I passed the exam!
Really?
I'm officially a police officer now.
-Are you that happy?
-Yes, I am.
I'm so happy
that my heart's about to burst.
Aren't you happy too?
Of course.
Guess what? My mom just told me
my dream was to become
a police officer
when I was in kindergarten.
Not only did I get a job,
I also made my childhood dream come true!
-Are you sure you're happy?
-Of course, I am.
I'll give you an hour.
Come to me in an hour.
I miss you.
Yes.
I'm Yeom Sang-cheol.
Call me Mr. Yeom.
You trust people more easily
than I expected.
It's actually the opposite.
Who you are, what your intentions are,
and what you do with what you buy from me…
None of that matters to me.
Because in our deal,
it's much more important
for you to trust me.
What does that mean?
JAERIM-DONG
Jaerim-dong?
What is he doing there?
MY HUSBAND
Hey.
Where should I meet you?
At the police station?
I'll see you at the park in front of it.
Oh, right.
Put a drop of this on your pillow
before going to bed,
and you'll sleep really well.
Let me assemble this before I go.
-What are you doing?
-It won't take long.
That's not what I meant.
It really won't take long.
Look at that.
It looks cozy, doesn't it?
You left me when I needed you the most.
I thought you had forgotten everything,
but I was wrong.
KIM MOO-JIN
I don't want to apologize
for what I did back then.
I never asked you to.
I don't need you anymore.
There's nothing you can do for me.
Back then, I ran away.
That's why
I can understand you the best right now.
I killed a man.
And like that wasn't enough,
I let Hyeon-su take the blame for it.
And the person he cherishes the most
thinks he's this gruesome murderer.
I need to reveal the truth.
So don't try to talk me out of it.
Hae-su.
-We can find another way.
-Please don't!
Hey.
Choosing to isolate yourself
and cry about it
makes you the worst person!
Do you know that?
Why is there nothing I can do for you?
If you're feeling sick,
if your toilet has clogged,
if you need to carry heavy things,
or if you suddenly get so scared
that you feel like dying,
you can call me anytime,
whether it's night or daytime.
Just call me.
Okay?
I'm neither pitying you
nor wanting to turn back time.
I…
I just don't want you
to endure it by yourself.
That's all.
DO HAE-SU
Cha Ji-won speaking.
I'd like to tell you what I couldn't
last time.
Sorry?
I know…
who the real killer of the Gagyeong-ri
Village Head Murder Case is.
What do you mean by the "real killer"?
Hyeon-su…
Do Hyeon-su is innocent.
He never killed anyone.
Someone else is responsible for it.
When it's time…
When I finish what I need to do,
I'll tell you everything
about what happened that day.
Please don't forget
this promise.
It took exactly 58 minutes.
I must've been
the only one you had.
And even now,
I must be the only one you have.
Ji-won.
Are you hurt anywhere?
Why would I be?
About that call--
I didn't mean it when I said
that I wanted to break up.
And I really didn't mean it when I said
I didn't love you anymore.
I know. I know that.
No, you don't.
I wish
you could live as me just for one day.
Then you'd know…
how much I love you.
If that was possible,
none of this would feel unfair.
There's…
something wrong,
isn't there?
Do you know what you just said means?
A human trafficking broker
is involved in a serial killing?
Are you confident?
-Do you have proof?
-Only speculations for now, sir.
-I need more time.
-More time?
What if Hwang Jeong-sun dies?
How will you find the mastermind?
The surgery just finished.
Tonight will be critical.
Damn it. How could things go this awry?
We can only start our investigation
once she regains consciousness.
Anyway, give me a call
if she gets any better.
Thanks. Bye.
Detective Choi Jae-seop
from Gangsu Police Station.
Who? Ms. Oh Bok-ja?
I'm Oh Bok-ja
from Homi Village in Gagyeong-ri.
Homi Village, Gagyeong-ri, Namchon-myeon.
Pardon? You have a photo
of Do Hyeon-su from five years ago?
-Do you not know me?
-Of course, I do, ma'am.
Hello, ma'am. How may I help you?
I just came back home
after recuperating at my daughter's place.
While cleaning,
I found a strange item.
This was…
GANGSU POLICE STATION
Why didn't I think
that Hwang Jeong-sun could've run
out the window while I was gone?
I was too sure of myself.
I'm too embarrassed to see my teammates.
Are things not going well?
The job's too tough for me.
How about you be the sole breadwinner?
I mean…
Eun-ha will be
going to school in two years.
I've been thinking
about this for some time.
How about a school in the countryside?
It's popular these days.
Once I'm done with this case…
I'd like to live a quiet life
raising her in the countryside.
What do you
think about that idea?
CHA JI-WON
POLICE AGENCY
I can still remember so clearly
how happy you were when
you first wore this around your neck.
It's okay. I'm tired of this life now.
You're a bit strange today.
No, I'm not.
You should go. I need to get back to work.
I have tons of work to do.
Bye.
I'm sorry.
I need to go.
Wait for my call at 12:00 a.m. tonight.
I'm listening.
The deal will begin at midnight tomorrow.
First, bring 100 million won
in cash to my office.
If you pick one of them,
you can buy them tomorrow.
But if you're making an order,
it'll take some time.
Do none of them interest you?
That kid.
I'll take him.
The name and photo
of Do Min-seok's accomplice.
I want those as well.
In that case…
I can't refuse.
Give our client a phone.
This is a burner.
That's how we communicate.
I'll explain the rules now,
so listen carefully.
Break the rules even by the slightest,
and I call off our deal.
If that happens,
I will get rid of all evidence
quickly and without hesitation.
And by "evidence,"
I mean people as well.
So you're telling me…
that the person I hit
with my car…
is living
as me right now?
We didn't think you'd make it.
Then…
what about me?
How should I live from now on?
What will happen
to my life?
Tell me that.
I'll live…
however you two want me…
to live.
Dad.
Can't you
ask him
to give my name back to me?
Let me…
Let me ask him in person.
Let me meet with him, please?
HEE-SEONG
Why are you calling me at this hour?
I have a favor to ask.
A favor?
I need money.
One hundred million won in cash.
What for?
I think I can catch the accomplice
in the Yeonju Serial Murder Case.
How?
I found someone who knows about him.
But he wants money in return.
Don't you want people to stop mentioning
the name "Do Hyeon-su," too?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Come by the hospital.
What is it? What does Hee…
What did Hyeon-su say?
It's nothing.
Dad.
Let me meet with him.
Never.
Why not?
He may feel bad
and give in once he sees me.
You shouldn't underestimate him.
Once he finds out that you're awake,
he won't be happy.
So…
what are you going to do?
There's nothing I can do.
We'll just
have to hope that
Lady Luck is on our side.
This time,
let's take a look at a happy face.
First, wrinkles form around your eyes.
Second, your cheeks rise.
Third,the wrinkles around your eyes move.
You're leaving already?
You didn't even sleep much.
Things are not looking good.
-Hwang Jeong-sun died.
-What?
Ji-won.
Wait.
Why aren't you asking me?
About what?
"What did you do with whom yesterday?
Why did you talk like that on the phone?"
You can tell me when you want to.
I'll always be ready to hear you out.
I'll get going.
Everything will work out.
Don't worry too much.
I'm Section Chief Yoon Sang-pil
of the violent crimes unit.
I'll brief you on the reinvestigation
of the Yeonju Serial Murder Case.
We've already given you the news release,
so I'll answer your questions now.
-Yes?
-I'm Park Jin-gyu from K News.
This news release
isn't detailed enough for us
to determine how Hwang is related
to the Yeonju serial killing.
We'd also like to hear your opinion
on whether or not this sting operation
that led to her death was reasonable.
Anything unusual
about Hwang's bank account?
Nothing much except for the fact
that she wired money
to a sanatorium once a month.
For her demented mother.
Have you found out
where she was yesterday?
I could only find out
that she was at Jaerim Market
in Jaerim-dong.
Jaerim-dong?
Yes. Why?
It's nothing.
No one has claimed her body,
let alone held a funeral for her.
Gosh.
Right, you went to Gagyeong-ri yesterday.
Right. It was nothing important.
Why did you go there?
Well…
Hello,
Detective Cha Ji-won
of the Gangsu reinvestigation team.
Hello?
I'm listening.
I'd like to report something important
regarding the Yeonju Serial Murder Case.
May I ask who's calling, please?
Do Hyeon-su.
Who?
Ji-won, who is it?
I'm listening.
Who is this calling?
Do Hyeon-su? The Do Hyeon-su?
Do Min-seok's son, Do Hyeon-su?
How many times do I need to say my name?
You bastard.
You'll be punished
for making such a prank call.
I could help you catch the accomplice.
But you're quite rude.
You're making me want to hang up.
Wait. Hold on a minute, sir.
He's Do Hyeon-su.
That's what he said.
First, do not bring any electronics
when we make the trade.
Second, I'll check the money first.
Third, once I've checked it,
you'll go to the designated place
and obtain the item.
Simple, right?
As for his photo,
I'll hand it over to you
once I check the money.
Mr. Do?
I'll put you on speaker now.
Will that be okay?
Sure.
How many detectives are there right now?
There are four.
Other than the four of you,
no one else should know about this.
Can you give me your word?
You have my word.
Just so you know,
I am recording this call as well.
What is it that you'd like to tell us?
There's a human trafficking ring
that kidnapped and handed over people
to Do Min-seok and his accomplice.
I know who they are.
Do Min-seok and his accomplice
were able to get
their victims through that ring.
And I'm making a trade with them tonight.
They'll be handing over a victim
and some information
about Do Min-seok's accomplice.
This will be your best chance
to catch them red-handed.
What time and where
are you supposed to meet them?
Now,
these are my conditions.
You probably already know, but this phone
is registered under someone else's name.
Also…
even if you succeed
in tracking my location…
it won't be easy to find me.
In order to help you put an end
to the reinvestigation of the Yeonju case,
I'll provide you
with all the information that I know.
I'd like you to swear
on the police's honor
and promise me anonymity.
In addition, I'd like you to get rid
of all the information you received
from our call once the case is solved.
Is there anything else?
No.
Hold on. That's all?
A fugitive of almost 20 years
called the police
merely for the sake of justice?
Do you expect us to buy that?
I'm not Do Min-seok's accomplice.
I just want to prove that.
I guess he really isn't the accomplice.
How can we believe him?
I mean, I don't even know
if you're the real Do Hyeon-su
or just a lunatic.
Mr. Do Hyeon-su.
Yes?
How about this?
Give us information on the person
who sold kidnapped victims to Do Min-seok.
We'll look into them,
and once we confirm
that you've told the truth,
we'll be open to more information.
And if we do receive more information,
we will agree to your demands.
Okay.
I'll give you information
on Yeom Sang-cheol.
Yeom Sang-cheol?
Please be prudent.
If he gets wind of this,
he'll kill all of the kidnapped victims.
And…
he'll kill me as well.
Hey, Ji-won.
What are you doing?
I'm on my way to buy some materials.
What is it?
Honey.
Come pick me up later.
Let's have dinner together.
Let's have those spicy noodles again.
I'm craving some.
Right, I don't think
I'll be coming home tonight.
-Why?
-I'm attending a funeral.
The father
of one of my clients passed away.
Don't go.
Why not?
Just don't. I don't want you to.
Ji-won.
The thing is…
I had a bad dream last night.
See? It's because
you're not getting much sleep.
So? Are you going to go?
Yes, I have to.
Do as you wish, then. Bye.
Ji-won.
I want
to be a decent person…
for you.
I really do.
I should get back to work now.
I'll call you…
around 10:00 p.m.
Okay.
Isn't it chilly?
Yes, but I'm okay
since the fresh air feels so nice.
Would you like a cup of warm tea?
Thank you.
How much
does she know?
We purposely hired
someone who can't read lips.
She also signed an NDA.
She wouldn't tell anyone
even if she knew something.
Hee-seong.
Last time…
you said you had to meet someone.
Who was it?
A woman.
A woman?
If I didn't get into that accident,
she and I would've met that day.
And if we did…
everything might have…
been completely different for all of us.
THREE MYSTERIES
ABOUT JUNG MI-SUK'S DISAPPEARANCE
"Three Mysteries
about Jung Mi-suk's Disappearance."
Everyone already knows this.
You're just hooking people with the title.
The important part
is that the title will hook them.
-What?
-You're really sly.
-Give it to me already.
-Give what?
The exclusive interview with Do Hae-su.
I didn't have that.
She came here and said
that she'd only speak with you.
If you didn't interview her,
what did you do?
I confessed my feelings.
Are you saying you guys are going out?
No.
-Then did she turn you down?
-She did.
It'll all work out, then.
Interview her. What's the problem?
How could you be so inhumane?
We need to meet up. It's urgent.
-I'm going out.
-Moo-jin.
I first met my husband
while interviewing him.
And you two divorced.
You told me to be prudent
about getting married because you weren't.
That's a different issue.
-Get out of here right now!
-Okay.
You are the wind.
You can go wherever you want.
On the count of three,
you'll arrive at your father's funeral.
One,
two,
three.
Ms. Do.
You have plenty of time.
Take a good look at the culprit.
It's strange.
The fingernails on his left hand…
are too short.
They look really uncomfortable.
You're doing well.
That design…
I've seen it before.
But where?
How does he look?
He's…
looking at me.
studying my face.
He's trying to remember my face.
I'm scared.
I want to get out of here.
Ms. Do, you'll wake up
on the count of three.
One, two, three.
He was trying to remember my face.
Don't you know what that means?
He's going…
to kill me.
Ms. Do, calm down.
What you just experienced
happened 18 years ago.
It's okay. You're fine.
Trust me.
I don't think
you should drive home yourself.
Is there anyone you could call?
I'm fine.
I just need a minute.
MOO-JIN
Yeom Sang-cheol, born in 1973.
He was sentenced to ten years in prison
for attempted murder and arson in 1990,
when he was 17.
But in 1997, he was paroled
in return for doing community service.
Here's what's important.
He did community service
at a place called
Deep Spring Children Clinic.
Isn't that--
Do Hyeon-su was treated there
from 1997 to 1999.
That means Yeom Sang-cheol
and Do Min-seok could've met.
That's right.
Then how could he have met
Hwang Jeong-sun?
Yeom owns an employment agency
in Jaerim-dong.
Ho-jun.
This footage was from yesterday.
She was caught on a security camera
in a parking lot across his agency.
I guess Do Hyeon-su
was telling the truth after all.
Yes, I'm positive.
How could a human-trafficking ring
be involved in a serial killing?
This is just unbelievable.
If we manage to arrest all of them,
our entire team
could get a special promotion.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
So,
we're also after Do Hyeon-su, right?
Are you feeling okay?
From now on, let me tag along.
She said you're not allowed
to drive after hypnotherapy.
I'm getting a new therapist.
She picked up my phone without asking me.
She only picked up
because my saved name
on your phone sounded very friendly.
MOO-JIN
REPORTER KIM
-Why don't you open your heart?
-Why should I do that to you?
Not to me. To your therapist.
She said you have deep-rooted suspicions
and anxiety towards others.
She said you could be
creating your own fears.
Why did Hyeon-su call?
I'm not sure.
He said he remembered something
and wanted to check yesterday.
I'm guessing it's about that.
You're going to fool Do Hyeon-su?
We promised to protect him
in exchange for more information.
There are no detectives
who protect murderers.
There's no such law either.
Aren't I right?
Well, yes.
The more times
we talk to him on the phone,
the easier we'll be able to locate him.
A few more phone calls,
and we'll be able to get
a rough idea of where he is.
We'll get the DNA samples
of men in that area
in their thirties and forties.
Then we'll compare them
to Do Hae-su's DNA.
-Since they're siblings--
-Exactly!
We'll be able to identify Do Hyeon-su.
Why are you so quiet?
I know you're totally up for this.
You called the police?
Yes.
And told them you're Do Hyeon-su?
That way, they'd move quickly.
We're running out of time.
Wait, have you gone insane?
They agreed to protect me
once they confirm
my information is true.
How can we believe that?
How can you trust the police?
They'll just put you away
after getting what they want.
Are you stupid?
You should've just received information
about the accomplice from Yeom Sang-cheol.
Once the police get involved,
he'll know that you've betrayed him.
Do you think you'll be safe?
I thought about…
what Ji-won would do if she saw those…
kidnapped victims.
I'm positive
that she would never turn
a blind eye to them.
Moo-jin, I need your help.
Perhaps, things may go awry.
We need to be prepared.
What about me?
I want to help out too. What should I do?
Nothing.
I want to help out as well.
I don't trust you enough to entrust you
with something important.
What?
You're too unpredictable.
Last time, you almost
made a mistake in front of Ji-won.
You're too emotional,
so likely to ruin our plan.
How could you hurt her like that?
I'm fine.
I know how much you love him,
but this bastard has no idea.
Hyeon-su's right, though.
It's Ji-won.
Don't pick up.
Yes?
This is Detective Cha Ji-won.
You're on speaker.
I'm Captain Lee U-cheol.
We believe what you told us.
I'll tell you one more time.
There are two steps.
First, I'll be handing
the money over to Yeom.
Once he checks the money,
he'll tell me the address
to the second destination.
Then I'll go there
and pick up the victim.
If things go awry during the first step,
there will be no second destination.
And consequently,
you won't have a chance
to raid the human trafficking scene.
So you're saying
you'll meet with Yeom first
then tell us the address
to the second destination.
After that, we'll barge in
when the victim's handed over. Right?
I'll take care of the first step,
and you'll have to take care
of the second step perfectly.
That's your only way
of apprehending Yeom's gang.
Mr. Do.
Doing this single-handedly
sounds too dangerous.
You need police backup.
Where is the first destination?
No.
I refuse to allow you to come there.
Look, Mr. Do.
We're saying we'll be keeping you safe.
Trust us. We won't arrest you.
Mr. Do.
Please trust us.
Here's what's important.
In order to track him,
we need to speak with him
on the phone many times.
When it comes to tasks like this one,
Ji-won is our best bet.
I can't do that.
Do Hyeon-su put himself at risk
and tipped us off
to save the kidnapped.
If we have to stab
such an informant in the back…
If that's our job,
then I'll just leave this team.
We're not some cheap bastards
who backstab their informants
who are working for the common good.
You can really count on us.
Your plan doesn't guarantee your safety.
That's what we're concerned about.
We're going to do
our best to protect you.
So please think about your safety first.
I won't be communicating
with the police in any way.
You should focus
on saving the kidnapped victims.
I'll focus on what I need to do.
How are our goods doing?
The elderly one isn't doing too well.
It's diabetes.
And the boy?
He's a bit exhausted, but he's okay.
-There's no problem as long as he's okay.
-Yes, sir.
-Is Hwang Jeong-sun really dead?
-Yes, I've confirmed it.
It's all for the best. We don't need
to get rid of her ourselves now.
She fell into the cops' trap.
What an idiot.
She had been so full of herself,
so I was getting annoyed, actually.
Why are you laughing?
She was still one of ours, you know?
I'm sorry, sir.
We should lie low for a while
once this deal is over.
Load the remaining goods on the ship.
Yes, sir.
I'm back, sir.
I'm happy to see him again
after a long time.
Do Min-seok and he
used to be attached at the hip.
Haven't seen him at all
these days, though.
I believe
problems that can be solved
with money are the easiest ones.
However,
I'm afraid this time
you'll only create a bigger mess,
and you certainly won't solve the problem.
I'll solve it.
Hyeon-su.
I'll give you ten times this money.
Leave without anyone knowing.
Don't worry about your family.
I'll take care of the rest.
I don't want to.
Why not?
I don't want you
to take care of my family.
What do you think of me?
I think you and I are similar.
What?
We'll both do
anything to get what we want.
And you?
Would you be okay
to let me take care of your family?
All right, then.
I somewhat feel at ease
by your frankness.
I'm very relieved that you and I want
the same thing.
I should get going.
All right.
Hyeon-su.
Goodbye.
Who on earth tipped you off?
I can't tell you, sir.
You refuse to tell me who it is,
yet you still want backup?
Yes, sir. I'd appreciate
as many men as possible.
To solve the Yeonju Serial Murder Case
once and for all, we must
catch Yeom Sang-cheol.
U-cheol, look me in the eye.
Are you absolutely sure about this?
Ji-won.
I'll never say this again,
so listen carefully.
I'm truly glad that you're on this team.
I realized it today once again.
What is this?
You seem a bit moved.
You're so slow-witted.
That's not it.
She's feeling nauseous because of
your unctuous words.
Ji-won, it's okay. You can vomit.
You little… Come here.
We'll talk after I take this.
Hey.
I'm calling about the formatted recorder.
The data recovery's done.
-Yes?
-I have a question.
Nam Sun-gil's wife gave me your bag.
And I got to listen to the recorder.
Can you tell me…
whose voice that is?
-If you don't want to--
-It's my mom.
Pardon?
It was in 1997,
right before my mom went missing.
She gave it to me saying
it was a recording of her voice.
My father reported her missing,
and the police took her belongings.
I didn't tell them about it
because I was afraid
they'd take it away from me.
You must have…
truly loved your mother.
I was diagnosed
as someone
who lacked empathy by a psychiatrist.
It's impossible for me
to feel such an emotion.
Then why did you hold onto it
for such a long time?
I'm afraid I don't know.
I've never seen a doctor
regarding the reason behind that behavior,
so I cannot explain it.
I…
don't want to lie to you.
Mr. Do.
Yes?
Please…
don't get hurt.
Pardon?
Goodbye.
I'll call you…
around 10:00 p.m.
I believe the sound on the cassette
encouraged and set him off
to be aggressive and violent.
Detective Cha?
Why didn't you know?
Sorry?
Why did you never consider
the possibility that the cassette might be
from his own mother?
Ms. Cha, I'm not following you.
His mother had just gone missing
when you treated him.
Then it should've been obvious
what that young boy was obsessed with.
Any normal kid would've done the same.
-Ms. Cha.
-You should've known that.
You were the only one
who could help him back then.
-But--
-At least you should've known!
Why are you all asking me for help?
You even have your own forensics team.
I hate leaving any records behind.
By the way, "you all"?
Someone else was here?
Yes, the detective
you brought along with you last time.
The female detective.
Cha Ji-won? Why was she here?
Come on. I can't do this work
for long if I tell things like that.
What a professional.
This is exactly why I like you.
Anyway…
He is quite strict.
He hates it
when things don't go as planned.
So he's obsessive about plans.
I can't wait to see the headline
of your article, Reporter Kim Moo-jin.
-Step on it.
-Hey.
Will we be able
to get there before they do?
Yes, for sure.
How so?
First, I'd like to thank Team Two
for backing us up.
Let me brief you on our operation.
As you all know, there will be
a human trafficking deal tonight.
But first, let me tell you
about the human trafficking ring.
Hyeon-su.
How did Do Hyeon-su
turn into Baek Hee-seong?
Forget about everyone else.
How did you fool your wife?
-Hey, Moo-jin.
-Yes? I'm listening.
I won't judge.
Ji-won doesn't know anything about me.
About my past or how I'm not normal.
Hyeon-su.
How did Do Hyeon-su
turn into Baek Hee-seong?
I'm against it.
The very fact that
you're obsessing over a ghost like him
proves that we're
completely lost on this case.
He's not the accomplice.
I'm sure. Trust me on this.
Mr. Do.
Please trust us.
We're going to do
our best to protect you.
So please think about your safety first.
Why are you staring at me?
Did you have to say that to Hae-su?
You don't know how hurt she was, do you?
Of course, you don't. How would you?
It's just too dangerous for her.
Then you should've said so.
That it's too dangerous,
so you can't let her help you.
The more dangerous it is,
the more she is willing to help out.
What? Then what about me?
Why have you dragged me
into this dangerous situation?
I asked you,
but you're the one who made the choice.
You're right.
Why the hell did I agree to help you out?
Because I asked you for help
in front of Hae-su.
You never say no to me when she's around
because you want her to like you.
What? So are you saying
that you manipulated me or something?
Yes. I've been doing it
since we were young,
and I'll probably keep doing it.
GREEN SILICONE BRACELET
2019 ILSIN HOSPITAL 21ST OPENING CEREMONY
FOR INTERNATIONAL MEDICAL VOLUNTEERING
ILSIN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
MEDICAL VOLUNTEER
Yeom targeted individuals
who either had no family
or had a history
of running away from home.
It's highly likely
that the currently kidnapped victims
have never been reported missing.
Get out.
What?
Get out now.
You have no right to be here.
-Detective Choi.
-What's wrong?
What is it?
Detective Choi.
Let go. Let go, and we'll talk.
Jae-seop, let go of her.
What are you doing?
You knew, didn't you?
About what?
You knew everything, didn't you?
How could you?
How could you of all people do that?
You knew everything.
And all this time…
you've been manipulating us.
You have
deceived us.
Mr. Do.
Please…
don't get hurt.
What you're feeling right now isn't real.
He would never harm other people.
Do you have proof?
I want to solve this case
more than anyone else.
Take yourself off the case.
It's only right.
I'm sorry for visiting so late at night.
My name is Do Hae-su.
You can't go home.
Run as far as you can tonight.
Detective Choi has proof
that you're Do Hyeon-su.
Hide somewhere even I can't find
and don't you ever come back to me.