[Weaving A Tale of Love 2]
[Episode 22]
Here comes the second glass of wine,
It's for thanking you for rescuing Fuxian
and saving Song'er,
Our Qu family
could finally get rid of the shackles
of the Princess,
Song'er,
you must make sure to express your gratitude
to Senior Official Pei and Madam Kudi,
They're our family's life savers,
Song'er,
Thank you, Senior Official Pei,
Thank you, Madam Kudi,
You're too polite, young master,
Chongyu, Lady Jing,
You two should also thank Senior Official Pei
and his wife heartily,
I've long considered Liuli as a sister,
and saying thanks would be too formal,
But I still want to thank you
for risking your life
for saving my sister-in-law and Song'er,
Let's go,
Sit here,
Shouyue,
thank you,
Minister,
you're welcome,
Protector-General, Minister,
please forgive my rudeness,
My wife and I
would like to propose a toast to Prefect Wang,
Prefect Wang,
we're grateful for your assistance that night,
If it wasn't for you,
our dilemma in Xizhou
would not have been resolved,
If it wasn't for you,
we would not have been able to settle here,
Prefect Wang,
you are the benefactor of both me and Shouyue,
I pay my respect to Prefect Wang,
Junmeng,
I treated you first as my brother-in-law,
then as my brother,
From this day forward,
I'll see you as a brother first,
then my brother-in-law,
You saved my family,
You saved my son,
and you also saved
the Senior Official and his wife,
You kept us a good official
for our people in Xizhou,
A toast for you
along with the Senior Official's couple,
Drink it up,
So many people are toasting to you,
and you're still pretending over there,
Without you,
I don't yet know when
I'll be able to see my lovely grandson,
Father-in-law,
I toast to you,
I,,,I'll drink it up,
Good, good,
Chongyu,
Brother, I'll drink it up,
Senior Official, Madam Kudi,
I have caused a lot of offense in the past,
I'll drink it up,
Aunt, I'll drink it up,
Junmeng, don't drink too much,
Young master, let's have a drink,
Sit down for me,
Come, let us all raise our cups together
to thank the Senior Official Pei and his wife,
Respect to the Senior Official's couple,
[Protector-General's Mansion]
Come, come, Make way, make way,
Take a look at the trinket,
Sanniang from An family requests an audience,
Master,
Please let her in,
Sister,
There's no outsider in this room,
why the need for such formalities?
Please come in,
My visit this time is to
report important matters to you,
Senior Official,
Sister, thank you for
having gathered so much grain and fodder,
I can't conceal anything from you,
From the past half month,
many merchants and families have rushed here
from various counties and villages,
which has indeed saved us
quite a bit of effort,
The weather is quite good this year,
The harvest in the counties of Xizhou
is also quite good,
and I've heard good news
from places like Dunhuang and Qiuci,
For now, we closed the deal
for 100,000 dan of grain,
More than 50,000 dan have also been put
into the warehouse,
The remaining 40,000 dan
are estimated to be delivered continuously
by the end of the month,
Most of the fodder has also been collected,
That's great,
It's just that
everyone's granaries are almost full,
If more grains are sent here,
I'm afraid we can't hold any more,
I don't know
when we can start using the government granary,
The granary will be opened for grain collection
in half a month,
When the military warehouse collects grain,
we pay half of the money to each business,
The other half will be paid
when they transport the grains
to the military warehouse,
The payment can be redeemed with
the military warehouse's expense slips,
What merchants fear the most
is the accumulation of unpaid goods,
Moreover,
purchasing such a large quantity of grain
requires a lot of money,
If one can truly
receive half of the payment as agreed
after half a month,
the pressure would be greatly reduced,
Sister,
you're truly a person of meticulous thoughts,
So many detailed matters
have all been arranged neatly,
It's all because of you,
It's nothing,
This was indeed a rare opportunity
not to be missed,
Even our An family has a solid foundation
in Xizhou,
but I have only been here twice,
And this time
almost all the wealthy merchants of Xizhou
participated,
Although there are difficulties
this time,
but as long as thing are carefully arranged,
I believe
the status of the An family
in the business world
will rise with the tide,
Master, Minister Qu invites you
to his residence,
and he says it's about the Military Commander
of Congshan Route,
General Su has sent a staff officer over,
General Su's people sure arrived quickly,
This General Su
is not the one you think of,
Senior Official Pei,
you are late,
You should be penalized,
Protector-General,
Minister,
Shouyue,
I didn't expect us to meet again
this soon,
It turns out to be Brother Ziyu,
This is truly a pleasant surprise,
You have followed General Su to Yizhou?
My father and I are now exiled to Yizhou,
All thanks to you,
Exactly,
I didn't expect the Emperor's grace
to be this immense,
He granted me to serve
under my father's command,
My father is now the Military Commander
of Congshan Route,
I came here this time
to supervise the military readiness in Xizhou,
I'm afraid it may disturb your watch
for several days
I couldn't ask for more,
For the matter of supply and tax in Xizhou,
just ask me,
These matters are all entrusted to Shouyue,
I am unaware of any,
However, if you want to know
where to find the finest wine,
or the most gorgeous performance,
then I'm your guy,
You guys keep going,
Just now, Chongyu mentioned he know nothing
about the money and grain,
I thought it was just his modest talk,
But I didn't expect that Pei Xingjian truly
had the means to isolate the Qu's family,
Shouyue,
let's talk about official matters first
before anything personal,
Okay,
I wonder how much supplies have been prepared
by Xizhou
for the army,
50,000 dan of millet and corn
have been prepared,
along with 10,000 carts of forage and grain,
Everything will be ready
by the end of the month,
Once the army is here,
we can immediately transport everything
to the military warehouse,
Shouyue, you're not joking, right?
The population of Xizhou is nearly 40,000,
How can you only prepare 50,000 dan of corn?
Yizhou's population is less than 10,000,
yet more than 20,000 dan have been prepared,
The expedition of the army to the west
is a serious matter for our country,
Do not joke about this;
take it seriously
and do not treat it as child's play,
Ziyu, there're things you don't know,
Yizhou is a place where the land is vast,
and the population is sparse,
Xizhou is
Crowded but with less land,
I have been struggling for the past two months,
Buying grain at a high price,
engaging traders,
I have tried all kinds of methods,
I was prepared for 100,000 dan
in the beginning,
But now
I could only be certain about 50,000 dan,
If you add the rent from the summer harvest
and the back-up supply in the granary,
it's about 60,000 approximately,
To be honest,
I also know this is a difficult matter,
But this time, the army has 100,000 people,
Chief Administrator Cheng issued
a military order to my father a few days ago,
Before the arrival of the army,
the three states of Xi, Ting, and Yi must
prepare the army rations
in the amount of three dan per household,
If there're any violations,
the military law will surely be discussed,
Three dan per household,
That's a total of 120,000 dan then,
Don't worry too much, Shouyue,
My father knows that you and I go way back,
therefore,
he specifically sent me to
lend you a helping hand,
I came with 300 elite solders this time
by order,
Once the grain is stored,
should there be a shortage,
I will then dispatch my troops
to levy grain from the villages,
Master Su,
I'll definitely do my best
to hand in the corns,
But 120,000 dan
have indeed exceeded the burden
of the people of Xizhou,
You really have a kind heart,
I respect that,
However, the military orders are unyielding,
there's no room for negotiation,
You go ahead and collecting grain as you could,
If it could be delivered in full,
that's the best,
If there's any shortage,
I certainly will not sit by
and watch General Cheng
have you subjected to the military law
even if it means bearing a bad name,
I have taken Ziyu's good intentions to heart,
but could you grant me a few more days?
The army is about to arrive,
Even if I want to help you delay
for a few more days,
but the military law is ruthless,
You better not harbor any wishful thinking,
Reporting to the Protector-General,
the plum juice is ready,
Is it ready?
Okay,
Now that you two have done talking business,
then let us
go together and have a taste
of plum juice from Meizhong County,
Protector-General Qu,
I will go and instruct the subordinates first
to hurry up in collecting grains
from all places,
Ziyu, I will take my leave first,
When I have time,
I will surely treat you to a good drink,
You're indeed diligent in government affairs
I am impressed,
It seems that Senior Official Pei is too busy,
Ziyu,
let's go try it together,
Let's go,
120,000 dan,
This is unreasonable,
The 100,000 dan of grain my people collected
in Xizhou
were already the work of miracles,
If we are to collect another 20,000,
it's not that we can't collect them,
We could collect some more
if we transport from other places now,
However, time is limited,
First of all, too much money will be spent,
Secondly, it's somewhat risky,
Listen to me first, sister,
I know that collecting grain locally in Xizhou
is the cheapest and lowest-risk way,
But nowadays, besides those wealthy households,
ordinary households do not have much left,
Even if we want to collect,
we can only do so by force,
I did the calculation,
The grain silos in Xizhou areas
have a few thousand dan of grain left,
If we include what comes out
of the official and public fields,
we can barely collect 10,000 dan,
But for the remaining 10,000 dan,
sister, do you have any plans?
In fact,
we 110,000 dan of grain
this time,
What do you mean?
You also know that
there're many rules about the army warehouse,
It's hard to deal with those
who are difficult to talk,
There's a chance
that they will deduct 20 percent from you,
There's nothing we can do about it,
Therefore, when collecting,
we left some margin,
Fortunately, this year's prices are 20 percent
higher than previous years,
so those farmers did not really mind,
if you can make sure
that the measurement is fair
when it comes to storage,
I'm sure that these 110,000 dan
might still have a surplus,
120,000 dan of military rations,
This far exceeds the capacity of the people
in Xizhou,
As Su Nanjin said,
he will send troops to the countryside
to collect grains,
The meaning behind these words
is so cruel,
This matters to all the people in Xizhou,
We cannot stand by and watch,
For the shortage,
I will try to make up for it
from the public field
and suspend the grain allowances
of our officials in Xizhou,
The rest,,,
I'll try to buy from the surrounding areas,
What's the matter?
I've heard that Su Haizheng,
the Military Commander of Congshan Route,
has sent his son Su Nanjin
to supervise the grain collection in Xizhou,
Did he give you any hard time about it?
Given Su Nanjin's narrow-mindedness
and his vicious nature,
of course he made big demand
in terms of numbers,
No wonder,
Back in Liangzhou,
Su Nanjin
thought he killed me, the Senior Official's wife,
without anyone noticing,
but now I am alive and well,
Besides,
he submitted a document impeaching you,
which would surely offend the Emperor,
Therefore, he and his father
suffered,
How could he not understand
that he has fallen into your trap
even if he's stupid?
His trip to Xizhou
made him face his enemy again,
He'll not let us go,
What happened in Liangzhou
is his own fault for his earlier misdoings,
He wants to use public office
for personal revenge,
and let's see
whether they have the capability or not,
Regarding the matter of gathering grain,
do you have a countermeasure ready?
Rest assured; I have my own plans,
But for you,
Su Nanjin already hates you thoroughly,
Now with him in Xizhou,
although the chances of you two
seeing each other are slim,
you still need to be very careful,
I will also be extra careful around him,
Don't worry anymore,
[The Great Buddha Temple]
Shouyue,
Shouyue, such a coincidence,
- Protector-General,
- You also come to the Great Buddha Temple?
My wife had a sudden feeling in her heart,
and she said she wanted to come
and pay her respects,
It turns out that Madam Kudi wishes to come
and worship the Buddha,
The same for me,
Master Juexuan is coming,
Amitabha,
Master,
The Senior Official and the Protector-General
have come together today,
Good, good,
Come, please,
Okay, please,
When I came to the Great Buddha Temple
to offer incense recently,
I have not seen the miracle
of the Bronze Buddha shedding tears again,
So did I,
I hope to witness the miracle one more time,
But despite many attempts at offering incense,
my wish has not been fulfilled,
Could it be
that my intentions are not sincere enough?
This Bronze Buddha no longer sheds tears,
It must be because our great Tang is peaceful
and prosperous,
and the weather in Xizhou is favorable,
The Bronze Buddha
no longer needs to pity the world,
Therefore, no more tears,
That makes sense,
The Buddha compassionately looks upon
all sentient beings,
Now, everyone lives in peace and happiness
in Xizhou,
It doesn't make sense
that the Bronze Buddha would shed tears,
Yes,
[The Great Hall]
I hope that Gods will not shed tears anymore,
May the people in Xizhou
live and work in peace and contentment,
Our Tang Dynasty is prosperous,
and the people are at peace,
The Buddha has mercy,
I pray sincerely to the Buddha,
Please protect our people in Xizhou,
The tea made by the Master is excellent
May I bother for a cup today?
I wonder if it will disturb you,
I couldn't have asked for more,
So, I'll bask
in the Senior Officials' light too
and ask you for a cup of tea, Master,
For sure,
Please go ahead, Protector-General,
Please go ahead, Senior Official,
- Please,
- Please, my lady,
Master Juexuan,
I came here today
to ask for a favor,
You must also be aware
that
Xizhou is now facing an unforeseeable crisis,
I wonder if the Great Buddha Temple
is willing to offer kindness,
contributing money and effort
for the people in Xizhou,
Senior Official,
you hold the secret of the Bronze Buddha,
Do you intend to use it as leverage
and forcing the Great Buddha Temple
to pay military provisions?
Amitabha,
Thank you for your support, Protector-General,
I believe
If Senior Official Pei wants to use the secret
of the bronze Buddha to blackmail,
he'd not have deliberately guided
public opinion just now by
dispelling the believers' expectations
of the Buddha shedding tears,
The Master is wise,
If the Master wishes to know the secret
behind the tearing Bronze Buddha,
I'll tell you without reservation,
It is not difficult for the Master
if he wants to know the secret,
The difficulty lies in
knowing how to conduct oneself afterwards,
A monk does not tell lies,
Let alone a high monk
of great virtue and esteem like the Master,
If the Master were to reveal to the devotees
after knowing
the secret of the tearing Bronze Buddha,
it would destroy the sanctity of the Temple
in the hearts of the believers,
If the Master wishes to preserve
the sanctity of the Great Buddha Temple,
then he must lie to the believers,
I wonder if you have thought of a solution
for this kind of dilemma, Master,
Amitabha,
Don't be aware,
Don't listen or ask,
Let the secret of the tearing Bronze Buddha
hide in the Great Buddha Temple,
It shall never to appear again,
This is true wisdom,
I here thank
the Senior Official's couple
for your kind intentions,
You two
indeed have great wisdom,
At the sacred land of Buddhism,
we hold compassion at heart,
However, this matter of money and grain
is indeed the intrinsic duty of us
imperial officials,
How can one shift the blame to others?
The Senior Official is truly dedicated
to working out plans for the people,
I'm also deeply impressed,
However, today's matter
was indeed too abrupt,
Rest assured, Master,
Regarding such government affairs,
my family will certainly bear
all the responsibility,
We'll neither let the people in Xizhou
feel uneasy,
nor disturb the pureness
of the Buddhist monastery,
Amitabha,
Thank you for your kindness, Protector-General,
Also, thank you for your family
for taking the responsibility,
But the matter of military provisions
concerns thousands of civilians in Xizhou,
The Buddha has mercy,
The Great Buddha Temple
should also bear its responsibility,
In this last half-month period,
the merits donated by the believers
are already more than 40,000 strings of coins,
The temple
is willing to donate them as military supplies,
On behave of the people in Xizhou,
thank you, Master,
The Great Buddha Temple
has been worshiped
by the believers of Xizhou for many years,
It should be so,
Protector-General,
there's no need to worry anymore,
Pei Xingjian
directly asked Master Juexuan,
hoping that the Great Buddha Temple
will make a move
to solve the problem of grain supplies,
Master Juexuan surprisingly agreed all at once,
And he decided firmly to make such a donation,
Father, you went to the Great Buddha Temple,
I know
I shouldn't go,
but in my heart,,,
As a father, I've wasted half my life,
In terms of great talent and strategy,
I'm far inferior to your grandfather,
In terms of charisma and popularity,
I'm also far inferior to your uncle,
The only thing I can do
is just
knowing how to lose,
I always lose,
In my heart--
Father,
in fact, you're not afraid to lose,
Father, you just fear
that people think
our Qu family has actually fallen into
a situation where we have to rely on outsiders
for everything,
am I right?
Father,
I actually believe
that up to now, our family's
the greatest achievement is you,
It's not the grand strategy of my grandfather,
or the charm and esteem of my uncle,
But rather, it is you, father,
because you know
when we should admit defeat,
Back then, Gaochang surrendered to the Tang
for the sake of the common people,
to prevent them from suffering
the horrors of war,
And father,
you also know
how to lose,
In this way, we can make sure Xizhou,
our family,
won't suffer from Advisor Su's hardships
because of the provisions,
And it's just because
I didn't learn your way of losing
and has made you worry so much about me before,
I made you do
so many
things that shouldn't have been done,
Father,
I know that
all these years,
have been constantly putting yourself
at a disadvantage
for Xizhou and for me,
As long as it's for the good of people
in Xizhou,
and for you as well,
this bit of hardship I endure
didn't count for much,
They didn't count for much,
Here you are,
No need,
Alright,
Then you
will work together
with Senior Official Pei,
Pei Shouyue,
for the sake of Xizhou and me,
And you two will
advance and retreat together,
Protector-General,
Advisor Su requests a meeting,
Let's go have a look,
Master Su,
I'm here to see you, Protector-General,
If there're places
where my son didn't take care of you well
in the past few days,
please forgive me,
Please come inside,
Protector-General Qu, please wait,
Let's make the long story short,
Senior Official Pei sent someone to inform me
that the military provisions have been prepared
and can be put into the warehouse tomorrow,
He invited me to go and inspect
and take over the matter
of the grain warehouse,
I wonder if this is your order,
This is how it works,
Senior Official Pei
is in charge of the finances and grain supplies
in Xizhou,
Since he said it's all set,
then it must be ready,
I think there's no need
to involve two masters for one matter,
It's bothersome to trouble you this time,
but it's to avoid
the hassle of going to the military warehouse
again in the future,
Protector-General,
you're unaware of this matter?
I've made you laugh,
The Senior Official is cautious and diligent,
He has always been proper in his dealings,
I
also take the opportunity to be lazy,
Since this is the case,
I understand now,
I'll take my leave then,
I'll walk you out,
I don't know
what trigger Pei Shouyue pulls recently,
He's able to make the merchants in Xizhou
help him to gather grains and fodder
before and after the saddle,
I suppose he must have been confident
since he let me go tomorrow,
However,
this matter of gathering grains
is not the work of one day,
Ziyu, you are saying,,,
Chongyu,
would you like to go see a good show tomorrow?
I have official duties tomorrow unfortunately,
So be it,
Just wait here for the news,
Giddy up!
Master Su is indeed bold and ruthless,
It seems the information I heard is correct,
They intend to tamper with the amount
and deduct 20 percent,
What do you plan to do?
Father,
I'd like to inform Shouyue about this,
Okay,
Come, give me a hand,
Come on, push hard,
Erlang,
- Alright,
- Be careful,
Put it here, over here,
Long time no see, how have you been?
Slow down,
- Okay,
- Slow down, slow down,
Come on, lend a hand,
- Everything is here,
- Let's go,
Push harder,
It's done,
You're short by twenty percent, Add more,
What's the matter?
How could this be?
This bag clearly holds the amount of one stone,
There can only be more,
How could there be less?
You have a lot of nerve,
You deceitful merchants dare to defraud
and deceive the military warehouse,
You really don't want to live,
Send someone here,
Yes, yes,
Drag him down for me,
Give him a severely beat
with twenty military canes,
- Yes, yes,
- You!
Who are you calling a deceitful merchant?
I'm the Commandant of Militant Cavalry
of the Tang,
Who dares to touch me?
Don't do this, Master Su,
Zhang Erlang is not from a merchant family,
He's from a prominent family in Xizhou,
He was appointed as a titled official
due to his military merits years ago,
He must not be subjected to punishment,
Step down,
Since you are an official of the Tang,
you should abide by the laws of the Tang,
Can this matter of military provisions
be manipulated?
If you continue to make such a noise,
delaying the military provisions
from entering the warehouse,
even if I can tolerate you,
the military law will not tolerate you,
Retreat quickly!
After handing over these four vessels,
take the rest back for me,
Don't be angry, Erlang, w
We will advance and retreat with you,
We'll advance and retreat together with Erlang,
Commandant Zhang is even braver than I thought,
If I allow these people to take the grain away
today,
opening the granary for grain collection
would become a joke,
It would be a slap in my face first,
Guards!
No one is allowed to leave!
Master Su, that won't do,
That won't do, Master Su,
Today's grain collection is a military affair,
For those who delay the military grain
from entering the warehouse,
don't blame me for dealing with it
in accordance with military law,
Brother Ziyu,
what's the cause of this excitement?
Senior Official Pei, Senior Official Pei,
Shouyue,
why are you late today?
Ziyu,
I went to handle the money and grain affairs
today,
Sorry for being late, please forgive me,
Please,
Shouyue,
the merchants and titled officials from Xizhou
are indeed very bold,
I collect grain
using the official measuring vessels,
and they even complain that it's too much
and refuse to submit the grain,
They really treat it as their own backyard,
huh?
Regarding those who despise the military law,
what do you think should be done
about the situation?
Despising the military law?
I'm here to see you, Senior Official,
The Senior Official's insight is clear,
How dare we despise the military law?
It's just that we clearly measured,
and here's a bit more than one dan of grain,
Yet during the handover,
it was a full 20 percent short,
- I don't know how to deliver this grain,
- Exactly,
Thank you for the great help in this matter,
Commandant Zhang,
Rest assured, Commandant Zhang,
The measuring vessels
are made under the court's regulation,
If someone deliberately
increases or reduces the volume,
they should be treated as thieves
according to the law,
If someone is negligent in supervision,
they should also be held accountable,
Master Su would never violate the law
since he knows it so well,
Shouyue, you're ignorant of certain matters,
The official vessels collected for grain
this time
were all taken out of the military warehouse
by myself,
They had always been used
by the military warehouse,
These ignorant troublemakers
even dare to levy accusations,
I have military orders to bear,
I must deal with it strictly,
Military rations concern the morale
of the troops,
Those who disturb the morale of my troops
shall be execute without mercy,
If Commandant Zhang is determined
to have a taste of the military law,
then I will have no choice but to oblige you,
Young master,
what you said doesn't makes sense,
This so-called military ration
is grain
that has entered the military warehouse,
All the grain carts here
have been purchased voluntarily by us,
The military has not paid any money,
nor have we signed a contract,
How did they become military grain already?
- That's true,
- If they collect every grain they see,
is this called collection or robbery?
Exactly,
This officer title of mine
was earned with a knife and gun
on the battlefield,
This grain was grown
in my own household fields,
Should this grain be turned over
to the military granary
or kept for personal use,
can't I make my own decision?
Whether this official measuring vessel
is large or small,
once sent to the Department of Treasury
in Chang'an for verification, it will be known,
I just don't believe it,
The world is such a big place,
and there has to be a place
that can discern this principle,
Ziyu,
this is a seventh-rank official,
If there's no solid evidence of guilt,
you can't just beat or kill him,
Arrest this one who is spreading wild rumors,
- Yes,
- How to you arrest someone?
Wait,
Are you going to protect her?
Exactly,
Senior Official Pei is really good,
Yes, he speaks for us,
By the time the army arrives,
Shouyue, please also take responsibility
for the lack of grain and fodder,
Ziyu, what you said was wrong,
It's exactly because we can't afford to
not having grains ready when the army arrives,
We shouldn't harm these merchants,
Think about it,
The grain and fodder in this training field now
is not even a tenth
of the required army's provision,
It's easy to beat or kill the merchants,
but where will you find
the remaining food and fodder?
If this matter causes a delay
in collecting the grain,
I deserve to die of course,
But Ziyu,
I'm afraid
you won't be able to escape censure either,
You would rather be short of a few vessels
than not protecting them,
then I won't stop you,
I dare not ask too much
about this grain collection matter,
We can only wait until the army arrives,
We will discuss it then,
The matter of grain collection is significant,
Indeed, not a moment can be delayed,
We don't have the time,
The only plan at the moment
is to make the merchants willingly comply,
The military grain must not be short
in weight either,
Only in this way
could the two of us fully complete this task,
Senior Official Pei, do you have a clever plan?
Nothing clever,
I suddenly remembered
that it should not have been you and me
collecting the grain today,
Once the person
who's supposed to collect the grain arrives,
let alone these merchants,
not a single person
in the entire Xizhou
dares to shortchange,
I wonder who this person is,
It's almost the time,
and he should be arriving soon,
Ziyu, please wait a moment,
[Drill Ground]
I write my longing for you in Spring
The red plum is in full bloom like you
By the pond, next to the willow trees
I write a poem
to tell our story from the past
The years pass by like a bird
The destiny always comes with regrets
Who could relieve my pain of love
Outside the pavilion, by the bridge
Under the moonlight,
we parted at the doorstep
I've endured hardship
to tell our lingering story
Remembrance of past things
As time goes by, seasons change
Flowers wither, and winter has come
Years pass by, and we're young no more
A snowy day, someone sings a sad song
Against the window,
I had a drink for pleasure
The moon still hangs in the sky,
but I'm no longer in the mood
It's quite and cold outside,
but I grab my pen again
The destiny always comes with regrets
Who could relieve my pain of love
Outside the pavilion, by the bridge
Under the moonlight,
we parted at the doorstep
I've endured hardship
to tell our lingering story
Remembrance of past things
As time goes by, seasons change
Flowers wither, and winter has come
Years pass by, and we're young no more
Winter comes again, and flowers wither
Who could relieve my pain of love
I look outside, like the poems asking
My love, have you
found someone good for you
Remembrance of past things
As time goes by, seasons change
Flowers wither, and winter has come
Years pass by, and we're young no more
Winter comes again, and flowers wither
Who could relieve my pain of love
I look outside, like the poems asking
My love, have you
found someone good for you