[Weaving A Tale of Love 2]
[Episode 12]
Is the Protector-General's
acting a bit over the top?
Shouyue, let me toast your second cup,
Sit down,
I don't think so,
- Look,
- Come on, Senior Official,
It's quite sincere,
You're all seeing to it, huh?
- Try this meat,
- I'll just have a drink,
Senior Official, I toast to you,
Isn't that a bit beneath his dignity?
Approachable and humble, Respectable!
Chongyu
- The third cup,
- Come on,
What, are you talking about
my grandfather-in-law, your father-in-law
having a guilty conscience?
Nonsense, I absolutely didn't mean that,
- Eat more vegetables,
- Okay,
I'd like to propose a toast to you as well,
Mr, Pei,
Sincerity,
Senior Official,
Madam, try these dates,
They're particularly sweet,
Madam, try our pears here,
Madam Kudi, this plate
of grapes in front of you
is extremely delicious, Have a taste,
Please, try this,
Thank you very much,
[Qu Zhizhan's Concubine, Madam Qi]
You may not be aware,
Madam Kudi, before marrying Senior Official Pei
was a master at the Bureau of Garment,
famous for her clever mind and skillful hands,
It is said that the dresses made by you
were greatly favored by Lady Wu,
Qu is well-informed,
Liuli is merely interested in dressmaking,
And Lady Wu shows favoritism,
Madam Kudi,
I wonder what kind of makeup is fashionable
in Chang'an now?
Can you tell us about it?
Yes,
The trendiest makeup now is probably
the bold green eyebrows,
Diagonal red should be drawn thinner,
Decorate the eyebrows with golden flowers
to accentuate the color,
It's so lively,
You didn't even call out for me,
How did she come back?
Weren't you going hunting
with Captain Yan and the others?
It was no fun with them, so I came back early,
So you are Kudi Liuli,
And this is?
[Qu Chongyu's Sister, Wife of Wang Junmeng, Qu Jingtang]
I am Qu Chongyu's sister, the wife of Wang Junmeng,
You may call me Lady Jing,
So you are the Madam of Ming's Mansion,
Lady Jing, since you're back,
let's eat together,
Shouyue, let me toast one more drink to you,
- Yeah,
- Thank you, Protector-General,
Lady Jing was here just now,
What a good drink tolerance!
You didn't tell her anything, did you?
No, I just said that
I don't like Kudi Liuli,
I really don't like,
I heard my elder brother has had a tough time
with you throughout the journey,
I came out of curiosity just to see
what you look like,
Have I made you satisfied, Madam?
It is better to see a person in the flesh
than to know him by repute,
I thought
you would be a woman with double-pupil,
a blue face and fangs,
and capable of lifting a cauldron,
But now it seems you're very ordinary,
However,
you are better looking than all of them,
Thank you for your compliment, Madam,
How delicate you are!
You don't seem like someone
who practices martial arts,
The Princess sent so many people to kill you,
If it were me,
it would be difficult to escape unharmed,
How did you and Pei Xingjian manage to do it?
Lady Jing, what are you babbling about here?
Which Princess? I haven't even heard of her,
If you make a fuss like this again,
I will call for Protector-General,
Alright, stop pressuring me
with Father all the time,
I'm leaving right now,
You're good, I like you a lot,
Come to my place another day,
Teach me that makeup,
I will certainly visit,
Alright then, you guys eat slowly, I'm leaving,
I'm giving you those two chickens,
no need to thank me,
She has been spoiled by her father,
I've made a fool of myself in front of you,
I'm really sorry,
I actually find her
quite naive and straightforward,
She is a very interesting person,
Senior Official Pei,
What's happening here?
Let's have another drink,
Drink,
The Senior Official has had too much to drink,
Someone help the Senior Official to rest,
Senior Official Pei can't hold his liquor,
Take it slow,
Have another drink,
Let's call it a day for now,
Slow down,
If you're that worried, go check on it,
I… I'll take a look,
Senior Official had a bit too much to drink,
He has been helped to the guest room to rest,
Got drunk?
She has already left,
There's no need to look for her anymore,
Lady, Madam Kudi,
I heard that Shouyue has gotten drunk,
is it true?
He's Happy today, and drank a few more glasses,
Minister has already ordered someone
to help Senior Official back to guest room to rest,
Madam, I want to see Shouyue,
Alright, I'll have someone take you there now,
Lady, Lady Jing hasn't caused any trouble,
has she?
[Qu's Residence]
Madam,
Come in,
Madam, the hangover soup is here,
You've worked hard,
How did I not notice before
my Liuli is so virtuous?
You are fooling me again,
How did I fool you?
Those officials in the Xizhou
asked me to drink one after another,
I have drunk at least a pound or two,
If I drink any more, I will really be drunk,
At first night in the Xizhou,
do you want to listen to a drunkard
talking all night nonsense?
I'll get you some sobering soup,
I'll do it myself,
Your body is finally a bit warmer,
Xizhou seems even hotter than Chang'an,
The weather here has always been hot and windy,
This house, being warm in winter
and cool in summer, is quite nice,
Moreover, the windows are unusually tall
and the walls are remarkably thick,
The effect of sound insulation
and thermal retention must also be very good,
Protector-General Qu
receives us with such enthusiasm,
I wonder what he wants to do,
Since we are here,
we might as well settle down,
No matter what tactics they use,
we will simply counter every move,
By the way, I saw Wang Junmeng restless today,
And he kept glancing at
the curtains of the female guests,
Nothing happened, right?
It was that darn peacock
that had a surprise for me,
What tricks is he playing this time?
Nothing much really,
He just wanted me to meet his sister,
Have you met Qu Jingtang?
I've heard this girl is arrogant,
willful, and domineering,
She is a villainous woman
that everyone in the Xizhou avoids,
She didn't do anything to you, did she?
Indeed, she is quite a troublesome character,
However, I can still handle her,
It seems that she quite likes me,
It would be wise
to have less contact with such a person,
Don't worry, I know how to handle it,
But that dead peacock,
He's full of cunning tricks,
Be careful,
You are not allowed to mention him again,
From now on, you should think of nothing,
Do not think about anyone,
Liuli,
Why haven't you gone to court yet?
My silly Liuli, have you overslept?
What time is it?
It should be past the time of Chen already,
I just heard some noise outside,
Has someone come to visit?
No hurry,
I just drank a bit too much,
Your ears are quite sharp,
Who is the visitor?
It must be either Madam Qi or that peacock,
Lady, morning,
Minister Qu just came by a moment ago
and just left,
He said he'd come later,
It's him,
[Zhao's Lamb Soup and Pancake]
Protector-General,
Please sit,
Father-in-law, breakfast is ready,
Didn't you tell Lady Jing
that we were eating together this morning?
I forgot,
Forgot what? She just doesn't want to come,
You ask even though you know,
You…
Time to eat,
Tell me, is it wrong
that I just want to protect this peace?
Of course, there's nothing wrong with that,
But the Qu family is not
what it used to be anymore,
Now, to protect Xizhou,
we still need to rely on
the power of the Tang Dynasty,
You mean, let me spare that person
for the time being,
That's not what I mean,
It's what Chongyu means,
Moreover, Chongyu is indeed considering
the Qu family's interests,
Even though we know
he was sent to counterbalance our Qu family,
Father-in-law,
I would like to say something out of line,
This place is no longer
the Kingdom of Gaochang,
but Xizhou of the Great Tang,
Is it I that
have not yet let go of what I hold in my heart?
I, on the other hand,
think Protector-General has already let go,
Otherwise, how could there be
this current scene of tranquility in Xizhou?
Then, for the time being,
let's slow down for now,
Allow that person to live a bit longer,
But,
that person will have to be killed eventually,
Wait for the opportunity,
Then, start by killing those around him,
I obey the order,
My lord, my lady, Minister Qu has arrived,
Shouyue,
I heard Minister had come early in the morning,
It was Xingjian who was rude,
Why so polite?
Indeed, I was wrong yesterday,
I didn't discipline those juniors,
which made you drink more,
They are very enthusiastic,
They are enthusiastic,
But it made me listen to a drunkard
talking all night long,
After a difficult journey to the Xizhou,
I wanted to sleep in peace,
As a result, I was hassled until dawn
before I could sleep,
Indeed, I was wrong yesterday,
I owe an apology to Madam Kudi,
You're too serious,
I cannot bear it,
We have just arrived in the Xizhou
and we are unfamiliar with everything here,
In many aspects,
we are relying on Minister's guidance,
How dare I blame you?
Madam Kudi is indeed aware of
the bigger picture,
I am quite relieved,
Shouyue, why don't you invite
Minister to sit down?
- Please,
I wonder what brings you here?
You saw
the situation around
the Protector-General's Mansion yesterday,
I wonder where you plan to settle down,
Thank you for your concern, Minister,
We have already bought a homestead
in Floating Water Workshop,
We are going to move there today,
Floating Water Workshop?
But to my knowledge,
there are more foreigners there,
I'm not sure with the status of Shouyue,
whether it is suitable to be in a place
like Floating Water Workshop,
Is that so? That actually suits me,
I think Shouyue wouldn't mind,
What do you think, Shouyue?
Yes, As long as you're happy,
Did you prepare a mansion for us?
I indeed prepared a good residence for you,
but I just did not expect…
I have to betray your kindness,
However, this may be a good thing for you,
In this way,
if a thief gets into our home in the future,
we won't be able to blame you anymore,
Liuli, all this is in the past,
How can you still blame Minister?
I hope you will not take offence
for my inappropriate words,
No worries,
How about this? Now that you're here,
let's all take a look at the new residence
together,
At noon, I'll personally cook
a few of my specialty dishes
to apologize to you,
Coincidentally,
your younger sister generously gave me
two wild pheasants last night at the banquet,
with their flesh still intact,
I'll cook them together for you to taste,
You are too kind, I have
numerous governmental affairs to attend to,
I shall take my leave first, goodbye,
Given such unfortunate timing,
let's postpone to another day,
I wonder what kind of food you prefer,
I can prepare in advance,
I have no particular preference,
I will take my leave now,
[Understand a Man by his Faults]
You little rascal,
It seems that
Qu Chongyu may have a vengeful nature,
It's better not to provoke him,
Why did he revenge? I invited him to dinner,
He irritated us early in the morning,
He asked for it,
I see they sincerely want to give us the house,
Unlike someone who have established businesses
before they even left Chang'an,
I didn't initially include you in this,
only buying a small residence,
If you don't like it,
there's still time to regret,
You're joking again,
What do I need Qu Chongyu's house for?
Am I supposed to let him ambush
in the neighborhood?
Anyway, I'm sticking with you,
As long as there's your bed in that house,
I won't worry about having a place to sleep,
Your face is getting thicker,
Always so thick,
- What are you doing?
- Always so thick,
[Rising Sun and Forever Moon]
Master and Lady,
It's really a trouble for Steward He,
How could someone of low status like me
deserve the word 'trouble'?
Everything's in order,
You go first and instruct
the kitchen to prepare for lunch,
Then, list the names of the elders here
in Xizhou to whom we need to give gifts,
After we have prepared the gifts,
you'll then take Ni
to deliver them to each house,
telling them that
we will visit another day to pay respects,
Yes, my lady,
The three rooms in the West Wing outside,
you may choose at will,
Ni, pack your bags and see
if you're missing anything,
Tomorrow, we shall go to the market,
Yes,
First come, first served,
You've arranged things quite quickly,
Why is it that you alone are visiting
the relatives of An Family?
Aren't we going together?
We have just arrived in the Xizhou,
Don't you need to handle official affairs
and make connections with colleagues?
Of course not,
Now, the most important thing for me
is to be with you,
That dead peacock is both
enticing and intimidating
He simply don't want you to get involved in
the affairs of the Xizhou,
Xizhou is the foundation of the Qu family,
The Tang dynasty has only been in control
for a dozen years or so,
Now it's back in the hands of the Qu family,
Listening to the words of
those officials' families,
I think these Xizhou clans
are intertwined with each other,
Alright, you can rest assured,
You don't have to worry about these things,
I have my own sense of measure,
This time, let's visit and socialize well,
Enjoy food, drinks, and fun, alright?
Okay,
Right, I saw you in the yard just now,
What are you so lost in thought about?
I'm not thinking about anything in particular,
Actually, before I came here,
I had never imagined
what this residence would look like,
When I entered today,
I immediately felt very familiar,
Everything looks pleasing to me,
The decoration of this room is quite ordinary,
But the more I look around, the more I like it,
I don't know why,
My silly Liuli, you still don't understand?
This is our home,
Our first home,
The more I look at it, the happier I become,
Yes, indeed,
This is the first residence
we bought ourselves,
No schemes, nor any glamorous traps,
Just a clean and reassuring scent,
The scent of home,
Take a look! Colorful glazed pot,
Gold Ewer with Chiseled Designs,
Lady, would you like
to take a look at this ewer,
This gold ewer with chiseled designs
is dazzlingly brilliant!
It suits your temperament so well,
I'll take this one,
- Here you are,
- Thank you,
Take care,
Take a look,
I want this one,
This is a divine stool from Persia,
My lord, please leave slowly,
[Tea]
[Rainbow Fabric Printing]
Look, there's a fabric printing shop there,
This signboard is so kind and familiar,
Giddyap!
My lady, be careful!
[Rainbow Fabric Printing]
[Art Beats Nature]
What I want is a golden eagle hunting rabbits,
What have you drawn?
Go… Golden eagle,
This eagle seems to have had a great awakening
and became a Buddha,
How can it hunt rabbits?
The artist in this shop really tries his best,
The artists in Xizhou mainly specialize
in making Buddha images,
No matter how much you push him,
he paints the birds and beasts all
in the same style,
There's nothing I can do,
Since someone in your store is capable of
painting this design,
he can paint the golden eagle that I want,
The painter of this design is far away
in Chang'an,
- I…
- Then, invite him here,
I'll pay the expenses,
The painter of this design is
of special status,
Truly, he's not someone
who can be swayed by money,
That's your business,
It has nothing to do with me,
Madam Qu, please don't make it
difficult for me anymore,
I paid a lot of money for a screen,
And also, according to your rules,
I paid half the deposit,
which shows my sincerity,
Now half a month has passed,
you still can't give me the design I want,
And you keep making all kinds of excuses,
You must think I'm too kind to bully,
This…
May I ask if your honorable master is
the An Family from Chang'an?
Kudi Liuli?
I didn't expect us to meet again so soon,
Madam Qu,
I told you, just call me Lady Jing,
Lady Liuli,
Madam Qu,
she is the painter you were looking for,
Lady Kudi of Chang'an
Ruyi Fabric Printing Shop,
She is also a master clothing maker
in Bureau of Garment,
Such a coincidence exists in the world!
It shows
that my fate with Lady Jing is not shallow,
Can Liuli draw eagles?
Understand a little,
You are really lucky, Your shop can be open,
[Art Beats Nature]
Thank you, Madam,
Would you like to visit my mansion
some other day?
I will prepare good brushes and ink,
waiting for you to draw,
By the way, teach me your makeup too,
You did promise me,
As commanded, Liuli,
Then it's settled,
Thank you so much, Lady Liuli,
I'm truly grateful, indeed,
We're all family here,
No need for such formalities, shopkeeper,
Lady Liuli, please come inside,
[Qu's Residence]
[Respect and Honor One's Origin]
[For the Benefit of the People]
Chongyu
[To Learn from Each Other's Experience]
I have something to tell you,
I have already persuaded Protector-General
according to your advice,
Protector-General agreed as well,
temporarily not killing Pei Xingjian,
So, what do we do next?
He will officially take office tomorrow,
So what?
Then, what if he is a person sent by Li Zhi?
Don't you have to come up with an idea?
Give these to Pei Xingjian
during the meeting tomorrow,
What's the point of discussing this?
Time to raise military funds,
Protector-General's Mansion also needs to
find more income and reduce expenditure,
A new broom sweeps clean,
I want to see how he sweep clean,
What did I say just now?
You are the backbone of Xizhou,
Without you, it won't work,
- Go quickly,
- Alright,
Junmeng,
what are you hiding from me after all?
It's nothing, What's the matter?
That's all you think about,
You should know that
not all matters can be resolved by killing,
I-I-I did hide the matter
about Guazhou from you,
But I did confess everything later, didn't I?
That's all,
[Silver Bright Moon of Tianshan Mountains]
[Protector-General's Mansion]
[But Golden Evening]
According to the rank of Senior Official Pei,
[Officer of the Yamen, Bai San]
you should have been accompanied by nine runners
and sixteen servants,
However, we have a workforce shortage
in the Xizhou,
Therefore, we can only select
from Protector-General's Mansion
these six people to serve you,
We hope that you understand,
Prefect Wang, you have been troubled,
I don't know what to call you all,
I'm called Bai San,
These are my brothers,
Liu, Si, and San,
Wang Xiaoxian, Changsheng,
Bai San was originally a serf of the Qu family,
Because of his great achievements in the army,
he was set free to become a commoner,
Since childhood, he honed his muscles and skills
with his ancestors,
When it comes to martial arts,
I'm afraid no one here can match him,
Bai San has no other skills,
I've never been afraid of anyone in a fight,
In the future, I will await your orders,
You're not modest at all,
Chongyu has really chosen some good talents
for Pei Xingjian,
These obnoxious people will give him
a hard time in the future,
Senior Official, Minister
and officials of all levels
are all waiting in the council hall for you,
I'll go now,
Thank you for your efforts, Prefect Wang,
You all take good care of the Senior Official,
At your command,
Bidding farewell to the respected Prefect Wang,
Protector-General asks me
to relay the message to you,
Next year's expenses must be reduced
by 300,000 coins,
which is also three hundred min,
But as for how to save,
you need to come up with a solution,
We officials have already
received very little money,
If they continue to cut down,
it would be an extreme oppression,
They are officials assigned by the court,
They stay in the house every day,
They have sufficient salary and office fields,
But they also want to deduct from us,
We didn't have much to begin with,
You've been looking at this account book
for a long time,
Do you have any idea now?
Mr, Pei is new here
and doesn't have any suggestions yet,
I hope
all my colleagues can put our heads together,
Only in this way can we live up
to Protector-General's expectations of us,
Actually, the overhead expenses
of Protector-General's Mansion are not that high,
Logically, Protector-General Qu is still holding
the position of Prefectural Governor of Xizhou,
He has provincial officials and clerks,
But now the positions are concurrently held
by officials from our Protector-General's Mansion,
Firstly, in terms of manpower,
there is no possibility for further reduction,
Secondly,
salaries and miscellaneous allowances,
Half of our officials are appointed
by the court,
Our spending on money and grain is also
below the amount set by the court,
Not to mention those yamen runners outside,
each of them costs only few thousand a month,
If we reduce further,
how can they support their family?
So it's really impossible to save,
I think,
it is appropriate to reduce expenditure,
But if we reduce too much,
it would cause unrest among the people,
The loss outweighs the gain,
I am aware of everyone's difficulties, but
next year, the imperial court
is planning a distant campaign to the north,
Furthermore, the arrears in tax revenue
from Xizhou are not a plight of just one day,
If we do not broaden sources of income
and reduce expenditure,
and the imperial court issue an order
next year to deliver military provisions,
I wonder if you can step forward
to donate your family's wealth,
or force the Senior Official Pei
to levy three to five years
of rent and tributes,
Senior Official,
the expenditure must certainly be reduced,
Go ahead and do it,
I believe everyone present here
will strongly support you,
- Drink,
- Come on,
I can't drink anymore,
Drink quickly,
Drink,
Brother Si, drink,
Hold on, Brother Si, Drink,
Brother Si, drink!
Brother San, drink them all under the table,
Fill up the wine, let's drink up, Brother San!
Fill up the wine!
Drink, Brother San!
Brother Si,
Liu, get the money!
Get the money quickly!
Quickly, Take the money!
Exactly,
Minister,
- Minister,
- Slow down,
Minister,
[Rising Sun and Forever Moon]
What official documents has been sent by Protector-General's Mansion?
It's the newspaper from Chang'an,
A month ago, Empress Wang
and Mistress Shu, Lady Xiao,
have been demoted to a commoner,
Their relatives have been exiled to Lingnan,
I'm afraid at this very moment,
we will soon have to start addressing her
as Empress Wu,
It was expected that
Lady Wu would take the position of Empress,
But why have they eagerly brought this to you?
Naturally, it's to remind me that
I'll never have the chance
to turn things around in Chang'an,
That ill-intentioned peacock,
In this way, I can accompany you more,
Are we going to continue
pretending to be stupid to avoid injuring?
Is this the newspaper?
If the newspaper is this thick,
it's going to be in trouble,
[Tang Xizhou Gaochang County's Civil and Military Officials' Salary]
This is last year's account book from Protector-General's Mansion,
They're willing to show you the accounts
so soon,
It is said that the tax arrears
in Xizhou are accumulating year by year,
It is time for the Protector-General's Mansion
to broaden sources of income and reduce expenditure,
This is indeed the most offensive job,
It is now most appropriate for me to do it,
You start packing things first,
I will also have a look
to see if there's any clues,
[Pei's Mansion]
[Rising Sun and Forever Moon]
Stop embroidering,
Comfort in shoes and socks is enough,
What's the use of making it so exquisite?
You're straining your eyes,
The expenses of Protector-General's Mansion
are nothing more than personnel and other items,
As for humans,
on the surface,
there are indeed some external officials
have received their salaries,
But Xizhou has five counties
and twenty-four townships,
The court has not appointed any officials,
It can only be assigned
by Protector-General's Mansion,
It's 50% less than what the court should give,
There is absolutely no reason
to reduce it further,
As the newly appointed Senior Official,
if the first thing you do upon assuming office
is to reduce the already meager treatment
of your subordinates,
Aren't you digging a hole for yourself?
Can't it be done without cutting?
Probably not,
Since this matter has been brought to me
and I'm asked to make a decision,
I guess that Minister Qu has his own methods
to force me to do it,
[The Wind Rises in the Western Province]
[Adapted from the novel "The Bright Moon of the Great Tang" by Yuewen Group author Lan Yunshu]
♫ I write my longing for you in Spring ♫
♫ The red plum is in full bloom like you ♫
♫ By the pond, next to the willow trees ♫
♫ I write a poem
to tell our story from the past ♫
♫ The years pass by like a bird♫
♫ The destiny always comes with regrets ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ Outside the pavilion, by the bridge ♫
♫ Under the moonlight,
we parted at the doorstep ♫
♫ I've endured hardship
to tell our lingering story ♫
♫ Remembrance of past things ♫
♫ As time goes by, seasons change ♫
♫ Flowers wither, and winter has come ♫
♫ Years pass by, and we're young no more ♫
♫ A snowy day, someone sings a sad song ♫
♫ Against the window,
I had a drink for pleasure ♫
♫ The moon still hangs in the sky,
but I'm no longer in the mood ♫
♫ It's quite and cold outside,
but I grab my pen again ♫
♫ The destiny always comes with regrets ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ Outside the pavilion, by the bridge ♫
♫ Under the moonlight,
we parted at the doorstep ♫
♫ I've endured hardship
to tell our lingering story ♫
♫ Remembrance of past things ♫
♫ As time goes by, seasons change ♫
♫ Flowers wither, and winter has come ♫
♫ Years pass by, and we're young no more ♫
♫ Winter comes again, and flowers wither ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ I look outside, like the poems asking ♫
♫ My love, have you
found someone good for you ♫
♫ Remembrance of past things ♫
♫ As time goes by, seasons change ♫
♫ Flowers wither, and winter has come ♫
♫ Years pass by, and we're young no more ♫
♫ Winter comes again, and flowers wither ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ I look outside, like the poems asking ♫
♫ My love, have you
found someone good for you ♫