[Weaving A Tale of Love 2]
[Episode 25]
Although you did not be famous overnight
in the battle this time,
you have already seen the gap
between you and others.
A gentleman should constantly strike to become
strong just like the evolution of the universe
and cultivate to become tolerant
just like the earth bears everything on it.
I surely believe in Chongyu.
He will definitely lead Xizhou
to its former glory in the future.
Drink a few more glasses with me tonight.
Drinking is harmful to your health.
So what? Let's go.
Father. Father.
Let's go.
Father.
Have a couple more.
Please don't drag me.
Hurry up.
Minister. Madam.
Each family in the village
has sent their capable daughters.
If Madam needs something, just tell them.
Thank you for your hard work,
Village Mayor Zhou.
You are welcome.
Village Mayor Zhou, please gather all men
to village gate,
Okay,
Yunyi. Minniang.
Take out raw cotton cloth without seeds
and the common cotton cloth made in workshops.
Please pass them around.
Okay.
Look! Take a look quickly.
Madam, what method did you use?
How can this woven cotton cloth be so soft?
How did this raw cotton cloth become so clean?
There's nothing particular.
The cotton cloth that you see
is deseeded and softened by a weaving machine.
As long as this cotton is used,
everyone can weave soft cotton cloth.
Not to mention that it could replace silk
for paying weaving tax.
If take it to the market,
one piece could also be exchanged
for a string of coins.
A string of coins? that's too much.
Senior Official allow us to use cotton.
Everyone knows that it can replace silk
for paying weaving tax.
In Xizhou, everyone knows that cotton is easy
to grow but difficult to be woven.
Just deseeding requires a lot of efforts.
Therefore, it's not because the family
really can't afford cloth.
Normal women would never try this.
But now there's such clean,
soft, and pure cotton.
And it's possible to exchange it
for a string of money.
It truly broadens our horizons.
I wonder
if Madam could possibly show us the method.
Then follow me.
Come on, let's go and have a look.
Now I show it to everyone.
As long as you handle the method,
everyone can learn it.
Please watch carefully.
Snacks in the countryside are not elaborate.
Ladies, please have a little bit.
Thanks for your hardworking.
I will prepare some drinks and dishes outside.
Madam, if you need anything, just tell me.
The pastries here hardly tasty.
Madam, please taste what Minniang has brought.
Is it edible?
Is everything fine
when you distribute errand boys?
Madam's idea is excellent.
If those women had not went there quickly
and strongly praised the cotton
promoted by Madam,
Today's distribution
would not be so successful.
It is Minister that organized well
and did everything by himself.
For promoting in every village and town,
Liuli dare not claim the credit.
Minister has been working hard all day.
Please sit down and have some tea and snacks.
Yes, yes, sit down quickly.
These are all brought by Minniang.
They all are your taste.
Excuse me for a moment.
Go to see how the meal is going.
I heard you coughing continuously.
Your voice is a bit hoarse.
I have added sanguisorba in it.
It can moisturize lungs and relieve cough.
Have it please.
Minister's meals are so exquisite.
He wouldn't eat such crude things,
not to mention such coarse tea sets.
Let alone unknown sanguisorba.
How could it be unknown?
I just dug it up in the courtyard on my own.
Minister trusts me. Sanguisorba is the best
for moisturizing lungs and relieving cough.
Yunyi, stop.
There are many famous doctors around Minister.
For a minor cough,
your folk remedies are not necessary.
But by drinking one or two cups
of Sanguisorba water,
he will get better.
Why do we make it so troublesome?
Minister, you are smart.
After drinking two more cups,
your cough will be cured tomorrow.
Minister agreed to drink the Sanguisorba water
offered by Yunyi.
It surprises me.
Based on my understanding of Minister,
Minister wouldn't touch unknown things.
Perhaps it's a moment of tenderness.
I have also been forced
to drift in foreign lands
but there never has been a moment.
I lived as brightly and simply as she did.
What things happen between sis and Minister?
They avoid us.
How would I know that?
I see Yunyi is very enthusiastic
towards Minister.
Does she love Minister?
Yes.
How could it be possible?
Why not?
Minister is handsome
and cares about the people in Xizhou.
He's a good man.
I mean, how could you
express your feelings so easily.
Liking is simply liking. Why do I cover it up?
What? Do you like him as well?
To tell the truth,
a few years ago, the elders in my family
indeed intended to match me with Minister.
Minister and I
can be considered as childhood sweethearts.
It's a pity.
It's a pity
that Minister doesn't like you, isn't it?
It's not just that Minister doesn't like me.
He doesn't like any girl in this world.
Even if Minister is excellent in all fields,
but he simply loves handsome youths.
Is that really true?
Of course.
Minister has already passed the age of thirty.
Considering his status and position,
have you ever seen any other women by his side?
On Winter Solstice, as vital as the New Year,
my lady herself is going out to shop.
I also wanted to be out for a walk
and see the current situation
of the people in Xizhou.
Madam, here comes a a visitor.
He mentioned
that he brings a message from Master.
I was just about to go out
to look for you, Madam.
Why is he so hurry?
You have to come all the way here yourself.
It's Mi Dalang who sent Yunyi back last time
He said that something happened
at the military camp.
Master sent him to Xizhou
to find Minister Qu to report to the dynasty.
To report to the dynasty?
Tan, please hurry to
Protector-General's Mansion for the Minister.
Yes.
My lady, that Mi Dalang.
His physical condition seems not so good.
I wonder if we need to invite Physician Han.
Let him come over and have a look.
Okay
[Lan Ruo]
Lady Kudi.
Just now,
a person with bloodstains entered your house.
He seems to be the trafficker, Master Mi.
He is not a good person.
Do you need us to go to the Mansion
to ask for some officers?
Thank you everybody, I have heard it.
No need to bother officers.
I know how to handle this.
Well.
Lady Kudi.
Stop talking nonsense about saving people
and sending messages.
[Rising Sun and Forever Moon]
Take a look of yourself.
I can't believe you play tricks on me.
Yunyi.
You go back to your own yard.
I'll handle these matters.
You all can stand down.
Yes.
[Floating Water Workshop]
What on earth has happened?
Sister, don't listen to him.
He is such a devious guy.
Now he fabricates nonsense again,
saying that the Tang army
massacred merchants in Dadu City.
He injured two Tang soldiers
while saving people.
After escaping from the Tang camp,
his brother-in-law asked him to find Minister.
He said to report this to the imperial court.
He does not think about the big city like Dadu.
It's not Helu's territory anyway.
Why would the Tang army massacre the merchants
for no reason?
Totally lie.
Massacre the merchants?
Although I am certainly not such kind person,
what I said today is true.
If I cheat, I will be killed by thunder.
Don't you think
you will not be killed by thunder?
Yunyi, go back to your own courtyard first.
No, sister, he is truly not a good person.
Put the question
whether he is good or not aside.
What he said today is likely to be true.
Thank you, my lady.
I'm grateful to you
for believing in me, my lady.
My lady, you must hurry to summon Minister,
otherwise it will be too late.
General Su said
that massacring the merchants is being a theft.
And I am unwilling to tarnish my reputation
by sharing their loot.
They falsely accused me,
regarding me as the remnants of a city rebel.
Senior Official Pei said
the court must be informed about this.
And the sooner, the better.
I've already sent someone to summon Minister.
Master Mi, please comes in.
I was born to be a bad person.
I entered the city with bad plans this time.
I intended to steal armor
and go to someone's home I know.
To swindle some silver.
But who knew
that household with dozens of family members
was only a teenage girl left,
Trembling in a water jar.
Recognizing me at a glance,
she burst into tears while hugging my neck.
I then hit two Tang soldiers
who came in after hearing noise.
I sent her out of the city
and helped her onto a horse.
It's all because of me
that I didn't consider things thoroughly.
I brought trouble for General Su.
On the third day,
General Su sent me out of the military camp.
I later heard that General Su refused to accept
gold and silver treasures
scraped from Dadu City
That Deputy Director Wang insisted
I am a scout from Dadu City.
He also said
that General Su has sheltered scouts
so that he showed mercy towards city rebels.
I barely managed to escape
to Senior Official Pei.
Now that it has come to this, the only way is
that we report it to the court.
Let His Majesty be informed of this matter.
It would be best to have Minister Qu,
Protector-General Qu, submit a report.
If that doesn't work,
you could ask Minister to secretly send someone
to take you to Chang'an.
My lady will know
how to make this matter be heard
by the Emperor.
How is the situation
at the military warehouse now?
The military warehouse of the Chief Historian
has no grain left to send.
Since half a month ago,
soldiers' food has already been halved.
The feed for the horses
has been reduced even more.
The warhorses
barely have forage to fill their bellies.
But the private horses used for transportation
by the foot soldiers
are dying in large numbers from hunger.
There is much complaining among the soldiers.
Wang Wendu must have massacred the merchants
in the city.
Aside from returning without nothing,
he loots food, grass, cash and silk
to stabilize the military's morale.
Master Mi, this is Physician Han.
It's better to cure your wounds first
before reporting to Minister.
Thank you, my lady.
I am fine.
I just fell off from horse and broke my nose
in the middle of the night.
Just lost a bit more blood.
Indeed, I am fine.
I just haven't had rest for a few days,
and the bleeding wouldn't stop after the shock.
There are other injuries.
Staying up like this for another two days
would only shorten my life by two years.
Madam, please step aside for a moment.
I need to check his wounds.
Thanks.
[Rising Sun and Forever Moon]
[Protector-General of Xizhou, Qu Zhizhan]
My lady, why are you looking at this?
Could there be some tricks?
Come help me take a look at this.
This one and the other
that maid brought back from An Family
are indeed a bit different.
It's newly issued this year.
This is a masterpiece
into which I've put a night's effort.
It seems
Senior Official Pei must be in danger now.
Advisor Su hated Senior Official Pei.
Senior Official Pei
is bound to have a hard time in the military.
With this fake clearance document,
I can ask Gu to take the An family's servants.
With the help of the An family's
financial power and horses along the way
they arrive at the military
under the pretext of delivering supplies.
To help for Senior Official Pei outside
to prevent persecution from Advisor Su.
The young servant that the lady sent
to wait at the city gate has returned.
He says the Minister has returned.
However,
that child couldn't even get close to Minister.
He said Minister was accompanied
by dozens of people in armor.
They enter the city gate together.
Those people all looked hostile.
Our young servant approached them
but hadn't even spoken one word yet.
He was pushed aside.
However, that child was quite clever.
He noticed that an attendant of Minister
was lagging behind.
So he went up and said a few words.
The attendant replied
that he would report to Minister when free.
Dozens of people in armor.
Do you find out who these people are?
They said that the leader
is the military advisor Su Nanjin.
[Peace and Safe Spread Far]
Is what you said true?
The army has already returned.
T-That Senior Official Pei
was already detained by the army.
How dare I speak nonsense
about this vital matter?
If this Pei Xingjian is just ineffective
in dispatching military provisions,
then let it be.
He also sided with Su Dingfang in showing mercy
to the scouts from Dadu City.
How could the Deputy Director Wang
tolerate him?
Logically speaking, Pei Xingjian
is an official of Xizhou after all.
It should be Protector-General Qu
to decide his fate.
Deputy Director Wang
wants me to inform the Protector-General.
In a few days,
Pei Xingjian will be escorted back to Xizhou.
Dadu.
Is Master Su referring to the Dadu City
on the west of Yingsuochuan Valley?
I believe
this city is quite affluent as far as I know.
The lord of the city is a sly character.
It seems to have the guts
to place a spy in the Tang army.
Is he totally unaware of the danger?
Isn't that the truth?
Deputy Director Wang originally wanted to
let Su Dingfang have dignity.
But he took advantage
of his previous military exploits,
unfairly protecting the spy from Dadu City.
He even secretly let him out of camp.
Now, this spy from Dadu city
has reached Xizhou probably.
Deputy Director Wang has asked me
to cooperate with Protector-General Qu
to catch this spy from Dadu.
What's your opinion, Protector-General Qu?
Since Deputy Director Wang has ordered,
I must obey.
I heard from Chongyu that soldiers and horses
who have joined the army
have secured the city gate of Xizhou.
I suspect that the spy cannot escape anymore.
The Advisor has been through many hardships
along the way.
Do you need to freshen up
and rest for a moment?
Military affairs matter.
The spy is likely hiding
in Pei Xingjian's house.
We should capture him immediately
to avoid more complications.
Master Su, don't worry.
I will arrange people
to spot Pei Xingjian's house secretly.
By the way, find out the situation there
these past few days.
If there is any news,
I'll inform you immediately
If so, thanks for Chongyu.
Chongyu, don't blame me.
I don't mean to concealed it from you.
It's just
that I accept military orders this time.
I can't reveal the news until we get to Xizhou.
I wondered why Ziyu said so
and asked me
who else is in the Pei Shouyue's family.
You'd better pay more attention
to catching the spy.
[Qu's Mansion]
Thoroughly inspect the merchants heading east.
Do not let them exploit any loopholes.
As long as we catch them red-handed this time,
This Pei Shouyue will definitely not
escape from punishment.
Ziyu, don't worry. I totally understand.
[Qu's Mansion]
Minister.
What's the matter?
The wife of Senior Official Pei
has sent someone to look for you.
Please visit Floating Water Workshop
as soon as possible.
Okay.
Madam, I have already change drug dressing
for Master Mi.
He will recover after resting for two days.
Madam, please do not worry.
Thank you, Physician Han.
I must the matter of life and death to you.
Please ask me as your will, Madam.
I wonder
if Physician Han could make Mr. Mi's injuries
appear more critical.
It's best to look like
he is on the brink of death.
Merchants in Dadu City have been murdered.
Master Mi. was falsely accused
of being a spy in Dadu.
I have already asked Ni to tell you.
If he is caught and sent to the army,
it's certain that he won't come back.
Even Senior Official Pei will be accused.
I have thought of a risky plan.
The more miserable Mi Dalang's appearance,
the better.
I am going to fake the wound right away.
Thank you.
Madam, I have a more convenient drug.
I wonder if Madam is willing to try it.
Alright, you prepare first.
Just follow my arrangements later.
Father,
there must be something strange about this.
Pei Xingjian and Su Dingfang are not someone
who does not know what matters.
How could it happen without reason?
To cover up for some sort of spy.
Go on.
Send someone to give a message
to Pei's mansion.
Senior Official Pei and his wife
are our benefactors.
They are also benefactors of the people
in Xizhou.
Help him.
Why is it so greasy?
Tell the kitchen to cut off all the meat
for my father next two days.
Just cut it all off
Naughty boy. How could I live without meat?
[Settled in Taishan]
Madam.
I already know why Madam has invited me here.
I came just to inform Madam.
Mr. Su has already taken orders
from the Chief Administrator
to investigate the Dadu spy in Xizhou.
Later,
I will lead people to patrol the whole city.
Madam need to make some preparations please.
I assume that Minister is not aware
what on earth has happened inside Dadu City.
What's the matter?
Master Mi,
please come out to greet the Minister.
Minister.
Master Mi.
Minister, the merchants inside Dadu City
have been slaughtered.
What did you say?
General Su Dingfang refuses
to collude with Deputy Director Wang.
Then Deputy Director Wang slandered him
that he helped me who is a spy from Dadu.
Minister, you know someone named.
I was born and raised in the Xizhou.
How dare I do that
stupid spy of Dadu? Minister.
Did you say
the merchants in Dadu City
were all slaughtered?
Minister, as Senior Official said,
things have happened.
Only you
can vindicate innocent people of Dadu City.
Protector-General Qu please report it
to the imperial court.
Inform His Majesty of this deep grievance
as soon as possible.
Convict those executioners, Minister.
My Qu family is located
in the remote southwest frontier.
We lack influence and are weak in power.
If we overtly confront General Su, I'm afraid…
I do have a safe and reliable method.
Minister, you must be aware as well.
I received help from Madam Rongguo,
the Empress's mother.
Madam Rongguo
has been exceptionally kind to Liuli.
I ask Minister to secretly send an officer
to deliver a message to Chang'an for me.
Liuli guarantees
that no matter how this matter is resolved,
it will not implicate the family of the Qu.
Furthermore, it might even make it possible for
the Empress to be aware of Minister's loyalty.
As for loyalty or not,
there is no need to mention it now.
I, on the other hand,
would like to see these utterly mad men.
I wonder what kind of fate will they meet.
Madam, if there is any letter
to be sent to Chang'an
Chongyu is willing to do for you
with whole heart.
Thank you very much, Minister.
This is the Ruyi that the Empress awarded me
and the letter I wrote to the Empress
When Minister's servants
have arrived at the Duke's mansion,
they Just give the word
that 'The Kudi clan sent someone
to greet to Madam Rongguo'.
Someone will probably report it.
Does the lady trust me so much?
Minister has pride,
and he would surely not feed the dragon.
Furthermore, this matter will sooner or later
become known to the world
There is no need for Minister stain his fame
by associating with the corrupt.
This letter will surely be delivered
by Chongyu.
It's just that the city gates are now closed.
Madam, what will you do with Master Mi.?
You don't need to worry.
[For the Benefit of the People]
[Qu's Residence]
[A Thousand Rooms of Resounding Strings]
How are things going?
Have you caught that Dadu scout?
Mr. Su,
you've been keeping me in such suspense.
I just went to the Pei Family,
but I didn't see the Dadu scout.
I only saw one man selling live stocks.
The merchant from Xizhou, Master Mi,
was beaten until he was almost breathless.
But he was still there, shouting and yelling,
that the merchants were all slaughtered.
Everyone is dead.
The treasure has been stolen,
and now they want to kill him.
Why didn't Chongyu bring him back?
Nut allow him to babble nonsense there.
Bring him back?
Easier said than done.
Given such event,
the Kudi family did not only invite a doctor
but also invited a mage to cast spells.
Now Pei family's crowded outside the door.
Everyone comes to see Master Mi
who has been bewitched.
Originally, Master Mi was a tyrant in Xizhou,
committing numerous misdeeds.
Therefore, everyone is clapping and cheering,
saying he was deserved to be bewitched.
I actually want to say this in public.
This person is indeed a spy form Dadu.
But I can't say it out.
How is Dadu now?
Have those merchants
really been slaughtered to the last man?
Well, some people were indeed killed.
They resist stubbornly.
Minister. Minister.
Minister,
isn't this just a case of the poor dying?
You didn't believe
that bully's nonsense, did you?
Instead,
you suspect Chief Administrator and me.
You also don't want to obey
the Chief Administrator's military orders.
Master Mi. is now
in the courtyard of the Pei family.
If you wish, my Lord,
you could capture him at any time.
Let the people of Xizhou know
that this person is not possessed.
It turns out
that the Chief Administrator is truly greedy.
He butchered the steadfast merchant.
So you really wanted to kill them to death.
Ziyu, please figure it out.
Chongyu is much different from you.
Qu family has been living in Xizhou
for generations.
I can't disregard the reputation
of my Qu family.
Sorry, I can't interfere in this matter.
Please, do as you wish.
[For the Benefit of the People]
[A Thousand Rooms of Resounding Strings]
[Qu's Residence]
Now the elderly ladies have taken a look at it.
Could you please check if
Master Mi has been better?
Madam, Master Mi's condition is getting worse.
Please decide early, Madam.
Since he has begged for seeing Senior Official.
Although I cannot save him,
I just can't abandon him.
Madam, I will take Master Mi to my place.
If I can save him, I will;
if not, I'll accompany him on his last journey.
Much thanks to Physician Han.
The city has been slaughtered,
all the gold and silver have been looted.
They-They want to kill people to death.
Everyone gets out of the way for me.
Move, move, move aside.
The city has been massacred.
Hurry up and make him shut up.
Such babbling is nonsensical.
Who's the doctor? Quickly shut him up.
If he dares to spout another nonsensical word…
And what of it?
Madam, I didn't find you were here.
Sorry for offending you.
I am helpless as well.
This Mr. Mi was struggling the other day.
And fall upon when entering my courtyard.
I've called for a doctor for two days in a row.
Unfortunately,
not only has he not regained consciousness.
But he started to talk nonsense instead.
I also want him to calm down.
But the doctor said
that Master Mi's injuries were too severe.
If give him more medicine,
he might not be able to bear it.
But if the medicine is not used,
he can't keep yelling like this for long.
Have you come here
for any official matters today?
Madam.
It was said that Master Mi forced good people
into bad one.
They want to take him to reply, madam.
You all have also seen Master Mi's situation.
Does he seem to be able to respond?
Move aside, move aside, move aside,
Advisor Su, how do you think what we should do?
Madam Kudi, long time no see.
Master Su.
I suppose he must be Master Mi.
You allow him to talk nonsense
and stir up people's hearts here?
This man, Mi Dalang, has committed
coercing the innocent into degrading acts
several times in Yizhou.
I'll take him back for questioning.
Hope that you can do me a favor.
Master Su.
Look at him. Can he bear such turbulence?
Could you please show mercy to him
and allow him to have a rest?
Let's talk about it after he wakes up.
It's also good to preserve his life.
It's not that Su is unwilling.
It's just
that official duties make it inconvenient.
And I must advise madam
not to indulge in momentary compassion,
thereby tolerating the demon.
I just fear it may affect
Senior Official Pei's good reputation
as well.
Since you come here on orders
to take someone away,
I shouldn't stand in the way.
May I trouble you to show us
the official document to everyone?
I was in a rush
when I left the house, so I did not bring it.
Who doesn't know
that Master Mi is a notoriously wicked person?
Could it be that you suspect
that I have wrongfully accused him?
Not at all.it is not I that suspect you.
Even if Mi has misconducted himself,
he has not yet been convicted.
He is the people of Xizhou.
Since you want to capture someone in Xizhou,
there must be some evidence.
Although I am a woman,
yet I cannot simply watch the people of Xizhou
losing their lives
in such an unclear and unjust manner.
Well, well. Nice speech.
That's right indeed.
Madam is determined
to obstruct my official duties.
How dare I hinder your official business.
Although it is official duty,
it has its own set of rules.
Which state
would take people from another place
without even a single official document?
Does your honor think
that Xizhou is a county of Yizhou?
As long as you want to take the initiative,
you can capture anyone you want.
Can you capture whoever you want?
This is the fish symbol of Chief Administrator.
I wonder if this can be used as a credential?
[Same as Commander]
How much longer does the lady want to verify?
Do you still suspect that Su is faking it?
Of course, this symbol is genuine.
So your father, Prefectural Governor Su,
has become the Chief Administrator.
It deserves congratulation.
Madam, what do you mean?
Isn't Governor Su the Chief Administrator?
Then why does this case of forcing good people
into servitude in Yizhou
require the military command
of the Chief Administrator?
Could it be that
Mi forced someone
from the Chief Administrator's family
to be scorned?
Madam, please do not speak nonsense.
How can you joke about Chief Administrator?
Nonsense? Who just came in and spoke
that Mi has committed a crime in Yizhou
and needs to be taken back for questioning?
Who cannot produce the documents from Yizhou?
But brought out a military token instead?
Claim to arrest a merchant
who forces the good into servitude.
But I didn't know this.
I didn't realize that Commander would care
for the people of Xizhou like that.
Even the merchants in the state and county
and forcing good men to demon
should be inquired into.
I am not unaware of what Mister Mi did.
What on earth has he done
to enrage the Chief Administrator?
So Master Su
indifferently take him away
regardless of his life.
Or is it that so-called forcing a good man
is merely an excuse?
Could it be that this Mi
hasn't truly succumbed to evil?
But has witnessed something
he should not have seen?
thus he must be silenced by death.
Hold on, don't speak nonsense.
Who said Chief Administrator
wants to arrest this person to kill him?
So, it's not Chief Administrator
who wants to arrest people. It's okay.
I have been hearing about murdering all day.
And now you come here
and can't even wait for a moment
to take him away.
Therefore, I was a bit over-concerned.
I am a woman, lacking insight,
I beg your pardon, Advisor.
Since it's not Chief Administrator
wanting to arrest him, it makes it easier.
Anyway, this Master Mi has been injured
so badly.
He cannot go anywhere.
Advisor, please wait a moment.
When his injuries get better,
you bring an official document to take him.
So as to prevent everyone from truly believing
that someone was robbing for money and silk,
slaughtering the merchants in the city,
committing murder to silence them
[Weaving A Tale of Love 2]
[Adapted from the novel 'The Bright Moon of the Great Tang' by Lan Yunshu, an author of Yuewen Group]
♫ I write my longing for you in Spring ♫
♫ The red plum is in full bloom like you ♫
♫ By the pond, next to the willow trees ♫
♫ I write a poem
to tell our story from the past ♫
♫ The years pass by like a bird♫
♫ The destiny always comes with regrets ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ Outside the pavilion, by the bridge ♫
♫ Under the moonlight,
we parted at the doorstep ♫
♫ I've endured hardship
to tell our lingering story ♫
♫ Remembrance of past things ♫
♫ As time goes by, seasons change ♫
♫ Flowers wither, and winter has come ♫
♫ Years pass by, and we're young no more ♫
♫ A snowy day, someone sings a sad song ♫
♫ Against the window,
I had a drink for pleasure ♫
♫ The moon still hangs in the sky,
but I'm no longer in the mood ♫
♫ It's quite and cold outside,
but I grab my pen again ♫
♫ The destiny always comes with regrets ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ Outside the pavilion, by the bridge ♫
♫ Under the moonlight,
we parted at the doorstep ♫
♫ I've endured hardship
to tell our lingering story ♫
♫ Remembrance of past things ♫
♫ As time goes by, seasons change ♫
♫ Flowers wither, and winter has come ♫
♫ Years pass by, and we're young no more ♫
♫ Winter comes again, and flowers wither ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ I look outside, like the poems asking ♫
♫ My love, have you
found someone good for you ♫
♫ Remembrance of past things ♫
♫ As time goes by, seasons change ♫
♫ Flowers wither, and winter has come ♫
♫ Years pass by, and we're young no more ♫
♫ Winter comes again, and flowers wither ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ I look outside, like the poems asking ♫
♫ My love, have you
found someone good for you ♫