[Weaving A Tale of Love 2]
[Episode 11]
The attire and mannerism of Minister Qu
really resembles a peacock
with its tail fanned out,
Mr, Mu, have you really made up your mind?
Anyway, my lord also said
if you refused to listen to advice
and insisted on going,
you would bear the consequences,
Then please thank your lord for me, Move aside,
Mr, Mu San has arrived,
Now, it's going to be fun,
San, following the merchants,
your journey was very arduous,
But it doesn't matter,
From now on,
Chongyu will surely take good care of you all,
Just now, Minister said after passing Guazhou,
he would take Jiu and Lady Liuli
via the Ohaido,
taking a shortcut to Xizhou,
Our caravan's camels walk slowly,
With many people and goods,
we cannot take the Ohaido,
So when we reach Xizhou,
we will part ways with Minister,
So what?
San, I will prepare the best horse for you
to go to Xizhou,
But…
Sanniang,
Without listening to your dissuasion,
I was wrong to go to the banquet,
But I could have anticipated
Minister Qu actually has such a strange hobby,
Jiu, as the Senior Official of Xizhou,
Y-You must have a way,
You can't stand by and do nothing,
Shouyue, you have to come up
with a plan for your cousin,
As for the plan, there is one, But…
No, if I tell you this idea,
you'll definitely think
that I'm trying to harm you,
Jiu, you can rest assured,
As long as I can get rid of
Minister's entanglements,
whatever you say, I'll do,
The Qu family has a deep-rooted foundation
in the Xizhou,
As for me, I've just arrived here,
We haven't even entered Xizhou yet,
What if we offend Minister before that?
What do we do then?
Shouyue, San is like my own brother,
Please help him,
Hurry up,
B-B-Brother-in-law,
please help your elder brother,
What are you calling me?
Brother-in-law, please give me some advice,
Alright,
Cousin, rest assured,
Just do as I say tomorrow,
I will naturally help you
get rid of Minister's entanglements,
Well then, I'll take my leave first,
Take care,
You're up to no good again, aren't you?
Qu Chongyu is always testing me,
Then I can give him back his own way,
Maybe I can kill two birds with one stone,
I can help Mu San break the blockade,
And also send this rival in love away,
isn't that wonderful?
I knew your motives weren't pure,
Your beauty would put the flowers to shame,
To have such a cousin by your side,
I really can't be at ease,
This is very good,
Since we have to put on a performance
for Qu Chongyu to watch,
then I shall continue to
play the role of ignorant and shallow shrew,
Then I will cooperate with you,
instilling a fearful, submissive husband image
deep into people's hearts,
I am a shrew,
I'm henpecked,
Listen to me, okay?
Okay,
It's not a solution for me
to keep hiding in the carriage,
Liuli, can you urge Shouyue for me?
We've already reached Guazhou,
What about his idea?
Shouyue, you're so magnanimous,
Mu San and Madam Kudi get along well,
Don't you mind?
Bah, that dead peacock always talks nonsense,
Minister, you misunderstood,
San, like my wife's biological brother,
has joined under my command,
He should receive extra care,
But there are many people from An Family
in this merchant family,
Why do you view San differently?
It seems
Minister pays special attention to San,
Then I'll do a favor,
How about letting San attend to Minister?
Gu, stop it,
Hush,
San,
from now on, what about following Minister?
You want me to follow Minister?
This is a great opportunity
to rise rapidly through the ranks,
How lucky you are
to attracts the attention of Minister,
I am grateful to Minister for your support,
Good,
Shouyue, will my elder brother
be considered as above his station?
I certainly wouldn't want my brother
to feel wronged,
Madam, why would you say something like that?
I can't love San enough as it is,
How could I possibly allow him to be wronged?
I'm afraid of taking away what you love,
Minister, you're joking,
You love talented people,
Brother loves the future, and Shouyue loves me,
Everyone takes what they need,
This is not about taking away someone's love,
Shouyue, the longer I sit in the car
the colder I get,
I want you to take me with you,
Okay,
Come here,
It's still warm like this,
With you by my side, it won't be boring,
As long as you're happy,
There are important matters to attend to
in my courtyard,
I shall take my leave now, Giddyap!
At last,
I know what this dead peacock is afraid of,
Shouyue, was my performance good just now?
Good,
[Respect and Trust the Talent]
Tomorrow, after leaving Guazhou,
we'll be on the Ohaido route,
If you still don't reject Mu San now,
it won't be so easy
to get rid of him in the future,
Say something,
You wouldn't let Pei Xingjian
so easily place his confidant
beside us, would you?
Why are you anxious when I'm not?
It's because you're not worried
that I have to worry for you,
Keep calm,
Wait,
Wait for what?
Wait for Pei Xingjian to come for me,
He… Come for you?
Minister,
Senior Official Pei can't stop ranting over
there,
Madam Kudi called over her servant girl
to invite Minister to persuade,
See, what did I tell you?
[Respect and Trust the Talent]
Here he comes,
Ni has brought Minister Qu with her,
Cheng, prepare quickly,
Yes,
Minister, you have finally arrived,
Shouyue just got angry for some unknown reason,
He ordered Cheng to bring my cousin in
for a scolding,
He's lost his temper badly,
No matter how much we call,
the door won't open,
Shouyue, San is your elder brother,
If you have something to say, say it properly,
[Respect and Trust the Talent]
Relying on the fact he's your elder brother,
he dares to deceive his superiors
and delude his subordinates,
Open the door, Shouyue, It's me, Chongyu,
Why are you coming, Minister?
Please come in now,
What in the world has happened
to make you so angry?
You ask him,
It's my carelessness, I mishandled the matter,
San is my wife's cousin, He's one of our own,
I specifically handed over
the matter of the Princess Linhai
to you,
After asking just now did I find out
that he didn't settle this for me,
You know full well the Princess Linhai
holds grudges against me and Shouyue,
Other tasks can be taken lightly,
but matters of Hedong Duke's Mansion
can't be handled carelessly,
I was indeed careless about this matter,
Then, how about I go back first?
After this matter is settled, I'll come back,
The day before yesterday,
I instructed you to serve Minister,
Today, you want to return,
Aren't you deliberately making things difficult
for me?
If this matter
is truly related to the Princess,
no wonder Shouyue would be so furious,
Princess Linhai might already be angered,
It's not too late to remedy problems
in a timely manner,
The princess loves ostentation the most,
She often invites the distinguished guests
from Chang'an,
At that feast,
she often talks about some romantic matters,
Back then, princess talks a lot
about my romantic matters,
San,
if you have time,
share the interesting things on this journey
to the eldest princess in detail,
Maybe if she's happy,
she'll forget your mistakes, right?
Minister, you always have a way,
Shouyue, since Minister said so,
let's send Brother back to Chang'an,
It seems this is the only way,
We've bothered Minister so late into the night,
Brother, you should escort
Minister back to rest
and say your goodbyes properly,
Then, after I say goodbye,
I'll set off the same night
to return to Chang'an,
Shouyue, you really guessed right,
This peacock is indeed putting on a show,
At the moment,
he can't wait to see my cousin off,
He simply turned my trick to his own use,
It seems that I have underestimated him,
The depth
of this man's scheming is truly terrifying,
Just now, within a few words,
he set up a small game,
He wants San to
pass his absurdities on to the princess Linhai,
and then let the princess bring this matter
into the palace,
so that His Majesty
would also know his absurdities,
and lower his guard,
Shouyue, henceforth,
you have to daily face this person,
It's indeed tough upon thinking,
Don't mention him anymore,
You have been traveling all day today,
You must be tired by now,
What about resting earlier?
[Respect and Trust the Talent]
You all are visiting late at night,
I wonder why you're here,
Kill,
Why look at me? They're disturbing my sleep,
Am I not allowed to be angry?
Yeah,
[Respect and Trust the Talent]
There are still so many people here,
Don't be afraid, I'm here,
What should we do now?
Call someone,
Assassin! There's an assassin,
Kill,
Kill Pei Xingjian,
Liuli,
Spare his life,
Liuli, are you okay?
You said a bit late, I couldn't hold back,
Where do they come from?
They come from Chang'an,
The leader is an imperial bodyguard,
Don't worry, They are all central Han people,
They have absolutely nothing to do with us,
How do you know so much about this?
Chongyu was careless
and let a few thieves slip in,
which disturbed
Mr, and Mrs, Pei's peaceful dream,
I am truly sorry,
A few thieves,
They were somewhat fierce,
You vile peacock,
I reckon you're up to no good,
No need to look, I'm talking about you,
Even if you look more, you won't find here
the second person
dressed like a peacock spreading its feathers,
Liuli,
Liuli, you can't be rude to Minister,
I am rude?
I live in his courtyard,
but in the middle of the night,
I was attached by some masked thieves,
I also narrowly escaped with my life,
But he told me it was just a few thieves,
- Recently in the north…
- Shut up,
That shield was thrown by you, wasn't it?
Yes, I…
You wanted to kill me, didn't you?
Just now, if not for my quick reaction
and timely evasion,
I would've been crushed to death
by that shield,
- You…
- What you…
Don't you know how heavy that shield is?
I'm such a delicate and weak woman,
If I were hit by that shield,
would I still be alive?
Just now, the situation was critical,
I admit I was indeed a bit reckless
in what I did,
But it was all to save your life,
It seems to me that you messed up
and accidentally saved me instead,
You…
If you had no intention of killing,
then how did that whole bunch
of assassins get in?
Could it be
that they sprouted from beneath the ground?
There's no need for excuses,
In my view, this group of assassins
are your people from your mansion
who are disguising themselves,
These people came from Chang'an,
The leader is the imperial bodyguard,
If you want to frame me,
please investigate thoroughly,
You seem to know clearly,
My lady, you must not speculate randomly,
If not for Minister arriving in time,
neither you nor I would be alive,
Apologize to Minister now,
Thank you, Minister,
No need, I can't take it,
It's good that you know,
Why are you all standing still? Clean up,
Okay, don't be angry, Ni,
My lady,
I'll take you back to the room to rest,
The doors and windows are all broken like this,
How am I supposed to rest?
Order the servants to clean my room,
and let the Pei couple use it,
Yes,
Minister, how could this be okay?
Chongyu cannot escape blame
for tonight's incident,
You all rest well,
I have something else to do,
I'll take my leave first,
Since Minister has already said so,
then let's reluctantly make do for the night,
Alright,
Someone, escort Mr, Pei and Madam Kudi back
to the Minister's room to rest,
Increase guard shifts,
Let's go,
Sanniang, what's been going on
with Lady Liuli recently?
She wasn't like this before,
Such a rude and impolite woman!
Don't be so angry,
You don't need to be angry with
a lady, right?
But after all these years,
this is the first time I've seen you so angry,
This really shows
that Kudi Liuli is indeed extraordinary,
Extraordinarily crude,
Have some tea, and calm down,
Don't be angry, or you'll lose your beauty,
Today's events were treacherous,
If anything happens to you,
I really wouldn't know what to do,
I'm fine,
There was such a moment
that I'm really afraid of losing you,
Don't talk nonsense,
I swear I'm sticking with you for life,
Even if I become an old woman
with a face full of wrinkles,
Don't even think about getting rid of me,
It was the Protector-General
who made you do this, right?
Yes, I never intended to conceal it from you,
Why didn't you discuss it with me in advance?
There was no chance,
All your energy on this journey
was focused on that couple, right?
I wanted to find an opportunity to tell you,
but I never got the chance,
Alright, I admit it!
They come from Chang'an,
There are royal forces behind the scenes,
But I don't know who they precisely are,
I really don't know much,
Pei Xingjian was targeted by them
as soon as he left the capital,
As for why they have to take action here,
If they continue further,
it's the territory of our Qu family,
They can only do it here,
Hence, I provided the map of the courtyard,
I diverted the guards away,
But I didn't know about the murder,
It's none of my business,
What a case of murdering a person
with a borrowed knife!
All advantages and no disadvantages,
Why not do it?
Have you thought about the consequences?
I admittedly have not thought about it,
But the Protector-General
surely has thought about it, right?
They truly weren't killed by us,
Think about it, It is well known
why Pei Xingjian was convicted,
The family Wu
and Grand Commandant Party will not let him go,
At most,
we are just failing to protect him adequately,
I have prepared the bodyguard
to take the blame,
What if Pei Xingjian is
an undercover intentionally placed in Xizhou
by His Majesty?
That's also what Protector-General thought of,
Then it would be perfect
to remove him through others' hands,
Fool,
If Pei Xingjian dies,
our Qu family is close to
a great disaster,
No, we didn't kill him,
Does it matter who killed him?
D-D-Doesn't it matter?
Rebellion in the north,
His Majesty is about to use troops, tell me
what he most worried about is at this moment,
The loyalty of our Qu family,
It is the loyalty of our Qu family,
So he sent someone over,
I know his intentions,
So, we sent someone to greet him
to show our attitude,
We take a lots of people
to welcome Pei Xingjian,
but he was killed in Guazhou
under unclear circumstances,
What would the emperor think?
It doesn't matter who killed Pei Xingjian,
The important thing is that
he can't be dead now,
Are you saying that
the assassin was sent by the princess?
Before you leave Chang'an,
the princess loses both her wealth and face,
Given her vengeful nature,
how could she let us off?
But this courtyard has many houses
and is heavily guarded,
How did they manage to evade the guards
and accurately locate the place
where we can settle down?
This is precisely what I am worried about,
Do you mean the Qu family is colluding
with the princess?
Only this explanation makes sense,
But the actions of Qu Chongyu are puzzling,
This assassination plan
was meticulously prepared,
The timing of the attack
was also extremely precise,
If Qu Chongyu had not offered help in the end,
you and I would have surely
found it difficult to emerge unscathed,
Although we still can't get a precise answer,
what we can be certain about is that
there must be a problem with the Qu family,
Once we reach Xizhou, I will work with you
to investigate the Qu family,
It is too slow to proceed
with the trade caravan,
Starting tomorrow, with Qu Chongyu,
we will set off together lightly equipped,
Through the Ohaido,
it will take only two days to reach Xizhou,
We won't rest up ahead,
We will pass the mountain pass in one breath,
Is the weather changing?
It looks like the weather is changing,
It's going to snow soon,
However, ten more miles forward
and we will be out of this mountain pass,
Twenty miles further,
After we cross the gravel Gobi,
we would cross the Ohaido,
Really, Shouyue?
Are we really going to cross the Ohaido?
If all goes well, before nightfall,
we could reach a small village town,
Then we must congratulate Minister indeed,
Finally, you can be free,
You don't need to face me every day anymore,
You're joking,
To be acquainted with Madam Pei,
even in the cold of winter,
it feels like a warm spring breeze,
Really? I didn't mishear that, did I?
Shouyue, slow down,
Don't you see? Minister can't keep up,
Madam, you go first,
I will be able to follow shortly,
Minister, if you're so far away from me,
how can you bask in the spring breeze then?
Too much exposure to the spring breeze
will wear away my will,
I might as well temper my mind
in this cold winter,
Giddyap,
Well…
You little rascal!
Who's the bad one?
I've been obeying you all along,
Now,
both of our reputations are completely ruined,
Most of these people are laughing at
your timidity and fear,
They say that I am crude and disrespectful,
Even Official Liu looks at me
and laughs in a weird way,
Ni and Tan are even more hesitant to speak up,
They tried to persuade me twice,
saying that
I should be concerned about your reputation,
So what?
Everyone in the world knows that
Prime Minister Fang Xuanling is henpecked,
But nobody looks down on him because of this,
Now it's getting colder and colder,
If you get seriously frozen,
how much reputation can be redeemed?
Moreover, the more they look down on me,
the more peacefully we live,
Just for this peace,
now I have to wrong you,
Then let's both suffer together,
♫ Promise to the death ♫
♫ Weaving a tale of love,
everything is settled ♫
♫ How can I resign myself to fate,
after living for a lifetime ♫
♫ The wind will rise again, listening closely ♫
[Hedong Duke's Mansion]
♫ Catch that echo of fate ♫
Good news, Madam,
What happened?
The news comes from the Advisor Su
of Liangzhou is that
Kudi Liuli is dead,
Is it true?
Absolutely true,
He said that
she was strangled to death by his deputy,
And he sent
the Divorce Notice written
by Pei Xingjian himself as evidence,
Good, that's great,
Reward the messenger now,
Hupo, I'm going to host
a feast to celebrate today,
Madam, the operation
to assassinate Pei Xingjian has failed,
So many people were dispatched,
and yet they've failed,
The letter also mentions that
Pei Xingjian and Kudi Liuli
have crossed over the Ohaido,
They will soon arrive in Xizhou,
Didn't you say that Kudi Liuli was dead?
Indeed, Su Nanjin said
that Kudi Liuli was already dead,
Then how did she go to Xizhou
with Pei Xingjian?
I don't know,
Useless, a bunch of useless people,
Princess,
Madam!
- Princess,
- Scram,
Get away,
Let's go,
Giddyap,
Hush,
Senior Official, Madam Kudi,
we are almost at Xizhou now,
[Xizhou]
Father,
Shouyue, you're here at last,
- Dear officials,
- Thank you for your hard work on this journey,
You've all worked so hard, really,
Thank you,
- You've been running around, Senior Official Pei,
- You've worked hard, Senior Official Pei,
Thank you, Protector-General Qu,
You've worked hard, Senior Official Pei,
Do you know?
We are all here,
waiting for you to come,
Finally, you have come now,
Xizhou has hope now,
Finally, we have awaited the arrival of
Senior Official Pei,
Shouyue, the banquet has been prepared
for a long time,
Join the feast with me now,
I want to give you a welcome feast, Let's go,
Protector-General Qu, I…
- Let's go,
- Liuli…
[Gaochang City]
Let's go,
Are all you people from Xizhou like this?
Minister,
I have really broadened my horizons today,
[Silver Bright Moon of Tianshan Mountains]
Shouyue, try this,
This is our Xizhou's specialty cuisine,
I guarantee that you've never tasted it before,
Okay,
Let me toast to you first,
Cheers, Protector-General,
Please sit down, You are a guest,
Cheers,
Thank you for your hospitality,
Protector-General,
No thanks,
Eat this, Shouyue,
- Thank you, Protector-General,
- A piece of meat,
It's extremely delicious,
Is the Protector-General's
acting a bit over the top?
Shouyue, let me toast the second drink to you,
Please sit,
I don't think so, I think
- Cheers, Senior Official,
- he's very sincere,
All of you greet him,
- Try this meat,
- I just want to drink,
Senior Official, let me offer a toast to you,
Isn't that a bit beneath his dignity?
Approachable and humble, Respectable!
[Weaving A Tale of Love 2]
[Adapted from the novel 'The Bright Moon of the Great Tang' by Lan Yunshu, an author of Yuewen Group]
♫ I write my longing for you in Spring ♫
♫ The red plum is in full bloom like you ♫
♫ By the pond, next to the willow trees ♫
♫ I write a poem
to tell our story from the past ♫
♫ The years pass by like a bird♫
♫ The destiny always comes with regrets ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ Outside the pavilion, by the bridge ♫
♫ Under the moonlight,
we parted at the doorstep ♫
♫ I've endured hardship
to tell our lingering story ♫
♫ Remembrance of past things ♫
♫ As time goes by, seasons change ♫
♫ Flowers wither, and winter has come ♫
♫ Years pass by, and we're young no more ♫
♫ A snowy day, someone sings a sad song ♫
♫ Against the window,
I had a drink for pleasure ♫
♫ The moon still hangs in the sky,
but I'm no longer in the mood ♫
♫ It's quite and cold outside,
but I grab my pen again ♫
♫ The destiny always comes with regrets ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ Outside the pavilion, by the bridge ♫
♫ Under the moonlight,
we parted at the doorstep ♫
♫ I've endured hardship
to tell our lingering story ♫
♫ Remembrance of past things ♫
♫ As time goes by, seasons change ♫
♫ Flowers wither, and winter has come ♫
♫ Years pass by, and we're young no more ♫
♫ Winter comes again, and flowers wither ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ I look outside, like the poems asking ♫
♫ My love, have you
found someone good for you ♫
♫ Remembrance of past things ♫
♫ As time goes by, seasons change ♫
♫ Flowers wither, and winter has come ♫
♫ Years pass by, and we're young no more ♫
♫ Winter comes again, and flowers wither ♫
♫ Who could relieve my pain of love ♫
♫ I look outside, like the poems asking ♫
♫ My love, have you
found someone good for you ♫