(He is Psychometric)
(Dec. 3, 2005, 6:25 PM)
That person is here, Mom.
Did he find us?
Promise me that you will do as I say from now on.
You must do as I say.
Okay?
(PSYCHOMETRY A combination of Greek words)
(PSYCHE/Soul and METRON/Measuring)
(An ability to measure the soul of a person or)
(an object and interpreting it)
(He is Psychometric, Episode 6)
You know who did this, right? Prosecutor Kang.
That man has been stalking you.
He's been watching you for a long time.
He was watching you on the day we fell
from the apartments, too.
That person is here, Mom.
Perhaps it won't end until I die.
How are you?
I know that you're watching him,
but Sung-mo is doing fine.
From now on, I'll protect him.
Ahn!
Wake up, Lee Ahn!
(Lee Ahn)
You jerk, why are you so late?
Do you know how long I've been waiting for you?
Let go of me, will you?
Tripping and falling would look less embarrassing, you know.
I've practiced these skills for years,
so I can do lots of things without using my hands.
Hey, are you okay?
Dae-bong told me that you got stabbed by a knife.
This is nothing.
You know, I've experienced so many troubles in my life.
This is why people say that the idiots are actually brave.
I'm worried that I will be dumbed down to your level.
Dumbed??what?
I'm worried that I might get into a mess because of you.
I might become an idiot for training you.
So you decided to do it?
Yeah, I'm here to tell you that.
Let's do it.
I look forward to working with you.
About my dad's case??
Can we try it when I have
improved you??enough?
Yes, let's do that.
We're ready for the meeting.
Okay, let's go.
From now on, we will investigate the two Kang Hee-sooks.
The first one is the real Kang Hee-sook, who was murdered
four to five years ago and was abandoned at the stream,
and the second one is the fake Kang Hee-sook,
who posed as the real one and worked as a caretaker
at Hanmin Nursing Hospital.
If that caretaker posed as Kang Hee-sook,
then that mysterious woman must be the culprit.
If so, did she also kill Park Soo-young, the first victim?
We have to consider all possibilities.
I'll look into the fake one who worked at the nursing hospital.
The woman wearing a ring.
A ring??
but I don't see any record of her wearing a ring.
Who said that? Is there a witness?
Yes, there is. You don't need to know.
Then I'll look for the family of the murdered Kang Hee-sook.
We need to know the time she went missing to find the suspect.
Yes.
Okay.
If we find new information, let's share it with each other.
I first need to go see Ahn.
Uh, sure??
- Go ahead. - I'll call you.
Did Prosecutor Kang just talk casually to you?
Did it sound like that to you, too?
I'm not the only one who heard it that way, right?
What's with him? It scares me.
Usually when someone talks casually to you,
that means he or she wants to be your friend, right?
Right?
But why, all the sudden?
People usually hate it when you suddenly drop honorifics.
Are you actually happy about this?
Let's go, we need to start investigating, too??
We need to go.
Hey, wait.
What about the thing I told you to look into?
When you leave the hospital, come to the station.
Until then, I'll think about how to train you.
Yoon Jae-in.
If you're going to thank me, then don't.
I'm not doing this for you. I'm doing this for me.
It doesn't matter.
I'm doing it for you, too.
You jerk, why are you so late?
Do you know how long I've been waiting for you?
That Yoon Jae-in. Seriously.
(Delicious Porridge)
I'm sure you have lots of questions for me,
but I'm not ready to answer them.
Make sure you eat well.
I'm not doing this for you. I'm doing this for me.
It doesn't matter.
I'm doing it for you, too.
Thank goodness you made a positive decision.
Ahn told me that
human memories are like mixed up pills in one container.
So he can't tell if it's poison
or an antidote.
I'm not sure if I have
poison or antidotes in my medicine container,
but I have to know, so I'll take time to do it.
Yes.
That's exactly what I want, too.
What?
By the way, who was this person who stabbed Ahn?
I heard that he's been stalking you for a long time.
I don't know who that person is, either.
But what I know is that I can't??
leave it all mixed-up anymore.
Detective Eun. Here it is.
(Seoheun Delivery Service)
Is this it?
And we got no photo of the suspect?
Yes, the CCTV at Prosecutor Kang's house and the road
showed the car only.
I called the delivery service company too,
but they said they don't know who took it.
We asked them for a list of the employees leaving at that time.
What about the place where Ahn was stabbed?
There was no CCTV there at all.
He was wearing a cap, so the witnesses couldn't see his face.
Did you check the CCTVs of the shops nearby?
What about the black boxes of other parked cars?
Ah??I didn't think of that.
"Ah??You didn't think of that?"
Those are the basics, you know.
If those are the basics,
then I'm sure Prosecutor Kang looked into it already.
- Prosecutor Kang? - Yes.
I called to ask for evidence materials,
but Prosecutor Kang already made copies
of all of that.
So that means Prosecutor Kang saw the faces of possible suspects?
Yes. Basics.
We're here. You can get out of the car now.
Why are we here??
I have something to give you.
This is everything I recorded about Ahn's power until now.
I'm sure it will be helpful.
(Sep. 10, 2008, Location: Church playground)
Did you write down everything from then until now?
From now on, you need to do this.
I have so many questions, but I'll ask only one of them.
Just how much do I have to improve his power of psychometry?
Enough so he can help with investigations?
Enough so he can find out the culprit with his power?
Would that be good enough?
This mission will end
when Ahn is??
able to perform psychometry on me.
Yes, I will wait. I will.
Just don't run away again.
It's all gone cold. Totally cold.
(Closed on Sundays)
It's been so long.
I'm sorry for being unable to come and see you.
Your aunt told me that you became a police officer.
I'm so proud of you. My daughter.
You saw how I'm doing, so it's time for you to say sorry, right?
Then I'll cry, again,
and suffer for a few days at home.
I didn't come here for a while, because I hate that.
I know.
I don't have much time, so I'll get to the point.
I am going to do it.
I won't run away or avoid that incident anymore.
I will re-investigate everything from the beginning.
- Jae-in. - I thought about living
my own life, regardless of you,
but there are unresolved issues at my foundation.
No matter what I put on top of it, it's a wobbly mess.
Jae-in, don't waste your time.
Me wasting my time was enough.
You go and live your life.
What can you even do at this point?
I heard that you fail your parole review every time.
You're doing that on purpose.
That's not it.
You're thinking that it's better for you to stay here.
Because you think you'll only hold me back if you get out.
Are you planning to die in here?
Go.
Don't come here ever again.
I killed all those people
at the apartments.
(Seoheun Medical Center)
- What are you doing? - Yikes, that scared me??
Don't touch my curtain with your dirty hands, you jerk.
Can you now even see without touching? I'll go wash them, okay?
Ugh, hey, move.
Ugh. Damn it.
Ugh, you're so damn grumpy.
Your hospital bill has been paid already.
It's been paid already?
Yes.
Was my "brother" here?
Oh, wow.
Is he your brother?
Ah, this reaction confirms that Sung-mo was here.
Wow, what a happy life you have.
He pays for everything and you drive my car.
How will you spend your parents' insurance payout?
That's not important right now.
Wow??Did you know he never came to see me here?
I never got to see my car, either.
If it's been paid, then let's go.
Yeah, you missed me, didn't you?
Yeah, me too.
There, there.
Did he bully you? Are you okay?
- It's okay. I'm here. - Hey.
- Come on, get in. - Okay.
By the way, isn't it weird?
This is my car.
But this looks natural.
(The World of Psychic Powers and Mystery)
(Seven Brief Lessons on Physics)
(Duration: six hours /Ahn actively uses his power)
(If he uses it too much, his physical energy declines)
(The more motivated he is to perform psychometry,)
(the more powerful his power becomes)
(Using the power of psychometry Negative opinions of the world)
Feb. 25, 2008.
A child who lost his parents came to the orphanage.
He said that he let go of his mom's hand at a theme park.
But Ahn performed psychometry on him
and found out the address.
But that child
was abandoned by his parents.
They didn't lose him. They abandoned him.
The police found his parents,
but they did not take the child back with them.
It seems that the truth he sees with his power
is still quite burdensome to him.
In the world seen through Ahn's power,
love, joy, and sadness,
are all fake.
(Ahn hates crowded places, but we went to the park)
(This is the place where Ahn never goes to)
(A place where he can feel the emotions of random people)
Is that so?
(Seoheun Police Station)
Hey, why are we coming here?
Because I have business here.
What is this place?
Bye.
Wow, you came straight to Yoon Jae-in after getting out.
You're so pathetic.
Children, let's go inside now.
- Huh? - Let's go inside.
But I didn't play that much.
Yes, come on in. Did you have fun?
Looks like you have business here, too.
I'm going first.
Hi.
Are you okay now?
I'm now well enough to chew and eat rocks.
Don't eat rocks. Eat these.
What is this?
Did you bring rice cakes for my discharge from the hospital?
Wow, I'm so touched.
Thanks.
Wow.
What??What is this?
What's in it?
Oh??
I delicately put mustard in it, but you didn't see it.
Mustard rice cake psychometry is a failure.
Water, water, water.
Water? Here it is.
What is this?
Pacific sand lance sauce?
The second psychometry is a failure, too.
Wow, this is a disappointing first day.
Hey, what did you expect from me?
Did you think that if I drink coffee, I'd see people picking
coffee beans in Africa or what?
Follow me.
To where?
I thought about so many things,
but I came to only one conclusion.
What conclusion?
Have you heard of the 10,000 Hours Rule?
It means that the time you try hard to be an expert
in one area is 10,000 hours.
Those hours may be for loving someone.
So-hyun is dancing in front of children.
Or for working, for someone else.
Anyway, this theory says that you require 10,000 hours
to become an expert in that area.
10,000 hours??
Three hours a day equals 10 years, five hours equal five years,
and 10 hours equal 3 years.
Even if you theoretically thought about it for 24 hours straight,
it would take 416.666666667 days.
Would saying 417 days make you look less smart?
How old were you when you got your power?
I was eight years old.
If you polished, tightened and oiled your power
for three hours a day for the past 13 years,
you would've become an expert by now.
You wasted a lot of time treating your power like a freak
and pushing it away from you.
Still, I had quite a bit of trials and errors.
Do you think I just wasted my time?
So,
considering all that time,
I think you need to study hard for at least three months.
Study?
So, what is this place?
They say studying is the easiest thing, but??
I'm not telling you to do differentiations and integrals.
Ugh, what are those?
Starting today, I'll assign 10 books to you per day.
You'll read all of them until I'm out of work, page by page,
and write about your opinions right here.
I don't expect book reports, so write at least one line, okay?
Weren't we supposed to
do "everything" for my psychometry?
This is the first "thing."
If you can't read them all, you can borrow them. So get ready.
Hey, I hate touching books read by other people.
And you're telling me to read them page by page?
I know that you hate it. That's why I'm telling you to do it.
I read lots of books about investigations, you know.
What, like "Case Closed" and "The Kindaichi Case Files?"
- You're keen. - Do you think those
locked-room murders would happen in Korea that often?
I read mystery novels, too??
Sherlock Holmes, Edgar Allan Poe, and modern mystery novels.
And American, British, Japanese and Koreans dramas, like CSI.
If crime movies are elective courses,
(Understanding and Studying of Practical Investigations)
this is a required course.
Hey, you shouldn't approach this like that.
My power is extraordinary and this is too ordinary.
Yeah.
You're a psychometrist.
You touch people to read their dormant memories.
And you read memories from objects, too.
Yes, that's who I am.
That's why I came to the conclusion to make you study more.
The more you know, the more you see.
You don't know that much, so you can't see that much.
Are you telling me indirectly that I am ignorant?
No, I'm telling you directly.
The more you know, learn and realize,
the more you'll see the pain of others and understand them.
That sounds too textbook-like??
Did you think about what kind of person
that woman in the luggage could have been?
Or about her family?
Or about how she died like that and the fear she felt
before her death? Did you think about those things?
That body??
No, that person,
isn't a tool to make your power come out.
Uh??
(Kang Hee-sook)
What? Are you here again?
How persistent.
I thought finding her name would speed everything up,
but it isn't easy.
Did you find the fake Kang Hee-sook?
No.
Ah, but there was one person who remembers her
at the hospital.
We're working on the composite sketch right now.
And this case will be openly investigated from today on.
Yeah. Do whatever you can to find her family.
She's dead, but no one is looking for her.
Poor woman.
Why are you so sentimental today?
Don't worry.
I'll stay at your funeral for the whole three days, Dr. Hong.
Hey, age doesn't dictate one's death.
You might die before I do.
Why are you so obsessed with life? That's unpleasant.
Okay then, I'll die before you do.
I hope you live long.
But make sure to come to my funeral.
What about that kid?
You mean Ahn? He left the hospital today.
- Why do you ask? - Will being stabbed by a knife
affect his power or do anything else?
Why are you interested all the sudden?
You told me to make sure you won't see him ever again.
So what?
Well, I'm going home early today.
I'm taking rest of the day off and getting some rest.
Go get some rest.
Ah, I got no time to play with you, Dr. Hong.
I'm super busy.
You're not the only one I can play with, Detective Eun.
I'm taking some time off, you dummy.
The autopsy room will be empty.
If you have to suddenly come to the autopsy room,
use this.
You know this, right? Make it "beep" and it "beep" opens.
Bye.
This is why I like Dr. Hong.
What's wrong with this?
It must be broken.
(Psychology of Psychology)
Why??Why is it in there?
How could a thief report the police first?
She got caught stealing a book last month,
so we let her go, thinking it was a mistake. But again??
I'm sure someone keeps putting the books in my bag.
Why is she always feeling victimized like that?
She's a habitual offender.
Ha, is she an attention seeker or a kleptomaniac?
Hey.
I really didn't do it.
Is this a big case?
Should I use my power like last time?
Well, sure.
Where were you sitting at?
Here.
And I put my bag here.
When did you leave your seat?
I leave my seat often.
I have to go eat, answer phone calls, and more.
Uh??
I saw the person who put the book
in this lady's bag.
The culprit is
someone wearing red nail polish.
Excuse me, but please show me your fingernails.
Nobody's wearing red nail polish.
That can't be.
I saw it for sure.
What if she ran away already?
I don't think so.
If someone really put the book
in your bag on purpose,
I'm sure she wants to see how this goes.
Watching his or her own crime.
That's a kind of criminal psychology.
When are you going to stop disturbing us?
Ugh, you're interrupting my studies.
So annoying.
Uh, wait.
Isn't that a fingernail?
What?
Yikes, what is this? Oh.
Yikes. Damn it.
Oh, no, I didn't do it.
Yes, you did.
You were carrying such clear evidence.
Damn it.
She dropped it?
She's not the culprit, right?
How did you know?
I have a firm belief about a certain suspect.
Can I have a conversation with you for a moment, please?
- Me? - When you showed me your nails,
I saw that the tips of your nails were damaged.
Like wounds formed by tearing out artificial nails in a hurry.
Ah??You see, I have a habit of biting my fingernails.
You know that we can do a DNA test not only with blood and hair,
but also with fingernails, right?
Your nails were damaged while tearing them out.
Wow, you're bleeding, too.
Shall we proceed with the case, do a DNA test and call you?
Or would you apologize now politely and end it?
Hey, did you do it?
She's totally obsessive-compulsive.
She attaches notes when I breathe, saying it's noisy.
She glares at me for shaking my legs.
And she freaks out when I use a pen.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
It seems like you're bringing the cases to us.
But the problem is that they're too petty.
Anyway, Officer lady, you're the best!
Thank you too, oppa.
Oh, come on.
Wow, what a nuisance she is.
I will never do that in the library.
(Focus!)
(You need to focus)
(Can't you stay awake?)
(Ji-soo)
Huh?
Hey, where are you?
At a library? With Officer Yoon?
Hey, do you think studying will help you with psychometry?
I don't know.
Anyway, I'm trapped by Officer Yoon due to
special order of Prosecutor Kang, so keep that in mind.
Hey, what's Prosecutor Kang plotting?
Who knows what he's thinking?
Hey, anyway, we need to meet. Meet me in a bit.
Later on? Where?
At the autopsy room.
I'm always available for the autopsy room.
Yeah, see you in a bit.
Okay.
Yes!
(Aren't you going to study?)
"Aren't you going to study?"
I got it! I got it right!
Yes, I got it!
Okay, okay, I will.
I will study, okay?
Officer Yoon is making Ahn study for psychometry?
Looks like there's something between Ahn and Officer Yoon.
No, would that make it between three people?
Including Prosecutor Kang?
(The abandoned luggage case now openly investigated)
What the heck? Why is he there?
I'm sure you remember the black luggage with a dead body in it,
which was found at a stream in Seoheun-dong, Seoul, last month.
Even though she has already been identified,
no relatives of her have been found, right?
No. This woman, presumed to have died four to five years ago,
has been identified as Kang Hee-sook, age 59.
But when she went missing is unclear,
and the investigation is experiencing a stormy passage.
Okay, could you please enlarge the photo
so the viewers can see it in details?
If you know anything about the deceased
Ms. Kang Hee-sook, age 59, or her family.
Any information
would greatly help with the investigation.
Yes. By the way, we did our own investigation.
We found that the deceased Kang Hee-sook
was determined missing during the fire at Hanmin two years ago.
What is this about?
That wasn't a prescreened question.
We received a report that the Kang Hee-sook who went missing
after the fire isn't the Kang Hee-sook in the photo.
That means someone's living with the identity of
the deceased Kang Hee-sook.
Can you please explain it,
so the viewers can understand it?
That's something we cannot speak of at this moment.
If you know Ms. Kang Hee-sook, age 59,
who died four to five years ago, please call us.
(If you know Ms. Kang Hee-sook, age 59, please call us)
He shouldn't leave like that, right?
That's a broadcasting accident.
He shouldn't do that, but??
Wow, he's so charismatic.
Our Daddy-Long-Legs.
- Stop saying Daddy-Long-Legs. - Why not?
Why is he your Daddy-Long-Legs, ma'am?
He seems too young to be called that by you.
You calling me ma'am sounds
even weirder, Lieutenant Nam.
Then what should I call you?
Ms. Sook-ja? That's embarrassing.
When did this come out?
Ugh!
Ugh, disgusting.
Just call me Ms. Oh.
Everyone in this town calls me "Ms. Oh, the singing teacher."
Haven't you heard?
Ms. Oh, huh?
Sook-ja, you were at the station as a fraud victim and cried,
with your eyeliner smudged like a horror movie. My, you've grown.
What??What are you talking about in front of Officer Yoon?
What is this? Did you two know each other already?
Oh, of course not.
We just??saw each other on the street, passing by.
Why are you here?
Because it's time to go home.
What is this?
"The title of the book."
"Understanding and Studying of Practical Investigations."
"My opinion."
"Why do they mix Chinese characters into the books?"
There are so many of them and I couldn't read it.
Ugh, damn it.
"The title of the book." "The Crime Scene."
"My opinion."
"The part about murders with guns was quite impressive."
"Do you think those a murder like that
will ever happen in Korea?"
"Featuring Yoon Jae-in?"
Murders with guns in Korea are
as rare as locked-room murders.
You little??
Do you actually have any will to study?
I will show you the understanding and studying of
practical investigations at the crime scenes.
Follow me.
(NFS public servant ID /Hong Soo-yeon)
Door unlocked.
Welcome.
I thought about bringing Officer Yoon to this place as well.
Thank you.
Of course, we should come here together.
We're playing big parts in this case.
Right?
Actually, my expectations for him aren't high.
Ahn has been here about 10 times,
- and he almost always failed. - Detective Eun?
Do you know what he saw with psychometry on his first try?
- Underwear sizes - Ji-soo!
Don't tell her.
But,
when in hindsight, that was a very important clue.
The underwear Ahn saw with psychometry
were for the women who died in the patient's room,
and that woman who posed as Kang Hee-sook brought those.
What??What do you mean?
That woman wearing a ring.
The woman you saw with psychometry two years ago.
The fake Kang Hee-sook.
The fake??Kang Hee-sook?
I saw it on the news.
That someone's living with the dead Kang Hee-sook's identity.
Yes.
That woman Ahn saw with psychometry
stole the name of this dead woman and was living with it.
It seems that Prosecutor Kang is taking his time to train you,
but I can't do that, so I need to see it now.
About why and who
killed this woman and lived her life.
Yeah, I have no idea about what you're talking about,
but I need to see it, right?
Wait.
- I can't agree with you, either. - What?
Ahn might be able to find something out
by doing psychometry on her.
He might see the moment of her death,
or something from when she was still alive.
But I'm sure he will be confused.
- And might not understand. - So?
So what? Are you telling me to wait for 10,000 hours?
- No, I can't wait. - No, you have to wait.
Please show us the investigation files
compiled thus far.
- What? - I know that this is
a rare opportunity, for both me and Ahn.
So, if you can give me one hour,
I will make sure Ahn understands this case.
I'm sure he'll be able to see a lot more.
Don't worry. Trust me.
Alright, Officer Yoon. I know what you mean.
I'll go get the files, so wait here.
She's quite good. That Yoon Jae-in.
Hey, you??
Ah.
I didn't tremble in front of Detective Eun, right?
Was I okay?
Yeah, you were totally awesome, Yoon Jae-in.
So much for awesome.
I couldn't understand what Detective Eun said, either.
What?
We can't leave here just after touching a body one time.
This is a rare opportunity.
It may be my last chance to go to a criminal team.
I will use you and
find out all of the information about this case??
So that was it, huh?
You'll go to a criminal team as a reward for
- training me, huh? - Uh, you see??
If so, are there two tools you can use to go to
a criminal team in this place?
Bragging has become my habit,
so I blabbered without thinking.
Well, alright.
I can start thinking right now. It's not too late.
About who she is,
and why she had to be lying here.
Let's do this.
Together.
Ugh.
Why are you here?
I heard that the composite sketch for the fake Kang Hee-sook is out.
Ah??
Why did they call you first, instead of me?
Ah, I saw you on TV.
Oh, you made an appearance in person.
You looked great on screen.
And storming out at the end was quite impressive, too.
It seems that the information leaked from somewhere.
Tell your team members to tighten up the security.
It wasn't leaked by us, the police.
I'm Eun Ji-soo, the meticulous. Don't you know?
The prosecution should tighten up their security.
By the way, why are you here at this hour?
I suddenly wanted to see Dr. Hong.
I heard Dr. Hong went home early.
Ah??
If so, can you explain where you are taking our files to?
Detective Eun Ji-soo, the meticulous?
Ah, you see??Uh??
Ahn and Officer Yoon are at the autopsy room right now.
I'm sure Ahn didn't ask you to show him the files.
Did Officer Yoon ask for them?
Yeah, she won't make Ahn do psychometry without information.
I knew it.
It's Officer Yoon, right?
What?
The one you want Ahn to do psychometry on.
- That's right. - Why?
Why is Officer Yoon the one?
What a disadvantageous relationship we have.
I clearly show my thoughts,
and you show nothing, unless you say it.
Officer Yoon Jae-in's father is
Yoon Tae-ha.
The culprit behind
the fire at Yeongseong Apartments.
I'll get the composite sketch and go to the autopsy room.
The direct cause of death must be hemorrhage in the occipital area.
You said you'll help me understand it.
It means that she died because she was hit on her head
and she bled a lot. Got it?
And the murderer put her into the luggage after killing her?
And then threw her into Han River.
Did you see the news with Prosecutor Kang as the guest?
This woman has been dead for four to five years,
but she has been found now, after all those years.
I'm sure she had something to say.
Something to say?
The fact that I found the body that has been underwater for
such a long time means she has something to show me.
Yeah, make sure to see it and boast about it.
I should.
Boasting is habitual and quite contagious.
Ugh, why are you so late?
The time you wasted doesn't count.
That one hour starts right now, okay?
Okay.
Officer Yoon Jae-in's father is Yoon Tae-ha.
The culprit behind the fire at Yeongseong Apartments.
(The abandoned luggage case with a dead body)
Kang Hee-sook. Here's the cause of death.
She did die from hemorrhage in the occipital area.
Hey, you were right.
So only her cause of death and identity are revealed, right?
Huh?
Yeah??
Can I see the files for the Hanmin Nursing Hospital fire, please?
The person posed as this woman worked at that hospital, right?
That's right. The woman wearing a ring. The one I saw.
Yeah.
Looks like the composite sketch of this woman is out.
Prosecutor Kang is bringing the materials here.
What? Sung-mo is?
Yeah, he knows that you guys are here at the autopsy room.
Will he??be angry by any chance?
For me coming here without any permission as well?
Don't worry about that.
I've never seen him smile
so sincerely like that before.
Her eyes were more gentle than these.
- Like these? - And she was skinnier than this.
Ah, okay.
Uh??Yes, like that.
051203??
Found him.
(Composite sketch of Kang Hee-sook)
Here's the composite sketch of the fake Kang Hee-sook.
Hey, hey, he is the witness.
(Witness)
(Kim Gap-yong)
Ugh, why isn't he here yet?
Let's begin on our own.
Huh? Ms. Kang Hee-sook, you aren't dead yet.
I'm sorry, but that person doesn't want any more trouble.
She was lying on the ground, bleeding a lot from her head.
Don't hurry and take time to think.
What did you see?
A piece of black luggage.
A hammer.
And a man.
A man?
What man?
I've seen him somewhere.
It was him. I'm sure.
Kim Gap-yong?
Are you sure it was him?
I'm sure. It was him.
He killed Kang Hee-sook.
He was the witness of the Hanmin Nursing Hospital fire, right?
But??A murder by sudden attack??
Did you say you were there at the Hanmin Nursing Hospital fire?
I am an insurance planner.
I'd like to hear the testimony about
the fire case for one last time.
I know it would be troublesome, but could you please come here?
I found you, Prosecutor Kang, on the call logs,
so I called you first.
It seems that he was attacked on his way to meet us.
I remember it clearly.
He was murdered right after getting Prosecutor Kang's call.
Why did he??
- Lee Ahn! - Ahn!
- Ahn! - Lee Ahn!
Ahn!
Lee Ahn, what's wrong? Wake up!
- Hey, Ahn! Ahn! - Lee Ahn!
- Ahn! - Lee Ahn! Lee Ahn!
What's wrong with him? Ahn! Ahn!
- Ahn! Ahn! - Lee Ahn! Lee Ahn!
Prosecutor Kang! Ahn collapsed!
I am going to do it.
I won't run away or avoid that incident anymore.
I will re-investigate everything from the beginning.
I thought about living my own life, regardless of you,
but there are unresolved issues at my foundation.
No matter what I put on top of it, it's a wobbly mess.
Ugh??you're being miserable, again.
Hey, go to sleep.
Ugh, the prison guards will be here soon.
They just did their last patrol around.
They won't come today.
Damn it, don't you get any sleep?
Damn it. Damn it.
Lee Ahn, are you okay?
Are you awake?
So you mean that man named Kim Gap-yong
killed the two women in the two pieces of luggage?
- With a hammer? - Yes.
But it sounded like someone was behind him.
"I'm sorry, but that person doesn't want any more trouble."
That person doesn't want any more trouble.
So that means someone incited the murder of the two women?
Ah, the composite sketch of the fake Kang Hee-sook.
Was she there, too?
No, that was all I saw.
Is she the fake Kang Hee-sook?
Yes. Take a good look at her.
Is she the one you saw when you did psychometry for
- Hanmin Nursing Hospital? - But I didn't see her face.
Still, I'm asking you just in case.
Could she have incited the murder?
To get a new identity?
Anyway, Kim Gap-yong killed the real Kang Hee-sook
and made a fake Kang Hee-sook, huh?
If so, since Kim Gap-yong testified about the fire case,
his testimony now has a higher chance of being false.
Just who is this woman, anyway??
Then we must start over with Kim Gap-yong for the investigation.
Looks like we saw everything to see from the dead Kang Hee-sook,
and finding the missing Kang Hee-sook is at a standstill.
That's exactly what I was about to say.
Me, too.
I'm sorry. I crossed the line, right?
No, you didn't. You made the correct point.
Uh??sorry to ask you this at this serious moment, but
when you said finding the missing Kang Hee-sook is at a standstill,
does that mean we're standing still?
What?
He's the powerful one who saw the murder scene,
so shall we forgive his ignorance for that?
I'm sorry.
Why, why are you sorry, Officer Yoon?
I know, right?
After all, I decided to teach him.
In accordance with the 10,000 Hours Rule,
just wait for 416.666666667 days.
I will turn over a new loaf.
- Turn over a new leaf. - Turn over a new leaf.
You two have done so much today.
With results like these, we might not have to wait for
416.666666667 days, you know.
That's what I mean.
Ahn, and you, Officer Yoon??
Cheer up.
Yes, I will polish, tighten and oil him even more.
What am I, a machine?
I'll leave Ahn in your hands, Officer Yoon.
Let's go.
Wait.
Aren't you going home? Don't you have anything to say?
Look at me, huh?
Not here. Look.
We haven't talked since this happened to me.
I'm sure you have lots of questions too,
but so does she.
Yeah, I'll take him today.
Move.
Wow, what kind of "brother" is he?
Hey, did you see? Wow??
Hey, you try hailing a taxi too.
Why did he kill them?
And why did he die?
- What? - He killed two women.
That man named Kim Gap-yong.
And then he was killed by someone.
About the fake Kang Hee-sook, you saw with psychometry
at the autopsy room for the first time.
The one wearing a ring.
Do you remember anything else about her?
It's been two years already.
It'd be weird if I actually remember something.
But I remember everything about you from two years ago.
What??do you mean??by that?
Because you were so peculiar.
Ah, ah??
Hi, Auntie.
Don't get shocked and listen to me.
Tae-ha??
No, your dad??
Taxi??
Taxi!
What happened?
I have to go now.
Is it that thing again? Hyperventilation?
A bag, do you have a bag?
I don't.
Don't worry.
I won't touch you until you allow me to.
(He is Psychometric)
I killed all those people at the apartments.
Why are you saying such weak things?
You know who that person is, right?
It's even more miserable if you waste my life because of me.
I will find this person and kill him or her.
I think he's asking for help.
Will you come with Prosecutor Kang
and Detective Eun next time?
At this rate, if you know Kim Gap-yong, raise your hand.