(He is Psychometric)
Has he been identified?
Uh, more than that,
I found a cold case in which the fingerprints are a match.
A cold case?
It was in Yeonhae-dong, Gangnyeong, Gangwon-do, in 1996,
and even though the fingerprints of the culprit was found,
it seems that they couldn't identify him either at the time,
so it turned into a cold case.
(Gangnyeong Steel Company)
(12-5 Yeonhae-dong)
What??what kind of case was it?
What is this?
Why??is this thing??here??
Is this a basement?
We need to go in there.
Sung-mo, run!
Run! Run! Run!
It's a case in which the culprit locked up a woman
and a child in a basement for nine years.
Detective Eun, are you listening to me?
That's all there is on the record.
I'll text you the station in charge and the case number.
(PSYCHOMETRY A combination of Greek words)
(PSYCHE/Soul and METRON/Measuring)
(An ability to measure the soul of a person or)
(an object and interpreting it)
(He is Psychometric, Episode 12)
What??what is all this??
Why does a basement have bars like this??
Was he locked up in here?
I saw Sung-mo running away.
He was??seven? No, like eight years old.
Ji-soo.
I'm sure he was nine.
Sung-mo had been
locked up here until he was nine years old.
What do you mean?
How is that even possible?
Officer Yoon,
take a look at this place with Ahn for now.
I'll go back to the station and dig deeper into this case.
Hey, Kang Sung-mo.
Why do you have so many secrets?
You've been thinking and worrying all by yourself for two years.
I'm telling you, I will help you.
Am I that unhelpful to you?
What a disadvantageous relationship we have.
I clearly show my thoughts,
and you show nothing, unless you say it.
Should I just step outside?
I think I'll only be in the way of you reading memories.
Please go check if there's any objects to do psychometry on.
Okay.
Don't overdo it.
Remember? You collapsed last time.
Okay.
Don't do this to me!
Let me out! Let me out!
Please let me out!
Don't do this to me!
If you mess with this child, I will die, too.
Is that what you want?
Sung-mo.
I will make sure that you get out of this place.
(Gangnyeong Police Station)
(Archives)
You assume that these confinement cases only happen overseas.
Most people don't know, but there's a lot in our country too.
Like the slavery case in Sinan,
or the case of confinement and assault by a pseudo-religion.
If it was a confinement case of this magnitude, it would've
attracted a lot of attention but I've never heard of it.
How could it not attract attention even after it became a cold case?
Because it became a cold case, it was swept under the rug.
What?
Please say something. Anything is fine.
Hey, you need to say something if you want us to help you, huh?
A woman was locked up for nine years and had a child,
but the police never knew about it.
The victims escaped on their own,
without the help of the police.
The police were about to be criticized to death for
not being able to find the culprit, or even a shadow no less.
And do you know what the worst problem was?
That this culprit was undocumented.
So, this was a case that could've brought to light every one of
the police's weaknesses,
so they covered it up as quietly as possible?
Ah, here it is.
(Confinement at a steel factory in Gangnyeong-si, cold case, 1996)
(Wanted: Suspect of confinement at a steel factory in Gangnyeong)
(Name: Kang Geun-taek (pseudonym) Unidentified individual)
Kang Geun-taek.
This is the name Kang Eun-joo, the victim, remembered
but since he's undocumented, the name was useless as well.
By the way, what is this?
A long scar around his neck?
The culprit allegedly had an old scar around his neck,
but we don't know from what.
Since Kang Eun-joo and her son were the only ones who saw it.
Uh, if so, by any chance,
is there any evidence from that time still archived?
The victim took everything a few years ago.
The victim?
Her son became a prosecutor.
Ah, I found out about this case when
I handed the evidence to that prosecutor.
I need to educate Sung-mo.
Buy me some books.
I beg you.
Why would he need that here?
The child does not smile.
Even with his ankle chained up, he doesn't say it hurts.
He doesn't want anything,
and he doesn't like anything, either.
Please??please. Any book is fine.
Even if it's just one.
Sung-mo needs to be able to feel something! Please!
If not, he'll end up??
As an emotionless monster, like me?
Yes.
I will never let my child
turn into a monster like you, obsessed with one person.
I will never let him become that.
Emotionless monster?
(Confinement case at a steel factory in Gangnyeong-si)
What is this?
"A behavioral analysis of Kang Sung-mo, the victim,"
"concluded that he suffers from alexithymia,"
"difficulty in expressing emotions."
Prosecutor Kang has alexithymia?
It is assumed that it was hereditary and
inherited from Kang Geun-taek.
Prosecutor Kang isn't very good at expressing his emotions,
but it's not because he suffers an emotional disorder.
What if Sung-mo
had been acting, perfectly?
Something's weird.
Not only Prosecutor Kang, but also Kang Geun-taek??
How can someone who has difficulty in expressing emotions,
love Kang Eun-joo, and obsess over her?
I don't know.
This isn't my area of expertise.
Anyway, I asked Dr. Hong, so she'll call me soon.
Yes, Dr. Hong.
If I just get to the point,
alexithymia occurs
when the amygdala is naturally small.
Amygdala?
All people have different personalities
due to the influence of the amygdala.
But this amygdala
can grow through conditioning
or under certain circumstances.
What kind of circumstance?
(Korean Dictionary)
Then, in Kang Geun-taek's case, it must be
the circumstances in which he met Kang Eun-joo.
She's the one who made him, someone without emotions,
fall in love for the first time.
Perhaps that's why he's even more obsessed with her.
Mom, what's out there, beyond those bars?
Trees.
Flowers.
Butterflies.
The sea.
The sky.
There are so many beautiful things out there.
Sung-mo, do you want to see them?
How do you like it? Isn't it pretty?
Go ahead and touch it.
Sung-mo, look over there.
I don't know what it means to "want to see them."
Or what "beautiful" is.
Does that mean Sung-mo was also under certain circumstances
where he started to feel emotions?
I'm sure Prosecutor Kang
kept trying hard, so he wouldn't become
a monster like Kang Geun-taek.
Ahn told me that he saw Prosecutor Kang
learning about emotions from his mother
through psychometry.
Dr. Hong.
Is someone with alexithymia
same as a psychopath?
I see why you would think that,
but alexithymia and psychopathy have different brain structures.
Psychopaths have no empathy at all,
no matter how much you teach them,
but people with alexithymia can change if they try hard.
Though they might not be perfect.
Thank you, Dr. Hong. I'll call you again.
Are you okay?
I always wondered why Kang Sung-mo
never asked me for help
during this whole time.
But now I know.
They risked everything to break the chains,
to come out into the world,
but people were busy looking the other way,
ignoring their wounds, rather than helping them.
Did Sung-mo find the basement more horrible,
or this world more horrible?
What's the use of breaking the chains?
That incident is
still holding onto Sung-mo by his ankle.
My dad once said
that wounds fester if you neglect them.
We finally opened the wound that's been covered up,
so everything will be fine.
Yeah.
A little more.
"What does 'tame' mean?"
said the little prince.
"It is an act too often neglected," said the fox.
"It means to establish ties."
I want to stop reading it.
I want to hear more.
The very last part.
No?
You'll regret it.
Don't do it.
No.
Don't do it!
Don't do it, please!
Don't hit him, please.
You should've acted like this from the beginning.
Okay, I'll read it.
But, I have a favor to ask of you, too.
What else do you need?
Clothes for the child, books, a flower pot??
You just need to answer my questions.
What is your real name?
Where are you from?
Kang Geun-taek.
That's my real name.
And??
I came from a place that exists, but does not exist.
What?
Now, as you've promised.
Read it.
"To me, you will be
unique in all the world."
"To you,
I shall be unique
in all the world . . ."
Yes.
I like
that very part.
Ahn.
Wake up, Ahn.
Lee Ahn.
Ahn.
Are you okay? Are you awake?
I told you to take it easy.
What if you die from doing this?
Don't get angry,
and just give me a candy.
Eat it.
If Officer Yoon and I collapse we at least get workers' comp,
you don't, so eat up.
Come on, Officer Yoon, make him eat.
What is this place that exists
but does not exist?
Was Prosecutor Kang able to find out the location of the culprit
with such a riddle-like clue?
An invisible man from a place that exists but does not exist.
Invisible man?
I told you earlier. He isn't even documented.
I saw it on the news too,
it said the invisible children whose births were never registered
have a high risk of being exposed to child abuse,
human trafficking and illegal adoption as they grow up.
I think there's a chance the culprit
had a similar childhood.
I think so, too.
Prosecutor Kang once won a commendation for catching
organ traffickers, human traffickers and panhandlers,
and some of the young victims who got rescued at the time
weren't registered??
Why did you stop speaking?
- I got it. - What?
All of Prosecutor Kang's cases,
I think it was a part of the process of finding that man.
If so, we need to look into the cases Prosecutor Kang worked on??
Hey, eat first. We need to go back quickly.
Eating isn't important right now.
If you don't eat it, I'll leave you here.
What do you mean, Ji-soo went to work at another station?
Ah, you see??A female officer was kidnapped
a few days ago.
It was a kidnapping and attempted murder,
but the culprit hasn't been caught yet.
The last time I saw her she said she was going
to investigate it herself and she left for Seoheun Police Station.
Wait.
Did you just say, Seoheun Police Station?
Yes, sir.
Seoheun Police Station??
(Fire and murder case at Yeongseong Apartments)
Time to eat.
By the way, about that Detective Eun lady.
Just what kind of case is she working on? Huh?
What does she need with a girl that just got discharged?
Dakgalbi.
You were announcing that Jae-in is your "kid" and stuff,
and you don't even know where she took your "kid"?
Beans boiled in soy sauce, stir-fried kimchi.
If she ends up in the hospital again,
then I will tell her to quit this damn job.
Bean sprout soup.
My nose is faster than my eyes, even in this uneasy situation.
Why?
By the way,
why are you here, Lieutenant Nam?
So I can eat.
No, I mean, you're more experienced than Jae-in
and you're a better fit for the job.
Why did she take Jae-in?
What about you, Lieutenant Nam?
What can I do, at my age?
Still, you're good enough.
Seeing you leading the investigation
when Jae-in was kidnapped,
you weren't completely lying about being a hotshot in your heyday.
"Being a hotshot in my heyday" means
that it's no longer the case.
I'm no longer interested in trying to smash a rock with an egg.
(Invisible children)
Looks like he's knocked out.
When I was asked to train Ahn,
I got a notebook from Prosecutor Kang.
Ah, you mean the notebook about Ahn's psychometry?
Do you know about it?
Yes, I've seen it before.
The one Prosecutor Kang recorded every single thing in,
since Ahn first got his power.
So he gave it to you, huh?
There was an entry about finding a lost puppy stuffed animal
made by his mom, using psychometry.
(Ahn actively used his power)
It said that Ahn's power of psychometry
reaches its maximum potential when
something he desperately wants is involved.
So that's how Ahn was able to find you in lightning speed
when you were kidnapped.
Now we know what that bastard did to Prosecutor Kang,
I'm sure Ahn will read about
that bastard with all his might.
Let's improve his power a lot,
and use him as much as we can after this case is closed.
(Yeongseong Apartments)
(Fire and murder)
(Kang Geun-taek)
Now I can see everything at a glance.
Yeongseong Apartments, Hanmin Nursing Hospital,
murder of Kim Gap-yong, and confinement at the steel factory
were all done by Kang Geun-taek, the one who kidnapped Jae-in?
Yes.
The motive behind all these murders was
Kang Eun-joo, Prosecutor Kang's mother.
Then what about the body of Kang Eun-joo found at Yeongseong?
I'm sure he murdered a woman who looked similar to Kang Eun-joo
beforehand and brought the body.
And since Kang Eun-joo's ID was with the body when it was found,
it seems that the arson was premeditated as well.
So he planned to have Kang Eun-joo be declared dead
and take her away, but he failed?
(Commissioner Eun Byung-ho)
Anyway, I'm sure only Kang Eun-joo and Kang Geun-taek know the truth.
- So, from now on, I will??- Wait.
That means you, Officer Yoon, knew that
your father was framed for sure.
Did you also know that Detective Eun Ji-soo's father
was in charge of that case, too?
Yes.
What a nasty twist of fate.
Detective Eun.
Let's speak privately.
Let's forget about our ranks, and talk as senior and junior.
Sure, go ahead.
You're going to investigate the Yeongseong case, even though
your father, Commissioner Eun Byung-ho, was in charge of it?
If the real culprit of the Yeongseong Apt. case is revealed,
my father will be held responsible for what happened,
but if all of the truth is revealed,
I'm sure he will tell me that I did a great job.
Everyone makes at least one mistake in their life.
Mistake.
Mistake??
Let me be direct with you as well.
I know that you worked at the same station with my father
when Yeongseong Apartment case occurred.
Even though you weren't on the same team.
At what point did that investigation go south?
Was my father's investigation for covering up the truth on purpose,
instead of an overlooked mistake?
(Blind Spot of the Law: Invisible People)
Lieutenant Nam acted weird, right?
Right.
It seems like he knew something about the Yeongseong Apt. case.
You said that after you became a junior cop,
you got caught looking into the Yeongseong case files
by Lieutenant Nam and he brought you here.
He even provided me with a place to stay,
so I thought he was taking pity on me,
but I guess not.
Was it because
he didn't want you to dig into this case?
Didn't you feel anything when you swept the human trafficking gang
involved with identity fraud?
I'm sure you've heard of the rumor about
that gang and YSS Construction being closely connected.
Yes.
But there wasn't a single mention of it in the papers or the news.
Yes, it was because
It's not just the identity fraud gang, YSS Construction's influence
reaches the police, prosecution, politics and finances.
This is beyond your power, Detective Eun.
But what does that have to do with this case??
YSS Construction's former name before it got this big,
was Yeongseong Construction.
The layout of the Yeongseong Apartment buildings
made it difficult for fire trucks to enter,
which led to a large number of casualties,
but people were not interested in that. Why?
Because there was another more shocking headline.
- No??- "The hero that saved people
turned out to be the culprit behind it."
"It was all a part of his plan."
Can you think of a more scintillating headline?
So, did my father point to Yoon Tae-ha as the culprit
to cover up the corruption behind Yeongseong Apt.?
Ha??That's just crazy.
After that fire,
well, I'm sure you know it better than anyone,
but Eun Byung-ho started to rise up through the ranks quickly.
And he is now the Commissioner.
What do you think that means?
You have more than enough reason as a detective
to dig into the Yeongseong Apartments case
As Prosecutor Kang and his mother's case is connected.
But as Eun Byung-ho's daughter,
that case is a Pandora's Box.
In the end, Eun Byung-ho,
your father, will become the target.
Looks like Detective Eun is not coming.
She's not answering her phone, either.
I'll take you home.
I live right there. You don't need to take me home.
But my mind is only at peace when you're right in front of me.
Ugh??I can't take you to my house, either??
Why should I go to your house??
Wait.
Those things piled up in Prosecutor Kang's room.
Weren't they all investigation materials?
Uh, I guess?
Let's go to your house right now.
Have a seat.
We need to talk.
Do you plan to be this reckless and selfish much longer?
How can you just take any random case and walk out?
Society has rules and regulations.
Are you doing this because I got your back?
Come back to work tomorrow for real.
Detective Lee is going to be in charge of
the kidnapping of the officer at Seoheun Police Station.
Dad.
Why did you do it?
Did you think that a castle built on sand
would last for a long time?
What are you talking about?
Do you want me to go everything
you've been hiding up until now?
I really don't know what you're talking about.
I know everything about the Yeongseong Apartments.
And everything about YSS Construction as well.
Eun Ji-soo.
Please let me officially re-investigate it now.
That's the best you can do.
It's all in the past.
No, it's still going on in the present.
Do you know how people are suffering because of what happened
and how they're living right now?
If you conducted a proper investigation at the time??
Even if I can go back to that day,
I will make the same choice.
How can you say that?
Because that was the only way to save you.
I was too poor and powerless as a father
to provide for you, who would collapse
a few times a year due to your heart.
I hated that, as much as death.
It was??because of me?
If you don't want to come to work, write a letter of resignation.
I can't sit by and let you do this any longer.
Oh.
Did Dae-bong feed you on time?
Weren't you scared, being home alone?
Should I take care of White Snow for a while?
My aunt is home, and you're busy.
White Snow will be lonely if she stays home alone.
- Really? - Let's go to my house, later.
(100-day plan to sweep crimes that threaten public welfare)
(Panhandling gangs)
- Is this the last one? - Yes.
By the way, is there a clue about that bastard in here?
If he brought these home,
then it means that he is concerned about these cases.
I'm sure there's something in here.
I'll help you look.
- You? - More than anything,
I can read Hangul quite well.
Article 152, Paragraph 2 of Criminal Law.
The purpose of causing injury with malicious perjury is??
Ah, I need to go wash my face. I can't see straight.
I overdid it today, you know that, right?
- I know. - Not because I can't understand.
This isn't your field of expertise.
Don't try to take over someone else's job, too.
By the way, aren't you uncomfortable?
What?
Being with you alone?
I'm not uncomfortable at all.
I don't mix business with pleasure.
I have clear boundaries, you know.
I was talking about your clothes.
Ah??
It does seem uncomfortable to work in, all night long.
Then, could you give me some clothes to change into?
What is this?
This silence, like the one right before the storm.
This feeling, like I will soon have a group of customers
storming in, even though I didn't prepare anything.
Mr. Hong, this place wouldn't be here without the alumni.
Why? I love the chicken here.
Don't compliment him.
It'll spoil him. And you,
hurry up and eat that chicken so you can take over at the station.
Aren't you going back to the gas station, sir?
He's not going.
It's time for So-hyun to pick up the chicken she ordered.
But doesn't she have a baby?
Woah, sir.
Are you hitting on a married woman?
Nothing's wrong with dating her,
both legally and morally, but??
Hey, Dae-bong.
Keep following her around if you can be responsible until the end,
and if not, just end it here, you jerk.
Are you sure you can convince your father about So-hyun? Huh?
Hey, this won't end after a few hits from a golf club.
Stop it, please.
Are you just planning to casually date her for a bit? Huh?
You little??So-hyun is already suffering enough, you jerk.
You're a morally corrupt bastard??
Let's go.
Are you leaving?
Mr. Hong.
I just wanted to make her smile.
Is that so wrong?
Goodbye.
Come on, sir. Shoulders back.
I think you're quite attractive as well.
Uh??
You're cute, nice, and rich.
I'm sure I'm attractive as an easy boss.
Not as a man.
And what if she has a baby?
My dad is a stepdad, but he's so nice to me.
Stepdad?
Uh, I??
I'm not saying that I am trying to marry So-hyun??
Why not? You can, if you love her.
Huh? It's that car, right?
Don't turn around, and just go.
Hey, stop it. So-hyun will have a misunderstanding.
Ugh, I'm doing this so she will have a misunderstanding.
- What? - You don't know women.
There's nothing attractive about a man that's always there.
Hey, let go.
- Ugh, hurry up. - Hey, let go of me.
Ugh, if you go now, you'll regret it. Hurry.
Hey, stop it.
Ah, then put your hand on my shoulder.
- Shoulder? No way??- Like this.
- Hey, stop saying nonsense. - It's okay.
Stop it, she'll have a misunderstanding. Stop it.
Come on, let's go.
- Let go. - Ugh, just go.
Stop it, I say. Stop it.
I don't want to hurt So-hyun's feelings
just to make her question her feelings for a bit.
Are you having a hard time because of me?
If you're sick of me following you around,
if you hate it and find it repulsive,
just tell me.
You'll never see me again.
Yes.
I hate it so much it makes me sick.
Okay.
I got it.
(Invisible children, human trafficking)
Surprisingly, a lot of these materials are connected.
Human trafficking, panhandling gangs, organ trafficking.
There are especially a lot of murders of the homeless,
and these cases have a high chance of
unidentified or unregistered people being involved in them.
You've done so much, reading what you don't understand.
Sung-mo!
If you're going to stab and kill someone with that short height,
you shouldn't have stabbed here.
You should've stabbed here.
Ahn. Lee Ahn.
Ahn.
Are you okay? Did you have a nightmare?
A nightmare?
I felt like I did psychometry.
What kind of dream was it?
It was in that basement.
Sung-mo??
stabbed that bastard with a knife.
It's because you saw too many shocking things earlier.
Is that why?
Go to bed and get some sleep.
So you can use your skills again tomorrow.
What about you?
I'm going to go home soon, too.
I'll take you home. Let's go.
- Murder of the homeless? - Yeah.
That case bothers me the most.
On the day Kang Geun-taek kidnapped me,
I heard that the ID he had was fake.
And the real owner of the ID still hasn't been found yet.
So he killed the homeless
for their IDs?
I found some more cases besides those,
but I'll tell you about that after I look into them more,
By the way, there's something I just can't wrap my brain around,
- for a long time. - What is it?
Who is this person Kim Gap-yong mentioned?
Ms. Kang Hee-sook, you aren't dead yet.
I'm sorry, but that person doesn't want any more trouble.
I'm not sure, either.
But if we think of the worst case scenario??
Is it Sung-mo's??mother?
(Steel construction materials)
(Knife)
It bothers me that Kang Eun-joo attempted suicide on the day
the murders of Kang Hee-sook and Park Soo-young were announced.
I know that you're watching.
If that's the only way
to stop you,
then I must take that way.
Did that mean you were coming to meet me?
Sure.
I will meet you.
You're the best bait I can use
to find Eun-joo.
(Case Report)
(Witness Statement)
A ghost station.
"Their hideout was a ghost subway station,
and most of the children ordered to panhandle
were unregistered, and they were locked up??
with chains on their necks."
What? Chains?
Where's the confinement case file Detective Eun brought us?
Here.
(Wanted: Suspect of confinement at a steel factory in Gangnyeong)
I remember your face.
You took my dad's clothes.
The scar on the culprit's neck.
That was a chain mark as well.
What do you mean? Explain it to me so I understand.
(Ghost subway of Sae Ki Dong)
(Transfer route from Sae Ki Dong Station to Kang Kook Station foundered)
"In 1988, a new transfer route running
from Sae Ki Dong Station to Kang Kook Station??
(After being foundered, it turned into an empty space)
had been planned, but it had been foundered."
(Confinement case at a steel factory in Gangnyeong-si)
- What's all this? - I think we found where
Kang Geun-taek may be hiding.
Ugh, where is Ji-soo, at this important moment?
Detective Eun isn't going to come.
- What? - And I'm out of this case, too.
Lieutenant Nam.
You can neither begin nor end this case.
Wrap all this up before I return from patrol.
Uh??
This gang is no ordinary gang.
They're even taking care of YSS Construction's slush funds.
You know that the corruption of YSS Construction
isn't something we can handle.
Eun Ji-soo, I think you should step down from this case.
So you knew everything already.
(Psycho Ahn)
Ji-soo, Jae-in found a lead for
the place that exists, but does not exist.
Hurry up and come here.
How can I go see you at this moment?
How am I qualified to
solve this case?
(Ji-soo)
Huh? This is weird.
I couldn't get in touch with her since yesterday.
What if that bastard went to Ji-soo?
Hi, I'm Detective Lee Seung-yong.
I'll be investigating your kidnapping case, Officer Yoon.
What about Detective Eun?
Ah, she's not feeling well.
Ji-soo is?
Are you sure she's sick?
The Commissioner told me this morning, so I'm positive, I guess.
Anyway, the case has been handed to me.
What do you mean??
Please take a seat and talk to me.
I didn't receive any materials from Detective Eun.
Excuse me??
Alright.
Could you please explain every single thing to me
in regards to what happened, from the moment you were kidnapped?
Every??single??thing??
Yes.
Oh, you didn't know.
It's time for her to go on patrol.
Right? Right?
Uh??Yes, right.
Uh??I'll call you later.
Goodbye.
Uh, Officer Yoon.
Officer Yoon?
Officer Yoon!
What the heck?
Where's Ji-soo, and why is that guy here?
Don't you think they lied about her being sick?
It seemed that Lieutenant Nam knows something about it.
It can't be helped. Let's go on our own.
To where?
(Sae Ki Dong Station)
(Authorized Personnel Only)
One of the cases Prosecutor Kang was in charge of was
arresting a panhandling gang as a part of the
100-day plan to sweep crimes that threaten public welfare.
Ah, the case that awarded Sung-mo with a commendation?
Yes. The assailants and victims of that case,
in other words, the panhandling kids and the gang members
testified about the place we've been looking for.
The Sae Ki Dong Station line?
That's no ordinary subway line.
There's a ghost station there.
A ghost station?
Explain it to me so I understand.
The platform we go to exists for sure.
But, have you ever imagined about what lies under it?
30 years ago, they tried to connect the route
on basement floor 3 in order to make a transfer subway,
but the plan was foundered,
so it resulted in a lot of unusable trains.
And out of those ghost stations, Sae Ki Dong Station was
often a hideout for the panhandling gang.
And that very panhandling gang
chained the children's necks to keep them.
(Sae Ki Dong Station)
You mean the chain mark on Kang Geun-taek's neck, right?
Yes. Kang Geun-taek avoided CCTVs
and moved through ghost stations,
so no one would see him for his entire life.
I think he learned how to move without being seen
when he was in the panhandling gang.
By the way, do you think Kang Geun-taek came back here?
It was where the panhandling gang was arrested,
so it makes no sense for him to be still hiding here.
We need to find the traces that cannot be seen.
That's your specialty.
Detective Eun.
We're on our way to the ghost platform of Sae Ki Dong Station.
If you hear this message, please come here quickly.
(Sae Ki Dong Station)
Detective Eun. We're on our way to
the ghost platform of Sae Ki Dong Station.
If you hear this message, please come here quickly.
How could you two just go there without a plan?
I'd like to apologize on my dad's behalf
about your father being framed.
I'm sorry.
I don't know if I'll be able to
pay off this debt by working hard,
but I won't make the same mistake.
Do you see anything?
No.
What's that?
Lee Ahn.
Why?
These are his.
(Detective Eun Ji-soo)
Detective Eun.
Damn it.
We just found the culprit's belongings
on the ghost platform of Sae Ki Dong Station.
We think Kang Geun-taek was here.
How could you two just go there without a plan?
No. I called you too late.
Officer Yoon, don't do anything dangerous, okay?
It'll take a while for me to get to Sae Ki Dong Station,
so I'll ask for a police backup.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
For getting there so late.
Please hurry, Detective Eun.
(Spy)
Yes, Detective Eun.
Send backup to Sae Ki Dong Station right now.
What? What's with Sae Ki Dong Station all of a sudden??
I just had a report about traces of Officer Yoon's kidnapper
hiding out there being found. Hurry.
I'm sorry, Detective Eun, but
the Commissioner told us not to provide you with anything
with any cases for a while.
- What? - I'm sorry.
Even if you call someone else, it won't be any use.
It's all in the past.
Nothing can change at this point.
No!
No??
Run! Run!
Run!
Is this the photo Kang Geun-taek took
from your house?
Yes.
I think it is.
(Gang, Guk)
What is this?
Why is Sung-mo??
Why? What did you see?
I once imagined what I would see
if I could do psychometry on myself.
The most painful memory in my past.
It's neither about the fire at the apartments,
nor the day Jae-in was kidnapped.
It's about that day,
at the ghost station.
(He is Psychometric)
I want it to be complete
both on this side and that side,
without any flaws.
What do you mean, you saw him with Kang Eun-joo?
Sung-mo lured us to Sae Ki Dong Station.
He left the materials, so we can find that place.
Sung-mo??
Was it you who told Ji-soo about Yeongseong Apartments?
Have you seen Prosecutor Kang Sung-mo
since the Yeongseong Apartment case?
I told her to go to where that bastard is.
So she can stop Sung-mo.