He Is Psychometric
December 3rd, 2005
6:15 pm
1 hour before Yeongseong Apartment Incident
Dad, I love you
Jae In, I'm going to go pass around some flyers. Wait here, okay?
Okay! Come back soon!
What's this?
Mister. I told you this before.
You can't hand these out without the owners' consent.
No matter how many times I tell the residents to stop blocking the fire truck routes, they don't cooperate.
Are you advertising the fact that our complex has
lousy parking?
We don't pay your salary out of our own pockets
so that you can intentionally lower the property value of our apartments.
I'm doing this to get my pay's worth.
I've done everything I can, checking the fire protection system
but the fire safety awareness is particularly a mess.
A mess? Who said that?
Madam, you may receive bribes behind closed doors in this line of work
and you may turn a blind eye here and there.
But you can't turn a blind eye to the residents' safety.
Wait, wait wait. What did you say?
Bribes? Wow, I'm going to go crazy.
You must be crazy!
No, no. I must be the crazy one.
I was told you were trustworthy because you use to be a firefighter.
- I was clearly crazy for believing it!
- That's not what I meant.
Mister, as of today, you're fired.
What?
My gosh. What a mess.
Isn't this your workplace?
How could you bring a child here?
She came to me because it was almost time for me to get off work.
That's enough. You're immediately fired.
What is all this?
Ugh.
Keep roads clear for fire trucks
Don't pay attention to them. You were just doing what you needed to do.
She's the weirdo.
What should I do?
What do you mean what should you do? You can look for a new job now.
That's not what I mean.
If this apartment catches on fire, it'll be really dangerous.
My daughter's shoelaces are untied again.
I can't have my daughter tripping over them.
- Go inside, okay?
- Okay.
Keep roads clear for fire trucks
Missing person, Kang Eun Sool
Daddy, I love you
Look up there! Isn't that a person?
Huh? Dad?
Dad! Dad!
- Dad!
- Jae In! I'll be right there, don't worry!
Okay.
Okay!
Pyschometry. Greek "Pysche (Soul)" and "Metron (Measure)". The ability to measure and interpret a person or objects soul.
He Is Psychometric
- Episode 4 -
Stop.
Oh sorry, my hand was cramping up.
Answers acquired any way other than solving the questions yourself is considered cheating,
and if you get caught, you'll be asked to leave immediately.
I found you, Yoon Jae In.
Exam Hall
Now. Please put your pencils down.
Let's talk outside.
I won't run away.
How come you keep calling me on my day off?
What's this? Are you undercover?
Oh, this? I went on a blind date. I ditched after ten minutes.
Oh right! I had to see Prosecutor Kang about something!  I just remembered. Do you want to go with me?
Why? Are you trying to show me off because I'm all dressed up?
Did you realize? I guess it would be too obvious how you feel if you just showed up like this?
Totally. Completely. He already knows how I feel.
No way. Did you actually go to him?
You know he's been working weekends for two years.
Oh, right. That case... Can't he let it go?
We can't indict because the suspect is dead.
What? The only witness who named that suspect was murdered.
You're reaching, it was simply theft that ended up as murder.
The caregiver disappeared from the fire.
My pride as an officer won't let me give up on this.
What about my pride? Your father who lived his whole life as a police officer.
We informed the public on the fire at the care home
you solved the Yeongseong Apartment case eleven years ago.
That's right. You would know better than anyone.
You had to sign your mother off to an autopsy at such a young age, you were following the case so closely.
Did you feel like my investigation at the time was sloppy?
- Do you truly believe that there was not a single thing that might've gone wrong?
- Prosecutor Kang!
If I remember correctly, like the care home fire, the Yeongseong Apartment case was also wrapped up fairly quickly.
- In terms of the law, procedure, and evidence, I did everything properly.
- Dad!
If you want another look, either bring me proof or the real arsonist, not a hunch.
I heard many prosecutors are also against this. Coming to me won't change anything.
Fine. I'll take it that means an unofficial investigation  is fine. I'll leave now.
Prosecutor Kang's mother wasn't a mere victim of the fire.
She was one of the victims that got stabbed.
Wow. That's why he was hanging onto that case.
I feel like there's something still there but he won't tell me anything.
But it doesn't look like his investigation is moving forward, either.
When you really look at him, he doesn't get close to anyone. He's only affectionate towards that psycho.
Not "psycho," psychometry!
Anyway, if there really is another perpetrator, he can't be an average guy.
He didn't even leave a trace behind.
Victims personal details
I felt so shameful having come out of the building by myself.
And sorry. Which is why I didn't report it sooner. I'm sorry.
I think this happened on his way to see us.
10mm stab wound in right stomach, abdominal aorta ruptured
Yoon Tae Ha
I will go save your mom and dad, okay?
Please take care of him.
This metal chain is a bit weird, isn't it?
It's not even like it's tied to anything and it doesn't seem like they tried to chain his other ankle either.
Kim Gab Yong Murder Case
It’s been a while.
I didn’t know you became a police officer.
How have you been?
There's no way she would shake my hand.
No, no.
This isn’t it.
♫   Some days when I look into your eyes  ♫
♫   Why do I keep seeing...  ♫
I need one thing to protect me.
Since I don't have parents or any support,
I held out all this time by being number one at school.
But if people found out I was just a poor kid living on a rooftop,
I'd be a recipe for disaster.
I won't be able to stand any more.
I'm going to reveal exactly who you are!
You got it?!
Are you okay? You don't need to go to a hospital?
I'm fine.
You can't keep running away.
Aren't you tired?
I'm tired. I'm so freaking tired.
I'll help you
whenever you're ready.
Lee Ahn. I wanted to tell you.
You saying you'd help me gave me strength for a short time.
Develop your skills, okay?
Yoon Jae In!
Then when I become more confident, I'll come to find you.
♫   It's okay to cry  ♫
♫  Someday we are all down  ♫
You were trying to cheat earlier, right? Right?
Those people sitting there are people who spent years sitting on their butts in
dorms without windows, studying for years.
Can you really take their effort just like that?
Is that the first thing you're gonna say to me after seeing each other for the first time in two years?
Then what? What else would I say?
I thought you were going to go to Seoul University. Why are you in the police academy?
I couldn't take my exams because I was too busy running away.
I took the detective and police tests.
I was really busy for the past two years.
So why did you run away, like a fool?
Then what about you? Did you live better than I did?
I definitely lived well.
Seeing how you're trying to become a cop...
Don’t tell me!
Are you helping your brother and that detective with your skills?
Like an investigative adviser?
A more technical term would be a "psychometrist."
Really? You're actually doing it?
Of course.
See anything?
I see a knife. Really long and sharp.
This person is definitely a gangster or a killer. I'm right, aren't I?
He's a sushi chef with 30 years experience.
Welcome!
Hyung.
You only need to see the hit-and-run driver's license plate number. Just the number.
If you say bra sizes again, you know what'll happen, right?
I definitely saw it this time! Confident this time!
One, nine, four, six.
Right? I told you he'd read this.
Thank you, thank you.
Hey. If you bring him here again,
the next person who'll be laying in one of these is you.
She and my hyung are going wild.
They said I need to join the force quickly, that I can't hide my skills any longer.
- That’s amazing.
- What about you?
How's it being a cop?
It’s hard, but it’s worth it.
Where? Near here? Seoul?
Seoheun Patrol Division.
Are you in the homicide squad by chance?
I'm still on probation. But I think I'll join them soon.
Figures, you were always smart, even back then.
Get in. I’ll take you.
- No, I have an appointment.
- Ah...
Look...
Develop your skills.
When I become more confident,
I’ll come to find you then.
What?
I still live where I did—right there, that rooftop.
Okay.
- I’ll be going now.
- Okay.
Bye.
Seoheun Patrol Division. That's good. That's good enough.
It’s been a while since you came here. Ahn is doing well, right?
Yes.
He isn't going around causing trouble, is he?
Well, he's an adult now.
So fascinating. How did you discipline a kid like Ahn?
As you know, back then,
if you just touched him, he was ready to destroy everything.
You helped him graduate. He's basically a normal human being now.
- Of course—
- Although, he's still unemployed.
Work hard.
Hyung!
Why are you so happy? Did you do well on the police test?
Oh, right. I took a test, didn't I?
- Did I write my name?
- You definitely cheated off the person in front of you.
- What a relief. I don't have to report you for an exam scheme.
- Were you going to report me?
Do you want me to be indebted towards you forever?  Aren't you scared? Especially in this generation?
It’s okay. You’re worth it to me.
Value?
What value do I have?
You are the person I saved.
It's kind of like keeping the virtue I've saved up to look at from time to time.
The person you saved...
If he became a policeman and did the same line of work you did,
in a pyramid scheme-like situation, he could bring you more value. Why don't you think of it that way?
So do you have to only become a policeman?
Of course. It was so obvious I was going to die
but you saved me and I gained this skill. I need to display it somewhere for this to be right.
- It's a crime to keep this hidden.
- But it's such a wishy-washy skill for it to be displayed.
Wow. You're so bad.
Do you like saving me, then hurting me, you pervert-psychopath?
Sorry, I didn’t think it would hurt you.
Anyway, you didn't think this through.
How can you call yourself a prosecutor if you buy chicken without beer?
It’s really a mystery, a mystery.
The smell of chicken is killing me.
By the way, why are you coming here instead of home?
This is home.
What?
I told you a few days ago that we’d move here. I put the address on the fridge.
I still live there. That place. That rooftop.
No!
Go in first. It’s number 614.
I'm going to go buy beer.
I loved that rooftop so much.
It's nice and cool in the winter, a scorching hot in the summer.
Because it's wide open, you have to worry about invasion of privacy, too.
The view there is the best in the country.
Wow. It's here.
This is our place?
Now it finally feels like a house a prosecutor would live in.
To be exact, it's an investment.
It's embarrassing to say it's mine because my share is so small.
I'm embarrassed too. I'd feel more comfortable staying in a tenement house.
I told you before, right? You're my...
Virtue.
Bean rice cake? Why are you his bean rice cake?
I just am.
What's this? Is this your newlywed home or something?
Anyway, this is my housewarming gift.
- Thank you.
- What’s that?
Did you guys just connect mentally or did you plan this?
That's right. I was planning on ordering chicken too.
Eat first. I'm going to go wash up real quick.
Okay. Wash slowly because there are two chicken legs.
I didn't think this through. I should eat first then wash up.
But what is this?
That girly girl type of outfit.
I went to visit my dad and then I came from a blind date.
Okay, then I’ll do a cold reading now.
Cold reading: Reading someone's mind without knowing anything.
Seeing that your face is a little red, you already had one round of beer.
Seeing how you bought ten cans of beer,
the blind date didn't go well.
Nope, it went really well.
He completely fell for me.
You?
I see. I guess the blind date went well.
What about your test?
Enough about the test.
- Do you know Seoheun Patrol Division by chance?
- Yes.
That's our precinct. Why?
Really?
Why? What are you up to?
She became a cop, that one.
- That one?
- The girl who made me out to be a pervert when I was a senior in high school. Remember?
Yeomsan terror.
You found her?
You remember her too?
Her name is Yoon Jae In, right?
She suddenly disappeared before her exams and became a police officer instead of going to college?
Yeah, she did.
Figures. Nowadays, as soon as you graduate from high school
there are a lot of people who bypass college and just prepare for official work.
Everyone is so impressive at such a young age, aren't they?
Very different from someone I know.
I'm going to go wash up now.
I’m sorry but I can’t get in touch with her either.
The deposits aren't going through either.
I think she needs more time.
I'm still in this state without a degree or a job.
But she became so cool.
They say first love is like that.
Just like the taste of beer, it's bitter
and nauseating the more you think about it.
Why are you so sentiment today?
SentimentAL. Mental.
There's something going on, huh? If you don't explain it thoroughly,
I can figure it out myself.
Where does your evidence-less confidence come from?
You only see useless things.
I don’t know about anyone else but
you're so transparent with me, like Dae Bong, so my psychometry works well on you guys.
I'm doing it!
Fine. If I'm going to get caught and be embarrassed,
I might as well confess and go from there.
I confessed to Prosecutor Kang and got rejected.
Again?!
What do you mean, again? You knew?
There's a rumor going around at the station that you and I are dating.
Only at the station? It's spreading across the district.
I mean, unlike the way you treat other people,
you treat me comfortably and we're seen close together
really often so people keep saying we look good together.
So I was thinking... With this opportunity...
How about we not leave it as a misunderstanding and just—
Sorry.
We really did spend a lot of time together without boundaries, huh?
I didn't think this through. I'll place some distance between us.
You get back safely.
I was so traumatized because I only saw that about you for the longest time.
But you confessed again?
That will is amazing. You're so cool, Eun Ji Soo!
Shut up.
If you knew, you should've told me that you knew!
Is there anyone who doesn’t know you like him?
It say's "I like him" all over your face.
You’re always chasing him around to eat and drink—even today.
You got rejected but why are you here? So embarrassing!
You guys said you moved and you took your exam today.
I’m always your excuse, huh?
Fine, just go ahead and ignore my efforts.
Do you know how much I think about you?
You really came for me?
Really? Without a single bit of dishonesty?
"No. My blind date went so well."
"He completely fell for me."
Those lines...
We saw right through them.
Really?
I'm so embarrassed.
I’m leaving.
You should ask my hyung to drive you home. If you keep doing embarrassing things, you eventually get desensitized.
Forget it!
I'm not seeing you out.
You want to eat this?
I still live there, that place, that rooftop.
Okay.
I have to tell her where I live now.
That's why I'm going to see her. Just for that reason.
- Are you not giving me my car back?
- Let me use it for one more day.
I have something really important to do.
Is there really another good reason why I should?
Yoon Jae In.
I found out where she is.
Yoon... Yoon... Yoon Jae In...
I'm hanging up.
I love you, Dae Bong!
Welcome!
What are you doing? Another car's here!
I know.
How long is he going to follow Yoon Jae In around?
Yes, how much gas would you like put in—
This is your gas station?
Yeah! I recently opened it.
- I just want 30,000 won worth.
- Huh? Okay.
Could you o-o-o-open this please?
Thanks.
What should I say?
Excuse me.
It's been a while, huh?
Can I pay?
Oh, right. It's fine, just go.
It's not like there are only a few classmates in this area.
I know. I put in gas for free for them, too.
I knew you'd be like this so I've actually been avoiding your gas station.
Don't do this. Let me pay.
So Yeon.
This is something I give to all of my first customers, seriously!
Okay.
I'll use it well.
Dae Bong Gas Station
Manager! What are you doing?
A baby...
I didn't know the words, "Baby on board" could hurt so much.
She's not here? There's no cop named Yoon Jae In here? Why not?
Because she's not here.
She said she was stationed here.
That's the first time I'm hearing that name.
What the heck?
Did she lie to me?
If it's Yoon Jae In, isn't she the probation officer at Seoheun Community Security Center?
The place where they only have one officer, you know.
- Oh, there's a place like that?
- Seoheun Community Security Center?
Okay, thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
Security center?
One officer... What?
Hello? Yeah, Noona?
Oh, Seoheun Community Security Center?
I know. It's at the very tip of Seoheun in a remote place.
Did they not get rid of that place yet?
What's a one-man-station by the way?
It's basically that you work while living and eating there.
Her house is in the police station?
Yeah. But she's stationed there?
That place is a bit... meh.
What do you mean?
I picked this up right in front of the convenience store.
Please look for the owner.
Here you go.
"This child performed a kind act above all other children
and is presented this award."
Good job!
Thank you!
Grandma, this is not the place.
Over there, you see the red door over there?
Joo Ha, did you lie?
Aigoo, this is a big deal.
- You might have to get handcuffed and go to jail.
- Say you won't do it again!
I won't lie ever again!
No, I mean, there aren't that many people there so there are hardly any incidents or accidents.
Start at 9 AM, get off exactly at 6 PM. The good thing is that it's an easy job.
The bad thing is that there's no way to get promoted.
How did a young girl like her get put there?
Police
- Kid.
- Grandma.
- Drink this!
- Thank you!
Go on, drink up!
I will! Get home safely.
Seoheun Community Security Center
I went to the Patrol Division and asked for you.
I didn't think you'd come looking for me.
I didn't lie to you.
This is under Seoheun Patrol Division's jurisdiction, and I will go to Violent Crimes.
This was my first pick.
Ji Soo said that this is where officers come before they retire.
How did you end up here?
My partner got transferred here. I asked if there were any cheap homes for rent
and he told me to stay here since he has an aparment here.
How did you end up asking someone to help you find a home?
- I got caught snooping through an old case file.
- Already?
So I told the truth. I can't become an officer if I get fired during probation.
I'm too old to keep running away,
and I kind of have social status now.
So, did you see your dad's case file?
My partner won't let me see it.
It'll leave a trace in the system.
If he's caught, they'll revoke his pension. He told me to look into it when I pass probation.
Then he brought me to this place in the middle of nowhere.
Do you think I got scammed?
Can you even get to the Violent Crimes Division from here?
I heard there are zero cases here.
How will you gain points to climb the ladder and reach the police headquarters?
Hey, how do you know the systems and processes?
Because that's what I'm trying to do too.
I need to score big if I want to land a position.
It's not easy to—
Aha!
You said you were helping your prosecutor brother and that detective on cases.
You still can't read your brother, isn't it?
Th-that's... Well, you see...
Officer! What do I do? My Joo Ha disappeared!
What do we do?
I think it's because we yelled at her earlier. I can't with this girl...
I'm sure it's not a big issue. You search this side and I'll search over here.
Shouldn't you be calling the Patrol Division?
This kid's a repeat offender, she's on our Community Security Center blacklist.
Hey! What if it's a kidnapping?
Joo Ah!
Stop saying ridiculous things.
Just because I need to solve a case to get transferred,
I'm not praying for situations like this to happen.
Who said you were? I'm just worried is all.
Hurry up.
Joo Ah! Joo Ah!
- Did you happen to see Joo Ah?
- I haven't. Is something going on?
Please give us a call if you see her.
Joo Ah! Joo Ah!
- Joo Ah!
Have you seen a little girl around?
Sorry.
- Joo Ha!
- Where could she have gone?
Hasn't it been one hour since she disappeared?
I do feel like she's hiding somewhere.
Kids like to cause trouble in places where they can't be seen.
What are you saying? You were saying you didn't want any situations earlier.
Why would you say that?
Wait.
Why? What's wrong?
That... That's a toy Joo Ah always carries around.
What is it?
Hey, what’s wrong with you?
Listen, don't get scared.
I think the kid's been kidnapped.
- What?
- I just saw it using psychometry.
Inside a suitcase—a black suitcase.
No way
Jae In! What are you doing there?
What are you doing here?
My bunny.
The river is stinking because of the drought. Look at the poop!
Be careful. You don't know when it''ll start flowing.
I'll be at the center then.
Is she the one who went missing?
Is she the one who was...
inside a suitcase?
That's weird. I definitely saw black hair sticking out of a suitcase.
Do you want to make a case like that?
Are you hallucinating or what?
You scared me to death!
But I saw it clearly. I definitely saw it!
How strange.
I picked the rabbit up here...
Yoon Jae In! Hey, Yoon Jae In
What is it now?
Don't even talk to me unless there's a suitcase with a body inside.
There is. There really is.
We'll have to look closely, but I think it's a woman's body.
What happened?
I don't know.
By the way, what should we do with that guy?
He already testified as a witness. I told him he can go back,
but he insisted on waiting for you.
Why don't you take the suitcase to Dr. Hong for now?
I'll come after I deal with him.
Okay.
I found the body.
I saw the image of the suitcase in my head.
Finally some good work. Anything else?
Anything else? Like what?
You mean like the culprits face?
Don't worry, I'll read every corner of this place overnight.
I'll touch every single leaf.
I'll see the culprit's face no matter what, even if I pass out.
I don't think that's necessary,
Oh well, you won't even listen to me if I tell you not to.
So you give me permission? You said it yourself
There's no need. You'll only waste your energy.
I told you about her, my friend from Seoheun Community Security Center.
It’s been a while.
By the way, she knows about my ability too.
What do you mean, he'll only waste his energy?
You already know, Detective.
I do, but I'm wondering if you know something else.
It's likely that the suitcase was flowing down the river,
and got caught in the bushes when it rained heavily about a month ago.
It's plausible that it got stuck here because of the drought.
What?
That’s what you think?
Bodies of suicide or murder victims often flow downstream.
But this is the first time it came all the way to our neighborhood.
You can't assume that it traveled here because of that.
We got a report that a black suitcase with a body in it was found in the upstream and I went to see it.
And it seems like it was the same suitcase and it's in a similar condition too.
It seemed like the murder took place about four to five years ago and we identified the body, but we still haven't figured out who the culprit is.
Is that enough?
You heard her, right? Your friend doesn't want you to waste your time here.
No way.
How could a suitcase with a body in it travel here all the way from Han River? It'd be too heavy.
When the body decomposes it becomes buoyant because of the gas it creates.
There's been a case where a body had a block of concrete that weighed 25 kg attached to it.
I read in a book that a body can even make weights up to 70 kg float.
- Will you be guarding the police line here today?
- Yes.
That's great. Please make sure he doesn't lurk around here.
He didn't understand a single word you just said.
I did! Gas from buoyance.
Gas from decomposition.
A body was found? In the stream here?
Yes, that's why I sent Officer Yoon there. How annoying.
I chose to come here because there's no crime here. This is a bad sign.
Jae In... I mean, Officer Yoon said she'll give the children a preventative education to teach them to keep safe.
She always volunteers to do stuff like that.
- Should I come back later?
- No.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
Alright, everyone, come gather around.
Come gather around!
I'll arrest you if you don't. Gather around!
Everyone in Petal Class!
Shall we gather round?
Yes, yes ma'am!
Come sit over here.
Everyone in Petal Class...
You sit there and you sit here.
I can't believe there was a crime in this neighborhood.
How strange.
I hate the people who dump body in the water more than anything.
You said you hate the people who dump in septic tanks last time.
In my previous life, I must've
killed people like this and dumped the bodies.
Otherwise, why would I be destined
to be doing this for a living?
I'm sure this is my punishment.
What about me then?
I must've been your accomplice or at least an abetter.
Restricted Area, undergoing investigation
I told you not to waste your energy.
This is the only thing I can do right now.
-Do you see anything?
- Of course.
Bird poop.
Dog poop.
Even human poop? What's wrong with them?
Don't waste your time. I'm sure the culprit didn't come here.
Today was my chance to prove myself.
At least I proved myself to Detective Eun.
Do you only care about yourself?
This is still my first case even though I'm just guarding the police line.
If I get lucky, I spend my day helping people finding things they lost.
And I found the body
for your first case.
I would've found it myself without you.
The suitcase was obviously very suspicious.
Who said I was imagining things earlier?
Someone yelled at me saying not to talk to them unless there's a suitcase with a body in it.
- Who was that?
- Okay, I admit it.
It's a little late, but I'll let it slide this time.
Look at you all excited.
By the way, could you repeat what you said earlier?
What? The buoyance thing?
I explained three times already.
No, not that. I kind of understood that.
You said you found a similar suitcase upstream.
Are you saying this was done by a serial killer?
The suitcase is the same one as the one we found Park Soo Young last time.
This time, we're assuming it's a woman in her 50s.
Considering she was wearing a winter coat and boots,
she was murdered in winter. There were cement blocks in the suitcase just like last time.
Was there anything to identify her?
Since the body is in adipocere state, we'll be able to get the fingerprints.
It better not be like last time. We identified the body but couldn't catch the culprit.
We couldn't figure out when she went missing since the victim didn't have a family.
- But this time—
- Are you saying you can't do it if you can't figure out when she went missing again?
Well, that's—
This is different. We just had a body then, but now we have two bodies.
I'm sure there's a connection between the two bodies.
I'm not worried because Prosecutor Kang is involved in this case. But finish it as quickly as you can.
Yes.
Cases like this get too much attention since there's no interesting news these days.
You'd better get it done before people start calling us incompetent.
Why is he so irritable today?
Seriously? Was it because he's upset you aren't getting married?
Be quiet.
Of course. He's really something.
I thought he was such a perfectionist when it comes to cases,
- but—
- Perfectionist my foot.
He's a crazy old man.
He thinks I'll quit and get married by stressing me out with work.
He's been setting me up on blind dates every week.
He changed his strategy now.
He's still admirable.
He went from a regular officer to a police commissioner.
Anyway, I'll see you later when we hear back from the forensic team.
Yes.
- What?
- Hey.
What do you think was the point of our conversation?
We're here to identify the deceased!
No, not the meeting. I'm talking about what we just talked about.
Your marriage?
Right? That's what you thought too, right?
But Prosecutor Kang mentioned my dad at the end.
He probably thought no one would notice, but I did.
- Isn't he so clever?
- Well...
Does mentioning Chancellor Eun make you clever?
How do I become clever?
Life must be hard for you.
How do you investigate with a brain like that?
Wait for me!
Han Min Rehabilitation Center Arson Case
Missing: Kang Hee Sook
Witness: Kim Gap Yong
A wound in the right abdomen
A shackle on the right ankle
Found in the Ra Ohn building's construction site
Who assaulted Kim Gap Yong?
Suspect: Yoon Tae Ha, the security guard at Yeongseong Apartment
Abandoned suitcase case
For your information, he's the one who found the body for this case.
He'd get harassed if they find out his brother was the prosecutor for the case.
You'd better brace yourself.
I made it sound as professional as possible.
There's nothing emotional about it.
Nice. I did a good job.
I should just do it like this from now on.
Yes.
This is the kind of text message,
without any emotions, Detective Eun.
I want to fight him even more.
The investigation for Seoheun-gu's black suitcase murder is in jeopardy
Last time it was a woman in her forties.
It was a woman this time as well.
Yes, I understand.
I’ll be back.
I'm going to the Community Security Center. Will you stay here?
What? Hey.
You mean no one will stay here?
I told you, there's no point in investigating this place.
All the evidence is in that suitcase anyway.
Aren't you leaving?
Also, a friend of his who became a police officer
found the body with him.
They're probably very excited right now.
You really should brace yourself.
I would've touched more things if I knew.
I was too tired. I should've touched what's inside.
Is that really all you saw?
The suitcase and the body with black hair?
Yeah.
That's too bad.
But there's something strange.
When I'm with you I get better at reading things.
I doubt it, it probably just feels like it.
It happened two years ago in the teacher's office too.
That's strange.
You must've studied a lot while you were away.
I mean, about police work.
I've been interested in this field since I was young.
I hated the police since they framed my dad.
But now that I think about it, I made a faulty assumption.
A faulty... right. So that's what it was.
That detective you know, Detective Eun,
she came to see me at the convenience store as soon as the math teacher got released.
She got upset for me and she told you to be my bodyguard.
And I thought not all the detectives are so bad.
Is that why you took the police exam?
I thought, "When I become a cop, if the suspect says they're not guilty,
I'll check three times or four times, over and over again
to make sure that they don't end up like me or my dad."
That's what I thought.
I thought it'd be worth it even though I don't get to prove my dad's innocence.
Did you finally get to think about your own life?
Instead of thinking about your dad?
- Hyung!
- Long time no see, Officer Yoon Jae In.
Daddy Long Legs...
Daddy what?
He is Psychometric
♫  See your eyes, I sense you looking at your eyes  ♫
♫  I know you like in your heart  ♫
♫  The coincidence that repeats  ♫
♫  So take, my hidden feelings  ♫
♫  Take, the time I saved for you  ♫
♫  Don't be afraid  ♫
He'll be misunderstood for the rest of his life.
You know this would end up being a cold case if we don't catch the culprit.
You'd better stay alert.
That's why they keep harassing you like that.
Could you give me some time to think about it?
Huh?
I'm sorry. He wants no loose ends.
♫  I can tell you now  ♫
Who did you say it is?
Don't you remember? Kang Hee Sook.
What are you?