(He is Psychometric)
What is this place?
Yes, that person.
I was about to go back after waiting for you.
What? Me?
Ah??Please wait.
Why would he wait for me?
I know, right? He might be able to make handcuffs, too.
Do you live here?
Ah??yes, I'm a cop working at this Police Station.
I'm sure he looked familiar.
Where did I see him?
Just where?
Dad, I'm sleepy.
Get some more sleep.
You.
(PSYCHOMETRY A combination of Greek words)
(PSYCHE/Soul and METRON/Measuring)
(An ability to measure the soul of a person or)
(an object and interpreting it)
(He is Psychometric, Episode 11)
Jae-in, where are you?
The caller cannot be reached. Please leave a message??
Long time no see, Kang Sung-mo.
I wanted to hear your voice,
but looks like I'm a bit late.
Did you find Eun-joo?
What are you going to do now?
Are you going to hide her in a place where I can't find her?
Just in case you're thinking of doing that,
I brought someone, too.
I thought that, if you take my girl away,
it's only fair if
I take your girl away as well.
Ah??I guess it may be unfair.
Because you can't kill my girl,
but I can??
kill your girl.
Well? Did that answer your question?
This is the reason why I brought you here.
I remember your face.
You took my dad's clothes.
It's you, isn't it?
The one who stabbed Ahn,
and the one who's been stalking Prosecutor Kang for a long time.
You were the culprit.
(You have one new voicemail)
Is that important at this moment?
I think what's important right now
is what I might do with you.
I can't see anything. Damn it.
Just why are you doing this?
Have you heard of the story of the Little Prince?
The Little Prince, who grew his own rose
on a small planet.
What are you trying to say?
How about we make some changes to that story?
Into a story of that preciously tamed flower
being picked by someone else.
Could it have been a beautiful tale?
How would you feel about it?
The feeling of losing the most precious thing.
Damn it.
What about Kang Sung-mo?
Ah, but looks like Kang Sung-mo now has
more than one precious thing.
He has a "brother" named Lee Ahn,
Detective Eun Ji-soo,
and you.
Kang Sung-mo has so many things to protect now.
For me, she is still the only one.
"She?"
It seems that you still don't know anything.
If you know who she is,
it would've been easier to understand my behavior.
Things will never turn out the way you want them to.
Look into every single potential clue, okay?
Yes, sir.
Yes, Detective Eun.
Detective Lee, listen to me carefully.
Use all of the backup you can to find Officer Yoon.
I'll take responsibility for everything.
Yes, ma'am.
And remember the guy who found the luggage at the stream?
You mean this guy you consider as your little brother?
Yeah, if he tells you to search a certain area,
- then do as he says. - Huh?
If Officer Yoon has been kidnapped,
he is our best chance of finding her.
- Hello? Detective Eun? - So you must??
- Hello? - Detective Eun?
(Spy, Call Ended)
Ugh, this is driving me nuts.
Oh, Jae-in.
Did you confirm the face of the kidnapper?
Not yet.
Jae-in! Oh, no, Jae-in!
Is this the control center?
I called you to add one more CCTV
in front of Seoheun Police Station. How did it go?
Ah, please wait.
Uh, what happened to the CCTV in front of Seoheun Police Station?
Ah, the prosecutor who came yesterday made a request too,
so we conducted an emergency installation.
Yes, it has been installed. Is there an issue?
Uh??Someone's been kidnapped in front of the police station
about two hours ago.
Please call me once you confirm the face of the kidnapper.
Alright, let's see.
Here, here, and here are the roads leading to
the streets without CCTVs. Please block them all.
And please tell them to search all the cars in the area.
- When did you prepare this??- Please hurry.
Yes, I see.
Will Jae-in be okay?
Will she be safe?
Of course, she'll be safe.
I never forgive bastards who kidnap my "kid" from my precinct.
I'll see you after I return.
Please find Jae-in, please.
Jae-in!
Oh, are you okay?
What the heck? Is he drunk? Let's go.
I won't collapse.
I won't die.
So,
please show yourself, Yoon Jae-in.
Hey, you jerk, why are you here?
Are you searching the streets marked on the map?
I gave the CCTV map you gave me to all of the units.
I also told them to be on the lookout for
abandoned houses and storefronts. So you go back, and wait.
I will search this way.
Lieutenant Nam, please search that way.
Lee Ahn.
I have to find her.
I'm sure Jae-in left a trace of her for me.
If she did, the police can find it.
No, I am the only one who can see it.
Please excuse us. We have to inspect your vehicle.
What happened?
A kidnapping occurred in a nearby area.
We'd appreciate your cooperation.
Please show us your ID.
(Driver's License: Kim Young-ho)
- Do a background check. - Yes, sir.
Please open the trunk.
Detective Lee, he's been identified.
What are you doing? Open the trunk, please.
Thank you for your cooperation.
(We have secured the photo of the suspect)
Okay.
- Hey, let him pass. - Yes, sir.
Thank you so much.
Ugh, the quality is terrible??
That car??
Catch that car!
Where are you taking me?
Ahn.
Lee Ahn.
(Closed Factory)
(CCTV Recording)
Yoon Jae-in!
Jae-in!
(Do not enter)
Jae-in.
Ahn.
Lee Ahn.
She's here.
Yoon Jae-in!
Jae-in!
Damn it!
Yoon Jae-in!
Jae-in!
No, no! You can't! No!
Jae-in! Wake up, Yoon Jae-in!
Jae-in!
Yoon Jae-in!
Jae-in??
I have something to tell him right now,
but telling him
won't change the fact that Ahn's parents passed away.
Uncovering the truth that my dad isn't the murderer
would heal my wounds only.
I want to go to him so much.
But I can't.
Don't cry.
Jae-in, don't cry, okay?
Don't cry. It's okay.
I'm sorry I came so late.
Please wake up.
What about Jae-in?
Ahn just called me,
she's stable.
Oh, oh, thank you.
Oh, thank you, God.
Oh, Buddha, ancestors, thank you.
- What about that??- What about that lunatic?
Has the bastard who kidnapped Jae-in been caught?
Damn it.
It seems that he abandoned the car and ran away.
- What should we do? - Isn't it obvious?
Search thoroughly.
If we fail to catch this bastard, Detective Eun will kill us.
- Split up! - Yes, sir.
If Officer Yoon is safe, that's enough.
Tell them to guard the hospital where Officer Yoon is,
Let's talk about losing that bastard when I get back.
(Muhyeong-ri Community Health Center)
Yes, it was her alright.
We told the prosecutor who came yesterday as well.
Ms. Kim Song-hee left this island.
Left the island? When?
On December 17.
It was the very day she got treated.
Could you please explain to me in detail
what happened that day?
Suicide attempt?
Yes. Well, the local residents found her,
before her life was in danger,
but she seemed unstable somehow.
It's pretty common with people that come here
when they have no reason to.
So, just in case,
I asked her name and resident registration number,
but she was being stubborn, saying that she wanted to leave
after paying for her medical bill.
I'm sure she did it because when medical record remains,
her whereabouts can be tracked down.
Anyway, we went back and forth for a long time,
but when we said that we'll call the police,
she showed us her ID only then.
And then she left right away.
Plus, she left her ring on the bed.
A ring?
Yes, she had a ring she kept touching, seemingly out of habit.
We gave it to the prosecutor who came yesterday.
December 17th is the day??
The day we did the briefing about Kang Hee-sook and Park Soo-young
being murdered by Kim Gap-yong.
Why did she attempt suicide on that very day??
Why is she keeping it as a secret from you as well,
when she is still alive?
Just why?
(Seoheun Medical Center)
Oh, you poor thing.
You must've been so scared.
You must've been so shocked.
Oh, Jae-in.
Jae-in!
Ah, but looks like Kang Sung-mo now has
more than one precious thing.
For me, she is still the only one.
I think Prosecutor Kang's mother is alive.
You miss her too, right? Your mom.
That woman who lived as the dead Kang Hee-sook and Park Soo-young
is Kang Eun-joo, Prosecutor Kang's mother.
I heard that Jae-in survived
thanks to you finding her early.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Don't worry.
Jae-in is okay now.
I've been telling her that over and over again
on our way here, but she didn't listen.
You should go home and get some rest, too.
You haven't been able to sleep at all, right?
You should get some rest, ma'am.
There are officers watching her, but still??
I want to stay with her.
Still, I have to stay with her.
Sook-ja, aren't you planning to feed her after she's discharged?
Hospital meals won't give her energy.
You think?
Let's go get some groceries before lunchtime is over.
I will prepare abalones and other ingredients,
so please prepare your love and support, ma'am.
Okay, tell her to call me when she wakes up.
Because I want to hear her voice.
- Okay. - Please.
Let's go.
Where should we go shopping for groceries?
Dad.
I remember your face.
You took my dad's clothes.
It's you, isn't it?
The one who stabbed Ahn,
and the one who's been stalking Prosecutor Kang for a long time.
You were the culprit.
Things will never turn out the way you want them to.
I saw the news about a police officer being rescued
after she was kidnapped.
It seems that he has come back.
Everything's happening just like you said.
What are you going to do now?
How much does Ahn know?
Ahn is no longer a kid
crying about seeing weird things.
He knows that man kidnapped Officer Yoon,
so it's only a matter of time until the truth is revealed.
About who he is??
and
what he had done.
Sung-mo.
At that time, there was no one to help you,
but it's different now.
Do not
make a hasty decision on your own.
Thinking about it now,
even back then,
I wasn't alone.
I don't know what happened,
but if you neglect wounds like this without treatment,
it festers. Underestimating them
might be fatal.
If I asked them for help at that time??
If you need any help, call me.
Let's go.
If I called him when we found out that
he came to us again??
I regretted
about that day
over and over again.
I do not want to
make those who are trying to help me
get hurt again.
I have to
find a way.
We checked it and the ID was a stolen one.
The car had been rented under a stolen identity as well.
What about the fingerprints?
We found some in the car, so I sent them to Dr. Hong.
I'll go meet Officer Yoon Jae-in as soon as I get there.
Did you find Kang Eun-joo?
I checked all of the CCTVs, including the ones at
the nearby bus terminal and platforms,
but there was no trace of Kang Eun-joo.
That means Prosecutor Kang couldn't have met her, huh?
I hear the same thing no matter where I go.
"The prosecutor who came yesterday made copies already."
Somehow following Prosecutor Kang has become my specialty.
Does that mean Prosecutor Kang might not know about
the whereabouts of Kang Eun-joo either?
Ah, by the way,
I heard that fingerprints were found from the kidnapper's car.
Yes, but as you know, it'll take time to identify him.
Dr. Hong.
I'd like to ask you a favor.
I know.
You want me to keep the story about Kang Sung-mo's mother
as a secret until we can confirm something, right?
Dr. Hong, you're the best.
Detective Eun, you be careful, too.
According to Kang Sung-mo, you could be in danger, too.
I'll see you when I get back.
Let's stay like this for a little more.
You're hurt, too.
I'll go ask for some ointment. Wait here.
I think I'll get better if we stay like this.
Weren't you scared?
I thought you'd come find me.
I was scared.
I was scared to death, thinking that
I might never hold your hand again.
Ahn.
That bastard??
That bastard who kidnapped me
took my dad's clothes.
That's why my dad was framed as the culprit,
and now I remembered that face.
I know.
You heard that Prosecutor Kang's mother is alive, right?
I'm sure
that bastard is looking for Prosecutor Kang's mother.
But it's not going well for him, so he's hurting the ones around??
You don't need to explain it to me.
So you've seen everything
that happened in that storage.
Yes.
So let's forget about it for a moment,
even for just a moment.
You kept crying in your dreams, too.
And you're saying that again as soon as you wake up.
I am going to
find that bastard, no matter what.
My power can only see
a few out of the thousands of pieces,
but I will
put those pieces together.
I'm sure you will find
both Prosecutor Kang's mother and that bastard.
I believe in you.
You have to help me.
You know that without you,
I'm just a psycho,
not a psychometrist.
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
Shhh.
Our visit will only bother them.
Let's just leave them alone.
Okay.
What are you looking at?
Come on.
Stop making a fuss, my heart.
I'm so glad that they ended up together.
Jae-in has been suffering for a long time,
so I do wish for her to be happy now.
Oh, you should care about your happiness more than hers.
What?
Nothing. I didn't say anything.
Ah, by the way,
- what's a psychorist? - What?
Uh, I heard him saying it in the room earlier.
Psychorist?
Psycho??mattress?
Ah, does it refer to some kind of a professional,
like a guitarist or a cellist?
Ah??Is it?
Well,
Lee Ahn is a professional psycho, after all.
Right. There's no match for him.
By the way, where? Eun-sol?
Ah, I asked Mr. Hong to babysit her for two hours.
It's been a while since I've had some free time.
I need to go buy some diapers.
I'm sure you'll need a porter.
I don't.
Prosecutor Kang's mother attempted suicide
on December 17th?
That was when Kim Gap-yong's murder of real Kang Hee-sook
and Park Soo-young was officially announced.
But why did it have to be that day?
No, more than that??
Why did she have to live under different identities for 13 years,
hiding the fact that she's alive?
I don't understand that.
My head is filled with question marks, too.
How was Kang Eun-joo alive?
And just who is that bastard?
Why did Kang Sung-mo disappear after hiding everything from us?
Perhaps Sung-mo really is trying to kill him.
If he found out that his mother attempted suicide,
and the fact that bastard
kidnapped Jae-in as well, then??
Ji-soo, we have to stop Sung-mo.
Yes, we have to find both Kang Eun-joo and that bastard
before Sung-mo does something crazy.
Have you found any clues to help us find that bastard?
No, I don't even know his name yet.
Dr. Hong is trying to identify him with
the fingerprints found in the car,
but it's not an easy thing to do.
If so, wouldn't it be faster
to investigate Prosecutor Kang's mother first?
If we can find out what happened before the Yeongseong case,
I'm sure we'll be able to find out who he is.
If Kang Eun-joo is his target,
then we should find out about their connection first.
I'm sure he's lurking around us even now,
looking for the clues about Kang Eun-joo.
Please be careful, Detective Eun.
I'm fine.
I'm worried about you, Officer Yoon.
I think I became the target
out of some misunderstanding because Prosecutor Kang
supported me before.
It's not like he likes me
or anything like that.
That's not a misunderstanding, Officer Yoon.
That bastard analyzed Sung-mo correctly.
What?
Anyway, what's certain right now is that Kang Sung-mo
and that bastard know each other very well.
They're trying to predict each other's next move
while trying to figure out each other's weaknesses.
I'm sure that's why Kang Sung-mo
couldn't approach you himself
and had Ahn besides you.
Sung-mo might've kept his feelings perfectly
from Ahn or you,
but he couldn't keep it from him.
So Sung-mo knew everything from the start, right?
That this bastard was behind the Yeongseong Apt. and
Hanmin incidents all because of his mother.
I'm sure Kang Sung-mo knew about it already.
The problem is, that bastard is so skilled that Sung-mo couldn't
catch him all this time, even if he knew that he was the culprit.
This??
This is still here.
I might have to live with this forever.
Wounds that have not been treated on time
become scars.
I heard that a scar is a trace of overcoming a wound,
but why does this one look like it still hurts?
It hurts.
It still does.
The memories from that moment still remain.
Sung-mo suffered
because of him, too.
- What? - He has the same scar
on his ankle, just like Jae-in's wound.
Ji-soo, can you please find out about where Sung-mo lived
before he moved to Yeongseong Apartments?
I was about to do that actually,
but 13 years ago is way too long ago to see anything
with your power.
Regardless of using my power or not,
I want to know.
About who that bastard is.
About why he does this,
and what his connection to Sung-mo is.
If I find out about them,
I think I'll be able to perform better
when my power is really needed.
Yeah. Let's do it together.
Ah, and these are the materials on
the Yeongseong Apt. case, Hanmin Nursing Hospital case,
and the murder case of Kim Gap-yong.
I thought you might be curious about them, Officer Yoon.
Why??are you giving these to me??
Why?
Ahn found out where you were being held
with his psychometry,
so I don't have any reason to wait any longer.
So you're saying
that you will co-investigate with us.
Huh? Am I right?
That sounds too grandiose.
Yeah, let's work together, officially.
Lee Ahn, the psychometrist,
and Officer Yoon.
Are you serious?
I can't perform an investigation while controlling him.
And Officer Yoon, you're the only one who'll put everything
into this case with a sense of duty.
Ji-soo, thank you so much.
Thank you so much, Ji-soo.
Hey, let go.
Ugh, my head is full of complicated thoughts right now.
Don't touch me. Don't read me.
Officer Yoon, what are you doing? Stop him.
Hug her even harder. With my share of hug, too.
Okay.
- Hey, let go. Let me go. - I love you.
Hey, let go. I have something to tell Officer Yoon.
To Jae-in?
Officer Yoon, you see??
I'd like to apologize on my dad's behalf
about your father being framed.
I'm sorry.
I don't know if I'll be able to
pay off this debt by working hard,
but I won't make the same mistake.
Ji-soo.
Are you okay?
Well, I'm used to being dumped by Kang Sung-mo.
See you after she gets discharged.
Excuse me, uh??Do you have a library or a bookstore here?
Over there.
(The Little Prince)
Compared to blocking the CCTVs beforehand
and carefully planning the murder,
the method of murder is quite simple.
Yeongseong Apt., Hanmin Nursing Hospital, and Kim Gap-yong.
They've all been stabbed on the abdomen.
The only notable thing is that
the knife found at the scene wasn't a manufactured product.
What do you mean, it wasn't a manufactured product?
I think he made it himself.
I saw it when he came to the wire crafts class
at the cultural center to check me out.
His skills were extraordinary.
And it is highly possible that he made the chains
he used to tie me as well.
By the way, where have you been?
Ah.
Oh.
"It's the time that you spent on your rose"
"that makes your rose so important."
"You become responsible forever"
"for what you've tamed."
Yes, he mentioned that book.
I read it, hoping to get an idea of his psychological state,
but I don't understand.
For me, it's just a heartwarming tale.
"The time that you spent on your rose"
That means they've known each other for a long time,
long before they moved to Yeongseong Apartments.
Jae-in.
You shouldn't overwork yourself just yet.
Let's stop here for today.
Now I can really feel it.
That my dad isn't the culprit.
So don't cry again.
Ever.
I won't cry.
Why would I cry, when I have you?
That sounds really nice.
Why?
I like you, Lee Ahn.
I like you, very much.
Well, people say
that your life flashes before your eyes like a panorama
when you think that you're about to die.
That happened to me, too.
And I recalled what I couldn't tell you.
Hey, I was going to say it first.
How could you say it before I do?
Then you should just say it, too.
Hey, that's not, you know,
if that's easy to say, then I would've said it already.
Yeah, okay then,
uh??say it with difficulty, later.
Be honest with me.
You want me to say it to you, right?
Yes, I do.
Why are you so straightforward today?
If you go straight like that, we might have an accident.
A big accident.
Can't I cause a big accident?
Do you even know what you're talking about?
Ugh, seriously.
See? It's good to smile.
Just like how you made me smile
whenever I was having a hard time,
from now on, I'll make you smile
whenever you have a hard time.
I'll do it.
It's okay.
You never listen to me.
The weather is a lot warmer now.
I wish that spring would come soon.
Yeah, that'll be great.
I told you, I'll do it later.
What are you doing? You just left the hospital. This isn't right.
It's not even that dirty.
I tried to stop her, but she wouldn't listen.
This might be my last cleaning here.
I got so attached to this police station.
Last cleaning? What do you mean?
Uh??I think Jae-in will soon
transfer to the special investigation team??
Hi.
We could've come to you if you called.
Why did you come all the way here?
What the heck?
Why did you bring your things here?
Why? Because I'm going to investigate from here.
Here?
Wow.
Uh, I said that I needed you two,
and asked you to investigate with me.
I never said anything about you working at special investigation.
Wow, how could you trick your "brother?"
Did you think that too, Officer Yoon?
Yes, I thought I was going to work at special investigation too??
Ah??So you didn't know.
Special investigation team has temporarily disbanded due to
Prosecutor Kang's absence.
Officially, I mean.
All of those cases, from Yeongseong to the luggage murder,
are all closed, so it's kind of weird to form a team.
So, in a sense, this is my personal investigation.
We've all been dumbed down into one group.
I'm disappointed in you, Officer Yoon.
How does being at a small police station dumb you down?
Lieutenant Nam right here
worked the hardest in this field.
He's not someone you can look down on, for retiring soon.
Does that mean Lieutenant Nam is on our team, too?
Of course.
Wait.
I don't know what's going on, but there's a misunderstanding.
I do not wish to take action and get stabbed
at my age. Not even for a bit.
What the heck?
If so, are you all totally against me?
Should I just go back, then? Huh?
You're not supposed to go back. You're supposed to take us.
To the special investigation team.
If the special investigation team isn't an option, then to
a criminal team??
You too, Officer Yoon?
How are you going to explain him to the superiors?
You have the title of a junior officer, but he's??
What? What? What?
- Anyway, you can't. - What is this?
You said we're a team, but why do I feel left out?
I'll explain it to you after I come back.
Let's go.
Let me borrow Officer Yoon for a while.
Let's go, let's go.
Wow, it's not that I feel left out,
but I am actually being left out.
(Fire and murder case at Yeongseong Apartments)
I am going to re-investigate
the Yeongseong case properly.
- What? - Don't try to stop me.
Don't try to stop me.
If you try to stop me again,
that would mean you're really hiding something.
Don't disappoint me anymore.
Eun Ji-soo!
Ji-soo!
(Congratulations YSS Construction)
I think it makes sense when Officer Yoon said
that the connection was made a long time ago,
so I'm going to go back to the beginning.
Starting from Kang Eun-joo's hometown.
Gangnyeong-si, Gangwon-do.
Yes. She lived there until 1996,
and she changed her address quite often after that.
It feels like she's been to every corner of this country.
If so, she could've been running away from him
since 1996.
Yeah. But there are so many weird things.
First, look at Kang Sung-mo's birth record.
Sung-mo's birthday is May 24, 1988,
but his birth was registered in 1996.
- Nine years after his birth. - What?
His birth wasn't registered for nine years?
In addition, he's registered under Kang Eun-joo,
and there's no record of her spouse.
Then could it be??
You said your father passed away early, right?
What kind of person was he?
You didn't hear anything about Prosecutor Kang's father, right?
Not at all.
I really hope our imagination isn't the reality.
(Gangnyeong Steel Company)
Looks like they've been out of business for a long time.
Let's go inside.
This must've been a steel factory.
It seems like it's been abandoned for a while.
Officer Yoon, go see if you can find anything from
when Sung-mo used to live here.
And Ahn, you know what to do, right?
Yeah.
Hello, Dr. Hong.
He must've been making
his own knives and chains here.
Wait.
- That's not the way. - What?
The direction of the footsteps
starts here
and heads to there.
Someone must've been here recently.
Has he been identified?
Uh, more than that,
I found a cold case in which the fingerprints are a match.
A cold case?
It was in Yeonhae-dong, Gangnyeong, Gangwon-do, in 1996,
and even though the fingerprints of the culprit was found,
it seems that they couldn't identify him either at the time,
so it turned into a cold case.
(Gangnyeong Steel Company)
What??what kind of case was it?
This way.
I can see it.
Sung-mo was here.
He came in here for sure??
Wait.
This is the only spot without any dust.
What?
Looks like this door was opened recently.
What is this?
Why??is this thing??here??
Is this a basement?
We need to go in there.
Sung-mo, run!
Run! Run! Run!
It's a case in which the culprit locked up a woman
and a child in a basement for nine years.
(He is Psychometric)
Did it mean that you were going to come meet me?
Did you not want me to look into this case?
What if he acted, perfectly?
Covered it up as quietly as possible?
You know it. That's my real name.
I came from a place that exists, but does not exist.
Please.
Was my father's investigation for covering up the truth on purpose,
instead of an overlooked mistake?
We need to find the traces that cannot be seen.
That's your specialty.
Detective Eun.