(He is Psychometric)
Fire safety system? Ha! He's nothing but a security guard.
It does show that he is a former firefighter, though.
Ugh, a firefighter??
If a dog barks at its owner,
then it can't be helped, right?
It has to be killed, right?
It should be killed.
Ugh, what now?
Who is it?
What is it?
Do you have something to say to me?
What's that bag?
I'm sorry.
Huh? That voice??
Oh, no!
Oh, no! What's wrong?
(PSYCHOMETRY A combination of Greek words)
(PSYCHE/Soul and METRON/Measuring)
(An ability to measure the soul of a person or)
(an object and interpreting it)
(He is Psychometric, Final Episode)
Lee Ahn!
Ahn!
Wake up, Ahn! Ahn!
No way.
Emergency, emergency.
Unit 702. Lee Ahn is injured.
Currently not breathing, no pulse.
Call for emergency rescue, call for emergency rescue!
Lee Ahn, are you okay? Are you okay?
Jae-in.
The one who
killed people and caused the fire here
was Sung-mo.
We, we have to find Sung-mo.
The police are looking for him, so you stay here.
If you keep using your power, you might really die.
I think I know where Sung-mo is.
Ahn!
Lee Ahn!
Lee Ahn.
Are you okay?
Officer Yoon, where are you going?
He said he thinks he knows where Prosecutor Kang is??
Which floor are we going to? 15th floor? The rooftop?
Lieutenant Nam, please go to the rooftop.
I'll go to the 15th floor.
Okay.
I'm too late, aren't I?
I should've come here and asked for help.
But I'm??
- way too late. - Why did you do that?
Did you want to make it look like Kang Geun-taek did it?
Did you kill people and start the fire
to turn him into a criminal?
I figured it out as soon as I saw the body Kang Geun-taek brought.
What his plan was??
A knife.
Lighters.
Mom's ID.
A body of a woman burnt in a fire.
(Yeongseong Apartments, Yoon Tae-ha)
And then I thought.
'What can I do
to get us out of this hell?'
I thought that if I put him into prison
before he found my mother, it would all end.
What is this?
I thought that if a lot more people died,
the more likely the police would look into our case.
I knew it was the wrong choice,
but I couldn't stop.
It was Kang Geun-taek who planned it
and brought the body,
but it was me, who executed it.
That was when I realized
that no matter how much I want to deny it,
I??
I am the child of a monster.
Then why,
why didn't you run away? Why did you remain on the 7th floor?
You had time to run away!
Why were you there, and why did you??
save me?
Lower your bodies!
To the stairs! Lower your bodies!
I was scared??
and terrified.
I was horrified of what I did.
Ironically,
at the moment I chose to become a monster,
I learned what fear was
and what guilt was for the first time,
so I couldn't move.
So, you felt emotions for the first time then,
and that's why you saved me?
Yes.
And went to unit 1501 to meet the police officer who
offered to help me, but it was empty.
Lieutenant Nam.
It's unit 1501.
Freeze!
I'm sorry, Ahn.
I'm sorry, Officer Yoon.
You're under arrest
under Article 212 of the Criminal Procedure Act.
You have the right to remain silent. Anything you say
can and will be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
Take him away.
Ms. Kang Eun-joo.
It's all over.
Kang Geun-taek has been caught.
He's in surgery right now,
Prosecutor Kang Sung-mo was arrested at the scene, too.
Detective Park, you stay here.
Yes, sir.
(Operating Room)
His skin necrosis was progressing due to sepsis, DIC,
and necrotizing fasciitis,
so we had to amputate his left arm.
Is his life in danger?
We need to move him to the intensive care unit
to see how it goes for now.
Do you admit that you kidnapped and
attempted to murder Kang Geun-taek?
Yes, I do.
I also committed murder and arson at Yeongseong Apartments.
Did you try to frame Kang Geun-taek?
I had only one priority at the time.
It wasn't the pain of others or the truth.
'If I go to prison, what will happen to my mother?'
'Can she deal with Kang Geun-taek all on her own?'
That was all I was thinking about.
But then why did you let Kang Geun-taek live?
You had enough time to have your revenge.
I didn't let him live.
I just wanted him to die slowly,
suffering.
He got caught that easily?
Without fighting back?
Ugh, then why did he run away to this place
and leave us to deal with this crap?
Wow, this is driving me nuts.
Officer Yoon.
Is it true that Kang Sung-mo confessed everything?
- Yes. - Ugh, I'm going nuts.
I will find that bastard, no matter what.
So promise me that you will wait.
Wow, you were always crying about seeing weird things,
but you've grown up, huh?
This is our house? Really?
Now, this looks like a house of a prosecutor.
Anyway, this is my housewarming gift.
Wow, thank you.
(Seized items)
(Item: wallet)
(Item: cell phone)
Kang Sung-mo, where are you?
If you're trying to threaten me with a ledger, then stop it.
I won't threaten you. I want to make a deal.
A deal?
What is it? Is he making a deal to get himself free?
- Please listen until the end. - What do you want?
I heard that you were interrogated by the police
as a suspect for kidnapping Kang Geun-taek or whoever.
Is that it?
Are you asking me for help in case something goes wrong?
Is that what you want?
That ledger is a complete record of bribery committed
by Dragon Head Hunting, under the direction of YSS,
to the members of the police, the prosecution
and of course, politics and finances.
And it's quite detailed, too.
Just bring the ledger.
Even if you committed murder,
I'll take care of it without any problems.
Where's the ledger?
Prosecutor General.
That ledger will be a small stone at the bottom of a rock tower.
What on earth are you talking about?
I have to pile up the rocks carefully, one by one,
but I don't have much time.
Let's talk in person. Where are you?
No matter what I have committed,
please don't do anything.
Leave it to the law and due process.
- What? - And,
please wait for the day the rock tower is completed.
Continue anxiously holding onto that power,
a power that will collapse one day without any notice.
That's what I want.
That ledger could've helped you avoid a murder charge,
but you??You turned yourself in.
So, where's the ledger right now?
I thought about whom I should ask to
take care of those materials, but there was always only one answer.
Lastly, please pass this message on to Ahn.
I'm sorry for ruining your past,
your present,
and your future.
Hi, Jae-in.
I asked Prosecutor Kang about where the ledger containing
YSS Construction's bribery is,
but he changed the subject, perhaps he didn't want to
- leak information. - Changed the subject?
He told me to tell you that
he's sorry for ruining your past, your present,
and your future.
Could the ledger... be there?
Does that mean something to you?
Why did you bring me to a crowded place, for a painting?
Choose what you like.
I'll hang it in my room.
You should hang the one you like in your room.
You're weird.
Oh, this one's awesome.
A wolf, a lion,
and is this a dog?
I like this one.
Why? Don't you like it?
I do. I like it.
The head of the lion stands for the present,
the wolf stands for the past,
and the dog stands for the future.
You must learn from the past,
and behave carefully in the present,
so you don't ruin your actions in the future??
That's what it means.
He told me to tell you that
he's sorry for ruining your past, your present,
and your future.
Wait??
Sung-mo. I have a favor to ask you.
Don't run away anymore.
Don't hurt those who became miserable because of
your wrong choice anymore.
And if you're trying to kill him and kill yourself,
you cannot do that.
If you do that,
you will never be forgiven by anyone.
That doesn't only include me, but also those children.
Please don't tell me to
understand or forgive Sung-mo just yet.
That's way too cruel for me at this moment.
From the current Prosecutor General to assemblypeople,
all kinds of bribery took place under YSS orders.
This is getting way too big.
This isn't smashing a rock with an egg,
but smashing it with a speck of dust.
Prosecutor Kang did commit murder and arson,
but it became a tragedy
because of the corruption in YSS Construction.
You already knew about it, Lieutenant Nam.
Yes, I did.
But those who knew about the corruption and covered it up,
are the ones currently in office.
If we turn this in to the prosecution, it's only
a matter of time before it becomes another scrap of paper.
Like Prosecutor Kang said,
this needs power and time.
What difference does it make if we wait?
Should we just sit here and watch those in the office
pass it from one generation to the next?
We can't do that.
We started this. We need to end this.
So, how should we end it?
How?
Wouldn't it be possible with
Commissioner Eun's power?
I braced myself for it,
but I didn't expect to sit here so quickly.
That ledger is a copy,
and we're keeping the original just in case.
So, are you saying
that I should be the bomb?
You weren't the only one corrupt in the Yeongseong Apt. case.
Those who kept quiet, neglected it, and complied,
are all in there.
Yes, let's do this.
Gather up the press first.
That's the only thing that can get this thing off the ground.
As of today, two months after we reopened this investigation,
the real culprit behind the murder and arson at Yeongseong Apt.
has turned himself in after 14 years,
unexpectedly turning the tables on the investigation.
Police Commissioner Eun Byung-ho, who was in charge of the case,
is about to make a statement, drawing attention and curiosity,
The corruption of YSS??
Isn't there anything that will grab the journalists' attention?
Find something to distract them. Cover this up.
First, I'd like to ask for forgiveness
from the victims who died from the Yeongseong Apt. fire
and their families who lost their loved ones.
I confess that I tried to cover up the truth by misconducting
the investigation to curtail the case,
forgetting my duties as an officer of the law,
and receiving bribery from YSS Construction
I confess to receiving bribes that
were in direct violations of my duties as an officer of the law,
and as such, I will be taking responsibility and stepping down.
Everything being reported in the press about
the corruption of YSS Construction is true and I promise to you
that I will do my best to cooperate with the investigation.
As a public servant who serves the people,
I failed to lead by example, and I humbly apologize once more.
The police exist to protect the people
and to keep law and order.
That is the duty and reason for its existence.
My one hope is that the whole ROK police force,
not be criticized and hated because I have strayed
and lost my sense of duty as an officer of the law.
Now let's wait and see.
If a special team forms, the prosecution's investigation
will begin and all we can do is hope,
that they fell very far from that tree.
Getting this far is enough for me.
Ah.
This is a lawyer I know well.
Kang Sung-mo confessed,
so there's no reason to wait any longer.
You need to prepare for a retrial.
Thank you.
Don't say that.
I only added my name to everything you've done.
Officer Yoon.
You have done so well.
Did you sleep at Dae-bong's house yesterday too?
Yes.
Didn't Dae-bong's father say anything?
His house is so big,
I didn't even see him.
Ah, I've never lived in a house like that before.
Same here.
The Yeongseong Apt. case, triggered by Police Commissioner
Eun Byung-ho's resignation announcement raised doubts
of not only the prosecution and the police, but also those in
the political and financial world, speeding up the investigation.
The police have secured evidence that proves corruption
in YSS Construction and bribery of personnel in
the political and financial world.
The prosecution claimed that the case was being exaggerated
and distorted, but there has been rising criticism over the rights
to the investigation, indictment and maintenance of indictment,
which are all held exclusively by the prosecution.
As support grew for a national petition demanding
checks and balances of the prosecution,
it has begun a late search and seizure.
Want to??go in with me?
I'll say hi to him properly later.
I don't think he'd want to say hi
to his daughter's boyfriend in there.
Okay. I'll be back soon.
You look too thin.
You look much better, Dad.
Your aunt has been visiting me often recently.
She told me that you're working very hard.
The culprit confessed,
and the residents at the apartments told the truth.
The lawyer said that it will all work out,
but we still have to wait for three months at least
before the verdict for the new trial is in.
I'm fine with that.
That's not a big deal.
I'm sorry.
About what?
Even though it was just for brief moments,
I did doubt you at times.
I thought you could've been the culprit.
Jae-in.
I'm sorry.
I made you suffer,
and couldn't do my job as a father.
When I think about it, we haven't had
a real date since our first date, right?
Is there anything you want to do?
Hmm??
There's a lot, but I don't need to do anything.
I don't want to risk my boyfriend's life to go on a date.
Ah??Everyone goes on a date, but I can't.
Ah, right. I've been meaning to tell you.
You, you're not allowed to touch dead bodies anymore.
- What? - Ah, no murder scenes, either.
No, not even murder weapons. No, no, don't touch anything.
Then what should I do?
You? Crime comes in many forms.
Hmm??Missing people, voice phishing,
vault thieves, and so on.
Then what about you?
You shouldn't go to the murder scene either. It's dangerous.
I have to go.
There's a rumor about me being specially promoted.
A special promotion? What about me?
Don't you remember?
At least I have the title of junior officer, there's no way
to explain you to the superiors. That's what Detective Eun said??
I know you're not talking about Ji-soo or Sung-mo on purpose.
But don't do that.
Well, you don't talk about them, so I??
If you neglect a wound, it festers.
That's what your father said.
So I'm not going to ignore or neglect it anymore.
I told you that?
Do you need to say it for me to know?
Prosecutor Kang's first trial will be held soon.
Yeah.
Are you going?
(Seoul Seoheun Main Police Station)
I'm telling you again,
but I didn't kill anybody.
Not a single person.
I've been asking him since he woke up at the hospital,
but he says that he didn't kill anybody.
He says that he didn't kill Detective Eun, either.
Let's deal with the charges where we can prove his guilt.
The fake body of Kang Eun-joo at Yeongseong Apartments
has been cremated already, so we can't prove that.
There's no evidence that connects him to Kim Gap-yong either,
just the circumstantial evidence of the use of chains.
Then the remaining ones are
the Hanmin Nursing Hospital case and the case of Ji-soo.
A ton of evidence and witnesses for Detective Eun's case,
but the problem is the Hanmin Nursing Hospital case.
If he doesn't sign the confession,
then having Kang Eun-joo take the stand is the only way, right?
That's Kang Geun-taek's goal as well.
So he's trying to see her face one last time?
Wow??He's cruel up until the end.
Having Kang Eun-joo, who was locked up by Kang Geun-taek,
take the stand at the court, is inhumane.
What if he's only in there for 10 years and he goes after her again?
That's even more horrible.
We need to tie him up and put him away for good this time.
Jae-in and I will go meet Kang Eun-joo.
Testify about Hanmin Nursing Hospital?
In front of him?
I know it'll be hard, but that case could be what determines
Kang Geun-taek's sentencing at court.
Can you??do it?
I know I have to do it,
but could you please??give me some time?
I'll think about it.
I??I have to grab some things.
Can you help me?
Okay.
Did you notice?
Prosecutor Kang's mother
has never called Kang Geun-taek by his name.
I know.
Do you??know the reason behind that, too?
What is your real name?
Where are you from?
Because she thinks all this happened
because of that name.
Is it true that you have no name and you're undocumented?
Sigh, you must've been abandoned when you were little.
This place is full of people like that.
The owner gathered guys like that only on purpose.
So he can pay them close to nothing.
Hey, get your resident registration number first.
Resident registration??I need a name for it.
Don't you have a random name you've used?
No.
Really?
Hey, Eun-joo!
You know Chinese characters quite well, right?
Give him a name.
How about Geun-taek?
"Geun" means "root," and "taek" means "house."
Geun-taek?
I'm sure you've been wandering here and there.
It means you should settle down at one place soon.
Hey.
Let's go inside and pack.
I like that name.
What's your name?
Me? I'm Kang Eun-joo.
Then I'll be
Kang Geun-taek.
That must be the memory Kang Eun-joo wants to erase.
Yes.
(Manual)
(Automatic)
Okay, I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
I'll leave after I'm done with this.
You promised Sung-mo.
That you wouldn't cry.
But if you just stay here like this,
then Sung-mo catching Kang Geun-taek
and turning himself in will be meaningless.
I??
I am leaving because if I stay here,
I recall too many memories of Sung-mo.
It's not because of you, Ms. Kang Eun-joo.
There's too much stuff,
so we need to come back later.
Okay.
You eat everything here today, okay?
It's all on me today.
Huh? Really? What's going on?
I didn't think you'd ever become functioning members of society.
But you've all grown up wonderfully.
So as your most admired teacher,
I should treat you, right?
Mr. Hong.
And, since it's on me,
one more person will join us.
What?
There she comes, just in time.
Here, have a seat.
What about Eun-sol?
Uh, your aunt said that she will babysit her??
So she told me to go and have fun.
Help yourselves.
What the heck? What's going on between you two?
Uh??You see??
While you two were busy, we too
went through some things.
What?
I'll tell you later.
Go ahead and have a drink. Cheers.
Cheers.
(Daebong Nara Gas Station)
What?
Did you see it? Did you?
Which side do you think it is?
Does she really hate me with all of her heart? Does she?
Hmm??If I were to mildly exaggerate,
it looks like she finally saw your true charm.
Good luck.
What if she asks you out today all of a sudden?
It's the man's job to ask a woman out, okay?
- Hey, let's toast. - Let's toast!
Come on, come on, gather your glasses.
Gather your glasses.
Cheers.
- Cheers. - Cheers!
Defendant, you have pleaded not guilty to all charges.
Is that correct?
I didn't kill anybody.
That bastard??
Order in the court!
Order!
Is Ms. Kang Eun-joo, the witness from the prosecution, present?
Witness, please take an oath.
Oath.
I will tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth,
under pains and penalties of perjury.
Prosecutor, you may question her.
Ms. Kang, did you receive a call from Kang Geun-taek
right before the fire at Hanmin Nursing Hospital in 2016?
- Yes. - Did you go there because
Kang Geun-taek, the defendant, threatened to kill
Song Hee-jeong, Yoo Eun-ok, Jung Man-soon, the victims?
Yes.
Could you please tell us in detail what happened after that?
Yes, I will??
I will tell you everything.
The defendant stabbed the vulnerable victims with a weapon
and committed arson to damage their bodies.
And his criminal activities didn't stop there.
He kidnapped an active police officer,
stabbed and killed another officer and ran away.
And the motive for these crimes, murder, abduction,
desecration of a corpse, and etc. cannot be accepted by the court.
He abused his status as an undocumented individual,
and his crime methods were cruel and unusual.
It is the judgment of the court, that he has felt
no sense of remorse or guilt up to present day.
I hereby sentence the defendant to death.
When we come face to face an uncomfortable past,
even though it might be painful,
we take a step forward through the wound,
(Police Commissioner Eun Byung-ho)
When the hand of a clock ticks for one second,
fair and square for all people,
the present becomes the past.
Some leave a painful past behind
to welcome a new life.
And some
are trapped in the past for eternity,
ruining their remaining future.
The defendant committed murder, taking three apartment
residents' lives, arson, causing a large number of
the residents to lose lives or suffer from property damage.
He has caused tremendous emotional pain
to the surviving families that cannot be healed,
proving the cruelty of the crimes.
And held his biological father hostage with the intent to kill,
calls for a harsh punishment as well.
But he has confessed to his crimes
and has asked for forgiveness from the families of the victims.
He was also confined and assaulted
by his biological father for nine years in the past.
And even after he escaped,
he was forced to live in hiding.
At the time of his crimes, he was legally a minor.
In addition, he suffers from alexithymia, difficulty
with expressing emotions,
With everything taken into consideration,
I hereby sentence the defendant, Kang Sung-mo
to 13 years in prison.
We use all kinds of methods to
treat the wounds from the past,
but the scars remain.
They become unforgettable memories.
They require a long time to fade away.
What kind of memory
will this very moment become for me?
(One year later)
How long are you going to sleep, huh?
Until it's fully charged.
Charged? Nah.
All I did was give you a place to rest your head.
What are you talking about? I was talking about my phone.
Until my phone is charged, I mean.
Ugh, you said you'll study after a short break.
You habitual study skipper.
(Share wireless battery)
Ugh, is this the only way?
Can't I become a cop solely with my power?
I told you.
There are professional investigation consultants,
but even such civilian experts have a Master's or Ph.D.
This terrible world only cares about diplomas.
That needs to be fixed first.
Still, the detectives are all dying to work with you.
Yesterday, Chief Nam told me to bring you,
but I stopped him, saying that you have to study.
What kind of case was it?
What??What are you doing here?
We arrested two homeless people
hiding in a deserted house.
Recently, someone's been going around
to the homeless to sign them up for life insurance.
It seems that they sign up for the insurance
for a tiny amount of money to buy some soju.
What they don't know is that they just got paid for their lives.
Why are you so obsessed with the homeless?
Kang Geun-taek wandered around without a job all his life by
fabricating the IDs of the homeless, too.
But he never spoke about how he got money
to live day-to-day.
I think this is how.
Stealing the identities of the homeless.
Kang Geun-taek did it for himself.
Dragon Head Hunting was organized.
I'm sure there's a big gang behind it this time too.
Hey, hurry up and put it on.
I have a police exam coming up soon, remember?
Here, smell it.
Ugh, what is that?
Ugh, that smell??
We're all set.
Okay then, scatter and lie down.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Should I drink a bottle of soju?
Do I have to put this on?
(Seoheun Police Station)
What??What happened to you two?
Oh, my goodness, where did this
pretty beggar and??real beggar come from? Huh?
Sook-ja, I'm starving.
Catching bad guys is a good thing, but look after yourself first.
Dad, since we cleared your name,
should I just quit? Huh?
Being a cop is a lot harder than I thought.
Don't say what you don't mean.
If we lose you, we lose our team.
Don't say that.
Did you hear that, Dad? I'm a big deal.
Go wash up and get changed.
The smell is filling the entire house.
Ugh, good grief. Ugh.
What the heck?
Why is Chief Nam's clothes at our house?
Huh? This is??uh??This is yours, Tae-ha.
That isn't mine, Sook-ja.
It??It isn't?
Sook-ja.
Looks like there's no perfect crime. So let's just??
What are you talking about?
Uh??Get out and wash up.
You, too. Go wash up!
My underwear is missing.
Ugh, just wash, and??put on whatever.
This jerk Dae-bong isn't answering.
Hey!
Wow.
Hey, long time, no see.
How are things at the station?
What do you think it's like after a demotion?
Ah, if you "see" any decent cases,
call me right away.
You'll co-investigate them with me, okay?
- Okay. - Promise me.
I'm not doing this because I have something to hide.
- Bye. - Goodbye.
What the heck? That Lee Dae-bong.
Where is he?
Why are you here every day? What about the gas station?
Hey, the gas station does fine without me,
but they can't do anything without me here.
When I go in, the crying child just stops crying.
- Give me the car key. - Ah, tomorrow's the exam, right?
Besides the exam,
I have to go somewhere.
Okay. Have a safe trip.
Hey, Lee Dae-bong.
What are you doing?
Oh.
Bye.
I hear about you from my mother sometimes.
I heard that you're on the investigation team.
It's unofficial for now.
You expected this day to come, didn't you?
So you came back to me, even after you left me,
you made me and Jae-in meet,
and asked Jae-in to train my power.
After that day,
the me who wanted to become human
and the me who was a natural born monster
kept fighting in my head every day.
Sung-mo, I've missed you.
I wondered how betrayed you'd feel
if you knew that I, a murderer, saved you.
I felt like a monster
as I stood in front of you after I did such a thing,
but at the same time, I was worried about you,
and I missed you, too.
I didn't plan all this
when I returned to you.
Perhaps when I saved you,
when you got that power,
I started.
I wish someone could tell us.
That it's enough.
Resentment, hate,
and self-blame.
That those things can stop now.
(The 1st 2020 Police Officer Examination)
Lee Ahn, did you forget that we're supposed to meet today?
Where are you? How did you do on the exam?
Exam went fine.
I got an urgent call from Dr. Hong, so I came to see her.
I'll come right afterward.
Dr. Hong?
Hey??I told you to not touch dead bodies.
You stay right there.
If you die, I'll kill you.
Wow, you came here flying, Senior Officer Yoon?
Dr. Hong, I told you.
If he keeps touching dead bodies, he'll die.
I know.
And I'm not going to be calling him over for a while.
She wanted to give me some books on legal medicine.
Dr. Hong is going on a long trip.
A trip?
I'm a bit tired.
The work isn't fun, either.
If I go and take some time off,
I'm sure I would want to return someday.
So, Senior Officer Yoon, train him until then
so nothing happens if he touches a dead body.
Okay?
Wow, this is great.
Good water pressure, too.
Did you always have money to buy such a house?
Hmm??
I think I can buy two-thirds of it with my money.
Then what about the rest?
Ah??With a loan?
No, with your money.
- What? - Ah??You can get a loan, too.
Uh??I, too, was??thinking of getting a house
with my dad's indemnity, but??
See? You have to move out of the police station, too.
You've been staying there for a long time.
So?
You??want me to live with you??
There are three rooms.
One for your father, one for me, and one for you and your aunt.
And I poked around,
it seems like your aunt will be moving out soon.
She is just trying to figure out the right timing.
No??with Chief Nam?
Let's live together, Jae-in.
I don't want to live alone. It's lonely.
If my power is going to make living with me uncomfortable??
No, I'm not uncomfortable at all.
Yes, sure, I love it.
Wow, I have a house now.
Do you know what the opposite of noradrenaline,
the thing that stores bad memories in your brain, is?
Hmm??
I don't know.
Beta-Endorphin.
As you smile and laugh more,
it stores good memories in your brain.
Oh, Lee Ahn, look at you. You know so much.
Dr. Hong must be
having a hard time because of her memories of Ji-soo, right?
I hope she doesn't stay lost for too long.
You should stop being lost, too.
I know that you've been only been studying
and not jumping into cases.
It's been more than 416.666666667 days already.
You should stop now.
(The wife is unconscious during childbirth! The baby is dead!)
(Medical accident, who should be held responsible?)
Please read it.
I beg you.
Hey.
Do you think you can understand medical jargon
that doctors use?
(Thank you so much for watching)
("He is Psychometric")
(He is Psychometric)
(Hahahahaha)
- What? Why? Why? - Cut.
Stop calling my name!
(A charming smile)
We'll go again.
Cut.
(Hahahahaha)
(Director's idea to have Ji-soo unable to enter the autopsy room)
(Ugh)
(Beep)
(She scanned the card, but the door won't open)
Go in. Go in.
(Hahahahaha)
(Park Jin-young, the genius actor)
(Lee Ahn giving a tremendous acting performance)
(The perfect final point as well)
Cut.
(Heeheeheeheehee)
- And then??- A candy.
(Jae-in, a lovely girl)
(Lee Ahn was sliding down fast on a wire)
(Swoosh)
(Holding in the laughter)
(Hahahahaha)
(Landed safely)
(Jin-young is practicing)
(an awesome entrance for Lee Ahn)
Right.
It works.
(Here's a closeup of this awesomeness)
(Lee Ahn, the charming guy)
(who's cute even when taking a shower)
(Dancing machine)
Salute.