[English subtitles are available]
[In the Name of the Brother]
[Episode 22]
Sir, what can I do for you?
[Binjiang Daily]
Sirs…
We're with him.
Hello, can I speak to Mr. Morikawa?
Please go in.
I have a photo
and can't tell if it's been tampered with.
Please take a look for me.
Mr. Morikawa hasn't come to work.
It's fine. I can wait for him.
Okay. When he comes,
I'll ask him immediately.
You can go take a rest in the reception room.
Where are we going?
Go to the photo studio at the intersection now.
There's a family photo in its window too.
Good morning.
Thank you.
That guy is Morikawa.
Go pick a fight.
You're Morikawa, right?
-What do you want?
-You're Morikawa, right?
Damn! What do you want?
You're Morikawa, aren't you?
I did that thing reported in the newspaper.
Why isn't my photo in it?
Who the hell are you?
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Who are you? Seize him!
Why isn't my phone in it?
How did someone like him get in?
Drag him out!
Stop fighting.
Get him arrested!
Let go of me!
Stop fighting.
Tell your superior
this photo is real.
I see.
Please.
I'll see myself out.
[Binjiang Daily]
I didn't have time to swap the photos.
What are you going to do?
I have to catch up with him
before Guan Xue sees the photo,
or my brother's cover will be blown.
What are you going to do
after catching up with him?
Grab the handle. Sit tight.
What are you going to do?
I'll go around to the front of his car, turn around, and hit it.
Hit his car?
I'll knock him out.
You'll get in his car and swap the photos.
Is it the Police Agency?
Please put Song Zhuowen from the Secret Service on.
Zhuowen, Zhouwen.
Come with me. You're exposed.
Are you crazy?
It's dangerous for you to be here.
Stop looking. Get in the car!
Come on!
Come in.
Ding Peng.
What are you doing here?
What's in your hand?
The family photo of Song Zhuowen.
Director Morikawa from Binjiang Daily's
photo department personally examined it.
It's not been tampered with.
It's real.
Ding Peng.
Didn't we agree
to let Ms. Guan check on it first?
Do you know who your superior is?
Yes, yes.
You're my superior.
Go give the photo to Ms. Guan.
Go.
Mr. Ma.
You asked my subordinate to run your errands without telling me.
Was it appropriate?
Ms. Guan.
We had an agreement.
It's all for work.
In the Secret Service,
I decide what is work
and what is a personal affair.
Stop the car.
What's wrong?
Turn around and send me back.
Are you crazy?
If Guan Xue sees that photo, you'll be in serious trouble.
I'll switch the photos.
Guan Xue probably hasn't seen the photo yet.
Hurry. There's still a chance!
Go back now, or it'll be too late!
Hello?
Fight?
Kai barely comes into conflict with anyone.
What's the reason?
I see.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
I'll come and deal with it.
What is this?
Who allowed you into my office?
Where did you get this photo?
Answer my question first.
Guan Xue, what do you want?
You want me dead after you used me?
You're still using me now!
Why are you yelling?
I quit.
Stop!
You have such a bad temper.
This photo was found in your old house.
What?
Ma is such a jerk.
He locked me up in the file room for three days
so that he could go to my hometown
to conduct a secret investigation.
It happened right under your nose.
Don't tell me you don't know about it.
It's unfair of Ma to do this.
What's wrong with a thorough check on you?
The Japanese are very meticulous.
The higher your position,
the deeper they dig into your past.
You should be grateful that they didn't
tear your house down.
I don't think it's as simple as you said.
It can't be.
Fine.
Ma and Pan Yue are very close.
They conspired against me.
Despicable!
He'll be dead if I get something on him!
Don't worry, Zhuowen.
This is my turf.
They don't dare to cross the line.
Okay.
Then, can you return this to me now?
You haven't answered my question.
Why are you in my office?
I've thought it through.
I can't give him these three gold bars,
especially not after what's happened.
I've done nothing wrong.
I don't need to do this.
Keep your trick to yourself.
I don't need it. Thank you.
Fine. Just do it your way.
Do it your way, okay?
Don't ever say you'll quit again.
Okay?
The acting chief
of the Intelligence Unit of the Secret Service
of Harbin Police Agency,
Mr. Song Zhuowen.
Mr. Song Zhuowen?
It's my turn to ask you for a favor.
Kai got into a fight.
He's been angry with me lately.
Go check on him for me.
Don't mention me.
Stop fighting!
Li Dongju, are you crazy?
Stop!
Why didn't you call the police?
Guan Kai is here. How can I call the police?
Don't you understand that?
Stop fighting! Stop!
-It's him!
-Stop!
He's the man Xie Yue has been seeing outside the school.
He's a special agent!
Are you talking about me, miss?
Wait. What does this have to do with me?
What? You don't dare admit it?
Is it because of Guan Kai?
What did I ever do to you?
She's just jealous.
Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about you!
What do you want?
Listen to me.
Go eat in the canteen
or go back to your dorms.
You, wait.
Don't go anywhere.
Go home immediately.
Answer your sister honestly after she gets back.
Don't lie to her.
Listen.
I have a way to make everyone in the school
believe that what's between us
isn't what they think it is.
Don't look at me. It's embarrassing.
That doesn't matter at all.
Can you do me a favor now?
What's it?
Take me away in front of them.
Do you dare?
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere.
Traitor! Get lost!
Stop causing us trouble at school.
Get lost! Go away!
Get lost!
Traitor! Betrayer!
Get out of our school!
Traitor!
Aunt Chang.
Come in.
Sir, you're back.
This is Miss Xie.
Aunt Chang.
Miss Xie.
She'll stay here for a few days.
Make up the storage room.
She'll sleep there.
Is there anything to eat?
There's…
No need to cook.
Anything warm will do.
Okay.
I'll leave tomorrow.
Since you're already here, forget about what happened today.
Solve tomorrow's problems tomorrow.
Hope you don't mind staying here.
Let me look.
I'm not trying to scare you.
Disinfect your wounds.
If they leave scars, it'll be hard for you to get married in the future.
Can I do anything for you?
I need to think about it.
Just don't stab me in the middle of the night.
I can't guarantee that.
Xie Yue is staying at your place.
Does Guan Xue know about it?
No.
Have you thought about
how she'll react if she finds out?
I can ask Xie Yue to move out immediately.
I just think Guan Xue won't go so far
as to interfere with my personal life at the moment.
Fine. You think this is a personal affair?
You invited a girl you don't know very well
to stay at your place
and will then ask her to leave without a reason.
Isn't that suspicious?
For people like us,
any abnormal change
will arouse people's curiosity.
And curiosity itself
means danger and disaster.
You're right. I admit I didn't think this through.
But there's really nothing
between Xie Yue and me.
I'm talking about Guan Xue.
She won't let this go.
In for a penny, in for a pound.
I might as well make Xie Yue stay
and let Guan Xue think
there's something between her and me.
Will that work?
I'll do it.
Has Song Zhuowen's appointment been officially announced?
Yes. He's now the acting chief of the Intelligence Unit.
The meeting just ended.
Ms. Guan announced it herself.
Are you upset about something?
You may leave.
Okay.
Who's it?
It's me,
Song Zhuowen.
[Chief of the Intelligence Unit, Song Zhuowen]
I wanted
to tell you about my promotion
to acting chief myself.
But someone beat me to it.
Are you here for the key?
Mr. Jin told you
I was the only one who had the key to my office.
He doesn't have a spare.
If I really wanted your position,
I could just change the lock.
To be honest,
I don't have a spare one either.
Actually, you don't want to go back to that office.
What do you mean?
Because it's too small for you.
Mr. Pan.
I'll take over your duties for now.
Get better soon.
[Chief of the Intelligence Unit, Song Zhuowen]
There must be a lot of useful information
in Pan Yue's lockers.
This is what I joined the Secret Service for.
Come in.
Here's the full personnel list of the Intelligence Unit. Please take a look.
[Personnel List of the Intelligence Unit of the Secret Service of Harbin Police Agency]
Why have I never seen
this guy called Yu Hong?
Mr. Pan decided what everyone's job was.
I don't know.
I see.
Congratulations, Zhuowen.
Mr. Hu.
You know what? It's the first time
I've taken a good look around Mr. Pan's office.
It's your first time in this office over all these years?
The Intelligence Unit is always mysterious.
So are Pan Yue and his subordinates.
It felt weird when I dealt with them.
The guy called Qiao Liang,
I'll teach him a lesson sooner or later.
He's worked for Pan Yue for a long time.
If I were him,
I'd give you the cold shoulder too.
So it's normal for me
to find one name or two unfamiliar.
I've never met them, let alone you.
They're affiliated with the Intelligence Unit,
but they've been assigned different tasks.
Others in the section call them rats.
Rats that move in the dark.
Great. I'm the head rat now.
Actually, those two guys you haven't met
don't have any specific tasks.
They just hang around the bar
at Modern Hotel all year long.
What are they doing there?
Make one for yourself.
That bar
is a secret place
where everyone goes for intel exchange.
It's neither too big
nor too small.
Everyone in Harbin who gathers intel for a living
frequents that place.
There are people from Russia, Japan, North Korea, Britain, Germany,
and even Belgium.
But most of the intel there is fake.
There's not much valuable intel.
Since everyone knows about that place,
why do the Japanese just let it be
without intervening?
Here.
Eat up.
The Japanese
turn a blind eye to it with purpose.
They're playing a long game?
You can also say it's their bait.
Harbin
is a strategic point in the Far East,
with various forces intertwined.
Take one force down, and another will emerge.
Banning those underground dealings only makes them more secretive,
making them harder to monitor.
So they might as well infiltrate their men into that place.
Who knows?
Maybe they can find something unexpected.
Zhuowen.
Can I say now
that from here on out,
we'll be Ms. Guan's right-hand men?
I'm still not capable enough.
Here.
I'll just take over Mr. Pan's duties for now.
Come here. Play for me.
You know what?
I had a straight flush
but lost to a full house. I went all in.
Really?
As long as you're still in the game, you haven't lost.
I can't believe I lost.
Sometimes, once the game starts,
you can't quit.
You're not the dealer.
If you don't want to play, find someone to take your place.
Who can take my place?
Pan Yue.
Hu Bin.
Zhuowen.
They can take turns to play for you.
But the current balance
has been disrupted by Asano Diago,
and he's the dealer.
It's a bit tricky.
I've been pondering over it recently.
Why haven't I ever won
since this dealer joined the game?
Actually,
you haven't really lost.
Asano Diago
just shook things up a bit.
He didn't kick you out of the game.
It's just that you don't know what he's up to.
I'm afraid that when I figure that out,
I'll have been bled dry.
He's not the only dealer in the world.
If this game is not fun for you,
go play another one.
I'm the dealer in the Secret Service.
I'll bleed Song Zhuowen dry too.
I gave him that position, so he has to work for me.
Zhuowen is always lucky.
Let him play for you.
I'll go play again.
Maybe I'll be lucky this time.
Move.
Don't ever be complacent.
Who are you talking about?
Me?
Am I?
Haven't you noticed that
you have intel written all over your face now?
I know. I know.
But honestly,
I've indeed gained more than I thought this time.
Pan Yue left us a treasure.
I'll find out what's valuable as soon as possible
and send it to you in batches.
We're short on time,
so you need to prioritize
and first sort out the key information
related to the fortresses of the Kwantung Army.
I understand.
Construction specifications, building materials,
garrison composition, weapons and equipment,
and supply quantities.
If we're lucky,
we can also obtain their firepower deployment diagrams.
One more thing.
You must find out the real reason
Asano Diago came to Harbin this time.
That's
too hard.
With Xie Yue and Aunt Chang at my place,
I appear to have a normal home
and be a normal man
in other people's eyes.
But for me,
I need to be wary of both those in the Secret Service
and Aunt Chang
at home.
Coming.
Who's it?
It's me.
Ms. Guan.
What happened?
So many dishes. Quite a feast.
Can you finish them all by yourself?
I'm in a good mood
because of the promotion.
So I asked Aunt Chang to make a few more dishes.
Have you had dinner?
How can you eat without wine?
Fortunately, I've brought wine with me.
You're my superior. It should be me giving you gifts.
You have a bright future.
I have to curry favor with you now.
I don't know what you want me to say.
Take a guess.
Why am I here today?
You're wearing the same clothes as you did during the day,
which is quite unusual for you.
Normally, when you drive yourself,
you'll have your car key in your hand.
It seems that you left it in the car today.
So I guess
you came here without going home or having dinner.
But you're not here for dinner.
You need to talk to me about something.
So observant.
I can't hide anything from you.
Keep guessing.
If you guess right, I'll eat with you.
If you guess wrong, you'll have to buy me two meals.
I guess it's still about the bombings.
Pan Yue is in the hospital.
Hu Bin searches the streets every day
but has made no progress.
Mr. Asano must have called to ask about it.
Take a look at the file.
Mr. Asano said
we have three more days at most
and must give him a clear answer.
I need to use the bathroom.
Don't mind me. I know this place.
You didn't let me down.
You're quick.
You've already moved in.
How do you know I'm here?
You just left the table.
The cushion was still warm.
Do you like how Song Zhuowen smells?
Smell?
I don't know how he smells.
Then hurry up and find it out.
Tell me when you have the answer.
I couldn't see your flaws in the past.
That scared me.
People who hide their flaws
usually hide their intentions and weapons.
Now that I've seen your flaw,
I'm not afraid anymore
but feel jealous instead.
I feel that I'm old now
and can't compare to that young girl.
Actually, Xie Yue…
It doesn't matter who she is.
You like her. That's all that matters.
Fine.
You really like her?
Not really.
I'll be frank with you then.
I don't like the way she looks at you.
I want to gouge her eyes out.
Can I ask you for something?
What do you want?
Just tell me yes or no.
Anything but my life.
I'm very patient.
I can wait.
But I don't have a big heart.
You'd better not upset me.
If I'm upset,
I may do anything.
Just tell me what you want.
What soap do you use?
It smells good.
I want one.
♫Silent night sky♫
♫Entangling wind; melting again♫
♫I can't find your traces♫
♫One second♫
♫Stars engulf the sky♫
♫Sleepwalking after a nap♫
♫In the fog♫
♫Your face♫
♫Silent undercurrent♫
♫Over countless mountains♫