[English subtitles are available]
[In the Name of the Brother]
[Episode 32]
Squirrel.
If anyone brings a child to the mountain lately,
find out immediately
who helped them escape
from the Water Department.
Are you here to collect wild wood ear?
No.
We only deal with leather.
Mountain goods are dealed quickly!
It's more profitable than leather goods!
My leather shop's passed down from my ancestors.
I can't change trades.
I repeat.
Tell no one about how
we broke out of the encirclement
and escaped
to the mountains.
Okay.
Hello.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's go.
Buddy.
I've something to ask you.
When did Mr. Hu come back two days ago?
It was late. I'm sure it was dark.
I want the exact time.
The residents in my building
come and go a lot.
How can I remember exactly?
Think again.
Did anything happen
or did anyone say anything?
Or did you see anyone
in the building
who comes and goes at a fixed time?
What were you doing then?
R-R-Right.
When Mr. Hu entered the gate,
I was listening to the radio.
Ganlu Temple just started playing.
Is this the daily radio program?
I want to ask
what time
Ganlu Temple was aired two days ago.
Hu Bin left home at 8:20 p.m.
The radio aired Ganlu Temple
at 9 p.m.
There were 40 minutes in between.
Ten minutes to hide the gun.
Besides waiting at the traffic light,
it's within a range of 20 km at most.
When Wu gets
the list of names and addresses
of his acquaintances,
we can start investigating.
When it involves Kai,
I can't think straight.
Isn't he your brother?
It's the same for anyone.
You can't be objective when you're emotionally invested.
It's normal.
Since the last letter from down the mountain,
we've checked several times.
But apart from
Qiao Er who Zhuowu killed,
no one else was a mole.
Looks like we've to start investigating again.
Where's the comrade from down the mountain?
Commissar Fang.
Qian.
Are you Broomstick?
Bro Qian?
You're the comrade from down the mountain?
I didn't expect to see you here.
He was a Counter-Japanese soldier!
I thought you were long gone.
I'm lucky.
Come on, sit!
You sit.
You came all the way here.
Sit now! Hurry!
Sit!
Don’t you know him?
After the Mukden incident,
the Japanese seized Manchuria.
Deng Tiemei and Miao Kexiu had been martyred.
Even someone like Cheng Bin defected.
He's a Counter-Japanese hero.
It's all in the past. Don't mention it.
You're so lucky.
Hurry, fly over here!
Wait for me!
Let me catch you!
Fly!
You too.
Come here.
The wind's direction has changed.
Almost.
Let me catch it.
Look above!
Comrades.
I'm infected by the plague spread by the Japanese.
So I'm leaving you.
Remember,
don't look for me
or touch anything I used.
Let me reiterate.
Qian Chongli and I were each other's only contact.
He risked his life to come up the mountain.
He's not idle.
It's time to find the mole.
We can't delay it any longer.
Fang, we have seven teams.
We still have to check them one by one.
Let's start with the four of us.
Bro Qian.
Let me ask you.
Some time ago,
a Song Zhuowu came from down the mountain.
Do you know?
If he hadn't violated the organization's rules,
we might have found the mole.
I was in charge of this.
I have nothing to explain.
Since I joined the organization,
I've been with the commissar.
There is a rule in intel work.
After ruling everyone out,
believe it or not,
the last one remaining...
is the traitor.
I see, Qian.
Commissar.
Let’s arrange to check the next team.
Why are you looking at me?
Are you suspecting me?
Ma Fumin, fellow townsman, No. 85 Tiandi Street.
Chen Dazhi, a friend before joining the police,
No. 152 Songjiang Street.
Wu Zi'ang, elementary school classmate,
No. 115 Liudao Street.
Fang Hongwen, fellow townsman,
Tonghe Pharmacy on Nanping Street.
Dong Xu,
No. 14 Guomin Street.
With the locations of Hu Bin's apartment
and your house,
I'm guessing the gun's hiding place
is about three km away from Hu Bin's home.
Exclude the farthest and closest places
for now.
The rest are all probable.
Among them,
find the person closest with Hu Bin.
Okay.
Who is it?
Me.
Take a look.
Do you like it?
Just say you like it.
I'm talking to my future wife.
You should leave now.
Try it on.
I'll change it if you don't like it.
Change it as many times
as you like.
Nice.
On December 26, 1931,
General Deng Tiemei led the Self-Defense Army
to split into four groups
and counter-attacked Fengcheng.
You were right in the front line.
Yes.
Later, the Self-Defense Army joined the Counter-Japanese Army.
You followed Commander Yang Jingyu
to fight in Sanyuanpu
and Liangshuihezi.
You even earned merits.
Yes.
Later, Cheng Bin defected
and took so many people away,
but you didn't follow them.
The Japanese have occupied Manchuria for 14 years.
You've been working with them for 14 years.
This is who you are.
How could you be a Han traitor?
I'm not a Han traitor.
I'm not even a Han.
How am I a Han traitor?
Manchuria's my hometown.
First Zhang Zuolin,
then the Japanese
and you communists;
all of you
want to occupy my hometown!
Shut up!
Was Deng Tiemei a Manchu?
Was Advisor Miao a Manchu?
Yes!
Unfortunately, they forgot they were.
I'm different.
I work for His Majesty.
If the Japanese trouble His Majesty,
I'll kill them.
If you trouble His Majesty...
I'll kill you.
Fang and I are from
the Second Division of the Fifth Counter-Japanese Army.
Under
Commander Chen Hanzhang.
In December, 1940,
Commander Chen
was surrounded by the Japanese
by Jingpo Lake.
When he was still alive,
they dugged his eyes out
and cut his tongue.
But he stayed silent.
He'd just turned 28 years old.
Commander Chen never ate dog meat
or wore dog-skin hats.
He said that's the Manchu rule.
Right?
Be it Commander Chen,
General Deng,
or Advisor Miao,
when they fought the Japanese,
they never differentiated Manchus and Hans.
They only knew they were...
Chinese.
Tell me. Are you Chinese?
Are you?
I am.
If you're not a Han traitor,
what are you?
Just because the Japanese troubled you?
Do you still have a hometown?
Where is it?
Tell me where your hometown is.
The Japanese seized your land.
They killed all your townsmen,
raped the women,
and didn't even spare the kids!
Just because they troubled you?
You bastard!
Let me ask you one thing.
Are you Chinese?
Speak up!
I am.
Then you are a national traitor!
Han traitor!
You lied to me.
You've been lying to me!
Commissar.
I was wrong.
Keep him alive?
I used to be in the Manchukuo Army.
What did you do before joining the Counter-Japanese Army?
What are you looking at?
Stop pretending.
Others don't know my background,
but you do.
I used to be a robber.
But I only robbed the rich and helped the poor.
I never burgled.
Yes, an old ex-warlord
and an ex-robber
both became communists.
Stop flattering yourself.
A warlord?
You were just a soldier.
Yes, a soldier.
A soldier.
Do you remember
what Commander Chen told us?
No matter who you are,
if you join the revolution,
follow the rules, fight the Japanese,
and change your past habits,
you're a comrade.
But Miao Changshou's different.
He's a Han traitor.
Is he really a Han traitor?
He did betray us.
But he also used to fight the Japanese.
All these years,
there have been diehard Counter-Japanese fighters
and hardcore traitors,
but most of them were in between.
The point is, Miao's not alone.
He's backed by Harbin's Secret Service
and Guan Xue.
That's our most dangerous enemy.
You're right.
All the more can't we kill him.
Germany and Italy surrendered.
Japan and Manchukuo should be
on their last legs too.
And then?
We have to think about the future.
Miao Changshou has a vast intel network.
Instead of waiting for the day of victory
to investigate
and arrest them,
you might as well make him
spill the beans now.
Dong Xu is Hu Bin's closest cousin.
It's most likely Hu Bin hid the gun in his house.
Who is it?
Dong Xu?
Yes I am. Who are you?
Did I offend you?
Did you forget
what you did?
Listen.
Don't touch me.
My cousin works for Harbin's police.
Have you heard of Hu Bin?
Hu Bin!
We came because of him.
Where did you hide it?
Hide w-what?
Sir!
One segment for one question.
Keep staying silent and you'll be fingerless.
Let me speak!
Where is it?
What is it? Please explain.
What do I have?
Wu.
Don’t waste time on him.
Where's the gun Hu Bin gave you?
What gun?
When did it happen?
Two nights ago.
Two...
Two nights ago,
I was on the train back to Harbin.
Really, sir.
I've been away for more than half a year. I just came back.
Ask around the business world.
I'm telling the truth!
I promise!
Wu.
Come here.
Search him.
Yes.
We've got the wrong person.
It's not him.
If he's involved,
he wouldn't have named Hu Bin from the get-go.
The train ticket he has on him.
[From Hsinking to Harbin]
Retreat.
Yes.
Let's go.
Hello.
Did you find it?
We got the wrong person.
What do you mean?
Don't worry. Tonight,
we'll check all the surrounding people
on the map again.
I'll let you and Xue know if there's any progress.
How can she sleep now?
Does Xue really want to get married?
Regardless,
we have to find the gun and bullet first.
Hello.
I'm looking for Ms. Guan.
You must be her brother.
Hello.
You must apologize to me.
It’s such a big deal.
Why did I just receive Hu Bin's invitation?
Where's your invitation?
Sorry.
I cleared tomorrow's schedule
to attend your wedding.
Thank you, Mr. Asano.
Yes.
Xue.
Don't talk.
-Let me go!
-Behave!
Don't move or I'll kill you!
Officer, what's wrong?
I didn't do anything wrong.
-Move!
-I didn't do...
Where's the gun?
What gun? I really don't know.
Think again! Where's the gun?
I really don't know about a gun.
Officer, I really don't.
I really don't know!
I didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't.
Nothing.
Confessions come out of torture, you know?
It doesn't matter where the gun is,
or if he has the gun.
As long as he confesses,
our job's done.
We really don't have any guns.
We really don't know what you are
talking about.
No!
Please let us go.
We really don't.
Everyone's afraid of pain and death.
Go.
Do it.
-Guys, come on.
-We really don’t know.
We really don't know about the gun.
-What are you doing?
-We really don't know!
Move!
-We really don't!
-Let her go!
Let her go!
Lian!
Hello.
Hello?
Say something.
You have to sleep no matter how happy you are.
Your throat's all hoarse.
Have some breakfast.
There's still time.
I'll pick you up later.
Once you're in your wedding gown,
we'll go straight to the church.
I'll just see you at the church.
Wait for me at the church.
Congratulations on the wedding, Ms. Guan.
-Happy wedding day!
-Congratulations!
Congratulations.
You look so beautiful.
So beautiful, Ms. Guan.
Happy wedding!
Asano Daigo's inside.
She's so pretty today.
Ms. Guan.
Very beautiful.
Beautiful!
You look great.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Where's Hu Bin?
Not with the bride?
According to the time,
this is the farthest he could've come.
We've searched all of Hu Bin's acquaintances.
I see.
We're going in the wrong direction.
Where's the safest place in Harbin?
The safest?
Where the Japanese are at?
Let's check Japanese-owned hotels and inns.
Thank you.
The priest said we can start.
What's the rush? Hang on.
Okay.
Ten more minutes at most.
I've calculated.
It's inauspicious after this hour.
Welcome.
I can't.
We're obligated to protect our clients' confidentiality.
Listen.
We're from the police.
I can't.
This is a business owned by
Mr. Yamazaki, the South Manchuria Railway's president.
Can you speak Chinese?
If you need,
please ask the Police's Deputy Director Liu...
Stop.
Can you speak Chinese? I don't understand.
I can't...
I don't understand!
Please ask the Police's Deputy Director Liu
to call Mr. Yamazaki directly!
Leave now.
Why don't we play hardball?
We're running out of time.
It's a Japanese territory
owned by someone from South Manchuria Railway.
We can't meddle with that.
Mr. Hu Bin.
Are you willing to marry Ms. Guan Xue
as your wife?
I do.
Ms. Guan Xue.
Are you willing to marry Mr. Hu Bin
and be his wife?
Wait!
Found it.
In Yamato Inn.
Hu Bin.
I won't marry anyone.
So don't feel wronged.
There are many women in Harbin.
Find a good one and bring her to me.
No man can marry me.
♫Silent night sky♫
♫Entangling wind; melting again♫
♫I can't find your traces♫
♫One second♫
♫Stars engulf the sky♫
♫Sleepwalking after a nap♫
♫In the fog♫
♫Your face♫
♫Silent undercurrent♫
♫Over countless mountains♫
♫Your lone courage to traverse the turbid waves♫
♫I understand♫
♫More touching hugs♫
♫Calmer impulses♫
♫In a state of confusion♫
♫Your original aspiration♫
♫Who can grasp it?♫