[English subtitles are available]
[In the Name of the Brother]
[Episode 37]
Have you been to Chongqing?
No.
But I heard it's mountainous
and very hot in summer.
It's not for Manchus.
But Chongqing hot pot
is addictive.
Do you think Jiang will stay in Chongqing
and not go back to Nanjing
if the Japanese lose?
Nanjing, Yan'an, Chongqing;
they're all too far now.
Hiking and sweating's better than
living in a cave eating potatoes.
Got it?
Yes.
If you need me to explore the way,
just tell me.
Two options.
Which one should I explore?
I don't think you want to take either.
This way.
Do you know why I brought you here
to feed pigeons?
You have an informant.
You deliver intel with pigeons.
His code name is Squirrel, yeah?
Honestly,
it's quite old-school.
Go to Hsinking with me.
Then to Japan.
Ms. Guan.
That's confusing me.
How could it be me?
Are you really gonna go all the way?
Do you remember me?
Maruta.
[No. 26, Harbin City]
Don't you wanna know who I am?
At worst, you're here to kill me.
I don't need to know who you are.
I shouldn't have disturbed you
at this time.
I know your son,
Long Xinliang.
A National University student
dating a Japanese girl
Junko.
Yes.
I gave him a lot of pocket money on the day he went missing.
I think he went on a date.
One of my friends saw
your son die...
in the hands of the Japanese.
So many people told me this.
So what if I believe it
or not?
His son is your daughter's boyfriend.
This is my daughter.
Where is she?
You need to ask the Police's Secret Service
or the Military Police.
Answer my question first.
Director Long.
Go ask him.
He was in the Water Department.
He saw how your son died.
You're Japanese.
Maruta.
All of you are Marutas!
Your son's a Maruta.
You too!
Even a fool knows
the chicken and egg question
is stupid.
Listen carefully. The ceramic I develop
will be the germ bombs' carrier.
It requires much experimenting.
Of course, we also need healthy Marutas.
But you can't guarantee the Maruta supply.
What are you doing?
Marutas escaping,
leaked intel,
and stopping me from doing experiments.
It means you're worse than a fool.
I don't understand
why General Ishii put you in charge
of the security of the Water Department.
I'll be frank.
Dr. Kojima.
I'm sure you know the war's situation better than I do.
To be honest,
my human, material and financial resources
have been greatly reduced.
That's why...
if the security isn't foolproof,
all your experiments
will be in vain.
If this is why you are
halting the research and production of ceramic bombs,
please explain it to General Ishii.
Dr. Kojima.
You should know
we are all soldiers of the empire.
We are!
Shut up!
I'm not a soldier.
I'm a scientist!
I'm only interested in my experiments.
All I care about are my experiments,
experiment materials,
the quantity of Marutas,
rats, and fleas.
It takes time to reproduce bugs.
No one can be forgiven
for stealing my time!
Don't you want Ishii to take you back to Japan?
Then shut up
and do your job!
I'm very busy.
Tell me.
What do you want me to do?
Director Long.
We all know
you're the secretary-general of University of Tokyo's Harbin alumni.
We have a list of alumni.
We are very interested
in one person.
[Kojima Shigetomo]
You sure know how to pick.
Our alumni association
has a long history.
Many people come and go.
I've only seen Dr. Kojima
once or twice.
I don't even know what he does.
I'll tell you what he does.
He's the chief scientist
of the Japanese Water Department,
where your son died.
What do you want from me?
Charge into the Water Department
to kill him?
Who said that?
Just find a way
to ask him out.
He won't come.
Unless someone else asks.
Who?
Minister of Transport,
Okazaki.
Isn't it ridiculous?
The war's at our doorstep,
but the Harbin alumni of University of Tokyo
are gathering two days later.
It'll be a mess
with all kinds of people.
Mr. Asano's assigned us
to do office work.
Do they really think we're idle?
If I remember right,
we're also in charge of
evacuating the first batch
of Japanese experts
from Harbin to Hsinking in three days.
That's why I say the Japanese are absurd.
It's their escape plan.
Can't you see?
They're acting like things
are lively and peaceful
before that.
I don't have time for what you said.
I can't think straight.
I think we should change our plan.
Mr. Hu, it's your turn.
Jin.
In three days,
I plan to only take Hu Bin away.
Got it.
It's also part of Operations' job.
Let's go in.
Mr. Song, look ahead.
Mr. Song.
It's a rare opportunity.
Let's take a group photo.
Have a seat.
Hu Bin, sit here.
My cap.
Sit properly.
Don't squeeze.
Hunch down.
Here.
Should I drink this or not?
Are you also a communist?
Think bigger.
Kuomintang?
Within two years,
I'll be the director of Fengtian Police Bureau.
Pan.
Good for you.
You're such an ingrate.
If you're the director,
what about me and Ms. Guan?
Director of Kuomintang's Shenyang Police Bureau,
Pan Yue.
Ms. Guan might not even
keep her life.
When the Japanese run away
and Kuomintang returns,
she'll only suffer.
And you.
You have...
taken many lives,
so Kuomintang's Secret Service will let you go.
Of course, I'll speak up for you then.
But you have to have the ability.
I'm afraid
my words aren't enough.
That's too far.
I always rely on my ability.
No matter how many chefs change,
they still have to light the fire.
Then I'll help you boost your resume.
For the alumni reunion at Sakura Hall,
Song Zhuowen would make a move.
If you find anything strange at the scene,
don't take action.
Push him out first.
Mr. Asano stationed me there
with my men.
Ding Peng will be waiting outside.
It's a deal then.
If we really catch him,
his intel will be yours
and he'll be mine.
Don't interfere with how I deal with him.
Skin him alive for all I care.
But leave him
his last breath.
[Harbin Police Agency]
Mr. Jin.
[Chang Yuming, Female, Communication Unit Chief]
Why didn't you give Aunt Chang more?
There's so much left.
Aren't you afraid she'll flee with the money?
No one can stand the test
of money.
Is the gunman reliable?
Do you remember Yu Hong?
He has been in prison.
A few years ago,
he fought the Japanese with Xie Wendong.
After they disbanded,
you recruited him.
Two years ago,
he drunkenly killed a Japanese.
You asked someone to protect him
from the death sentence.
His position
in the Intelligence Unit still exists
and he still receives salary.
Isn't Pan Yue
taking care of his family?
What if they run into each other?
Don't think too much now.
There are 12 individual photos
of the special agents.
Ten of them and other special staff
are for the Japanese.
That one's for Yu Hong.
The rest are the group photos you want.
Where's the gun I asked for?
Belgian Browning.
Just like Pan Yue's.
Close the door.
Why are you acting like a thief?
Ms. Guan
has an uncle in Harbin.
Do you know about this?
When I was checking backgrounds in Japan,
Guan Xue's mentioned it.
Didn't he die later?
No.
No?
Isn't it better if he's dead?
This is...
This is Ms. Guan's uncle.
I heard they're close.
After his accident,
Ms. Guan's been paying
for all medical expenses
and visits him often.
You know
how cautious Ms. Guan is.
Besides going to the office,
going home,
and working outside,
she seldom goes out.
But she often goes to this nursing home.
He's an expert.
What?
I said the shooter's an expert.
Seven shots in total.
All hit the target.
But he avoided
the vital areas, the brain and the heart.
He wanted to make him suffer.
Must be a huge grudge.
Sober up.
The shooter's
your beloved Guan Xue.
Jin helped her suppress this.
One more tidbit.
The nursing home said
last month, an expert
who returned from Japan told Ms. Guan
that a surgery
could help her uncle stand again,
but she rejected it at once.
I got it.
Guan Xue
must've been assaulted by her uncle.
Mr. Hu.
I'm not telling you this
as gossip
because I'm free.
If a woman
has such a big burden in her heart,
how can there be a place for you?
Search every guest
for weapons tomorrow,
including the Japanese.
Yes.
Search.
Cheers!
Kojima!
Long time no see.
I missed you.
Teng.
Mr. Hu.
Did you check the cabinet?
No.
Check it.
Yes.
If all goes according to my schedule
and my route,
I can successfully
get Dr. Kojima out
and pass him to Zhuowu at the back door.
It's going too well.
It's unbelievable.
Out of the many kidnapping plans for Kojima,
this is the most reasonable one
with the highest success rate.
From the agents
being arrested in Hulan
to Director Long
suddenly saying Kojima will show up,
isn't it all too smooth?
It's as if the alumni
are your underlings,
following your schedule
and escape route.
Kojima will finally
appear at the spot you confirmed
and surrender?
You're right.
But I'll set the time
of the explosion in advance.
At the exact time.
During an explosion,
everyone only thinks of escape.
Kojima's no exception.
I'm just worried
someone will see me placing the bomb.
Hu Bin's eyes
are sharper than eagles.
Director Long's suddenly holding an alumni reunion.
Won't Guan Xue question it?
Qian.
I've thought about all that.
But at this critical moment,
we'll have to take a bet.
So what if we're exposed?
I beg you.
The Japanese will be defeated.
I'd hate for
a comrade to be killed!
Qian.
If so,
it'll be my turn.
You've switched them?
I asked everyone
to hand in their guns for an operation today.
Pan Yue agreed without a thought.
I'm drinking with him tonight.
Why?
Something might happen at Sakura Hall.
He wants to get drunk
and ignore it.
Got it.
Has Yu Hong arrived?
Yes.
Right across Sakura Hall.
Okay.
[Sakura Hall]
For the alumni reunion at Sakura Hall,
Song Zhuowen would make a move.
If we really catch him,
his intel will be yours
and he'll be mine.
Skin him alive for all I care.
Dr. Kojima.
You really came.
I'm not here for the reunion.
Do you know
the University of Tokyo
has nothing to do with me?
We even made a bet
if you'd show up for my sake.
You can't watch me lose money.
Long.
This is Dr. Kojima.
Welcome.
I happened to see your name on the list.
I heard you were in Harbin.
So I called you here
to get together.
Welcome.
I really came here for you.
I heard
you're promoted to Minister of Transport.
Congratulations.
No.
It's a hard job.
Don't complain.
I came here today
to ask for a favor.
Is it also about transport?
No.
Why'd I come to the Minister of Transport?
As you can see,
we just launched the Tonghua Defense Plan,
where everyone
will move to Tonghua.
The Russians are really coming.
My friend in China said
the war is getting worse.
I'm afraid Okinawa can't be defended either.
Before the last moment,
every soldier of the empire will not give up.
During the General Staff meeting,
everyone was very depressed.
Only...
General Ishii
was full of fighting spirit and confidence.
His attitude
must be related to your research.
Of course.
Thank you, Peng.
Peng.
Keep watch.
Don't worry.
Come on, let's drink.