[English subtitles are available]
[In the Name of the Brother]
[Episode 15]
Aunt Chang, I'll get it.
Have you been waiting for my call?
You got the money?
You're indeed a special agent.
A bait with 500 yuan.
Clever, Mr. Song.
If you catch me today,
you'll kill me, right?
You've got what you want.
Why are you still following me?
You want more money?
Is the great Song Zhuowen
only worth 500 yuan?
That just proved your sincerity.
So now
we can start doing business.
Tell me.
I want ten gold bars.
Don't worry. This is it.
Once I get the money,
I won't contact you again.
I don't have that much money on hand.
I need time.
Three days
are the most I can allow you.
Hell yeah!
Sir, are you
looking to stay?
It's cold in the mountains.
Is the quilt thick enough?
Yes, it's 9 lb.
Freshly-spun cotton.
A dog skin mattress under it.
Is the food and accommodation expensive?
No.
Just some simple fare.
We built the place ourselves.
You can pay as you deem fit.
What food do you have?
Roe deer, wood ears, mushrooms,
and chickens we raise.
Any wine?
An eccentric one?
He has a weapon on his waist.
If he's looking for lodging at this time,
he mustn't be a good guy.
A bandit or this?
I don't care.
Let's take him down first.
Sir, the food's ready.
Wine.
Enjoy.
Wait.
Try it.
What are you waiting for? Eat up.
What? You don't like your cooking?
Or are you snubbing me?
No way.
Hurry, thank him.
Thank you, sir.
Enjoy.
Manager.
Where are you from?
Suihua.
47 miles away from here.
How does such a remote restaurant
make money?
Ginseng diggers, herbalists,
beekeepers,
and leatherworkers
enter the mountain when it's warm.
Sir, what do you do?
What do you think?
Looking at your outfit,
are you a mountain forager?
You have to have money to do that.
I use my brains to do business
without capital.
Please enjoy.
I still miscalculated after all.
Didn't you eat the food?
Why are you fine?
Let me show you.
Your chopsticks are modified.
There are small holes on it,
where I put the medicine
that's sealed with deer oil.
It melts with steam
and goes into the food.
How is it?
Didn't see it coming, did you?
Sir?
I...
Come on.
Now tell me
who's the sir?
Come on, say it!
Call me sir!
Fatty.
Mountain foragers have it hard indeed.
Tell me.
What do you do?
I've already told you.
You don't believe it?
A bandit?
You do look the part.
Maybe in the past.
But not anymore.
Looking for Counter-Japanese soldiers
in the mountains?
Counter-Japanese soldiers?
Otherwise, why's your luggage empty?
Make it clear.
Uphill or downhill,
let's all go
our own way.
If you don't make it clear...
I'll tell you.
At this point,
I might as well tell you.
But I have a condition.
It's simple.
It's nothing.
Say it.
Kneel
and kowtow to me.
Loudly.
How dare you...
Yes.
Lower.
Pry it open.
The iron box behind the wall.
Take all the money.
Don't leave a cent.
I don't want the money.
I want the radio.
I run an inn.
There's no radio.
Keep lying to me
and I'll off you. Try me.
How can I have a radio here?
No.
There were three people here.
You sent the accountant to Harbin a few days ago
to contact a special agent.
But he didn't make it back.
Am I right?
Do you really think you're
the Yama of the mountains?
You stole these
from people who went up the mountain, yeah?
Do me another favor.
Keep an eye on someone for me.
He's Quan, a worker in my shop.
He's been out for a long time.
Until today,
he hasn't written back to his family.
How old is he?
He's already in puberty.
But he still wears his childhood necklace.
Where's this kid?
It wasn't me, but the cook.
That kid was too smart.
He caught the cook
swindling a mountain forager,
so the cook silenced him.
Was his name Quan?
How did you know?
I'll really kill you today.
Don't test me!
Go meet Yama.
I don't know. I really don't!
Who is the mole in the Counter-Japanese Army?
I'll let you meet Yama today!
The accountant's dead too.
If you don't want to live, don't say anything.
I'll kill you today.
What are you doing?
I'll tell you!
The radio...
-The radio is...
-Speak up!
The radio's in the shabby shed in the forest.
But I've really never seen the mole.
I only go to get intel.
All I know is...
the...
the next transaction time.
Tell me!
Tomorrow night.
In our plan to leave the city,
your brother replaced the car plate.
Our men were watching the coal yard's entrance
and the gaps in the coal piles.
Just in case.
No one could've seen Zhuowu
replacing the car plate.
So that guy's lying.
He's cheating me.
Try to recall
who else saw you that day.
Other than the sentries guarding the bridge,
no one else.
So I'm definitely safe.
Don't worry.
We'll wait one more day.
If you still can't find the blackmailer,
leave immediately.
Qian.
Can you trust my judgment this time?
Give me more time.
No.
This is not a gamble.
You have no right to bet your life.
Three days.
No.
Just three days!
No way.
Evacuate if there's even a hint of exposure.
That's our policy.
Fine. One day then.
The tea's ready.
I'll pass.
Just two days' time.
Where should I go
to find all the sentries?
It might be more dangerous to go to them.
But there's no other way.
Because
I'm selfless,
I didn't keep the reward for myself.
I called you here
just to
remind you,
if you encounter a similar situation,
don't be a coward.
Just follow the rules.
Yes, don't be a coward.
Then maybe you can get a reward too.
Sure.
Let me tell you
what he looks like.
A high nose,
long eyes,
in a gray suit, white shirt,
and a purple tie.
Another incognito inspection?
Have you met me?
No, but I've heard of you.
You're from the Secret Service.
Ms. Guan was with you last time.
Do you have cigarettes?
Yes. Here.
Who said that?
Well,
Cui Anping.
Lighter.
I don't have it.
Cigs but no lighter?
Who said that?
Cui Anping.
That bastard.
I remember him,
the one on duty last time.
What did he say?
To think he remembers me.
That stingy scrooge
actually invited
all his peers on duty that day for drinks.
It's conceivable that
it was just to brag.
But explaining the details of how I look
and inquiring if I were
at other checkpoints
means he has an ulterior motive.
Above all,
Cui Anping did two shifts that afternoon.
If he saw two cars leaving the city successively,
we're screwed.
Time to change shifts.
Guns down.
On the dot.
Come on.
Get ready to change shifts.
How many dishes will your wife cook for you tonight?
Change shifts.
He came again this afternoon.
Who?
Who else?
You were right.
The Secret Service's
taking it seriously.
A routine check every few days.
Even re-inspections.
I wasn't as lucky as you.
No rewards this time.
Was it a man or a woman?
A man.
He didn't drive this time.
What did you two talk about?
I...
Just some small chat.
What can people like me talk about?
What we talked about over dinner
last time.
March!
Where are you going?
Hello, who is it?
I’m Cui Anping.
What’s up?
Let me buy you a meal.
That won't do.
My treat.
When?
8 p.m. tonight.
Private Room 6, second floor, Juxian Building.
Will you come?
I won't miss it.
As I expected,
me showing up at the checkpoint
worked.
No matter what,
I must meet Cui Anping.
Stop whining
or I'll kill you.
[Investigate: Tian Xiaojiang, Yue Baocheng, Tian Geng, Song Zhuowen]
Who are you?
Sir, this way, please.
Sir, it's here.
This way, please.
Welcome, Sir!
We're different from you.
We're just soldiers.
But it's our blessing
to know Mr. Song.
Right?
Yes.
Please look after us in the future.
I'm not good with words.
Come on.
Cheers.
Sure! Cheers!
You flatter me, Mr. Cui.
I just do
as my superiors say,
just like you.
You're too modest.
Everyone in this line of work
knows you are
a hotshot secret agent.
Right?
Yes.
Mr. Cui is really thoughtful.
You inquired a lot about me.
You are my benefactor
and lucky star.
Rather,
I'm curious about Ms. Guan.
But who am I to talk to her?
Why don't I introduce you to her?
No, no, no.
Knowing you
is my greatest blessing.
I can't afford
to have too much good in my life.
We've never interacted in the past.
Mr. Cui's indeed an honest man.
Now, we're officially acquainted.
With time,
our friendship will surely last.
Yes, come on, cheers.
Here.
Sir.
Eat up.
Okay.
Wen.
I have something to ask you.
After you and Ms. Guan just left that day,
you came right back and left the city
urgently.
I was wondering
if something big happened.
I have no filter when I'm drunk.
I know. Military secret.
It's confidential.
I'll drink as punishment.
You guys too.
What Mr. Song and I talked about
is confidential.
Yes.
In one ear and out the other.
If word about the Secret Service's affairs gets out,
you'll have to die.
Understand?
Yes.
They're tight-lipped.
Come on. Cheers.
Cui Anping's really something,
using this trick to let everyone know.
Come on.
If these sentries
get the word out,
the fact that I have a twin
will be exposed.
I'll propose another toast.
Let's wish Mr. Song peace, safety,
and a prosperous career!
A prosperous career.
Cheers!
Sir, I'm sorry.
I'm looking for Ms. Guan.
We don't...
She called me over.
My surname's Song.
Okay.
A moment, please.
Mr. Song.
This way, please.
I can't dance.
Are you stalking me?
I dare not.
I don't know
who else to discuss this with.
So I came to you.
It's urgent.
Someone called to blackmail me.
For what?
He accused me of communist ties.
Why?
I don't know.
I don't even know who he is.
Who do you think
he is?
Who do you think he is?
Someone called me to tip me off
about the Communist Party.
He wanted to sell the intel,
so he was vague about it.
Did you agree to pay for it?
You can
steal from me or rob me,
but you can't blackmail me.
Do you really think
he's just after money?
Anyway, as a special agent,
someone stealing from you,
robbing you,
or blackmailing you
is no big deal.
I'll get back to dancing.
You two are twins.
Come on!
You ruined the plan, you know?
What's wrong with getting rid of the mole?
We've been keeping up
with Qiao Er's movements.
We left him alone all this time
to get to the more dangerous mole
through him.
On the first day you came up here,
I emphasized on discipline
and obeying command.
Why did you act on your own?
Qiao Er's a mole anyway.
Getting rid of him
gives you a peace of mind.
If you suspect
he's the mole, just report it.
Why did you kill him?
Now
all our leads are gone.
I have no idea what Qian told you
before you came up the mountain.
Comrades from the city
just take us as fools.