[English subtitles are available]
[In the Name of the Brother]
[Episode 25]
Mr. Li.
Mr. Li!
Something bothering you?
Not really.
Just a bit disappointed.
I came all the way here
just to return in vain.
Mr. Li.
Who exactly are you?
With all due respect,
you don't know how to write the cursive script.
No.
You can't write calligraphy at all,
right?
You guessed right.
I'm Intelligence Unit Chief, Song Zhuowen.
Mr. Li Cunliang
was injured in an assassination in Harbin,
so I had to come instead.
I still have a question.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry for staining your shirt.
But when I told the orderly
to wash it immediately,
do you recall how you reacted?
Stop it!
I'll do it myself.
Didn't you notice your invisible ink's missing?
I have it.
Save the explanations.
When we return to Harbin,
Mr. Asano will tell us what this is.
Don't move! Let him go!
Don't move!
Turn around!
Fly to Harbin!
Tell me who you are!
Turn around!
I'm still worth using.
We are all worthless.
No one can go back.
Song Zhuowen's death
means nothing to me!
It's your business to mourn him!
Go back to your office
or home!
Go cry and drink
and burn your Manchurian incense!
He's an outstanding person.
You said it yourself!
An outstanding person
should die for his faith.
That's the spirit of a warrior!
From the day he chose this job,
he'd already known
he could die anytime.
Song Zhuowen has faith.
Although he failed his mission
and didn't catch the mole!
Have you considered...
who should take up his position?
Is it so urgent?
Of course!
The Secret Service can't go a day
without the Intelligence Unit Chief.
I'll make arrangements now.
Sorry to disturb you.
Write a report to the Army Headquarters.
Dongning Fortress is no longer safe.
Cut off all its connections with the outside world
as soon as possible.
Like a lizard cutting off its tail.
I have another opinion.
What?
The plane accident
was not due to bad weather
or a mechanical malfunction.
Since the higher-ups think so,
let's not create more trouble.
Humans...
really can't defy fate.
Who would've thought
the heavens would take Song Zhuowen away?
It saved us a lot of trouble.
Here.
Put this on.
This feels like a special occasion.
So, buddy,
isn't it time you come back to work?
Only if Guan Xue comes to beg me sincerely.
Has she visited you once in the hospital?
No.
So I need either her or Mr. Asano
to come and beg me.
Don't be ridiculous.
Quit while you're ahead.
But I've not witnessed his death
myself.
Nobody has seen
Zhuowen's corpse with their own eyes.
What if he rises from the ashes?
Take that back!
Keep calm.
Wait a little more.
Here.
The latest news I got at noon
said the plane
crashed.
A Japanese search and rescue team
found it.
Because you're his brother
and his only family,
if there's anything you need,
we'll try our best to satisfy them.
Don't resent the organization.
Because back then...
When the organization
sent Zhuowen for this mission,
no one expected such a thing to happen.
I'm devastated by Zhuowen's sacrifice too!
There are also kids
younger than Zhuowen.
All of them, I...
I watched them grow up.
I watched them fall
and grow up.
And then they died one by one
in front of me.
Whenever I spend
even just
a few months
with some young kid,
it's as if I've known them
for a lifetime.
Enough, Qian.
You can't do anything.
I did do nothing.
Back then, I was the dumbest in our team.
Before Secretary Luo was arrested,
he put me in charge.
Many comrades questioned it.
How can he be in charge?
He says he can do anything
but fails at everything.
Who'd wanna entrust their life to him?
They all said that about me.
But I think they're right.
Later, Luo said this to them,
that as a member
of an underground party,
it's not about how strong you are,
but how long you can live.
How can one live long?
By abiding by the rules.
I disagree.
I think about
how to let the enemy die before us.
Yes.
Zhuowu, you don't know this,
but...
there are about a dozen of us old folks from Manchukuo
who are all considered as capable.
But they all died.
I'm the only one left.
So, I brought young people in.
One batch
after another...
Now it's Zhuowen.
In the end, all of them died.
I'm the only one left again.
Do you know
how that feels?
This life is worse than death.
But I have to persist.
I have to.
Enough.
Persist?
No wonder you live longer than them.
Qian, don't worry.
My brother won't die easily.
When we were young, the fortune teller said he was tough.
He can't be dead.
This is my oath.
First,
fight for communism for life.
Second,
put the Party's interests above all else.
Third,
abide by the Party's rules.
Four,
never fear difficulties and always work for the Party.
Five,
be a role model to everyone.
Six,
keep the Party's secrets.
Seven,
have faith in the Party.
Eight,
be undaunted
and forever loyal to the Party.
Yours sincerely,
Song Zhuowu.
Stop crying.
Hold it in.
He was just a tool.
Why are you crying?
If it weren't for Wen,
we would've died twice!
Fates are predestined!
It only proves I shouldn't die.
Xue!
Stop being so inhumane!
Sit down.
Let's eat.
Sit down and eat!
Kai.
Life's short.
Don't be swayed by emotions,
or you'll be controlled...
-Enough!
-You...
I, Guan Kai,
your brother,
am a stumbling block
who hinders your future!
Who is it?
Me!
Why are you here at this hour?
Something urgent!
The munitions warehouse was burgled?
We lost a lot of explosives.
It's enough to blow up the Police building.
Let Public Security take care of it.
Let's handle Zhuowen's funeral first.
This is your urgent matter?
You're right.
This is my urgent matter.
You...
Hu Bin!
Don't move.
Why don't you point the gun at me?
It's fine if you insist.
Now you know I'm not to be messed with.
Touch me after I die.
If you kill me now,
you'll be in big trouble.
Song Zhuowen's dead.
Dead, you know?
It'll still never be your turn.
Hu Bin.
People hold grudges and forget acts of kindness.
I've been hard on you all these years.
I knew you'd do this someday.
I'm not a fool.
You're not.
I'm the fool.
How many times have I told you?
There's no shortcut here.
If you can't fly to the sky,
just crawl earnestly.
Don't worry about my situation.
Let's pretend this never happened.
You have until dawn to move on,
or I'll cut ties with you.
Prepare for Zhuowen's funeral.
Go.
You'll not realize your folly until the worst has happened.
I saw Hu Bin at the door.
Our organization in Fengtian
was severely destroyed by the Japanese and Manchukuo Secret Services.
Many comrades were arrested.
That line's concealed for now.
So we...
What do you mean by this?
Qian, leave me alone.
I can't be bothered about rules now.
As you said,
I've worked with you for only a few months,
not even a year.
I have to avenge Zhuowen no matter what.
Or it might be too late.
Are you the only one who wants revenge?
Is this your own grudge?
Does our grudge against the Japanese
and the grudge the 40 million Chinese hold
not count?
Does only your grudge count?
They have you.
Qian.
You're the most capable.
That's why you live long.
I'll avenge my brother,
and you can do so for the 40 million people.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you determined to defy the organization
and do this?
Qian, don't pressure me with the organization!
I'm Zhuowu!
Look carefully!
I'm not Zhuowen!
I only have one brother.
You still have a son.
Imagine if I used the organization
to pressure you when your son's dead!
My son's dead.
Really?
We were on a mission.
It involved Zhuowen's safety.
They just told me.
I was the last to know.
[Desheng Gate]
Don't move!
Let go of me!
The enemy's raid this time is especially intense.
Be extra careful.
Once you get in contact
with comrades in Harbin,
get them to build a new transport line.
Xia.
Rest assured.
I'm not a rookie on my first mission.
I'll be careful.
Our comrades who are exposed in Fengtian
will evacuate through the new transport line.
Remember,
at 3 p.m. on the 12th of next month,
I'll wait for him at the teahouse on the west of Minfu Street
in Harbin.
I got it.
Three p.m. on the 12th of next month.
Teahouse on the west of Minfu Street in Harbin.
Your new identity.
[He Guoxiu]
[Harbin Station]
Next time, I'll ask Xia
to let you act as a teacher.
We can meet outside.
I'll treat you to a nice meal.
A teacher's boring.
If I get to choose, I'd like to be an opera actor.
I’m a die-hard opera fan.
I can play the role well.
I'm sitting on the city tower.
It's too flamboyant. Sit down.
I love it.
Yes.
I'll build a new transport line right away
so we can initiate it.
The streets are filled with spies these days.
Be careful. Don't leave the inn for no reason.
Harbin's just as intense as Fengtian.
I'll just stay in the inn.
Until the day of contact.
There are other comrades in this contact.
Here.
I'll ask Xia Tao to get another box of desserts
to facilitate the contact.
Everything about Dongning Fortress and Unit 731
has been deeply engraved in my mind.
What I need to do now
is to report everything I know
to the organization as soon as possible.
Is Xia Tao exposed?
We've even met?
No. Just in case, he's retreating to the mountains
with a few underground party members
from Fengtian
by following the new transport line
through Harbin.
Why must they pass through Harbin?
Because other roads are blocked.
They can only take a detour.
What do you need me to do?
Just stand by.
You don't have to contact them.
Zhuowen's still alive.
What?
He's sent back the longitude and latitude
of Unit 731's equipment depot
[Lost and found]
in Dongning Fortress.
It's Zhuowen?
He's still alive.
Our intel is reliable.
This person's arrived in Harbin
no more than 24 hours ago.
He must still be in the urban area.
Ms. Guan.
Harbin is bigger and more complex than Fengtian.
It's easy
to hide in the shadows like a rat.
Besides,
he'll change his identity and image.
It's looking for a needle in a haystack.
Ms. Guan.
What do you think?
Peking opera.
The photos you display at home
must be your favorite.
If he happens to be an opera fan,
this theater is not a coincidence.
This is a clue.
What else is in his home?
Peking opera records.
When we broke the door down,
the record player was still on.
Investigate it.
Find all the records
and sort out the most worn-out ones.
If these records
belong to the same person,
it'll be a breeze.
Yes.
Come in.
I said, come in.
Do you resent me for not visiting you
at the hospital?
The doctor said
you came to see me twice
when I was asleep after taking sleeping pills.
All that matters is you're alive.
All that matters is I'm alive.