What are you reading?
Huh?
First.
Stop being mad at me. Please.
Please, First.
Please.
Yes!
I won.
Sam.
You think you're handsome, huh?
Hey.
Let's continue.
Create a room, Koh.
Do you need the poster?
Are you done, Koh?
Let me play.
Come on. Let's play, Zee.
Come on, Zee.
Zee.
This hairstyle looks good on you.
You're so obvious.
What do you think, First?
Will you let Zee play with us?
Up to you. Do whatever you want.
I don't think First wants him to.
Can you guys stop taking sides?
We're just enjoying the game.
I really want to play.
Koh.
Create a room and invite Zee.
Hold on.
Done.
Tell me the code.
H?
Zee, the code.
D G K H N F.
(Twins)
(Episode 6)
I'm sorry I broke the promise.
I really had something important to do.
Feel free to scold me.
But please don't be like this.
It makes me uncomfortable, First.
Leave me alone.
When you're mad,
I should try to make it up to you, right?
This will be the last time
that I will tell you
to leave me alone.
Tan.
Damn it, Sprite.
- Come on, Sprite.
- Come.
Hey.
Why are you upset?
Come.
Ouch.
Hey.
When you're mad, I should try
to make it up to you, right?
This will be the last time
that I will tell you
to leave me alone.
Damn, Sprite.
It really hurts.
Sprite.
Who are you mad at?
Yeah.
Don't let it out on us.
I'm sorry. I was too rough.
Who are you upset at, Sprite?
Why are you that upset?
Damn.
First hates me.
He told me to leave him alone.
So why are you upset?
You're just friends.
Yeah, just friends.
I think
if you don't want him to hate you,
you should keep being nice to him.
He'll give in eventually.
By the way...
Which First are you talking about?
Yeah.
Hey.
Where is he going, Tan?
I don't know.
Come on, Tan.
Hey.
Tan.
First who?
(Two volleyball players from
a well-known team are in love #ZeeFirst)
Hey.
(Two volleyball players from
a well-known team are in love #ZeeFirst)
(I love this, shipping #ZeeFirst)
(#ZeeFirst only, what great chemistry)
(What kind of looks are they
giving each other? #ZeeFirst)
Shit.
Is this for real?
We have to tell the others.
All he does is cause trouble.
Higher.
Better.
Zee and First are together.
Is what we see in social media true?
Yeah.
They used to hate each other.
When did they become so close?
Or...
Is something going on
that we don't know about?
Hey.
Haven't you seen
the posts on social media?
What are you talking about?
Teammates turned lovers.
People are shipping them online.
Yeah.
Those two?
I don't think so.
I think it's possible.
What if Zee and First like each other
and become a couple?
Hey.
Are you sure?
Go ahead.
Hey.
Do you guys have a crush on each other?
You only believe
what you see on social media.
First and I are friends.
Friends?
I saw your photos on social media.
Like...
Lovey-dovey.
What the fuck?
We're all friends here.
Don't you guys have any?
Hey.
Fuck you.
Calm down.
You're the one without friends.
Don't let me find out
that you guys have a crush on each other.
He's pissed.
He's really mad.
All done.
Not yet.
Coach asked us to paint the court lines.
Paint the court lines?
What are you looking at?
You're looking at me too.
I'm not.
Huh?
If that's the case, how do
you know I was looking at you?
You've seen the posts
on social media, right?
Yeah.
I have.
Are you uncomfortable?
Of course I am.
Strangers are making things up.
It's too late to fix anything.
Just ignore it.
You should spend your time training me.
Who said I was going to train you?
People might misunderstand us even more.
I will find a way to tell
everyone that it's not true.
Just ignore it.
The netizens will care
about something else in a few days.
You don't seem upset at all.
Just ignore it.
Pay attention to your ankle.
There.
Does it still hurt?
Here.
Take it.
If you can't do as promised,
don't make a promise.
Did you wait for me that day?
I'm sorry
for breaking my promise.
A promise only has meaning
if you do as you say.
From now on, I promise.
Don't promise to do something
if you can't do it.
Then I'll just ask.
Ask what?
Can you be my volleyball practice buddy?
I don't want to practice alone anymore.
Please.
Receive.
First.
You're going to be my practice buddy?
When you play volleyball,
you must communicate with your heart
or you won't be able to play as a team.
If you fight the same way, the
competitor will figure out your moves.
Even I can.
Sprite.
Damn it.
If you fight the same way,
the competitor will figure out your moves.
Yeah.
I'll discuss with Coach
about changing my style.
Damn, you're messed up.
You look like a dog.
Hey, don't fight. Please don't fight.
None of your business, Att.
Yeah, none of your business.
Let's not get into a fight.
If you do, it won't look
good for both of you.
I'm in a good mood today.
I don't want to fight with anyone.
Unbelievable.
Yeah.
Hey.
Damn it.
Focus on the practice.
How am I not focused?
Be more focused.
Come here.
Do the under.
When you do the under,
you must go even lower.
Go lower.
Yeah.
Your arms must be straight.
Straight.
So it's easier to receive the ball.
You don't normally do this.
I'm not used to it.
Hey. Don't be upset.
Fine, let's try it again.
Receive the ball.
Come.
If you do that,
your teammates will get injured.
If I don't do that,
how will you be close to me?
You told me
that we must communicate
with our hearts when we play.
I want to communicate with you.
You don't have to physically
be that close to communicate.
Wipe that smile off your face.
Why are you mad?
Receive.
Zee is working hard.
Why has Zee been practicing early?
He must be afraid
he won't be a starter.
Jack.
Let's discuss about us.
What?
You're going to pass me the ball.
Let's talk about that later.
Guys, gather around.
Okay.
Coach wants me to tell you guys something.
Wait, where is he?
He's not here today.
He's in a meeting with the board.
So he wants me to tell you.
He must be discussing how we lost.
So he has been pressured
by the university.
But...
There's always a winner and a loser, Tom.
I must say
that the last match
did not turn out well.
Even though it was the first match...
If that's all you are capable of,
forget about the tryouts
for the national team.
Coach wants me to remind you
that there will be an internal tryout
among team members.
Everyone must practice harder.
Especially Zee.
You must work harder than others, Zee.
Who's going to volunteer
to practice with Zee?
Raise your hand.
First.
Why don't you practice with him?
You're like a couple anyways.
A couple.
Are you guys still not done
being nosy netizens?
I'll help him practice, Salmon.
If you guys can't talk nicely,
then don't talk to me.
Are you uncomfortable?
If you're uncomfortable
practicing with me,
just tell me.
What are you going to do?
I'll stay away.
Why do I have to stay away
from my friend?
Just because they're mocking us?
I'm just pissed at them.
Do you want me to take care of it?
What are you going to do?
I'll punch them.
Nonsense.
Are you still going to help me?
Yeah.
I already told Salmon that I will.
Thank you, bestie.
I have something to do.
I have to go.
See you later.
What's the matter with him?
Come on.
You're practicing early.
Yeah.
I don't want to be a liability.
Is that all?
What do you want to ask me?
I'll answer yes or no.
Do you have a crush on First?
Come on.
You also believe
what you see on social media?
No.
I was just curious.
We're all friends.
Don't forget
why I'm here.
How are you dealing
with the rest of the team?
Have you made any friends?
It makes me sick.
Why does everyone hate Zee?
I'm not sure either.
When I became the team manager,
I noticed that everyone hated him.
The Zee we knew and the Zee now
are totally different.
I really want to know
what happened to him.
Yeah.
But he's the same to me.
You're the only one.
But everyone on the team
hates him.
Salmon?
Yeah?
Do you think everyone can be nice to him?
Of course. I think it's possible.
But the problem is
that Zee won't be nice to anyone.
Zee.
That was a long break.
Okay, I'm going.
Where are you going later?
Do you know that you're annoying, Mike?
Why?
It seems like you want something from me
and you're always being sarcastic.
Do I want something from you? Yes.
But I'm not being sarcastic.
This is how I normally am.
You're only normal when we fuck.
Just tell me what you want.
I've said everything, Jack.
What's wrong with you?
Guys.
Do you want me to help you
with the dishes?
Hey.
Are you guys fighting?
You can talk to me.
I'm not good with advice,
but I can help you.
Zee.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Why are you pretending to be nice?
Why would I be pretending?
I just want to be nice to you.
We're on the same team.
Let's clear the air and not fight.
I'll help with the dishes.
Zee is crazy.
Yeah.
You're crazy, not him.
Zee.
Stop practicing and clean the floor.
Wait a minute.
Put the ball away and clean the floor.
Okay.
What?
I need the mop.
I'm sorry.
That was a bit rough.
Just take it and clean the floor.
What the hell?
Ugh.
Zee.
I have a question.
Go ahead, what is it?
Sam.
Yes?
Well...
I saw Zee doing this.
Keep your voice down.
I'm sorry, Sam.
Well...
I want to do it too.
Can you teach me?
Fine.
Really?
Have you had lessons before?
A little.
Then...
Can you teach me as well?
Okay.
I was wondering where my dear Sam went.
You're here.
Let's play games.
Do you want to?
If Zee's playing,
I'm not playing.
What about you, Mike?
Do you want to play?
I don't really want to play anymore.
Wait for me, Koh.
Tom.
What about you?
My mother is calling.
Go ahead.
What?
Yes, Mom?
What's the matter with them?
Okay, I'll get going then.
Huh?
Jack.
Hey.
What the hell?
Zee.
Please teach me.
Teach me too.
Fine.
Look, Deddeaw.
Okay.
Hey.
So cool.
Sam.
Look.
There.
Follow me.
Okay.
Do this.
Your arm.
Twist.
Hey.
Good.
So cool.
Gently. Ouch. Do it gently.
The last match
was tiring and a waste of time, Mom.
It's Zee's fault
that we lost.
Don't say that about your teammate.
He was probably tired.
No one wants the team to lose.
Okay, then I'll stop talking about this.
Mom.
I'll stay with you at the hospital
on my day off.
Is there anything you would like to eat?
I'll get it for you.
Anything's fine.
Just seeing you
will make me feel so much better.
That's all I need to be happy.
Okay, Mom. I'll see you soon.
That hit was amazing.
You should aim a little higher next time.
The other team is tall. It's hard.
Here.
Water.
What's wrong with you?
You guys didn't get any water.
You must be tired.
So I got you some.
What are you trying to do, Zee?
Being kind to other people
is a good thing.
Thank you, Zee.
Can we talk to each other nicely?
Talk nicely?
Yeah, we're on the same team.
You guys and I don't see eye to eye.
Don't you find it strange?
Hey.
Just tell us what you want, Zee.
Don't pretend to be nice.
Yeah.
Your little act
can't fool any of us.
What did I do to deserve so much hate?
You don't remember
what you said to us?
Let's calm down.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
What the hell did you do, Zee?
I will make you be friends with me.
Tom, let's practice. Come on.
Don't act confused. Come on.
Come on, Koh. Let's practice.
Hey.
Come.
You set the ball so well, Jack.
It's true.
What's the matter with you?
When we practice, pass me the ball often.
Of course I have to do that.
So I can score.
Fine.
Thank you.
It's fine.
Just stay focused.
Okay.
I'll keep practicing.
Pass me the ball again.
Show me everything you've got.
Damn it.
I'm tired.
It's hot.
Today...
It's strange.
Are you tired?
Yeah, give me the ball.
What are you looking at?
Do I look strange?
Yeah.
Why are you naked?
We're all men here.
This is normal, isn't it?
I didn't do well during practice today.
My wrist hurts a little.
You hit the ball too fast and too hard.
I took a video of the practice session.
Do you want to get it checked out?
Hey.
Let me see it.
It could be dislocated.
Don't come near us.
You're being nice because you really
want to be friends with us?
Yeah. Are you just pretending?
Here.
Massage your wrist with some cream.
I'm being nice to you all
because I want to.
I'm not pretending.
Someone once told me
that when it comes to volleyball,
we must communicate with our hearts.
That's how we should play.
If I don't treat my teammates nicely,
why am I playing this sport?
We're on the same team.
If we can communicate well,
then it's a good thing, right?
Fine.
I'm fine with it.
You?
Good.
Thank you, First.
Yeah.
You were waiting for me.
Did you miss me that much?
Stop daydreaming.
I don't miss you.
What a waste of time.
I thought you do.
Hey.
What do you want to ask about Zee?
I want to know
about Zee and First.
Is it true?
About Zee and First?
Well...
So many people are shipping them.
You're good at making things up.
I'm not.
Do you
know about them?
I do.
Are they dating?
Do you want me to tell you?
If you do,
you must give me something.
What?
What do you want?
Well...
Be my boyfriend
and I'll tell you everything.
No. I'll find out on my own.
Why should you put in the effort for that?
Be my boyfriend
and I'll tell you everything.
Don't mess with me.
Don't tell me then.
You're annoying.
Ouch.
Is every volleyball player this violent?
For him, I'll do anything.
(Next Episode)
Come and pick your team.
First.
Why are we not on the same team?
Don't make it a big deal.
Does anyone want to switch with me?
Me. I do.
Why did you ask to switch teams?
Nothing.
Do you care?
Stop acting like this.
It makes me uncomfortable.
I don't like it
when you're close to someone else.
Does it mean
that I like you?
Stop liking Zee
and like me instead.
Let me take care of you.