[Fangs of Fortune]
[Episode 12]
Kill Zhao Yuanzhou for me.
Say
yes.
Yes.
That was just an insignificant skill.
Hey.
What is this place?
We were just lying
in the coffins, right?
Why are there so many dead people?
Gosh!
Break!
It was just an illusion.
It was fake.
He was pulling my leg just now. It was really scary.
I guess someone cast a spell
on the wind chime,
so that it can affect and bewitch people.
They're here.
Good archery.
Awesome.
-Awesome.
Let's go.
I'm here.
Don't be afraid.
Well,
if only Mr. Zhuo were here.
This is where the demonic energy in the town came from:
Lingxi Villa.
[God Bless Lingxi]
There are demons here?
There are demons here.
Don't be afraid.
Both of us are demons.
A demon catching Mr. Zhuo
is like a rat catching a cat, right?
Looks like in this world,
I'm not the only one who wants to commit suicide.
Interesting.
This is the only way to Mount Kunlun.
But now,
plague is rampant here,
[God Bless Lingxi]
and demonic energy is everywhere.
And Zhuo is missing.
Looks like someone
doesn't want us to go to Mount Kunlun.
But...
few people know
we're going to Mount Kunlun.
How could we be ambushed by demons?
Who is so annoying?
The one who wants to destroy
the Wilderness.
Li Lun.
[God Bless Lingxi]
Hands off!
Come here.
It's improper for men and women to touch each other.
It's not appropriate
for you to hold Ms. Pei.
What are you talking about?
How old am I?
Are you an idiot?
If you hold Ms. Pei,
she won't be able to shoot arrows.
If we encounter a demon,
she won't be able to protect you.
Don't imitate Mr. Zhuo.
Who is imitating Mr. Zhuo?
Sorry.
My bad.
You should learn from him
so that you can understand the differences between you two.
Right?
Sorry.
Stop wasting time.
Let's find Mr. Zhuo first.
Zhuo is skilled in swordsmanship.
Ordinary people
can never catch him so easily.
Is there a possibility
that Mr. Zhuo wanted to be caught?
Then he would definitely leave a clue.
A clue?
I'll look for it.
You're not afraid now?
Ying Lei,
you have an acute sense of smell.
Go.
Okay.
I found
Brother Zhuo's bell.
[God Bless Lingxi]
Let me smell it.
Smell it and see if there are more bells ahead.
Go.
This way.
Found it.
Not bad.
Your nose works well.
No more bells.
No more bells?
This is strange.
It means there must be a secret tunnel here.
Let's split up.
Okay.
You go over there. I'll go this way.
It's...
a prescription.
Jiu, take a look.
It's for promoting blood circulation, relieving stagnation,
detoxifying, and clearing pestilence.
It's for treating the plague?
Why is a prescription
for treating the plague here?
Gosh!
Why is it here?
It's too scary!
Why is this happening?
It's too creepy!
It's gone.
There is nothing there.
See for yourself.
It's gone.
What's wrong?
Xiao, behind you.
Gosh!
Xiao, there's a demon behind you.
Don't move.
There's a demon behind you.
It's so scary.
Why are you teasing Jiu?
I will never come here again.
Your friends are here.
They will find me.
Yes.
So give them a warm welcome.
Demon friend,
you have a distinctive personality.
What kind of demon is he?
He should be... Fei.
Fei?
I learned from a book
that this kind of demon can deplete water
and wither grass.
And its appearance would bring plague to the world.
So you are the root cause
of the plague in Sinan Water Town.
But it seems
he is without malice.
Sister Pei, you've learned to observe demons
and defend them now.
Hello.
Have you seen our friend?
Maybe your description was not good enough,
so he couldn't recognize him.
Let me try.
Have you seen our friend?
He's in blue.
He's not...
He's not as handsome as me.
Hello.
Have you seen our friend?
He's taller and more handsome
than this great demon.
Zhao Yuanzhou, see?
Where is he?
Why do you want Zhao Yuanzhou's inner core?
Because I want freedom.
What does Zhao Yuanzhou's inner core
have to do with your freedom?
There is a blood feud between you and Zhao Yuanzhou.
How would you feel
to be with someone
who is your sworn enemy?
Would you hate him?
I...
He killed your father and brother.
He killed so many innocent people,
but you can't kill him.
And you have to face him every day.
How can you not hate him?
You should hate him.
What's in this incense burner?
This is Lingxi Villa.
Of course it's a rhinoceros horn.
Burning rhinoceros horns
can connect Yin and Yang.
It can help me attract the malicious energy in and outside the villa.
Mr. Zhuo.
Do you know what malicious energy is?
Hatred in this world
transforms into malicious energy.
It's natural sustenance for fierce beasts.
It can also awaken the hatred and pain
deep in your heart.
Come on.
Listen to the hatred deep in your heart.
Let it tell you what to do.
Kill him.
It's dark in the secret tunnel.
Let's use the Baize Divine Power
to explore it.
As a great demon,
you actually need my power
to feel the barrier?
Actually, I can do it myself.
Just say it if you want to hold Xiao's hand.
How old are you?
You already understand this kind of thing?
I remember I first knew what love is
when I was 370 years old.
Zhao Yuanzhou.
Go to jail.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Our route here has been completely blocked off.
Kill him.
You scared me.
Friend,
why are you so mysterious?
What is this?
In a world plagued by a disease,
Qing Geng Goddess used red pigments
to dye Jinli stones
and gave them to everyone
to ensure their safety.
The people on the mural
also have the red bead bracelet.
Qing Geng Goddess?
Everybody wants to be a goddess.
Do they really think it's very easy to be a goddess?
I learned from a book
that Qing Geng lives on cypress trees,
living off their flowers and fruits.
It does have the ability to ward off plague.
Qing Geng...
can only protect herself from plague.
In fact,
she is just an ordinary demon.
I saw her in the Wilderness before.
She was always flying in the forest.
She was noisier than Jiu.
How can a small sparrow
be called a goddess?
Most so-called deities exist
merely to satisfy people's desires.
When they want something,
they turn to deities.
But when a calamity strikes,
they would complain
that deities are unresponsive,
nature is merciless,
and all beings suffer.
Then they would do bad things without guilt
and shift the blame
to those imagined deities.
If everyone wearing this bead died,
it was not for warding off the plague.
Could it be...
But there's only an ordinary mural here.
There is no exit.
Fei.
Fei?
He's so mysterious.
Since Qing Geng
wants to be a goddess desperately
and wants everyone
to worship her as a goddess,
let's just do it.
What?
Goddess, you...
Let's go.
We don't know what's inside.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
you go first.
I'll follow in the rear.
Let's go.
Wen!
Goddess!
Great Demon!
Open the door!
So, is what you found an exit
or a trap?
Whatever it is,
we can only move forward.
Come on.
Protect me.
Or we'll die together.
Of course.
Open the door!
Why won't it open?
Sister Pei, pray...
The door is not responding.
It won't
open.
Is it broken?
Sister Pei!
Sister Pei, what's wrong?
Gosh!
Sister Pei, you have been infected with the plague!
The plague?
Zhuo.
Zhao Yuanzhou.
Don't come near us!
He's being controlled by malicious energy.
He's very dangerous now.
Why is there so much malicious energy on you?
I'm going to kill you.
We share the same thought and are like-minded.
But you can't do it now.
Don't move.
I'm helping you.
I'm going to kill you.
I promised you long ago, right?
But not now.
It's you, an evil bird.
I've heard a lot about you,
Zhu Yan.
After seeing you today,
I think you truly are as insufferable as the rumor says.
In order to control the malicious energy on him,
you must have used a lot of demonic power.
I have plenty of demonic power.
I know that.
But you can't restore it
within a short time,
can you?
I didn't expect
the famous evil demon
to hurt himself in order to save someone.
Zhu Yan,
I didn't know you have such a kind heart.
The person I want to save
is not just someone.
He's my good friend.
You consider him as your good friend.
But what does he consider you as?
Zhuo Yichen,
who is the man standing in front of you?
My sworn enemy.
What should you do when your enemy
is standing in front of you?
I should kill him.
Zhuo.
What exactly do you want?
I want your inner core.
You have one.
Why do you want mine?
In this world,
only your inner core
can destroy the seal of the Baize Token.
I want to break the Baize seal on me
and regain freedom.
Seal?
Because of this damn seal,
I've been trapped in Lingxi Villa
and I can never go out.
Baize Goddess was so cruel.
Zhuo Yichen,
what are you waiting for?
Kill him!
Zhuo.
Zhuo!
The malicious energy and demonic energy here are really strong.
They even blinded me.
I didn't realize there is a seal of the Baize Token.
You two were acting to trick me?
No.
I was not acting.
My fear was real.
Mr. Zhuo's Cloud Light Sword
is really scary.
I am scarier.
Do you want to try?
Okay.
When did you regain your consciousness?
Don't move.
I'm helping you.
I'm going to kill you.
I promised you long ago,
right?
But not now.
Let me kill...
You've regained your consciousness, right?
Why do you still look stupid?
You're the stupid one!
Don't you want to know Qing Geng's real purpose?
Do what you're good at.
Now?
I don't think it's a good time.
Acting.
I meant acting.
Oh.
Are you sure you are not taking this opportunity to settle personal grudges?
No!
Mr. Zhuo,
are you
ready?
Shut up!
What a pity.
Indeed, the seal of the Baize Token can be broken.
But it requires me to use the malicious energy
to cast the spell myself.
If I die,
it'll be useless even if you have my inner core.
The one who tricked you into taking my inner core
is either a fool or a liar.
You're a liar.
In this world,
no one believes in sincerity.
Hypocritical people always win.
Forget it.
I just want to know who tricked you
into taking my inner core.
I can guess it even if you don't tell me.
There is a loathsome and familiar smell
on you.
-Wen Xiao!
So hot.
Your hand...
It really hurts.
I meant that thing on your hand.
It's the plague.
Wen Xiao.
Zhuo!
Jiu,
stay away from me.
Yes.
Come.
Stay away from her.
I'm half-god and half-demon.
I have the bloodline of the God Race.
I should be fine.
Well,
I'm fine too.
That's strange.
No.
She's having a high fever.
We need to get out of here as soon as possible.
Otherwise, she'll be in danger.
Okay.
Even if I have to break my knife,
I'll dig a tunnel and crawl out.
Eh?
Fei?
Qing Geng?
What Qing Geng?
Isn't the one he was helping Qing Geng?
Are you sure?
Yes.
She looks exactly the same as the one on the mural.
Take care of Sister Pei here.
Hey.
Bai Jiu!
Don't come near me!
I don't need you to save me
or help me.
Gosh!
You're hurt.
Let me do it.
I'm a doctor.
Why do you want to save me?
My master always said
doctors are benevolent.
We can't just let people die.
Doctors are benevolent.
If I tell you
I am the culprit who spread the plague,
will you still save me?
Actually, I've already guessed it.
You spread the plague
through those red bead bracelets, right?
That red bead...
was stained with Fei's blood.
Why did you do that?
Do you know I was
a goddess worshipped by everyone?
I've lived in this town
for a few hundred years.
People worshipped me
and prayed to me
that I could protect them
from the plague.
Their piety and faith
gave me strength.
So I blessed them
and protected them.
It was like
feeling guilty for receiving their gifts
and wanting
to give them something in return.
But one day,
Fei came here.
He is the origin of plague by nature.
I did everything I could,
but I still couldn't stop the calamity.
Please save us.
Many people died due to the plague.
The survivors vented their anger
and called me a liar
and a fake god.
They destroyed Lingxi Villa
and splashed dirty water
and filthy things
on my statue.
No one wanted to believe me
or worship me anymore.
Shortly afterwards,
Baize Goddess also came.
She realized Fei causes plague,
while Qing Geng can ward off plague.
I'm the natural enemy of Fei.
In order to suppress Fei's plague miasma,
Baize Goddess
[Lingxi Villa]
sealed us
in Lingxi Villa.
I've been sealed here
for a few hundred years.
I can't
see the end of it.
You are a mortal
and a young boy.
Your life is short.
You can't understand this kind
of endless suffering.
Someone told me
as long as I spread the plague
to lure you here,
kill Zhao Yuanzhou,
and get his inner core,
I could break the Baize seal
and leave here.
Brother Zhuo.
I know the person you just mentioned.
His name is Li Lun.
Right?
Qing Geng,
you spread the plague
to harm the mortal world.
Do you confess to the crime?
It was not her fault.
It was all my fault.
Because of me,
she was sentenced to life imprisonment here.
So you can speak?
If I were her,
I would also resent fate for being unfair.
I have a way to treat the plague.
As long as you help me save her,
I'll help you save everyone.
Really?
But she's badly injured.
I'm afraid even deities can't save her.
If we were somewhere else,
I'm afraid she couldn't be saved.
But here,
maybe I can give it a try.
You have a way?
Because of the plague,
Sinan Water Town is surrounded by malicious energy.
The stronger the malicious energy is,
the greater my demonic power is.
I can try to use the malicious energy here
to treat her.
Thank you...
for saving her.
She is very important to you?
Yes.
Very important.
I've been cursed by fate since I was born.
Wherever I go,
[Glorious Flowers in Spring and Solid Fruits in Autumn]
plague arises.
Both humans
and demons
consider me the source of calamity,
fearing
me.
But she's different.
She could have been
a Qing Geng bird
flying freely in the clear sky.
I yearned to go to the mortal world
and didn't want to be sealed in the barren Wilderness.
So
I escaped from the Wilderness secretly.
The mortal world is prosperous and bustling.
Grass, trees,
flowers, and leaves
are full of vitality.
Only in the mortal world
do I truly feel alive.