[Fangs of Fortune]
[Episode 11]
Sister Pei.
Zhao Yuanzhou asked me
to give you
Pei Siheng's puppet.
I don't know what he wants to do.
Sister Pei.
You must want to be alone.
Then I'll
be off.
Sister.
♫If you were a spring night♫
♫I'm the silent mountain♫
♫You're a sad firefly♫
♫Guarding the last moment of the night♫
♫Why don't you remember♫
♫I'm always by your side?♫
♫Like wind surrounding flowers♫
♫Guarding the memories♫
You're still alive.
♫Never fading away♫
Of course not.
I died a long time ago.
You know that.
♫I guard the eaves♫
♫And watch the times fade♫
♫You hold the flame and watch the night♫
Then why are you…
Zhao Yuanzhou used the Chaos Spell
♫I count the winters♫
to keep my soul.
♫And waited for one more year♫
I know a spell
♫My heart is full of passion♫
called Chaotic Impermanence.
It can make your soul
re-form in the puppet.
♫The stars dazzle and the crescent moon curves♫
But since it's chaotic,
♫The guilty greed♫
it's orderless and ever-changing.
♫Thousands of dark hairs, long and short♫
Maybe you won't be able to
♫The cruel entanglement♫
show up in this world ever again.
♫Lend me the cold lamp for one night♫
Or maybe
you can accompany and protect your sister every day and night.
♫Let regret stay before dawn♫
What do you say?
♫Turns out I'm a wanderer♫
♫And you're a song of reluctant parting♫
♫In the sky of floating snowflakes♫
♫You are the only warm bloom♫
♫But why don't I remember♫
I can occasionally…
♫How much the plot has twisted?♫
I can occasionally keep you company now.
♫I forgot the bitter karma♫
♫I missed it again and again♫
♫Helpless♫
♫Turns out I'm a wanderer♫
Heng.
♫And you're a song of reluctant parting♫
♫I'm a black-and-white wound♫
Why are you so silly?
♫You're the vibrant red color♫
I often got sick when I was young.
♫How can I not remember♫
I'd always been a burden for our family…
♫You're always by my side?♫
♫Like wind surrounding flowers♫
and for you.
I never saw you as a burden.
♫Guarding the memories, never fading away♫
It was for myself that I wanted
to be a demon hunter.
It wasn't because of you.
You often got sick when you were young.
The medicine in the mortal world didn't work at all.
But there might be miracles in the Wilderness.
So I worked hard to hunt demons
so that one day
I could find some miraculous medicine
to cure you.
I didn't feel tired.
Because that was my biggest wish.
Sister,
your wish has come true.
I'm very healthy
and strong now.
I won't make you worry anymore.
I can even protect you.
Sister.
Back then…
Back then, I didn't want to become a demon.
I was very scared.
Because
as a demon…
I couldn't be your brother anymore.
Don't be afraid.
If you became a demon again,
I'd become a demon with you.
You finally learned to joke.
Smile more.
That's good.
So, Sister,
look,
no matter what…
this is somewhat of a good ending.
Isn't it?
Sister.
Remember
to smile more.
In the days to come…
don't cry again.
You can't sleep?
Are you guys
going to Kunlun tomorrow?
Yeah.
That's great.
How about you?
Are you coming with us?
Me?
I'll pass.
Those at the Demon Hunting Bureau need me to cook for them.
They all like me so much.
You'd rather stay in the mortal world as a cook
than return to the Wilderness
to be the Mountain God?
Yes.
I don't understand.
The mortal world is so good.
There are all kinds of
amazing things here.
But Grandpa and the others
are willing to stay in the Wilderness,
a desolate and lonely place,
till the end of their lives.
I see no point
in spending my life like that.
There are many ways to live your life.
Responsibility is a choice,
not a constraint.
Neither shouldering responsibility
nor pursuing dreams is wrong.
Some people
only wish to be a quiet lake in the forest,
while other people
want to become a running river.
Lady Goddess,
what about you?
What's your choice?
Master said
it's not the Baize Token that made us the Goddess
but the determination to protect the Wilderness.
I want peace between the two worlds.
Because in the Wilderness
and the mortal world, there are people and demons…
that I care for.
Come with us to Kunlun.
Jiu is waiting for you to cook for him.
The plan is going more smoothly than I thought.
How about a toast?
The way you look at me
makes me very uncomfortable.
The plan is going smoothly,
but you'd better stay committed.
Look at who I am.
Don't get smart.
Relax.
We have the same goal.
I believe we can get the Baize Token very soon.
Aren't you happy?
Getting it
can't make me happy.
But destroying it
is very delightful.
Five days later,
there will be a blood moon.
That's the best time to destroy the Baize Token.
So those from the Demon Hunting Bureau
can't get to Kunlun too soon.
Do something about it.
Don't worry.
Qing Geng is already waiting at the foot of Mount Kunlun.
But don't forget
what you promised me.
Zhao Yuanzhou's inner core,
I'll definitely get it for you.
What about your promise to me?
Can you fulfill it?
I don't need to fulfill it myself.
Someone else will fulfill it for me.
And she can do better than me.
Stall them at Sinan Water Town.
Can you do it?
I'll try my best.
[Lingxi Villa]
To be obsessed
is to be trapped.
Life is full of ups and downs.
It's just all about obsession
and karma.
Wen Xiao.
What are you writing?
Cheng Huang was obsessed
with keeping the Goddess alive.
He was so obsessed
that he swam against the tide
and eventually hurt himself.
Obsessions
trap not only mortals
but also immortals.
I'm so happy!
We're going to Mount Kunlun.
Let me tell you.
I've packed a lot of things in my box.
It's very heavy.
Brother Zhuo.
My box is so heavy.
Give it to me if you're tired.
I can carry it for you.
I told you I could carry it for you.
Thank you, Brother Zhuo.
I'm stronger than Zhuo.
Someone stronger is coming, in terms of malicious energy.
Morning.
Friends.
Everyone is here, Yinglei.
Lend us your incense burner.
Just Mount Kunlun.
No problem.
My turf.
This...
This is Mount Kunlun?
Well… sorry.
When I was thinking about Mount Kunlun just now,
I suddenly thought that
Ms. Pei once mentioned
Sinan Water Town at the foot of Mount Kunlun
which had an interesting Lantern Festival.
And I got distracted.
Sinan Water Town is at the foot of Mount Kunlun.
I came here for investigation once.
It happened to be during the Lantern Festival,
so I casually mentioned it to Jiu.
Why did you eavesdrop?
It's fine.
Mount Kunlun is not far away.
We just need to hike a bit.
Hike?
Hiking is good for your health.
Sinan Water Town
is a beautiful place.
People here live in peace.
It's a wealthy paradise.
But this place
doesn't look like it.
Looks like
many people have died.
They've arrived at Sinan Water Town.
Then we can kill him soon.
The plague has spread across the town.
This red string can make you immune to it.
Otherwise,
you'll be infected too.
When I came here for a case,
things were completely different.
It's been just a few months.
What on earth has happened?
This place is so scary.
It's like a haunted town.
Don't be afraid.
With me by your side,
you…
Jiu.
With you holding me like this,
how can I use my sword?
But I'm really scared.
I'll hold this instead.
Don't pull my hair.
Here.
Hold this.
What has ruined this wealthy town
is either war
or plague.
I made these detoxification pills myself.
You each take one.
Try not to come in contact with the residents
or animals here.
Stay away from dead bodies.
How did it happen so suddenly?
The news never reached Tiandu.
No one knows this town is in such a grave situation.
Let's split up to make inquiries.
Be careful.
Come back!
Brother Zhuo!
Before we find out the source of the plague,
we have to isolate this place
to prevent the plague and miasma from spreading.
Zhao Yuanzhou, lend me your Baize Token.
You want to hold my hand?
No problem.
Now, to you, is he
the cruel demon who killed your father or brother
or a friend who fights alongside you?
Both.
But it doesn't matter.
No matter what,
I'll kill him myself.
But he has half of the Baize Token now.
I can't kill him.
Is that the real reason?
After we reach Mount Kunlun
and find a way to merge the two halves of the Baize Token,
Wen Xiao can get back
the power of Baize Goddess.
By then,
I'll settle all my grudges with him.
I didn't expect
to find the other half of the Baize Token so soon.
And it happened to be with Zhao Yuanzhou.
It seems that the universe
is protecting the Wilderness
and the mortal world.
I don't think so.
What do you mean?
I don't think it's accidental.
It's more like by design.
Pei Siheng's puppet suddenly appeared,
leading us to investigate the case of Cheng Huang
and learn the truth about the Baize Token.
Your brother's appearance
is too much of a coincidence.
You suspect my brother?
I just suspect Cheng Huang's motive.
Pei Siheng has always been under Cheng Huang's control,
but Cheng Huang is leading us to catch him.
Don't you think it's strange?
I have the feeling
that we're like puppets
that are manipulated
by a pair of invisible hands.
We got what we wanted too easily.
Everything has been going so smoothly.
This feeling
unsettles me very much.
Well…
I'll go check the perimeter again.
I can do it alone.
Why are we in a drug shop?
I want to see if they have enough herbs in stock.
Master?
Jiu?
Master, it's really you.
What are you doing here?
Hello, sir.
I'm…
good friend.
Master.
Shouldn't you be in Tiandu?
Why are you here?
I was told that
a plague broke out in Sinan Water Town,
so I came to have a look.
But I didn't expect it
to be so serious.
It started five days ago.
Local physicians couldn't do anything about it.
Some people were too scared and ran away.
Ran away?
Wouldn't they bring the plague to other towns?
Life here was always peaceful.
With the protection of the spiritual energy of Mount Kunlun,
this town never saw any plague or natural disaster.
The only plague I know
happened hundreds of years ago.
It's said to have been horrible,
and almost everyone in the town died.
I wonder how it'll end
this time.
Master.
Can't you do anything about it either?
To end this plague,
we need to find the source.
There are four causes for plague: unnatural energy,
imbalance in the seasons,
lingering fog and dew,
and the build-up of harmful miasma.
I've checked them one by one.
None of them are the cause of this plague.
None of them are?
Then what could be the cause?
Could it be that
there's a demon in the town?
Demon…
Don't be afraid.
With me protecting you,
no demon
or poison…
Brother Zhuo!
Brother Zhuo…
Jiu!
What's wrong?
Brother Zhuo.
Come with me.
We were talking about you just now.
Let me introduce you.
This
is my master,
the best physician in Tiandu.
I'm Wen Zongyu.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Zhuo.
No wonder Jiu is a medical prodigy.
It turns out that he trained under you.
What have you found out?
Zhao Yuanzhou and Wen Xiao have found the source of the plague.
Some demon
has been messing around here.
Demon?
Demon.
If it's a demon that caused the plague,
my medical skills can't be of any help.
Mr. Zhuo,
please save the people here.
Oh, right.
Could you please
take this token of the Demon Hunting Bureau
to borrow soldiers from the nearby government offices?
We need to lock down the town
and cut off all access
to prevent the spread of the plague.
[Demon Hunting Bureau]
Lives are at stake.
I'll definitely make it.
Jiu.
Be careful,
okay?
I'll go then.
Okay.
Sir, don't worry.
Shut up!
I'll keep Bai Jiu safe.
Do you see it?
Yes.
Red malicious energy is everywhere.
Indeed, this plague is caused by a demon.
The red malicious energy
is from me.
See if there's anything else.
Okay.
In red malicious energy,
there are strands of black demonic energy.
That's right.
Can you see the source?
It's over there.
[Lingxi Villa]
Mr. Situ, you're absent-minded
and about to lose.
Don't be a sore loser later.
Mr. Fan,
are you really not worried?
How can you focus on the game
when you're worrying about something else?
I'm leaving.
I'll play chess with you another day.
Come.
Send this letter
to Mr. Zhuo immediately.
Yes.
[Glorious Flowers in Spring and Solid Fruits in Autumn]
Just normal joss paper.
Mr. Zhuo, why have you drawn your Cloud Light Sword?
You've opened your umbrella too.
Jiu!
Zhuo!
Brother Zhuo!
Jiu!
Wait.
Wait for what?
For Jiu to be eaten by the demon?
Don't you think it's strange?
It's obvious that the demon took Jiu
to lure us over.
Mr. Zhuo and Zhao Yuanzhou have gone into the fog.
They're so capable.
They can definitely save Jiu.
We'll only distract them if we follow.
Let's just wait here
for them to come back.
I'll protect you.
Brother Zhuo!
[Good Virtues Shine Forever]
[Carry on the Legacy]
[A Magnificent Story]
Who are you?
Where's Jiu?
Wake up.
Where's Brother Zhuo?
Jiu!
Jiu.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Where's Brother Zhuo?
I saw Zhuo running in here
and followed him into the yard.
Before I could find Zhuo,
I saw Jiu.
Where is Zhuo?
It seems that
their target is not Jiu
but Mr. Zhuo.
People don't disappear out of thin air.
It's the blood of the Bingyi Clan.
Mr. Zhuo must have been hurt.
Open the coffin.
The Cloud Light Sword
is indeed worthy of its reputation.
In ancient times, the Bingyi Clan killed Ying Long
and used its horns
and soul
to make two Cloud Light Swords.
They can kill all demons in the world.
Of course they're powerful.
Only the descendants of the Bingyi Clan can use the Cloud Light Sword.
If you want to kill Zhao Yuanzhou…
you have to rely on him.
[Carry on the Legacy]
Red string?
This body has a red string too.
This body also has one.
What can you smell?
Nothing.
Just weird.
Tsk,
we should've brought a dog with us.
You're being
very rude to the Mountain God!
Pointing your finger at me
is even ruder.
You're rude.
Great Demon.
What are you doing?
I want to experience the feeling of lying dead.
Wen Xiao.
Do you want to have a try?
Bring Jiu with you.
Zhuo bled.
You'll definitely get hurt too.
It's safer to bring
a physician with you.
Xiao.
He
is a bad influence
on you.
No.
I refuse.
I feel insecure when I'm with him.
You can't refuse.
I'll protect you.
Zhao Yuanzhou is really smart.
Something is wrong with the coffin.
Wait.
Why is it wet here?
You're actually awake?
Who on earth
are you?
Qing Geng.
A demon?
A demon.
However,
without the Cloud Light Sword,
the famous Zhuo Yichen
can only be under the thumb of a demon.
I didn't expect you to be so bold
as to pretend to be in a coma
and throw yourself into danger alone.
You're indeed a descendant of the Bingyi Clan.
If I hadn't pretended to be unconscious,
how could I have found out
your secret plot?
Once Zhao Yuanzhou is dead,
I can get his inner core
and finish my unfinished business.
Then I'll give his inner core to you.
You want Zhao Yuanzhou's inner core
but can't kill him.
So,
you need me to do it.
To be precise,
I need your sword.
Only the Cloud Light Sword
can kill Zhao Yuanzhou
and help me get his inner core.
Who brought me here?
You don't need to know that.
If you don't
tell me who is behind this
and what they want,
I'll never help you kill Zhao Yuanzhou.
Interesting.
He killed your father and brother,
yet you really see him as a friend
who fights alongside you?
I'll kill him,
but it has nothing to do with you guys.
Mortals are really hard to understand.
I'm kindly helping you to take revenge,
but you don't appreciate it.
This was originally a spine from the fierce beast Qin Yuan in the Wilderness.
Surprisingly, it's been made
into a needle in the mortal world.
They all say demons are cold-blooded and evil.
But humans are worse.
It's said that if one is jabbed by it,
they'll suffer greatly
and wish they were dead.
The Cloud Light Sword can actually feel your pain.
Are you afraid?
Are you
afraid?
I only
follow my heart.
I don't take orders from anyone.
People say humans are greedy,
cowardly,
and selfish.
They stop at nothing to get what they want.
Are you
any different?
Try me.
Sure.
Mr. Zhuo, since you're so stubborn…
how about now?
Kill Zhao Yuanzhou for me.
Let's do it together.
You'll help me,
won't you?
Say
you will.
I
will.