Why are those eyes looking at me?
It's like sending a signal that we're going to get to know each other.
One day, one day when we are together
Set the clock to run a little slower.
Let me get a little closer to you.
Take it slow
There will come a day when we are ready.
It's too hard to feel
Deep down it's crying out
She was there and I could only look.
Before we got into a relationship
I will write a love song for you to listen to.
From that day we passed each other
What a strange dream!
Hoy!
Are you dreaming?
Not dreaming
Oh, I didn't dream.
Ha!
Hoy!
Who the hell is this?
How did you get into our room?
mother
Mom, help me!
There's someone in the room, Mom.
mother
What happened, son?
Get out!
What happened, my son?
mother
What's wrong, son?
There's someone in my room.
Who is your son? I don't see anyone here, Sia.
There is, right there.
Oh, where did it go?
No children
What is it?
I guess you went to bed late.
Whose guitar is that?
Are you still playing music, son?
Uh huh
Oh, it's Jod's, Mom.
It's like they created the content and then forgot about it.
So, Sia picked it up and gave it to me.
If it comes to get it, it will tell Xia again.
Okay then let's go.
Anyway, study hard, my child.
Go... go take a shower and eat something.
I'm going to be late for school.
okay
What happened? Where did it go?
Hoy!
hello
Who are you?
Wait, take it easy.
Why are you following us?
We didn't follow you.
You're the one who brought us here.
Ha!
Are you crazy? Who brought who here?
You also showed up at our house.
Wait a minute.
Are you imagining it?
Oh, never mind.
Okay, who are you? Why are you following us?
Is that a thief?
We have nothing, just a guitar.
wait a minute
We are not thieves.
If we were thieves, we would just steal things.
Then just run away?
Oh, why are you following me again?
Not following
I'm following you. Can you please stop pestering me?
Can you stop following me?
Hey, Xia!
Xia
What's wrong with you?
No, let's hurry up.
What's wrong with Sia?
do not know
Strange
No matter how long
I can't wait any longer.
I miss you so much that I want to hug you.
Did you play the wrong chord?
Who are you?
How did you get into my room?
Get out now!
already
So how did you get in?
Listen to us first.
My name is...
go out
Get out now!
Get out of here right now or else.
Not so
I called the police.
Now, listen to me first.
enough
My name is Blue.
We saw that you didn't know how to play the guitar, so we wanted to help you.
What do you need help with?
Hey, don't come any closer.
this
This is my bedroom.
Now it is that I need to ask for help.
Please help me.
help
Get out!
Please help me.
Hey, can you please stop talking?
Mr.
Who the hell are you?
In that case
I'll act like
That thing just now never happened.
Hoy!
Are you crazy?
Listen to us first.
We are in good spirits.
Uh huh
Okay, so what's up?
My name is Blue.
That guitar
It's ours.
Whose guitar is that?
Can I play this to relieve my boredom?
Hoy!
Are you here to collect it?
If you're jealous, I don't have to play.
We are not jealous.
We just want to say that
That guitar
It's really ours.
Which is why we came here.
It's because of that guitar.
While we were alive
I also like playing the guitar like you.
this
Do you even know our name?
Since you picked up that guitar
We've seen it in passing
In that case
If I go to the bathroom
Can you peek?
So, do you want me to watch it?
mental disorder
Hey, hey, calm down first.
We just want to help Xia.
We know that.
That Sia has been under a lot of pressure
We want to help you become better.
Do you know how to play guitar?
It's our big dream.
We see people who have the same dreams.
So we want to help Sia.
successful
already...
If you say you're dead
How did you die?
Well, we're not breathing.
Not like that.
Refers to the cause of death
Just kidding
We just...
we
We don't remember anymore.
oh
Why can't I remember?
This is who you are.
It's your business too.
oh
Haven't you heard?
They say that...
The dead person
Memories of the past will fade away
If I could see the images from the past again
You should be able to remember some things.
Sigh
We say that
We have to adjust ourselves a bit in this regard.
At first, it might be a bit awkward.
We are not used to it either.
But you saw us first.
But between
Where we teach you how to play guitar
Please help me find the truth.
Can we talk about our deaths?
It's considered an exchange.
Why do you want to know?
Because there are still things that we are worried about.
And then there are some unfinished matters.
And we still haven't found the answer.
And if we can make you feel less worried,
You will be free from worries and disappear, right?
That's right.
Okay, okay.
but
The cause of death is one thing.
already
What is the other thing?
It should be
That you became an artist
Hey, so we have to be together for a long time, right?
but
we
I'm not that good at playing.
this
Stop looking down on yourself
There's a whole person here.
can
We also
I will do my best to be the best.
already...
Why you?
So you want us to be artists?
What do you think we think of you?
It's a bit strange.
Are you crazy?
I really want you to be an artist.
stop
kid
Well, we want to be artists.
but...
We didn't have a chance to do it.
Because if you are successful,
It is also our success.
already
Why...
Can we even see you?
So... do other people agree?
If other people see the performance, then...
This means that you are no different from a normal person.
Xia
Come quickly and help your mother prepare the food, my child.
Mom called already.
Xia
Yes, Mom.
I'm leaving now.
Stay here, don't go anywhere.
Yes, where do you want me to go?
We have to stay with the guitar.
Okay, that's it. Let's go eat.
But wait a minute.
But if you have to be on the guitar
already...
Can you make the guitar walk by itself?
So that we don't have to carry it.
So we won't have to carry it.
We are joking.
just...
You keep reminding us
Just hide the guitar so mom doesn't see it.
okay
Then let's go.
Don't go anywhere. Don't be naughty.
Xia
What's wrong, son?
Is the food not delicious, son?
Oh, the food my mother makes is the most delicious.
We are over-praising our mother.
Mom,
Is anything up?
Does Mom believe in these mystical things?
Mom, I think it might actually exist, my child.
But it depends on whether we see it or not.
If the minds communicate with each other
We may meet
Or you can see it, son.
already...
If one day Mom really sees it
What will mom do?
If mom can see it?
Mom probably won't do anything, son.
Because if he comes in a good way
We don't need to chase him away, son.
As he said.
Good people are protected by ghosts.
Good people are not protected by monks?
It's a child's idiom.
But anyway
Ghosts and humans cannot coexist.
Everyone walks their own path, without disturbing each other.
Happiness or suffering depends on the karma you do, my child.
amen
Hey, this is us?
When my mother spoke seriously, I acted like I was joking.
But...
Ask this template
Or...
Brother Tham greeted me with a story.
really?
But
Have you ever felt hungry?
No, no.
I just felt like eating.
But I don't feel hungry at all.
Wow!
already...
before
Have you been playing guitar all along?
yes yes
And no one has ever seen you before?
That is, we never show ourselves to anyone.
Because no one has ever held a guitar before.
oh
Are you saying we hit the jackpot?
I think it's good luck.
You will have someone to teach you how to play the guitar.
Is it lucky that I saw a ghost?
What are you complaining about?
Oh, no, nothing.
So why do you want to be an artist?
Us?
I'm not sure either.
It's a feeling that we can't describe.
When we see our favorite artists on stage
We would like to be up there too.
I want to make music.
And many people love us.
That's good.
You still have a chance.
There is still time to make it happen.
And we believe that you will definitely succeed.
Okay, I guess I'll have to try it first.
But thank you for giving us more encouragement.
Let's just say I have to go to sleep.
I don't know if you'll sleep or not.
But we will sleep.
Are you sleeping yet?
Si Luk
Talking to someone is fun.
Wow, when I talk to my mom, she's not like this at all.
Go to sleep, child. It's late.
Yes, Mom. I'm going to sleep now.
Can I sleep here next to you?
It's better than putting a guitar down instead.
By the way, how old are you?
Probably around 20-21 years old.
Then let's be friends.
Be my brother.
Because we die, our age remains the same.
So you mean to say that when you die, your lifespan is the same as if you were stuffed?
How long has it been?
Can I ask?
It should be about 2 years.
2 years like that. Now I'm 22-23 years old, right?
I'm the same age as P'Tham.
Probably so.
already...
What faculty did you study? Do you remember?
It should be journalism.
We see a vague picture.
In our room, there are pictures all over the walls.
But we can't remember where our house is.
I'm in the same faculty as Phi Tham.
Are we friends?
I think it's very late. You should rest, Sia.
What the heck? You just cut the conversation short.
Okay, I'm going to bed. I'm sleepy.
sweet dreams
Let's be honest.
Drinking alcohol doesn't taste good these days.
It's like there's always something on my mind.
What's the matter?
Hey, if you have something to say, just say it.
If there's anything bothering you, just say it.
We are friends.
It's Sia's business.
It's very bothersome.
Especially when I saw Sia walking back and forth in the club.
Very annoying
You are right.
It's very messy.
We think the guitar is broken.
Then Xia will disappear from the club.
Crying heavily
But Xia still came back.
Hey, guys calm down.
If the story of Xia is annoying to you guys,
Look at the three women looking at our table.
It's a pleasure to the eyes and ears.
Really, very cute.
Stand up now. What are you waiting for?
Let's go, let ....
Stop first.
It's not our way yet
What's wrong with you?
Aren't you guys in a hurry to leave?
All the women will disappear.
Oh, yeah. Let's go. Let's go.
you
Don't you want it?
Hey, are you guys working offline yet?
Off, who is this?
Off is Teacher Frame. Have you guys done it yet?
Done
Really? Can I have a look?
Stop it, sis. Slap her bald head.
Oh, do it yourself, man.
Whatever, we just want to see it as a guideline.
Who would copy you? Oh dear.
We can do just this. Oh, it's just a little bit.
Hey Liu
Those guys
When I saw your face, I lost all my temper.
I don't like them at all.
Actually, I don't like acting like this.
Talking all day long
Xia
You go with them, you have to be careful.
We don't want you anywhere near them.
But you chose your dream.
We still support you.
True, if you get bullied by them again
Tell us.
We'll send Liu over.
Wow, at first you said it like you were helping a friend.
In short, throw it to us.
Oh, come on, thank you guys so much.
What time?
Where are you rushing to?
The teacher will check the roll call now.
Hey, I got free milk too.
Whose milk is this?
no
It's like the vending machine is stuck.
And the woman in front was in a hurry.
The cabinet didn't stay there long before he walked away.
Hey, so you just picked it up, Type?
Wow, look at his heart.
A woman?
Is it cute?
It's normal. We saw it from the corner of our eyes.
Hey, if you say that, you're trying to block Q, right?
Do you want it?
Crazy nonsense
Just kidding
Hey, hey, you guys.
Look at the Xia women.
It's not just Liu.
There are others.
very cute
I don't know if this group was selected or not.
What Q said is true.
Every woman, your style too.
But men are also a problem.
You see, as an art student like this, he's very handsome.
In that case, a young lady like you has to meet us.
Hey, it's full of people.
Oh, Type, aren't you interested in this group?
Not only Xia, we also don't like his face.
And then there's Liu too.
We are bored.
That's great.
We will be able to see it alone.
No need to compete with anyone.
The sky is very white today.
Where is it white?
It looks like it's going to rain. The sky is white.
C, you don't know anything.
oh
Oh, you're here, Sia.
Hey guys
Let's play basketball.
That's right, my friend. The women are all waiting.
Okay, let's go guys.
It's okay, Sia.
That's just the way they are.
do not think very much
I'm okay, Brother Tham.
It's okay, I understand.
Then come practice with me. I'll help you watch.
okay
come
What are you guys doing? Why are you taking so long?
Wait a minute, this
Turn around and I'll give you a shot.
It's okay, friend. I can inject it myself.
oh
this
What kind of spray is this?
Puree's
We tried it and it was good.
Acne problems on the back caused by sweat
When exercising, it all disappears.
Once we use it
The back is white and smooth like this.
Huh?
Then, after we finish playing basketball.
Can we try it?
Hey, let's go play basketball!
Hey, wait for us.
I'm going now.
Type A
Hey, it's not coming down.
One more round, another ball goes.
Let's go
Hey Ho Type
excuse me
Did you get hit by her just now?
Is this yours?
Are you okay?
It just rolled on the floor and didn't get hit at all.
It's fine if it's okay.
Now that I have my basketball back, I can go back to playing.
What are you standing there looking at?
I don't even want to look at you. Why would I be in trouble?
It's not a big deal.
You have a big mouth. Live until you're old.
Let's go love
Love, is your name Love?
We type
Nice to be loved
Hoy!
pleased to meet
That's the group of friends we're looking at.
The real person is cuter than the picture.
We like
Yes!
How do you play basketball to find your soulmate?
We booked, glad to love you.
Hey, nice to meet you.
What are you doing with your hands?
I love it.
Nice to meet you. Hey, nice to meet you.
Let's go, love. These guys are annoying.
Are you lonely practicing alone?
I was shocked. You came without any warning.
How was it? Where did you practice just now? Come, let me help you take a look.
Hey, didn't you see me standing there watching?
But we still can't play here.
oh
Then try the index finger, first fade.
okay
And then just keep going up.
Hold the C chord, okay.
try
Wow!
How are you?
Much easier to play
This guy
You're equally good.
certain
Go ahead and play.
Why did Xia stop playing?
Where are you going, Xia?
Quietly
Xia
What are you looking for? Someone will see.
Brother Tham has gone back. No one will come in now.
Nixia, what are you looking for? Can you tell me yet?
Sigh
We will help you find your story.
In case you find any information
At least you were a member of the club.
So will it really happen?
Oh, why is it locked?
Xia
If it doesn't open, then never mind.
Hey, it's okay.
We will help you find the truth.
Let's take it slow.
Oh, thank you, Sia.
How about this? Would you mind...
Oh... Blue
oh
yes
Xia hasn't come back yet? Is something wrong?
Brother Tham is...
My brother said that he would like us to lock the room.
But I forgot to leave the key with us.
I thought you had already gone back, so I came back myself.
But... why haven't you come back yet?
Uh huh
Oh, I'm just about to go back.
But I got too carried away practicing the guitar.
Then, would you like to go back with me?
Oh, it's okay, Brother Tham.
I'm sorry. I'll go back myself.
Is that so?
yes
okay
Is there anything I can help you with?
No, it's very easy.
Look flustered
Oh, it's nothing, Brother Tham.
It's normal.
okay
I'll go first.
bye bye
Come back safely.
Yes, hello.
Hello, Brother Tham.
yes
Hey, watch out. Are you okay?
Okay, that's fine.
Then Love will go first. Bye-bye.
Hey, wait a minute.
Today's story
What's the story today?
Story of the evening
What's the matter?
Liu
Tell me, Love is waiting to hear you.
Story...Type
Are you okay?
What does that mean?
Well, it's a basketball...
It's not love, it's fine, it's fine.
Are you sure?
Sure, then I'll go with Love first.
bye bye
See you.
Hey, wait!
It's time to go home. It's getting late.
meet tomorrow
Don't be swayed by type.
No matter how long
I can't wait any longer.
I miss you so much that I want to hug you every day.
I want to tell you I love you every morning and before I sleep.
Being together and doing things together
It's good...
But once a week is not enough.
Very good, Siah. Now you can play.
Would you like to try playing another song?
Where? What song?
Then can we play?
Give it a listen first.
What song?
Experimental Song
can
I feel like I've heard this song before. Is it popular?
Try opening it first.
Whose is this?
Twinplus +
Why does this name sound so familiar?
Of Twinplus +
Twinplus + ?
yes
Twinplus +
Is this it?
This is it.
What chords are there?
Try playing this chord.
Bm
What's the next chord?
A
Xia, mom brought some warm milk for you.
Xia
Uh...
It's nothing, Mom.
Mom doesn't see it.
It's Xia...
Xia is reading a book.
That's good, son.
Mom brought me some milk.
Oh, Mom can put it on the table first.
Xia would like to sit down and rest for a while.
What did you do? You look tired.
Don't overdo it, dear. Mommy is worried.
Yes, Mom.
It's late. Mommy's going to bed now, dear.
Okay, good night, Mom.
Good night, my child.
mother