(All characters, organizations, places, cases, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
(Episode 13)
Hello.
Where's Han Su?
He went down to the treatment room.
Thank you.
What is it?
What did you want to tell me about Su Ah?
What happened to her? Did she wake up?
You stabbed her to kill her. Why do you care?
You confessed in court that you stabbed her.
Answer me. Did Su Ah wake up?
Figures.
What's wrong with me?
I tried to find out something I didn't need to know.
Whether you stabbed her or not,
the conclusion is the same.
Did she wake up or not?
Han Su!
Han Su, is that you?
Who are you?
Why are you here with Han Su?
I'm a detective. I was in charge of his case.
But who are you?
I'm his classmate.
You are?
Then can you excuse us for a minute?
We still need to talk.
Must it be right now?
The nurse said he still needs his rest.
It's very important for the case.
Can you wait downstairs? We'll be done soon.
Did you think it would be over if you killed him like Lee Tae Seok?
Don't do anything stupid and leave.
I'll take care of things here.
Please just leave for today.
Please, officer.
I'll take Han Su to his room.
Is that all right?
Yes. I want to rest.
Sure.
Okay.
Are you okay?
How did you know...
I was here?
I've been waiting for you to wake up.
I needed to tell you something.
And what's that?
Is it about Su Ah?
Did you know?
What happened...
to Su Ah?
It wasn't long after...
that happened to you.
I'm sorry. I really didn't want...
to tell you this.
No.
Su Ah...
couldn't have died.
It's a lie, right? You're lying to me.
Right? She didn't die.
She's alive!
Han Su.
I... I couldn't protect her.
That's why she...
(Hospital room)
Where are you?
The roof.
Han Su!
Beom Jin.
You're late,
Mr. Lawyer.
What did you do to Han Su?
I simply told him the truth.
Tell me the truth.
What did you do to him?
Get lost!
Leave now.
I don't need a lawyer like you anymore,
so leave.
Han Su.
Beom Jin.
Take me to my room.
Okay.
Stay out...
of my life.
Or I'll kill you.
Stop right there!
Tell me, Han Su.
What did you want to tell me that day?
From whom did Su Ah want to escape so badly?
Let's go.
Tell me.
Han Su!
Remember what I said earlier.
We shouldn't let people kill Su Ah twice.
You are the only person who can protect Su Ah.
Okay.
I didn't ask you to do that, did I?
I'm sorry, sir.
By the way...
Did you think it would be over if you killed him like Lee Tae Seok?
Don't do anything stupid and leave.
I'll take care of things here.
Is there anything else you want to say?
No, sir.
I promise it won't happen again.
Don't contact me for the time being and just wait.
I'm afraid you can't see him now.
He just woke up, and he's done too much already.
If what happened today happens again,
it can be seriously dangerous. So please be careful.
Okay.
- Mu Hyeok. - Mr. Gi.
Wait.
What happened?
Yu Beom Jin...
came to the hospital to see Han Su.
What?
Yu Beom Jin?
Won Suk.
Can we check the video footages?
Actually, I set up some cameras in Han Su's ward...
and the hospital corridors just in case.
Lieutenant Oh?
He's taking Han Su somewhere.
It's the rooftop.
Rooftop?
Why rooftop, of all places?
Yu Beom Jin.
Lieutenant Oh...
came down alone.
Yu Beom Jin must have stopped Lieutenant Oh...
and said something to Han Su.
Something important...
that can keep Han Su's mouth shut.
It's a lie, right? You're lying to me.
Right? She didn't die.
She's alive!
Han Su.
I... I couldn't protect her.
That's why she...
Others might not know it, but I know...
that you didn't kill Su Ah.
Byung Ho told me everything.
That he came to see you...
because Lee Tae Seok told him to.
Lee Tae Seok, that punk...
Where is he now?
Where is he?
Calm down.
He got punished too.
"Punished"?
He was found...
hanged in the school.
Lee Tae Seok...
killed himself?
His will was found too.
He has paid for what he did.
He has paid for killing Su Ah...
and framing you as a murderer.
The media has finally quieted down, but since Lee Tae Seok's death,
it started talking about Su Ah again.
Saying he was Su Ah's sponsor.
Do you remember...
the attorney that revealed your pictures at court...
and insisted there had been men that frequented her place?
Gi Mu Hyeok,
the attorney.
You risked your life to keep Su Ah's secret,
but he revealed everything.
At this rate,
people will...
defame her, saying she's immoral.
No way.
I will never let that happen.
Never.
But...
why are you...
doing this for me?
Because I liked her too.
I have always liked her ever since she transferred to our school.
That's why...
I wanted to protect her, just like you did.
We must protect her.
Once her relationship with Lee Tae Seok is revealed,
Su Ah will remain as an immoral working girl...
in people's memories.
Then what should I do?
Take back what you confessed at court...
and say you saw Lee Tae Seok escape from the window of Su Ah's place.
Say that I saw Lee Tae Seok?
Then it will be all over.
Lee Tae Seok is dead...
and people are only interested in his sin right now.
It will clear you of the false charge too.
I know how you feel.
In order to protect Su Ah from people attacking her,
you went to prison and even risked your life.
This is the only way to protect Su Ah.
And you are the only person who can do it.
You're late.
I was meeting a friend.
A friend...
that had been away for long came back.
What did you do with your friend?
We just...
talked.
We talked about his ex-girlfriend.
Don't do anything stupid.
"Stupid"?
Do you like this painting?
"Camouflaged Selves".
A camouflaged object may have camouflaged itself...
Or it can be camouflaged by someone else.
The woman with hollow eyes stares at her glamorous self...
and casts endless questions on her own identity.
It's an interesting description.
Identity.
Do you think that's something worth thinking over?
What people see and believe is...
my real self and my real identity.
Whether it's camouflaged or not is not important.
If you can't tell the difference,
it's not a camouflage anymore.
What's this painting?
It's cool for sure, but it could be scary to look at in the dark.
Are you okay with it?
Why? I love it.
So what's the painting about?
Does it mean something?
There's a way to figure it out.
Pop art.
Camouflaged Selves series.
It's a painting about identity.
It expresses the struggles between the camouflaged self...
seen by other people and the real self.
Identity? I see.
Don't act like you know.
Do you even think about such things?
You have a death wish, don't you?
What's there to think about?
What people see and believe is my real identity.
If you can't tell the difference,
it's not a camouflage anymore, right?
Look at you, Su Ah.
Su Ah.
Yes?
What makes you think that?
Does it sound strange?
Actually, that's what I heard from another person.
It's you, not me,
who's going around and doing stupid things.
(Donghan Hospital)
Su Ah.
What am I going to do now?
On the verge of passing the national petition...
for a reinvestigation of the Townhouse murder case,
Mr. Kim, the murder suspect, has recovered consciousness.
Since the Townhouse murder case has become...
such a big issue due to growing suspicions and speculations,
the news of the suspect's recovery...
is drawing public attention...
to the resumption of the trial.
Meanwhile, the focus is now on whether Songha Law Firm,
which has been accused of having a plea bargain with the prosecution,
will take the case or not and also on what defense strategy...
they will choose.
(President Lee Do Jin)
Gosh, why now of all times?
Submit a resignation letter to the court.
Tell them we're resigning from Kim Han Su's case.
Yes, sir.
Convict him no matter what.
Whatever it takes, convict him of the murder of Jung Su Ah.
And give him a maximum sentence.
Otherwise, we'll have to take all the responsibility...
for his attempted suicide.
But right now, public opinion is...
What? Public opinion?
Is public opinion law?
You know I've been looking after you despite your incompetence.
How dare you whine at me?
- I'm sorry, sir. - Get yourself together.
- Got that? - Yes.
Last night, Mr. Gi came to the academy.
Why?
He's been asking what I was doing on the night of Su Ah's murder.
Last night, he took me near Su Ah's house...
and showed strange things.
Strange things?
That was...
a video of you getting out of a taxi.
And he said that was near Su Ah's house.
As if that means something.
He probably thinks you killed Su Ah.
We were watching a movie back then.
But he didn't believe that too.
Did you tell him we were watching a movie together on that day?
I did.
I said it was total nonsense since we were together back then.
Don't worry.
I didn't say you went out.
How did you know?
Sorry?
The fact that I went out.
Have you known all along?
I woke up once in the middle.
You didn't come back for a long time,
so I got back to sleep.
(No Caller ID)
Hello?
Who's this? Are you there?
You're trash.
What's wrong?
What?
I guess it's just a prank call.
(No Caller ID)
Who's this? I'm going to call the police.
Get your act together.
Or I'll cut your face.
(No Caller ID)
Tae Ra, what's wrong? Are you okay?
Beom Jin.
What do I do?
I think people found out everything.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
From now on, don't pick up calls from unknown numbers.
(Writing a post: Han Tae Ra's personal information)
I'll make you so miserable.
I've called Han Tae Ra. She has a pretty voice after all.
A voice scrambler is awesome.
She's such a witch.
She was really mean.
(Teaching License)
How could you think of forging a teaching license?
In my 20 years of teaching experience,
this is the most absurd thing that ever happened to me.
Ever.
Pack your things quietly and go.
Then I won't report you.
Since we've already got enough trouble,
I don't want to make a big deal. You should be thankful.
I don't want to.
- You don't? - Yes.
Why? How come?
Look at how you said that without batting an eye.
You are so brazen.
I may be brazen,
but I don't hold a candle to you.
What?
Mr. Gi.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm in a mood for coffee. Make me a cup.
(Voice file)
This smells nice.
A handsome man makes even instant coffee taste good.
Here.
What is that? When did you...
The most basic step to take in case of sexual harassment...
is to record everything and everywhere at all times.
I recorded all of our conversations...
in the pantry.
What?
What...
How could you do something so despicable...
You did much more despicable things.
Think of the times.
How could such improper things come out of your mouth all the time?
You took it all.
You played along, and now...
I was...
playing along because you are my superior.
So? Should I make this public...
and we both leave here?
Or should we just keep one secret each?
Thanks to you, I've lost all of my positions,
so I'll use my class times very freely.
If you're in the mood for coffee in the future,
make it yourself.
Like this.
What will happen now?
Because of the articles and the video,
everyone knows that it's our school now.
I'm so afraid the police may barge in at any moment,
that I can't teach my class.
And Ms. Jun is telling us to give an academic achievement award.
She's a total psycho.
Hang in there.
Things are headed in the right direction at least.
That's true.
That's right. I heard Han Su woke up. Did you see him?
No. He still needs his rest.
Still, he's alert...
and much better than I had feared.
That's a relief. I know you were very worried.
How is that a relief?
It'll just be a headache going forward.
The trial will start up again.
Plus, after what happened to Su Ah...
That's true.
It isn't over just because he woke up.
Townhouse...
murder case.
Hey.
This isn't your room.
How dare you come in here?
This is a school. No one owns any room.
Are you a dog?
Do you mark your territory here and there?
What? Why you... I'll kick you out.
Don't you think it's too late to kick me out?
Give it a rest. I'm not being nice because I like you.
Also, speak respectfully.
I'm more than a decade older than you, you rude punk.
(Townhouse murder case)
("The Suspect of the Townhouse Murder Points out Another Suspect")
Mr. Kim, the suspect of the Townhouse Murder,
which the entire nation has been following closely,
has retracted a part of his confession made in court.
What? Is that about Han Su?
The police state...
that Mr. Kim asserts he saw Mr. Lee,
general manager of a high school,
who was found dead last month, at the scene of the crime.
What gibberish is that? He saw Butler Lee?
Did he lose his mind from being in a coma?
Thus, the police are considering all possibilities...
and will reinvestigate the case accordingly.
(Donghan Hospital)
(Patient: Kim Han Su)
Explain in more detail.
You're saying you saw Lee Tae Seok flee from the scene, right?
Yes.
What was the situation? Explain from the beginning.
From the moment you walked into the victim's home.
Su Ah.
Su Ah, are you in there?
Stop right there!
Su Ah.
He fled out the back door.
The back door?
I was too worried about Su Ah to run after him.
But I clearly saw Lee Tae Seok...
run out the back door.
(At victim's house,)
(he saw Lee Tae Seok run out the back door.)
Why did you try to kill yourself?
Lee Tae Seok used a classmate...
to threaten him and tell him to kill himself.
So he's the culprit.
If he didn't stab Jung Su Ah,
he had no reason to threaten him to kill himself.
Yes. Kim Han Su was the sole witness,
so he tried to eliminate him.
Good work.
Okay. In that case, get the statement...
of the kid who brought Jung Su Ah's picture to Kim Han Su.
I will.
Are you here to see the suspect?
And you are?
I'm the detective in charge of the case.
You're the lawyer Gi Mu Hyeok, right?
What brings you here?
You're not a lawyer anymore, from what I've heard.
I'll be returning to work soon...
and I'll represent Kim Han Su again.
Is that right?
Yes.
That's why I'd like to see him.
Sure. Go ahead.
Let him in. He's here to see him.
Yes, sir.
Why did you come again?
I said I don't need you to defend me anymore.
Did you really see him?
Did you really see Lee Tae Seok...
in Su Ah's place?
Get out.
I don't have anything to say. So get lost.
Take him out!
(Police)
You must leave now.
Okay.
What else are you hiding?
Why don't you tell me the truth now?
What was the thing...
you tried to tell me that day?
Get out!
If you don't leave right now, we will have to arrest you.
Kim Han Su.
- Kim Han Su! - I warned you.
Stay out...
of my life.
Or...
I will really kill you.
Han Su.
Get lost!
Goodness. What are you going to do now?
Do you think...
you can be his attorney again?
From now on,
don't you think of seeing the suspect again.
What if he loses his mind and passes out...
after seeing you?
That will put us in a difficult position.
Nurse?
Yes, sir.
If anything happens by letting him see the patient again,
the hospital will need to take full responsibility for it.
I see.
Okay. Thank you.
(President Lee Do Jin)
About the offer...
I'll come to you to give my answer.
(Memorandum of Agreement)
What is this?
It's a memorandum...
that says even after you get your license back,
you will not defend Kim Han Su's case...
and will not let out any information regarding it.
Lest it will be legally misinterpreted,
I reviewed the content myself,
so all you need to do is to sign on it.
- What are you waiting for? - Sir.
Do you by any chance remember what you said to me...
when you kicked me out of this firm?
You said I was a cog.
A cog that works...
stuck in the system you made.
You're nothing more than a cog.
You're stuck in a system I created, and you must turn...
until your teeth wear out.
You're just a cog.
- That's... - I'm afraid you have to...
be my cog now.
Me?
Your cog?
I feel hurt, President Lee.
This was the only way I could talk to you.
What is it? After cutting Yang Sang Bae off,
couldn't you bring yourself to face me?
Will you shut it?
Who are you trying to involve me with?
So you want to pretend to be innocent?
Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office!
Assistant Prosecutor General Yang Sang Bae...
at Criminal Department Three.
It was your order, President Lee Do Jin!
What do you say?
Should we keep listening to it...
or tell him to get out?
Who do you think you are to say that?
Get out.
- Excuse me, sir? - You heard me.
Yes, sir.
Now, shall we listen to the rest?
Watch what you say in front of Ms. Woo.
Give me something that will keep my mouth shut.
It was what you wanted, President Lee.
You wanted to frame Han Su for everything about Su Ah.
I think we have listened enough.
Shall we get back to our conversation?
Do you think you can threaten me with the illegal recording?
Of course I do.
The suspicions on the plea bargain between you and Yang Sang Bae are...
spread through the media already.
Now, with just a drop of oil, which is your voice,
the public will be outraged.
Tell me what you want.
I like that you are quick-witted.
For now, I want you to give my license back to me.
As soon as possible.
- I will. - And I want Songha...
to keep dealing with Kim Han Su's case.
Look on the bright side.
If Songha manages to prove Han Su's innocence,
it'll help eliminate the suspicions on the plea bargain...
with Yang Sang Bae.
Okay. Is that all?
One more thing.
I want Songha to pay for all the costs.
Our client, Kim Han Su, has no money...
and I'm quite short of money too these days.
Then...
(Memorandum of Agreement)
Let's forget about this.
Let's make a new one.
I'm glad...
you got your license back...
and you can keep defending Han Su.
The problem is...
Han Su is refusing it.
No matter how willing I am, if the client doesn't want it,
there's nothing I can do.
What could Beom Jin have possibly said to him?
The bigger problem is...
that Han Su stated to the police...
that he saw Lee Tae Seok at the crime scene.
He made a false confession at court last time.
If his statement turns out to be false again,
people won't believe him anymore, no matter what he says.
Do you think Beom Jin calculated that too?
I won't be surprised if he did.
Covering it up with Lee Tae Seok's death...
would keep his father, Yu Yang Ki safe,
and even if his statement turns out to be false,
it will be only Han Su that will be cornered.
Either way, it doesn't harm Yu Beom Jin.
Then what do we do now?
First,
since I can't visit him now, I want you to meet Han Su.
We need to hear from him what he's hiding about the incident...
even though he knows it.
Okay.
Won Suk, did you check the theater?
Yes, I did.
Hey.
All right.
Now let's find out...
what is the thing that Han Su is hiding...
and if Yu Beom Jin really has an alibi.
Hey. What's wrong with you?
Do you not know it...
or do you pretend not to know it?
Listen.
Whether Lee Tae Seok is the murderer or not,
it has nothing to do with us.
You...
You said you'd give me an incentive.
Getting your license back...
and proving Kim Han Su's innocence. Aren't they all we need to do?
No.
We need to find out who the real killer is.
Exactly. Why should we?
Too many people died and got hurt...
for it to end with just Han Su being acquitted.
Su Ah, Han Su,
and Hyun Jung.
If everything gets buried with Lee Tae Seok's death,
the killer will create a second Su Ah and Han Su.
He'll have no fear now.
Since he wasn't punished at all after committing a heinous crime.
We must prevent that from happening.
Are you...
the same Mu Hyeok I used to know?
(Yu Beom Jin)
That's it for today.
If there's a discrepancy with your grade, come to my office.
Okay.
Good work.
Thank you.
The literature midterm was so difficult.
I wonder where I'll place.
If a certain someone came in first,
it would mean she has zero shame.
(Tae Ra)
I can't take it.
I really want to just die.
It's too hard to be in the classroom.
I feel like I'll go crazy.
Just today.
I'll talk to them again tomorrow during the joint class.
Would I be at peace...
if I admit it all?
People I don't know are calling me,
threatening, and cursing at me.
It's so scary.
I want to at least be at peace.
People don't stay interested in other people's lives for that long.
Once we graduate, let's go study abroad together.
Then everyone will forget.
Do you want to go somewhere after school?
Let's eat yummy food and go somewhere pretty.
I'll make your depression disappear.
Okay.
Thanks.
- What is it? - I warned you...
not to trust your boyfriend.
Did you decide to stick next to her and watch her closely...
so she can't talk about you?
Leave Tae Ra alone.
Talk to me if you need to.
I'm shocked.
You really sound like you're trying to protect her.
How did you silence Han Su?
Did you use Su Ah?
You're the one that should stop using Han Su.
Using him?
Me?
You don't care what he wants.
You just want to win in court.
I call that using him.
At least...
I try to give him what he wants.
Unlike you.
Let's go.
What he wants.
There are two theaters near Su Ah's place.
One of them...
was rented out for a screening.
Then that can't be it.
If he were going to sneak out, he wouldn't have picked a screening.
That's right. Then this is it.
The theater in a mall.
Han Su was arrested...
around 8:30pm Friday night.
A movie at the same time today as back then is...
(Screening schedule)
It starts at 7:55pm and ends at 10:10pm.
Theater four.
Today is Friday,
so it's a similar time, too.
Why do you look so sick?
You already look old, but you look jaundiced.
Your liver must have gotten worse.
This is my normal skin tone.
This is all your fault.
It's because you make me work night and day.
Okay. Sorry.
In light of that, let's go rest.
Go buy the tickets.
Rest?
I got excited for a minute.
Where's the box office?
(Donghan Hospital)
I'm so glad...
you're awake.
Sorry...
for worrying you.
Then recover quickly.
That way, you can run in the schoolyard again...
and practice for the physical fitness test.
When you were asleep,
I brought Su Ah's things from the orphanage.
This is her diary.
She wrote a lot about you.
(They served sausages today at school.)
(I decided to tutor Han Su.)
Early tomorrow morning,
my new parents will come get me.
I'm happy to have Mom and Dad,
but I'm worried about Han Su.
I'm not sure if this silly boy will be all right when I'm gone.
When I grow up...
and meet him again,
I will protect Han Su then.
(I will protect Han Su then.)
Su Ah...
wanted to protect you too.
She felt the same way you did.
Just as you wanted to become a gym teacher...
to live in the same world as her,
maybe she was doing the same.
Su Ah...
also...
Han Su.
I know it's hard for you,
but can you tell me...
what Su Ah was like?
Su Ah...
was abandoned twice.
First by her birth parents,
and second by those jerks...
who adopted her.
Thank you.
More scallions, please.
Scallions? Okay.
Her adoptive parents were finally able to have kids.
Once their baby was born,
they treated Su Ah like a piece of baggage.
They emigrated with just their biological child,
and after Su Ah finished middle school,
they stopped supporting her financially too.
(Part-time job)
(Recruitment)
She couldn't pay her tuition,
so she dropped out of high school without completing a single year.
After then,
she worked multiple jobs to make money for tuition.
Our research facility is the only one...
in all of Korea conducting this study.
Please show us your support.
- Please. - Okay.
I'd like to thank Pastor Kim for inviting me to speak...
The movie started 20 minutes ago.
I need your support and belief...
It takes about five minutes to leave the theater...
and walk to the taxi stand.
Get in a cab at the taxi stand and leave.
(Vacant)
Thank you.
It takes 15 minutes to get here from the theater.
20 minutes.
How long did it take from here?
Am I too early?
Tae Ra!
Here, take this.
Is this for me?
Yes. A boy said...
to give it to the prettiest girl here.
Really? Thanks for giving it to me.
My pleasure.
Enjoy your date. Bye.
He said he'd make my depression disappear.
Did he mean this balloon?
A note?
(Come to the rooftop. I've prepared something.)
"Come to the rooftop. I've prepared something."
What is it?
He must have prepared a lot to cheer me up.
(5G Building)
40 minutes.
You called a cab, right?
Yes.
I'm sure he didn't leave any evidence.
Oh my gosh.
That scared me.
Are you awake?
Hey.
How is the movie?
Watch for yourself.
The climax is about to start.
It took 57 minutes.
A movie runs for about two hours,
so there's plenty of time to commit the crime...
and get back.
Then was it really Yu Beom Jin?
But...
there's no way to prove it.
Why not?
There's Tae Ra, who watched the movie with him.
If he left for an hour for whatever reason,
there's no way she didn't notice.
Then...
Only Tae Ra can attest to it.
That Yu Beom Jin...
had no alibi whatsoever that day when Su Ah...
was stabbed.
(Class of Lies / Mr. Temporary)
(I will protect Han Su then.)
Beom Jin killed her.
He faked it as a suicide and killed her.
It's over.
Tell it to me straight!
If you had done as I said, Tae Ra wouldn't have died.
Beom Jin!
We must stop him.
I don't know how far he'll go.
He manipulated the people around him...
and created situations that are most favorable to him.
We have to make changes.
I saw the man Su Ah was seeing.
How long will you turn a blind eye and just watch?
Han Su!
He may be thorough, but he must have missed something.
Maybe Su Ah left behind evidence.
He made a mistake.
Beom Jim.
It's nice to meet you.
(I will protect the people.)
Assemblyman Yu Yang Ki.
Thank you for your time.
In return, I will tell you...
who murdered Su Ah.