(All characters, organizations, places, cases, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
(Episode 15)
"Camouflaged Selves".
What a great painting.
It suits well with you too.
Do you know who killed her?
So, do you admit you were seeing her?
Answer me.
Who killed her?
But first,
shouldn't you ask how I found out about it?
Shouldn't that come first?
I found out about it through your son.
He's very interested in his father.
Interested enough to install a spy app on your phone...
and monitor you.
He was using that to look at everything on your phone.
Do you get it now?
Your son knew that you were seeing a girl...
who went to his high school. He knew everything.
If you don't trust me, why don't you check now?
If he saw the texts that you and I exchanged,
wouldn't he show up here?
Because he'll be very curious about our conversation.
I'm warning you.
Don't try anything funny.
Answer me.
Who killed her?
I thought I made myself clear, but you still don't get it.
Then...
why don't you see for yourself?
Do you see it now?
Congratulations.
You've found out one more thing about your son.
You...
I'm disappointed.
Father.
You're pretty good,
Attorney Gi Mu Hyeok.
You came sooner than I expected.
We didn't get to the heart of our conversation yet.
What do you plan to do?
What else?
I planned to tell him about Su Ah's killer,
and you showed up.
Thanks to you, I don't need to bother with a long explanation.
Congressman Yu.
Su Ah's killer came...
here...
right now.
Gi Mu Hyeok.
What are you doing now?
Your father didn't seem to know much about his son,
I just tried to give you two a chance to talk to each other.
What's there to be so upset about?
You're acting as if you met someone you're not supposed to meet.
You'd better watch what you say.
If I don't watch what I say,
will you kill me like you killed Lee Tae Seok?
Or will you hit me from the back...
like you did to Prosecutor Cha Hyun Jung?
Bang.
Like this?
What's the point of killing everyone to shut their mouths?
Can you kill your son too?
Stop talking nonsense...
and get lost.
I was going to anyway.
I'm sure the father and son will have a lot to ask each other.
I hope you have a good time.
Gosh.
How did it go?
I poured a lot of oil between them.
So hopefully there will be a big fire.
Yes!
Mu Hyeok, are you sure about this? Aren't you being too reckless?
If we don't gamble this much, we could die.
Is it ready?
- Let's go. - Okay.
Did you really...
kill that girl?
That's right.
I did it.
Why? Why on earth did you do that?
What if I didn't?
What do you think would've happened if I didn't kill her?
A politician who dated a girl from his son's school.
Even if he was lucky enough not to get caught and become the President,
what next?
The more power you gained,
the more Lee Tae Seok would have wanted things from you.
After Woonam University, who knows what he would have asked for next?
Do you think he would have kept his mouth shut about Jung Su Ah?
If he wanted, he could have asked you for money and everything.
So you did that...
for me?
I can't keep listening to your nonsense.
I said I killed her for my own sake, not for you.
For my future!
Do you get it?
Why? Now that you know your son is a murderer, are you worried?
Come clean with me. You were more worried...
about yourself than me, right?
I did too.
Once this gets out,
I will be pointed at and stigmatized as a son...
of a congressman who was dating his son's friend.
So why?
Why do I have to lose face because of you?
Still,
how could you kill a person because of that?
You killed Lee Tae Seok too.
For your own sake.
"No matter when and where you are,"
"don't forget that you are my son."
No matter when and where you are,
don't forget that you are my son.
It's for my good...
and it will be eventually for your good too.
You should have kept that in mind too.
No matter when and where you are,
you shouldn't forget that you are my father.
You know how critical it is for politicians to have failed kids.
You don't have time to do this to me now.
Stop the attorney before he makes problems. That's your job.
If you want to keep that lame congressman position.
Do you understand?
(Post office)
Let me take a look.
May 3, 2019.
A post that doesn't have a sender's address...
Here it is.
(Delivered)
It says it's delivered.
We went to the orphanage,
but they said they didn't get it.
Could it be...
Actually, there's another orphanage near that one.
Sometimes, some posts get misdelivered.
Where is it?
This looks serious.
Are you confident?
Don't worry.
Could you check Lee Tae Seok's credit card record?
Check if there's anything suspicious.
Why?
He was dealing with a big shot like Yu Yang Ki.
He must have had a plan B.
Find something that's not ambiguous like a notepad.
There must be something solid than that.
Okay.
I'm going.
(Songha Law Firm)
(Press Conference to Reveal the Truth of the Townhouse Murder)
You came on time.
(Yu Yang Ki, Suho Party)
(Daily Weather, a spy app)
Are you telling me...
to become Congressman Yu's enemy?
Why not?
Are you afraid?
Even if you hold onto him, nothing good will come out of it.
Do the math.
What would be the best choice for Songha Law Firm?
The answer is already out there.
This is your chance...
to cut ties with Congressman Yu.
Then I'll let go of the past...
and move on.
Fine.
What can I do for you?
First of all,
I'd like to use your law firm's name.
Everything I say and do from now on...
will represent Songha Law Firm's official stance.
(Nullification of disciplinary action upon Gi Mu Hyeok)
Will you be the Head of Crisis Management...
at Songha Law Firm once again?
Is that really necessary?
Once this matter is settled,
I hope we don't see each other again.
Whether personally...
or in court.
Attention, please.
We'll soon start the press conference...
to reveal the truth of the townhouse murder.
- Here he comes. - It's starting.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
(Press Conference to Reveal the Truth of the Townhouse Murder)
I'm Gi Mu Hyeok at Songha Law Firm. I'm the attorney...
of suspect Kim Han Su from the townhouse murder case.
(Press Conference to Reveal the Truth of the Townhouse Murder)
I'm here today...
to tell you the truth of the incident...
and prove my client, Kim Han Su's innocence.
- What? - What's going on?
The townhouse murder case...
was fabricated...
to frame Kim Han Su.
- What? - It was fabricated?
- What is he talking about? - Really?
- What does that mean? - What?
The person behind the fabrication is...
(Press Conference to Reveal the Truth of the Townhouse Murder)
It's the Suho Party's presidential candidate,
Congressman Yu Yang Ki.
- What? - Yu Yang Ki?
- Is that true? - He fabricated the case?
Make sure no one at the office acts up.
Then I'll see to it...
that your confirmation hearing for prosecutor general goes well.
Congressman Yu.
I think you really need to see this.
The reason why he tried to terminate the case through fabrication...
is because Congressman Yu had an inappropriate relationship...
with the murder victim...
through the deceased Lee Tae Seok, General Manager of Cheonmyung High.
That little rat.
- What does that mean? - What's going on?
Excuse me.
What exactly do you mean by "inappropriate relationship"?
Do you have any evidence?
Is Congressman Yu related...
to Lee Tae Seok's death too?
- Did Congressman Yu... - Is there any evidence?
- Is this certain? - Is Congressman Yu...
- I have a question! - Please answer!
(Press Conference to Reveal the Truth of the Townhouse Murder)
- Please answer! - Say something!
Answer us.
Here are some text messages that Congressman Yu exchanged...
with General Manager Lee Tae Seok.
(Press Conference to Reveal the Truth of the Townhouse Murder)
- What's that? - Oh, my.
(Text Messages between Congressman Yu and General Manager Lee)
To take over Woonam University, Lee Tae Seok, who committed suicide,
used the models at his agency...
and offered sexual favors...
to numerous politicians, businessmen, and prosecutors.
A key player in the university takeover...
was the chairman of the Education Committee.
- That's awful. - Unbelievable.
Congressman Yu Yang Ki.
Lee Tae Seok introduced the victim to Congressman Yu,
and Congressman Yu met the victim regularly...
at her apartment in secret.
(Congressman Yu Yang Ki Met the Murder Victim at Her Apartment)
These text messages support this.
- Oh, my. - Unbelievable.
If your accusation turns out to be false,
it'll create a tremendous stir.
Can you prove the authenticity of these materials?
It's the presidential candidate registration day today.
Why are you revealing this just today?
- Please answer! - Is there more evidence?
- Why are you revealing this now? - Please answer my question!
Congressman Park is here!
- What's going on? - It's him.
I'm Gi Mu Hyeok.
Have you looked through...
the materials I sent you?
I have.
I find them quite interesting.
You can help me win the primaries?
You win an election...
by either winning more votes...
or making your opponent lose votes.
If I reveal this without enough evidence,
it might backfire on me.
Don't worry about that.
It'll be revealed by me.
What's your plan?
Songha Law Firm is holding...
a press conference tomorrow.
All I ask...
is that you show up and finish it up nicely.
Then I'll make sure...
Congressman Yu's votes go to you.
(Press Conference to Reveal the Truth of the Townhouse Murder)
First of all,
as the party leader,
I feel morally responsible...
for the current unfortunate situation...
regarding Congressman Yu Yang Ki, one of the Suho Party members.
I apologize.
I promise to thoroughly investigate...
all the suspicions regarding Congressman Yu...
on behalf of all citizens.
I cannot let someone unqualified...
represent the Suho Party...
in the presidential election.
I will do everything I can to prevent that from happening.
It's just a political maneuver.
(Press Conference against the Unfair Political Maneuver)
(We will protect the people. We will stay with the people.)
All the allegations released in the press earlier today...
have nothing to do with me and are completely false.
I, Yu Yang Ki,
have nothing to hide from the public.
Despite any negative campaigning against me,
I will finish the primaries as planned.
Also,
I will bring Attorney Gi Mu Hyeok at Songha Law Firm...
to justice...
for maliciously slandering me.
(Congressman Yu Starts Primaries by Fighting Revelations)
Go in there, and he'll die.
(Yu Beom Jin)
"Yu Beom Jin."
- What did you... - If you go in there right now,
he really will die.
Kim Han Su.
Who's Kim Han Su?
I heard back at the rooftop.
"Do you want to end up like Han Su?"
It may be an interesting story to some, but it's a wound...
to us.
If the teacher that heard about the photos from C...
tries to steal A's photos...
to find out the truth and fails,
how will the teacher be punished?
That's why I warned you, Attorney Gi Mu Hyeok.
I'll give you one last chance.
Leave our school quietly and keep your mouth shut.
Then nothing else will happen.
I'll give you that chance as well.
If you sinned, let it all go and ask for forgiveness.
Then...
I may be willing to represent you. What do you say?
Did you decide to stick next to her and watch her closely...
so she can't talk about you?
Leave Tae Ra alone.
Talk to me if you need to.
I'm shocked.
You really sound like you're trying to protect her.
You killed her.
- What? - I warned you.
I gave you one last chance too.
If only you listened to me,
Han Tae Ra wouldn't have had to die.
You freak!
It's all your fault,
Attorney Gi Mu Hyeok.
Look at this punk. He spent a lot with the corporate credit card.
(ISEE Guard)
"ISEE..."
What's this?
What place is this? Why did they pay them 3,000 dollars?
(ISEE Guard)
(Donghan Hospital)
That's right. This is what Su Ah asked me to mail that day.
It was misdelivered to another orphanage nearby.
Luckily, it was still there.
I thought it was only right that you see it first.
(Recipient, 75-6, Sangrae-dong, Hwamyeong-si, Gyeonggi Province)
(July 27, 2018. I went to the shoot and...)
It's a diary.
(May 3, 2019. Today is the most important day...)
I guess she kept a diary even after she left the orphanage.
(May 3, 2019)
"May 3, 2019."
Until the day of the incident.
(I'll tell him that I'm actually a high school student.)
(I'm going to muster up my courage and end it with him. Yu Yang Ki.)
(I went to the shoot and met someone...)
I went to the shoot and met someone...
who said he'd sponsor me.
Come out when you're ready.
Put your arms together.
Okay, flip your hair. Okay.
Nice.
That's good. Good.
- Hello. - Hi.
I like seeing people work hard.
Hello.
How about a more chic look this time?
Who's that? She's new.
She's a new model.
The ad she was in was well-received,
so we're shooting her profile. I have a good feeling.
I especially like the look in her eyes.
Nice.
(Cheonmyung Foundation)
(Lee Tae Seok, General Manager of Future Strategies)
"General Manager of Future Strategies"?
Why? It's so fancy, right?
What future strategy does a private foundation...
that isn't even a conglomerate need, right?
No, that's not it.
It's different from what I expected.
I thought you owned a studio...
or a modeling agency.
That's true too.
I do this and that for the future of the foundation.
How much did you make from modeling?
About 1,500 dollars this month.
1,500 dollars?
Drink.
How does it taste?
Not so great.
Not so great?
Okay.
But what you just drank costs...
about 100 dollars.
If we drink this entire bottle, it would be similar...
to everything you made while modeling.
What do you think? Is it still "not so great"?
Give me more.
The more I drink it, it's growing on me.
This is trouble.
A person's taste can keep getting more expensive,
but it can never go the other way.
You'll have to make...
a lot of money from now on.
What do you want to do most when you make money?
You know, what you truly want.
Study.
"Study"?
I want to study and succeed.
I want to go back to school too.
I dropped out because I couldn't afford it.
It was in the stars...
for us to meet.
How could he...
He approached her with ulterior motives in the get-go.
It'll be hard...
to enter that diary into evidence in court,
but it can affect Yu Yang Ki if it's disclosed.
When she said there was something that could protect her,
she must have meant this diary.
To bring Yu Yang Ki down,
we must make the content of the diary public.
If we don't, they will blindly interpret it...
in a negative way.
I will do it myself.
There's something I want to say about Su Ah to the people.
(Patient name, Kim Han Su)
I'm the suspect of the townhouse murder case,
Kim Han Su, and I'm a junior student at Cheonmyung High School.
I didn't stab the victim.
I went to her place...
because I was worried about her.
What about the victim were you worried about?
That day,
before the incident happened, she asked me a favor.
(Recipient, 75-6, Sangrae-dong, Hwamyeong-si, Gyeonggi Province)
She asked me to send this post.
What's inside?
From the day she first met Congressman Yu Yang Ki...
until the day she got murdered.
This is the victim's diary that has everything that happened to her...
during that period.
What's written in the diary?
That she met Congressman Yu through Lee Tae Seok for the first time...
and that Congressman Yu...
visited the victim's place every week since.
That's very important information.
If it's needed to reveal the truth,
are you willing to make the full text of the diary public?
Yes.
But before that,
there's one thing I want to share...
to all the viewers of this video.
Please go ahead.
It's true that the victim made the wrong decision.
But no one.
No one was there to protect her from making such decisions.
Before you criticize her, please think about this one thing.
She...
was a victim that Lee Tae Seok and Yu Yang Ki took advantage of.
Although she made a bad decision,
she lost her life...
while trying to fix it.
(Cheonmyung High School)
You're Yu Beom Jin, right? Congressman Yu Yang Ki's son.
I have nothing to say.
Come on. Yes, you do. Things have gotten out of hand now.
Just tell me honestly about how you feel now.
What was your relationship with Jung Su Ah?
The word around is that you were close to the girl your father dated.
Is that true?
Have you two met in private?
Is this related to your girlfriend's suicide?
No, it's not. Get out of my way.
- Wait. - I have a question!
- Please answer my question! - Just this one!
Everything was fabricated!
There's no evidence whatsoever that proves the diary as solid proof.
And I don't even know that girl.
Just because she went to the same school my son goes,
they are creating such lame and nasty fake news.
I'm beyond disappointed. I'm furious.
Today,
I'm making myself clear once again.
I have never met the girl...
and I don't know anything about this incident.
He's lying.
(Press Conference to Reveal the Truth of the Townhouse Murder)
Congressman Yu Yang Ki has continuously been seeing the victim,
which is the reason why the victim got murdered.
What?
Are you saying Congressman Yu is related to the murder case?
Yes, he is.
- What? - He's related?
Are you saying Congressman Yu is the murderer?
No, I'm not.
If not, who is the murderer?
Is there anything else you know?
- Who is the murderer? - Please clarify.
- Please answer. - Who tipped off about it?
- Then why did Congressman Yu... - Are you sure?
The murderer...
The real criminal of this case...
is Congress Yu Yang Ki's son, Yu Beom Jin.
- What? - His son?
(Press Conference to Reveal the Truth of the Townhouse Murder)
- That's unbelievable. - Is that true?
Are you sure? What's your reason?
Do you have evidence?
- Congressman Yu's son... - What's the evidence?
Please explain!
Please answer the question!
(Attorney Gi Spots Congressman Yu's Son, Yu Beom Jin, as the Culprit)
Ma'am, I think you should stay in the hospital.
There's no time to be lying down.
If not now, we can't drag him down.
"Drag down"? Drag down whom?
Assistant Prosecutor General Yang of course.
What?
Are you out of your mind?
That's wrong.
Yu Yang Ki is a congressman, so we can throw suspicion on him.
But Yu Beom Jin is not even a public figure.
He's just a high school student.
He's underage.
And you want to reveal his information at the press conference?
Just with suspicions and circumstantial evidence?
If not,
do we have other options?
We should look for them.
You're usually not this emotional.
You have been calm until now. Why are you suddenly doing this?
Just because there's a chance that his alibi might be ruined,
he killed his own girlfriend who has been supporting him all along...
and disguised it as suicide.
We can't just let him do this.
Who knows what he's going to do next?
Hey, Mu Hyeok...
We have to do this and stop him.
Don't worry about me.
Just make sure to catch Yang Sang Bae at the right time.
When I reveal the truth about Yu Beom Jin,
I'll reveal his too.
I saw the broadcast.
Let's meet at Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office right now.
(Press Conference to Reveal the Truth of the Townhouse Murder)
This is the CCTV footage of Yu Beom Jin...
near the victim's place a week before the incident.
- What? - What is that?
- Who is that? - Can you see?
- Isn't that Congressman Yu's son? - I think he is.
That's Congressman Yu's son.
Yu Beom Jin went to Han Su's hospital as soon as he woke up.
He told him about an escape route that even the police didn't know...
and asked him to make a false statement...
that he saw Lee Tae Seok on the scene.
And the only girl who could testify about what Yu Beom Jin was doing...
on the day of the incident...
jumped to her death from a skyscraper.
And Lee Tae Seok, who knew Yu Yang Ki's secret...
hanged himself...
at his own office.
Everyone.
(Attorney Gi Spots Congressman Yu's Son, Yu Beom Jin, as the Culprit)
Isn't it strange?
I'm casting doubts...
on the consecutive deaths.
Attorney Gi Mu Hyeok spotted Congressman Yu Yang Ki's son,
Yu Beom Jin, as the culprit of the townhouse murder case.
He presented a video footage of Yu Beom Jin that was filmed...
near the victim's place as evidence.
What's more shocking is that Yu Beom Jin talked to the victim,
Kim, into making false statements.
- Until now... - I just got goosebumps.
It wasn't Kim Han Su that killed her, but Yu Beom Jin?
Gosh, I had no idea.
By the way, the temp is Kim Han Su's attorney?
Does that mean he fooled everyone and faked his identity?
Beom Jin and the temp. I got fooled by everyone.
Mr. Gi didn't have bad intentions though.
Thanks to him, Han Su's innocence will be proved.
Here's Attorney Gi's speech at the press conference.
Yu Beom Jin installed a spy app on Congressman Yu's phone...
and monitored him.
And he figured out that Congressman Yu...
was having an inappropriate relationship with the victim.
Yu Beom Jin, you scumbag.
Is that the motive for murder?
Yes.
Once Yu Beom Jin found out about it,
he made a horrible decision in order to break...
the relationship between the victim and his father.
Kim Han Su.
Was your testimony about seeing Lee Tae Seok false?
Is it true that you were forced to give false testimony?
It's true.
I was told I had to give that testimony to protect the victim...
No.
To protect Su Ah from being criticized by the public.
I was told to testify that I saw Lee Tae Seok flee out the back door.
I sincerely apologize for giving false testimony.
But everything I just said...
is true.
When I first became...
Han Su's attorney in this case,
I had a plea bargain with the prosecutors.
- What's that? - What?
The prosecutor in charge of this case...
was Assistant Prosecutor General Yang Sang Bae...
at Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office.
He secretly met women...
at the modeling agency run by Lee Tae Seok...
and received bribes and favors.
He also interfered with other prosecutor's investigations...
to hide the truth.
That crazy jerk!
How dare that reckless punk do this to me?
Hey.
Indict him for defamation right now.
Arrest him this instant!
Okay.
Gosh.
What are you two doing?
Who says you can barge into my office like this?
Sorry we forgot to knock.
Don't get too worked up.
You'll have to move out of this room anyway.
What?
Look, Hyun Jung.
Have you lost your mind after being hit in the head?
Who are you to tell me to move out of this room?
Everything has been revealed now. You better disappear quietly.
You're getting a little too desperate.
"Revealed"?
What do you mean? What's been revealed?
Do you mean that lame photo of me?
Fine, I went to a movie with her.
What's so wrong with watching a movie with a girl?
Apparently, my colleague worked very hard while I was bedridden.
What?
Would you like to talk to the girl you met...
on the phone?
(Model from Lee Tae Seok's Agency)
What did you say?
We've also recorded her testimony.
She met you through Lee Tae Seok...
and delivered bribes to you as well.
You must have enjoyed wielding the scant power you had so far.
Now it's time to pay for it.
As Han Su's attorney, I will continue to do my best...
to prove my client's innocence. Therefore,
I also request that the prosecutors reveal the whole truth...
of the victim's death...
through a thorough and fair investigation.
You shameless murderer.
- Did you see that on TV? - Goodness.
- That's right. It's Beom Jin. - You didn't see it?
- Is it true? - What's going to happen?
- His dad and Su Ah... - What's going on?
- That's what happened, right? - Oh, my.
What happened?
You knew all about it from the beginning.
You knew your dad was playing dirty with Su Ah.
How could you do that to us?
Is Beom Jin really a murderer?
You coward.
What?
You were jealous of Han Su, so you framed him as a bully.
And you followed Su Ah around and took secret photos of her.
Do you suddenly feel guilty now?
- What did you just say? - Am I wrong?
You were a stalker who took secret photos.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Also,
is there evidence that I killed Su Ah?
Apart from those circumstances that stupid attorney is babbling,
is there any evidence that I stabbed Su Ah with a knife?
How dare you all look at me like that?
Without me,
you can't even think for yourselves.
- Unbelievable. - What is he saying?
Who does he think he is?
Listen up, everyone.
I didn't...
kill Su Ah.
If you want to keep arguing that I did,
bring evidence.
A video of me stabbing Su Ah or anything!
Bring it so I can see it.
- He's crazy. - What's with him?
He's totally creepy.
(Regional Investigation Unit)
You finish it up.
What can I do...
in this situation?
Do I even have to tell you what to do?
Turn yourself in...
and testify that you were following Lee Tae Seok's order.
He killed Su Ah,
and you fabricated the scene.
Then...
who killed Lee Tae Seok?
You, of course.
Lee Tae Seok never rewarded you for fabricating the scene.
Out of resentment,
you killed him and disguised it as suicide.
Think of your daughter's future.
What do you mean by that?
I'm the one who saved her.
And I'll keep supporting her.
If both of us get arrested,
who will take care of her future?
The basis has been laid now,
but we still don't have enough evidence...
to take him to court.
Even if we do manage to make him lose the primaries,
It'll be hard to get him kicked out of the National Assembly...
or imprisoned.
We know what happened,
but we can't prove it.
It's so frustrating.
What happened to what I asked for?
The thing is...
I found something slightly shady.
"Shady"?
Lee Tae Seok...
paid for something regularly using his corporate credit card,
so I dug into it.
It was a home security video company.
What is the company name?
ISEE.
What?
No, no. The company name is "ISEE".
I see you. "ISEE Guard".
ISEE.
So? What did you find?
Well, what's more suspicious than the transactions with the company...
is the large sums of money that were transferred to a person.
So I looked him up,
and he works here.
He gave money to an employee...
of a home security video company?
A whopping...
20,000 dollars.
"20,000 dollars"?
Why did he pay that much money to one person?
That's why it's suspicious.
So I went to see him myself.
Police?
(Park Bo Gum, Police Agency)
What? Have you never seen a cop before?
No, sir. I just...
How may I help you?
We already investigated thoroughly, so don't be nervous,
and spill it.
What?
Hold on.
Let's see.
Look at this. Closer!
The recipient works here, right?
Yes, he does work here, but...
(20,000 dollars)
20,000 dollars?
You are a good actor.
You look like you're genuinely shocked.
Tell me the truth. Okay?
Your company took money on the side in this employee's name!
Right? You did illegal things for them...
and got a kick-back!
Hold on.
Darn it. This punk. Again!
We didn't take this money.
Then?
Then? Darn it.
You'll kill our good rapport if you do this.
We really didn't take this money.
- Hey, mister. - Yes?
Tell me the truth while I give you...
the chance.
The thing is, he worked here,
but he took money on the side and installed hidden cameras.
That jerk.
I'm glad I fired him.
Did you really fire him?
You're not covering for him?
It's the truth.
I fired him right away after seeing the hidden camera he installed...
in our customer's bathhouse.
Okay. Fine.
Then where is he now?
I don't know.
Darn it.
(Prosecution Service)
Wait.
Didn't you say you were a cop?
There you go again. If you do this,
you'll really kill our good rapport.
Don't judge a book by its...
(Prosecution Service)
This says "Prosecution Service".
Not "Police". They're similar though.
I got it as a souvenir when they opened their office. So?
Freeze!
Don't come out.
Wait.
Darn it.
Lee Tae Seok had a hidden camera secretly installed in Su Ah's home,
and paid that guy in exchange. I'm sure of it.
Ta-da.
So, I got his business card from back then.
Nice.
We'll use this to find out.
How?
In times like these,
we must use governmental authority.
Governmental authority.
He's a serial offender.
Distributing pornography, running an illegal site...
Plus, he has several related priors.
Can you find out right away?
Yes. Don't worry. I'm sure he's doing something similar.
I'll check and get a warrant and search his place.
Okay, thanks.
We have to hope she'll find something.
Since they saw Han Su is well enough to hold a press conference,
it'll be difficult to continue to stay the trial.
I'm glad...
he doesn't have to be in detention during the trial.
Ms. Ha. Please stay with Han Su.
I need to see someone.
Who?
There's something I want to say...
before Han Su's trial...
to that jerk Beom Jin.
You shameless murderer.
Beom Jin is the murderer?
No way.
You saw his CCTV footage, right?
- Yes, It's Beom Jin. - Did you see?
It's him.
It is suspicious, especially with what happened to Tae Ra.
But still. No way.
His dad and Su Ah were seeing each other.
- Oh my gosh. - It must be true.
Those worthless punks.
How dare you...
They can't do anything by themselves.
(Attorney Gi Mu Hyeok)
Gi Mu Hyeok.
How do you feel, being stomped on?
Come to the roof. I'll be waiting.
I was stomped on?
Me?
Seriously.
That annoying jerk.
Do you think you've won?
No.
You lost, Gi Mu Hyeok.
You're an attorney, but you couldn't win in court,
so you used the media to beat me.
That in itself shows you lost to me.
Who said I wanted to win?
You must only know about the law,
and nothing about the real game.
The best attorney in this industry...
is someone who doesn't step foot in court.
The attorney who gets...
what he wants without going to trial.
He's the best of his kind.
And what I want...
is just ending you.
Not winning.
Got that?
You're already finished even without going to court.
You can get angry,
but people will not act as you wish,
nor believe what you say, or follow you.
Shut it.
As much as they envied you,
they'll be excited to mock you, criticize you, and curse at you.
That's human nature.
People enjoy...
seeing a hero fall more than seeing a hero succeed.
- Why you... - The fact that you are...
Yu Yang Ki's son will follow you until the day you die.
No matter what you do,
that will always get in your way.
Shut it! Shut it, you jerk!
You won't be able to decide any future ever again.
Because you won't be Yu Beom Jin.
You'll be the hypocrite who fooled the entire nation.
You'll always be the son...
of the sex offender and murderer, Yu Yang Ki.
You...
Until you die.
No.
It'll follow you for life.
What?
When you think things finally quieted down,
someone will dig it up all again.
Whenever something similar happens,
the media will talk about you.
You'll be stigmatized for the rest of your life...
and never be forgotten.
Until you die.
In that case,
where would you suffer more?
In prison or in this world?
(Class of Lies / Mr. Temporary)
Between you and me, who will end up in the fiery pit?
We'll find it out in the end.
Do you want to fall further down?
Further down than Han Su?
I swear that I didn't kill her.
For Songha Law Firm to take your case,
you shouldn't hide anything from me.
Give him all his weaknesses.
Silence!
Is it true?
After finding out that my son killed the victim,
I wanted to cover up what he did.
I had Lieutenant Oh Ki Hwan fabricate the scene...
It's all a lie.
I'll be a witness and prove my innocence.
I request...
that Yu Beom Jin be selected as a witness.