I will still be with you
henceforth
Spring rain is me, Xia Yang is me
Autumn leaves are me
Winter snow is also me
I want you, I just want you
Tongfeng
Little Mencius asked me at that wedding
When did I fall in love with you
Actually I don't know either
but
you are already deep
Engraved into my heart
Can't erase
don't want
No
As a prince, I order you
henceforth
forget me
Sacrifice Jiuyou with my blood
Can only be restored in the mortal world
no no no
She is Chun Yu, she is Xia Yang
She is Akiba
She is Xia Yang
She is autumn leaves, she is winter snow
she likes sweets
Recognize ducks as mandarin ducks
She is the god of all things in the world
she is my wife
She is Chunyu She is Chunyu
from now on
There is no more Tongfeng in the world
This is He Junwei
I want to be with Hyun Bae forever
four hundred and forty disease
Lovesickness is the most painful
If you forget
If you can calm your heart that is in extreme pain,
Is it because the world underestimates the power of lovesickness?
Deep love has been engraved into the bone marrow
Mere memory
How could I resist his fatal lovesickness?
Pluto, why are you so sentimental?
Have you read too many storybooks?
Or is it that you have found someone?
you
You don't understand anything
Yes, yes, we don’t understand anything
By the way, I’m not sure how many pages there are in the Book of Life and Death.
Let you fix it
He is just old
right
Xiao'e
Do you remember when this emperor
Do you have this pair of earrings?
Since Xiao'e first saw you
You've been wearing this pair of pearl earrings
Lived too long
I don’t even remember who gave me the earrings.
I just think he is a very important person
Si Mo
You said that I obviously made up this bracelet myself.
But why do I always feel like me
given to others
But I can't remember who it is
Have we forgotten something?
What did you forget?
I was born as Lord of Jiuyou Mansion
Receive blessings from heaven and earth
Enjoy the love and respect of mortals and shoulder the burden of common people
Use my blood to protect all things in the world
I protect the world
But what I want to protect most
It's still you
Did I forget to feed you again?
I really don’t know what you have been doing all these years
How did you survive?
adult
My subordinates have sorted out the book of life and death.
Ah Ming, I always feel at ease when you do things.
Sir, what's the matter?
Everything is fine now
Everything is normal in the mortal world and Xiuweijing
But I don’t know why
I always feel like something is missing
It's like something has been cut off
I don't know
Be a god and live as long as heaven
Long lasting life
Is it really a good thing?
Everyone longs for the art of immortality
Maybe for mortals
That's a good thing
Have a long life
Equivalent to eternal loneliness
We manage the replacement
But I have never experienced earthly fate
I want to go to Fantasyland and experience it myself
Feel the encounter like a mortal
Reunion, parting, meeting again
Sir, have you really decided?
Your Excellency, the repair well has been opened
After drinking this bowl of Wangchuan soup
You will lose all your power
Fall into fantasy
adult
May you get what you want this time
sisters
my novel
Rush to the bestseller list
First place
true or false
Is it the book "Nine Netherworlds"?
Um
Treat, treat, treat
no problem
Xiaofeng
What about your book being on the bestseller list?
It seems that the counselor found out
He was sent to the grade group
What
you see
What's the point? Number one on the bestseller list
This is a good thing
Are you stupid?
It was written based on Pei Xuan and her
Now it has been sent to the grade group
What about her secret crush on Senior Brother Pei?
Isn’t it already known to everyone?
Is Xiaofeng Xuanpei the same as Senior Brother Pei?
Is it you Tong Feng?
Tong Xiaofeng came to the counselor’s office
I have something to tell you
The counselor came to see me
I heard it's behind the counselor's office
The lights on that path were broken recently.
No one dares to go there anymore
Anyway, you must pass by it when you go back to your dormitory.
What
It's really dark
No way, we can’t really meet each other, right?
Pei
Senior brother
Tong Xiaofeng
Scared me to death
If you haven't done anything wrong, why should you be afraid?
I
I can walk and sit upright
Brother Pei, what do you mean?
You are the spring rain, the summer sun, the autumn leaves, and the winter snow.
is my wife
Xuan Pei
You really thought I was Xuan Pei
No, no, it’s not you who read the novel
That novel was actually not written by me.
You've all seen the ending
Why write such a sad ending?
The editor asked me to write it
She said she would have it
A sad ending will make it more soul-stirring
Admit it was you who wrote it
Senior Brother Pei
You deceived me
Do I really look like a cat?
Isn't it just a cat that is mysterious, elegant and loves to show off its fur?
No artistic processing
Then why should I be the model?
Senior Brother Pei
You lied to me again
Thought I was going to kiss you
No no
That me
I might have misunderstood
You guessed it right
How is Xiaofeng doing?
What did the counselor tell you that you were there for so long?
yes
He asked me to give
Juniors and juniors
Hold a sharing session about novels
Okay, good thing, then you should behave well then
I'm on my way there
Met Senior Brother Pei
What
He seems to have read my novel
Then did you take the opportunity to confess to him?
he seems
Sister, please tell me quickly. Some of the sisters are in a hurry.
he he seems
For me writing him into the novel
I'm not angry at all about this.
He's definitely not angry
Authors like this kind of young beauty
It's not too late for him to be happy
But
Why did he kiss me?
What
ah
He kissed you
Ouch, big news
Then what did he say after kissing you?
Without me, I would
I'll be back in a panic
said nothing
This beast
scum
rogue
He might have said something at that time.
But I, I was so panicked that I came back
It's okay, I have his class tomorrow
See if he looks for you after class.
The students seem to be very lively today
Brother Pei, have you watched "Nine Netherworld"?
Please discuss anything unrelated to class after class.
Everyone, open the book to the first chapter
This concludes today’s lesson
Do you have anything to ask, classmates?
Senior Brother Pei
Just now a classmate said that you were
Confessed to Tong Xiaofeng
Is this true?
This woman
I have to beat her up when I turn around.
What does it have to do with you?
I don’t know, I don’t know
is it true
yes
I confessed to her
Xiaofeng, where are you going?
Why is he like this?
in front of so many people
wrong
When did he confess his love to me?
last night
Senior Brother Pei Pei Pei Pei
Classmate, you don’t seem to have a very good memory.
When did you confess your love to me?
How come I don't know
Don't try to lie to me
What can I do?
My bride doesn’t seem very smart
who is your bride
You forgot what you wrote in the book