Xuan Pei
you are back
Have you gotten into any trouble recently?
I didn't cause any trouble
I know you're not with me
No one is covering me
So I don't dare to cause trouble
Have you practiced well?
Xuan Pei, the firefly you turned into for me is so beautiful
Want to change the subject again
You're not with me
How can I have the time to study?
Xuan Pei
Can you promise me?
Don't leave me again
Otherwise I won’t be in the mood to do anything
OK I promise you
But Tong Feng, you have to promise me
Next, you have to practice hard
Don't worry, you're back
Of course I will practice hard.
Xuan Pei, what's wrong with you?
fine
Are you hungry? Go home and I'll cook for you.
OK, I learned a trick from Xiao Mencius
I will cook it for Xuan Pei today
Why are you looking at me like that?
Xuan Pei you
How is your business trip going this month?
The inspection was pretty good
The Yinte magic array in the mountainous area is not very good.
I'll go back and let the life take my life and then upgrade it.
Fortunately, I'm back
What
nothing
Is the food I cooked today delicious?
Still barely
You don't even praise me
I lied to you that it was delicious.
Then eat more
Eat this and this
Give back the gift of the meal
What's this
a very beautiful flower
Xuan Pei is the best
Wait a moment
Ma Yichun Ma Yichun
Ma Yichun, do you know what this is?
Xuan Pei suddenly gave it to me
Planted a pattern like this
Sir how could he
Say it
what is this
This is just an ordinary pattern.
Maybe adults think it looks good
I'll print it for you
Jiuyou, the latest popular patterns
Isn't that right?
That's right
Scared me to death
Xuan Pei is feeling very strange lately
I thought something big happened
What big thing could happen?
Our Jiuyou has always been peaceful.
Then I'll leave first. Bye.
Bye, continue.
Your current body
How can we support him to grow the underworld pattern?
Adult business
We have never been able to intervene.
What are you doing?
Sir, how can you do such a thing?
Sir, please don't hide it from us.
Ma Yichun and Sister Niu both know
You planted a dark pattern on Tongfeng
It turned out to be for this matter
Sir, your body has recovered somewhat
But you can’t plant underworld patterns either.
The secret technique of Mingwen
You inject some spiritual power into Tong Feng
She will be hurt in the future
The underworld pattern will protect her from harm
And your spiritual energy will also suffer.
How could Tong Feng be injured in Jiuyou?
It is impossible to even fall down on weekdays
But she loves to run around
Last time she went to the devil world, she
Sir, you want to plant dark patterns on Tongfeng
The subordinates have no right to interfere in this matter
But you are still a little weak now
After planting the underworld pattern
There will be complications
You can know about these complications
complication
Tongfeng's five specific feelings will be temporarily received by you
what five senses
I know
The five specific senses refer to
Touch, taste, smell, pain, mind
It will be up to you to help her feel this
There is such a thing
It's a ruler
It was probably Liu Taigong who took advantage of Tong Feng
Wait until your body recovers
The complications will disappear
Why doesn't it hurt?
Teacher Liu, haven't you eaten? It doesn't hurt at all.
no pain
It really doesn't hurt
If she can't eat sweet food
I'm afraid I'll be so angry that I won't eat for several days.
When did this happen?
Are you still full of heart? Can Tong Feng eat sweets?
It was a subordinate who made a mistake
Adults are just
Tong Feng, she has a stomachache recently
Isn't she causing trouble?
Can I avoid having a stomachache if I eat randomly all the time?
Even so, it doesn't matter
Presumably there won't be any big problem
I am the king of Jiuyou House
Block thousands of thunders
Block the ancient ferocious beast
What to fear
Ah Ming, come quickly
Caught it
You kicked so far again
I don’t know what’s going on lately
My stomach doesn’t hurt anymore and I feel more relaxed.
Sir, I saw when Tong Feng was in pain
I will drink this water while it is hot
Feeling of pain relief after drinking
Shouldn't it be given to Tong Feng?
Is she okay if she gets better after drinking?
you have a point
Tong Feng wants grilled chicken wings as his teacher
Do you want to eat it or not?
I want to eat, I want to eat, I want to eat twice as spicy
I can’t taste saltiness anymore lately.
It feels like my sense of taste has failed. Ma Yichun
water water water
No feeling at all
adult
Xuan Pei
You stay here obediently
Not allowed to go anywhere
Xuan Pei, what's wrong with you?
Why do you look weird today?
I can rest assured that you stay by my side
Xuan Pei, are you feeling sick to your stomach?
It's okay, just don't move around
Hyun Bae's stomachache seems to be very similar to mine.
Xuan Pei, just lie here obediently
I'll come right away
where did you go
Hurry, Hurry, Xuan Pei
Drink this while it's hot
This is
Oh I'm not
I understand that you can't control your mouth.
It'll be fine in a few days. It's okay.
Ah Ming
What do you mean by the connection between these feelings?
When will it be lifted?
Wait until the adult is well
The connection between these five specific senses is naturally eliminated.
You should be recovering now
These five sense elimination inductions start with touch
The order is taste, smell, pain, and finally the heart.
mind
Is the feeling in the heart the change in Tong Feng’s mood?
yes
If it is something you like
Or the emotional changes of the person you love
can i feel it
meeting
Come and order your dishes
Tongfeng
Come
New pastries made for you
It tastes better than before
Thank you Simo
This bad girl
Do I usually give you less food?
Sweet Bride’s Beloved
The domineering ruler finally found the one he likes
This mysterious lover
Looks a bit familiar
Why did her heart suddenly beat so fast?
Isn't this the one I love?
Who is Xuan Pei’s crush?
These spies are really unreliable
Always scribbling
It turns out it was because of her heartbeat
This is a split
But it's very particular about talent.
I think I also practiced for seventy years as a teacher.
Only to split
Is it that difficult?
God is not me
It’s really not me who caused Concubine Tian to have a miscarriage.
I only believe what I see with my own eyes
Send an order to bring Linglong into the mortal world
Never be reincarnated forever
God, don’t want it, don’t want it
Why is this drama so boring lately?
My chicken
It was indeed stolen by that black-hearted Wang Laosi
I drank the medicine in anger
Just came over
Too bad
It's so miserable
Sir, are you okay?
Ah Ming
Don’t you think this woman is really
It hurts to look at it
why am i crying
It can't be Tong Feng again, right?
Nonsense
How could you become so physically fit?
You are really not afraid of any pain
willing to try that pain
Kyuubi teacher
Just tell me if you can increase the force value.
My force value has never been able to increase.
I promised Xuan Pei that I would practice hard.
What can I do?
I can't be biased
So I looked through all the information
Found this little shortcut
Please two of you come over and help me.
And recently, my body has become very strong.
Is it Kyuubi-sensei?
right
good
Then we will take this class
Analytical Course on the Situation of Women in Ancient and Modern Times
as we all know
Whether it is ancient women or future women
Their situation is always much more difficult
Not only do they want
Facing the pain of childbirth
I also have to take on the work of raising children.
So this class
We are going to let you feel it in advance
Women’s hardships during childbirth
Teacher Liu, just let your horse come over.
I want to see how painful this class is.
Don't talk nonsense for a while, you're pretty
The latest research on Jiuyou Book School
Fully automatic production of pain sensor
This mortal pain
There are twelve levels in total
And this birth is the twelfth level of pain
Yes, there are twelve levels of pain in total.
Let's try it level by level
As soon as you say you can't stand it, we'll stop.
Teacher Liu
You look down on people too much
Where did this go?
I don't even frown at all
I said, why are you so proud recently?
What Old Man Liu said is right.
Students
When you cry out in pain later
Don't blame me for not reminding you
Just watch it, you two
arrange
The adults drank this last bowl of medicine
The five-sense connection between you and Tongfeng
It can be cut off
Ah Ming, thank you for your hard work
This is level one pain
Similar to the feeling of being bitten by a mosquito
I can't even feel the bite from this mosquito.
Why did I feel it at the beginning?
We push it directly to level six
Feeling similar to gastroenteritis
This gastroenteritis is nothing more than that.
No feeling at all
Why did it suddenly start to hurt?
Is your ability to withstand pain okay?
Let’s push it directly to level eight
Feeling similar to menstrual cramps
You used to be most afraid of menstrual cramps
Things are different now
What's the pain in the wind and rain?
plus
Is Tong Feng taking a martial arts class?
Today’s lesson is the birth pain experience
Okay, good student
This is already the eleventh level
Mortal appendicitis level pain
Why do I feel that you don’t feel anything at all?
Yes, why don’t I feel anything?
Is this machine really useful?
Of course there's nothing wrong with this machine
The soul that experienced the pain of childbirth last time
That was carried out
Then just push it to level 12.
pain of childbirth
I can't feel it this time
plus
Just the pain of childbirth
That’s all
How is this possible?
Are you not a soul?
Could it be that she has the legendary pain-bearing physique?
Tongfeng
And the legendary thirteenth level of pain
That's several times more painful than the pain of childbirth
Similar to trigeminal neuralgia in mortals
Do you want to try
arrange