Meng Dihua
It's over, it's over, the game is about to begin
Where did Meng Dihua go?
Meng Dihua
Tongfeng Tongfeng
Quick, quick, quick, drink this soup.
Haori continued to score points through smashes in this game
Tong Feng needs to find his own rhythm.
What's going on? I suddenly want to sleep.
The second game has already started
It's over, it's over
Player Tong Feng’s condition seems to have declined.
Continuous mistakes
What's going on
Oh, boss lady, where have you been?
Let me have a good meal
let me drink some let me drink some
this
What's going on?
This death sign
I don’t know how to point towards my own people.
That Yuzhi obviously hit Tongfeng on purpose.
Fujun Demon Lord
Just a little soul
You guys are a little too nervous, right?
I just don’t allow anyone to be in Jiuyou
disregard the law
The next game is between Jiuyou and Demon Realm
God is not worried
It makes sense
how could i
Got knocked down by a small badminton ball and fell to the ground
No problem with this ball
The feathers on the badminton are from my feather clan
Naturally obey my orders
It's up to you
Where can I see the key?
You will definitely lose this round
Come on I can do it
No matter what you did to this badminton,
I will never give up
What's going on?
Is it because she, Haori, is deceiving?
Let me tell you
If Yuzhi dares to cheat,
I will
I'll hit her with this spoon
I'm so worried about Tong Feng
As expected of our Jiuyou Tongfeng
Come on, hold on
Tongfeng, hold on, Tongfeng
Tong Feng catches up
The score gap gradually narrows
seventeen to twenty
It’s match point
Haori took the lead to hit the match point
Tong Feng is already lagging behind Princess Yuzhi by a huge margin
Tong Feng will wipe away the shame of Chao's life
Still no miracle happened
Where is the proud Princess Haori who lost to the demon world?
seventeen to twenty
It’s match point
Haori took the lead to hit the match point
Tong Feng has fallen behind Princess Yuzhi by a huge margin
Tong Feng will wipe away the shame of his life
Still no miracle happened
Where is the proud Princess Haori who lost to the demon world?
It's almost time to reach the match point
You lose by one point
Otherwise, you'd better admit defeat now
His face is not that ugly
I have been a poor student of Jiuyou for three thousand years
Finally got a chance to make a comeback
I will never give up
Come on, come on, come on
please
It's getting more and more interesting
Mr. Jiuyou Mansion will end in person
Could it be
Do you think there's anything wrong?
On the field
Using demonic magic openly to hurt people
Every move is fatal
That's enough
I I I don't understand what you are saying
Jiuyou will never allow such things to happen.
The feathers on the badminton come from the feathers of the Yu tribe
Feather tribe can use
Magic that cannot be seen in other worlds
Just now you turned the badminton ball into several cold knives
The above technique is still in effect
If you don't believe it
Just ask someone from the Feather Clan to find out.
The situation on the field has now reached
white-hot degree
Our wise and mighty Lord Fu
Got into a fight with the Demon Lord
After all, is it just a matter of anger for beauty?
The cheating behavior of the Demon Princess
I don’t know if it’s true or not
if true
Then Princess Haori
This behavior is a bit despicable.
I'll just say it
She must be cheating on that Haori
Ugly
alright
The princess of the demon clan is eager to win
It’s the nature of a little girl
It's not intentional
Why don't we play a mixed game for men and women in the second half?
Mr. Fu seems to be preparing
Becoming Miss Tongfeng’s partner
The prince of the mansion fights with the princess
It is inevitable that there is a suspicion of bullying.
It's better to team up with the Demon Lord and the Princess
This game is evenly matched
Walk
last game
I'm your teammate
But I'm afraid of holding you back
This is your game
Is there anything that can't hold me back?
Sit here first
How's the injury?
Are you okay? Tong Feng
Tongfeng
minor injury
Feeling better?
Don't let me get hurt again in the future.
Just now, I, the Princess of the Demon Realm, used some tricks
Please don't mind, girl
Why does this Demon Lord look like Si Mo?
Hurt my Jiuyou soul
Do you think a bottle of water can solve the problem?
I just care about Miss Tongfeng
Not allowed?
Fu-kun
If a person in the devil world makes a mistake
I will definitely give Jiuyou an explanation in the future.
But this game
It's between me and the prince
Principal image
must win
Demon King
Before the game starts
It's better to be cautious in your words and deeds
Fu-kun
please
After the Tongfeng player was injured
Both sides changed their players.
The game starts
As soon as Lord Fu comes on stage
There was a wave of cheers
Look at these beautiful muscle lines
Look at these women from all walks of life
Crazy handsome face
Look at this unparalleled jumping ability
Look at this breathtakingly handsome guy
catching action
Beauty and strength coexist
Is the most powerful idol group
He is the most handsome and capable guy
Player Tong Feng has also recovered his form
The Demon Lord’s strength should not be underestimated either.
Actually and Mr. Fujun
It's hard to tell the difference between them
this game
It's not just
The battle between Tong Feng and the Demon Realm Princess
There is already a faint demon world
The war with Jiuyou
Mr. Fujun, come on, Mr. Fujun.
Come on Tongfeng, Tongfeng
The scores of both sides alternately lead
It feels like I’ve reached the match point in one breath
Wonderful, really wonderful
It is indeed a duel between Lord Fu and Demon Lord.
The pace is terrifyingly fast
Who will be the final winner?
Let us wait and see
Wait and see
Wonderful
It's so wonderful
Twenty-nine versus twenty-nine
The score was evened again
It is indeed a duel between Fujun and Demon Lord.
It's so wonderful
The intensity of this game
It has reached an unimaginable level
game over
Jiuyou wins
won
This game is so beautiful
At the end of the final match
Win the final
This is a competition between endurance and mentality.
This can be recorded in badminton history
badminton match
I feel like I'm going to cry
Watching Tong Feng walking step by step
It's really not easy
The winner of the preliminary rounds of the Three Worlds Talent Competition has emerged
That’s our Tongfeng
That's it
This is how it feels when your daughter gets married, right?
Tong Feng doesn’t want to be your daughter.
Children can be taught
we all know
Tong Feng is the most ignorant student in Jiuyou.
But today
She changed her ways
Turn around and find the shore
Let us give you the warmest applause
Let’s wish this thousand-year bottom king together
Her success tells us
Just work hard
will create miracles
Miracle
alright
The coronation ceremony has been completed
I think everyone is interested in the prize for the champion
All curious
Now I will be the champion of this preliminary round
Awards
Dream lottery jackpot
Now we invite the winner of this preliminary competition
Tong Feng gave an acceptance speech
Thanks to the organizer
Thanks to the judges
this champion
When giving an acceptance speech
Don’t look at the cheat sheet in the palm of your hand
In fact, that part just now
I copied it from the Internet
What about me?
He is a soul who has never won an award
so i don't know
What should I say in my acceptance speech?
But if you want to thank
I want to thank someone
He has been with me for three thousand years
Teach me the principles of magic
And cook for me every day
In the past when I was ridiculous
He always covers me
Later I practiced hard
He urged me to study
I used to think about it all the time
Is everyone as lucky as me?
Later I found out
My luck
Just like a mortal won the lottery
Scaryly rare
How lucky
Thank you
Have been by my side for so many years
May the years to come be
See you every year
good
Won first place
take you to a good place
where
You'll know when you go there
won the championship
It’s natural to celebrate happily
Si Mo
Will you follow me back to the devil world?
Not yet
I still have important tasks in Jiuyou
What other tasks do you have?
you saw
That woman is obviously Xuan Pei's
Shut up
You won't forget the purpose of coming here, right?
You're not here for that woman
how do i do things
I don’t need you to teach me
I
How can it be so similar?
How could it be?
God, who are you talking about?
My best friend is also a god in the world
She is extremely kind
Also extremely terrifying
She has been burdened with many
Her name is Jun Wei
She is also called Blood Demon