In summary
Sister, have you met a scumbag?
right
I don't think he is a good person either.
Sets of sweet words
He didn't confess to you last night
But I said I confessed to you
I just want you to think that you two have confirmed your relationship.
Then I will take you down in one fell swoop, not wanting to be responsible
Too grandson, right?
That's so outrageous, I'm going to beat him up.
Who are you going to beat? How old are you now?
But you can
Post a post online
Just say that the prince of the Pei Group shows mercy everywhere
Xiaofeng
I don’t think that Pei Xuan is a good person.
If he had liked you a long time ago
Why haven't I contacted you?
Want me to see if he's a sly black cat
You are just a stupid fat-headed fish
Otherwise, forget it.
Fat-headed fish, can't I be a mermaid?
Are your classmates going together?
Are you writing about me?
121 121 121
Everyone, keep up.
Xiaofeng, run faster
If you don't hurry up
You can't finish the 800-meter run in four and a half minutes
You failed again
I really can't stand it anymore, why don't you go first?
I'll come find you soon
Go, go, go
what are you doing
why are you avoiding me
I
I don’t want to deal with scumbags
I'm waiting for you at the end
What's going on
what are you doing
What's going on?
Pei Xuan, even if you are really a black cat
I also want to show you that the fat-headed fish is not easy to bully.
The boss is here to play scratch-off games
good
The boss also gave me one
Why did you think of buying lottery tickets today?
Take two more
I've been so unlucky lately
It’s okay if you meet a scumbag
Still embarrassed in front of the whole class
Mercury retrograde buys two lottery tickets for joy
Let's go well
Take it
Two scratch-off tickets for the boss
boss boss
Give me one first. Give me one first.
Why are you cutting in line?
Not two sisters, I'm in a hurry
Just let me go first
How's that? We've been here for so long.
Forget it, forget it, let him buy it first.
Thanks
Anyway, this money is all used for wasting money.
When to fight or not to fight?
Boss, I think I won the first prize
What a first prize
Young man, your life is really good.
It's really a first prize, a first prize, a first prize.
Thank you two beautiful sisters. I'm going to redeem the prize.
Look how good this life is for me
that lottery ticket
should be mine
Okay, okay
Hello fellow students
I am Tong Xiaofeng
Hello, senior sister, I have watched your "Nine Netherworld"
I'm still your fan
Senior sister
Is the male protagonist based on Senior Brother Pei?
You and Brother Pei
You and Senior Brother Pei, you two
How do you act like a reporter?
Senior Brother Pei
Too romantic
Cinderella should wear your glass slipper
So romantic
Go ahead
Senior Brother Pei
Could you please invite classmate Tong Xiaofeng?
Tell me about it
Understanding the role of Xuan Pei
How come this person is being chased and intercepted?
Or a top scumbag
Or I really like that silly girl
I hope it’s the second kind
Xuan Pei’s original body is a cat
Can cause nerve damage indirectly
become
Love fish farming
But in his heart he pretends to be the world's common people
He is a qualified prince
I like the character Hyun Bae very much
Since it is a sharing meeting
I also want to share my favorite line
Brother Pei, do you want to recite Xuan Pei's lines?
Very good
This is a public execution
I'm going to have a heart attack
The clouds in the mountains float and the moon in the sky hangs forever
The clouds in the mountains chase the moon in the sky
There are all kinds of ingenious arrangements in the world
Arrange the staggering second by second
All the coincidences laid out
All are revelations
No, I never wrote this paragraph
Senior Brother Pei
I don't know what you are thinking
about novels
I admit
I wrote it based on you
But in the early stages of creation
I don't know at all
This novel will be on the bestseller list
Don't know either
It will be known to the whole school
if
you
It’s because of the novel that you treat me casually
That
That's sorry
I shouldn't be based on you
I shouldn't like you either
There are twenty-eight stars in the sky
There is a star named Shenxing
There is a star named Shang Xing
People say that ginseng merchants don’t meet each other
but i
I have to wait for this miracle
What do you mean
My teaching assistant's class ends next week
You, you want to leave
Tong Xiaofeng
You put me in your book
Having been a leading actor for so long
as compensation
you
Are you willing to be the heroine in my life?
Husband husband
Get up, Xiaochun, it’s time to go to school
let him go
You are still a human being
Your child is only eight years old and you let him go to school by himself
mom and dad
Mother
Dad, why hasn't he gotten up yet?
daddy
Dad can't send you to school today
Pei Xuan, what's the matter with you?
How could you treat your own son like this?
Mom and Dad won’t give me a gift
My classmates all thought my parents were divorced
Koharu
You are really daddy’s breathable little cotton-padded jacket
son
The confession that dad arranged with you
Remember everything clearly?
I remember clearly that I went to English class today
Didn't go to the amusement park to eat ice cream
What a good daddy's son
You two
Wife, listen to my explanation
It was all instigated by my son
Mom, dad insisted on taking me there
Come, come, come
Wife
Wife, please listen to my explanation
I'm really not
tap tap tap
Be gentle, be gentle
Your best friend from college is coming to see you today
Yes, they even brought their family members with them.
Husband, please help me clear the table in a moment
Okay, my supreme wife.
Mom and dad, please stop showing affection. I'm so hungry.
Then be hungry
Is it your own? Go and clean it up.
knew
I'll eat it soon
they arrived
knew
surprise
welcome welcome
This is Professor Liu
Professor Liu, my boyfriend
Hello Tong Xiaofeng, actually we have already received the certificate.
Leave him alone first
Just mind your sisters. I'm exhausted.
Come in and sit down
Hi Brother Pei
Little Huahua, long time no see
haven't seen you for a long time
Tong Xiaofeng, right?
listen to my sister
You are the prettiest girl in this neighborhood
This is
my brother
Hello brother
It's just a pity
She's so good-looking that she's already married
Okay, okay
If you don't do it well, I will starve to death.
I bought all the ingredients yesterday
Mother
Auntie Niu is here
Xiaochun hasn’t seen her aunt for so long
Do you miss your aunt?
Um
this child
They are all the same aunt
Buy the same toys every time
Why does he like Sister Niu so much?
This may be fate from a previous life.
Come in and sit down
good
Senior Brother Pei
Hello, Senior Brother Pei
Long time no see everyone
Husband, are you ready?
Come on, it's all done
Thank you Xiaofeng
welcome everyone
You're welcome, eat as much as you like
Okay, okay, I'm starving to death
My son should eat more vegetables
Xiaofeng
Is this Tian Xuan's latest starring role?
"Falling in Love with Me Accidentally"
Brother is so handsome, I love him so much
Take a break, please
Professor Liu is angry
What is he angry about?
He can't be compared with Tian Xuan
You're the kind of person who judges quality based on appearance
This statement is very outrageous
we as men
In the end, it still depends on character and knowledge.
You can pull me down
You only have these two things
Xiaofeng and I toast you all
Come
thank you for the treat thank you
This tastes better than the one you got last time
This tastes delicious
Come on, come on, add some food
Thanks
Just stay happy like this
Tong Xiaofeng and Pei Xuan in the 21st century
Have the cutest children and the most precious friends.
The most sincere love, such a happy life
adult
your time is almost up
Do you want to return to Jiuyou?
I've got what I want
Don't want to go back
Ah Ming Jiuyou, I feel relieved to have you
The illusion can only last for decades
Do you really want to give up your identity as Fu Jun?
Will the illusion remain forever?
But only this
to keep her
Husband, why are you awake?
I just had a dream
Dreaming about someone wearing ancient clothes
Said he would take me somewhere
Stinky man
Where does he want to take my husband?
You can't go anywhere without me
husband
If there really is a next life
what you up to
If there is a next life