Is it because I went to Yuancang Mountain?
You're the one who's angry
more than
Do you know how dangerous that beast is?
Even I am not completely sure
Can subdue him
You went alone
If I'm a step too late for you
I know
Then I went there because I was worried about Xiao Mencius?
I know it's wrong
Never happen next time
Got it, got it
I listen to Xuan Pei on everything
But Xuan Pei
I feel like that beast knows me
He said something when he saw me
it's you
That ferocious beast has been trapped for thousands of years and has already lost its mind.
You don't need to listen to him
It's getting late now
Go back and rest quickly
I have class tomorrow
injured
Um
Tell me about it
How to get hurt
Xiang Liu ran out
Almost bit me
Thanks to Tong Feng for helping me avoid the disaster
It hurts a little
Thanks
What are you being polite about?
Today you are brave enough to fight against Xiang Liu
It's worthy of a handsome man like me to apply medicine on you
It’s not me fighting but Tong Feng
But speaking of Tong Feng
Today when I was fighting with that Xiang Liu
It's like I'm inside her
I saw a dazzling golden light
golden light
Tong Feng is just an ordinary soul.
Why does she have a golden glow?
I feel strange too
Could it be that I saw it wrong?
But Xiang Liu is also very strange
He seems to know me
get to know you
He said to me when he saw me
haven't seen you for a long time
But I've never seen him
I'm here again to get the class schedule for next week.
complain less
Are you just trying to create a good opportunity?
Take your life, what's going on?
Playing games with those little kids in the fantasy world
Is it that happy?
Ma Yichun, you are still young
These children in Fantasyland would never imagine
Playing games with them now
He is the dignified Jiuyou life-killing master.
The pleasure this stimulation brings
It's hard for you to understand
Stop playing
There are souls in the mortal world who want to enter the Nine Netherworld
You have to take over the soul
I haven't seen it yet
Brother seduces souls and brother kills souls.
Isn’t the seducing brother so majestic?
The deadly brother is so aggressive
Then
Delivering the soul and attracting the soul
What you are talking about are all old almanacs.
Now just use the electric purple array
Okay, it’s time to reach Jiuyou.
That's it
Otherwise
Pick up a soul and let's go to the fantasy world
Then Guhun and I will die from exhaustion.
Now there is no need to dance with knives or guns.
We are civil servants
But I think
Still more handsome as before
That's very handsome
You're crazy
Acting like magic here at night
Sir, are you still filming this?
Moisturized and good skin
Yue Lao Essence
god's choice
you deserve it
Who is this?
You don’t even know him
He is the most popular star king in the world today
Tianxuan
This play is now popular in the Three Realms of Heavenly Demon and Nine Netherworlds
He starred in "President, Emperor, Don't Do This"
Oh, never heard of it
It’s not like adults don’t allow you to see it
So many
Then when can I finish watching it?
Then do you still want to know?
Why did your heart beat that night?
Big Bad Wolf CEO
little red riding hood wife
The cat prince is sure to eat me
My puppy roommate
This is not about medicine
This seems like the animal world
Do you really think your heartbeat can be related to medicine?
I checked
What does this book say about my situation?
Myocardial infarction caused by myocardial hypoxia
I'm about to have a myocardial infarction because of your anger.
Please read and study the script carefully for me
But don’t let the adults know
I'll show you this kind of script
Why?
If adults knew
I'll show you this kind of script
My iron rice bowl is probably not guaranteed.
oh
You are not Linglong
Why does he look exactly like her?
I am the Linglong Emperor
I am really Linglong
You are definitely not Linglong
You can deceive my eyes
But you can't deceive my heart
Emperor of Heaven
My heart is not beating when I look at you
Only Linglong
only her
can arouse my heartbeat
Do you understand?
Got it
Emperor Tian also had a myocardial infarction
don't don't talk to me
Not myocardial infarction
That's myocarditis
Yes, I like it
The Emperor of Heaven likes Linglong
That's why his heart skipped a beat when he saw Linglong
My heart won’t beat when I see someone pretending to be Linglong
you like adults
That's why your heart beats
If you like me, you like Xuan Pei
But I also like you, Ma Yichun
And Miss Niu and Xiao Mencius
The seducing brother and the killing brother
And Teacher Jiuwei and Teacher Liu Taigong
Oops, I'm too lazy to tell you.
Think about it yourself slowly
There are still a lot of things going on in Xiuweijing.
Ma Yichun
Why does my heart beat when I see Xuan Pei?
like
and like
It seems the same
It seems different again
My heart is beating so fast
My face is so hot
I seem to
I dreamed that Xuan Pei married me as his bride
I don’t know Hyun Bae’s muscles either
What does it feel like to touch
Why am I drooling?
Drooling
my muscles
Tongfeng Tongfeng I’m here to see you Tongfeng
Tongfeng
Why did I come to Sansheng River again?
Don't be in a hurry
Everyone has it, come on, come on
A handsome and kind-hearted man like me
It’s really hard to find in a thousand years.
yes
as confident as you
wait a moment
A narcissistic male soul
It’s really hard to find in a thousand years
Tong Feng come here
Tongfeng
You recruit from the real situation
Have you learned any super advanced spells recently?
What spells can I learn?
Then I'll go find you a few days ago
Every time I come to Biluo
You will be blown away by a gust of wind immediately
That's not some super advanced magic you learned.
Did you slap me away?
It must have been Xuan Bae who did it
Dafu, I can learn magic without you.
That's right too
yes
So what's going on with this sinister wind?
Is it possible
Haunted
Yes, yes, it is haunted.
That's not right
Then aren’t we in Jiuyou?
That can't be haunted
That's that's
Making trouble
Dafu, you are so smart
i know i know
Dafu Xiaomengzi invited me to try new dishes
let's go together
OK, OK
It just so happens that I haven’t eaten yet after giving alms all day.
Go, go, go
Let's go, let's go
You can get that yourself
I went to eat
you
I
You have magic marks
Do you know the magic pattern?
Tell the truth
I was born with this magic pattern.
That's because inside my body
The blood of demons flows
Waiting for the fateful person to take me back to the devil world
This hot feeling
This sense of resonance
Could it be said
Are you the destined person I'm waiting for?
are you
How could this person use his identity as a demon?
Published in broad daylight
don't say it
Do you want to die?
This is the sin we carry in our destiny
It’s a secret that you and I need to protect with our lives
do you know me
Don't know me
This is not important. This is not important.
The important thing is that this imprint is on the magic pattern
and the pain in the soul
Let me fully realize
You are my kind
You hurt so much
are you okay
Why should I be burdened with this?
no
Li Dafu, you are such a good actor
Look, it scares Si Mo
Si Mo, ignore him
He is not a demon
He is just an ordinary soul
But there is it on his face
That was what he drew
He painted
Pictorial
Smashed my foot
Tong Feng, I made some pastries for you in the kitchen
Want to eat?
Are the pastries delicious?
very delicious
OK, OK
Zhang Juqian can be reincarnated
Yes, my lord, you punish him with three months of confinement.
We give it to him as you commanded.
Prepare Baohun Decoction to take daily
Now you can reincarnate normally
Arrange for him to be reincarnated
Don't let Tong Feng know
yes
but
Zhang Juqian proposed to use the luck of three generations
In exchange for leaving memories of past lives
Meet my daughter again
No
Where did Tong Feng go?
Did you see it?
I heard that Meng Dihua asked her to try new dishes
Went to Wangchuan Soup Shop
Wangchuan Soup Shop
It’s Wangchuan Soup Shop
So cute
How do you want to eat?
Be careful when burning
tasty
Delicious
let's go out to eat
Little Mencius made a new dish
It will be delicious with this pastry.
Xuan Pei, why are you here?
I come to Wangchuan Soup Shop
Let me inspect the drying conditions of the cucumbers
But what you got was a carrot
adult
Why did you suddenly visit?
The adults said to come and see us
The drying conditions of cucumbers here
cucumber
Sir, why don't you go sit in the front hall?
Tong Feng is about to try out new dishes
I think the soup shop's business is better today
Tong Feng and I won’t stay any longer.
several adults
The day after tomorrow is the day when the villain will be reincarnated.
congratulations
You can finally let go of your past
Tongfeng girl villain
Do you have anything else to do?
The little man heard that Jiuyou once had
The soul of one life is exchanged for all the luck of the next three lives.
Don’t drink Wangchuan soup when you are reincarnated
No, no, no
Teacher Liu Taigong once said
This will ruin your luck for three lifetimes.
It doesn’t matter if the villain is willing to exchange all his luck
I just want to meet my daughter
You didn't get up first
please
Sister Niu Sister Niu
please me
He, he is so pitiful
Yes, but it's not something we can control.
You listen to Niu Mei
It is a taboo for ordinary people to damage their luck in life.
Destroyed for three lifetimes, miserable life
Zhang Juqian is not a villain
He can't be punished like this
Then let me go and beg Xuan Pei, okay?
Lord, in order to prevent him from escaping into the evil spirit realm,
It’s been a lot of painstaking efforts
The so-called confinement for three months is also to protect his soul and body.
Give him soul-preserving soup every day
Now this request is made again
I am afraid
Absolutely not
If you don’t drink Wangchuan soup, you can be reincarnated with your memories.
But the luck of these three lives
As long as you don’t drink the Wangchuan soup, the reincarnated soul will
This life book will automatically change
Three lifetimes of bad luck cannot escape
There is no soul here that can be reincarnated without drinking soup.
Tomorrow night I will take Zhang Juqian to reincarnation
You hold Sister Niu back
In this way, Zhang Juqian can
No need to drink Wangchuan soup
Went to meet his daughter with the memory
do you think i'm smart
don't think
In this way, Zhang Juqian’s luck in the third life will be gone.
And the adults said
I don’t agree with him being reincarnated with his memories.
You insist that he be reincarnated with his memories
It’s because the good luck of the third life has disappeared.
The good luck in the third life is not good enough
Do you know how difficult it is to survive the third life?
So
Not only do I want him to be reincarnated with his memories,
I also want to change his destiny