Sick for a few days
There is still so much homework
Kyuubi-sensei is so inhumane
Tongfeng Tongfeng
Someone is looking for you
Xu Jing
Miss Tongfeng
I have been officially removed from the Evil Spirit Path
I came here specifically to thank you today
What are you grateful for?
It's all small things
Don't take it to heart
I have a few words to say to you alone
alone
Isn't this just carrying me behind your back?
I brought you here
Do you still have any conscience?
What to say
This is something that the noble Lord Ma Yichun cannot listen to.
Ma Yichun
As a soul, you must learn to read other people’s eyes
Sorry, Mr. Ma Yichun
Ma Yichun
That's pretty much it
Please take a seat
It’s great that you can avoid entering the realm of evil spirits.
Before falling into the path of evil spirits
All I can think about is
Why am I treated poorly?
Why can Wang Ruonian love other people so much?
Dancing girls of Peony orchid Paramount
certainly
And the person he can't face
he loves them
But put me to death
Since he doesn't want my precious love
It's him who loses, not me
Because to this day
I understand one thing
What's up
there is a person
He gave me his unique love
In a fantasy world, I am the richest person
Miss Tongfeng
I will wait patiently for Lin Qing in Jiuyou
Wait for him to tell me
The love that surpasses all in this world
That's great of you to think so.
in life
Money and power are fleeting
Once you enter the Nine Netherworld, everything is empty
But there's only one thing Jiuyou can't take away
Is it true love?
Only true love can't be taken away
Um
To truly love someone is a miracle
If you have such a miracle
You must tell him quickly
my miracle
That day I fell into the realm of evil spirits
Almost hurt the girl
The gentleman in white next to you
Knock me back with magic
He cherishes you in his arms
The way he looked at you then
Make my heart tremble
eyes
Lin Qing looked at me that way back then.
Miss Tongfeng
Now I tell you this
Can you find your own miracle?
my miracle
It's Xuan Pei
Tongfeng
Xuan Pei
What do you want to see me for so late?
My magic can only create this moment of fireworks
But I still want to give you this starry sky
Tongfeng
Xuan Pei Xu Jing came to me today and told me a lot of things
She made me understand one thing
What
She said human life is short
Being able to truly love someone is a miracle
to be truly loved by others
It is God’s best blessing
Xuan Pei
I have been bathing in God's grace
Ever since I opened my eyes in Jiuyou three thousand years ago
There are many friends around me who love and care for me
Unlike those lonely ghosts in Jiuyou
I'm very grateful
God gave me such a gift
Xu Jing let me know
I have already
got my miracle
But people are always greedy
get a miracle
I still want to tell it
Ask for another good blessing from it
you got a miracle
right
Xuan Pei
I
i have always liked you
More than I like rag dolls and lotus cakes, there are also scripts
In total, I like you a lot more
I didn't understand the meaning of love before
But she said that if you love someone
Just tell him immediately
Because you don't know the next moment
What kind of accident will happen that will cause lifelong regret?
Xuan Pei, let me tell you
I tell you all my love
are you willing to accept
My miracle?
The resurgence of fireworks in the mortal world is called a miracle
The appearance of stars in the Nine Nether Sky is a miracle
Now I will give my miracle
Give it to you
Xuan Pei, let me tell you
I tell you all my love
are you willing to accept
My miracle?
The appearance of stars in the Nine Nether Sky is a miracle
Now I will give you my miracle
Who is it?
Tongfeng
There is definitely something wrong with these two people
What’s wrong with you
This ice bowl is so cold that it touches my fingers
it hurts
Really
Oh my god
I'm blind, I'm blind
release
Niu Mei and the others just now
That them over there
Speak slowly
what happened
allow me to slow down
Tong Feng finally understands what love is
I, Ma Yichun, have taught her earnestly over the years.
It’s not in vain.
What do you mean?
Don’t you understand this?
Tong Feng understood her love for adults
is different
Tong Feng and the adults are going to be together completely
You said Tong Feng and Sir are real and fake?
You still don’t believe me when I tell you this?
you just now
I really don’t know what I saw
Your Excellency, I have been struck twice by lightning.
Didn't shout a word
I just got a bowl of icing cheese
He just screamed to Tong Feng that his hands hurt.
Tong Feng breathed hot breath on the adults' fingers
Her eyes are so gentle that they are about to drip with water
I'm really going blind
So where is this big news?
I want to see it too
Just over there
Meng Dihua, you are here too
I
It's a good thing that Tong Feng knows
Yes, yes, yes
Come here quickly
what
The little wife nicknamed Mr. Waifu Jun is here to stay
The Lord of Bingbing Mansion wraps his fingers around his beloved wife's incarnation
Exclusive insider gossip
Do you want one?
I want it too
The boss gives you money
Take it yourself
release
Come here
Niu Mei Niu Mei Niu Mei pay attention
You said you don't have a handle on what you say?
You clearly know what Ogihana is to adults
How did I know that Ogihua was here?
Does she still like adults after all these years?
Didn't you see her back as she left just now?
So lonely that it almost rains
It seems that I took less
One bottle is enough. The wine in the store is quite expensive.
landlady
Do you like Hyun Bae?
do you know
in everyone's heart
There are all extremely regrettable things
but something
No need to get to the bottom of things
Everyone has regrets in their heart
What about you? Do you have one too?
my brother is missing
I also found my brother
a long time
But I still can't find any trace of him
Someone told me that your brother has passed away.
Stop looking for it, but I don’t believe it
My brother is very good to me
We have been dependent on each other since childhood
I don't believe it
He will leave me alone
your brother
I've never heard you mention it
landlady
You've never mentioned it
Is it about you and Xuan Pei?
I know
Probably only
When the heart is seriously injured
Only then will I bury it deep in my heart
The deepest words are revealed
Don't say anything
I'm afraid it's really hard for my heart to bear the load.
Do you like Tong Feng
turn out to be
It's really too late
this is not for you
Who is that for?
secret
This is what you eat
You can't blame me
Xuan Pei, why are you like this?
Still don't want to tell me
Who is it for?
not tell you
Tongfeng, where are you going?
Let me give something to Xiao Mencius
did you see her
Little Mencius is in the room
Then I'll go first. Bye bye.
Bye-Bye
It turns out that she came to see Meng Dihua
Little Mencius
Tongfeng
You are here to bring me food
you see
Still my favorite caramel strawberry
What can you do with your little clumsy hands?
Little Mencius
I heard Ma Yichun say
You to Xuan Pei
In fact, you don’t have to do this for Xuan Pei
I'm worried about you
Tongfeng
You and Xuan Pei have always been very good.
I can't find any reason to destroy you
If you because of this
To be alienated from me
That's what saddens me the most
How can I be alienated from you?
Tong Feng, listen to me