This matter is finally over
Didn't expect mortals
So afraid of ghosts
Usually lies
When I see a ghost
All the truth has been told
There are thousands of people in this world
Very few people have actually seen ghosts
Complexity and coldness can be seen everywhere
greedy people
That's what's really better than ghosts
Something more terrifying
Do you know that because of hurting mortals?
You will be punished after returning to Jiuyou
Even I can't protect you
This is the Nine Nether Laws
no one can change
I know
When I promised Lin Qing
I've already thought about it
no matter what kind of punishment
I work with one soul and do the work with one soul
Even if the soul is gone
I won't regret the decision I made at this moment
You really haven't changed
Get out of the way Get out of the way
It's almost gone
get out of the way
It's gone, it's gone
You must die a good death
Go to hell
Lin Qing Wang Ruonian was imprisoned
Why don't you look very happy?
I'm not unhappy
I'm just thinking
If the eldest young lady is still here
Seeing Wang Ruonian finally being punished by evildoers
I don't know how happy she will be
She will definitely know
Lin Qing
Now you and Wanwan are both safe and sound
No one will harass you anymore
Thank you both for your help
This matter is settled
Wait until I arrange for someone to take care of Wanwan
I can rest in peace now
Wanwan quickly expresses her gratitude to the two benefactors.
No, no, no, no
We will definitely meet each other under Jiuquan
Sister, this was won by my brother
Wanwan wore it for a few days
I think this is more suitable for my sister
Last night I heard Uncle Lin say
You and your brother are leaving soon
Wanwan gave this beautiful ring to her sister
Sister, you must not forget Wanwan
after
Just see this ring
I have to think of Wanwan
Wanwan
I will never forget you
Since Wang Ruonian has been eliminated
It's time for us to go back
Sister, you must take good care of yourself
Um
Walk
Wait a moment
Tong Feng, you’re late
She has now completely become a resentful spirit.
Forget it, Tong Feng
Too late
The seducing brother and the killing brother
Can I have a few more words with her?
good
But you have to be careful
Xu Jing
do you remember me
Do you remember this bottle?
Do you remember the words engraved on this vase?
plum blossom snow
Rikazuki
Always lovesick
Xu Jing
Do you know what Lin Qing has done for you?
Wanwan is still alive
Just eight years old
So cute
She will pull my clothes
call me sister
Lin Qing said
He really likes you
Although I don’t know what I like
But someone once told me
There are many kinds of love in the world
parental love
conjugal love
children love
I understood after meeting Lin Qing
He doesn't like you
It's love, do you understand?
He spent his whole life loving you
I lost my most cherished life.
You accepted all his love alone
plum blossom snow
Rikazuki
Always lovesick
Her resentment began to dissipate
Xu Jing
I know why you are so angry
Because you feel like no one in the world loves you
But do you know
Lin Qing's original opportunity
After leaving the palace, he went to join the army.
When you are thirty, your life is precious.
For the freedom of the motherland
fight hard
Pledge loyalty to Governor Lin to the death
He changed his life for you.
After he left the palace
Didn't join the army
Choose to take care of your daughter Wanwan
He also wants to avenge you
his love for you
Changed the most unchangeable destiny in the world
His love for you changes God's will
his love for you
It is the most surging love in the world
Do you still feel that no one in the world loves you?
Are you going to be contaminated by Jiuyou’s most resentful and poisonous resentment?
Xu Jing
Na Lin Qing
What will be his next chance?
Your resentment dissipates
Lin Qing
He gave up joining the army to protect your daughter.
It is a taboo to change one's destiny against the will of nature.
His chances in the second half of his life
Will die young
He will die of tuberculosis in a few months
He's a fool
He should have told me
Why didn't he tell me?
He's a fool
Xuan Pei
Xu Jing will not fall into the evil spirit path, right?
Don't worry, her resentment is gone
I will never enter the path of evil spirits again
Does Niu Mei really want to punish Tong Feng?
Even adults can't protect Tong Feng?
no way
Tong Feng really made a big mistake this time
She went to the fantasy world and used magic to hurt mortals.
If you protect her, sir
It's just unfair law enforcement
Adults can't do this
adult
Tong Feng uses magic to harm mortals
Violating the "Nine Nether Laws"
must be punished
Don't worry
I didn't want to protect her
Please also ask the adults to seal the dark patterns on Tong Feng’s body.
Ah Ming
adult
This is Tong Feng’s mistake
Her punishment cannot be borne by you
you
If you insist not to seal it,
Then let your subordinates come and seal it
enough
I'll do it myself
It's okay, Hyun Bae
If I make a mistake, I should be punished.
What's the punishment?
Walking through the torture of extreme cold and fire
I cast Jiuxiao Handao
Taking lives and burning heavenly karma fire
The punishment of extreme cold and fire
It is the soul that punishes the great treacherous and evil people.
punishment
Nine Nether Soul Tongfeng
Injuring the mortal Wang Ruonian in the illusion
Violate the laws of Jiuyou
Deservable to the punishment of extreme cold and fire
You can plead guilty and get punished
I receive the penalty
But I don't admit guilt
Ordinary King Young Wolf Heart Dog Lung
Almost caused Xu Jing, a mortal, to fall into the realm of evil spirits
If you are not punished by God, then it is unfair.
Nine Nether Laws
It is the law that binds the soul
But one lives forever
There are always areas where the law cannot take full care of
A mortal's life is like a candle in the wind
injustice happened to them
I always just pray to God for destiny
Punish the evildoers and punish the evil consequences
If everything is based on the Nine Nether Laws and Orders,
What's the use of gods and damnation?
stubborn
Seducing one's soul and taking one's life
execution
Tongfeng
It's fine
The seducing brother and the killing brother
You will be punished how you want to be punished
When I committed a crime in the fantasy world
Already prepared
Burning Heavenly Fire
Burning Heaven's Fire Execution is Completed
Tongfeng
I'm fine
I can still hold on
next punishment
Jiuxiao Handao
Tongfeng
Is Niu Mei Tongfeng okay?
Your Excellency will not let anything happen to Tong Feng
adult
Tong Feng, is she okay now?
Has basically recovered
Rest for a few more days
can recover
Fortunately, Tong Feng is blessed with good fortune.
Tongfeng
you wake up
Xuan Pei
Let's go out first
Take a walk
Gone
Walk
Are you satisfied?
He was punished and his body was bruised
Do you know the punishment of extreme cold and fiery fire?
It is the spirit that punishes the great evildoers.
The punishment that will only be used
Aren't you afraid of losing your soul?
because i know
Xuan Pei will not let me die
Didn't you promise me
Won't you get yourself hurt?
Na Xuan Pei
Are you going to punish me again?
What penalty?
You
I really have no choice
Tongfeng
how are you
Look what can happen to me
It was just roasted by the fire
you don't have to worry
How could I not be worried?
Why are you trying to be brave?
The punishment of extreme cold and fire
Is this something you, a tender-skinned person, can handle?
It's okay, just a minor injury
It's okay
And Xuan Pei lost a lot of spiritual power to me
How many days will it take?
I can be alive and kicking now
Already almost recovered
It will take a few days to recover
So Tong Feng
why are you punished
Is there no one to protect you?
I'm in fantasy
Injured a mortal with a spell
You can't do it for no reason
To hurt a mortal
What happened to Tong Feng?
There is a mortal
Almost killed a kind soul
Fall into the realm of evil spirits
If not punished by God
Xu Jing of Jiuyou
Lin Qing and Wanwan in the fantasy world
Everybody will live in pain
Isn't this a good deed?
Why are you punished?
fukun adult
If you can’t take good care of Tong Feng
Let her move to the soup shop
I'll take care of her
Biluo courtyard is very big
Tong Feng is also very comfortable here
I don't need you as an outsider
Come here and give advice
Si Mo, it’s my fault for this.
Nine Nether Rules
You cannot use magic to harm mortals.
Since I broke the law, I should be punished
This makes sense, right?
Such an inhumane Jiuyou
Are you still willing to stay?
If you don't want to stay
Si Mo
I think you are Tong Feng’s friend.
I tolerate you again and again
If you transgress again and again
I will use the power of Fujun
Of course I want to stay in Jiuyou
There are so many good friends here
and
Still a warm place