How to sing your dream?
I'll draw the sky with my own hands
Let everything be the glory in the dark night
I'm not afraid
Listen to the sound of your favorite
How to forget the memory
It turns out to be a kind of encounter
Don't be afraid
Listen to the sound of your tiger and your wolf
Listen to the sound of your favorite
How to forget the memory
It turns out to be a kind of encounter
Don't be afraid
Listen to the sound of your favorite
How to forget the memory
It turns out to be a kind of encounter
Don't be afraid
Listen to the sound of your favorite
How to forget the memory
It turns out to be a kind of encounter
Don't be afraid
Listen to the sound of your tiger and your wolf
Listen to the sound of your favorite
I'm not afraid
How to forget the memory
It turns out to be a kind of encounter
Don't be afraid
Listen to the sound of your favorite
How to forget the memory
You failed
I will follow the agreement
I won't come again
It's okay, Shengnan
Even if you can't enter the Hualan team
I will always practice with you
Even if we practice alone, we can practice slowly
It will be better slowly
Zhou Yue, Lin Shengnan
You can rest assured
I won't come again
I said I would do it
Okay, from tomorrow on
Don't let us see you again
Ah Jie, you are too old
Shengnan has been working hard for this period of time
You use this attitude
Be careful not to sit down
Shengnan, you are too old
Shengnan, don't pretend to be old
Shengnan's fun
Shengnan, you are too old
You are too old
Shengnan, your hand is too old
No, you don't have to pity me.
I didn't do the moves I just did.
I know.
I haven't taught you the secret of the truth.
How could you succeed?
You were fooling me at the beginning.
No.
If you succeed, I will make it.
I will let you join our team.
It's a pity that you didn't.
You said we can practice together.
Because I believe you.
Believe me?
I believe you are different from those who are curious
and stupid to learn how to play the ball.
You didn't pass the exam,
but you touched me with your love for the ball.
You are even more popular than many boys.
So I decided to take you as my disciple
and train with us.
Jian, you finally figured it out.
You are the one who should be rewarded.
I will follow the rules.
After all, I am the one who should be rewarded.
You failed this time.
You can't join our team.
But I am sure to train with you.
Why are you so stubborn?
Jian, thank you.
No matter if you can join the team,
you have already agreed to train with them.
I am very grateful.
Don't worry. I will cherish this opportunity.
Jian, you are here.
Yes, I didn't expect it.
You should play the ball first.
Then let the ball pass the ball.
Then you can turn the ball to the inside.
Then you can catch the ball to the inside.
It's so interesting.
Forget it.
Look at the fixed time.
It's a skill to be on the top and bottom.
Once you are on the top,
you don't need to write the textbook.
It's not your homework to write your textbook.
Why are you so afraid?
Come on.
It's not enough to write the textbook.
The most important thing is to understand.
Did you know what I just told you?
If you don't know, I will tell you again.
I heard it, Yangyang.
I will write the textbook.
My colored water bottle.
It's so boring.
It hides my hand and skin.
It hides my water bottle.
Just kidding.
It's so fun.
You are so good at learning.
You should try to find the right way.
Don't know it.
The next goal I will test is to surpass you.
Fine.
If you can surpass me, I will teach you.
You are so smart.
You are a man of the world.
You should treat them well.
Fine.
If you can't pass me the test,
I will teach you to train the wind and wind leg
when I practice the flower and basketball next time.
Deal.
I will teach you to practice the wind and wind leg.
I will teach you to practice the wind leg.
稚草
You can protect the ground where the wind blade is looking at
with the part of the skin on your body.
I will take cover past you.
Let's believe in this.
Okay.
I have a plan.
Let's do preparations on our trip.
organic
A Wizards diamond
Jubiner
generates the 100 walking medium
Who?
Okay, come here.
What did you choose after the game?
Who?
I choose...
C.
I'm in the wrong team.
You've finished the exam.
Can you let me have a rest?
What did you choose?
Thank you.
Did you choose the wrong team?
I'm so annoyed.
What's the arrangement?
Han Jia Yu is not a summer vacation.
He can use any arrangement.
It's just half a year.
Brother Han Yue,
do you have any idea?
How about
Xiaonian Ye come to my house to play with friends?
I think it's okay.
I'll do it.
I'll do it, too.
Why can't Wang You Xi come to me?
What's wrong?
Where are you going?
Wang You Xi, are you going?
I'm going to the play.
We...
Let's go together.
Okay.
People are all excited.
I'm not going.
I don't like playing games.
Are you afraid that
you can't compare to Yao Yao after the game?
That's why you don't dare to come?
Who said I don't dare?
I'm going.
Come on.
Zhou Yue,
you're so big.
I heard that you have such a big belly.
You're so big.
Hello.
Uncle Yue.
Hello, Yao Yao.
Hello, uncle.
I'm Ruzong Dong.
I'm done.
Hello, Dong Dong.
How are you?
I'm very happy to see you.
Hello, uncle.
Hello.
You're Shengnan, right?
I often invite you to my house.
Hello, uncle.
My name is Zhang Lei.
Hello.
My name is Zhuang Wen Jing.
Hello, uncle.
My name is Jiaxin.
Hello.
Yue,
take care of my friends.
You guys play first.
We'll have dinner later.
Come in.
Come on.
Let's take you to the restaurant.
Come.
Let's take a look at my study.
So many awards.
These are all from my hometown, Lao Zhou.
Uncle used to get a bag of ginseng.
How come?
That's right.
Lao Zhou used to have two pairs of gloves.
Before.
Lao Zhou used to be a soldier.
He was a soldier in the army.
But he changed his job.
Why?
Uncle was injured in the army before.
He had to retire.
After he returned to the local army,
he did some cultural books in the police station.
What a pity.
But I'm so proud of him.
There's a saying.
The father and the son are always together.
Yes.
He's really good.
He's so good.
But Zhou Yue,
your family is so good.
If I were in my family,
I'd call my dad like that.
He'd probably give me a head shot.
I've been shouting like this since I was a kid.
Lao Zhou is so sweet.
He's a brother.
You've never tried it.
How do you know?
Really?
How about trying it?
I'll try it next time.
Let's go.
Let's take you to other places.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's go.
Zhou Yue,
your dishes are so good.
They are.
Guys,
I suggest
you to finish your food.
Okay.
How's it going?
Have some fruit and fruit.
Okay. Thank you.
Uncle,
we'll play a game together later.
You guys play.
You should cut something.
We'll play together.
Let's play together.
Just a moment.
I'll show you.
Come on.
Okay.
Let's go.
Come on.
Let's play together.
Let's go.
You're so fast.
Right away.
No one is looking at you.
You're so far away.
Hurry up.
I'm not good at playing.
I'm good at drawing.
There's a sale in the supermarket.
There's a school store.
There are many brands.
Uncle,
please describe the words on the table.
This thing
is long strip.
Long square.
Okay.
The first round is over.
Let's start voting.
I said three, two, one.
You guys are
the people in the bottom of the box.
Okay?
Come on. Three, two, one.
Go.
The first round.
The third round is out.
Go. Go. Go.
Go there.
The audience is used to it.
Go. Go. Go.
Go. Go.
You want to play with me?
The people are wrong.
The game continues.
No. 1.
The packaging is
usually purple and pink.
I've seen blue before.
The packaging is white.
It
will be purple
before and after it's used.
It's not used.
It's now used.
This thing
is long strip.
Long strip.
Okay.
The second round is over.
Come on. Three, two, one.
Go.
The second round is...
Come on.
The audience is used to it.
Go. Go. Go.
Go. Go. Go. Go.
The game continues.
It should have
different size.
It should be
a person who is on the table.
In a certain specific situation,
people will use black plastic bags
to put it in the box.
Many times,
people will put it in the box.
This thing is used to stick it.
Okay.
Stick it.
The third person is worth it.
The ticket.
Let me explain.
It's the number one and the second.
You two continue to speak.
The rest of you
can only vote for them.
Okay?
The number one is to speak.
I got it.
This thing
is too young to use.
According to you,
it's too old to use.
You are playing water.
How can I see
you two
like a group of people?
Playing water.
He is learning.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Go.
Okay.
The score.
Come on.
The last digit.
The number one is to speak.
Let me explain.
This is the last digit.
If the object is still on the field,
it is the object's victory.
So please vote for it.
Come on.
The last digit.
The number one is to speak.
According to my limited knowledge,
this thing
is used every month.
Only girls can use it.
You have to choose the one who is透气.
This thing
is related to blood.
It's used when there is blood.
Zhou, you...
Say it.
You said it too directly.
Come on.
Let's hurry up and vote.
Three, two, one.
Vote.
Okay.
I will announce
the game is over.
The object is on the field.
Who is the object?
It must be the same.
It's Yao Yao.
Yao Yao is the object.
You voted wrongly.
Uncle, it's not me.
It's not me.
Yao Yao, you...
Uncle, you are the object.
You are the object.
I am the object.
I don't suspect
it's uncle.
Dad, what is it?
It's me.
No.
What are you?
Come on.
Let me see.
Sorry, uncle.
Sorry.
You kids
are living in a new era.
They are living in a new era.
Uncle, you are so old.
You can't catch up with them.
But you can
take this question out
and say that you are very happy.
Yes.
But this girl
is not easy to deal with.
You boys
can't take this
to make fun of girls.
Do you know?
Yes.
It's my fault.
Uncle Zhou, you are so kind.
If my dad is like you,
that would be great.
Uncle.
I want to have
a dad like you.
No.
I am the one.
You can be mine.
It's our fault.
You guys are so mean.
It's my fault.
Yes.
You are so mean.
No.
Come on, uncle.
I will massage you.
Bye.
Be careful.
Uncle Zhou,
I am used to it.
Have a rest.
Okay.
I will leave it to you.
Yue.
Shengnan is interesting.
Yes.
If I didn't stop him,
he would recognize you as his dad.
He is not good
with his dad.
Really?
You have to be with him more.
This girl
should be very careful.
I will be there soon, uncle Zhou.
Mom and dad, I am back.
Nannan is back.
Are you hungry?
Do you want to eat something?
I am not hungry.
I am full today.
What did you eat?
Mom, I ate
sweet and sour ribs,
green bean curd fish,
garlic and vermicelli,
red-braised pork,
duck soup,
crab meat,
and a big dragon.
You have a feast today?
They are so rich.
I didn't go to the hotel.
I did it alone last month.
He is amazing.
He is a soldier.
He is good at making food.
He can do housework
and play games with us.
Most importantly,
he can understand
what our children think.
He is good.
That's because
he is good at listening to our children.
Yes.
Zhou Yue is more sensible
and knows how to do housework.
I should learn from him.
Nannan,
I hope you can grow up
and be happy.
I am very happy.
I don't need you to do housework.
Zhou is so dangerous
and like a brother.
You have never tried it.
How do you know?
Old Lin.
The child is calling you.
What is it called?
It's not big or small.
The child is so good.
It's not necessary to teach him.
Don't be so stubborn.
Mom, forget it.
I am going back to my room.
Okay, take a rest.
What did he call me just now?
Didn't I perform for you 150and 70.
Zhou is inside.
What?
He can find it?
I'm left here 10 minutes late
Okay.
Answer me,
when I go to the group show podcast,
we should
truly let you see
the way the coach is singing the song.
OK, Mom,
The Daddy otherwise
there will be great interior music.
If you can't win this game,
you can't win the 1st Street Cup.
Their efforts are a great help to us.
And I think they really like Hualan.
They have a talent.
So I think...
I want to give them a chance to prove their friendship.
We don't have any chance.
Boss, we've already treated them as family.
We're very familiar with our family, right?
Then we'll give Zhou Yue and Shengnan a chance to prove their friendship.
Prove it!
Okay.
Thank you, Jiange.
We'll work hard to train to follow everyone's steps.
I'll cheer for Yao Da.
Welcome!
Yao Wei!
We're the trainees.
The more we train, the more we'll be able to grow!
Okay!
You're the one who gave this to Yao Yao.
It's a chocolate.
And...
What's on your mind?
I wish you the best.
What's on my mind?
Besides, I really don't know what she likes to eat.
Then you can ask me before you give it to me.
Mom, I'm so poor.
Don't worry.
It's not expensive.
It's definitely cheaper than this chocolate.
Double-edged snow crab and ice cream.
How is it?
Then I'll give you two chicken wings with a glass of warm water.
Really?
So she wants to eat it?
It's not good.
Really?
I've been a big-headed person since I was a kid.
But, bro,
I have to remind you.
No one can dig a hole in the Pacific Ocean.
Think about it.
Go back to the same world.
Who said I was a big-headed person?
I'm still a little bit rich.
I'm rich.
I'm a little bit rich.
I'm going to...
I'm going to give it to you.
When you come back today,
I'm going to give you an order to drop your bag.
premier
iş
The younger brother comes and tries to open a garden for the previous month.
He is tired and he is not willing to eat something.
Yes
He was here until like four years ago.
He just takes up the clothes just to play.
He was in all those clothes at twelve years.
He loves it
It's so粗
I'll see.
What kind of trick is this?
Who sent these?
These days, besides these snacks,
there's nothing else.
Wait a minute.
Who can send these things?
I probably know who it is.
I'm sorry.
I can't waste it.
I'll take it to the chef.
I'll go.
Why am I so stupid?
Forget it, bro.
I know Yao Yao too well.
She's not interested in dating.
I know.
Then you can send it.
If you keep sending it, there won't be any result.
I know what you mean.
Isn't this the first time I like someone?
I'm not good at it.
Bro, have you ever thought about it?
Sometimes you think it's good for her.
But it's just a wish.
Okay, bro.
I know what you mean.
I know she's a kind person.
I'll send her snacks to her.
I won't send them to you.
You're both my friends.
I don't want her to be troubled.
You don't want to be hurt, do you?
I'm fine.
You don't care.
I'm a big man.
You don't care about me.
Okay.
I'm a big man.
I don't care about you.
You don't care about me.
I'm a big man.
Take care.
We will be friends for the rest of our lives
My friend, my friend
Let's fight and let go together
Let's fight together, the strongest monster
Let's make the most beautiful dream together
My friend, my beloved friend
Let's face the dream together
No matter how far, let's cheer together
Always be your friend for the rest of our lives
Translated by 中文字幕 李宗盛