(Shin Hyun Been)
(Moon Sang Min)
(Yoon Bak, Park So Jin)
(Jin Hee Kyung, Lee Kyu Sung, Kim Gyu Nam)
(Kim Tae Jeong, Hong Bi Ra, Jung Ji Soon)
(Creator Park Jun Hwa)
(Scriptwriter Oh Eun Ji)
(Directors Seo Min Jung, Bae Hee Young)
(Cinderella at 2AM)
(Production support by the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism...)
(and Korea Creative Content Agency)
You left your car by the Han River.
I'll drive you.
Let's talk on the way.
Okay.
I'm sorry, but she was talking to me.
Don't you want to know how I knew who you were?
I'll explain. Let's go and eat.
Let's go to the Han River.
Let's go eat.
- The Han River. - Let's eat.
- Let's eat the Han River. - What?
I mixed up the two sentences.
Eat the Han River on your own.
Let's go and eat.
I'll hear your explanation another time.
Let's go. I have something to say.
What are you doing?
Give me a ride too.
You're going to the Han River. I'm heading that way.
What way is that way?
You don't know where my car is parked.
It'll be somewhere on earth.
Seoul's not as big as you think.
Somewhere close to Yongsan works for me.
Director. You should get going.
My gosh.
(The director)
(The director's your ex?)
Is he?
Erase it right now.
(The director's your ex?)
So...
how did you get to know each other?
Oh, well,
how should I explain?
We got close by texting each other.
You can't say we got close.
You texted me by mistake.
Exactly.
I texted her thinking she was someone I knew.
Was it because the texts were wistful?
Ms. Ha mistakenly thought they were from her ex.
Did you say your heart sank as if you'd gotten a red alert?
What are you doing?
Don't you think this is wrong when we decided to break up?
You two.
You seem pretty close for people who got phone numbers mixed up.
We are emotionally closer than you'd think.
Is it because we texted and talked a lot?
That was a one-sided...
Forget it.
How did you know I was Ha Yoon Seo who works at AL Group?
I happened to find out by chance.
AL Hanok Stay's opening exhibition?
I get that you're in a bind,
but you need a fill-in.
You know you were our first pick.
Let's meet and I'll explain in person.
No. I have the proposal you sent last time.
I'll read that and get back to you.
(Ha Yoon Seo)
(Ha Yoon Seo, Jae Hee)
I thought it would be a fun project with a fun acquaintance,
so I accepted right away.
I don't care much about destiny,
but I almost believed it this time.
Drop me off at the subway station. That would be faster.
(Saebit Station)
I'll be in touch, Ms. Ha.
Save my number.
I asked you to drop me off back there.
There was a lot of traffic.
It's just a few steps. You can walk.
The street was empty...
Okay. See you next time.
What's going on? Is this...
You've been working here for a while and you call this a report?
- Do it over. - Okay.
- Oh, and Ju Won. - Yes?
Get me a latte.
Sure thing.
Did you see how I got revenge?
I waited for three seconds before answering Mr. Bae.
Did you? What a cruel way to get revenge.
He picked on me a few days ago,
so I drove 30m by the subway station he asked me to stop at.
You must be tired. Can you drive?
Yes.
Was that your timid way of getting revenge?
What?
It wasn't.
I think...
Mr. Lee teased us a bit knowing we used to date.
He's just an odd character. Don't mind him too much.
I have to mind anyone who shows interest in you.
Why would you call that interest?
It's not that.
Can't you report his number as spam?
Why would you say that?
The exhibition opens on Monday...
and we have tons to discuss.
Why do you work so hard when you said you'd quit?
You said yesterday...
that you were disappointed by how irresponsible I was.
I wasn't disappointed.
I was jealous.
I hadn't sorted out my emotions yet,
but you went on a blind date...
and was going out to eat right after an all-night shift.
That makes me look like a fool.
Mr. Lee just followed me outside,
and the blind date...
I met him because he was a headhunter...
and I wanted to switch jobs.
What?
I showed him my resume not knowing it was a blind date.
My goodness.
I had such a stressful day.
And you were so cold...
and you upset me.
Were you upset?
Because I turned cold?
To be honest, it wasn't nice.
Goodness.
But then,
even I don't know how I feel.
I thought I wouldn't mind if you disliked me,
but it was frustrating to be misunderstood.
We're going to break up,
but I didn't like how cold you were.
But...
we can't do this.
Why can't we do this?
We can't keep going on...
with longing and regret,
failing to get over each other.
I'll keep doing this.
Failing to get over you.
Like right now.
You said before...
that you could...
live just fine without love.
But I...
don't want to live like that without you.
Can't you come back to me?
What number time is this?
We broke up so many times I memorized the pattern.
Are you singing in repeat?
Why are we always at square one?
I must be out of my mind because I didn't get any sleep.
Let's call it a day. Now go home.
Go on home.
(Coupon)
Did you get home safely?
I'll visit AL Card on Monday.
How about fried chicken for dinner?
I'm fascinated that we met like this.
It feels like it's meant to be.
It's fascinating but I'm not sure if it's good or bad karma.
Don't make any comments about me and the director.
I almost took the bait.
Get a grip, Ha Yoon Seo.
This guy is no longer that psycho.
He's an artist I must work with.
An artist.
(Artist Lee Sung Min)
What happened?
How dare you stay out all night?
I texted you to say we had an emergency...
and would work all night.
Get out of the way.
Do you mean that? You weren't with Wimp, were you?
I worried about you all night.
I heard that Wimp had left home.
I thought you eloped or something.
As if we'd elope.
Get out unless you want a nosebleed.
Yoon Seo. You need to be strong.
I watched lots of crazy dramas.
You don't want to marry into a family of mad in-laws.
Are you bragging about watching dramas...
instead of studying when you're a high-school senior?
Yoon Seo.
Did Wimp not go home yet?
- What? - If he’s moved out,
is he just out and about all day?
I don't know.
Look at you.
You look worried. You still care about him.
Get lost.
Out.
Darn you.
Who is it?
It's me. Open the door.
Si Won?
What are you doing here?
Is this where you're staying?
What? Well, yes.
Take this.
Instead of staying at a hotel, pick one of those apartments.
No. I'll take care of myself.
What can you take care of?
Do you know people are talking about you moving out?
They think you're no longer in line...
to inherit part of the company.
- What? - If you like her that much,
win Yoon Seo back.
But...
if you haven't managed so far, it means she won't take you back.
Give up on what you can't do and go back to where you belong.
Mother asked me to give that to you.
It looks like it means she wants you back, not gone.
Hello.
- Hello. - Mr. Lee.
Hello, Mr. Lee.
Have you heard, Mr. Lee?
People crowded the gallery as soon as the exhibition opened.
I expect that much.
I'm pretty popular.
You sure are popular.
I thought we were in so much trouble on Friday.
I guess we can say a misfortune turned into a blessing.
I don't know how to make it up to you.
Thank you again for making a tough decision to help us out.
Instead of just talking about it,
how about we have chicken and beer?
- What? - Yes?
Chicken and beer isn't good enough.
You can have something more expensive.
On AL Card's dime.
Will you treat him to a decent meal today?
Well, of course.
Do come inside. The contract's ready.
Okay.
- This is for you. - Thank you.
Yes.
Let's not let my emotions ruin a business deal.
(Artist and Gallery Contract)
Let's move ahead with the deal.
Don't you need another look?
I read it for long enough.
You know I studied law.
Didn't we meet a few times at university?
You were famous for being a third-generation conglomerate,
and I was famous for my looks.
I too was famous for...
We'll go over the contract again before signing and sending it over.
I'll see you at dinner tonight.
You attend team dinners?
What does that mean?
I'm just wondering...
if it's to treat me or to keep me in check.
Don't get me wrong.
You're Ms. Ha's red alert.
Her ex.
I wondered...
if you were over her.
Why do you want to know that?
Why do you think...
I want to know?
Hi.
Right now?
A sudden meeting was scheduled to discuss the General Cars' MOU.
The client happened to be in Korea,
and can meet with us on Jeju Island.
Are we leaving in an hour?
Yes.
Right now?
I'll be there.
I apologize. Something urgent came up.
I'm interested.
Should I call it curiosity?
I don't know how honest I can be to her ex.
She seems cold, but she's interesting.
And I'm grateful to her for something.
Mr. Lee.
I happened to read the texts you'd sent to your ex-girlfriend.
It looked like you broke up recently yourself.
How can you move on so easily?
Those texts weren't for my ex-girlfriend.
I haven't dated in a long time.
I see.
Ms. Ha could've gotten the same idea too.
I should explain it to her.
- Seo Ju Won. - What?
Didn't you hear what I said yesterday?
Don't cling to what is over and focus on work.
Okay.
(Monhyeon-ro)
- It's a pleasure to meet you. - It's a pleasure.
Where's the director? He said he'd be here.
He went to Jeju Island on urgent business.
Oh, I see.
That's perfect.
Why are you staring at me like that?
You look like you should be...
an actor and not an artist.
Instead of drawing landscapes,
why don't you paint a self-portrait?
That's a bit much.
The thing is, however hard I try,
I don't think I'll be able to do my face justice.
You're right.
That's so right.
- Mr. Lee. - Yes?
This might be the last time we get to eat together.
Can we take a photo?
Yes, sure. Sounds good.
- Yes. - Me too.
Okay.
Let's see.
Ms. Ha, join us. It's a rare opportunity.
No, thanks.
Let's not take a photo if we won't all be in it.
Ms. Ha!
What's wrong with you?
- Lean in. - Are you ready?
Here goes. One, two, three.
- Shall I take one? - Yes, sure.
- Get into the frame. - Okay.
Ms. Ha, look at the camera.
One, two, three.
I will be delighted to meet at our next meeting.
Thank you. Bye.
Good job.
- Yes. You too. - Yes.
(Group chat)
- Mr. Kim. - Yes?
What time is our flight?
It's in two hours at 9pm.
Two hours from now...
Three hours to Gimpo and four to Gangnam.
No.
No what?
What's this photo?
Actually,
someone's showing interest in Yoon Seo.
What?
Let me see that.
Isn't this Lee Sung Min?
You asked me to get his number to sign a business deal.
Did sparks fly in just a few days?
- So soon? - There are no sparks.
- They're at a team dinner. - What?
Oh, you said you had an acquaintance who was close to Lee Sung Min.
- Yes. - Did you hear anything?
What kind of person he is and so on.
I do know some things about him.
He comes from a family of politicians.
His parents had set everything up for him to get into politics too,
but he gave up on his secure future...
and suddenly announced he'd become an artist,
so his family went bonkers.
Then he said he'd estrange himself from his family and moved out...
He's just like you.
No. He eventually ditched his family and became an artist,
so shall I say he's even more stubborn than you?
My gosh. It won't be an easy fight.
Forget it. Let's go.
Hey. Isn't Yoon Seo so pretty?
Here, look.
Yes, she is pretty.
My goodness.
I thought you didn't like theatres because they were dark and stuffy.
But I've been watching movies often lately with Yoon Seo,
and it was all right.
Yoon Seo is acting a bit weird.
Do you think I upset her?
I knew you'd try to keep Yoon Seo by your side,
but I didn't know you'd even refuse to go abroad.
Ju Won did really love her.
Ju Won!
What is it?
I'll help you.
If I don't understand how you feel, who will?
Hey, what's with you? People are looking at us.
Listen to me carefully, Ju Won.
I will...
fulfil Mother's expectations since I'm the eldest son.
So, promise me that you will live the kind of life you want.
- Mr. Kim. - Yes, sir.
We need the helicopter.
The helicopter?
The helicopter? Why, all of a sudden?
Fly there now.
Fly there now and make your dreams come true.
Go and join the team dinner right now...
and make her yours.
Can I really do that?
Nice! Let's do this!
Okay. Here comes the propeller!
- Cheers! Bottoms up! - Bottoms up!
Nice, bottoms up!
She didn't finish her drink. That's not good.
- Finish it. - Drink up!
How much longer will you make me do this shoulder dance?
- Drink up. Bottoms up! - All right, another one.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Why don't we call it a night?
Mr. Lee has to go to Yeosu tomorrow...
for the artist talk event.
He's already had many drinks.
Well, not too many.
Oh, come on.
See? Mr. Lee says he can drink more. Why are you being like this?
Listen. We're putting this on the company credit card,
so I ordered more meat and booze when I went to the restroom earlier.
I also ordered four bowls of doenjang rice.
Oh, that must be it.
Come on in, my doenjang rice!
I'm going to feast today. Don't stop me!
My gosh! Director Seo. Please have a seat here.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I kept you waiting, didn't I?
Why would I wait for you when I didn't even know you were coming?
Well, I thought you went to Jeju Island. Am I wrong?
Oh, Mr. Bae kept calling me nonstop,
so I had no choice but to come here.
Me?
Yes! That's right. Of course.
This team dinner is so important.
Not having Director Seo here makes no sense,
so I kept calling him like crazy.
I went out of my way to come here to help build teamwork.
Let's eat.
I'm sorry we made you go out of your way, but I'm glad you came.
My, this looks delicious. Ms. Ha, try this.
Thank you.
I was in a meeting and didn't have time to eat dinner.
This looks delicious.
Gosh, it's hot.
Yes, I did it.
Nice! I managed to get a reservation.
This bar is very popular. Let's go for another round, okay?
What? Director Seo, what are you doing here?
Oh, the thing is...
I called him a bunch of times, so he came here to join us.
I see.
I'm sorry, but I should call it a night.
What? Why?
Oh, I guess you're uncomfortable because of Director Seo.
Come on. A team dinner is part of work.
I get that you two broke up,
but you should separate your emotions from work...
Fine, let's go.
Come on, let's go.
- Nice! Let's go and drink more! - Okay, let's go.
I'm telling you. This bar is super popular.
(Mother)
Yes, Mother.
Yes, I think the collaboration will go well without any issues.
I see. Well done. Good.
And what's going on with Ju Won?
- Ju Won? - I told you to help...
and guide him as his older brother so he wouldn't feel lost anymore.
He stormed out because he was angry in that moment...
and couldn't come home because of his pride. It must be hard for him.
Well, I'm not sure about that.
In my opinion, he's not back yet because he doesn't want to go home.
What?
Even if that's the case... Like I said,
you should comfort him and persuade him to...
Gosh, Mother. As if he will be persuaded.
For now, we should just wait until he pulls himself together.
That's the best thing we can do now.
Mother, I'm not wearing anything now.
I'll catch a cold.
I'll call you later. Bye.
Hey...
My gosh.
These brats.
The eldest son carrying the weight of the family's expectations.
That's me, Seo Si Won.
Very cool.
Anyway, I wonder if he arrived at the team dinner without any issues.
I hope the traffic wasn't bad.
No, don't get the wrong idea.
No! Stay back. Don't come any closer.
I'm leaving.
I thought you'd be home late because you went to Jeju Island.
Well, yes. But my schedule changed a bit,
so I took the helicopter to return earlier.
Hey, about that just now. I didn't do that to show you.
I never closed the door while living by myself,
so I did it without thinking, purely out of habit.
I'm just saying I'll be careful from now on.
Okay. Let's both be careful now that we live together.
Okay.
I'm sorry for screaming like that earlier.
I saw nothing but skin when I opened the door.
I was just so surprised.
Hey, those pills...
Are they supposed to calm you down?
Then can I take one too?
To be honest, I was really startled earlier.
These are sleeping pills.
Oh, they're sleeping pills.
I guess you're so shocked that you can't even fall asleep.
It wasn't that impactful.
I always have a hard time sleeping.
I see.
I'll add it to the rules we must follow from now on.
"No nudity allowed." I'll write it down.
- Okay? - Yes, for sure. Sounds good.
Come on down. Hurry.
Mr. Lee, it's here.
This place is awesome. It's your first time here, right?
- No, I've been here before. - Oh, really?
- When did you come here? - Wait.
Director Seo, are you sure I called you?
I don't see your name in my recent call history.
Be honest. You came because you still have feelings for her,
because you wanted to have a drink with Ms. Ha.
I'm sorry. Gosh, sorry for being nosy.
Hey, Ye Young! Wait up.
Seriously, why are you doing this?
What?
You said it bothered you. That's why you're here.
It's not like Mr. Lee likes me.
Why did you come all the way here from Jeju Island?
Why are you overreacting like this? Just why?
Do you think I'm being like this for no reason?
What?
You two, aren't you coming?
Are you back together?
Get back together!
I hope you two get back together!
I'm sorry.
Kiss! Go ahead and kiss!
Kiss!
Let's go inside.
And I think you know...
that I'd never do something like this for no reason.
Oh, my.
Seriously, this place is so cool.
Right? Aren't you glad I brought you here?
Yes, totally.
All right. What shall we drink?
Cocktails? Whiskey?
- Whiskey. - Let's have whiskey.
Oh, I guess you both like whiskey.
You two are very similar.
Then as for food, between gambas and a cheese plate...
- A cheese plate. - A cheese plate.
- They chose the same thing again. - Yes.
Goodness. You two should never go on a blind date together.
You'd choose the same girl.
Well, on my way to the ladies' room,
I'll order whiskey and a cheese plate for us.
- No, I'll go. - No, I'll go.
Well, I'll just go.
Excuse me for a moment.
My gosh, Director Seo.
Why are you drinking so fast? Here, try this.
Slow down, okay?
Why? They say latecomers must down three drinks when they arrive.
He was late but didn't do it.
I'll do it now.
I'll down three drinks.
Oh, my. Applause.
Director Seo is a man of his word.
Come on. He only had three glasses of whiskey.
Anyone can do it.
Then why don't you go ahead and do it too?
Sure, why not?
By the way...
Mr. Lee, do you not have a girlfriend?
No. I've been single for a long time.
It's been over three years.
Someone thinks that I recently went through a breakup.
Anyway, I've been single for a long time.
My gosh, I see.
Then may I ask you what your type is?
Well, my type is...
someone who's cold but funny at the same time.
Someone who's charismatic and silly.
Someone who has to work hard to make ends meet...
and does her very best every day.
Someone beautiful like that.
I must do whatever it takes to call it a night.
All right. Why don't we call it a night and go home?
Come on. We should finish this, at least.
Director Seo, you should go home if you're tired.
Me?
You look tired. You should go home.
I look tired?
Are you sure you're not exhausted?
I can finish this by myself.
That night was really weird.
Ju Won is normally polite to everyone,
but he kept losing his cool in front of this man.
I can finish this by myself and have another bottle.
This weirdo who appeared in front of us out of nowhere...
kept provoking us.
I can finish this by myself and have two more bottles.
I can have three more.
I can have four more.
I can easily have five more...
That's enough. You've all had enough to drink.
Once I finish this, we will all go home.
That night, for some strange reason,
I wanted to end the night and that situation as well.
- Oh, my. Amazing. - Nice.
One more bottle!
And eventually...
- Cheers! - Cheers!
- Cheers! - Cheers! Let's drink!
Nice.
He's a real man. Nice.
Excuse me. Give us another bottle.
Pour him another one!
Slow down.
Let's drink!
What's going on? What is this place?
Is this Lee Sung Min's studio?
Why am I here?
What is this? What on earth happened?
Gosh, be careful!
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know, I'm not such a lightweight.
But I got so drunk because I drank too quickly.
Oh, my. You are the prettiest woman I've ever seen.
Can you not forget me because I'm so pretty?
Am I that charming?
Of course, you are!
But aren't I a pretty good catch too?
I'm handsome, tall, rich, and young!
Why do you keep saying you want to break up with me?
I wish you were just adequately good-looking, tall,
- and well-off. - Oh, boy.
Why do you have to be so incredibly charming? Why?
Oh, dear. You're both way too charming.
What am I going to do with you guys?
Hey, charmers. You woke up.
Good morning!
It's so sunny here. What a nice place. Oh, my.
Yes, totally. My gosh.
This is so comfortable. It's better than my bed.
It's amazing!
I guess you're embarrassed, seeing how you're talking nonsense.
Yes, I am embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed!
Yes, I get it.
My gosh. Last night, you two went on a drunken rampage.
Well, so tell me. You two.
Why did you do that last night?
What? What did we do?
Last night, you guys made everyone so uncomfortable.
I tried to call it a night and ended up like this.
I mean, who does a drinking competition? It's so dumb.
Wouldn't it be nice if you two got along?
Why couldn't you just get along? Why did you have to cause this?
Why?
Are you saying this is our fault?
I'm sorry.
Anyway, do not cause another situation like this.
I'm off.
I'm hungover.
You're hungover?
Shall we have pizza? Let's have pizza and go to work together.
What? Who eats pizza when they're hungover?
How about some soybean sprout soup with rice?
I'm good. We'll all recover from the hangover on our own.
Well, thank you for your help.
Gosh.
Wait.
Yoon Seo.
Can we talk?
Can we talk later?
I have a headache now.
Is it a bad headache? Shall I give you a ride...
or pick up some medicine for you?
No, it's not that bad.
I'll see you at work.
(Fresh)
- I'll settle up. - Sure, I can help you with that.
I'm sorry. I didn't bring my wallet.
I'll come back another time.
What?
Gosh.
Darn it.
Hey, charmer. Wait up.
Aren't you grateful that I showed up with your wallet?
Then let's go eat something for our hangover.
How about the gukbap we couldn't have that day?
I have to hurry home and go to work.
Just say that you have a meeting with me first.
Then can't you go to work later?
How about some gukbap and a drink to cure the hangover?
Why on earth are you doing this?
What did I do?
It might be funny to you that I can't get over my boyfriend...
and that I'm acting like a fool in the same space.
But it's not for me.
So, why do you keep making fun of someone else's pain?
I mean...
I was just glad to meet you like this.
I'm not glad.
I only want to meet you for work.
It's humiliating that you know who my ex-boyfriend is...
and how I feel on the inside.
When we were in the car and at the dinner yesterday,
you keep acting friendly with me and provoking him.
It feels like you're crossing the line, and it makes me angry.
You speak so coldly.
I have no reason to be warm to you.
So, stop teasing me in this way.
Even if you don't, I'm already suffering enough.
Yes?
You know I'm going to Paris today and coming back in a week, right?
Yes. You sent me your schedule via messenger app.
Yes. I'm leaving after breakfast. Let's eat together as a family.
Okay, then.
Two bunches of scallions and two sacks of rice.
Yes, that's right, sir. I'll wire the money right away.
Thank you, sir.
So, I'm not the owner.
My niece here is the owner.
I'm just a mere employee. And a very lowly...
Hey, Yoon Seo!
What? What's going on?
Why didn't you go to work and come here at this hour?
Yi Rae.
My stomach hurts so much.
What?
Did you leave home early...
or not go home at all?
- Go away. - Okay.
- Take your time and eat up. - I will.
What's going on?
Did you really drink all night and stay out?
Yes. I have to get going after I eat this.
Then why didn't you just get some soup near the office?
Just because.
I wanted to see you.
Gross.
What is going on?
It's just difficult.
What is?
Breaking up?
Yes.
I don't know how I feel.
I don't understand myself,
and it's so painful.
If he treats me coldly,
it's hard to see him that way.
When I see that he still likes me as he did before,
it seems so childish,
but I feel reassured without meaning to.
I can't let go...
or cling onto him.
My heart keeps breaking apart into pieces.
What is all this?
Ms. Lee told us to prepare it.
She said we'd have breakfast together as a family.
This is way too fancy.
No way...
Did she fall for me after yesterday?
My gosh.
Seriously, I can't help myself.
Mother?
What brings you here...
Didn't you know I was coming?
- Didn't you tell him? - I did.
I told you we were eating together as a family.
Oh, was this what you meant by "family?"
- Have a seat. - Okay.
Well...
It feels strange that you're eating breakfast here, Mother.
It doesn't feel familiar to me either.
But what's going on, all of a sudden?
Just because. It's hard to make time for dinner.
I wanted to say goodbye before I go to Paris.
By the way, Ju Won ran away from home.
I thought she might feel lonely if she's in that big house alone.
It was weighing on my mind.
Don't you...
find me difficult?
Well, I do.
But I don't feel uncomfortable.
I want to get along with you, Mother.
You're my role model.
Gosh, I knew you two felt similar.
Sometimes, it gives me chills how similar you...
Can I come to you for advice now and then?
Yes, you can.
All right, Mother.
Also, I don't know too much about why Ju Won ran away, but...
Hey, Mi Jin...
I know this because I'm the type who must do what I want.
But you have to fight and butt heads until the end...
not to have any regrets.
He will figure out your intentions someday.
You should take good care of Mother until Ju Won comes home.
You should eat with her too.
Yes, I should.
Don't gang up on her with Ju Won.
Right. Of course not.
Give me your hands.
What's this?
What?
Mother, Si Won prepared this to give to you.
Yes, I prepared it for you.
It's a brand that came into our department store.
It'll give you an energy boost if you take it.
(Red Ginseng)
Oh, yes. I'll give you one.
Here you go.
Oh, that's nice.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
What are you doing?
Getting ready for my trip. Why?
I mean...
Thank you for today.
I only ever thought of Mother as a strong person.
I never thought she'd be lonely.
Strong people get lonely too.
Father has been staying abroad for years.
How lonely must she be in that big house by herself?
Here.
You should read it if you can't sleep while you're abroad.
("Healing Words")
Hey, what is it now?
You should hug this when you go to sleep.
A stuffed animal?
Well, a cooperative firm gave it to me as a present.
You can have it.
It helps you fall asleep if you hug something soft.
Have a good trip.
(Sleep well every night.)
Hey, Hyung Jin.
Yes, thank you for last time.
You even gave me Lee Sung Min's number.
He suggested we have a meal together sometime.
Do you have time next week...
Yes.
What?
Vice Chairman.
What's this? I told you not to come here.
There's a problem.
("Bareun Peace Party's Assemblyman Lee Kyung Seok's Eldest Son...")
("Debuts As Artist, Controversy About Special Privilege")
Did you know too, Director Seo?
About Mr. Lee Sung Min's background?
I only found out recently too.
We went to the same university but weren't close.
The Vice Chairman had asked a friend for his contact information.
But he didn't get any special treatment. Can this become an issue?
I thought so too,
but this could make our group seem politically inclined.
First, you and I should take care of this.
Ms. Ha, please prepare to deal with the press.
Yes, sir.
And there's something I must tell you.
Goodbye, sir.
Ms. Ha.
The Vice Chairman came because of the news articles, right?
Well, yes.
Gosh, what do we do?
Is this position cursed or something?
After Artist Park Jong Seo, now even Artist Lee Sung Min?
Ms. Ha, take a look at this.
People are having a blast.
They're saying things like "Didn't Artist Lee Sung Min start..."
"the controversy about Artist Park Jong Seo?"
"He only got in because of his connections."
"His artwork wasn't great quality anyway."
The comments are awful.
First, you two should prepare the press release.
Please cancel the artist commentary event scheduled for today.
I'll go down to the art gallery.
What? The art gallery?
You'll go all the way to Yeosu yourself?
Yes, the reporters might be swarming there,
and I think it'll be better for me to deal with things in person.
Ms. Ha. And there's something I must tell you.
Actually, I believe Artist Lee Sung Min is...
estranged from his family.
So, he could take these news articles in a sensitive way.
I can't tell you too much more since it's his personal matter,
but I thought you should know.
(Contacts, Artist Lee Sung Min)
(Stay Arang)
Is he just going to go off grid or what?
Are you okay?
Did you come because you were worried I wasn't okay?
Of course. We've invited you as an artist,
and you came all this way.
But the event was cancelled,
and reporters might be coming in droves.
Of course, I should take care of you.
How reliable.
But things will be okay now.
My father has released an article denying the accusations.
What?
"It is true that Artist Lee Sung Min is the eldest son..."
"of Assemblyman Lee Kyung Seok,"
"but there was no special treatment."
"Artist Lee previously attended law school until suddenly switching..."
"his career path,"
"and due to these conflicts,"
"the father and son have been out of touch for years."
"Assemblyman Lee Kyung Seok found out about the exhibition today,"
"and said he was supportive of his son's decision not to give up..."
"on his dream before it was too late,"
"and he said he intended to attend the exhibition as well."
Isn't that too much information?
Well, I don't feel that great,
the commentary event was cancelled,
and I came all this way.
Do you want to go see the ocean?
Having something I didn't want others to know about...
revealed to the whole world makes me feel weird.
I get it.
Your wounds have been revealed involuntarily.
You must feel upset.
What?
Is that really you, Ms. Ha Yoon Seo?
Why are you being warm to me? You said you had no reason to.
Sorry about everything so far.
But actually, I was grateful to you about something.
About what?
Assemblyman Lee Kyung Seok...
He acts like he's pacifist,
but he's actually very violent.
Pardon?
It's not just to his family.
He even laid hands on those around him.
He found out his aid helped me begin doing art.
What is this?
(Bareun Peace Party)
My father made it impossible for him to be in politics.
After that, I cut ties with my father.
But recently, I got a postcard from that aid.
He told me to do what I wanted and live well.
I wasn't even sure...
if I could apologize to him.
I worked up my courage and looked up his number, but it was wrong.
That was how I got in touch with you, Ms. Ha.
Was that why you sent those texts?
Still, I ruined a person's life.
I was feeling confused about whether I could begin doing art again...
and whether I could just live well by myself.
Then, I heard your voice that day.
(Jae Hee)
(Be sure to eat dinner. You skip when you're busy.)
(Are you well? I am if you are.)
Hey! Who on earth drives like that?
You were the one who made an illegal U-turn first.
What? You're just a young brat.
Thank you for thinking I'm young,
but I'm not that young, actually.
And you can't curse and speak down to someone because they're young.
My life was so hard...
that I kept working my butt off when others were having fun.
Do you know about my hardworking DNA that goes bone deep?
So, let's stop fighting as people...
who both have to work for a living.
In that moment,
I felt like I was in a different world.
The voice on the other side of the phone was strong.
She said her life was hard,
but she sounded full of the will to live.
(Stay Arang Special Exhibition Proposition)
(Ha Yoon Seo, Jae Hee)
That was why I wanted to meet you at least once.
Anyway, I wanted to meet you in person after that phone call.
It was good to meet you.
And I think I considered that interest.
But I was so wrapped up in my emotions...
that I put you in a tough spot.
Sorry.
Well...
Since the articles are out, I just wanted to explain myself.
You seemed really angry this morning.
That is...
Actually, I haven't been feeling very great lately.
I want to part ways.
I know I should.
But it won't go as I hope.
So, perhaps, I took my anger out on you.
I'm feeling drained physically and emotionally.
Should we go and have a nice, warm bowl of gukbap?
How about something other than gukbap?
There's something I do when I feel emotionally drained.
Do you want to do that with me today?
Artist Lee, when you feel emotionally drained,
do you paint outdoors like this?
Well, painting is nice,
but I like the moment...
I spend to look at the scenery before I start painting.
If you sit still and focus on nature,
you hear sounds you didn't hear in daily life.
That really makes you feel relaxed.
That was how I ended up painting landscapes.
This is unexpected.
You're even worse at painting than I thought.
What? Come on. Why are you laughing?
I mean, it's so cute.
Still, I'll praise you.
You did well, considering it was your first time.
Then, I'll praise you too.
I think you've gone through a hard process.
But you made your dream come true in the end. I respect you for that.
And I thought, "I feel proud of you."
Enough for me to want to pat you on the back.
Then, why don't you go ahead and pat me on the back?
Well, that's just a figure of speech.
I can't accept just empty words.
Go on and pat me on the back.
That I've been through a lot, and that I'm doing well.
You've been through a lot.
You're doing well.
You said you wanted me to pat you on the back.
If you really want to get her back,
let her go about this much, and then pull her back.
The first thing you must do...
is to move to a different office.
Things really must be over. The end!
Is he really trying to get over his feelings?
From now on, you will become a bad guy.
The jealousy strategy.
The jealousy that you feel. Yoon Seo should feel...
that instinctive feeling to realize how precious you are.
Going through a hard time...
keeps reminding me of him.
Has something happened to Yoon Seo?