Timing and Subtitles brought to you by General's Lady Team @ Viki
[For One Person by Ye Xuan Qing]
♫  The wind speaks like you  ♫
♫  Talking about the distant rain falling  ♫
♫  I pause within my dream  ♫
♫  Counting the years of memories  ♫
♫  Waiting for some passionate loving words  ♫
♫  Willing to trade a lifetime of prosperity for life's highs and low  ♫
♫  Let a bottle of wine seal the story  ♫
♫  Love is just the spare warmth from this mortal world  ♫
♫  Flowers bloom and fall, leaving an impression  ♫
♫  Naively letting the years pass for one person  ♫
♫  Love is the spring to a lifeless land  ♫
♫  Opening the door to my heart without sound or notice  ♫
♫  Stars change positions, time passes  ♫
♫  I wish to be your loyal servant  ♫
[General's Lady]
[Episode 24]
[Ruonan Textile Shop]
♫  White, tranquil moonlight  ♫
♫  Secretly came through the window  ♫
♫  Softly laid by my ear  ♫
♫  Wandering along with the mind  ♫
♫  Gentle, elegant moonlight  ♫
♫  Love sparks fly from fingertips  ♫
♫  Worries causes brimming red eyes  ♫
♫  Under the stars, tears flow  ♫
♫  The cool breeze blows  ♫
♫  A light floral scent  ♫
♫  The aroma overlaps with sorrow  ♫
♫  The sea of stars light up the sky  ♫
♫  Tranquil moonlight, white moonlight  ♫
♫  While it's desolate, fall in love crazily  ♫
♫  How deep is your admirable love?  ♫
Enough. I'm full.
You didn't eat much. How can you be full?
I'm not a pig. How can I eat that much?
You can leave now.
Wife, how can you abandon your benefactor after achieving your goal?
After eating your fill and wiping your mouth, you don't recognize your own husband anymore?
Well, it wasn't me who asked you to deliver this.
You did it willingly so don't blame me.
Is that so?
All right, all right. Whether it is or not, just leave.
My mother will be back soon.
This isn't right. My mother should have been back long ago.
Yes, she should have been back long ago.
It must have been you who didn't allow my mother to come back!
I-I can eat it myself.
How is it? Does it taste good?
- It doesn't.  - It doesn't?
You... You—
It's pretty tasty.
Chu Xiuming, you—!
So hot.
What are you doing?
You—
I'm too cold.
Chu Xiuming, don't touch me.
I will just look at you like this, Jin'er. I definitely will not touch you.
Chu Xiuming, you are going overboard.
Just let me hug you like this. Be good.
♫  Counting the years of memories  ♫
♫  Waiting for some passionate loving words  ♫
♫Willing to trade a lifetime of prosperity for life's highs and lows♫
♫  Let a bottle of wine seal the story  ♫
♫  Love is just the spare warmth from this mortal world  ♫
♫  Flowers bloom and fall, leaving an impression  ♫
♫  Naively letting the years pass for one person  ♫
Why are you still here at the manor?
I will go wherever you go, Jin'er.
You have already stayed overnight for several days now.
My mother has been sleeping in another wing for several days now.
How could you treat your mother-in-law this way?
Then come sleep with me in the other wing, Jin'er.
No. I want to sleep with my mother.
No. I can't sleep without you.
Why are you such a rascal?
You are a dignified general. Don't you have any official business to attend to?
Why are you watching me all day long?
You are not allowed to follow me. Don't follow me.
Older Sister Jin'er is so fortunate
to have someone who's so considerate and attentive like you, General.
She must be spoiled by you.
If it were me, I wouldn't be like that.
Eavesdropping on others is not a good habit.
I was here waiting for my older sister.
I have always been working hard to try and get close to her,
but I don't know why she seems to be avoiding me.
Then you should ask Jin'er why.
Mother, I'm back!
You are back just in time. Hurry and get going.
- Where am I going?  - Back to the general's manor.
It's about time.
How is it acceptable for a Great General to be living here?
For your sake, he doesn't care about that.
What about you? You should care about his reputation.
But isn't this a bit too urgent?
The carriage is already waiting outside.
Your general is also waiting for you outside.
But I should still notify Royal Father and Mother Consort.
I already did it for you.
Mother.
[Rui Royal Manor]
General.
I'm handing over my daughter to you.
If she's stubborn again, tell me and I will discipline her.
- Mother—  - Keep quiet.
However, General, don't let her run back here in such a sad state again.
Don't worry, Mother. I will surely not make the mistake again.
That's good then.
Mother.
Whenever you want to come back here, I will accompany you back at any time.
Aren't you going to help me up into the carriage?
Older Sister Jin.
Older Sister Jin, why didn't you tell me you were leaving?
General, can I be a guest at Yongning Manor?
My wife decides everything regarding home affairs.
Older Sister, I have never been to the Yongning Manor before.
Can I be your guest on another day?
It's not very convenient. There are not many servants at the manor.
Besides, many of the courtyards are sealed off. Even if you were to come, there is nothing fun.
I merely just want to get close to you.
I know that when you were originally here at the manor,
you had some disputes with my mother.
However, at the end of the day, we are both daughters of Royal Father.
Royal Father also certainly hopes that we would get along with and love each other.
I'm not even close to your mother, where would the disputes come from?
Jin'er, speak calmly. Don't be anxious.
My mother raised me when I was young.
After growing up, it was Mother Consort who raised me.
However, Concubine Xu was constantly weak and sick.
She never went to Mother Consort's court.
I rarely saw her.
Younger Sister Jing, is there some kind of misunderstanding?
Older Sister, don't be angry. I was being rude.
Younger Sister Jing, did I say anything harsh that offended you?
I merely want to get close to you.
Is there a need to be so aggressive?
For you to say that, it seems like you still have lots of animosities with my wife.
Wife, as an older sister, you should concede to your younger sister.
Thank you, General.
In the future, wherever you are, please forgive us but my wife and I will not be there.
Even if we are in my father-in-law's manor, please avoid us or we shall avoid you.
We shall not be in the same room.
I get it now. I will listen to you from now on, Husband.
Younger Sister Jing, in the future, remember to tell us where you are married off to.
Come on. Let's go home.
What a relief.
Wife, as long as you are happy.
You did well this time.
Wife, you taught me well.
- Where's Rou Rou?  - She has already gone back to our manor.
You will be able to see her when we are home.
By the way, I don't want to see Xiao Su for the time being.
Tell him to stop coming to the manor.
I shall obey you.
But don't say that it's my idea!
Okay, Wife.
Lord Liu, Chu Xiuming has already been in the capital for more than a month.
Why haven't we taken any actions?
That's right. We should seize this opportunity to take him down.
He holds military power.
With his presence at the Imperial Court, our plan will never succeed.
Do not panic.
The time isn't right yet.
Wait a little longer.
Your Majesty, regarding the embezzlement of the military funds,
I haven't been able to find any further evidence.
I'm afraid the person behind it is hidden very deeply. Please give me a little more time, Your Majesty.
Just keep investigating, Prime Minister.
You must find out who is behind this.
Lord Yongning has been in the capital for some time now, right?
Send him back to guard the border.
I will arrange for it right away.
"When will the endless cycle of the spring flower and the autumn moon come to an end?"  (The poem "Spring Flower and Autumn Moon" 《春花秋月何时了》 was written by Li Yu (李煜),)
"How much remembrance of the things past does a heart know?"  (the last ruler of the Southern Tang state during imperial China's Five Dynasties and Ten Kingdoms period.)
"Last night, in the attic revisited by the eastern wind,  (This poem was translated by Qiu Xiaolong (裘小龙).)
it was unbearable to look toward home in the fair moonlight."
"The carved rails and the marble steps must remain unchanged,
but not her beauty."
"How much sorrow do I have?"
"It is like the spring flood of a long river flowing east!"
Hu Zi, you read it once.
"When will the endless cycle of the spring flower and the autumn moon come to an end?"
"How much remembrance of the things past does a heart know?"
"Last night, in the attic revisited by the eastern wind,
it was unbearable to look toward home in the fair moonlight."
"The carved rails and the marble steps must remain unchanged,
but not her beauty."
"How much sorrow do I have?"
"It is like the spring flood of a long river flowing east!"
You did really well. Let's read it once more.
"When will the endless cycle of the spring flower and the autumn moon come to an end?"
"How much remembrance of the things past does a heart know?"
Everyone, read it with me!
"When will the endless cycle of the spring flower and the autumn moon come to an end?"
"How much remembrance of the things past does a heart know?"
Louder!
"When will the endless cycle of the spring flower and the autumn moon come to an end?"
"How much remembrance of the things past does a heart know?"
"Last night, in the attic revisited by the eastern wind,
it was unbearable to look toward home in the fair moonlight."
"The carved rails and the marble steps must remain unchanged,
but not her beauty."
"How much sorrow do I have?"
Thank you.
I didn't know you would come today.
- If you knew, you wouldn't come?  - Yes.
Why?
I promised I wouldn't bother you.
You also said you'd keep waiting for me.
I just need to remember that you are willing to bear everything with me.
That's right. That will never change.
Chu Xiuyuan, are you a fool?
I'm not a smart person, in any case.
- I always thought I was a smart person.  - Listen to me! Listen to me!
I always knew I was someone who knew what I wanted.
However, I didn't know... and can't say clearly when
my insistence started to waver.
Chu Xiuyuan.
When you are by my side,
I feel very at ease.
If it is possible,
I want to be the one who speaks up first.
I want you to know
that I care a lot about you, too.
You fool.
"It is like the spring flood of a long river flowing east!"
"When will the endless cycle of the spring flower and the autumn moon come to an end?"
"How much remembrance of the things past does a heart know?"
Madam, your pulse is very steady.
You just need to control your diet a little.
You should eat a little but have more meals.
I've... had a great appetite recently.
I haven't had morning sickness either, so I ate a little more.
Older Sister, why don't you have your pulse taken, too?
I came to visit you. Why would I have my pulse taken?
You have nothing else to do anyway. Come on!
- Then I will have to trouble you, doctor.  - All right.
These past few days, my loss of appetite has been much better.
My appetite has been pretty good.
My Lady, please give me your other hand.
Is there really something wrong?
Don't talk nonsense!
Congratulations, My Lady, you are more than a month pregnant.
- Congratulations, Older Sister!  - Congratulations, Eldest Miss!
Would that mean that your child
will have to call my child "Older Brother" or "Older Sister"?
But I-I—
Doctor, is My Lady's body all right?
She had a miscarriage before.
She is rather weak.
The pulse is a little unstable.
But she is fine.
She just needs to take more medicine and rest for a while.
Thank you, Doctor!
Then I will take my leave first.
Rou Rou! Quickly go tell Mother Consort and Heir Apparent!
- They'll be delighted!  - Yes!
Wait!
Just tell Mother Consort.
All right!
Older Sister, do you want to return to the Marquis's manor?
I won't. I will find a way to tell the Heir Apparent.
This time... I definitely will not lose this child.
Little brat, once you are born,
you must call my child "Older Sister" or "Older Brother!"
Come, come, come! Sit down.
You are pregnant. Did you send someone to notify the Marquis's manor?
Not yet.
Send someone to inform the Marquis's manor of the good news.
Yes.
Don't wander about for the next few days.
Rest in your room, all right?
Yes.
It's so early, can you hear anything?
I think I should be able to.
Or else, when would I be able to hear him?
How would I know? I don't have any experience with this!
This is my first time, too!
Next time! We'll have experience next time!
How shameless!
Let me listen again.
Shu'er, why are you crying?
Young Master, My Lady is worried about the child.
Is something wrong with it?
Young Master, think about the last child who was aborted.
It was already a fully formed male child.
And this time, Miss...
The doctor told her to rest quietly.
Don't talk nonsense! The last time was last time.
How can those incidents be a common occurrence?
Young Master, please think about it more for Her Ladyship's sake.
The matter back then was very strange.
My Lady completely trusts you.
But how was the child aborted?
Just that Yun Niang, how could she do so much?
How could she trick you?
It's because the real person behind it all
is a person you never guarded against!
What is the meaning of all this that you're saying?
Don't say any more.
Young Master, do you still not understand?
If Madam didn't destroy the evidence,
then when My Lady sent someone to investigate immediately after she woke up,
how could there be nothing found?
To be able to do all this,
in the entire manor, who else could it be?
Shu'er, don't worry.
Stay here.
I will go and tell Father.
It's all my fault.
If I had taken over the home affairs at the manor earlier,
I wouldn't have made things so hard on you now, Husband.
It's fine. Don't think so much.
I will go back right now and come back to accompany you later.
Take good care of her!
Miss, he really believed it.
Why wouldn't he?
It's better than admitting he was tricked by a woman,
in addition to bearing the guilt of causing his own child's death.
Isn't that right?
Prepare the water.
Help me wash up.
I want to sleep.
[Yongning Manor]
Jin'er, let me take another look once we get back.
- You still want to look?  - I really think I heard some movement just now!
You can't hear anything, it's too early!
- I really heard something!  - I don't even feel much right now.
How could you hear anything?
You two really came at the right time.
Older Brother, we didn't come here to beg for your approval.
It's just that Ruonan feels that we should let you know.
I got it. You two can leave now.
- All right.  - Don't! Don't!
Husband!
Jin'er, I said "I got it." Is there something wrong with that?
General, can you really not give us your blessing?
I believe I already made things clear.
You also told me you had no romantic feelings for Xiuyuan.
Why did you come here right now?
I want to say that he is very good, but I'm not that bad either.
That's just about what I mean.
My Lady, there's no need to say that much to my older brother.
Xiuyuan, I don't want you to lack your family's blessing.
Husband, they've known each other since they were young.
That means it's been at least seven or eight years!
But Xiuyuan has never forgotten Sister Ruonan.
Are you not touched by this affection?
Jin'er, you know why I'm against them.
Are those reasons important?
Could they possibly be more worthy than this affection?
Then if someone came here with those reasons,
- would you give me up, too?  - Never!
That's right! Then, why must they give up?
Jin'er, Xiuyuan definitely cannot marry a regular commoner!
But, General, didn't you also marry a regular commoner?
- How could that be the same?  - It is different.
How could I be the same as Sister Ruonan?
How could I possibly be compared to her?
In this world, it is difficult for a man to live,
much less a woman!
And this woman also bears the burden of supporting old and young lives!
This is a great love.
It is an unconditional sacrifice!
Tell me. How could I possibly be compared to Sister Ruonan?
Chu Xiuming, have ever you fought this hard for someone before?
My little wife is really growing up,
yet I have become increasingly foolish as I live.
Then... do you agree?
I will listen to you about everything, Jin'er.
Thank you, Older Brother!
You should thank your sister-in-law!
Sister Ruonan, it looks like our shops can finally become one!
We can finally work hard together!
Starting from tomorrow, I shall work hard for our shops!
- You cannot!  - I cannot what?
You cannot go out.
Chu Xiuming, you—!
I'm so bored!
Stop! Where are you going?
I... came to find you!
Find me?
Find me... For what reason?
You... Don't misunderstand!
I didn't come to take you out!
This isn't the Rui Royal Manor.
If I take you out, then the general will kill me!
I didn't say I wanted you to take me out!
As long as you don't want me to take you out, you can order me to do anything!
I will not refuse!
Just leave!
I came to find you for something!
What is it?
Two more came.
Two what?
It is said they are your 7th Aunt and 8th Aunt.  (Her 7th Aunt is from her paternal side, and her 8th Aunt is from her maternal side)
Do I have... two relatives like that?
Do you want to see them?
I'm bored anyway. Let's go see them!
Slow down! Slow down!
Slow down, Miss!
Listen to me.
I haven't seen our Jin'er in so long!
You really have become more beautiful!
You are indeed in a position of authority,
the primary lady who's cherished, and is successful.
You cannot say that.
Our Jin'er's textile business in the capital is very prosperous.
She didn't claim any of our nephew-in-law's glory.
Alone in the business world,
Jin'er is the Zhuge of the industry!  (T/N: Zhuge Liang, an famous and brilliant, ancient military strategist)
Of course, she would have vast riches.
Primary Lady, you are a heroine amongst women.
You are being too courteous, too courteous.
That... 7th Aunt. 8th Aunt.
You must be aware that my husband is usually busy.
I take care of this manor myself.
Besides, my business
is very busy!
So I won't be drinking tea with you two.
7th Aunt! 8th Aunt! The general has already given orders.
My Lady is pregnant, thus people cannot come too close.
What a coincidence! What a coincidence!
I came precisely to help share her burdens!
That's right, I also have official matters to discuss with you!
What is it?
The thing is—
Primary Lady, look!
I know you are busy.
The general's manor is such a large place
- and all of its affairs rely on you, Primary Lady.  - Precisely! Precisely!
On that topic, it is said that "two heads are better than one."
Even if you have exceptional capabilities,
you still need a good helper. Isn't that right?
- That's right.  - Besides, you are pregnant now, too.
If you really are tired out, then the general will blame us!
That's right, that's right.
Now is the best time to get concubines for the general!
On the one hand, she can help you
take care of your business and the manor.
On the other hand, she can give the general more children!
This is the best merit you could possibly do for the general as his primary lady.
The general will also praise you for being kind and demure!
Those two old women are trying to butter sister-in-law up right now.  (T/N: bewitch by means of flattery)
They said they want to give you concubines!
Oh? What did they say?
They said she is a fine lady who is as "delicate as a flower and refined like precious jade."  (T/N: Idiom – exquisite)
I'm asking what did your sister-in-law say.
Did she become furious and drive them out?
She didn't.
Sister-in-law was very calm and peaceful.
Then that means someone is about to be in huge trouble.
Since ancient times, men have always—
Since ancient times, men have—
Since ancient times, men have always had multiple wives or concubines!
Not to mention, your husband is a top-ranked general!
Rather than benefitting those outsider women with ulterior motives,
why not become even closer as a family and marry our own people into this manor?
This is your younger paternal cousin, Xiao Qing!
Primary Lady, why don't you take her in?
How about letting her be the general's second wife?
Greetings, Older Sister.
Primary Lady.
- Primary Lady.  - 8th Aunt! 8th Aunt!
You must "hold a bowl of water evenly."  (T/N: Idiom – be impartial and just in handling matters)
You shouldn't treat your younger sister from your own family unfairly.
Look! This is your younger maternal cousin, Xiao Bai.
Just take her in as well, all right?
She's so obedient!
How about this?
I will give five taels of silver to each person. Take the money and leave.
This...
This...!
Older Sister, I will definitely take good care of you and the general!
You don't need to thank me!
Then... how about we give a little more money to each person?
We'll treat it as part of your dowry from General's Manor!
You two are so beautiful and lovely.
Don't worry about not being married off.
I only want to serve by your side!
- I definitely will not bother you—  - You don't need to serve me.
I have people serving me.
Primary Lady, just take it as pitying Xiao Qing.
Her father died early—
How pitiful!
Then... how about... we send Xiao Qing to learn some craftwork?
If the family isn't dependable, then she must depend on herself!
Rou Rou, there's no need to get money for Xiao Qing.
She's not worried about marrying anyways, why does she need a dowry?
Miss, you are right!
Younger Cousin, do you also want to learn craftwork?
Then I will not be walking you all out.
Please come this way, everyone.
- Older Sister—!  - This way, please!
I'm so angry!
Let's go!
How is it? Are you still bored?
Why don't I go walk them out?
Come back!
Miss!
Where are you going?
Slow down!
You! You're not...?
Yes, my old tricks!
That won't do.
I climbed this wall myself, it has nothing to do with you. Just pretend you saw nothing.
You can't, Miss!
Your body is heavy right now, if—
- Turn around!  - No.
Turn around! Turn around!
Miss.
You—! If you go out,
then the person in trouble is me.
No matter if I participated or not in your climbing over the wall to go out,
as long as you go out, the general is surely going to blame me!
If he says "kill Rou Rou,"
what will I do?
Rou Rou, are you waiting for the general to come back and kill you,
- or should I kill you now?  - Then just kill me now!
All right. Once the general returns,
and if anything happens to the child in my belly,
I will tell him you didn't take good care of me.
How could you do that?!
Be careful! My little life is below your feet!
Cut the crap!
You've gotten much heavier recently.
Are you just spouting nonsense? There's another person in my belly!
Come on!
Great wide world, here I come!
Rou Rou, a little higher!
Still higher?
What are you two doing?
General.
Miss! I didn't to do that on purpose!
General, she threatened me! I don't know anything!
How could you be so careless?! What if something happened?
It's fine! I frequently climbed over walls in the past. I have great martial arts skills!
Things are different now.
You have to be careful with everything, got it?
I just... wanted to go out for a walk.
I'm so bored!
Then once you have given birth,
I will take you out to travel and play,
and walk around the entire world. Does that sound good?
Really?
When have I ever lied to you?
Husband has never lied to me before!
Then I have never lied to you either!
All right. Then I will send my wife back to her room first.
Servants!
From now on, nothing can exist in the manor that could cause Her Ladyship any harm.
Also, this bed should be layered to be softer.
- Yes.  - Yes.
Also, have you prepared the nourishing tonic I asked for?
We have prepared it according to your orders.
Go on.
Yes.
Husband, I'm not that fragile!
Jin'er, you have to treasure your body well.
I can't even finish eating all of the gifts in the manor!
You don't need to prepare any more for me, all right?
Jin'er, you have put aside the textile shop business,
but if you need anything,
you must obediently tell me.
You have to believe in me. I will take good care of you.
Yes, Husband!
Be good.
I will have to trouble you, Mother.
You are too courteous, General. I have to thank you.
From now on, just call me Xiuming.
[Rui Royal Maor]
Mother!
- Jin'er.  - Mother!
You're going to be a mother, why are you still so childish?
Wife, if you act like this, people are going to think
that I have been treating you poorly!
I said I wanted to go pick you up, Mother!
This person! He insisted that I wait here!
You're pregnant right now.
Your body is heavy so you cannot be reckless.
It's fine, Mother!
Mother, I have no elders at home.
Please stay a few more days.
Thank you, General. Then I will shamelessly bother you for a little while longer.
- Take Mother to her room to rest.  - Yes.
Then I'll go first. I'll come and see you later.
- Be good.  - Don't worry, Mother!
Thank you, Husband! You treat me so well!
As long as you are happy.
That's right, Jin'er.
I might have to make a long-distance trip.
Then you must come back safely!
Of course!
Then... can you not go?
That's obviously not possible.
Then, can I go with you?
Then...
Mother! Mother!
Wife, don't be like this.
I'll feel even worse if you're like this.
But I've never been apart from you before!
I definitely will come back safely.
Think about it. The border is very far away.
Your body cannot take the hardship.
But I really miss Xiao Cong, Qing Qiu, and the others.
Also, all the delicious foods by the border!
I don't know what's wrong with me recently.
I always feel so sad!
Perhaps because you are pregnant,
your emotions will fluctuate.
After all, you're going to be a mother.
I should be happy that you are going out.
Because no one will order you around?
But right now I'm so sad!
Husband, don't come back too quickly!
What?
Husband, I want to bite you.
[Bonus Scene]
What's going on with Su Su?
What is he doing?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by General's Lady Team @ Viki
[Tranquil Moonlight by Shang Shi Da]
♫  White, tranquil moonlight  ♫
♫  Secretly came through the window  ♫
♫  Softly laid by my ear  ♫
♫  Wandering along with the mind  ♫
♫  Gentle, elegant moonlight  ♫
♫  Love sparks fly from fingertips  ♫
♫  Worries causes brimming red eyes  ♫
♫  Under the stars, tears flow  ♫
♫  The cool breeze blows  ♫
♫  A light floral scent  ♫
♫  The aroma overlaps with sorrow  ♫
♫  The sea of stars light up the sky  ♫
♫  Tranquil moonlight, white moonlight  ♫
♫  While it's desolate, fall in love crazily  ♫
♫  How deep is your admirable love?  ♫
♫  The black shadow is stretched  ♫
♫  Worries ripple through my heart  ♫
♫  Tranquil moonlight, white moonlight  ♫
♫  While it's desolate, fall in love crazily  ♫
♫  Worries ripple through my heart  ♫
♫  Tranquil moonlight, white moonlight  ♫
♫  Dreaming with hot tears  ♫
♫  Sounds of the zither travels with me to a distant place  ♫
♫  Falling into a hazy fantasy  ♫
♫  Difficulties weigh on my mind, the night is long  ♫