Timing and Subtitles brought to you by General's Lady Team @ Viki
[For One Person by Ye Xuan Qing]
♫  The wind speaks like you  ♫
♫  Talking about the distant rain falling  ♫
♫  I pause within my dream  ♫
♫  Counting the years of memories  ♫
♫  Waiting for some passionate loving words  ♫
♫  Willing to trade a lifetime of prosperity for life's highs and low  ♫
♫  Let a bottle of wine seal the story  ♫
♫  Love is just the spare warmth from this mortal world  ♫
♫  Flowers bloom and fall, leaving an impression  ♫
♫  Naively letting the years pass for one person  ♫
♫  Love is the spring to a lifeless land  ♫
♫  Opening the door to my heart without sound or notice  ♫
♫  Stars change positions, time passes  ♫
♫  I wish to be your loyal servant  ♫
[General's Lady]
[Episode 20]
Younger Sister Jin.
If you are leaving, then take me with you.
I was the one who brought you here. I've let you suffer.
Younger Sister Jin, if you've been mistreated, please let me know.
Since you said that then I will be frank, Brother-in-Law.
Is that Yun Niang your younger cousin?
She is.
Is she your concubine?
Yun Niang is indeed my concubine.
Yun Niang, since you have offended Younger Sister Jin, shouldn't you quickly apologize?
General's Lady! It's all this little woman, who overestimated their capabilities and offended you. (This little woman (小女子) – humble third-person pronoun used when talking about oneself.)
If you must blame someone, then blame it all on this little woman.
It has absolutely nothing to do with the manor of the Marquis of Yongle!
Yun Niang is pregnant.
Since she has already apologized, please allow her to get up, General's Lady.
That's right. Yun Niang, hurry and get up. Don't harm the child.
Here.
Brother-in-Law, there is something I want to ask you.
Go ahead.
Why do I seem to recall that only nobility who are conferred as Dukes or higher (He is only a marquis, a rank lower than a duke.)
could have concubines?
Younger Sister Jin, in this, I am at fault.
My Young Miss is a noble concubine, so she's naturally different from other concubines.
What nonsense are you spouting?
Madam, please do not be angry. That was what the Heir Apparent said himself.
What an arrogant maidservant!
Wouldn't her mistress be even more impressive, then?
Her Ladyship is present, what is this nonsense you are spouting? Slap your own mouth!
Please don't, Aunt.   (T/N: One's mother's elder sister.)
She's been with me ever since I was little. My mother handpicked her for me.
Just spare her this once. I beg of you.
What rubbish is this servant girl saying?
Your status is so lowly, you won't be able to bear the responsibility after shooting your mouth off like that!
I only wish... that I'll be able to remain by Elder Cousin's side.
I am even willing to be a maidservant!
I'm begging you, Your Ladyship.
Younger Sister Jin, I am to blame.
Another day, I will host a special banquet and invite you and Third Younger Brother-in-Law so I can apologize with wine.
Yun Niang is pregnant, why don't you just let it go for today?
Brother-in-Law, forget about apologizing.
It's just that this Yun Niang does not understand the rules.
If the child is educated by her when it's born, wouldn't that be a scandal?!
My Lady, please rest assured.
I will certainly educate my child properly.
That's right, that's right. Don't worry, My Lady.
I will surely teach this child well.
Madam, you are getting old. I'm afraid you may not have the energy for it.
Besides, etiquette isn't something that can be learned in a day or two.
Those of us from the Rui Royal Manor learned the rules from those in the palace since we were little.
Amongst all of my sisters, Elder Sister Shu is the most educated and reasonable.
Elder Sister Shu is the most suitable person to raise the child.
Younger Sister Jin, I do want a child,
but the child's biological mother is around. How could I dare?
Shu'er is the most filial.
I was thinking that it was because she wasn't paying attention that her child was aborted.
It's inevitable that she would feel hollow and long for her child.
I was also thinking of letting Shu'er raise the child once the child was born.
Abortion?
Why didn't you notify the Rui Royal Manor about such a significant matter?
In any case, her child would've been a legitimate grandchild of the Rui Royal household!
Why on earth didn't you tell us?
My Lady! This is the Heir Apparent's first child.
Naturally, the child should be raised by you.
Since Yun Niang has agreed to it, then please rest assured, General's Lady.
We will take good care of Yun Niang during her pregnancy.
Madam, this Yun Niang has been living in the manor for a long time.
It would be impossible to publicly disclose the matter of her becoming a concubine.
However, she is your relative after all.
This child is also Eldest Brother-in-Law's flesh and blood.
After she's given birth, why don't you give her a sum of money,
marry her off back to her hometown, and forget about the whole matter?
Elder Cousin! I am your woman, too!
How could I marry someone else?
Younger Sister Jin, you make a fair point.
But... Yun Niang is pregnant with my flesh and blood after all. I–
Eldest Brother-in-Law, you may disregard your own official career,
but you cannot disrespect the reputation of the Rui Royal Manor!
If my husband Chu Xiuming were to be implicated in your mess, I cannot predict how he will take matters into his own hands.
General's Lady, you're right. We will do as you say.
I know how difficult this must be for Madam and Eldest Brother-in-Law.
But fret not, I will leave this matter for Elder Sister Shu to handle.
I'm tired now so I'll be returning home first.
Let me send you off.
It'll be fine.
[Yongle Manor]
Younger Sister Jin, if it wasn't for you,
I really wasn't sure how I was going to live out the rest of my days.
Elder Sister Shu, stop being so courteous. You always looked out for me in the manor.
This small matter is nothing.
But I know that girl, Yun Niang, won't be willing to give up in regards to today's matter.
If she starts creating trouble again, come find me at any time.
To be honest, I'm not that adamant about wanting her child.
After today's commotion, I'm afraid Yun Niang will not be willing to give the child to me.
This child will become the eldest son of the Heir Apparent of the Marquis of Yongle when he's born.
Your mother-in-law and Eldest Brother-in-Law are hoping fervently for a son
thus they will definitely make sure that Yun Niang has peace of mind during the pregnancy.
If this malicious Yun Niang were to raise the child,
then the child would be bound to become a villain after he has grown up.
Why don't you let the child stay with you? I know you will definitely raise the child well.
You have a point there.
But Younger Sister, what I reminded you of before...
About having a child, you should start thinking about it.
All sorts of feelings are welling up in my mind after witnessing your family affairs.
Elder Sister, I will take your advice to heart.
I'm going to head back first.
[Yongle Manor]
Husband.
Jin'er.
This is a nourishing soup that I made especially for you. Hurry and drink it all.
Husband, you must be tired.
I'm not.
On the contrary, you must be tired from working to open the textile shop, Jin'er.
Lately, I've been busy with other things
so I can't help. I hope you are not angry.
How would I dare to be angry at you?
I should be at home taking care of you.
But because of the textile shop, I've been busy and neglected you, Husband.
Don't' be angry with me, Husband.
There's not even enough time for me to cherish you, how could I possibly be mad at you?
Husband. I have something to ask you.
Is there something in regards to the textile shop that is troubling you?
Jin'er, please ask. I will help you as much as I can.
I will naturally take care of the textile shop, you don't need to worry.
It's just... We have been married for a while now.
We spend every day like this together, is there anything you're tired of?
What kind of question is that? I feel like I don't even see you enough every day.
I wish I could have you by my side for every moment.
Then... Husband, do you want a son?
Having a son is definitely good,
but this isn't something we can have just because we want it.
You've been taking care of the textile shop recently so your body is fatigued.
How about we wait for the textile shop to be on the right track
and for your body to recuperate before having one? Is that okay?
Okay. I will listen to my husband.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
[Jin'er Textile Shop]
Great!
Congratulations!
Great! Great!
Who sent this congratulatory gift? It's so respectful.
I also don't know.
Great!
[Hoping that the money comes to you from the three rivers.]
It's indeed a gift from my husband. Even a gift from him is so bold.
[Jin'er Textile Shop]
Miss Lan, come this way. Have a look.
I know about the fabric that you are talking about. It's over here!
Only our shop has it on this street. We have it!
Miss, even though this fabric is a little expensive, but it's worth it. Right?
You two both have really good taste.
This fabric, from embroidery to its color, is the most fashionable lately.
I personally chose them. Look, look.
Don't leave!
Miss, what is happening?
Great! Great!
[Ruonan Textile Shop]
Ruonan Textile Shop...
Everybody, today is our grand opening!
You can visit our shop for everything you need!
- Great!  - Look as you please!
You really have incredible foresight.
She chose the same day as us to open and it's a textile shop!
I'm going to go take a look.
I'm also going!
[Ruonan Textile Shop]
- The fabric here is really good.  - There's some other colors over there too.  - I really like this.
Please have look, it's nothing.
Look again. Is there anything you like?
Miss, the fabrics here are much like ours.
Why do they have such good business?
This embroidery and quality are indeed really similar to ours.
My Ladies, today's weather is really hot,
how about we sit down and drink some tea to refresh ourselves?
- Okay.  - Please. This way.
Miss, this treatment is not bad. I can also brew tea for our customers.
- Customers will definitely be happy!  - This is a first-class fabric that just came from Jiangnan.
- Customer, feel it. It's really silky.   - It's really not bad!
This embroidery is also very popular right now.
- Many officials from the capital like to make their clothes from this material.  - Is that so?
- The price is also absolutely reasonable.  - Hey!
How much for this fabric?
Miss, that piece of fabric is fifty copper coins.
Fif—
Then, what about that piece?
Miss, you really have great taste.
Miss, have a look. The embroidery on this, was all hand embroidered.
So the price is a little more expensive.
80 copper coins.
This fabric, at other textile shops, would cost 100 copper coins!
Why is it so cheap here? Are these clothes authentic?
All the fabrics in our shop are real.
We aim to make small profits but sell more.
What about you take a piece?
Are you the shopkeeper?
I wouldn't dare. I'm just working here.
The shopkeeper isn't here. Would you like to take one?
We're going to look around some more.
Good. Good. Take a look around.
Let's put it on us to see.
- What is this?  - You're welcome to come to drink tea, too!
This really suits him.
[Ruonan Textile Shop]
The silks and satins of this house are basically all from the same place we get ours.
Including the production and transportation costs,
their price is still 20% lower than ours.
From where are they making a profit?
How about we also lower our prices?
We've already set prices at their lowest since it is the grand opening.
If we lower the price even more, then we would have no profit.
Then that means we cannot compete with this textile shop.
Forget it.
Lord Jin.
Are you calling me?
It is you indeed. I recognized this back silhouette.
What is it? You really don't recognize me?
Have we met each other before?
You're Lord Jin from South street and I'm Brother Nan from North street.
Back then we were the bosses of the opposite ends of a street.
We've fought many times to get more territory.
- Wu Ruonan!  - Wu Ruonan!
You... How come you are a girl?
You're Rou Rou?
Not seeing you for a few years, you're now a big girl.
Where did you go?
We agreed to go against the people on Changsheng Street together but then you suddenly disappeared.
Rou Rou and I looked for you for a very long time!
We even thought that you were in danger.
Back then, I was really poor and having a hard time in the street.
I encountered the Armed Escort Agency recruiting escorts, so I just happened to go with them to do the escorting.
I've really traveled all over the lands.
But you, on the other hand, seem to be
very well-dressed.
Miss is now the wife of Lord General Yongning.
Wife of a general?
That's great. That's really impressive.
Did you also come to buy fabric? Did you see anything you like?
It's a long story.
I opened this Jin'er Textile Shop across the street today.
But isn't it a coincidence? This store also newly opened today.
It stole all of my business. So I came to have a look.
Why are we talking while standing?
- Let's go sit somewhere.  - Yes, yes!
It's been such a long time since we met! Rou Rou, go get Su Su, too!
- Okay!  - Su Su is also here?
- Yes!  - Let's go, let's go.
- Let's go, let's go.  - Hurry.
I, Ruonan, thought no girl was any match for me until I met you.
She's a girl even more masculine than men!
Do you remember? Back then you came alone to South street to steal my territory.
She arrogantly said she could take on the three of us.
In the end, she got beaten up by us.
I remember! But back then Sister Ruonan was bald.
- I even thought she was a guy!  - What?!
That's not what I remember. Clearly, I beat the three of you.
Especially Rou Rou. I held her to the floor to beat her.
- How is that possible?!  - No, no.
- It wasn't like that back then.  - You remember it wrong!
Back then, it was Rou Rou who hit you more than a few times.
Also, how could I possibly let our Rou Rou get beaten?
Exactly!
It seems it was a lifetime ago.
- Thinking about it... Hasn't it been four to five years since we have seen Ruonan?  - Yes.
Back then, we wouldn't have known each other if we didn't fight. It really was a coincidence.
Being able to meet up again today is really fate.
A toast to this fate!
Cheers!
Ruonan, I, Lord Jin, am now the general's wife.
I'm no longer the little lackey who was always bullied in the street.
If there's anything, just tell me. If I can help you, then I'll definitely help you.
Lord Jin, we met again after such a long separation. It's already great that we're all still alive!
From now on, there won't be any difficulties. Only good things!
From now on, there won't be any difficulties, only good things?
Let's drink again to those words!
- Come on!  - Come on.
Cheers!
I'm in such a good mood today!
Ruonan, come to my textile shop and choose some nice fabrics.
I'll have my seamstress make you a few nice clothes!
There's no need for that. Traveling around, what I'm wearing is enough.
It's not. I opened this shop not long ago.
I haven't even sold a piece of fabric.
Just take it as a blessing to me.
All right. That's fine.
But I must pay for the fabric. I can't let you suffer a loss.
All right. As you wish!
- Let's go!  - Let's go!
- Then you two go.  - Okay.
Come on.
I never thought that the one fighting with us back then was a girl!
I really miss that time.
Come on, Ruonan. Chose whatever you like!
I'll gift you whichever one you like.
Earlier you said you went to the shop across the street. How was it?
They sell the same fabrics as mine,
yet their prices are 20% lower than mine!
They stole all the business.
Why don't you lower your prices, too?
This fabric is of high quality.
If I lower my prices, then I can't earn any money.
So I suspect that there must be something fishy about this shop.
They must have used some underhanded tricks!
My Lady.
Lord Xiuyuan, what is it?
I'm on duty as a City Supervisor right now. I heard that the Imperial Palace is in the process of procuring a batch of fabric
but the price must go through a bid. I came by to inform you, Your Ladyship.
The Imperial Palace is procuring a batch of fabric?
What are the requirements for the bidding?
These three requirements of importance: price point, quality, and quantity.
If these three requirements are met, then the bid will be successful.
I'm very interested in this.
I won't lose to any other store when it comes to quality.
However... the remaining stock...
I really do have to replenish the stock from Jiangnan.
It's just the price!
The store opposite mine is selling at too low a price! I surely won't be able to beat them.
Your Ladyship, I have to notify every textile shop regarding the bid.
I have to go notify the shopkeeper of the shop across the street later.
Why don't I go with you? I shall go meet that shopkeeper.
Ruonan, wait for me here. I'll come back soon.
You guys don't need to go.
I already know.
What do you mean, "You already know?"
I'm the shopkeeper of the Ruonan Textile Shop across from here.
Ruonan.
Ruonan!
Lord Jin, I'll come back another day.
[Ruonan Textile Shop]
Wait a moment!
Lord, is there anything else?
- I have good tea inside. Why don't you go inside to have a seat?  - Okay.
Please.
[Ruonan Textile Shop]
That Wu Ruonan is clearly the shopkeeper of the "Ruonan Textile Shop" opposite mine,
but she didn't tell me?
She even tricked me into telling her information!
What is the meaning of this?
Does she think of me as a fool?
I really like this color.
Yes, their shop is so cheap.
- It's quite nice.  - Drink some tea.
Thank you.
My Lord, what is it that you want to tell me about the bid?
Miss, what is your full name?
Wu Ruonan. Just call me Ruonan.
Why do you have such an expression?
- I have a few questions to ask.  - Go ahead.
During the Wuxu period, you were about ten years old. Did you ever go to the forest by the border?
Ten years old?
Tell me.
That's right. That year, I went to make a delivery with my master.
It really is you! On a rugged mountain road in the forest, you met a little boy.
He almost fell down the cliff!
I think...
I think that did happen.
At that time, you helped him.
You used a whip with this pendant on it!
You tied it around that boy and saved his life.
How could you be so careless?
If I didn't save you in time, you would have fallen down the cliff!
Thank you. What is your name?
- We are children of Jianghu. It was nothing, why dwell on it?  - Young Master!  (T/N: Jianghu means a society with loose structure and rules)
Young Master Xiuyuan!
Your family has probably come searching for you. Hurry and go back with your family.
- From now on, when you are alone, be more careful. Don't run around everywhere.  - Young Master!
Where are you going?
Children of Jianghu will, of course, travel in Jianghu.
I am the youngest armed escort in my agency. I have boundless prospects ahead of me!
Then will we meet again?
Let's follow fate!
Ever since that moment that you saved me, in all these years,
I've been trying to find you in order to say thank you.
It was nothing. Why dwell on it?
I've saved countless little boys before.
From the moment I saw you as a child,
my heart was captured.
I...
I, Brother Nan, am a child of Jianghu.
I have no intention to love someone.
Please go back, My Lord.
Then I'll come to see you another day.
Such coincidences actually exist in this world!
A few days ago, I was preparing for the grand opening. Right?
I saw the shop across the street was doing the same thing!
Guess what they are selling.
Could it be that... they're selling fabric?
Exactly!
Also, their fabrics and mine
are about the same in quality, but theirs are 20% cheaper than mine!
Even more of a coincidence is
that this shop owner is the friend I used to play with on the street!
If she's selling it for cheap, then change your price.
I was just trying to run a small business.
For the grand opening, I intended to make small profits but sell a lot. My prices are already at their lowest.
If I lower them any further, I won't be able to get back my costs.
Looking at how worried you are, should I think of some ideas for you?
There is one thing that you can really help me with, Husband.
Go ahead.
Xiuyuan came today, too.
He mentioned that the royal palace is going to use a bidding process
to procure a batch of fabric.
But I can't beat her in terms of price.
Neither can I obtain a huge amount of funding in a short period of time
to acquire such a large batch of fabric to restock.
If you're worried about money,
I'll figure it out for you.
Money isn't the most important problem!
Husband, can you help me come up with an idea to get me this business deal?
I'm afraid I can't do that.
First, I cannot interfere with court procurements.
I can't step forward to help.
It's best that I don't come into contact with court matters in case I do anything to dissatisfy someone.
Secondly, Xiuyuan is a city supervisor,
but plays favoritism.
That is not how I do things.
Hearing those words makes me a bit upset,
but you are right.
I don't know how to talk well. Don't be angry, Jin'er.
Why would I be angry?
I should use my own effort to win the bid for this deal.
I should use my sincerity to get this business.
If you have any troubles in the future,
you must remember to vent to me about it.
Isn't that a certainty?!
If I don't come vent to you, who else would I vent to?
You're done talking now?
Let me take a good look at you.
Let me comfort myself by looking at the cause of my longing today.
If we lower our price by 20%,
only then will we be exactly the same as Ruonan from across the street.
But if I do that, our profits will become next to nothing.
If I want to get more stock,
then I have to use money from the manor to fill the deficit.
On top of the rent and other expenses...
Then... if this continues, is our textile shop going to shut down in one month?
Unless we get the business order from the royal palace!
Looks like I have to go beg our Xiuyuan.
Then, Miss, I will go out and get some customers.
Miss, isn't that Lord Xiuyuan?
- This... It is.  - It's him!
Recently, Jiangnan silks are selling well. There is very little left in inventory.
Have Brother Chen take people to escort another delivery of stock here.
Got it. I will go do that right now.
Wait.
What is Lord Xiuyuan looking at?
Does that mean Sister Nan also wants to compete in the bid for the business with the royal palace?
This escorted delivery will be a long journey. It would take at least two months to go there and come back.
If we get the business deal with the royal palace, I'm afraid I won't be able to deliver it all at once.
But we haven't gotten the deal yet, right?
How could we possibly wait for the bid to be over before restocking?
That would cause a delay and there may be some obstacles in between.
How about this? Have Brother Chen transport all the goods back in a single trip this time.
Then, what about the money?
We have already split all the money we have earned.
I— This—
I have some money saved. If I put all of it into this, it should be enough.
Go take care of it.
Okay, I'll get going then.
My Lord, are you here to buy fabric?
This is a gift for you, Miss Ruonan.
At my textile shop, there are many people who come and go. Since you are a city supervisor,
others will misunderstand that I am trying to gain favor with you.
You mean...
Regarding the bad, I have a question.
How about we meet at a tea house tomorrow and discuss this privately?
Let's do as you said. I'll get going now.
My Lord!
My Lord, please take this gift back with you.
You hold onto it.
I really cannot accept it.
This— Sister Ruonan is actually giving a gift to Lord Xiuyuan!
He also accepted it!
He's "turning his elbows outwards!" (T/N: help an outsider instead of the people close to him)
This Xiuyuan clearly knows that I am locked in a deadly business battle with the shop across the street,
yet he dares to see them privately!
I will surely teach him a lesson, if he dares to favor them!
Rou Rou, go invite Xiuyuan over here!
I will go do that right now.
Xiuyuan.
I invited you over here to ask you about the bid.
Go ahead, Sister-in-Law.
Since you have informed all the city's fabric stores of the procurement by the royal palace,
then you should know which stores will be the most likely to secure the bid.
Can you tell me?
These past few days, I have indeed visited all the fabric shops. There actually are a few that are suitable.
But based on the quality and price, your store's chances are quite high.
And which other stores?
The store opposite you, Ruonan Textile Shop.
What prices are they offering?!
I'm afraid I can't tell you those details.
But I can share a little.
Her prices are the lowest. Sister-in-Law, just be prepared.
Xiuyuan, although I am your sister-in-law,
I don't want to make things difficult for you by asking you to favor me.
Ruonan is my friend but she is also my competitor.
I hope you won't lie and favor anyone. That is best.
Sister-in-Law, rest assured. That is a certainty. I've always been open and honest and won't be favoring anyone.
That is good, that is good. You can go now.
You don't have any other questions?
That's all.
I have a question then.
Go on.
Stop looking. There's been nobody for several days now. Go ahead.
What is a good gift to give to a woman?
Fabric!
They can make some new clothes. All women love that.
I, your sister-in-law, sell fabrics!
But, Xiuyuan, who are you giving a gift to?
To a girl I've known for a long time.
A girl you've known for a long time?
Does Chu Xiuming know about this? How come I don't know?!
Which family is the girl from? Tell me.
You two don't know each other. You two don't know each other.
Drink some water, don't choke.
You're even blushing, Xiuyuan!
Bring her here to my store on another day to select some fabrics.
I'll make her a set of nice clothes.
At the same time, let me see what kind of girl she is.
That's not very convenient, right?
Besides clothes, what else can you gift?
Cosmetic and perfume. Women also like cosmetics and perfume.
You can also gift hairpins and pendants.
Then I understand now.
But, Xiuyuan, don't be troubled.
I know it would not be appropriate if you were to go buy cosmetics and perfume.
But I can go buy them for you!
After I've bought it, you can then gift it to that girl. What do you think?
That would be best. I will give you the money later, Sister-in-Law.
Of course.
[Yongning Manor]
Husband, you're back?
Wife, you've opened a textile shop. How come you are looking at cosmetics and perfume?
Could it be that, because business is not good, you are preparing to switch industries?
I picked out all of these for your younger brother, Xiuyuan.
He said he wants to give a gift to a woman he has known for a long time.
I, as his sister-in-law, should definitely put in some more effort.
A woman he has known for a long time?
How come I never knew he had a woman he has known for a long time?
Of course, you wouldn't know!
Currently, Xiuyuan is a city supervisor! He is busy all day.
Getting to know a few officials' daughters is quite normal.
When would he have the time to tell you about everything?
Besides, Xiuyuan has also reached the age where he should start getting to know someone who could be his future wife.
Then he should tell us about it so we can scope them out on his behalf.
They all say that older brothers are like fathers. They really are not wrong!
Oh right! Jin'er, if you find out who the woman is that Xiuyuan is talking about,
you must tell me.
I got it, Lord Older Brother!
Also, you are busy all day. You need to remember to rest properly.
I know my husband dotes on me.
But I must do what I already promised others I would do.
Not to mention, it's Xiuyuan's matter!
Okay, my wife. It is already late.
I'm also tired. Let's rest early.
Tomorrow's matters can be left for tomorrow to do.
This is an order. Do you hear me?
Since the Lord General has made an order, then following his orders is the sincerest form of respect.
Let's go.
Husband, I have a question for you.
What is it?
Come, let's sit down.
Regarding the procurement by the royal palace, the prices that Ruonan and I offer are at an advantage.
But at the moment, I do have a troublesome matter.
If I do get the business deal, I need to deliver the goods as soon as possible.
But the source for these fabrics is very far from the capital.
This land and water transportation would also require quite a lot of time.
Are you thinking of purchasing the order in advance?
Yes, I am indeed considering that.
But if we fail to get the bid, I would have acquired an abundance of fabric.
I'm afraid it will be difficult to sell it all in a short amount of time.
Jin'er, your concern is reasonable.
Then, other than customers who come to your shop, are there any other customer streams?
Last time, when I delivered clothes to Xiuyuan, it reminded me of something.
The Rui Royal Manor uses a lot of fabric every year.
In the capital, there are quite a few high-ranking officials!
I was thinking, can my textile shop specifically supply them with fabric?
Jin'er, we've spoken about this. Let's not draw too much attention to ourselves.
If you do that,
then everyone in the capital will know that my wife is selling fabric throughout the place.
I'm not asking for your help. I just want your opinion.
If you think that by doing so you will lose face, then I won't do it.
Jin'er, don't get angry. This is not what I meant.
If you really want to do that, then I won't stop you.
I am your strongest support backing you up, Jin'er.
I know you dote on me and love me, and are my biggest supporter.
It's just that, I also want to be able to do something.
That's why, in a moment of impatience, I brought up those kinds of ideas.
I understand.
I also believe my Jin'er can provide for half of our household.
Then you just need to stay by my side and assist me.
Okay! I accept your command!
But... it's already late. Shouldn't we also rest early?
[Bonus scene]
It turns out that it's him.
We really are fated.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by General's Lady Team @ Viki
[Tranquil Moonlight by Shang Shi Da]
♫  White, tranquil moonlight  ♫
♫  Secretly came through the window  ♫
♫  Softly laid by my ear  ♫
♫  Wandering along with the mind  ♫
♫  Gentle, elegant moonlight  ♫
♫  Love sparks fly from the fingertips  ♫
♫  Worries cause brimming red eyes  ♫
♫  The cool breeze blows  ♫
♫  A light floral scent  ♫
♫  The aroma overlaps with sorrow  ♫
♫  The sea of stars lights up the sky  ♫
♫  Tranquil moonlight, white moonlight  ♫
♫  While it's desolate, fall in love crazily  ♫
♫  How deep is your admirable love?  ♫
♫  The black shadow is stretched  ♫
♫  Worries ripple through my heart  ♫
♫  Tranquil moonlight, white moonlight  ♫
♫  While it's desolate, fall in love crazily  ♫
♫  Worries ripple through my heart  ♫
♫  Tranquil moonlight, white moonlight  ♫
♫  Dreaming with hot tears  ♫
♫  Sounds of the zither travels with me to a distant place  ♫
♫  Falling into a hazy fantasy  ♫
♫  Difficulties weigh on my mind, the night is long  ♫