How did you know his name was Fang?
Is this the business you told me about?
Have you ever slept with him?
Yes.
But...
Pan...
Listen to me.
Listen to me, please.
It's only one time.
And it was a long time ago.
Please listen to me.
It's not what you thought.
Pan.
Pan, please listen to me.
Listen to me.
Let me go.
Ouch.
Pan.
(War Of Y)
(Episode 5)
((What happened In from of TTV today.)
(Was it this bad?)
(He needs to see a doctor.)
(This is better than a drama.)
(- It’s getting worse every day.
- Now I know why they didn’t sign him.)
(- I was right not to like him.
- He ruined my favourite TV drama.)
(P is doing an IG live.)
Hello.
Miss you all very much.
(My baby, P)
Today I will live for fifteen minutes.
(Will you be here for how long?)
(I miss you.)
Today I will live for fifteen minutes.
(Oh my god. You’re here.)
(Where are you, P?)
I'm very busy today.
(A lot of people are watching this.)
(I want to meet you.)
I miss you.
(My cutie pie.)
(Did you see the video clip?)
What video clip are you talking about?
I'm very busy these days.
I didn't get to see anything.
(The clip where
they fight in from of TTV.)
Aah.
To be honest,
I sympathize with him.
This industry is not easy.
If you're not a person
with a really good heart,
it's very difficult.
(That was harsh.)
Hey, but I didn't say that he's not.
When I ever I get to meet him,
he's alright.
He's sweet.
Do bad, get goods.
We've seen it in every industry.
(Going viral)
(Know every movement)
(With two hot MC’s here)
(Detective Entertainment)
[A BL series actor got exposed, tips all over social media]
Oh my gosh, you all.
- The social media is heating up!
- That's right.
Because of a hashtag
- that is currently trending.
- My gosh.
It's about a famous BL actor.
Oh my god.
Things are heating up.
Which it is... What?
Oh, there's an update.
Okay, tell us.
Damn.
Let me tell you, this is a real time update.
We going strong.
Oh, my. What is it?
OMG.
Someone left a message saying
"it's about."
- Sweet shipped couple".
- My, my.
Sweet...
"But in real life..."
You're so worried about him.
Like he was good to you.
That's the both of you.
No one has ever made me feel at ease.
Only create problems.
I only create problems?
Do you want more headaches?
Have we promised
that we won't talk about it outside?
Wherever we talk, it's the same.
I think you should have known already
that between me and him,
who should you care more about?
(Elizabeth Hotel)
Pan.
You know?
How are you?
You're long gone.
When you called,
I was shocked.
You naughty.
So you didn't tell anyone, right?
That you came out to meet me.
So I was right
to call you.
P'Song.
What are you doing here?
I'm hungry.
Hmm?
That smells great!
Would you like to try one?
P'Koon.
What's this clothes?
For you to take a profile tomorrow.
Pharaoh, try them out.
See if it suits you or not.
If it does not fit, I'll arrange a new one.
Yes, P'Koon.
It's ten o'clock.
You don't need to get the car?
Huh?
- Today?
- Yes.
Oh, didn't you postpone it to today?
- I did?
- Um.
Hello.
Can I ask you something?
Do we have an appointment to pick up the car today?
- Yes, it's today.
- It's today?
And I arranged the date too?
Yes, we have an appointment at half past ten.
Yes, yes, I'm sorry, sister.
If so, I'll be there in half an hour.
Thank you.
Be good. I'll go get the car.
P'Koon...
let me go with you.
I want to be the first one to drive it.
Let Song watch over the house.
Ok.
Don't want to be late.
OK.
(From Mr. Suthat)
Well, I really want to thank you.
You help me a lot.
No problem.
Things that P'Koon did.
I don't agree with.
You can tell me anything.
I'll do what I can.
You help me because
you want anything in return?
(Pharaoh: Hello,
I’m from P’Koon’s agency.)
(Pharaoh: We’ve talked before
about your casting calls.)
(Pharaoh: meet me this Saturday.
Here’s the location.)
(Rice: All right. Thank you.)
(Next Break)
These paper
contains a list of executives,
famous politicians and businessmen
that P'Koon took me to meet.
Telling me that it's a try out.
An audition.
[Transaction Evidence]
How many times have you done this to me?
(Mr. Chalerm, 4 hours for 50,000 baht)
(Mr. Pramot, 3 hours for 35,000 baht)
Mr. Suthat.
He really likes you.
(Mr. Kittkorn, 1 hour for 30,000 baht)
(Mr. Songpol, 3 hours for 40,000 baht)
but he said.
your look is.
(Mr. Suthat, 4 hours for 80,000 baht)
- not right for the channel.
- Not right?
You're the one who told me
to sell myself like this.
(Contract termination letter)
Have you been able to remember the names?
When we got there,
don't call anyone by the wrong name.
It's a big deal.
I know.
Please see my back.
Is it okay?
(Today at 9 sharp.
We’ll hear the truth.)
The news these days is weird.
Have to wait for the right time.
It's already nine o'clock.
Do you want to play a series?
Yes.
If so, take it off.
Take it off?
Hey.
Did you say that if I could get you in,
you won't blackmail me?
I didn't do it.
If you didn't do it, then who?
Hello, I'm Pan.
The people in the VDO that
many people are talking about right now.
You may wonder.
[Pan Thanamin clears up hot mess]
that in the clip and on TV, I look very different.
I admit that that was not me.
And today I'm going to stop faking.
Well, it has to be like this.
That I acted all cute
and sweet,
because I think everyone will like it.
But the real me,
it was as you can see in the clip.
I'm an angry person.
But I never had any malicious thoughts
toward anyone.
The only one who thinks badly toward others
is P'Koon.
These papers
have a list of executives, famous politicians
and businessmen that.
P'Koon took me to.
Telling me that it was a tour to channel.
Auditions.
But the fact it’s like this.
She took me to entertain people at dinner.
Without my consent.
And I never received a single baht.
From the evidence I've gathered so far,
the damage was more than 3 million baht.
Madam, something big happened.
The reason I am saying this,
I have no intention of hurting any family
because in my head it's only about work.
Even though I've devoted myself to work,
she still say I'm not right for big channels
and turned to support another actor instead.
Because that actor consistently find
college students for my former manager.
To her bed.
From all I've said,
you can choose to believe it or not.
I believe that people nowadays are smart
and if someone.
Or you know someone who got hurt from this,
I want to you show yourself
or if you are afraid, contact me.
I'll take you to police.
Thank you.
Very good, Pan.
You spoke very clearly.
Thank you very much, Pan.
You did the right thing.
I have to thank P' Sai and P'Tan.
Pan, listen to me.
Pan.
Pan. Please, listen to me.
Let me go.
Pan.
We must thank you
that made it possible to collect
evidence on the auditioning.
I promise you, besides my kids,
if a victim contacts us,
I will help you sue Koon and Pharaoh.
So.
If there are more victims,
tell me and P'Sai.
We will take care of this from now on.
And legally too.
And you...
You don't have to think too much.
Start a new life well
and this time
you can stay at my condo.
This is how I can repay you
that to find the evidence
to pinpoint the bad people.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Come.
So you can rest.
Yes.
[The manager so fucked up,
the actor didn't do anything wrong]
(Rumour! A certain actor
was fired from his drama!)
(I’m glad Pan left the drama. No one
would watch it now. #BanMafiaBaby2)
(Given the rumour, the drama isn’t
going to be a hit #BanMafiaBaby2)
(I’m not watching it. #BanMafiaBaby2)
(Next Break)
Can I ask you the truth?
You guys don't feel sorry for Pan?
What did he do to you?
I feel sorry for anyone.
If we invest in something,
we must get our capital back.
[Three months later]
Hello, hello. Welcome all Mafiababy fans.
(Oh my god.)
(This is so exciting!)
to the online fan meeting, the greatest in Thailand.
(Finally.)
(My god.)
to the online fan meeting, the greatest in Thailand.
(It’s here!)
(It started.)
to the online fan meeting, the greatest in Thailand.
(The stage needs more light.)
(I want to see Gus.)
to the online fan meeting, the greatest in Thailand.
(#GusAndBew)
(Who will be here today?)
to the online fan meeting, the greatest in Thailand.
(Please ask Bew a lot of questions.)
(Bewwwww!)
to the online fan meeting, the greatest in Thailand.
(The show has garnered 500 million views!)
(We can watch this fan meeting for free?)
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
(King shit.)
(Can’t wait to trend the hashtag.)
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
(Omg, look at their outfits!)
(Gus is so cute. Omg.)
And, of course, we will meet with all 3 actors.
(The white suits!)
(Is this a fan meeting or a wedding?)
And, of course, we will meet with all 3 actors.
(I’m fainting.)
(I want an offline fan meeting.)
And, of course, we will meet with all 3 actors.
(I want to be there.)
(Where is the fan meeting? Can anyone tell me?)
And, of course, we will meet with all 3 actors.
(Nott is too hot.)
(I want to be there too.)
That is Gus, Nott, Bew.
Clap our hands please.
(Will I get to meet them if I wait outside the venue?)
That is Gus, Nott, Bew.
Clap our hands please.
(How can I give them gifts?)
That is Gus, Nott, Bew.
Clap our hands please.
(The show was brilliant!)
That is Gus, Nott, Bew.
Clap our hands please.
(Turn on the light!)
That is Gus, Nott, Bew.
Clap our hands please.
(Congrats.)
That is Gus, Nott, Bew.
Clap our hands please.
(Season 3, please)
That is Gus, Nott, Bew.
Clap our hands please.
(I don’t mind 20 seasons.)
Thank you. Thank you.
(Why are there only three of them?)
(Is this a fan meeting or a haunted house?
The stage needs more light.)Thank you. Thank you.
(I watched it when it aired and watched
it again after that. It’s so addictive!)
(Gus and Bew rocked. I couldn’t believe
it was their first drama.)
Hello hello welcome.
(The show was alright, but
I’m tired of forced product placements.)
Hello hello welcome.
(The first season is better.)
(Pan won’t be there?)
Hello hello welcome.
(Good actors. Terrible script.)
(The most impressive BL drama this year.)
Hello hello welcome.
(This is sad. I don’t want it to end.)
Nong Nott, Nong Bew, Nong Gus. Yay!
(My Gus and Bew!)
(Gus and Bew were so good in this.)
Nong Nott, Nong Bew, Nong Gus. Yay!
(will real-time viewers hit 100,000?)
(Will there be only three of them?)
Nong Nott, Nong Bew, Nong Gus. Yay!
(500 million views were possible
because of the actors and the actors only.)
Nong Nott, Nong Bew, Nong Gus. Yay!
(Bew did a very good job.
He practically carried the whole show.)
Nong Nott, Nong Bew, Nong Gus. Yay!
(They gave nothing
to the extras but plain water.)
Nong Nott, Nong Bew, Nong Gus. Yay!
(My baby Bew.)
Now, let's interview
the new era's shipped couple.
(I love the crown he’s wearing.)
Now, let's interview
the new era's shipped couple.
(Ask them about the sex scenes.)
Now, let's interview
the new era's shipped couple.
(They’re all handsome.)
Now, let's interview
the new era's shipped couple.
(Season 3, please.)
Now, let's interview
the new era's shipped couple.
(Nott, are you lonely there?)
Now, let's interview
the new era's shipped couple.
(I want to pinch your cheeks, Bew.)
Now, let's interview
the new era's shipped couple.
(Gus is so hot I want to wire him money.)
Let's start with Bew.
(The title belongs to Nott and Pan!)
(Hi there.)
Let's start with Bew.
(Will there be a season 3?)
Today we have more than seventy thousand fans
around the world with us.
(Will you restock the calendar?)
Today we have more than seventy thousand fans
around the world with us.
(Can they sing the ending song together?)
Today we have more than seventy thousand fans
around the world with us.
(Gus and Bew had more
screen time than Nott and Pan.)
Today we have more than seventy thousand fans
around the world with us.
(Why isn’t Pan there?)
Today we have more than seventy thousand fans
around the world with us.
(Whenever Bew walks,
I think I hear a peep peep sound.)
Today we have more than seventy thousand fans
around the world with us.
(But the show only got popular because of Pan.)
What do you want to tell them?
(I miss Pan.)
(The crown is very cute.
The stylist did a very good job.)
What do you want to tell them?
(Everything about the show is so fluffy.)
First of all, I'm so happy that everyone likes me.
(Wait a minute.)
(It was practically Gus and Bew’s show.)
First of all, I'm so happy that everyone likes me.
(I’ve been their fan since their
internet idol days. They’ve come a long way.)
First of all, I'm so happy that everyone likes me.
(Why aren’t Gus and Bew sitting together?)
(Congrats, kids.)
First of all, I'm so happy that everyone likes me.
(They already told us Pan wouldn’t be there.)
(They weren’t even leads and yet they hogged the screen time.)
First of all, I'm so happy that everyone likes me.
(Don’t fight, you guys.)
(Gus and Bew, sit together please.)
I would love to thank all of you.
(The event is free to attend.
That’s why you brats are here.
I would love to thank all of you.
(Is the event taking place in a cave?)
(A lot of people are watching this.)
I would love to thank all of you.
(Bew, you’re so cute.)
(I thought you guys
weren’t gonna support the show.)
for supporting us well for all this time.
(Bew, you aced the role!)
(I almost cried when the scene where
Bew told Gus to go away came up.)
(Why isn’t Gus sitting next to Bew?)
Today is like I'm in a dream.
(This season was amazing!)
(Thank you for making a good show!)
Today is like I'm in a dream.
(Do a spin-off where Gus and Bew are leads!)
(Nott’s the lead.
Of course, he’d sit in the centre.)
(The fans are too demanding!)
Not like a dream.
(Thai people are quick to forget and forgive.)
(It’s not a fan meeting for the show.
It’s Gus and Bew’s fan meeting at this point.)
Not like a dream.
(This is disrespectful to the lead couple!)
(I’m only watching this for Nott, otherwise…)
Yes, but we are still just a new couple in the industry.
(Anyone wants lava cookies? Please DM.)
(The first season was great
but the second was even better.)
Yes, but we are still just a new couple in the industry.
(There were too many sex sciences.
I couldn’t watch the show with my mom.)
Yes, but we are still just a new couple in the industry.
(I thought Gus and Bew played supporting roles in this.)
(Bew is so cute it hurts.)
Yes, but we are still just a new couple in the industry.
(Supporting actors don’t sit in the centre.)
Still have to learn a lot.
(He’s too cute. Omg.)
(My baby sure has a lot to say.)
Still have to learn a lot.
(I love you, my baby.)
Please keep us in mind.
(Thank you for existing, Bew.)
(Who told you they were supporting actors?
You didn’t watch the show, right?)
Please keep us in mind.
(What can I do to make him mine?)
(He’s so cute.)
Aww, so cute.
(That’s practically what Pan said
after the first season ended.)
Aww, so cute.
(People actually watch this shit?)
(I had to drop the show
because it featured sex scenes.)
Aww, so cute.
(This is what you call ‘soft power’ people.)
(500 million views for a BL drama and yet
the marriage equality bill was turned down.)
And now the OG.
The first season was very successful.
(I bet he smells of powdered milk!)
And now the OG.
The first season was very successful.
(You’re my favourite, my baby.)
And now the OG.
The first season was very successful.
(He talks too much.)
And now the OG.
The first season was very successful.
(The show was all right.
The acting on the other hand…)
And now the OG.
The first season was very successful.
(This is so cute. I want to pinch his cheeks.)
And now the OG.
The first season was very successful.
(Why aren’t they sitting together?)
And now the OG.
The first season was very successful.
(Their acting was so natural.
I thought they were playing trees and rocks.)
This two is not ordinary, but legendary.
(I miss Pan.)
(Pan did it better. A lot better.)
This two is not ordinary, but legendary.
(Did they mail out the calendars?)
(The world, please be nice to him.)
This two is not ordinary, but legendary.
(I’m so proud of you.)
Let's talk to Nong Nott.
(I can’t wait for your next project.)
(This is like seeing your kid succeed.)
Let's talk to Nong Nott.
(They couldn’t accord more lightbulbs?)
(I blame the organiser!)
How are you, Nott?
(We want the lead couple.)
(Pan carried the whole show.
There, I said it.)
How are you, Nott?
(I love the second couple.
They don’t look forced together.)
How are you, Nott?
(Nott is so handsome.)
(Do you know how
many girls want to be yours?)
(I want to see him with Pan.)
(Say something about Pan!)
(He’s that TTV actor.)
I'm absolutely happy.
(The whole cast is handsome.)
(Is his father President Tiwatin?)
I'm absolutely happy.
(They should’ve done the second season.)
(He looks sad.)
Because all of us work hard and it works.
(I’ll be your fan forever, Nott.)
(I once saw him in a club.
Believe me you don’t wanna hear it.)
Because all of us work hard and it works.
(I want a fan meeting for Gus and Bew.)
(Will Pan make a surprise appearance?)
Because all of us work hard and it works.
(Is he talking about Pan?)
(#Pan, Nott’s baby)
Because all of us work hard and it works.
(- My bad boy, Nott.
- Do another fan meeting for them!)
(I’m about to cry.)
It's nice to have some new shipped couples.
(I’m not kidding
when I say I want to be his wife.)
It's nice to have some new shipped couples.
(Please come and visit my apartment.)
(Who would get bored of you? Be serious.)
It's nice to have some new shipped couples.
(I won’t get bored.)
So the fans are not bored.
(I still watch the first season
when I have time.)
So the fans are not bored.
(His word were touching.)
(He was the best in the show!)
(Did he talk about Pan or the crew?)
(I want Pan there with him.)
So I think many people would like to know.
(This shit got 500 million views?)
(#MafiaBaby2 Congrats on 500 million views!)
So I think many people would like to know.
(Out of the 500 million views,
450 million views were mine.)
So I think many people would like to know.
(I love this show.)
(Thank you the cast and the crew!)
So I think many people would like to know.
(Go scream in a pillow
if you hate the show that much.)
So I think many people would like to know.
(I’m jealous of those who are there.)
(Mafia Baby will always be in my heart.)
So I think many people would like to know.
(Bew, go sit next to Gus.)
(Nott is practically radiating.)
Will we get to see six pack or not in this series?
(I need 3,000 episode for one season.)
(Love the cast. Hate the producers.)
Will we get to see six pack or not in this series?
(The show has everything you need!)
(The production was top-notch!)
Will we get to see six pack or not in this series?
(The hashtag is trending at no.1!)
I've heard that you three like to play sports and exercise.
(Give the cast a medal. They all did a good bye!)
(They’ve been through a lot.
I’m glad the show was a huge success.)
I've heard that you three like to play sports and exercise.
(Gus will be nominated for something
at The Greatest Y. I’m sure of it.)
I've heard that you three like to play sports and exercise.
(I’ll watch the show
until it gets one billion views.)
I've heard that you three like to play sports and exercise.
(The scene at the warehouse still breaks me.)
(Nott, you’re so handsome!!!)
I've heard that you three like to play sports and exercise.
(If it weren’t for the actors, no one would
watch the event. I hate the production team.)
I've heard that you three like to play sports and exercise.
(I don’t want the show to end.
I want to watch it every week.)
I've heard that you three like to play sports and exercise.
(I’m #TeamGusAndBew)
(I recommended the show to my friends.
And they all loved it.)
(500 million views are nothing.
We need to stream more!)
Many people want to see healthy bods.
(Bew, my baby mafia.)
(I want to see Nott with a gun again.)
Many people want to see healthy bods.
A little confident, a little confident.
Go, go, go, go!
[I think I saw you today]
Let's go, let's go.
[I must miss you too much]
Everyone! We got a problem.
What?
P called.
- P'P?
- Yes.
Nong P.
Hello, P'P.
Hello. Gus, Bew.
Congratulations to you.
- You're too kind.
- Yes, bro.
Can I take a screen shot for IG.
Sure, P'P.
1 2 3.
I'll tag you.
[You've been tagged by PPwang]
Did he really tag me?
I'll tell my mom.
Uh, where's Nott?
Nott? Let's go, he's there.
- Hi. Hello,
- P'P.
Congratulations on the a contract with TTV.
And I'm sorry about Pan.
Why are you sorry? He's not dead.
A talented person like him
won't go away easily. He'll be back soon.
I'll wait and see that day.
Yes.
Take it easy. Are you drunk or what?
If I'm drunk, I curse even more.
Actually, it's unfortunate that
Koon and Pan didn't get to come to this event.
Because they are a part
that made this series a success.
Can I ask you the truth?
Do you have something to hide from me?
Nothing to hide, only things that don't need to be told.
Like the things that you sold ​​my stories?
Have you sent the news to the page yet?
Oh, what is it? The kids were just arguing.
This is how news is made.
If we can make journalists go to events
PR would give us an additional 30%.
I brought a souvenir for you.
Is it true that you two fought so hard
that the crew have to stop?
Tell me. Don't you feel sorry for him?
What did he do to you?
Feel sorry?
I don't think anyone is pity for my sorry.
I just thought that if we invest on anything,
we must get something back.
Oh, don't look at me like that.
For Nott...
You are perfect.
I don't have to invest anything on you.
Let's think of us as partners.
In fact, P'Koon, she loves Pan.
The person who is a manager.
She created someone, she had to love that person naturally.
Oh, cheers.
In the end, he was right about everything.
Here, they just need someone to be on their side.
One day it might not be me.
(- Nott Pachanon Damrongpol.
- Pan Thanamin Anumanee)
(Gus Kittidech Pongpattanapan)
(Bew Bannawich Kedubol)
Why do you do this?
Why do you lie to me?
Do it, Toh.
If it makes you feel better, do it.
Do it.
Toh.
Why?
Why does it have to be you?
Why do you have to be mean to me?
I'm sorry.
So good.
Very good.
I like when you cry.
It's connecting with the next scene that Toh
will agree to be arrested
by the police instead of Nuer.
I can assure you that the audience
all over the country will cry.
You're gonna really end it like this?
The audience will be all dead.
Well, it ends like this.
Make it a legend.
Because
we don't have a sequel anyway.
Nott, TTV will talk to you about a drama.
Tomorrow, we have to go in.
It's a pleasure to work with everyone.
Thank you very much.
Well, Nott-Nott,
I'm going to get my hair done in the morning.
You have to wake up. Got it?
Good luck the two of you.
Hope we have a chance to work together again.
Thank you bro.
Thank you very much.
I'll see you next time.
OK.
Good luck.
Thank you very much.
Ok. Bye.
Good, very good.
Very good.
Thank you.
Nott too.
Yes.
Good bye.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for being a good partner of mine all along.
You..
You are the best partner for me.
(Song: Pan.
I went back to search the room.)
(Song: I think you should read this.)
(Song: She didn’t exactly ditch us.)
(Pan: She probably did it
out of guilt.)
(Song: You’re right, but…)
(Pan: Thanks anyways.)
(Pan: Do you want your reward for this?)
(Song: Stop it. I told you about it
because of our friendship.)
(Song: And stop offering yourself to
just anybody! Otherwise, I’ll punish you!)
(Koon: Can you get us an ice maker?)
(Koon: He concentrates better when
he has some ice to chew on. Please?)
(Mod: I’ll make sure he gets his ice.)
(Next Break)
I want to compensate for everything.
I can take it if it makes you feel comfortable
but don't expect me to forgive
or go back to the way it was
because the old me is no longer here.
I'm giving you a blessing.
Ayu Wanno Sukkan Palang.
I really want to eat Lod Chong at that stall.
It's delicious.
Will eat at the next market, then.
Hey, who's on the ads?
Looks familiar.
Oh, is it Pharaoh?
The scandalous one?
Oh.
He was scolded by Live people at that time,
now he is on JJTV channel.
Oh, what a sin.
- Yes!
- Suit each other.
That channel is full of scandalous people.
I think so too.
Let's go to the next market.
Hey.
Is that Pan?
Yes! Let's go ask for a photo?
- Uh, Nong Pan?
- Yes?
Would you mind taking a picture with us?
Come here.
Alright, let's take a photo. Smile.
Make it handsome and cute.
1 2 3.
So cool.
So cute.
When you're not selling cuteness,
you're so handsome.
- Thank you!
- As handsome as how beautiful I am.
Well, I'll go now.
Yes.
Thank you.
- Yes, see you.
- Now my Lod Chong is delicious.
Why did you come?
Well, I was around the neighborhood.
There was a shooting.
So I came.
You doing alright?
Yes.
Actually, I want to apologize.
You're right
that I have everything today
it's because you have been working so hard.
I want to compensate for everything.
It might not be a lot of money.
But I really want you to have it.
I can take it.
If it makes you feel comfortable
but don't expect me to forgive
or go back to the way it was
because the old me is no longer here.
OK.
It's okay.
I have done my part.
I want to thank and apologize for my part as well.
If I ever caused you any trouble.
But after this,
it's better we go separate ways.
When action,
Tar and Poh walk in and see him crying,
So you walk to him.
Then, you sit down and ask what's wrong.
What's up.
Never mind.
Then.
Never mind so let's go.
- Come up.
- And, wait!
Get up.
Get up and
can I have a kiss please?
Wow. Really?
Palm, this is not the era that
someone has to sit and wait like an idiot.
We have to start.
Pan, your cue to come in.
Run in from over there.
Stop them. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Run away.
As soon as it's done,
ask him,
Teacher, I want to try what they did just now.
You walk out.
Ok. Like this.
Let's shoot.
Children, watch PLAY BACK.
Oh, P'New.
I have errand to run, can I go?
Can I go with him?
I have an appointment as well.
What appointment are you having today?
We talked, no?
What's done is done.
Can you be here, Pan?
Yes.
Let's finish it.
So let's take it real.
What about me?
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Make a wish first.
Oh, can I do something first?
Sure.
I understand now that
being a new actor, an old actor
or being at the top is meaningless.
If we are not in the place that really suits us.
Blow them!
Yay!
- Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday to you!
Whatever we thought was the end,
it's actually a new beginning.
In the world of actors, we can start over as many times as we want.
If someone still gives us love.
And it's really great when we have someone who loves us
even on the day we're not the cutest.
Do people tell you this a lot today?
Happy birthday to you!
Yes, lots.
So how about this word?
0 1.
Now who will be the new or old partner?
I don't care anymore
because I found my happiness.
(Next Week)
I could see that everyone was always by our side.
Support.
Cheer up.
It's so deep that I can't explain it.
Damn, Gus!
There are no fans out there,
don't have to say this.
I got chills.
They cheered for them to be real couples.
But when they come out as dating
they'll lose the attention.
Why can't you play?
We did lots of takes.
When
the teacher have
me think of the person that I love.
I see P'Gus's face.
Even though it wasn't intentional at all.