(Disclaimer)
(This series is created
for entertainment purposes.)
(This series is suitable viewers for above 18 years of age.
It may contain violence, sexual situations and inappropriate use of language.)
(Parental guidance is suggested for viewers under 18 years of age.)
(Ranking Week 2)
Peek will be able to choose a partner.
With anyone.
From P's Team.
Before anyone else.
Help? Bro, brother.
You get frightened really easily.
Ouch.
You stepped on my foot, Korn.
Will I survive.
Sing together.
♪ Feeling lonely ♪
But we haven't spoken after that.
There will surely be drama.
Umm. One more left.
Hey.
What the heck you doing.
This is against the rules of the show.
Your bra, hey.
Just a little.
No.
How's it going.
P and Dew are waiting inside.
Have you chosen yet.
(War Of Y)
(Episode 13)
And the person Peek chose as his partner is?
Most.
Please take care of me Most.
Sure brother.
Peek might want to win.
He's really good at playing games.
And are you angry at him?
That he stole your partner.
Staying away from Most might be good.
So Most will miss me.
The person who should be angry.
Shouldn't it be Kla?
Are you pissed
that your partner did not choose you?
♪ I swear from now on ♪
♪ Every love song will belong to only you ♪
♪ Only you ♪
Oh wow!
How's it.
Amazing.
Should we go with this song?
I think there should be
a verse where you can...
sing well.
Gateway.
We choose this song.
Sure.
Here.
Thank you.
Fight there kids.
I'm surprised that you chose me.
Why?
Well, I see that
you are very close to Kla.
Or Korn.
Didn't think you would choose me.
Honestly.
I really like to sing.
But I am not that confident.
Do you remember your live
And I came in to sing with you.
Aha.
That's it
I sang with you and I got more confidence.
Oh.
I thought you had a fight with Kla.
Kla likes to annoy me.
So I wanted to try working with someone else.
It must be really fun to work with you.
Come. Let's divide the verse.
♪ Since I met you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Thank you, heaven ♪
♪ For letting us meet ♪
♪ Thank you to that person up there ♪
♪ Who made us able to meet ♪
♪ Thank you for every ♪
Korn.
I think.
Your singing. Should we try the low key.
Low key?
It's like.
♪ Thank you, heaven ♪
♪ Who made us able to meet ♪
Something like this.
Okay, I get it now.
♪ Thank you, heaven ♪
♪ Who made us able to meet ♪
♪ Thank you to that person up there ♪
Like this?
Yeah.
Well, it's okay Achi. But.
I won't get to show anything.
Umm
I think they do not focus
On the show this week.
They look at the chemistry.
Ah.
Think after me.
Like just now.
You were too focused on singing high keys.
You didn't convey.
It wasn't sending the message like me.
Right?
Um, yeah right.
Try again? I will help you.
Yeah!
♪ Thank you, heaven ♪
♪ Who made us able to meet ♪
♪ Thank you to that person up there ♪
Like this?
- Yes, like this.
- Yeah.
It's good. Not too tiring.
Right?
But is it okay?
It's very ok Korn.
You should go for like.
Warm, warm but sound cool at the same time.
And I will help with the sync.
And lets add.
Moments. Holding hands
Some hugs to make it more beautiful.
Umm.
Yeah. Sure.
For the team.
Let's try.
I did the right thing
By choosing you.
If I chose Kla.
We would be fighting
And not agree to anything.
That's for sure
I'm good.
Don't let Kla know that.
- Come on.
- Let's try one more time.
♪ Thank you ♪
Again.
♪ Since the first day I met you ♪
♪ There's no flower that ♪
♪ Blooms and glow's ♪
♪ As beautiful as your smile ♪
♪ Since the first day I met you ♪
♪ There's no night I would ♪
♪ Look up at the stars in the sky ♪
♪ Because they are not as beautiful
Compare to your eyes ♪
Can I have one more time.
Start with "Since".
♪ Since the first day I met you ♪
♪ There's no night I would ♪
♪ Look up at the stars in the sky ♪
♪ Because they are not as beautiful
Compare to your eyes ♪
What are you doing Most?
Well.
You can sing the wrong keys all the way.
So we don't stress out.
Won't we be more stressed like this.
- The keys are already wrong anyway.
- Really?
♪ Since the first day I met you ♪
- ♪ There's no night I would ♪
- Try it.
♪ That is ♪
♪ As beautiful ♪
Go.
♪ As your smile ♪
There's nothing.
I was stressed so
Most was trying to cheer me up.
♪ But hey, how come when I met you
My heart started to misbehave ♪
♪ Don't know if it's right or wrong
But I want it to be you okay ♪
♪ I'll do everything possible for you to be
Ma baby ba ba ba baby! ♪
♪ I getting love sick ♪
♪ You're made me love sick ♪
♪ Whatever I think about
I stuck stuck ♪
♪ Stuck on you
Like that ♪
Kla.
I know you don't want to be my partner.
But can you concentrate
Focus a little here.
I wanna win.
So I can get a badge like others.
Sing! Quick.
It's not that I don't want to partner with you.
♪ Since the first day I met you
There's no night I would ♪
Peek.
Peek, stop it
I'm ticklish, I'm ticklish.
They are fighting.
Gosh.
It's like a Thai Soap Opera.
Peek. I'm ticklish.
What are you guys doing.
What's wrong with you?
We are rehearsing.
What's your problem?
This is called rehearsing?
When we rehearse
There's gotta be some noise.
Right, Most?
♪ Since the day ♪
Are you trying to piss me off Peek?
Hey, calm down Kla.
Peek is not purposely annoying him.
Don't know why is Kla so angry
We were just playing
I have to be angry.
He's completely ignoring me.
I'm his senior.
Relax.
What the hells wrong with you Peek.
Why are you doing this to me.
It's not at all about you Kla.
I enjoy rehearsing with Most
That's it.
What is your problem with me.
You are purposely agitating me.
Since the time you picked Most.
If you have a problem, say it.
Didn't you say
You were feeling uncomfortable.
They asked me to choose
I chose someone
Who I feel comfortable with.
You have no right to be angry.
Pla and Toon said it clearly.
But Pla and Toon are not producers of the show.
The show doesn't care
if we are being shipped outside.
They care when we are in here.
You focus on your work.
I'm going to get some water.
You want to do like this right?
I want water.
Move.
Hey.
Damn.
(Announcement: Make the show as dramatic as you can!)
(- Boss: Took Kla Earth to practice next to Most Peek.
- Bank: Korn and Achi are nearby too)
(Boss: Honestly won't the sound mix in?
We have a lot of rehearsing rooms)
(Gateway: Because we didn’t put them there for them to practice.
Did you not read the announcement above?)
(Boss: But it’s getting tired now.
Can we not make them right at least for a week?)
(Aom: I told Most to make jokes
so that Peek can loosen up)
(Gateway: Good job. If they don't start fighting,
then keep adding fuel until they do)
(Next Break)
For the singing week.
Voice should be the most important.
What was with the ending.
Did you forget it.
Achi must be like.
Thinking of ways to steal the scene.
(Honestly, Korn is already handsome)
(#KornAchi ship?)
(What is the show thinking?)
(I want P's shirt)
(Kla Earth are coming this week)
The environment for this week's singing week.
(Muscle over muscle, I'm scared)
All idols are doing well.
(This can be made into a drama)
With their singing and acting.
(Waiting to see Peek's singing)
(Is this a reality show or finding a dramatic actor)
And the chemistry between the pairs.
There's only Peek.
Who seems to be sulking at Kla a bit.
Doesn't it hurt?
I'm not clearing.
I'm not taking any revenge.
I am just.
Focusing on my work.
Annoyed with what?
That time I was concentrating with
Preparing the show.
Really?
But during the show
You didn't seem to have concentration.
♪ Never thought this would happen to me ♪
♪ I wanna thank all the good and bad
That brought us together ♪
♪ I swear from now on
Every love song will belong to only you ♪
♪ Only you ♪
What was with the ending?
Did you forget it?
I was excited
There nothing with Kla.
Because from now
I will only focus on my part.
I think, Peek
You need to pay more attention.
Heart problems isn't cleared.
He's now getting scolded
About the mission as well.
And will Peek be able to do it?
Let's wait and see.
Peek.
I think for the singing week.
Voice should be the most important.
We can just look into each others eyes.
Hold hands.
That's already okay.
The song is already beautiful.
But if there's a story
It will be even better.
Viewers will like it.
Peek.
You also know.
I and Achi.
Already have a fandom.
But you shouldn't stop thinking
About yourself Most.
We don't know in the end
Who will the show choose.
But if your chemistry is good
with everyone, Isn't it good for you?
I don't want to have any problems Peek.
Do you know?
For FC's.
A broken ship
Is the most hurtful thing for them.
Hey.
Korn.
I think you should remove the necklace.
It looks like.
A little too much.
It looks weird
I think.
We shouldn't wear the necklace.
One more thing, it doesn't look.
Matching with each other
I think you should remove it.
- Umm.
- So we can look matching.
Oh yeah. Can, can, can.
Take it off.
Achi. Can you help?
Yes, sure.
Can?
Yes.
Can I ask you to help keep it?
- Of course.
- Thanks.
- Welcome.
- Looks better right?
You look handsome.
Korn.
Why did you take off the necklace?
I think it looks good on you.
Achi thought it was too much.
And we didn't match.
Really?
Careful. You will drop.
How so.
I don't know.
Achi might be like...
Trying to steal your scene here.
Hey.
Aren't you thinking too much.
Hes doing it for the team.
But only one person can win.
I'm sincere with you.
Because you were good to me too.
(Achi Y6 Vote for Achi Y6 at 1212022
10 votes Y6*10 at 1212022 20 votes Y6*20 at 1212022)
(Music: You're All by Tur Tung Nun)
(Korn Y2 Vote for Korn Y2 at 1212022
10 votes Y2*10 at 1212022 20 votes Y2*20 at 1212022)
Achi might be like.
Trying to steal your scene here.
Hey.
Aren't you thinking too much.
Hes doing it for the team.
But only one person can win.
(Every Tuesday at 9pm, On TTV)
They look like real celebrities.
Your son was really good.
Face expressions and eyes
All on spot.
We are not Achi's parents.
We are Most's parents.
- I am Mosts's father.
- Yes.
The staff said that Achi's father isn't here today He's busy.
He's always like that.
Always busy. He's never free.
But the children are cute.
He knows it well
They always talk.
Singing competition.
Amazing.
- Really good.
- Hmm.
No ones giving in to one another.
Both of them, really good competition
Both are handsome.
Hows it? The show has already ended.
(How can he be okay, it was messed up)
(What can I trust about this industry?)
(Then who asked you to trust them)
(How can he be okay, it was messed up)
(What can I trust about this industry?)
(Then who asked you to trust them)
Not okay.
(How can he be okay, it was messed up)
(What can I trust about this industry?)
(Then who asked you to trust them)
(Gateway: Korn, damn it. Can't you hold your emotions
Can't go into the ad now, time isn't enough)
(Bank: Achi will handle it)
(- Aom: We are on trend 2.
- Gateway: This is good then, good drama)
(Gateway: Boss, get Earth Kla to standby.
Praise the moment of Achi and Korn, don't forget)
(- Boss: Don't they have to focus.
- Gateway: Oh you, do it so they want to service more.)
(Gateway: This week we need
to be on number 1)
(Next Break)
I might change the plan a bit.
You just go with the flow.
What.
And now the results...
Are in my hands.
Wohoo.
No ones giving in to one another
Both of them really competitive and handsome.
Hows it? The show has already ended.
(How can he be okay, it was messed up)
(What can I trust about this industry)
(Then who asked you to trust them)
(How can he be okay, it was messed up)
(What can I trust about this industry)
(Then who asked you to trust them) Not okay.
(How can he be okay, it was messed up)
(What can I trust about this industry)
(Then who asked you to trust them)
Not okay that the show ended too quickly.
(The last moment was so cute.)
(Would be cuter if it was with Most)
Ah. Not okay because it ended.
(Y fans only come to cheer.)(How far will this industry go)
Because the happy moments always go by fast.
(The upper comment is so nosy. If you don't like, don't watch)
That's right Gun Aeng.
That's right.
Our next show is...
(If you want to listen to songs
then go to the Voice, this is celebrity show)
Also ready.
(Because you think like this, that's why it isn't going anywhere)
Right and they are.
Kla and Earth.
♪ Did you know I was looking ♪
Aow.
Why is it like this Toon.
Here.
Did you see Korn and Achi.
The last moment.
The audience were screaming.
We already rehearsed well.
Mentors like it.
The teachers like it.
We also liked it, right?
We just do as we rehearsed.
Don't think about the other pairs.
Okay.
Come on. Let's do it bro.
- Alright. Let's go man.
- Let's go.
(Music: Love Sick)
(Earth Y5 Vote for Earth Y5 at 1212022
10 votes Y5*10 at 1212022 20 votes Y5*20 at 1212022)
(Kla Y3 Vote for Kla Y3 at 1212022
10 votes Y3*10 at 1212022 20 votes Y3*20 at 1212022)
(Every Tuesday at 9pm, On TTV)
Oh wow.
The best.
The best, the best.
Hmm! And you were saying backstage.
That you weren't ready
You were nervous.
(I love how his accents sings Naughty)
(At first he looks stressed but Kla consoled him, so good)
(Guys, Kla Earth, no no. Don't think about it)
Therefore, let these two go and rest.
(Upper comment, stop ghost shipping #Kla belongs to Peek)
Most and Peek.
(Please, let there be some friendship in the industry. No need to ship everyone)
Thank you.
(Most Peek is coming, I'm excited)
Yes.
I might change the plan a little bit.
You just go with the flow.
Huh?
(Most Y1 Vote for Most Y1 at 1212022
10 votes Y1*10 at 1212022 20 votes Y1*20 at 1212022)
(Music: From now on,
all love songs belongs to you)
(Peek Y4 Vote for Peek Y4 at 1212022
10 votes Y4*10 at 1212022 20 votes Y4*20 at 1212022)
Honestly.
If we just look.
Not being bias.
These two look good together
I think they look fine.
But I think for Korn and Achi.
The fandom would be a chaos.
Umm.
(Peek Y4 Vote for Peek Y4 at 1212022
10 votes Y4*10 at 1212022 20 votes Y4*20 at 1212022)
(Every Tuesday at 9pm, On TTV)
Oh my gosh.
You need to do this to become a singer?
Adorable.
It's so cute.
They must be able to do everything.
Absolutely.
Now that all the 3 shows are now over,
it is the time.
To close the votes.
And the pair to win.
Are.
Pairs of...
Most and Peek.
And for sure everyone.
One of them will be the winner of the week.
Or get the Best Singer award.
And the results are.
Now in my hands.
And the winner.
Who will receive the Best Singer award is?
Most.
Congratulations to Most.
Yay.
Good job.
Woow.
Good job, good job.
Oh, I'm shaking.
Go get your award.
Thank you, thank you.
Good job, really good.
And giving the doll too, how cute.
Ummm.
When will the car come.
Hey.
Did you see me up there?
When I was singing
I think I did really well.
Don't you think.
Umm.
Hey, Kla.
Our scores weren't that bad.
Not much difference from Most.
Umm.
Sigh.
What is wrong with you guys.
Damn.
Korn, Korn.
Korn, wait.
Listen to me.
I didn't mean to steal your verse.
When a lot of people were cheering up.
I couldn't stop singing so I continued.
Don't be mad at me.
Really?
You don't say anything Peek.
You are another one.
If you didn't instigate me
I won't be over thinking.
Hold on.
How did I insigate you?
I only came to warn you.
But in the end
Didn't Achi do as I said.
Oh wow.
Were you that scared of loosing.
You want to find a selling point to create a story
It's your problem.
But what right do you have.
To destroy someone else's story.
Wait.
Whose did I destroy.
And why did you kiss me.
We spoke about this.
The feels was right.
And what problem do you have.
Because of that moment, you won tonight.
I just can't kiss with anyone.
And I didn't allow you to kiss me.
You kissing me like this is harassment.
If I told the crew.
You would be doing against the rules.
But isn't it a game.
Everyone does it.
You want to play like this Peek.
Playing the game
Without caring about other peoples feelings.
Is this your truth.
Calm down Korn.
Yeah.
Someone else recognizes you now.
Good.
I won't be lonely anymore.
What are you saying?
About you playing the game.
It started since you hurt your leg.
Hold on Achi.
What about the leg.
Peek.
Don't tell me that the leg.
Was really a lie.
Say it Peek.
Voice: Can we have all the idols in the main hall.
Voice: For the special surprise.
Woo.
(Gateway: Fans favourite person
got the trend up to number 1)
(Bank: Mom, they are fighting in front of the house, should we get the camera)
(Gateway: No need because foot of Peek
kissing Most can't go out)
(Boss: Means he can just go against the rules.
But FC needs to get their moment, like this?)
(Gateway: And that's showbiz, kids)
(Next Break)
Most, son.
It's money dad.
If I win, we would get lots of money.
Our situation will be better.
Next time.
Don't mess with my life.
Most, son, Most
*Chatting in excitement*
- Dad.
- How are you? Are you okay?
There he is, Peek.
Peek.
Peek, I am here.
Dad, he's here.
Come here quick.
Quick.
Oye! My son. Oh.
Come here quick.
Come here. Sit first.
Sit, sit, sit.
How are you.
Achi.
Your parents can't come today.
Do you want to go wait inside?
Oh.
It's okay
I will go out and stay by myself.
Why did you lie to me.
Calm down dad.
Didn't you say...
it was just a singing competition?
If I told you honestly
You would never allow.
Whatever I am doing.
Do you think it's fun?
Do you know what all I have to go through?
What I'm doing, I'm doing to help the family.
By kissing with guys on TV?
Hmm.
Have you ever thought...
if it was suitable?
I'm not your student dad.
And can't I teach my own son?
Huh?
Why didn't you think of me?
What if other relatives...
or the principal sees this,
what will I do?
Dad.
Softer.
Amazing.
Other parents, when they see their kids
They ask...
Are you tired? How are you?
But you.
You do like you're ashamed.
I'm not ashamed.
I just don't understand.
How did I go wrong?
Huh, how did I bring you up...
that you became like this?
Umm.
Ah.
Hello dad, hello mom.
Peek.
You ready?
In a bit.
The crew will come to interview.
This is money dad.
If I win, we will get lots of money.
Our family will be a lot better.
Please.
Help be nice to me for 5 minutes
At least in front of the camera.
You can hate me all you want.
I don't hate you.
Do this for me.
Do it for our family.
Next year you will be retiring.
We need money from this show.
Are you ready?
Mom, dad?
Ready.
Son.
Why are you sitting there.
Come here quick. Come sit here.
Come here, here.
Come
5,4,3,2
Mom and dad
Do you have anything to say to Peek.
I do.
Don't overdo son
I am so proud of you.
My son.
Oh, and.
Please support my son, everyone.
Do not forget to press like
Lots of likes.
I hope that you.
Succeed in everything you think of doing.
Can you say a little more please.
However, we are.
Always here to support you.
Keep fighting son.
Hearing like this, I am ready to fight.
Take care of yourself.
Can you?
Here.
You've lost weight.
Go home safe.
Um, yeah.
Oh, here.
Um.
I got this for you.
In case you missed my cooking.
Your dad is not angry at you.
He came here to cheer you.
You know! He was taking
hours to choose his clothes.
But...
After reaching here. Yeah.
He might...
Have been shocked.
Look at your face.
Sulking like a baby.
You're my son. You must be strong, okay?
Hmm.
Oh and.
Don't lose to anyone.
Do you understand?
Fight!
Yes.
Hm! This is it.
Come here. Give me a hug.
Go home safely.
Sure.
Win and come.
I'm here for you.
Fighting.
I'm going. Bye.
Dad. Where did he go.
You know your father is a teacher.
And look
You got called into the principal's office.
Hmm.
Sigh.
Boys fighting these days
It's normal.
But this is not something to fight about.
Next time.
Tell me.
Huh.
Let them see me.
I guarantee.
They will never tease you again.
Why?
Who teased him?
Oye.
His friends, they teased him that he's gay.
Oh that?
The reason he fought with them
was because he was called a gay?
And you.
Stop doing those girly things.
Um.
Dad.
Don't make him feel worse.
He's already hurt.
And why are you crying.
Being Teacher Sakda's son.
You must be strong.
Come. Let's go. Let's have dinner.
Lotus root soup.
Your favourite, isn't it?
- Let's go eat.
- Come on. Quick.
Why are you crying.
Did it go bad?
I'm sorry.
I just don't want to see you sad.
I just came to know what all you've been through.
I understand you.
Really?
But I don't.
In this era. There are people who can't accept this.
If the show puts this on the highlight.
The viewers will think this is so cliche.
It's okay you.
Whatever the era is.
There are people.
Who understands.
And those who don't understand.
They were brought up that way.
It's not easy for them.
And they think it's easy for me?
Come on.
Give him some time.
Don't be angry at your dad, Peek.
I'm not angry
I just feel sad.
He acts like I don't mean anything.
You have value Peek.
At least.
For me.
♪ The more I forbid
The more the heart resists ♪
♪ My heart is stubborn and refuses to listen ♪
♪ The more I try to force it ♪
♪ The more it defies me ♪
♪ And I end up thinking about you every time ♪
Hey.
Let me warm this for you.
Your mom made it.
It's easy for you to say.
Your family isn't like this.
Next time.
Don't mess with my life.
Focus on your work.
Peek.
You had to be this harsh.
I'm worried about you.
Why are you lashing at me.
I didn't even say anything about.
You messing with other people.
Honestly.
In this house.
Nobody wants you anymore.
Except for me.
If the day, I can't tolerate you anymore.
You will have no one else Peek.
Hello, can you hear.
Can you hear me.
You can't then that's it
I'm hanging up.
Bye.
Hello everyone.
Today we are not here in the afternoon.
But we are here at night.
Sundays like this.
We bring you all to look at the stars
No. Probably not.
Because I am here today
For the show.
Waii Jai Y Idol.
(Waii Jai Y Idol)
You all must be missing this.
- Do you miss it?
- We do.
The whole time you are in the camp.
You don't get to touch it.
(The rules are very easy)
(Right now the crew have hidden these phones
in different parts of the camp)
(Go and find it)
(If it's the one that can open and has signal)
(That is the right one)
(Who can bring it to Seoulsay first)
(That person is the winner)
Therefore, now.
If everyone is ready.
Go and give support to everyone. Let's go!
The privilege that Peek got last week.
Was really peak.
If I get the mobile phone.
I might get airtime like other people.
It's the final week now.
To play it just for fun would be.
Can't do it anymore.
Game on.
There is no friendship in the battle field.
If you can kill, kill
Who ever dies, let them be.
Hello Pond.
What are you watching.
Did I come disturb you?
Oh no
Just watching something interesting.
You came at the right time, K. Tai.
Um. Not sure if TTV is interested in him like me?
(He'll win the whole thing.
Who needs talent to be trended?)
(Love triangle. Is 3P a new trends in the BL World.)
(Y-Idol Crew)
(Gateway: Why didn't anyone get the footage
of Kla Peek fighting in the kitchen? Answer!!)
(Boss: It's past filming time.
We shouldn't invade their privacy)
(Gateway: Boss, he signed the contract.
They allow us to do everything)
(Boss: He signed the contract that no filming after 10pm
We created the rules, why are we breaking it?)
(Gateway removed Boss. Gateway invited K. Pond
K. Pond joined the group)
(K.Pond: Anyone else got any problem?)
(Next Week) What ever role you played
You were always taken, right.
Hey, Achi.
This time is too much.
I don't want you to do any more worse, Peek.
Peek, come with me.
If there is nothing, he should be back now.
He did against the rules twice.
There must be some penalty.
What did you speak to K. Pond?
You weren't punished, were you.
But you were taken, right?