BEHIND YOUR TOUCH
We're going to track down
the psychic on this day.
Mom.
It's Kim Seon-woo.
He's our prime suspect, so focus.
I'll really have to decline.
He can't be the killer.
A quick check will do.
Goodbye.
I saw Kim Seon-woo
going toward Mount Mujin.
Try to locate Kim Seon-woo
as you touch other people.
-Make way for the car, please.
-Seon-woo
-was following Assemblyman Cha.
-Please move to the side.
Why does Kim Seon-woo
keep crossing paths with Assemblyman Cha?
Where is he now?
-At his barn, sir.
-Let's go there.
Assemblyman Cha came to the barn that day.
I think he came to meet my father.
-You have to take this call.
-Who is it?
The representative of the Central Party.
There's someone there.
It's Mr. Park.
Yeah?
He was there.
Kim Seon-woo.
He was behind that pillar
on the night of the meteor shower!
Then Kim Seon-woo must be the killer.
There's a good chance that he is.
Then shouldn't you catch him quick?
Right.
He might kill again.
Arrest him already.
And what?
Why is Kim Seon-woo the killer?
He was standing behind the pillar
near the barn
on the night of the meteor shower.
What's so wrong about that?
Let me explain.
Based on the wounds of the murder victims,
the killer commits murders
with his eyes closed.
Why is that?
It's to hide his crimes from being seen.
Seen by who?
By those with psychometric powers.
But how did these people
come to have these powers?
It was through the light
coming from a cow
that got hit by a meteorite.
They see people's memories
by touching either the leg or the butt.
But they can only see what's been
projected onto people's retinas.
So if the killer closes his eyes,
the psychics can't see anything.
And the serial killer knew this!
But how did he find this out
in the first place?
It's because he too
had psychometric powers
that let him see people's memories!
With these clues put together,
I've come to the conclusion
that the guy who was standing
near the barn that night
is the serial killer!
And how did you know he was near the barn?
The good-hearted psychics saw it
by touching each other's leg and butt.
And that guy was Kim Seon-woo?
Yes.
But there's no concrete evidence,
is there?
Sadly, that is the case for now.
What do you mean, "sadly"?
We already have more than enough evidence.
Take him away.
Hey, buddy.
Let's take your medication
after your meal.
Why are you drooling so much?
We need concrete evidence
to catch Kim Seon-woo.
The rain poncho
or the murder weapon, for instance.
How do we find them?
We have to get him on the Butt of Truth.
Then we'll be able to find evidence.
Bong Ye-bun.
-Yes?
-You heard me, right?
Yes.
We're almost there. Let's do this.
Okay.
There you are, Justin.
Your dad's looking for you.
He is?
Justin!
You got a teddy bear?
I won it for him.
Why were you looking for Justin?
What? I was?
His eyes were getting teary,
so I assumed that he missed Justin.
Didn't you miss him?
I mean, I always miss my son.
I knew it.
Oh, and I saw that you can have
your pictures taken over there.
Let's go check it out.
Justin would love it.
But I have to watch the booth.
Come on, Seon-woo can watch it for you.
Right?
Yes, I'll be here.
-Go ahead.
-Really?
Then I'll be right back.
Let's go.
Justin!
There you are.
I've been looking for you.
For me?
Why?
I'd like a word with you.
So have a seat.
I'm fine standing.
It's going to take a while, so please.
I'm not sure.
I can't think of anything
to talk about with you for that long.
I heard you made this.
I did.
Quite impressive.
Did you learn woodworking?
I'm self-taught. It's just a hobby.
Why would a Hankook University graduate
with such great skill
be working part-time
at a convenience store in Mujin,
a place you have no connection with?
Because I wanted to kill people.
Is that what you wanted to hear?
Why do you keep
suspecting me?
I've never done anything suspicious.
It's my instinct as a detective
who is desperate to catch the killer.
Instinct? More like incompetence.
You're exercising violence
by suspecting someone
without any evidence.
Let's call it a skill.
Sometimes, detectives have to trust
their guts rather than evidence.
This feels a bit unfair,
but I guess there's nothing to be done
since it's your job.
I'll try to understand.
I'll just swoop in and touch him
one of these days.
No, don't do that.
If Kim Seon-woo really is the killer,
he's probably onto us already.
We don't know what he'll do next.
It could put both of you in danger,
so please don't do anything rash.
Then what are you planning to do?
I've caught criminals just fine
without psychics before.
You all did great.
Thanks for your help today, Ok-hui.
I did it for Ye-bun, not you.
Bong Ye-bun.
Yes?
Is something wrong?
No.
Nothing's wrong.
As if you would understand.
Captain, I see that you met
Dr. Bong's grandfather recently.
This is the last article my sister wrote.
She was investigating this case.
But she died
before she could finish investigating it.
Hey, you're home late.
Yeah. I'm going to bed.
Ye-bun.
What the… Are you drunk?
A bit.
What is it? Is something wrong?
Nothing like that.
It's just that I'm proud of you.
You grew up to be
such a wonderful young woman.
Do you want to
go visit your mom tomorrow?
It's been a while.
Hi, Mi-ok.
We're here.
How have you been?
HERE LIES JUNG MI-OK
Your mom passed at 40,
and you're already 35.
I know.
You remind me of her more and more.
Both your face and your personality.
What was she like at my age?
She was passionate and righteous.
She never turned away from people in need.
She stood by their side
and got their stories out.
She was
a great journalist.
Then why would she
do such a thing?
I wish I could have read
her mind back then.
She didn't leave any notes,
so nobody knows.
I wonder why
she didn't leave any messages.
She could have
said something to her own daughter.
Apparently, she told Ju-man
that she'd been having a hard time.
To Mr. Cha?
Yeah.
I guess some things
are harder to talk about with your family.
Were the two of them
very close?
You could say that.
He used to have a huge crush on her
when he was younger.
He did?
Yeah.
I don't know why I just told you that.
I guess being here takes me back.
How many times do I have to come here?
Who's going to run my business?
The faster you answer our questions,
the faster you can return to your store.
What am I supposed to tell you
when I don't know anything?
Why are all these people here?
They're here
regarding Ms. Lee Ji-suk's murder.
Again? Why?
We were told to start over.
Everyone, you can all go home. It's fine.
You're dismissed.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
They have nothing to do with the case.
You can go.
If you're so sure,
why haven't you found a single lead?
God knows what you're up to.
Yes, Chief.
Yes, sir.
Captain, the chief
wants you in his office.
But why did he call you?
Has he been somewhere?
He'd been called by the higher-ups.
Okay.
Damn it.
Hey, where's my other kneepad?
The traffic captain took it
to play soccer.
I can't believe him.
He's never any help.
Goodness,
-if it isn't Captain Won.
-Yes, sir.
-Captain Won.
Good to see you, Captain Won.
Or should I say, "Chief Won"?
Come sit.
-Well…
-Come on.
What's going on?
I feel like you're not catching
the killer on purpose
so you can get me fired and take my seat.
No, sir.
I haven't been home
or changed my underwear in three days.
Do you want to see it?
Don't be like that.
-You know I trust you.
-Okay.
-Have a seat.
-Yes, sir.
Look at you. You look so haggard.
Have you eaten?
Yes, I had ox bone soup.
Good.
Do you have the receipt?
Yes, I do.
Show me.
Here.
Three of you had regular ox bone soup,
and one of you had an extra-large.
Well, you see…
I've been feeling weak lately.
Good job.
So did your soup
come with extra meat?
For some strange reason,
it didn't.
That's interesting.
What do you mean?
You said…
your soup didn't come with any extra meat
but guess who's dead meat.
I don't understand.
I think you do.
Wait a minute.
Where's my sunscreen?
Sunscreen?
I don't want to get a tan
when I bury you later.
Sir, I'll work harder from now on.
So that's why you're so pale.
You've been slacking off.
No, it's been pretty cloudy lately.
-Is that right? Listen.
-Yes.
Do you know the poem,
Song of the Yellow Bird?
How does it go?
Look at those orioles
Flying in the sky in pairs
But alas, your kneepad is all alone
My goodness.
Excuse me.
Do you have a moment?
You didn't have to.
Thank you so much.
I've heard
that the victims of the redevelopment scam
used to get together and protest.
That's right.
We were grasping at straws
after losing everything we had.
Looking back,
it was all pointless.
Could you take a look at this?
Here.
Now I remember.
This woman was the chairperson
of the emergency committee.
She brought her son with her
because she couldn't find a babysitter.
I felt for her since she was a single mom.
MUJIN REDEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE PROTEST
Let's eat some gimbap.
No.
Come on, let's eat.
No, I want chips.
You only ate chips yesterday.
No more chips.
Here, sweetie.
Thank you.
Do you perhaps
have her contact information?
There's no use trying to contact her.
She's gone missing.
Sorry?
Her boy was so adorable and smart.
I wonder how he managed without his mom.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
NAME: KIM SEON-WOO
Hello.
-Hello.
I wonder why Mr. Cha is here.
It must be tedious and lonely
to stay home after having been so busy.
Not at all.
This is where I belong.
Come now.
Please tell me what I can do for you.
You're my number one contributor.
It's the least I can do.
Stop it.
It's detestable to see
politicians doing stuff like this
as soon as they enter office.
Now that you won, I couldn't ask for more.
You're so selfless, sir.
You're making me ashamed of myself.
-Hey, good to see you.
-Hi.
Oh, my. What's this?
Thank you so much.
Hello.
Hey, Ye-bun.
How have you been?
I've been okay.
All right then.
You should get going. You must be busy.
Okay, sir.
I'll visit again soon.
Wait up, Mr. Cha.
Did you meet with Captain Won recently?
I heard you asked him for a favor.
It was nothing.
Then why were you collecting
Mi-ok's articles?
Every article she wrote,
including the very last one.
Why are you digging into something
that happened over a decade ago?
What is this about?
What are you hiding from me?
I wanted to ask you something.
Auntie told me
that you and my mom used to be very close.
That's right.
We used to be pretty close.
Mr. Cha.
I want to know
the reason why my mom committed suicide.
She left without saying anything
to me, my grandpa, or my aunt.
But I heard she told you
that she'd been going through a hard time.
What troubled her so much?
You must know.
Your mom seemed strong on the outside,
but she was so soft-hearted.
She even suffered from depression.
Did you know she was on medication?
No.
She probably didn't want to worry you.
The story she had been covering
was eating away at her.
She used to rant about it to me,
but I was too busy back then.
I should have taken better care of her.
I was so caught up in climbing the ladder.
I hadn't seen her in months
until she passed.
Make sure to call whenever you need me.
I'll be on my way now.
Your sister
didn't kill herself.
OK-HUI DEOK-HEE CORNER STORE
He doesn't have any criminal records.
He's clean.
I suspected that much.
What about his military service?
He was exempt from service.
When he was perfectly fit?
His father is deceased,
and his mother is missing.
Missing?
But why did you ask me to look into him?
I was just curious.
Why did you sneak into his room
while he was away?
You probably think
Mr. Kim is such a kind and polite person.
You know he's tutoring me
in English, right?
He scolds me so harshly
whenever I get something wrong on a quiz.
He scorns and humiliates me.
He even threatens to show my quiz
to Justin if I don't make the cut.
Are you happy
now that you've shown him everything?
I think I got a question wrong,
so I was going to fix my answer.
You thought gemstones
were measured in "carrots"?
Yes.
So what were you doing in his room?
I was…
I wanted to make sure
he was doing all right by himself.
You're not a good liar, Detective Moon.
You're suspecting him, aren't you?
How did you know?
Why else would a detective
sneak into someone's house?
It's not like you're here to steal.
Am I right?
I should mind my own business.
I should…
I followed Kim Seon-woo to his workshop.
Stay away from him.
I think he fell asleep.
This is our chance.
No, it's too dangerous. Get out of there.
JEON GWANG-SIK
Gwang-sik.
Gwang…
I told you not to act on your own.
Gwang-sik.
Gwang-sik…
Gwang-sik, no!
Gwang-sik!
Gwang-sik…
Detective Moon?
Gwang-sik?
There's nothing wrong with my bones.
They gave me a tetanus shot
and an antibiotic shot.
But my hands will be wrapped
in bandages for the time being.
Take these for a week.
Thank you.
What on earth happened?
The thing is,
I quite enjoyed woodworking
at the festival,
so I wanted to ask him to teach me and…
Did you do this to him?
It's not like that.
He was asleep when I went inside,
so I walked over to wake him up.
But then his eyes opened wide,
and I got so startled
that I fell on my back.
And that's when the lumber fell on me.
Yes.
So I brought him to the hospital.
But how did you know to find him here?
That's…
We are very close.
We're like brothers.
Right, bro?
-Yes, bro.
-Yeah.
I'll call you a taxi.
You got hurt because of me.
No way. It's fine.
I shouldn't have snuck in
in the first place.
Still…
I can drive Gwang-sik home.
-Let's go, bro.
-Okay, bro.
-Is that really it?
-What?
Are you sure you fell on your own?
Yes, it's true.
Luckily, Mr. Kim blocked
the lumber with his hands.
Otherwise, it would have been really bad.
He just
doesn't seem like such a bad person.
Do you really think
he's the serial killer?
Whatever the case, I apologize.
You got hurt while helping me.
Don't worry about it.
You were the one who got Ae-ran out.
I wanted to repay you.
Just leave things to me for now,
and take care of yourself.
Ae-ran would be worried.
Gwang-sik!
Are you okay?
You're okay, right?
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Hey, Bun Bun.
Where are you?
Do you want to have a drink with me?
It's been a while.
No, I can't drink while I'm on the job.
What job?
A very important job.
You know it's dangerous
to go out for a drink, right?
Of course, I was going to drink at home.
Okay, make sure to drink at home.
Don't go anywhere else, all right?
All right.
Sorry for calling you over again.
-Not at all, sis!
I want to ask you
for a personal favor today.
I have a friend
I cherish more than my life.
I need your help to protect her.
-Yes, sis!
Did you all bring
the deadliest weapons you own?
Eun-hye, show me.
What is that?
It's hair dye.
How is that a weapon?
Put this in your hair,
and your eyes sting like crazy.
You're incapacitated.
Fair enough.
Su-jin, what did you bring?
And that is?
Five layers of gel nail polish.
All right.
Mi-yeong.
You didn't bring anything.
Just a second.
You had your vocal cords done too?
Yes, sis.
-Yes, sis.
-Good for you.
Thank you.
Yeong-hui.
-Who's this?
-She's my mother-in-law.
Hello, ma'am.
Why did you bring her here?
She's the deadliest person I know.
Would you like me to demonstrate?
Sure.
You impudent brat.
Have you no manners?
Am I invisible to you?
You still shouldn't have tagged along--
Who are you to lecture me?
You must take me for a fool
to spew that nonsense at me!
You awful little snake.
She really is deadly.
Okay then. Let's divide up the roles.
We'll be working in two shifts.
This half will patrol around
Bong's Animal Hospital whenever you can.
And this half will stand by
at my family's corner store
and be dispatched
as soon as something happens.
All right, get moving.
Why are you here?
I told you it was over between us.
The prize we won at the festival arrived,
and I didn't know what to do with it.
Didn't I tell you to sell it
and split the cash?
Why would you bring me this?
It's a prize we won together.
How could you tell me to send it away?
What are you suggesting?
I think it'd be best if you take it.
Will you be okay with that?
I'll just come by whenever I miss it.
Once you send it over, that's that.
I think I deserve that much.
Then you just take it.
Throw it away if you want.
The TV is listening!
What's going on between them?
Can't you tell?
-Neither wants to keep the TV.
-You're hurting its feelings.
Like a couple fighting
over custody of their children.
What are you doing here?
What were you thinking about all alone?
You looked sad.
I was thinking about my mom.
The last time I saw her
was by the sea right here.
When she was feeling lonelier than ever,
I was busy chatting with my friends.
I should have been there for her.
But I didn't know anything.
I didn't know what she was thinking about
or what was troubling her so much
that she wanted to die.
I was too immature.
You're a good person, Dr. Bong.
I never wanted to know about such things.
Sorry?
I hated her.
I didn't want to forgive my mother
for leaving me behind when I was so young.
At least
that's how I felt back then.
What about now?
Now I just…
miss her.
BONG'S ANIMAL HOSPITAL
You should go inside.
After you leave.
You have to stare harder
if you want to burn a hole into his head.
How much did you see?
"After you leave."
About that much.
Are you out of your mind?
-That guy--
-Are you sure it's him?
I just don't think it's him.
We could consider that he may be psychic,
but he might not be the serial killer.
But the only explanation
is that the killer is psychic.
He's just too soft-hearted and nice
to be the killer.
Gwang-sik got hurt
while he was with Kim Seon-woo.
Gwang-sik…
He got hurt?
Why would you word it like that
and scare me?
Technically speaking,
Gwang-sik hurt himself.
It wasn't because of Seon-woo.
Whatever.
Gwang-sik still lost his power.
Do you want one?
No, thank you.
What if Seon-woo offered it?
I'd drink it.
Jeez.
Let me ask you something.
Do you really think
Kim Seon-woo isn't the killer?
I'm not 100% sure,
but maybe about 51% sure?
Why such a random number?
I'm still leaning toward trusting him.
On what grounds?
Serial killers are usually psychopaths.
But Seon-woo knows
how to empathize with people.
That's ridiculous.
I guess you wouldn't know
since you're the left-brain type
with psychopathic tendencies.
I'm very good at empathizing with people.
Sure you are.
Let's say I texted you,
"I had a drink by the breakwater
because I was feeling down."
How would you reply?
"It's dangerous to drink there.
You could have fallen in."
How about this?
"I went to my mom's grave today."
"Where's her grave?"
See? It's impossible to talk to you.
You have zero ability
to empathize with people.
Fine, let's do this.
Give me one more.
This is the last one.
"I want to know
why my mom committed suicide."
What are you doing?
I'm comforting you.
How is this comforting?
This is how you do it.
Like this.
See?
This is how you comfort someone.
MUJIN POLICE STATION
What are you doing here?
Were you waiting for me?
What's with your face?
My father gave that to you, didn't he?
You already know the answer.
Father thinks
Mi-ok didn't kill herself.
But to be honest, I'm not sure.
I've spent the past 17 years
thinking she killed herself.
But all of a sudden, she didn't?
It's confusing.
Here.
Wait in the car. I'll be right back.
Reinvestigate the places where
Park Seung-gil and Lee Ji-suk were killed
and where the streamer's body was dumped.
See if we missed anything.
But we already searched thoroughly.
Then search even more thoroughly!
A piece of fabric, a single lint.
Anything could be linked to the murders!
-Captain, I have something else--
-Be quiet!
When forensic science fails us,
we have to rely on legwork.
So charismatic.
Won Jong-muk.
Where's Won Jong-muk?
If we follow that data,
we'll find out what Mi-ok did,
who she met, what she found out,
and
why she died.
-Here, look at this.
-Okay.
-From here to there, right?
-Yeah.
This was the most valuable property
during Mujin's redevelopment wave.
Assemblyman Yoon Deok-hyeon
had bought all this land
for 100,000 won per pyeong
right before the redevelopment wave.
And when rumors spread about
Mujin becoming a special tourist zone,
he sold it all at a premium,
for two million won per pyeong.
If you look here, that's when your sister
started writing these articles.
I remember this.
Mi-ok told me to never let Father
buy any of these lands.
In the end, Mujin wasn't even considered
for a special tourist zone,
and the redevelopment plan
went down the drain.
As a result, the land prices
plummeted to the ground.
If you look over here,
your sister was the only person
who wrote articles
in favor of the victims back then.
And the people over here…
They were probably the people
she spent the most time with back then.
That's right.
I brought her a change of clothes
a few times.
She was practically living
with these people.
So where should we begin?
We should look for these people.
Thanks.
They couldn't have sold
those useless pieces of land,
so they probably still own them.
-What in the world…
-What's wrong?
One person owns all the land.
-Let me see.
-Here.
Oh, my gosh.
CHA JU-MAN
They all belong to Ju-man.
Right.
MAY YOU REST IN PEACE
FROM CHA JU-MAN
HERE LIES JUNG MI-OK
It's been a while
since I visited Mi-ok.
Did you leave those here?
I'm sorry.
I thought it was someone else.
I can't see well these days.
So you can't see well?
You should take good care of your eyes.
So that's why you took the donor list
from my campaign office.
Of course.
You only took it
because you couldn't see well.
And here I was thinking
you had ulterior motives.
Yes.
And that's why you had
Ye-bun return it the next day.
Now I get it.
I almost misunderstood you.
I'm glad we cleared up
that misunderstanding.
You should head home now.
No, I'm going to stay a little longer.
Come on now.
Just let me take you home.
It must've been exhausting coming here.
I parked my car way too far away.
We're almost there, sir.
-Keep going.
-Okay.
How did all this land become Ju-man's?
There's only one person
who hasn't sold his land.
Maybe we'll find out if we talk to him.
Hello?
Does Kim Seon-woo
have connections to Mujin?
What? That's a random question.
I heard his mom was from Mujin.
Has he ever lived in Mujin before?
He told me
this was his first time in Mujin.
I can't believe him.
Why?
Let me warn you one more time.
Don't meet with him ever again.
All right.
Bong Ye-bun.
Please don't.
So how did all that land
come to belong to Assemblyman Cha?
I had been told
the land was going to be redeveloped,
so I paid two million won for it.
But then the price dropped
to 200,000 won instead.
I invested all the money I had saved up
and even took out loans
in the hopes of the redevelopment.
So even if I sold the land then,
I would still have been left in debt.
With the land price plummeting,
I got dragged into the gutter.
Who would sell their land
when it can't even pay off their debts?
That's when Cha Ju-man
showed up out of the blue.
He said it'd be better to get out of debt
if I was going to be homeless anyway.
And then he started buying all the land
for 500,000 won per pyeong.
So why didn't you sell yours?
Come on.
How could I sell the land to that bastard?
He's the one who sweet-talked everyone
into buying the land,
acting as Assemblyman Yoon's minion.
Cha Ju-man was the one who told people
they'd hit the jackpot
once the land was redeveloped.
Do you know of a journalist
named Jung Mi-ok?
-This is the journalist, Ms. Jung.
-Yes.
She stood by our side until the end
and wrote articles for us too.
Is there anything else
you remember about her?
I only crossed paths with her a few times.
Right. Look.
She was the chairperson
of the emergency committee at the time.
She and Ms. Jung were like sisters.
Where is she now?
She turned out to be a bad one too.
-What?
-The word on the street is
she took a ton of money as compensation
and ran away to Seoul.
-To Seoul?
-Yes, to Seoul.
-See you.
-Thank you. It's gotten so much better.
-Have a nice day.
-Take care.
Ye-bun.
Hello, Mr. Cha.
We ran into each other
at your mom's grave.
Take care, Dr. Jung.
Ye-bun.
Could you hold me?
Grandpa.
All right. Careful.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I told you I could go by myself.
How are you so stubborn?
I take after Mi-ok, of course.
We're sisters.
What are you, a magnet?
Why are you clinging to me?
We've been apart for so long.
We need to use every opportunity
to be close.
Goodness.
Stop it.
I know you love it.
My windows aren't even tinted.
This seems to be it.
Are you sure it's here?
Yes, I'm sure.
Can I help you?
Isn't anyone living here?
The old lady went on a trip
with the senior citizens' center.
She's coming back tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yes. Why don't you come back tomorrow?
Okay.
What a nice lady.
Listen.
I'm going to spend the night here
and investigate some more.
You should start heading back now.
I'm not going back by myself.
Let me stay here too.
What are you talking about?
There are tons of
hotels and motels in Seoul.
Hyeon-ok!
Yeah?
For goodness' sake.
HOTEL GUNG J
Maybe we should have rented two rooms.
What for?
That would be a waste of money.
We just need to sleep here.
Are you going to wash up first?
No.
You go first.
Well…
Sleep tight then, okay?
What are you doing?
Would you rather sleep on the floor?
We can both sleep on the bed.
No, that's not right.
What's not right about it?
You're over 50. Don't be shy.
Still…
That's just not right. Good night.
Fine. I'm going to sleep down there too.
Then you sleep on the floor.
I'll sleep on the bed.
Me too.
I'm going to sleep up here too.
-Come on, go down.
-No, I'm not going to.
Go down, for Pete's sake.
-Go!
-Jong-muk.
-Oh, my!
-Oh, no.
You sleep on the floor. It'll be comfy.
What are you doing?
Take it off. Hey!
Take it off right now.
Are you insane?
Goodness gracious!
I had to do it so we could sleep
on the same bed together.
You're driving me nuts.
Jeez.
You must be so tired.
Let's go to sleep.
Man…
Jong-muk.
What's that noise?
I don't know.
Hyeon-ok!
The building's on fire!
What do we do?
For God's sake!
Why did you have to throw the key away?
You could have just slept on the bed
with me from the beginning!
Jong-muk.
It's over for me.
Save yourself.
Are you crazy?
I'm not leaving without you!
Don't clutch it that tight. It hurts!
Are these all the guests?
Some are still in there.
I think someone's coming out.
Jong-muk, this way!
Jong-muk.
Help!
What are you looking at?
All right…
Hurry up and cut this off him.
Do you happen to know
a student named Kim Seon-woo?
He graduated from here.
You mean Seon-woo?
Why are you asking about him?
He's a close friend of mine,
but I lost touch with him a few years ago.
I'm worried about him.
He recently dropped out of grad school.
Is that so?
Do you know why he dropped out?
I'm not sure.
The professor would know more than I do.
Our professor was very fond of him.
That's why he was a TA for so long.
The professor even helped him
with his thesis
and wrote him
recommendation letters too, but…
But?
He just dropped out all of a sudden.
Could you tell me when exactly he quit?
Let me think.
Oh, right. Just a moment.
There it is.
Seon-woo put these up
and quit school soon after.
That was in 2019, so 3 years ago.
LECTURE WITH ASSEMBLYMAN CHA JU-MAN
RETURNING TO FARMING AND RURAL AREAS
I see Assemblyman Cha Ju-man was here.
You mean the poster?
The students weren't interested,
but Seon-woo insisted on putting it up.
I see.
Do you know what the lecture was about?
You can probably watch it online.
Farming areas lack young energy right now.
The president of Mujin's
Youth Association is 60 years old.
The reason young people
don't move to farming areas
is because there are no jobs.
More specifically,
there are no jobs for young people.
But are jobs enough
to attract young people?
No.
Unless they want to work all the time.
They want to have fun after work.
Young people flock to entertainment
and convenience store areas.
Entertainment is as important as jobs.
Then what should we do?
We have to create jobs
and sources of entertainment
and then seduce them.
That's why we started…
THE SECOND ANNUAL PRAWN FESTIVAL
…the Mujin Prawn Festival.
Mujin has a population of 30,000,
and the festival attracts 50,000 visitors.
The festival will cause
more infrastructure
and residential spaces to be built.
Abandoned land will turn into
restaurants, malls, and even bars
where you can meet attractive strangers.
I see you like the last one a lot.
This is how we'll convince young people
to move to the rural areas.
In other words, developing the area
is how you attract young people there.
-This is it.
-Here?
Who is it?
Ma'am, you're home today.
-Hello.
Can I help you?
We're looking for someone.
A woman named Lee Eun-suk.
I heard she lived here
around ten years ago.
You mean the woman with her son?
Do you remember her?
Of course.
She rented the room across from us
for a long time.
She lived a tough life.
We heard she received
a ton of money as compensation in Mujin
and returned to Seoul rich.
Rich? Nonsense.
She got kicked out penniless.
When she arrived here,
her cheeks were all sunken
as if she'd been to hell and back.
Her son must have starved too.
The little thing basically scarfed down
the meal I made for him.
Do you know where she is now?
I wish I knew.
She asked me to watch her son
for a few days,
and that was it.
She never came back for her son.
I don't even know if she's dead or alive.
I kept him for about a year,
but I couldn't take care of him anymore,
so I sent him to a children's home.
I'll develop Mujin
so that young people can move there.
I'll turn it into a special tourist zone
so that young people can thrive there.
Just have faith in me and move to…
It's all right.
Not everyone would agree with me.
Making sure that Mujin can embrace
even people like him
is my dream.
BEHIND YOUR TOUCH
Request backup and come to
Assemblyman Cha's office with the captain.
Hurry!
I was there to kill Cha Ju-man.
He deserves to suffer
the wrath of the gods.
Why are you packing all of a sudden?
-Jang-yeol. He disappeared.
-What?
I hear you've been spending a lot of time
with Detective Moon.
If you're that suspicious of him,
just touch him.
A brief touch won't work.
-Hello, Assemblyman Cha!
-So all you need
is enough time to touch him?
Mom didn't kill herself, did she?
And you think Mr. Cha
had something to do with it.
I'll be the one to take care of it,
and I'll be the one to tie everything up.
Breaking news.
…was found dead.
The murder weapon
is the same as the other murders.
Everything points to him.
-No visitors allowed.
-Get out of my way.
Why won't anyone tell me anything?
Subtitle translation by: Hyun-soo Cho