MkvDrama
[1 month earlier]
I'm Queen, Pitinan Teerakietsakul.
My name means
"a lady who enjoys her possessions."
Mom, I miss you.
But I don't think you miss me
or even hear me.
I'm sorry for always letting you down.
Nonetheless, thank you
for the house and the money.
I promise you that I'll spend it wisely.
I guess this is what it feels like
to be wealthy but lonely.
♫Caught your eyes,
now I'm feeling weak inside♫
♫Your glance broke my guard,
no place to hide♫
♫Though I tried, keep it cool,
but it shakes my soul♫
♫Lost myself in the dark,
but found the truth♫
♫I'm losing my control,
I've got to let it go♫
♫You're keeping me alive,
I just cannot hide♫
♫Even if it's wrong, alright♫
"If you're lonely and want someone
by your side, as a partner or a friend,
to read books or stargaze with,
feel free to reach out to me.
Payment by the hour
or by the day works for me."
The ID is...
Huh?!
This kind of gig?
How uninteresting.
Whoa.
The client's house
sure looks nice to live in.
Good morning.
- Uh...
- Good morning.
You're Ms. Queen, right?
Yes, I am.
No need for such formality.
You can just call me "Queen,"
as we're probably around the same age.
Understood, Ms.
Sorry...
Understood, Queen.
You're such a tease,
making jokes
the moment we know each other.
Actually, I'm an introvert,
but I got blown away by your smile.
That's great. I like that.
I mean, I like quiet people
who love making jokes.
- Alright, let's head inside.
- Understood.
This way.
- Hey, Ms.
- Oh!
Are you okay?
Sorry, I got a bit distracted
by my own thoughts.
Uh...
Is there anything wrong?
You're living alone, Queen?
Mm.
Yes, I am usually,
but sometimes, Maew,
the housemaid, would be here.
You're living by yourself...
Mm.
You used the app
because you felt lonely, right?
Well, it goes without saying.
My loneliness brought you here.
By the way, you haven't specified
whether to pay me by the day or hour.
I'll pay you by the day if you don't mind.
Let me know if there are any extra charges
not mentioned in the app.
Absolutely.
I'm pleased to be of service.
It's a pleasure.
By the way, how do you like the service?
Do you want me to be your personal chef,
cooking up your lunch?
How does that sound?
Mm...
That does sound great.
However,
I prefer a partner who cooks for me.
At your service.
Your spaghetti is ready.
You can cook Western food?
Of course, I do.
I love cooking for myself.
What if it tastes bad?
I guess you might
have to order a takeout.
You can also have me instead.
Well?
Hm?
You look tough.
It'd be too hard to chew.
Ms. Queen!
We've talked about this!
We're a couple, so don't say "Ms."
What would you like me to call you, then?
Um...
How about "Babe?"
Yes, Babe.
The spaghetti's getting cold.
Let's give it a go
and see if it's delicious.
How is it?
It's tasty!
It's on my lips?
Mm.
No, let me do it for you.
No, I'll do it myself.
I know that you can do it yourself,
but, just for today, can I do it for you?
Excuse me, Ms. Queen...
Excuse me, Babe.
You're such a messy eater.
There you go.
Now, enjoy your spaghetti.
Dig in!
Why? It's not tasty?
It is tasty!
But it's kinda awkward
having someone stare at me while eating.
You look cute while you're eating.
Can't I just have this moment?
Wanna join me?
I've had it so many times already,
so please, enjoy.
Are my lips still a mess?
Nom!
Am I a little girl to you?
I'm not a kid, you know?
Thank you.
Mm.
What's the matter?
Are you sleepy?
Here.
Please, rest your head on me.
Queen.
- Queen.
- Hm?
Wake up.
I've gotta go.
Can't you stay just a bit longer?
I can't. I have other clients to tend to.
How much is the payment?
I'll double it.
No, I actually can't.
This client has already
paid me in advance.
Fine.
Why?
You can't live without me?
It's just that I'm bored.
By the way,
when will you be available again?
This Wednesday.
I'll sort it out just for you.
What? Wednesday?
You're not available tomorrow?
At least let me stay with you
for a couple of hours.
You want to see me?
Nope!
I was just asking.
Aww...
I'm free from noon to 2 P.M. tomorrow.
I was about to put your name
in that time slot...
Yes, please!
Well...
I'm too lazy to cook for myself.
Mm...
Can you please cook for me like today?
Absolutely!
You're mine for tomorrow, okay?
See you at noon.
Understood, my dear client.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Text me when you're home.
Is this against
the terms of service, though?
It's not,
but that's outside my working hours.
Aww, it's nothing much, though.
Please?
Mm... What should I say?
Sure, I guess.
I'll keep you posted
the moment I'm home.
Hopefully, I've alleviated your loneliness.
A lot of tips
would be greatly appreciated, too.
I'm kidding.
I've gotta go now.
Bye-bye.
I've just realized that
having someone to do simple things with
can make the world feel so much livelier.
What's wrong with me?
Why is my heart racing?
"A friend for rent."
"I can be your conversation partner,
travel buddy, or confidant.
I'm available 24/7."
Here we go.
I'm going with her, then.
"Are you available tonight?"
"I am. I actually just got ghosted."
"Let's meet up at this location."
"Sure."
Hi.
You're Bam, right?
Yes, I am.
I'm Queen.
Got it.
Uh...
You look more beautiful in person.
Okay.
By the way, what kind of vibes
are you looking for, Ms. Queen?
Do you want me to be your friend
or your partner?
Be my partner, please.
Alright...
I don't do overnight stays, though.
That's fine.
Right.
Do you have other places
to go to after this?
No, actually.
Do you want to hang out
with me after this?
I actually don't mind if you want me to.
Do you mind, though?
But you said no overnight stays.
I'm not saying that I'm going to.
Right.
We can just go to other places, right?
Watch your step.
That's one.
One more.
Okay, nicely done.
Be careful, okay?
Whoa! Whoa!!
Be careful.
Keep going.
Okay.
There you go.
Bam.
Okay.
Who's treating who, really?
Not only do I have to pay you,
but also take care of you?
Bam?
Hey...
Bam! Don't throw up just yet!
You can't throw up here.
Please go to the bathroom.
Let's head to the bathroom.
Please stand up.
Don't throw up, okay?
Hang in there.
Oh, hang in there, Bam.
Okay! We're here!
There you go.
Don't mess up my bathroom, okay?
Okay!
Good heavens.
Bam!
Be careful.
Gently, okay?
Onto the couch, you go.
You're kinda funny, actually.
Tonight, I guess I'm no longer lonely.
You sure gave me a headache.
What?! Where am I?
Good morning.
- Uh...
- You're finally awake.
Did you have a good sleep?
You're Ms. Queen.
I'm supposed to be happy
that you still remember
my name, aren't I?
Of course, I still got your name.
How did I end up here?
My memories were kinda blurry.
You didn't remember anything?
Did I accidentally do
something horrible to you?
I usually don't drink,
so I lost control of myself.
I don't mind, actually.
Taking care of a drunk person
is better than being alone.
Right.
By the way, I've already made my payment.
- Oh, thank you.
- No problem.
Wait! It's 11 A.M. already?
Ms. Queen, I've gotta take my leave.
Wait! Don't you wanna
have breakfast with me?
I can't. I need to go to work.
I have a lot on my shoulders,
so I have to work hard.
Okay, then.
I'll call you for
our next session later, okay?
You still enjoy my service?
Well, I like it.
- It's an odd experience.
- Okay.
- You're into this kind of stuff?
- I guess.
Thank you for using my service,
but I've gotta get going now.
Thank you!
Bye-bye.
Is she alright?
Did you forget your phone?
It's here.
Oh...
Sea. You're here already?
It's before noon, though.
I got here early because I was worried
that my partner might go hungry.
So I wanna make you some tasty dishes.
But no, the truth is that I miss you.
With you being this sweet,
how many clients have
you drained their pockets?
I've never treated anyone like this.
What kind of dish are you making today?
What do you have in mind?
Thai food? Western food? Indian food?
Thai food, Western food,
or Indian food...
Let's go with any
that you think I'll enjoy.
I guess it's gonna be me, right?
I don't know. I've gotta go shower now.
I want the dish ready when I'm back.
Do you want me to help you
with the shower?
No need!
Ms. Queen,
I must've forgotten my phone
at your place.