(Please Tell Me So)
(He's my ideal type.)
(I like men with glasses on whenever they read books
He tied a bow with his hoodie string, Cute)
(I like men enjoying their sweets)
(The man with a scar and its history)
(Soft)
(The man who looks good with a cap)
(The man gulping his coffee)
This is on the house.
I didn't really mean to drink coffee today.
Then I'll make another drink for you.
I was just kidding.
Thank you.
Here's what you ordered.
Thank you, please visit us again.
Would you want me to light it for you?
Ah, alright.
My high school senior...
My high school senior used
to light cigarettes like that.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yes.
I was smoking secretly
during cleaning time.
It was not the same way, but.
He held two cigarettes on his mouth
and like this.
So I thought he was doing it in a really...
unique way.
Are you recalling…
your old love story…
because of me?
No.
Not at all.
I should've lit up with a lighter.
No...
Is your place this way?
Yes.
Ah, okay.
Need a ride?
Yes?
(Why aren't you updating your ideal types?)
(I'm with him now.)
Me?
Sorry?
I asked if it's me.
What is?
(Why aren't you updating your ideal types?)
(I'm with him now)
So you knew all along?
Mostly.
But why, why didn't you tell me?
I could ask you the same thing.
Why didn't you tell me that you like me?
How could I possibly tell you?
What about me?
I wanted to tell you
but you were talking
about your first love.
He's not my first love.
I think he was.
No!
My first love…
My first love is...
you...