September 14th.
Please book two rooms for me.
Today is Jiang Yue's birthday.
Hello.
Is the cake ready?
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Yue'er.
This is your mom's favorite necklace.
Keep it for me, okay?
[The painting in the necklace my mother left me]
[seems to have a similar totem.]
Mom.
Young Master, let's go home.
Take him away.
Yes.
Young Master, be good. Let's go.
Mom.
District 45 has always been isolated.
I'm worried
even if you send the young master in person,
they won't cooperate with us.
How did it go?
Very well.
Good.
You can go now.
Here is a guest list.
Only by sharing this list can we protect ourselves.
Who is the trading partner today?
Your task
is to ensure that each mission is completed successfully.
Don't ask what you shouldn't ask.
It's the anniversary of my mother's death.
Go to the grave with me.
You haven't been there for several years.
I don't have time today.
I'll fly to Duke County tomorrow morning.
Do you remember what she looks like?
You actually have the nerve to mention your mother to me.
Look how busy I am now.
If you could help me a bit,
would I be this busy?
Since you were a child,
you said you were not interested in the group's affairs,
and were determined to avenge your mother. Okay.
I thought you were a dutiful son.
But now?
Black Snow is still alive.
He is still eyeing us
covetously.
What have you done?
Your mother has been dead for 16 years.
16 years.
Tell me,
how are you going to meet your mother?
Get out.
Jiang Yue.
Jiang Yue, it's me.
[Sorry, the number you dialed is powered off.]
Qi Qi.
Uncle.
Why are you up so late?
Do you know where Jiang Yue went?
What do you need him for?
He didn't answer my calls
or reply to my messages.
It's nothing.
He'll come back when he should.
Uncle.
Today is his birthday.
He doesn't celebrate his birthday.
Why?
Have a good rest.
Mr. Gao,
why are you here?
I'm worried about the young master.
Do you know where Jiang Yue is?
Qingci Cemetery.
Cemetery?
Today
is also the death anniversary of his mother.
April 5th,
1977.
September 14th,
2009.
Mom,
it's been 16 years.
I'm tired,
but I won't give up.
I will find out
who
hurt you.
Jiang Yue.
Why don't you answer the phone?
Qi.
You'll make auntie sad like this.
How do you know I'm here?
I'm worried about you.
Let's go home, okay?
Go.
Come on.
Sit.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know today was...
I'll take it away now.
It's okay. I'll eat it tomorrow.
It won't be wasted.
I want to eat it.
Really?
Wait a minute.
Look.
Do you have a lighter?
Okay.
Now it's time to make a wish.
Let's welcome our little birthday star Jiang Yue to make a wish.
Make a wish.
I haven't thought of what to wish for.
Then I'll make one for you.
Wish Jiang Yue...
Three,
two,
one.
Let's cut the cake.
How should we cut it?