Jiang Yue,
Vice President of 3Z Group,
Jiang Changfa's delivery man,
I'm really looking forward to
how you're going to deal with
the chess game I've prepared for you.
Hiding here, huh?
What are you waiting for? Go!
You're looking for death!
I'll kill you!
Are you okay?
Don't bother.
Retreat, go.
This matter
should have been dealt with long ago.
It's my fault.
I apologize to you.
Let's go, I'll take you to fix the camera.
Let's go.
Don't bother.
You go.
This job was arranged by my father.
Do you think I'm happy to be a bodyguard?
Then he's the one who's meddlesome.
We are family now.
Family?
What kind of family are we?
Jiang Yue, I never considered you
and your father as my family.
Before you came,
I was doing just fine.
And if you hadn't intervened,
no one would have interfered with my life.
I would have been better than now.
Don't follow me anymore.
I also want to go home.
Qi,
what's wrong with you?
Are you hurt again?
It's nothing. I just fell on the road.
I told you
to let Jiang Yue drive you,
But you insisted on walking to school.
Now you've made yourself look so miserable.
Are you worried about me,
or worried that his new daughter
won't be under his control?
Qi,
don't worry.
I won't let him lose face.
I won't mention him to anyone.
Because he'll never be my dad.
Qi Qi,
I bought you a new camera.
Don't use the old one all the time.
This is the first camera my dad gave me.
Don't you know?
Yue'er,
Changfa asked you to take care of Qi Qi.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Never mind.
Dad, I want to take a picture of that.
OK.
Daddy, did I take a good picture?
Baby,
you will become
a hundred times,
a thousand times better photographer than me.
Daddy, I'm going to be six years old soon.
But I don't want to grow up.
Why?
When I grow up,
you will get old.
When you get old, you will leave me.
Dad, can you never leave me?
Okay.
I won't leave you.
Who is it?
It's me.
Open the door.
This CCD is already over a decade old.
Many of its parts are no longer produced.
Then,
do you have any other way?
Then you should tell me first
what's wrong with it.
It's this one.
This one is broken.
Help me find this camera accessory.
I found it.
In a watch shop in Luocheng.
Send me the location.
Young Master, it's so late.
It's over 300 kilometers away.
You're still up?
Why did you come back so late?
Parts.
Where did you find them?
What happened to you?
How did you get hurt?
Don't move.
It hurts.
You...
Why are you willing to help me?
Because I know this is very precious to you.
My mother left it to me when she died.
Does it look good?
It's really beautiful.
Then do it for your mom.
Don't get hurt anymore.
I've taken care of it at school for you.
No need.
I figured it out when my dad died.
There's no need
to waste time on useless people and things.
But
thank you
for making me feel important.
Will you come to the opening of the art exhibition
in a few days?
What exhibition?
3Z
Okay.
Jiang Yue
This is the first big gift
I prepared for you.