What is this?
Dark Web.
Dark Web?
Behind this encryption key
is a hidden
dark and bloody world.
Now, for Jiang Yue,
the most important thing is
to find this encryption key
and reveal the truth behind it
to the public.
What truth?
You're getting greedy.
Mr. Chu,
I really want to help him.
I won't drag him down.
You have to believe me.
Behind this encryption key
is the truth about Jiang Yue's mother's death.
On the day of the shooting,
when Jiang Yue saw the totem
hidden in Andrew Bell's painting,
Jiang Yue's reaction
should be related to Aunt Xu's death.
Then the necklace Aunt Xu left for Jiang Yue,
could it be like Bell's painting,
leaving clues?
Jiang Yue has a necklace.
I suspect
there is important information in it.
Sir, did Master kill Gu Lan?
What do you mean?
He could kill, but he didn't.
Sir, let's get out of here first.
You go first.
My mother died 16 years ago.
You always told me
it was Black Snow that killed her.
Look me in the eye.
Is it true?
The human trade
will make you rich.
With money,
we can get rid of Black Snow.
Honey.
Kill her.
Long Hair, this is a crime.
You can't do this.
Long Hair.
Qingwan.
I'll tell the outside world
that you are seriously ill
and don't go out anymore.
I can't just watch you sink into the quagmire.
I hope to reveal the secret of the totem
to reveal the secret of the totem
and let you get out of it.
Jiang Yue,
you actually set me up.
Long Hair,
what are you doing here?
I want to ask you,
Qi's dad,
do you know something
about Lu Qingyuan's death?
Why do you think I know something?
How did the driver who hit him
get off the hook?
Lu Qingyuan died because of his own fault.
The driver is also a victim.
Isn't it obvious?
Go back.
Where are you going?
I'm on a business trip.
I've checked these photos.
There's no important information
except for this totem.
There are numbers.
Three.
How do you know?
Qi's eyes are
sensitive to colors.
Does this one have it?
No.
Stop.
Seven.
The password is 37.
The key is six digits.
Does she leave any other paintings?
No.
It's okay.
I'll go out for a while.
Qi Qi.
Give me the location of Jiang Changfa.
Jiang Yue.
Jiang Yue, what's wrong?
He's gone.
I didn't catch up with him.
He didn't even have the courage to see me one last time.
He didn't even give me an explanation.
Your blindness
was caused by me.
That shot
was because of me.
For these past dozen years,
I smuggled for him.
I helped him with everything that was under the table.
I just want to know
if he killed my mother.
It's okay if he did.
It's fine if he didn't.
But he just left.
I'm just a bad person,
an unforgivable sinner.
In my heart,
you are gentle,
considerate,
and kind.
You always try your best
to help others.
Without you,
my life would be colorless.
It's because of you
that my life is so colorful.
You made me who I am today.
Alright, go wash your face.
Look, there are numbers on it.
9152.
379152.
Let me try.
How's it going?
I finally know
why my mother
held the art exhibition on my birthday.
She wanted to expose
the group behind Jiang Changfa
and save those innocent people.
But she sacrificed her life.
This encryption key
is just a part of
the human trafficking.
But their agents
are all over Hongdu,
Nordic countries,
and even the world.
I'm just one person.
So,
you want to fulfill her last wish.
I do.
Of course, I do.
But I don't have the ability
to attract international attention.
If we alert them,
they will only intensify their efforts.
It's okay.
We'll face it together.
This is not something you should worry about.
Right now, you just need to think about
winning the award from abroad and coming back,
and then focusing on your studies.
What do you mean?
This card
contains my savings over the years.
The money is clean.