Lu Qi is actually talented
in photography.
No wonder Jiang Yue likes her.
Lu Qi.
Professor Chu.
Sit.
Put it here.
I've seen your work.
Do you also think it's evil?
Lu Qi,
you're special.
Your work is special too.
My work
is the scene
I saw
that day
when you took me to a near-death experience.
I was thinking
I'd thank you properly after I won the award.
Who knew
I didn't even make it through the initial selection.
This is quite normal.
They're just some ordinary folks,
yet they think they're the best in the industry.
Using their
limited knowledge
to set rigid rules.
You expect these people
to discover geniuses,
talents,
and even more so, the quirky talents.
I can introduce you to Professor Müller,
the master of surrealist photography.
Professor Müller.
I know him.
He will like you.
He can take you to the international stage
and show the world
your extraordinary talent.
Really? When?
Jiang Yue.
why are you here?
I told you
if you harass her again,
I'll kill you.
Mr. Chu, let's go.
You asked him to follow me, right?
I didn't ask him to follow you.
He found you during his mission
and informed me.
And
what if I asked him to follow you?
If he hadn't told me
what was going to happen between you and Chu Mo,
why were you so close just now?
I told you long ago
to stay away from him.
He's not a good guy,
and he's very dangerous.
Did I ever tell you
I don't want to
wander aimlessly anymore?
Mr. Chu is willing to recognize me.
He helped me.
He will introduce me to the international photography master,
Mr. Müller.
I have no reason to refuse him.
Let go of me.
I'll accompany you
on your way.
Jiang Yue, let go of me.
Hello.
Mr. Chu.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Lu Qi,
I really like the work "Tearing".
I can't bear to see it
in a dark corner.
So I took the liberty
to send it to Müller.
What did he say?
In the 1980s,
Müller made a series of promotional videos
for a jewelry brand.
That series of promotional videos
changed people's views
on luxury at the time.
The moment he saw your photo,
his impression of Hongdu Photography
changed.
He told me
he really liked it,
as if he saw his younger self.
Really?
Would Professor Chu lie to you?
Lu Qi,
Mr. Müller wants to meet you.
When do you have time?
I can take you abroad to meet him.
I...
Your brother must be worried about you.
You can tell him
that I can take you abroad.
Jiang Yue,
are you going to find Mr. Chu Mo?
[Jiang Yue,]
[the moment I saw you,]
[I knew you were dark inside.]
[But I didn't expect]
[that it was not just dark,]
[but also soul-stirring,]
[and mind-blowing evil.]
Senior Gao,
have you seen Jiang Yue?
I can't get through to him.
Master wouldn't ignore your calls
for no reason.
Has something happened between you?
What could possibly happen between us?
Miss Lu Qi,
if I may be so bold,
before you came into this family,
Master and Mr. Lu had no conflicts,
and no one ever found their weakness
and humiliated them repeatedly.
What do you mean?
Young Master's intuition is rarely wrong.
Since he suspects that Chu Mo is the Butterfly,
Butterfly?
You don't know?
Butterfly,
the highest-valued assassin on the dark web.
As long as he appears,
it means death and bloodshed.
At first, his target was Young Master.
But he found
it's hard to find a breakthrough with the young master,
so he frequently
appeared in your life.
Because he knows the young master values you.
A person
will not approach another person
without a reason.
Chumo is more suspicious.
At the 100th anniversary of Zhangyi College,
you didn't go to the lecture,
But you came to our school.
We're just an ordinary high school.
Because of you.
So what's your purpose of contacting Qi?
I like her, just like you.
It seems like a joke,
but actually,
it's really because of me.
Miss Lu Qi,
I don't hope...
But as far as I can see,
you have become the blade
to hurt the young master and destroy 3Z.
Professor Chu,
are you free now?
Okay, I'll see you later.
You're still in contact with him?
I know what I'm doing.
I'll see you later, Senior Assistant Gao.
Thank you.
If we can lure Chu Mo out,
we can find Jiang Yue
and stop him
from making a big mistake.
Is this mine?
Yes.
Thank you.
Didn't your brother come with you?
I sent him a message.
He'll be here in a while.
Mr. Chu,
I'm happy that Mr. Müller likes me.
And I'm also happy that you're willing to help me.
But after careful consideration,
I think it's too hasty.
I can't repay such a big favor.
Thank you for helping me.
I'll always remember it.
Jiang Yue,
what did you give her
to make her give up on Müller?
Do you know what you're talking about?
Yes.
That's good.
You two have a nice chat.
I'll be going.
Thanks for the coffee.
Well,
Mr. Chu,
he didn't do anything to hurt me,
but I shouldn't have
ignored your feelings.
My life is already like this.
I don't want your dream to be shattered.
I'll do my best
to help you become who you want to be.
Sir, it's okay to have someone with physical strength.
I'm just afraid of emergencies.
You can't deliver without Jiang Yue, right?
How about I cover for you
and go with him?
Sir,
it takes at least 40 minutes
to get to the port from here.
We need to make a decision.
Otherwise, 3Z's reputation will be affected.
Listen,
I can
let you display Lu Qi's work,
and I can also
hand over the entire Cloud Court
to you to manage.
Hurry up and deliver the goods.
If you're late, you'll get nothing.
Be good,
don't wander off.
Okay, mom.
I'm off.
Bye.
Master,
the theme exhibition
is all works from famous masters.
The product layout has been agreed.
There's no good place to display
Miss Lu Qi's works.
You need Mr. Lu's permission to change it.
Don't worry about
Lu Qi's business.
Okay.