Shh.
You're back.
I heard you didn't eat.
I'm not hungry.
You still need to eat.
You need nutrients now.
Lie down.
I'll get you something to eat.
No.
I don't want to eat.
Eat a little.
I'm not hungry.
Drink a little.
I think you are hungry.
Is it good?
Master
Mr. Shen asked you to go back with me.
It's too late.
I have to stay with Qi.
He wants to see me.
Let him come himself.
Master
Shen Yu
Yes.
Yellow.
Cyan.
Red.
Black.
Orange.
Cyan and green
are a little hard to distinguish.
It doesn't matter.
At present, the recovery is still okay.
I can still see clearly, right?
Yes.
I can't guarantee this to you.
But this is the most optimistic result.
I'm satisfied as long as there is hope.
The family should also be positive.
The patient is in a better mood than you.
Thank you.
Jiang Yue
I saw it that day.
it was Chu Mo who fired the gun.
I didn't listen to you
when you warned me.
I was not careful enough.
I'm sorry.
I dislike Chu Mo.
But he didn't fire the gun.
Who did?
You know?
No matter who it is,
it's not your fault.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Let's go out for a walk.
You've been with me for so many days.
Is everything okay with uncle?
It's okay.
I know why you
have to obey him.
I'm okay.
Don't give him
the chance to hurt you because of me.
You once asked me
how I want to live my life.
Yes.
I thought about it.
I devoted everything I had before
to a lie.
That lie is like a gun
pointing at my heart.
My fate
is in the hands of a gun holder
who doesn't love me.
But after I met you,
I figured it out.
I won't allow anyone in this world
to hurt you,
and no one will hurt me.
If I have to choose,
I'd rather the person who hurts me is you.
Changfa,
I'm so worried about Qi.
Just let me go.
What can you do here?
Wait at home.
What did you say?
Miss is alone.
So, Master...
Call ASO here.
Qi Qi, Qi Qi.
Qi Qi.
The medicine the doctor sent
was switched.
I'll call for help.
No need.
There's no time.
Contact the dock
and prepare for the reception.
Yes.
Master, go now.
Master.
Sorry.
Go.