I'm getting married.
Mom. Auntie Mi Ju is going to get married.
With whom? When?
You don't mean to say right now,
but that you'll get married someday
with some guy, right?
No. I want to get married right away.
Did you borrow money from someone...
and agree to get married instead?
No.
You left home to work.
Why are you suddenly getting married?
Did you get in trouble with someone?
No. They said it wasn't trouble.
Talk to us, then.
You must've found a guy
if you want to get married.
Who is it?
Jeong Woo Sang.
What? Who's Jeong Woo Sang?
Yes. Who's Jeong Woo Sang?
It can't be the actor Jeong Woo Sang.
It is the actor Jeong Woo Sang.
"I Lost My Memory but I Want Revenge."
He's the male lead.
My gosh.
Are you talking about...
an imaginary wedding you do on your own?
No.
Then did a lookalike seduce you saying...
he was Jeong Woo Sang...
No.
The woman in the news
he was at the hotel with.
It was me.
What?
Wait.
(Top Star J with Mysterious Woman)
No way.
Why would Jeong Woo Sang
the actor date you?
Hey. Is Jeong Woo Sang famous?
He's really famous.
Auntie. Did you party with him all night?
Why didn't you invite us?
Let me see your phone.
(Top Star J with Mysterious Woman)
What is this?
Is it you in this embarrassing state?
You two, go to your rooms.
Dong Won. Take Ji Hyun to Tae Ri's.
I'm not finished eating yet.
Take this upstairs with you.
Go now!
Let's eat.
Do you think...
we're missing a main dish?
No. It's okay.
Is it?
Who is it?
It's Dong Won and Ji Hyun.
It's unlocked. Come in.
Hey. What's this?
It's kimchi jjigae.
We were to bring it up here.
It looks delicious.
But it's too much.
Can we eat with you, then?
You haven't eaten?
Okay, then. We can share the jjigae.
- Sit down.
- Okay.
What?
So you want us two...
to find someone
to pretend to be our husbands...
and bring them to the wedding
and sit with us as if we're family?
What are you thinking?
I can't tell her now
that everything was a lie.
Because you don't want to become a liar,
you want to turn...
our whole family into frauds?
Don't think of it as fraud.
Call it a sweet real-life play...
we're putting on to put Ms. Oh at ease.
Hey!
How can you say that?
If the truth comes out later on,
we'll end up in handcuffs.
Do you want to get locked up again?
That would happen if I did this
to dupe my future husband.
But this was Woo Sang's idea.
I only added some details.
Do you want to go to such lengths
just to get married?
Yes. Totally.
Why did you...
come upstairs with the whole pot
instead of eating downstairs?
We got thrown out mid-meal.
Why?
Our youngest auntie said
she'd get married.
Why would you get thrown out
if she wants to get married?
I don't know. She's in trouble.
I see.
Okay. Let's all eat.
To be honest,
neither of you was a great deal of help.
Can't you do this for me?
Let's be frank.
None of us turned out great.
I want to marry well at least
and live happily.
I'll spoil Mom since you can't.
Neither of you
have the time or money to do so.
You have a way of
worsening your punishment.
Marrying well and being happy.
Do you think you'll get that
by marrying Jeong Woo Sung?
It's Jeong Woo Sang, not Jeong Woo Sung.
It's the same thing.
It's not the same thing.
Woo Sang is way more handsome.
I'll marry him and live happily.
I really don't want to end up
like either of you.
- What did you say?
- Can you not hit me?
You deserve a beating.
You evil witch.
You don't need to bring a guy.
Just tell people...
Dad is abroad and living just fine.
To be honest,
if you three were to
sit around a table at the wedding,
it would be embarrassing.
You can't just say what you want.
- Mom.
- Mom, don't.
Must you hurt us so deeply?
How happy do you think you'll be...
if you get married like this?
Let go of me.
Forget it, you brat.
You evil thing. Come here.
You're the worst I've ever seen.
Get back here.
My goodness.
Hey. Let's talk.
Since Mom is here, let's go out...
You're all out here?
I heard you're getting married.
Congratulations.
Are you going somewhere, Mr. Kim?
The kids are feeling restless,
so we'll walk around the block.
Would it be okay
for us to have a meeting...
at your place upstairs?
- What?
- For a bit while you're out.
Jin Ju.
Do you mind?
We can't fight freely because Mom is home.
And we're too embarrassed to go to a cafe.
Okay, then. Go ahead.
Behind me, you can see the work
done by average people.
It's quite easy...
Did something good happen?
Why are you laughing?
I should do as Mom says
when it comes to dating.
How did you feel when Mom
showed up at your doorstep?
Don't be silly.
Do you know why my eyesight is so poor?
It's because I was struck
by your mom's dazzling beauty.
What? That's so corny.
I can't believe you said that, honey.
I'm home.
You're late.
Did you have dinner?
Yes. I'll go upstairs.
Why is she in a bad mood?
I'm not used to you being like this.
Why do you suddenly...
care so much about Seon Ju and I?
- What?
- Are you worried our tracks will cross?
Why would you worry?
It's unbelievable.
He could never talk back at me,
so how could he and Seon Ju...
Who is it?
Are you in a bad mood?
Why are you so on edge?
How could I be in a good mood?
So Woo and Seon Ju
are taking turns aggravating me.
Those two...
I'm sick of saying this,
but Mom went through a lot
to raise us three.
We feel this bad about it.
How do you think Mom feels?
How could you ask us to put on a show?
Do you want to get married that badly?
Why? Are you possessed by a ghost
that died a virgin?
I used to wonder...
if I was adopted or something.
What's she on about?
Mi Ju.
Think about it.
If you were adopted, would we have...
kept you around
after all the trouble you caused?
Mom would've kicked you out long ago.
Exactly.
Would she have scolded us three
exactly the same?
When you were the troublemaker?
We got chewed out way more.
That's what I used to think. At one time.
You two were smart
and got all the attention.
No one cared what I did.
But recently I learned
what it was like to be loved.
It was like I was special to someone.
Don't we love you?
You didn't. Not much anyway.
Especially you, Jin Ju.
Seon Ju at least brought me gimbap
when I was locked up.
It was the worst time in my life
and you didn't even visit.
Pay for all the food I cooked for you.
Forget that. Let's hear the truth.
Does Jeong Woo Sang love you lots?
Yes. And he's good-looking.
Do good looks put food on the table?
Maybe not,
but it makes it easier to digest food.
You worry about digestion?
No, but...
I really want to marry him.
If you want to marry him,
pull off the fraud on your own.
Why drag us all into it?
If you're that ashamed of us,
none of us will be there.
I'd have done it on my own if I could.
Ms. Oh says the only thing she cares about
is that I'm from a normal, happy family.
How can I appear to be normal and happy
if none of you are there?
Mi Ju. Enough with the nonsense.
Come clean to her right now.
If she objects, break things off.
Or find people
to pretend to be your sisters...
and seat a whole family of fakes!
Are you...
Yes.
I'm pregnant.
Are you sure?
I used a pregnancy test
and it was positive.
- Oh, save me.
- I used two and...
Get up, Seon Ju.
I need a drink.
- My gosh.
- Me too.
Hi. Is the meeting over?
Dong Won. Don't wait up for us.
You too, Ji Hyun.
- Watch your step.
- Take the snacks.
Ji Hyun, you too.
See you.
Nam Jin. Join me for a drink.
I'm tired.
Show some appreciation for my effort.
Goodness.
You're stressed out, aren't you?
Drink up.
Sang Ah is not divorced yet,
and Seon Ju is up in your face at work.
And Sang Ah's not-yet-ex.
Her future ex lives upstairs from Seon Ju,
and they seem to be having fun.
That's what you're stressed about.
- No.
- Nam Jin.
Shall I buy a talisman
that'll get rid of Sang Ah's husband?
Don't do that.
Good night.
Goodness.
There's no way it's easy dating a woman
who's not yet divorced.
I should meet her husband soon.
The witch.
What should we do with her?
What can we do?
As a boy's mom and a future mom-in-law,
I can't take part in
a fraudulent marriage.
That's right.
I'm a girl's mom and I feel the same.
How could she?
Do you remember what she said?
She said we were no help to her.
She doesn't want to be like us.
My own sister said that to my face.
I'm still in shock.
Why would you be so shocked?
To be honest, like she said,
we don't have anything
to show for ourselves.
Why don't we?
You graduated from
a prestigious university.
So what if I did?
Ever heard of the term
"intellectual loser?"
You might be a loser,
but at least you're an intellectual one.
And I have a decent job now.
We can be proud of ourselves.
Your decent job.
Your ex's mistress' dad's company?
Darn it.
Goodness.
- My glass is empty.
- My gosh.
Here you are.
Why are you here?
I just came looking. Can I join you?
- Yes, take a seat.
- Thanks.
When I saw you...
leave home earlier,
I noticed you looked upset.
Is something wrong?
Mr. Kim.
Could you be honest about something?
- What?
- Objectively speaking,
are we an embarrassment?
- What?
- If we happened to be...
your own family,
would you be ashamed to be seen with us?
- Why would you say that?
- Jin Ju.
Of course not.
Apparently, that's us.
I should've had a husband
or done something with my life.
It's neither.
What does she mean?
She asked you to bring
fake husbands to the wedding?
I'm so flabbergasted
that I can't even get drunk.
How great is the guy
that she'd demand that?
I don't know.
What should we do with her?
We can't blame just her.
She said it was the guy's idea.
The fool who wants to hoodwink his mom...
and the girl who went along with it
and asked her sisters to lie.
They're perfect for each other.
But...
since she's pregnant,
you might have to do as she asks.
But I also think you shouldn't
take part in something like that.
Are you playing a neutral politician?
What?
No. What I mean is...
Jeon Ji Heon, Kim Tae Hwi, Son Ae Jin.
Just you wait.
Pi Mi Ju will be your equal one day.
What are you grinning about?
- What?
- Are you that pleased?
No.
As if you're not pleased.
This is why sons are useless.
Pretend you're gaining a daughter.
I might need you to move out.
How am I to watch this
for the rest of my life?
Darn you.
I know you don't mean that.
You're such an idiot.
What are you two doing?
Tae Sang. Put him in his place.
Sit down.
Goodness.
Woo Sang.
I'm a bit concerned.
This is from a guy who was married before.
Are you sure about this?
What do you mean?
You saw Mi Ju too. She's a great girl.
Even so.
They say you should spend four seasons
with someone before tying the knot.
Aren't you rushing into it?
I'm grateful for the advice,
but let me live my own life.
Yes.
I can barely fend for myself.
Mom will freak out...
if she hears Mi Ju is pregnant.
Yes.
Let's think about...
how we should break the news to her.
Until then, let's keep it to ourselves.
Yes.
Wait out here. I'll get Tae Ri for you.
Thanks.
Good night, then.
Wait.
Forget being a neutral politician.
Let's think about what's right.
Don't you think
your mother's solution is right?
What? You think we should cause a scene?
No, not like that.
Meet the guy's family and tell the truth.
"I'm sorry about the lie,"
"but they're pregnant and in love.
Let's marry them off."
Shouldn't you persuade her?
- Maybe.
- If you all lie and they get married,
it would be infuriating for them.
- Hi.
- Dad. I'm sleepy.
Come here, Tae Ri.
Let's go to bed.
- Go on inside.
- You too.
Say goodbye.
Let's go.
I was kind enough to accept you.
No one from your family
will object or complain, will they?
- Of course not.
- They're not like that.
You.
Do you really love him?
Forget the want to marry well.
Do you really like him?
Yes.
Does he like you too?
I think so.
When did you fall for him?
That's a bit fuzzy.
It's Korean beef. Let's go.
Shall I?
Blackmailer.
What about you?
- Do you want in?
- What?
It's Korean beef. Let's go.
Was it since then?
Hey. That must've been about the beef.
Wasn't that why you got excited?
No.
He asked me to share his packed lunch...
which he'd never done with Jin Chu Ah.
He gave me a sausage too.
Guys don't share with just anyone, right?
Why did you fall for him
when it involved food?
Not all the time.
It wasn't just about food.
He's really...
quite cool.
Oh, my gosh.
The darn thing.
Is Jeong Woo Sang that great
that we must put on a show?
I never got to see
if he was worthy to be my son-in-law.
If I don't like him,
I might lie in bed and object.
Where are you going? Go to sleep.
But...
having and raising a kid
is a huge undertaking.
It's like having to juggle
a whole other life.
You'll have so many things to worry about.
What did you just say?
Mom.
"Having and raising a kid?"
What was that about?
Mom.
Are you pregnant?
Oh, no...
Tell me what happened.
Yes.
I'm pregnant.
What?
Then the nasty dream I had...
with the squawking crow...
was a conception dream for you?
I guess?
Mom. Jin Ju, Seon Ju.
She said she'd accept me
if I were from a normal family.
Let's do what we can.
If we must break it off,
instead of telling the truth to do that,
let's use the dowry or something
as an excuse instead.
Are you serious?
Lost of couples break up over that
and that's not embarrassing at all.
But I don't want to break things off
by becoming a fraud.
It's my first and last request.
Did I ever ask for something
this desperately?
Mom.
Let's marry her off.
What?
Marry her off.
You want to commit fraud with her?
If you like Jeong Woo Sang that much,
marry him.
You can marry him, but that play...
Do it.
That's most important.
It's that or I can't marry him.
Why not?
Explain our situation to his mom.
Tell her that though
we couldn't stay married,
we're not bad people and...
How can I explain that?
The more I try,
the worse she'll think of me.
That's like making excuses...
about all the lies I told.
How long do you think you'll last
if you marry on lies?
Woo Sang said it would be fine.
Won't it be okay if we stay apart
for a while after the wedding?
Then maybe she won't find out.
What?
I know I can't
get married like this, but...
I really...
like him a lot.
That's it.
We're done.
I wonder
if the downstairs people are okay.
Did they fight again?
No, they didn't fight.
No. They always fight.
But they always make up.
You're right. It looks like
they're always fighting,
but then they work together. Don't they?
Yes.
Okay. Take part in the play.
Mom.
Do that just to marry her off.
She said she'd be happy.
Mom. Even if it's for her,
you want to play along too?
I don't like it either.
But what can we do? She's pregnant.
She likes the guy.
Do you want to ruin her life too?
Do you really want us
to find a fake husband?
Get some random guy
to sit with you for two hours.
Do it and save your sister's life.
Mom.
Yes.
I get how you feel.
She's pregnant and pleading
and tugging at your heartstrings.
You want to give in to her
because you're her mom.
But still, since you're her mom,
shouldn't you tell her not to do this?
Do you think I'm giving in...
because I don't have a conscience?
I don't want to do this either.
But I want at least one of my girls...
to be happily married.
Don't you think...
one of us four deserves to have
a happy family with a husband?
Mom, even so. This isn't something...
that'll go away if we somehow
get through the wedding.
Yes.
It might be a landmine now,
but it could become nuclear later.
You're a widow and you're divorced.
Do you want her to be a single mom?
Three of us four are already single.
If she were to end up a single mom,
then I...
I really don't think...
I'll be able to live anymore.
Mom.
(Desperate Mrs. Seon Ju)
Where am I to suddenly find a husband?
- Can you do a part-time job?
- A part-time job?
Do you know you've changed a bit?
You left Seon Ju. Do you regret it?
Finalize your divorce first.
What's wrong with you?
You're so embarrassing.
I'm embarrassing?
You're divorced.
What?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)