(Episode 65)
You're here this late
when the wedding is tomorrow?
When a couple is madly in love,
they'll travel around the world
for just a few minutes.
Don't you know that?
Oh, really? Is that what this is?
Shall we bring out some fruit?
- Do we have fruit?
- No.
Go and buy some, then.
No.
It's fine. I won't stay that long.
We might not have a house,
but we can afford some fruit.
Here.
Mom. You always mention the house...
when it has nothing to do with the matter.
She's reminding us, that's all.
Look at your cheeks.
They're red because you were in the cold.
Dong Won, adjust the thermostat.
Okay.
You want us to wear thermal underwear
so we don't have to heat the house.
Look at you now.
A star son-in-law must be a huge deal.
Hey. Are you crying?
Why... What's the matter?
We didn't say anything.
Why did you make him cry?
Yes.
Quit yapping and go.
Is it that hard to get some fruit
from around the corner?
- I'll go, then.
- No, don't.
I won't stay that long. It's fine.
What...
Oh, dear.
None of your girls are remarried,
and you got no news of your husband?
Are you going around digging into
people's painful past?
Yes.
They're all trying to pull a con.
Your family doesn't seem to know
about Dong Soo.
What if his dad
were to come looking for you?
She dare blackmail me?
Goodbye, then.
Woo Sang.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for everything.
Why would you apologize?
I should be thanking you.
She's a pretty face,
but she knows nothing about life.
She causes trouble sometimes,
but she has a good, kind heart.
I know that.
What we're about to do...
It weighs on me heavily.
Wouldn't it be nice if we could
tell your mother our flaws...
and have her accept us as we are?
But I'm such a coward.
She likes you so much,
and so I couldn't insist.
I know.
You came up with the idea
and we're going with it.
We're basically
hiding behind you and using you.
But I really want you to know
that I wanted to tell your mother...
the whole truth.
Okay.
I'm sorry we have so little.
I don't know...
where the girls will find fake husbands,
but let me...
take full responsibility for this, okay?
Take good care...
of my daughter for me.
I will. I'm sorry.
Mom.
How will you get through...
the tough world
if you're so weak at heart?
Walk him to his car and come right home.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Goodbye. Get home safely.
- It's cold. Go inside.
- Get going.
It's not that cold tonight.
It's not.
Hang on.
I'll be really good to you.
You treat me well enough already.
What more will you do for me?
I'd caused nothing but disasters so far.
I think I did something good this time.
My place in the family shot up.
It's like they forgot
they sold the house because of me.
All your past hardships...
and the wrongful treatment you suffered.
I can't make it go away,
but I'll treat you well...
and heal you from that.
Will that do?
I love you.
Hey, who's that?
Isn't that
the troublemaker third daughter?
Who's the guy she's with?
I can't see his face.
My gosh.
What on earth are they doing?
Auntie Mi Ju was grinning from ear to ear.
She was.
Did Dad leave?
Yes.
Nam Jin was here? What for?
Well,
I guess he missed Ji Hyun.
My gosh. I find that hard to believe.
Dear sisters.
What?
Shall I sleep with you tonight?
Ji Hyun, will you sleep with Grandma?
Yes, of course, I will.
- Are you that happy?
- Yes.
Mr. Jeong and I
have so many great memories.
When you asked
when I fell in love with him,
I couldn't really answer,
but there were many moments.
When did you feel butterflies?
Well...
When he said I looked like a cross
between Jun Ji Hyun and Kim Tae Hee.
Hey, that was because
he was cross-eyed or something.
If he said that about you,
he'd have fainted when he saw us.
No. He really said that.
He's a really cool guy.
He looked out for me
like it was his second nature.
You're a member of my team.
And very competent.
- Congratulations.
He believes in me and trusts me.
Watch out.
He helps me.
- Let's go.
- And consoles me.
He's great at putting up a wall
when people poke and prod.
You're head over heels in love.
He gave me a job and let me stay with him.
Would you like to...
work with me instead of...
Ms. Jin starting tomorrow?
Before I knew it,
- that's how...
- Let's do our best. Cheers.
- my love for him grew.
- Cheers.
To be honest, I liked him from the start,
but I thought he and I could never be.
I pushed down my feelings...
to stop myself from falling for him.
- Let's see.
- Wait.
But I enjoyed every day I spent with him.
Every single day I was with him.
So when he said we should marry,
I thought he'd blurted it out
because he was arguing with his mom.
But I still loved it.
Goodness.
Even I think that's cool.
What's up with you?
Oh, it's nothing.
He seems like a nice guy.
Enough to make me think...
if I should've looked for someone
to bring to the wedding.
That's how nice I think he is.
So live happily ever after.
Seon Ju. Whatever I did,
I'll make it up to you...
by living happily from now on.
You can both hit me once.
Then let's say we're even.
Okay, then.
Live happily,
you brat.
One, two, three.
My gosh.
Hello. You came outside.
Yes. I have a lot to think about
and I can't fall asleep.
I see.
I thought so.
What are you doing out here?
I was weighing things out.
What do you mean?
The favor your sister asked of me.
Tell her I'll do it.
You will?
I overheard your mother...
talk to Mr. Jeong before he left.
I felt quite...
I'm a father too,
and I'd feel bad if I ignored your plight.
Is that how you felt?
Oh, right.
Take this.
My gosh.
I don't think we should have it.
Okay.
Good night, then.
Bye.
Does Pi Seon Ju...
appeal to you as a woman?
He didn't answer right away.
What's up with you?
Will alcohol help?
My gosh.
What can I do, then?
Think of a way to get back at them.
Should I tell the press...
about Woo Sang's secret wedding?
Girls. We need to talk.
I met with Ms. Oh.
She has no idea what kind of family...
Woo Sang's in-laws are.
- She doesn't?
- No.
She thinks the girl's dad works abroad,
and that her older sisters
are both happily married.
She believes
they're an ordinary, happy family.
Are they?
They're not.
Did they lie to her?
My gosh.
She doesn't know
they're the family of frauds...
that caused a scene at Mom's salon, right?
Ms. Oh wouldn't let her son
marry that girl if she knew.
Let's tell her everything
before the wedding.
Will the husbands be there tomorrow?
Yes.
If they haven't gotten remarried,
they'll find fake husbands to join them.
This is actual premeditated fraud.
I'll be your husband if you want.
Well, I have plans for tomorrow.
Like Chu Ah said,
should we tip off the press...
or tell Ms. Oh
before the wedding starts...
to stop it from...
No.
- We should all go.
- Go where?
It's no fun to tip anyone off.
Instead of talking to someone,
let's see for ourselves
if they put on a con,
and if you're right,
let's put a stop to the wedding.
We weren't invited.
Do we just barge in?
What? You're not up for it, Mom?
Are you okay with that?
Pi Seon Ju and her family will be there.
So what?
We have a few uncomfortable reasons...
to want to stay away from that family.
For example, you stole Nam Jin.
I see Seon Ju every day anyway.
It's fine. Most of those who know me
know that I cheated.
You're awesome.
Your family doesn't seem to know
about Dong Soo.
What if his dad
were to come looking for you?
She won't bring that up, will she?
What's wrong?
You're not up for it?
It's not that. You're right.
If we can't have it,
we must make sure no one can.
We can't sit and watch
as someone else takes it.
(Han Hair Line)
My gosh.
You look beautiful like this.
Because I'm your daughter.
Let's do the other side.
You want to overwhelm them...
with your look and presence.
You're right.
She'll be in her full bridal makeup.
Make me look amazing
so I look just as good.
I will.
You look great.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Really?
It was scheduled so suddenly?
Where is it at?
Okay. I'll see you later.
Honey, today...
Are you all going somewhere?
Yes. The three of us
decided to have a ladies' day out.
All together?
- Where to?
- An art gallery and...
A concert.
We only got three tickets each...
because we thought you'd be busy. Sorry.
It's fine.
I was going to invite you to a gathering.
Have fun.
Okay, sorry. See you later.
Bye.
- Are you going somewhere?
- Yes.
Where to? You're all dressed up.
I won't be out for long.
You're not going somewhere nice
without me, are you?
Goodness.
Kyung Ae will come for you a bit later...
to take you to an indoor play area.
Have fun and don't get hurt.
Okay.
My gosh.
You look awesome today.
- Doesn't he?
- What?
Yes, he looks nice.
Dad. Ms. Pi is pretty too.
She is.
If you're ready, I'll bring my car over.
- Let's go together.
- Okay.
I'm ready too.
Let's get going.
Let's go.
- You look great.
- Let's go.
Watch your step.
- Do you need help?
- My gosh.
But I live here.
- See you later.
- Bye.
My husband's name is Gang Dan Myeong.
We met at a publishing house
and dated for three years before marriage.
If he were alive, he'd be 45 now.
Gang Dan Myeong, aged 45,
met at a publishing house,
and dated for three years.
- That's right.
- Okay.
Hey. Get in here.
Even if the old hag catches and fights me,
I'd rather die alongside you
than on my own.
Look. My legs are shaking.
You idiot.
Yes. If you're committing a crime,
it's better to do it with someone.
Let's go inside.
- It's this way.
- Okay.
It looks like no one is home.
Leave what you took
and find what you came for.
Okay.
Oh, no. I didn't bring it with me.
How could you forget to bring that?
Stupid me.
Whatever.
Darn it.
What should I do?
I don't think this is Seon Ju's room.
Guys. Shall we just play at home?
Why was the indoor playground closed?
I don't know.
What do we do? Someone is coming.
- What do we say if we're caught?
- What?
Do we say I thought I lived here?
No.
Say I missed Ji Hyun?
Yes, that would be best.
Okay.
Kids. Are you okay being on your own?
- Yes.
- Are you?
I'll go home, then.
I wonder how
Auntie Mi Ju's wedding is going.
I'd have liked to go too. What about you?
They're putting on a play.
They wouldn't want to do that
in front of us.
They don't seem to get that we understand.
Why is Auntie Mi Ju
marrying someone that famous?
I can't even brag
that Jeong Woo Sang is my uncle.
Dong Won.
Out of us three,
you lived with one parent for the longest.
- What's it like?
- What do you mean?
What do you hate the most about it?
Don't ask.
What's wrong?
Grandma.
Ji Hyun.
How did you get in?
What?
I came over because I missed you.
Even so, you can't come inside like this.
You took these two
without telling anyone and...
Hey. That was no big deal.
A grandma can see her grandchild.
How dare you talk back at me?
Is your auntie marrying Jeong Woo Sang?
Well...
What did you really come here for?
I said I came here
because I missed Ji Hyun.
Seon Ju would make a fuss
if I called to ask,
so I just came over.
What if we didn't come home?
We meet if we can and not if we can't.
I got to see you, so I'll go now.
Come on out.
Hi, kids.
Who is that woman?
The jobless girl
is marrying Jeong Woo Sang?
How come?
Is it really the Jeong Woo Sang we know?
You heard them.
What's happening?
My gosh.
The only lie I tell...
is that I should die
because I'm sick and tired.
I'm really nervous about this.
But since we're doing it,
let's do a good job.
Come on.
- One, two. Let's do this.
- Let's do this.
Let's sit down.
- Mom, you sit here.
- Okay.
- Honey, you sit here.
Are you free after this?
My gosh.
- Thanks.
- You look amazing.
Shall we check the menu?
What do they have?
What do you want?
They're here.
- Hello.
No. Please stay seated.
You look lovely, Mi Ju.
Thank you.
I'm so pleased to welcome
a great young man into my family.
I guess I'm being blessed
for living an honest life.
Do you think so?
I was a huge fan of yours.
Oh, my gosh.
My mother was a massive fan of yours,
and she was overjoyed...
to be connected to you by marriage.
Was she?
Are you the eldest daughter?
Yes. It's a pleasure to meet you.
Hello. I'm Woo Sang's older brother,
Jeong Tae Sang.
- Hello.
And you are...
I'm...
He's my eldest daughter's husband.
People had been telling me
he was handsome,
but I didn't see it
because he was my son-in-law.
Today I finally realize the truth.
He's good-looking, isn't he?
Yes, he is.
If you're all here, shall we...
start with the official introduction?
Where's the middle son-in-law?
I apologize.
My husband is on a business trip and...
Hello.
Hey, Nam Jin...
Sorry, Mi Ju.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm the second brother-in-law,
Jeon Nam Jin.
You're sitting over there?
Yes.
Your other brother-in-law is handsome too.
If you don't mind,
can I rush to the ladies'?
Come with me.
Okay.
Excuse me as well.
I guess married couples
go to the toilet together.
Right, honey?
Yes, I guess?
Is he a fake too?
No. He actually was my brother-in-law.
My gosh.
What are you doing here?
I was invited and came over to help out.
When did I ask for your help?
I clearly said I didn't need it.
That was not what Mi Ju said.
- She thanked me.
- What?
She pleaded because she wanted to
get married so badly.
I couldn't ignore it.
Don't you see how your sister feels?
It's her wedding day. Think only of her.
Pi Mi Ju, that brat.
Your mother seemed to be pleased...
that I came to fill a seat.
She's not pleased! Who's pleased?
Keep it down.
Let's go back inside.
They'll be thinking something is off.
Be quiet.
Since you're all here,
shall we eat?
Yes, let's do that.
Mr. Jeon, you're an architect?
Yes, I am.
It would've been nice
if Mi Ju's father were here.
It's a shame.
Yes. It's peak tuna season,
and he couldn't spare the time.
Right, darling?
Yes, right.
You're so polite to each other
even though you're a young couple.
It's because they're so close.
I'm jealous to death, Brother-in-law.
You shock me with your audacity, Nam Jin.
- How about a drink?
- Woo Sang.
- Are you okay with that?
- Something is off.
Are you sure they're a happy family?
Yes. You know how...
some families are tense but close.
Why do I only feel tension
and no closeness?
I wonder.
Did you find the wrong guy?
What does that mean?
Can you not cause a scene?
Anyway,
both brothers-in-law are handsome
and seem to be decent men.
I'm pleased about that.
My gosh.
You shouldn't praise us
when you have sons like yours.
I'm flattered.
Honey. Dig in.
Hey.
Why is your face so red?
Are you warm?
How about a toast, then?
- Yes, good idea.
- Shall we?
We'll cut the cake after the toast.
Mr. Jang. Take some photos.
I am.
Cheers, everyone.
To the bride and groom!
- Cheers.
Wait!
(Desperate Mrs. Seon Ju)
Both brothers-in-law are fakes.
One is my brother-in-law...
and one is my sister's lover.
Seon Ju. I'm bleeding.
Did you lose the baby, then?
Did I steal your husband?
You stole mine.
Whatever con we pull,
we don't deserve to be told off by you!
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)