Mi Ju called.
Is my sister-in-law getting married?
Get the titles right.
Who's your sister-in-law?
I can help you out with that.
I'll be your husband if you want.
Darn it.
What did you just say?
You'll be whose husband?
No. What I meant was...
I've had enough.
I'll let you two fight this out.
- Move.
- Darn you.
You...
What were you doing with her?
"I'll be your husband?"
Do you want to get back together with her?
Seon Ju's sister is getting married...
and she asked me to come
and pretend to be her brother-in-law.
Do you expect me to believe that story?
At least make up an excuse
with some common sense!
If you don't believe me, ask Seon Ju.
Her sister really called me.
She actually asked you to do that?
Yes.
But would I actually go there?
And meet up with
my ex-mother-in-law and her family?
But the girl pleaded for help.
I was complaining to Seon Ju
out of disbelief.
Telling Seon Ju...
"I'll be your husband if you want"
was you complaining?
I was being sarcastic.
Her whole family is crazy.
What's wrong with...
Don't even talk to Seon Ju anymore!
Okay.
Is Pi Mi Ju out of her mind?
(Seon Ju)
Look at her.
You do feel sleepy
in the early stages of pregnancy.
The cute thing.
(Seon Ju)
I saw the sticker photos
of you and Mi Ju in your car.
You were really busy with her.
You...
Do you think she's pretty?
Yes.
How so?
She has a figure of a pre-pubescent girl
and the face of a simpleton.
Do I have to put everything in words?
My look is more modern and elegant.
She looks common.
If you don't get it, memorize it!
You're right.
You're right that you're pretty,
and that I should've...
drawn the line with you
if I didn't care for you.
I'm not saying that's your mistake!
How could you like her?
Why did you spend time with her?
Do everything with me.
Take photos and play on the claw machine.
Let's go on dates.
Do everything over with me.
How could you like her?
I can't say.
- I'm not sure...
- You don't know.
You don't know how you feel about me.
Like my line in our drama,
you like me,
but you haven't realized it yet.
You're wrong about that.
I don't know what Mi Ju means to me,
but I like being with her.
I can say for sure
that's why I want to be around her.
I'm sorry...
I can't return your feelings.
You've fallen for her...
because she's pretending to be
piteous and sweet.
Your marriage...
won't happen.
And if it does, it won't last!
Give up.
Get lost.
Do you have a favor to ask?
Something like,
"Could you sit next to me at a wedding?"
My gosh.
Should I wear something that fits...
my fighter character?
My gosh.
I knew you were a good boxer,
- but you can kick too.
- You think so?
Does he want us both or what?
Darn her.
You're home.
Hey, you.
Did you call Nam Jin
to ask him to come to the wedding?
What?
Yes.
I can't believe or understand
how you think.
You used to be married.
Wouldn't that be less of a fraud
if you brought him...
instead of a complete stranger?
I'd love to take a look at your brain.
Hey. He had an affair
and left his own kid for his mistress.
How would it make me look
if you were to ask him that favor?
Just so you can
make your wedding a success,
how dare you throw salt
onto my painful divorce?
That was too much.
You kept saying you had no one to ask,
so I got worried.
My gosh. You still won't apologize?
You deserve a beating.
- Come here.
- No.
Darn you.
Stop it.
In case you forgot, I'm pregnant.
I can't take this.
My fist would love to
punch something right now.
Don't you dare
ask a favor like that again!
(Jin Architecture)
Pi Seon Ju.
Did you ask Mr. Jeon
to act like your husband?
What?
I didn't ask him to do such a thing.
Your sister did.
Would she have gotten the idea on her own?
Do you still want him back?
I do not.
I live in fear
that you'll give him back to me.
Stop getting ideas.
I'm sick of men and marriage
this time around.
I don't think you are.
Kim So Woo. Aren't you interested in him?
- What?
- You want Mr. Jeon back...
and you're interested in my husband.
Do you want all the men in my life?
Your designs are nothing of the sort,
but you're really creative
when it comes to picking a fight.
Are you sure
you're not interested in So Woo?
- Hello.
Good morn...
Come to the meeting room.
Okay.
Goodness.
Which is Seon Ju's room?
Is it this one?
My gosh.
Hey.
This is Seon Ju's windbreaker.
This is her room.
I should do something...
now that I know
I can help Nam Jin prosper.
No mother could be devoted enough
to steal for her own son.
These are outer clothing.
Where does she keep her underwear?
Is this it?
Wash your hands first.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyun.
I called Tae Ri,
so wait until he comes over to eat.
Okay.
I'm home.
- You wash your hands too.
- Okay.
I wonder if the potatoes cooled down.
My gosh.
Don't tell anyone you saw me.
I bought you a nice treat, right?
Good. Let's go out
and have fun again someday.
Bye.
(Grace Shim Beauty Studio)
(Grace Shim)
You can't just walk in like this.
My gosh. Shim Soon Ae has come a long way.
What brings you here?
Me? I'm here to see your boss.
She's not in.
Where does she live, then?
I can't tell you that.
If you have no business, please leave.
I'm really close with your boss.
My point is,
I'm going to keep track of
all merits and demerits.
I'd like you to work even harder.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
As the new executive director,
I want us all to excel.
Is anyone displeased or offended?
Why won't you answer?
Ms. Pi. I'd like a response.
Sure. Point taken.
I'm not yet done!
Staff who think this company...
is some small hairdresser
run by a grandma.
Staff who are consistently out of line.
Insubordinate staff
who bring their private lives to work.
Such staff could get fired,
so keep that in mind.
Is that so?
I know someone who practically brought
their private affairs to work.
I think the meeting is over.
You three can leave.
- Okay.
- Excuse us, then.
The executive director called the meeting.
How dare you cut it short?
An "emergency meeting"
to review personnel performance.
"I'm the new executive director."
You called this meeting to brag.
Don't you think...
that's an example of bringing
personal issues to work, director?
What?
If you don't mind,
we'll leave too now, director.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Do excuse us.
Director.
After you.
I'll get the door.
I'll close the door, director.
Goodbye.
How dare they...
Director.
Why did you aim at me?
That hurt, director.
- Stop it!
- Director, your coffee...
That was almost laughable.
Did she want to be called
"director" that badly?
I should entertain her when I can.
Let's do that.
Can we have a word?
Well, okay.
Of all the houses you could've bought,
you bought Ms. Pi's and moved in with her.
Was that truly just a coincidence?
Yes, it was a coincidence.
I've had enough of the bad blood.
Send her family away.
Or you could move back in with us.
Why should I do that
when the house is mine?
I'm offering you a way out.
Be wise enough to give in and take it.
Don't you feel bad for Tae Ri?
Tae Ri is doing well.
He's doing better than before.
That's what you think.
I bet Tae Ri misses his mom.
You know why we separated.
I'd like you to stop
coming to see me about this.
Sang Ah is slowly coming around.
I know that much.
I really don't get it.
You didn't like me much
when I was with Sang Ah.
Is there something else
I don't know about?
I don't know why you're doing this.
I just want to see you and Sang Ah...
reconcile and live happily.
I have nothing more to say.
You don't...
have feelings for Seon Ju, do you?
If you do, control yourself.
It could end terribly.
Why would you buy me food?
You bought a house from me
and agreed to participate in my play.
The deal you signed was my first.
I was so grateful.
You're a huge help in many ways.
Give and take. It goes both ways.
You're helping me with the new show.
You can treat me too, then.
- Hey.
- What?
How much should we share to pull off...
the one-day husband charade?
Things your sister's in-laws might ask?
How old is your husband?
No. What's his name?
Can I just say my name?
You can't. My son's family name is Gang.
I can't change that just for you.
That's true.
How did you meet him?
I briefly worked at a publishing company
before I was married.
He worked there too.
And? How did you get together?
We had a team dinner at a beer joint.
He got drunk, went to the toilet,
but wouldn't come back.
I got worried and went looking for him.
When I found him, he told me he liked me.
It was a unisex toilet.
Hey.
Wasn't that too weird a place
to confess his love?
It was, wasn't it?
I don't have a single anecdote
I can brag about.
My mom told me off nonstop
that I was widowed...
because we started off in the wrong place.
Did she?
But then...
I was made to feel like I was in the way
of my younger sister's happiness.
That was so upsetting.
But then you agreed
to pretend to be my husband,
and I was able to show off.
"I'll do it for you once, but not twice."
"Make it up to me."
That was what I said.
For once in a while,
I got to be a proud big sister.
It felt nice.
Yes. I'll come over later to try it on.
Bye.
I'm going to the hanbok place.
Drive me to Gangnam.
Okay.
I wasn't entirely pleased about it,
but preparing for the wedding
is actually fun.
Is it?
I just need Chu Ah
to keep quiet and not do anything.
It's fun preparing to marry off your son?
You just need me to keep quiet?
How could you say that?
Chu Ah, what I meant was...
I trusted you.
Let's say Woo Sang was bewitched
because he had low standards.
You're the adult!
How could you allow them to marry?
What choice do I have?
A parent gives in to their children.
You mustn't give in if it's bad for them.
Not when their child...
What?
"Their child?"
They're expecting?
Yes!
Nothing happened between them.
How could she be pregnant?
Something had to have happened.
That's why she's pregnant.
Did he really sleep with her?
- Chu Ah.
- No.
- That can't be.
- Oh, dear.
It can't be.
Oh, no.
You're in shock. Are you okay?
- Chu Ah.
- Ms. Oh. Let's go to the car.
We must rush
if we want to get to Gangnam in time.
Okay. I have to go, Chu Ah.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
Are you really pregnant?
It's not a lie?
I'm not like you.
Don't call me again.
I'll report you if you do.
My gosh.
I almost died thinking I'd be caught.
If that loud-voiced woman had caught me,
I'd have ended up in handcuffs.
Goodness.
What's this?
It's a baby's swaddling clothes.
Why did I take this?
No. She said the older the better.
What could be older than this?
You're home.
Yes.
So whose is this...
Hey.
What's this?
It's a note.
"Honey.
This is my daughter from another woman."
"I have my reasons.
I'd like you to raise her for me."
"I promise to come back for her.
I'm sorry."
"Pi Su Il?"
Goodness. What's this?
One of them was the result of an affair?
My gosh.
Is this even Seon Ju's?
Hey.
Your old in-laws.
Was one of the three girls
born out of wedlock?
What are you on about?
Did you hear anything like that?
No.
But they did say the youngest sister...
didn't take after anyone.
It's the youngest.
My gosh. Her husband had an affair too,
and she rejected my son?
The ones with dirty secrets
are even worse.
My gosh.
Honey. You're home.
I met with So Woo today.
Did you? What did he say?
He didn't care to listen.
I told you so.
Do you think...
it could be because of Pi Seon Ju?
- What?
- She's always around So Woo.
Could she be manipulating him...
to get back at Sang Ah
for taking her husband?
I get the chills whenever I see her.
It can't be that.
Your flaw is that you're too trusting.
- I'm home.
- Hi, Sang Ah.
Can I have a word?
I met So Woo today.
You did? What for?
He was alone with Seon Ju.
What are they up to?
They're on the same project.
They looked at each other so fondly.
Are they just working?
Are you unable to see
how they feel as well as how you feel?
"How I feel?"
You didn't show up on your court date...
because you partly wanted to stay married.
Or you'd have shown up
even if we stopped you.
I don't know what I want.
I should like and want just one man.
I don't want Nam Jin
to go back to Seon Ju,
but I hate it when I see So Woo
smile at Seon Ju.
It's not bad to feel that way.
In your heart,
you can want every man in the world.
That's not a bad thing. But...
you must make a choice.
You must decide
which will benefit your future.
What are you saying I should do?
You can go after Mr. Jeon
whenever you want.
But So Woo?
Get him back now or you'll lose him.
- Why?
- Love...
burns like a flame at first.
So Woo and Seon Ju
are just about to light the flame.
They might not see it, but I do.
Will you hand over your husband to her?
Why did she glare at me like that?
I wondered why Sang Ah was like that.
She's exactly like her mom.
Tae Ri is So Woo's weakness.
You have tomorrow off.
Why don't you go see him?
(Jeon Nam Jin)
- Hello?
- Hi.
What are you doing today?
Let's grab lunch together.
Sorry. I have plans.
- What plans?
- I'm meeting a friend.
What friend?
You wouldn't know
even if I were to tell you.
I have to go.
Where are we going?
Well,
shall we ride up to the stone pile?
We can get tteokbokki on the way back.
Sounds good.
Where are you going?
Mom. Mr. Kim is taking us out
to ride our bikes.
We'll go to the pile of stones.
The kids wanted some air.
Did they?
It's cold. Tae Ri,
aren't your clothes too thin?
Will this do?
I think he'll be fine.
Have fun. I'll make you spaghetti.
She said she'd make spaghetti.
Quack, quack.
Let's go, then.
Don't you think
this is too much like a family?
Mom.
Yes, Tae Ri. Hi.
How dare you come here?
I missed Tae Ri.
- Who, you?
- Yes.
Let's have lunch together.
What do you want, Tae Ri?
Mom will take you to have something nice.
No, wait.
It's cold. Will you two wait in the salon?
- Yes.
- Go on.
You were a pretty good guy.
I didn't see that until now.
We were together for years.
Now you suddenly see it?
I did as you said...
and spent the time to see how I felt.
And now I see you in a new light.
You were so warm.
I was warm?
Didn't you like hot and fiery love?
Have those flames died out?
I thought we never had a fiery love.
We had embers that lasted longer.
You're really quite interesting.
You asked me what I wanted to do with you.
I thought about it.
I think...
I don't want to divorce you.
What?
(Desperate Mrs. Seon Ju)
Woo Sang is getting married.
Why must you both lose your men
to the girls in that family?
My younger brother is
getting married there that day too.
Who's your younger brother?
Jeong Woo Sang.
You don't have a thing
with our homeowner, do you?
Can I ask for his help?
To be your husband?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)