(Episode 19)
You got me from somewhere else.
Who said that?
That means you could abandon me again.
If Mom and Dad hate each other...
and hate me too...
Who said that?
You said...
the three of us
would live like the three bears.
Yes. Let's do that.
We won't split up.
Mom and Dad will stay together.
I promise, Tae Ri. Dad...
Dad will try harder, okay?
Don't cry.
You wanted Tae Ri.
I asked many times
if you'd thought it through.
You said you'd make him
the happiest kid ever.
I can't help it that he's not the kid
I expected him to be.
Is that my fault?
- What?
- I was flustered too.
I tried, but I couldn't love him.
What was I to do?
Is love something you can force?
Jin Sang Ah.
What do Tae Ri and I mean to you?
You were not too bad as a husband,
and Tae Ri...
That was greed on my part.
Everyone else had a kid, and I didn't.
It drove me crazy.
Hearing I was infertile...
I failed to think straight at the time.
If that was your greed,
you should've tried harder.
You should've tried harder
than any birth parent!
Why take it out on me
when some people abandon their kids?
- What?
- Sang Ah, are you upstairs?
It must be so easy for you.
You ditch me for not being fun,
and you ditch Tae Ri because he's not
what you expected?
Sang Ah, you're home.
Did you sort things out
at the police station?
Yes.
Sang Ah, can I have a word?
Sure.
- Sit.
- Okay.
Are you aware
the executive director will retire...
and we'll shuffle
some personnel next month?
What?
Well, yes.
I'm not sure if you know,
but what I value...
the most in a person
is how they are at home.
So Woo has been looking down lately.
Are you two having problems?
No, we're not.
Good, then.
So Woo allowed you to study abroad.
You should make it up to him.
Don't work too hard and upset him.
I can't give a hefty position
to someone who can't even...
handle a household.
I have no need for such people at work.
My board will agree with that.
Not even my own blood is an exception.
Do you understand...
what I mean?
Yes.
You can continue.
Tae Ri needs a mom.
You said it must be easy for me,
that I was ditching you and Tae Ri.
I won't.
I'm still his mom.
It wasn't all easy for me either.
It's tough to raise your own kid,
so raising a kid that's not your own?
It's extra hard.
But I'll try harder.
So you...
Though it won't be easy
as I know you must be upset,
for a while,
let's pretend we don't have...
any problems.
You want to put on a show?
A happily married couple.
Let's pretend that's what we are.
Lots of people pretend.
Why?
For how long?
Until Mr. Jeon gets divorced...
and comes to you?
We could end up reconciling first.
Tae Ri lashed out today.
- Did he?
- He knew that we had...
adopted him.
I didn't tell him.
I don't know how he found out or when,
but it would've been hard on him.
And these days...
Because we've been fighting too...
Let's do it.
Let's pretend that we're happily married.
You made that suggestion so apathetically,
and I don't get it,
but Tae Ri thinks the world of you...
and wants you to remain around him.
I'll keep a safe distance and observe.
While we do this,
I want you to do your best
as Tae Ri's mom.
At work and home, I'll act...
as if we have no problems.
- Okay.
- Even if we split up in the end...
If you hurt Tae Ri in the process,
I won't let either of you off.
While we're at this,
you'd better really do your best.
I will.
Mom.
Oh, dear.
- You woke up?
- Yes.
Did Dad buy you something tasty?
Yes. Why didn't you keep your promise?
It was so hard
to get Dad to agree to a date.
I'm sorry.
Something came up at work and...
Did you apologize to Dad?
How will you make it up to him?
Ask him again to take us somewhere.
He's busy these days.
Even so.
Say "darling" sweetly
and put him in a good mood.
Everyone calls you dull and thick
because you can't do that.
Okay. I'll spruce myself up,
get the timing right,
and get my darling to take us somewhere.
Let's go to bed.
Are you wide awake?
No.
He's so cute.
I love this baby.
He'll grow up to be so smart.
Will he?
Tae Ri.
We're your mom and dad.
Thanks for going with what I want.
Why would you thank me? Thank Tae Ri.
The adorable kid came to us
without you having to suffer or struggle.
He's a good son already.
I'll make Jin Architecture
ten times bigger for you to inherit.
You'd better become a sweet kid.
I'll scold you if you don't.
- Shall I play some music?
- Yes, do.
Listen, Tae Ri.
Isn't that a pretty sound?
He's smiling. Look at Dad.
My gosh. Look at his tiny feet.
They're adorable.
(Jin Architecture)
Good morning.
Let's say it is.
Working with your wife's affair partner.
The pain must be unimaginable.
I'm really impressed.
You said no love lasted forever
and no families were complete.
Do you think your affair will last?
It's a one-off thing.
You wanted to keep it apart from work.
You should do that yourself.
We're not a perfect couple,
but Ms. Jin and I...
decided to work things out.
So aren't I still...
Ms. Jin's husband...
and your superior?
It's true.
Hee Kyung in HR told me.
Really?
Then there must be some truth to it.
- Hello.
- Hello, Mr. Jeon.
What were you talking about?
Well, it's still a secret,
but our executive director...
will retire and move abroad.
There's a possibility that Mr. Kim
will be promoted to fill the position.
Ms. Jin's father is the owner and CEO,
but there are four planning teams
and one each for interior and inspection.
Wouldn't Mr. Kim have
more influence and say in the company?
I agree. The previous director
was from planning too.
I see.
Let's talk.
What's up?
I met your husband on the way to work.
He proudly said he had no issues with you.
Didn't you two decide to split up?
Just for a while,
we agreed to act like a couple.
- Why?
- Promotion season is coming up.
Nothing good would come from
asking for a divorce right now.
I must get promoted if I'm to help you.
Are you sure
you'll get promoted and not Kim So Woo?
What does that mean?
Don't get silly ideas
and get rid of Pi Seon Ju first.
You agreed to divorce her first.
If one person gets divorced first,
it'll make things much less complicated.
Did you give Seon Ju the ultimatum?
I will.
What phone costs so much to repair?
I'd rather just buy a new one.
Darn it.
Boss.
Are you home?
Are you in?
Goodness.
Did you really run away?
- Boss?
- Ms. Pi?
It's Gwangyang Villa, the place
you worked on three months ago.
Oh, hi.
Did you change your number?
Yes. So there's this gaping hole
in the wallpaper.
Come and take a look at it.
- What?
- You said you'd fix anything for me.
Okay. Sure.
Did he really move away?
This is madness.
How did this happen? It's all on you.
I don't remember anything
about the accident.
How could you?
Your memory never was the best,
and you dozed off.
I would like to know how I dozed off
and how the accident happened.
Her dashboard camera broke too.
Hey.
Excuse me.
I'm sure I saw.
- Saw what?
- When the accident happened,
someone else was there.
A squiggle like dung?
A guy wearing a cap with that design
got out of Jin Chu Ah's car.
If someone got out with a dung-like cap,
would that make you innocent?
If you find him, will he settle for us?
He wouldn't,
but Jin Chu Ah denied
being with anyone, and that's weird.
She's an actress of sorts,
so maybe it was a secret date.
Oh, whatever.
I'm making green onion kimchi
because Mom is upset.
You...
can peel all these.
My back aches.
A secret date?
Was that it?
What made you decide
to accept the drama role?
Could you tell us?
This drama portrays
the revenge of a man with amnesia...
who falls for a terminally ill woman.
As soon as I read the script,
I knew it was the role of a lifetime.
So I jumped at the chance.
Did you feel it right away?
Yes.
That cap is quite unusual.
- You wear it often.
- Hey.
Oh, this?
A fan said that snake imagery suited me...
and embroidered this herself.
Then it's a one-of-a-kind cap.
- Can I try it on?
- Sure.
(Hot Scoops,
Actor Jeong Woo Sang Random Interview)
It looks like an actual snake.
That cap.
- Jeong Woo Sang.
- Does it suit me?
It was Jeong Woo Sang.
- I'm a flower, and it's a snake.
- He got out of the car.
It wasn't a dung-like squiggle.
It was a squirming snake.
Darn it.
Let's see.
Let's give it a go.
I might not get paid anyway.
Hello, ma'am.
It's Jeil Interior Design.
You still owe us 1,000 dollars
for the work we did.
What?
Who told you that?
You still owe us
even if we're out of business.
Hello? You...
What's this?
She's rotten.
My gosh.
My goodness.
You're out of business?
Yes.
That was why yesterday...
Let's talk.
Where are you going?
Follow me.
I heard the police took you away
for assaulting Ms. Jin's family.
Didn't I tell you she was my superior?
- What?
- You all barged in...
and hurt her mother,
so she had to get admitted.
What's wrong with your whole family?
How much of a pickle
do you want to put me in?
I'm embarrassed to death.
How could you say that?
If you heard what happened,
if you found out your wife, mother-in-law,
and sisters-in-law
went to the police station,
shouldn't you have asked
if we were okay...
and if everything was sorted?
You didn't pick up then,
and now you show up and say...
you're embarrassed to death
to face your superior?
Did they hit you?
You were brought in for assault.
Why wouldn't you be okay?
Jeon Nam Jin.
It's me.
I'm still your wife.
You are.
And I don't want you to be.
I came to say that.
Let's end it.
Honey.
Jeong Woo Sang.
It was Jeong Woo Sang.
The guy in Jin Chu Ah's car...
It wasn't a dung-like squiggle.
It was a squirming snake.
Think. Think, Pi Mi Ju.
Let's end it.
You really...
What about Ji Hyun?
Don't you care about Ji Hyun?
That bothers me too.
But I don't want to stay married
out of a sense of duty.
Jeon Nam Jin.
You're really out of your mind.
Then...
how should I explain it to her?
Should I say her dad...
went crazy for someone else and left?
- It's not like that.
- As if it's not.
You call me dull and thick,
but even dull people think.
You said she was there
to help you put on pain relief patches.
"Oh, I see. That was it."
Do you think anyone would buy that excuse?
Think what you want.
Honey.
Ending things quickly so we can both
settle down...
might be better for Ji Hyun.
If you can't tell her, I'll talk to her.
My gosh...
You made up your mind.
In your mind,
you divorced me and started over...
with the other woman.
While I was...
clinging to the cell rails...
and wailing my eyes out,
you were busy filling in these papers.
Right now...
You don't know...
what I'm going through right now.
Is this that urgent a matter?
We waited for two years
for you to come back.
How could you abandon us like this?
How could you do this to us?
Darling?
Honey. Stop this and come back.
I'll forget all about it.
Whether you have someone else or not,
who she is,
where you met, and how far you went.
The more I know, the more I'll hurt.
I won't ask anything.
I have...
so much to handle,
and I'm really stressed out.
So...
I'll forget about it all.
I'll be cool and let it go.
Okay?
Come back to us.
Are you sure you're okay?
You should've stayed a few more days.
I just have to be careful.
You're too stubborn.
What about the assailants?
They were caught at the scene,
and we had CCTV footage.
There's no way out.
You can go and shower.
Okay.
Han Man Eun.
Why did you show up and get on my nerves?
- Goodbye.
- Bye. Thank you.
- Hello?
- Hi.
Nam Jin, it's me.
Are you busy?
Yes, I'm at work.
Yes, you should work hard
to support your wife and kid.
- The breadwinner should...
- Why did you call?
Oh, well...
Could you lend us some money?
Seon Ju was against me telling you,
and it's hard to even ask you for help,
but since you found a nice job...
I can't help with that.
Oh, okay, then.
Pretend you didn't hear anything.
Don't tell Seon Ju I called.
Bye.
How is this fool so cold?
Did you talk to Seon Ju?
I gave her the divorce papers.
What did she say?
She can't accept it right now.
But I'll see to it that she does.
What about the kid?
Seon Ju will want custody.
Still,
I want to be the dad.
You mean you want to pay child support?
She's going around asking for cash.
It looks like she has nothing.
How will you split your assets?
Don't worry about that. I'll handle it.
Your father has passed.
What's your mother like?
She's a homebody.
Do you pay her expenses?
She lives off of Father's inheritance.
You're better off than I thought.
I am.
(Boxing Club, Main Branch)
Where do you think this is?
Where are we?
It's where people learn to do this.
It's a boxing club.
They had some pretty nice reviews.
Let me check.
(Manjang-gu Boxing Club)
Hello. I'm in front of the building.
Are you in?
Oh, really?
Okay, then. Thank you.
Let's go, Tae Ri.
(Manjang-gu Boxing Club)
Hang on.
Someone's inside.
Excuse me.
Hello? Excuse me.
Let's end it.
That bothers me too.
But I don't want to stay married
out of a sense of duty.
Excuse me. Can you...
Oh, dear.
- Goodness.
- Hey.
Oh, gosh.
(Desperate Mrs. Seon Ju)
Say hello. This is my mom.
I'd have liked you to be my son-in-law
if Sang Ah wasn't married.
What...
Are you okay?
She must be in lots of pain.
Are you even thinking about the money?
Do whatever it takes
to think of a plan by this evening.
Should we all buy lottery tickets?
Mother. Did you see a lottery ticket?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)