Watch out!
- Goodness.
- My gosh.
My word.
That was close.
I can't believe you saved my life...
the very day we first met.
Isn't this a huge sign?
Yes.
Right. What we were talking about.
When will your divorce be finalized?
I'll be done for good
with the kid's dad soon.
But I'm not yet ready to...
Wait.
"The kid's dad?"
You have a kid?
Yes.
Oh, you have a kid...
I didn't know about that.
That's a huge deal.
I see.
My gosh.
I'm sorry,
but I don't think we're a good match.
I'm really sorry.
You can go back to the pagoda
and take the leftover pajeon.
I'll take the makgeolli.
My gosh.
Did he just reject me?
Goodness.
I didn't even want to meet him.
This is unbelievable.
You can't do this ever again.
I get that you're trying to be caring,
but I'm in no position to remarry,
and I'm not interested.
Please don't do this.
I was as polite as I could be to Yu Ra...
Hey. Did you meet the guy?
- How did things go?
- You too?
You too?
How was it?
My gosh...
Do you even need to ask?
He's way better-looking than Jeon Nam Jin.
He had this air about him.
You want a guy who looks just like him...
or they act like
they're better than others, like Nam Jin.
Do you think selling fried chicken
is a worse job than an architect?
He could make a fortune if things go well.
I bet he makes way more than Nam Jin.
Stop it, Mom!
Don't just accentuate
the fried chicken place.
He's a police officer too.
Hey, he's in Violent Crimes.
Isn't that cool?
Stop it, Jin Ju.
I get why Mom is doing this,
but why are you playing along?
I'd be so embarrassed
if others were to find out.
Hey.
I'd love to go on a blind date,
but no one will set me up.
People are volunteering to help you
when you're not even divorced yet.
I've been widowed for so long,
but no one cares about me.
I asked Mom if I could
meet the policeman and she said no.
Mom. How could you?
That hurt.
Listen. Kyung Ae's mom...
showed him both your photos,
and he insisted on meeting Seon Ju.
I didn't tell you in case you got upset.
Is that true?
What's wrong with him?
Darn it.
Anyway, Mom.
Don't go and do something silly
like this again.
Oh, my gosh.
Why does my head ache all of a sudden?
Oh, dear. My head is splitting open.
Oh, gosh.
She's a nice person,
but I can't handle it when she does that.
Neither can I. She's such a troublemaker.
And she's getting worse with age.
I apologize instead.
- It's fine.
- Seon Ju!
Get over here!
Let's go.
Something happened
in a park in Manjang-dong today.
It became known
when two young content creators...
- submitted their footage.
- Mom.
- You're on TV.
- A small woman...
notices a boulder falling from above...
and throws herself onto a much bigger man.
A boulder fell from a mountain
in a park in Seoul today.
You just saw footage...
two YouTubers filmed of the incident.
We managed to secure an interview
with the young lady.
How did you feel at the time?
(Ms. Pi)
My mind went blank at the time.
I just thought I'd die.
I think that was why...
I jumped on him like this
to get him out of the way.
Did you know the man you saved?
No, we'd just met today.
Then for a complete stranger...
Well, no. He's not a complete stranger.
It was...
It was a blind date.
I see.
It's hard to find someone
who'd risk their life to save someone...
they'd just met in real life.
We're reminded
to break away from stereotypes...
that smaller people are weak...
You're so brave, Auntie.
You actually did an interview?
Only because she offered me these.
She begged me to make a few comments.
You said you didn't want others to know,
but you broadcasted it yourself.
I didn't know they'd play it all.
Why didn't they cut out
the part where I whispered?
And I swear I asked them
to blur out my face.
My goodness.
That's unbelievable. Nam Jin.
- My gosh.
- What is it?
Go online and watch a replay
of today's MBS news.
- The news?
- Yes.
This report here.
Play that part.
(Ms. Pi, "How did you feel at the time?")
My mind went blank at the time.
I just thought I'd die.
I think that was why...
I jumped on him like this
to get him out of the way.
Did you know the man you saved?
No, we'd just met today.
Then for a complete stranger...
Well, no. He's not a complete stranger.
It was...
It was a blind date.
I see.
It's hard to find someone...
- who'd risk their life to save someone...
- How humiliating is that?
- they'd just met in real life.
- I don't dare say that's your ex.
She went on a blind date.
She went on a blind date
and you had an affair.
There's not much of a difference.
You don't need to feel bad at all.
She went on a blind date?
What now?
Your blind date is now a part of history.
Are you teasing me?
It was a joke topped with concern,
but it didn't seem to work.
How could you?
Hang on.
I got a message.
You said you were not yet ready
to meet someone.
I know you said that
because you felt bad for me.
I think both love and marriage...
are a lot like plastic surgery.
If we only operated on those
who decided to get surgery and came to us,
not that many people out there
would become pretty.
But...
those who take just one brave step...
get to live a whole new life.
Would you like to take that step with me
and venture into a new world and life?
Will you tell your mother...
not to do this ever again?
I will.
Are you asleep?
- Hello?
- Seon Ju.
- Are you asleep?
- What?
I saw the news.
I'm grateful that you saved me
from the falling boulder,
and so I called because the news
reminded me of what happened.
But there's our reality to consider.
Shall we give it a go anyway?
What? Give what a go?
I think I can. What about you?
Mister. You sound very drunk.
If you record your calls,
play this back when you're sober tomorrow.
For now, you should go to bed.
Seon Ju!
I liked you a lot, Seon Ju!
Oh, my gosh. What the heck?
Your blind date.
He sounded a bit weird.
Is he really a police officer?
He doesn't look like one.
He said he was,
and he runs a fried chicken place too.
Maybe your blind date...
won the favor of the deities from above.
Let's go upstairs.
Why the heck did I do that interview?
I'm exhausted.
Why did it take so long?
You must be tired after all that driving.
I'm fine.
- Did you just get back?
- Yes.
I had some friends over,
so there's a stack of dirty dishes.
Wash them before bed.
Okay.
I think hiring her was a good idea.
Right?
Darn you.
Why make you do this now
when you could do it tomorrow?
It's not nice to keep
dirty dishes out too long.
I'll wash them real fast and go to bed.
We have an early start tomorrow.
What's this? Is it a love letter?
Don't read it.
It's to "Han Man Eun?"
What kind of name is that?
What's so funny about that name?
It sounds weird, like a silly nickname.
It's my mom's name.
If your mom is called "Han Man Eun,"
is your dad called "Dae Dong Gang?"
Who'd name someone that?
Her family is from Cheonju
and her name means "full blessings."
"Han Man Eun" is my mom's name.
- For real?
- Would I lie about that?
It's a name
that tugs at your heartstrings.
There's pathos.
Whatever.
I mean it.
It sounds like
there's a whole story behind it.
What a great name to have.
Forget it.
You're getting on my nerves. Go away.
You wrote a letter to your mom?
Only because...
I couldn't talk on the phone.
What did you say?
That I'd make lots of money...
and get our house back.
That she shouldn't grow old too fast.
Did you lose your house?
Will you...
Oh, no.
Hey.
Why did you use your bare hands?
You made me take off the rubber gloves.
Do you need help?
No.
Hey, leave it. I'll do the rest.
But...
I'll be fine with the gloves.
I'm not taking over
as a favor for an underling.
You're hurt.
Call this an employer looking out for
his employee's welfare.
Don't you fall for me.
I don't have any feelings for you.
Why do you keep worrying about that?
What is it?
Choon Hyang's sister Pi Mi Ju moved into
Woo Sang's as a live-in caregiver.
- So what?
- What if they end up...
discussing the accident
while they're living together?
The accident?
Why can't they talk about it?
She did cause the accident.
We settled with them,
so what's the problem?
Well...
That's right.
She caused the accident.
I'm off. Bye.
Then for a complete stranger...
Well, no. He's not a complete stranger.
It was...
(Ms. Pi, "For a complete stranger?")
It was a blind date.
I see.
- It's hard to find someone...
- Pi Seon Ju.
- who'd risk their life...
- What a mess.
to save someone
they'd just met in real life.
(Jin Architecture)
Mr. Jeon. Why are you moving?
Well...
Mr. Jeon.
Work with me in my office from now on.
While we compete on the Hansung project,
Mr. Kim will share his office
with his designer.
We should do the same.
For security's sake.
Right...
Will this do?
Yes, thank you.
Why didn't you tell me about the move?
I was flustered
because I couldn't explain.
Why would you be flustered?
Focus on coming up with
a perfect business proposal.
The width...
Goodness.
Well...
Once we beat them,
they'll have no excuse to stay on.
They'd be too ashamed to stay.
And my dad will see us in a new light.
But remember this.
You can serve her
and grovel at her feet all you want,
but you'll amount to nothing more
than her minion.
Wait.
My gosh.
You dislike the last place that much?
It looked too old.
How could that cost over 700,000 dollars?
The area will be redeveloped
because it's old,
and it's expensive
because it'll be redeveloped.
You got the cause and effect all wrong.
Don't you have a clean,
atmospheric place...
that looks cozy and fits my budget?
Are you looking for a place with a view...
that's also close to a subway station?
It's an investment,
so I want the best if possible.
Fine. Let's check out
the next place, then.
Hey.
Wait for me.
- What's this?
- What's what?
Look at this.
"A woman cheated on her husband
whom she works with,"
"and her lover's ex-wife
got a job with her."
"So all four are working together."
Read the comments.
"What? What are you saying?"
"How can a cheater work with her husband?"
"Don't you mean she works with her lover?"
"It says all four met up."
"The story checks out. Read it again."
"It's the world's worst combination."
Isn't this about them?
It must be.
This kind of story can't be common.
What's going on?
Why are we so famous?
Do you think they'll become
online celebrities?
To think that we work with such people.
It's an honor.
What?
Someone posted about it
on an anonymous website?
Okay. I got it.
What's the matter?
This is humiliating.
- I must go to work.
- Okay.
She started
working for my family yesterday.
Hello. I'll see you every now and then.
(Arcade entrance)
Darn it.
- My gosh.
- What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Oh, dear.
Is she hurt?
Hello?
What? Chu Ah passed out?
She fainted in the middle of a street.
How come?
Nothing is wrong with her, though.
I think she was under a lot of stress.
Okay. So it's not serious?
She can go home
once she wakes from her nap.
See you at home later.
Okay.
She could be weak
because she tried to lose weight.
Tell her to eat well.
- I will.
- Bye, then.
Hello.
You're awake.
Mom.
Call Woo Sang and tell him I fainted.
You call him.
How can someone who fainted use a phone?
Call him for me.
Why do you need my help with that?
Be as foxy as you can be and seduce him.
Did you seduce Dad by being foxy?
How did you marry him?
Tell me.
I didn't seduce him.
How did you two meet?
You only said a friend introduced you.
What was Dad like when you first met him?
When we first met?
What's taking her so long
to buy a packet of noodles?
An old man from Seoul
about to board a train for the first time
Excuse me.
Gosh.
I couldn't believe
someone so elegant existed.
Do you want your hair done?
- He was so handsome.
- No.
- I don't know her name...
- He's handsome even now,
but he was
so much more of a looker back then.
Even young girls these days
would've fallen for him.
I wanted him to like me,
so I secretly spat out the chewing gum
I'd just put into my mouth...
and stuck it to a wheeled tray.
I think I fell for him that very moment.
You're a romantic
who goes for a guy's looks.
Am I?
What did you do when you first met?
He took me out in his car.
He took you out back then?
How sweet.
So how did you get him to marry you?
I went to where he lived...
and asked for a cup of tea.
(38 Hangang-dong)
I said I'd come to the hospital.
You're busy with your wife's funeral.
Here.
- Thanks.
- She's so pretty.
Just like your wife.
How about you? Are you all right?
My back...
still aches a bit, but I'm fine.
First, you saved my father's life,
and now my child's.
Thanks so much.
It's nothing, really.
I'm a bit thirsty.
Can I have a cup of tea?
Yes, sure. Come in.
My gosh. You went to Dad's home?
Back then,
it was the guys who did the courting.
But I took the initiative in a way.
I see...
The new hire.
The one who works with Mr. Kim.
Ms. Pi Seon Ju?
Yes. Tell her to come see me.
Her portfolio...
was full of effort like a journal
that was kept for a long time.
I thought...
her interpretation of space
matched our vision.
What on earth is she like?
The CEO wants to see me?
- What for?
- I don't really know.
Okay. I'll come over.
Tell her to eat well.
Bye, then.
Hello.
Come in.
Take a seat.
Ms. Pi Seon Ju.
You were married to Mr. Jeon?
Yes. We're waiting
for our divorce to be finalized.
That means
you're the person in the video...
who was also mentioned
in the anonymous post.
I just don't get it.
Why did you accept a job
at a company where your ex...
and Sang Ah work?
- Well...
- Mr. Kim told me...
you were a promising talent.
But word is spreading like wildfire,
and I don't want...
my company to be
reduced to a laughingstock.
I want you to leave.
(Desperate Mrs. Seon Ju)
Does Pi Mi Ju come into your bedroom?
My gosh.
You went on a blind date.
You called me all sorts of things
for having an affair.
What?
That man is perfect for you.
I didn't join the company to get revenge.
I don't think it's right to stay on.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)