I didn't expect to arrive so late.
It's fine.
We won't make it.
Mr. Yoshimura was supposed
to help me with my research.
Hold him we'd be there at noon.
- Really?
-Yes
That's because we had
to wait at that diner.
Your seafood fried rice
arrived quickly...
but my fish set took
more than 20 min.
We should have started earlier.
Everything is slower in the countryside.
You could have seen it coming.
Eh?
You mean it's my fault
because I ordered fish?
I didn't chose the right dish?
That's not what I said.
It took you ages to drop
Mayu at your mom's.
Women are such chatterboxes.
And now it's my fault.
It's very kind of her
to take take care of her.
I couldn't just drop Mayu
and say bye-bye. That's rude.
Fine, forget I said anything.
I'm just pointing to what
our time was spent on.
Shouldn't you call him?
Alright, I get it.
Hello, Mr. Yoshimura, it's Kawatsu.
We're going to be late.
If we arrive later tonight, could
you still come and help me?
There you have it.
I missed this place.
When was the last time?
Mayu wasn't yet in kindergarten.
Probably 8 years ago.
That long ago?
I see.
Certainly, I hadn't spoken
with Uncle in two years.
What did you tell him?
That I left the college
to write a book...
and we'd like to use the villa.
He gladly agreed to let us.
What's this?
Don't touch it.
Hey.
Why are you always so snoopy?
Hold you not to touch it.
That's because...
I wanted to surprise you.
I'm sorry.
You've ruined the occasion.
Not at all...
I'm so happy. thank you.
Let's hurry, I want to use them.
So tired.
Having to drive all the
way was exhausting.
I offered to drive half the way.
No, I really wanted you to rest.
That's the purpose of this stay.
How about a barbecue tonight?
Say...
You remember our last barbecue?
It was great.
You got drunk and threw up on the cover.
Hey, easy now.
That was 8 years ago.
It was an accident.
Aunty is still mad about her cover.
We're offering her this new cover.
It was a bargain, but good quality.
You recommended the shop.
You don't have to tell me.
You'll tell her when
you bring it to her.
You didn't tell her about it?
I'm not telling her
you bought it on bargain.
But still it's a good quality cover.
It's fine.
It's in the past, we can
laugh about it now...
and it becomes good family memories.
Need to take a leek.
You have to sit down.
I got it.
What the hell.
And now we have a whole week
just for the two of us.
Ks, hello.
Hey, Mom, what's up?
Hold you there's no
cell phone signal here.
What? Is she alright?
Too bad.
I'm sorry, could you
take her to the hospital?
Right.
I'll be there soon.
Yes.
What is it?
Mayu had a sudden belly ache...
and even a bit of fever.
Was it something she ate?
Sorry, I need you
to take me to the station.
- You're going back?
- ks.
You need the car here.
And the train is faster.
Darn.
You were so looking
forward to this week off.
I'll be fine.
All the fresh food
we bought will go to waste.
Maybe Mayu will soon get well.
You'll come back.
Sorry to arrive so late.
Please, drink.
Do you remember in Tokyo recently...
that serial killer
nicknamed Jack-the-Ripper?
Ah, that murderer who was
breaking into houses.
He was raping women and
then stabbing them.
That was awful.
I think he even killed a couple of men.
So...
to be on the safe side...
I thought you could meet this officer.
Wh... what do you mean?
You mean that this murderer
is operating in the area?
We aren't sure yet.
The truth is, even in this village...
there were two very similar cases.
Is that right?
That is so scary.
Even in the countryside you
have to lock the doors.
I will.
But I feel safer knowing that
you're watching, officer.
At least you didn't come here.
Believing that I am that
Jack-the-Ripper.
Weren't you supposed
to come with your wife.
Her mother just called in
saying that our daughter is sick.
She had to take a train home.
I see.
You must be worried.
Yes.
I also came to tell you.
Tonight it's going to start raining.
When it rains here, the
roads are very difficult.
Don't forget to check
the weather report.
Alright then, I will.
Anyway, I'll call you tomorrow afternoon.
Ah, thank you sir.
What?
I thought we had internet.
What the hell?
Maybe the Ethernet plug?
How about now?
Ah, still not working.
Really now.
Hello.
Ah, it's you dear.
Ah, Mayumi.
So, how is she?
It's a mild appendicitis.
An appendicitis.
Her appendix is inflamed.
I see.
Does she need surgery?
It's not serious, maybe drugs will do.
I see.
The do: said it could
be caused by stress.
By stress?
You know how she was affected
by your conduct.
Yeah, right.
She's going through a rough time.
I want to stay with her.
I see.
I'm sorry, you'll have
to manage without me.
You know, we wanted
to mend our marriage.
It's not the right time
to discuss this.
Come on, you wanted it too.
I thought it was important.
Come on.
Surely...
we have no choice but to move on.
Right.
Gotta go.
Hello? Hello?
Mayumi?
Ah? What happened?
Excuse us.
You're the only house
with the lights on.
We lost our way...
and we have no cell phone signal.
Could we use your land line?
Would that be a bother?
Sure, please come inside.
Excuse us.
Thank you.
Ah, a heater.
You may sit down.
Thank you, sir.
Don't you need to dry your coats?
Let me have it.
Thank you, sir.
It's completely soaked.
You feel better?
Please, have a towel.
Thank you so much.
The phone is over there.
Thank you sir, I'll call.
Hello.
We're from the hiking club.
Right.
Are they back already?
Good, thank you so much.
Could you give me your address?
Right away.
Here it is.
It's In Fukazawa village...
Sorry, the screen went black.
- There you are.
- Thank you sir.
In Fukazawa village, house number 711.
Right, we're so grateful.
Thank you very much, goodbye.
You've been so helpful.
They are coming to pick us up at 10.
That's good news.
The area doesn't have phone signal.
That phone is only good
to give me the time.
Excuse me.
We're sorry to impose.
Would you let us stay
until they arrive?
Sure, no problem.
I'm not throwing two ladies
out into the night.
That is so kind of you.
My name is Nami Onishi.
I'm Mr. Kawatsu.
I'm Yuka Konishi.
Ah, you're not sisters?
No, we work at the same company...
and we both decided
to join the hiking club.
We got separated from the group.
That's too bad.
At least you are safe.
That Jack-the-Ripper from Tokyo...
is hiding in the neighborhood.
really?
I'm scared.
I'm cold.
Are you OK?
It's so warm.
We're finally warming up.
You feel better?
It feels great.
You have a foam beard.
You give me one too?
You do it.
You're so cute.
Let me see how cute.
Suits you so well.
It's great.
Let me clean your back.
- Turn around.
- OK.
Oh, that is so nice.
Alright, your turn now.
My turn now.
- How is it?
- Great.
'Ks, keep going-
Does it tickle you here?
No it doesn't, you could
keep going forever.
It's so warm now.
I feel relaxed.
Your tits are showing.
Sorry, I didn't dare take
my wife's clothes.
I hope mine will suit you.
There.
Your hospitality is boundless.
Nice shirt.
- Is it big?
- Yeah.
You manage?
Smells like my dad's.
Ah? Was it washed properly?
It feels safe.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
So you are married?
We came here from Tokyo...
for my research.
What research?
I'm going to publish a book.
Amazing.
You're a writer?
Can I have your autograph?
No I'm not a writer.
I write history books.
That's still great.
I was a college Professor.
Unfortunately, I had to resign.
I never spent much time with my wife.
We wanted to have
some quality time.
So nice of you!
Your wife is so lucky.
I can't say that...
My wife doesn't see it that way.
Most men are inconsiderate
of their wife's feelings.
But you are so considerate.
You're a great husband.
I'm not sure.
Where's is Madam?
Our daughter suddenly got sick...
and she had to go take care of her.
You must be worried.
It's not that serious.
As soon as our daughter
is better, she'll come back.
You could get lonely until she comes.
I miss her...
but look, your little adventure
enlivened my loneliness.
So kind of you to say that.
We feel less guilty for imposing on you.
You are such a good man.
I wouldn't say that.
- So delicious.
You have to eat your carrots.
You can have them...
There.
Oh, come on.
It's good.
If you like...
You're being too generous.
Cheers!
Yuka, you're such a kid.
Forgive her, Professor.
It's fine.
Make yourself at home.
Enjoy the beer.
You really don't mind us here?
Of course not.
Alright then, I'll take
you up on your offer.
You really seem to enjoy it.
So good.
Nami doesn't handle alcohol very well.
I'm sorry, I gave her too much.
They're late.
There is a storm going on.
It seems they won't be coming tonight.
Maybe we should go anyway.
Be careful of that
Jack-the-Ripper at night.
You'd better stay indoors.
But...
Don't be embarrassed.
You can sleep here tonight.
Thank you, Professor.
Your clothes should be dry by now.
Do you think that my tits are showing?
Well, I didn't notice anything.
- Sorry if I inadvertently...
- Come on...
I don't wear a bra.
You know where the nipples are.
I'm not sure.
Look...
They're here.
This is not a good joke.
- Are you mad?
- No, I'm not...
I'll sleep in my bedroom.
I'm sorry I can only
offer you the sofa.
Good night.
What just happened?
Professor.
I'm so sorry.
Forget about it.
But you see...
I wasn't joking at all.
Professor.
Don't do that.
But WHY?
What do you mean, “Why?“
Come on...
I'm just a man you met today.
- Why?
- Is that wrong?
I'm not saying, you can't do that.
Well... you can't do that.
My nose is sharp...
I can smell a man hungry for sex.
You do want to have sex
with me, don't you?
Even if that was true...
obviously, I can't.
So I'll do it alone and you just watch.
Professor.
It feels good!
What's that?
Why did you tie me up?
Enough fooling around.
Set me free.
Hey, Papa was born the same year.
Can I call you 'Papa?
Enough, it's not a good joke.
So, this Mayumi is your wife?
Stop that.
Did you...
Professor, it doesn't look good.
A man of your status being so naughty...
What? But you assaulted me.
How about asking your wife's opinion?
She would...
Until she comes back...
you're gonna do as we tell you.
If you don't, we'll send her this.
Don't, we're trying to mend our marriage.
You mean, your marriage is
in bad shape?
Why is that?
That's none of your business.
Don't tell us you cheated on her?
Did I guess right?
A disgraced Professor
who had to resign.
Ain't that great?
What do you want?
Do I have to explain?
Don't do that.
It seems you like it.
Nami, can you look this way?
Yeah, good shot.
"Hey"-
Can you lick me?
There!
Good, you're doing good.
This feels good.
You don't mind, right?
You came already?
Good boy.
Who are you?
What do you want?
We want your body.
What's that?
Hold you. We want to have sex.
That's silly.
If you satisfy us, we'll go quietly.
Before your wife comes back.
Look at this, top quality meat.
Let's have a barbecue.
May:
Let's have meat!
I did it!
Look! Top quality charcoal.
Can we use it?
He wanted to impress his wife.
How impressive.
Indeed.
A disobedient Professor.
What are you doing?
That charcoal was hard to light.
It's because it's long-lasting charcoal.
You think we care?
"Tell us, Professor"
You told us to enjoy and
make ourselves at home.
Make yourselves at home?
Now you're going too far.
Disgusting raw meat!
How come men who are
so bad at cooking...
insist on having barbecues?
Why are you doing all this?
I already told you.
We want to have sex.
You girls don't have
to go to all that trouble
to find a lay in town.
You really don't get it, do you?
“Please stop."
"Let me go"
“No, don't do that'!
While his mouth says 'no',
his body says 'yes'
This is what gives us pleasure.
We're thrill-seekers.
You're crazy.
Why?
Men want the same thing.
A man forces himself on a woman...
while she cries and kicks
and begs for mercy.
And he finds it delightful
that she's wet anyway.
Why can't women have
the same kind of fun?
I'm not that kind of man.
You like to be forced, then.
I don't.
Which are you, then?
Why should I have to choose?
Isn't the world divided between...
those who do and those who are done?
It's not about do or be done.
Common people don't think like that.
Common people?
Common people get married,
and care for each other.
Goodness, you can't be
talking about 'love'?
That's it.
You mean, you girls don't
believe in love?
When you have good sex,
who cares about love?
Without marriage, how can you
know whose kid it is?
What do you mean?
When the baby is born,
we take good care of it.
A poor kid who doesn't
even know its father?
Why?
Why is he a poor kid if he
doesn't know his father?
A kid needs to grow up with its father.
Look at you, isn't a kid better
off without a father like you?
What are you saying?
Give me a break!
You believe you're indispensable
to the growth of a child?
Kids are the fruits of love.
It's irresponsible
to bear kids without love.
If love is the fuel necessary
for raising a child...
what happens to the kid if
the couple runs out of fuel?
There's nothing more
important than raising a child.
A child is what binds a couple together.
So the child is your tool
to hold her hostage?
I didn't say that!
Those who invented this concept.
Are Western despots who needed it
to keep the masses under control
by dividing them into families.
Since you're a historian you
probably understand that.
Originally, humans are born
to live free of any bonds.
Right?
I agree.
I like to give men pleasure
and I enjoy it too.
Now. you just tried to escape...
What should we do with you?
Look how cute this is.
Which one do you like?
Huh?
Now, chose a scrunchy.
I choose and then what?
You can't decide?
Why should I?
OK, you can wear both.
That's a great idea.
Hey, what? Don't do that.
It's cute! It's so cute!
This way the blood flow
is held at the base...
and your erection lasts longer.
We should have used it the first time.
If I fold it once and then twice,
it doubles the effect.
Ouch! seep!
Papa, otherwise you come too quickly!
It's no fun for your little girl!
If you tie it for too
long, you risk necrosis.
Right!
Look, like this.
It's amazing!
It's so hard!
No.
Let me go! No!
You'll be fine!
Soon you'll enjoy it.
Right?
Help me!
- Help me!
- Shut up!
You keep quiet!
We mean it!
Can I help you?
Ne you...
I'm Mr. Yoshimura, the Park Ranger.
Is the Professor there?
You are Mr. Yoshimura?
He told me about you.
I'm Mayumi, his wife.
Such a young wife.
Thank you for the compliment.
Do you have business with my husband?
I was supposed to give
him a call today...
but the line was busy.
We had an interview today.
Right, it seems that the
storm cut off our line.
Where is the Professor?
He went out early this morning.
Are you on your own?
I do not know where he went.
Maybe he went to Ehara...
But the road to Ehara
got flooded last night.
Help me... Help me... Help me...
He took his phone with him,
so you should probably call him.
NM see.
I'll do that.
Excuse me.
His car is still here.
Right, he didn't feel like driving.
He called a taxi
He took a taxi this morning.
Yes.
I see.
I guess your husband told you...
that there's a murderer
in the neighborhood.
They nicknamed him Jack-the-Ripper.
Ks, he told me about it.
You'd better lock yourself inside.
Right, understood.
See you.
I'm back.
He made so much noise that
I feared he'd be heard.
She gave you pleasure.
You should have been quiet.
How did you drive him away?
I pretended to be the wife.
He was surprised I was so young.
Well done.
Such a young wife.
You have to earn her.
- Look at that.
- Ouch! Ouch!
That Mr. Yoshimura seems
to be well endowed.
I bet he'd come many times.
Really? Let's do him next!
He warned me about Jack-the-Ripper.
He did?
Soon we'll have to move to another area.
But that Mr. Yoshimura sounds very sexy.
We should visit him before we move on.
No way, are you...
Jack-the-Ripper is not a man?
He could be a man.
Or he could be a woman.
He could be just one person.
Or there could be more than one.
Nobody knows since all the
potential witnesses have been killed.
You're going to kill me?
Be quiet.
Look at him!
You feared for your life?
Well done.
It's gone purple but it's still fine.
Oh Papa, come on.
You're pissing yourself.
He's not hard anymore.
Men are so high maintenance.
Is that how grateful you are?
What's wrong with it?
What can I do about it?
After all, your only redeeming
quality is your erection.
Ouch! Ouch!
If you can't get it up, what's
the point of keeping you alive?
You become useless.
I beg you! Don't kill me!
Look, an expensive wine.
That's the...
What is it?
It's from the year 1999.
Let's drink it.
This is the year Mayumi
and I got married.
Now that's great.
And when did you get married?
I just told you, in 1999.
What day is the anniversary?
It's In June... I mean in May.
Damn, I can't recall the day.
You can't even remember that?
If you care that little, what's
the point of the occasion?
Papa, you're a disgrace.
Papa, do you remember my birthday?
The hell if I know!
You don't?
That's hurtful.
How would I know your birthday?
You don't remember my birthday?
That's hurtful?
What terrible father can't
remember his daughter's birthday?
What the hell did I do to you?
I helped you out of kindness.
But forgetting one's
Wedding's anniversary...
How could we sympathize
with a person like you?
You criticize me, but you have no clue
how much a man has to remember.
We don't have the kind of memory
for dates that women have.
You men have such a hard life...
I had no clue.
I do everything I can.
I try to make Mayumi happy.
I'm doing my best.
How about this wine?
I wanted to enjoy it here with Mayumi.
But now she's gone.
She had to.
You wanted to warm her up
with the wine.
Please, don't do that!
Mayumi will have to clean up your mess.
No, you'll clean it up!
If your only contribution
is the barbecue...
it's all about your own pleasure.
But this time you'll have to clean up.
What are you talking about?
I'm always so careful
to keep everything clean.
You're so careful just because
you don't want to clean?
You're really pathetic.
Look, are they handmade?
Don't touch them.
With your names and all...
Did you make these yourself, Professor?
creepy-
What was that?
It will help you regain your
vigor and last all night.
Professor, it feels so good!
It feels so good!
Amazing!
Professor, it feels so good!
Can you feel it, Professor?
I'm sorry.
What?
What are you apologizing for?
I'm sorry that the cover is dirty.
And for what else?
I'm sorry about the anniversary.
What anniversary?
I'm sorry I forgot our
wedding anniversary.
There's something else.
I'm sorry I slept with
one of my students!
You finally apologize for it.
Such a good boy.
But your apologies are
not needed anymore.
That was a long time ago.
Look, there's still something.
This one goes into your bag.
Alright.
We're all done?
OK.
Let's go then.
Bye-bye.
Oh, I forgot my hair scrunchy
on the Professor.
It's OK, I untied his hands.
He can manage on his own.
You're right.
Where should we go next?
The weather is getting cold.
I'd like a warmer climate.
I heard it's easier to gain
the trust of Southern people.
Why?
Maybe because the weather is warmer...
so their heart is warmer too.
Whatever.
Harada District Park Ranger
Thank you for the ride.
Are you there? You didn't
pick up the phone.
What's that?
Hey? Dear?
Dear!
What are you doing?
Now I have to clean up your mess'
Are you crazy?
A man pisses standing up!