Wang Jing
Could it be...
Impossible.
Zhao Wan Wan.
Don't talk nonsense.
Zhao Wan Wan...
Yes, Brother Jian.
Don't scare us.
No, I'm sure
Others don't know.
Don't you know that?
Fight back!
What are you doing?
Still...
What should I do?
What the hell?
I don't believe it.
It must be done by someone.
I don't care who it is.
Come out now!
Let's play fair.
Don't play dirty behind my back.
Okay.
It must be the monitor
Chen Chaoyang
Why are you always picking on me?
Did I offend you?
I'm not targeting you.
We're all in the secret room.
You're the only one outside.
You said you were in the secret room too.
But what did he do in the secret room?
in the secret room.
You must want to avenge Zhao Wan Wan.
Why would I avenge Zhao Wan Wan?
Everyone knows what happened back then.
You were with Zhao Wan Wan back then.
I saw all the photos.
Let me show you something nice.
It's awesome.
Don't grab it.
Take one last look.
Enough
Chen Chaoyang you're too much, you're dirty
Chen Chaoyang don't talk nonsense
The school said the photo was P
Zhao Wan Wan has left for so long.
Why are you still badmouthing her?
Can you show some respect
Chen Chaoyang
When I was in school, I suspected you
I suspected it was you.
I didn't even say anything about you. How dare you?
I didn't.
The whole school knows about this.
I only said it might be you.
Think whatever you want.
I don't want to argue with you.
I shouldn't have come here today.
Do whatever you want.
I'm leaving.
You can't leave.
You haven't made it clear.
What do you want?
What do I want to do? I want to leave.
You want to leave after you finish us?
How is that possible?
Tell me.
I won't.
Say it or not?
You...
Li Jian, what are you doing?
If you don't make it clear today,
none of you can leave.
Let's talk.
I didn't say I'm the monitor
Stop fighting.
We've fallen into the trap of the organizer.
Lin Yu, take the monitor to bandage first.
I'll go find the medicine box
Chen Chaoyang
I have something to tell you
Monitor.
I trust you.
You're our former monitor.
Even if you want to restore her dignity,
I believe you won't use this method.
What monitor?
I'm no longer your monitor.
And you never
as a monitor.
Monitor
Monitor!
I found the medicine.
Monitor
I saw it anyway
I wouldn't have come
I wouldn't have come.
The school sent you an email.
It can't be right now.
Hang in there.
Do you know why I didn't tell you
what happened in the secret room?
The game starts now!
Stop joking. Let me out!
Hello?
Do you know how hot it is inside?
Let me out!
Remove your disguise.
I'm not.
Okay.
Okay?
Remove your disguise.
You won't let me take off my clothes, will you?
Remove your disguise
I took off my wig
and forced me to take off all the wigs.
and took photos for me.
Take nude photos for me.
I can't get out.
Let me out!
Who is it?
It would be fine if it was a game.
Now it seems
this is not just a game.
I don't care who it is.
Li Jian
Chen Chaoyang
or you
It doesn't matter.
When I was in school,
you spread the Yellow Quogue of Zhao Wan Wan and me.
just to humiliate me.
I did it.
The actor.
Lanbo.
Luan Yujia.
Lin.
Thank you, Liu, Zhu.
Sun Hao.
to perform.
Wang Fu Yu, Yang Qiming, Li Yuyang, Song, Yoon. Meng Yihan, Wang Shuo,
Wang Fu Yu, Yang Qiming, Li Yuyang, Song, Yoon. Meng Yihan Wang Shuo
Cui, Liu Yuhan, Yu Xinrui, Dong Meiling. Anki Wang, Xiao Junyi.
Lin Tian Jing, Yue Hua Feng, Gu Jinhui, Donglu Yan. Hu Yanmeng, Xie Zhaoyu.
Lin Tian Jing, Yue Hua Qing, Gu Jinhui, Donglu Yan. Hu Yanmeng, Xie Zhaoyu, Luo Qianqian.
Product.
Zhang Minfei, Huang Li, Zhou Hao
Producer.
Allen.
IP company.
Twinkle.
Screenwriter.
Lu Yao.
Director team.
Director.
Tian Tian.
Doggie.
Kim Miu.
Roxy
Producer team
Kim Ja-qi.
Jin Ziqi.
Li Tao.
Photography team.
Art team.
Golden Bull.
Costume team.
Lighting Team.
The recording team.
The venue team.
The venue.
Driver team.
An audition company.
Simple Castinging.
Li Nuo.
Late production company.
to create an idler (Beijing) film and cultural company.
Sun Di
Voice instructor, Jose.
Rose.
Jose.
Product Company.
Beijing Water Thinking Technology Development Co., Ltd.
In Sight (Chongqing) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Chengdu Minhui Film.
(The First Producer)
The first producer,
Zhejiang Ruohong Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
of Zhejiang Ruohong Cultural Media Co.,Ltd.
Beijing Tiantian Film Co., Ltd.