Wang Jing
When I was in school,
the Yellow Song of Zhao Wan Wan and me.
just to humiliate me.
I did it.
I'm not doing well.
I stayed up late every day
My hair is gone.
I can't make much money.
I spent all my savings
to invest in business with my friends.
I was cheated by my friends.
I'm not as good as you guys.
You all drove here, right?
I rode an electric bike.
I was afraid you would see me.
I parked my car at the foot of the mountain.
I walked up on my own.
I didn't want to come because I was afraid you would see me.
my real situation.
Monitor
It doesn't matter.
If my wife wasn't pregnant,
I could have died here.
But I just want to leave this place.
I can't let my child
have no father.
Monitor, don't worry.
We'll be fine.
We'll leave together tomorrow morning.
Yes, monitor
Let's go together tomorrow morning.
Monitor I
Chen Chaoyang don't worry
Everyone is nervous now
You said the monitor is a suspect.
Do you have evidence?
I didn't say it was him.
I just said I know.
Lin Shanshan must have heard it too.
Besides,
he couldn't say it.
What did he do in the secret room?
I did it for everyone.
I know your intention is good.
I'm just afraid the monitor might think
you said that
because of your personal grudge.
There's no personal grudge between us.
He's the one who slandered us.
It was his fault.
I'm a victim too. It has nothing to do with me.
I was also framed.
Okay.
You're anxious again.
Everyone knows what happened back then.
Someone posted
and the monitor.
Didn't we prove it was P later?
Right?
Yes.
But Zhao Wan Wan
jumped off the building because of this.
It has nothing to do with that.
Zhao Wan Wan jumped off the building
were posted two weeks later.
she jumped off the building.
It has nothing to do with the photo.
I didn't post it.
I didn't send it either.
I just saw it.
What do you think it has to do with?
How would I know?
Stop eating.
Who do you think it is?
It's not me anyway.
I don't care who it is.
Don't let me catch you.
I was the only one who bullied others before.
No one has ever bullied me.
Aren't you afraid?
I'm afraid.
If he wanted to kill me,
I would have died.
Now that I'm alive,
that means he doesn't dare to.
Besides,
you should be the one who should be scared.
When have I ever been afraid of others?
I just want to know who it is.
I can't let them lead me around all the time.
If it weren't for the rain and no car,
I would have left.
Could it be Lin Yu?
for his Zhao Wan Wan?
Lin Yu.
If Lin Yu really cared about Zhao Wan Wan,
he wouldn't have left her alone ten years ago.
That's Cheng Si.
Cheng Si?
Look at her. Does she dare?
You're right.
She's still like a bunny
like a bunny in school.
Who is that?
Don't let me catch you.
Then why did you say
this has something to do with the monitor?
Zhao Wan Wan called Ruan Zhang.
He didn't answer it
Chen Chaoyang you're too much You're dirty
You dare to do it but you dare not admit it
It's not me.
It's your photo.
Ask them if they were edited.
Ask Ruan Zhang if this is P.
Unfortunately, the monitor didn't come today.
I don't know if he's afraid or running away
Chen Chaoyang wait and see
I'm afraid of you
I'll wait for you on the rooftop.
Monitor, answer the phone.
Hello, monitor.
Do you know
about us.
They even gave us photos.
Can you come back and explain?
What do you mean?
I'm a girl.
I've been criticized at school.
at school?
She can't explain it alone.
That's why she did that.
She can explain it alone.
She didn't even have a chance to explain.
When the photo was released,
her only family
Her grandma is seriously ill.
Hello?
I'm...
What?
Okay.
She's been with the hospital.
and waited for her to come back.
everyone thought it was true.
She jumped off a building a few days later.
Yes, because her grandma passed away,
because her grandma passed away.
That's why she jumped off the building.
It has nothing to do with the photo.
It has nothing to do with us, right?
Who did this to us?
Who?
I must have mistaken.
Rest early.
We'll talk tomorrow morning.
I just want to borrow some money.
Why is it so hard?
Stop thinking about it.
With your brain,
with your brain.
Although I'm not smart,
but I'm healthy.
Do you want to take a shower?
It's not impossible.
Go back and wash.
What's wrong with you?
Get lost.
Shanshan.
Okay, I'll go back and wash up.
Actor table.
Lanbo.
Cheng Si.
Lin Shan.
Zhu.
Sun Hao.
to perform.
Wang Fuyu, Yang Qiming, Song Yuyang. Meng Yihan. Wang Shuo.
Lin Tian Jing, Yue Hua Feng, Gu Jinhui, Donglu Yan. Hu Yanmeng, Xie Zhaoyu, Luo Qianqian.
Lin Tian Jing, Yue Hua Feng, Gu Jin Hui, Dong Lu Yan. Hu Yanmeng, Xie Zhaoyu, Luo Qianqian.
Product.
Zhang Minfei, Huang Li, Zhou Hao
Producer.
Allen.
IP company.
Twinkle.
Screenwriter.
Lu Yao.
Director team.
Tian Tian.
Doggie.
Kim Miu.
Roxy
The production team
Li Tao.
Photography team.
Mr. Kim.
Art team.
Golden Bull.
Costume team.
Lighting Team.
The recording team.
Voice guide Zhang average
The venue.
Driver team.
Audition company.
An audition company.
Simple Castinging.
Li Nuo.
Late production company.
to create an idler (Beijing) film and cultural company.
Sun Di
Rose.
Jose.
Zhao Xiu Yuan.
Product company.
Beijing Water Thinking Technology Development Co., Ltd.
In Sight (Chongqing) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Chengdu Minhui Film.
(The First Producer)
The first producer,
Zhejiang Ruohong Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
of Zhejiang Ruohong Cultural Media Co.,Ltd.
Beijing Tiantian Film Co., Ltd.