♪It's a sordid story that you've made♪
♪Up to fill my mind with doubts and pain♪
♪Blood I shed, and tears I wept,
are you satisfied?♪
♪Enjoying what's mine♪
♪Have you found a way
to bury guilt and shame♪
♪I'm coming back to life♪
♪Through the seven gates of death♪
♪I'm coming back survived♪
♪Feeling great to see you fall♪
♪I'm taking back what's mine♪
♪Bringing horror to the battlefield♪
♪Lay it to waste♪
♪Til the day my kingdom is reclaimed♪
=Her Blaze=
=Episode 15=
Hello, Miss Rao.
We finally meet.
I am an actuary
of the Beauty Pearl Society.
The instructions I received
are to cooperate with you fully.
Go ahead.
what else do you need me to do?
I need to gain access
to an offshore account.
(Username and Password)
(SECURE CONNECTION)
(Evil acts are carried out
with impunity,)
(vainly trying to cover
the sky with one hand.)
(But I know)
(the destination I want)
(is right before my eyes.)
(Bai Muran,)
(do you still remember the knife
that pushed me into the abyss?)
(Linwei Alley - Lane 21)
Bai Xia.
Bai Xia!
Hey, Rao Yuci.
Don't forget,
you have a weakness too.
You dragged Bai Xia into this
to make me suffer.
Don't think you'll have it easy either.
I won't let your parents off the hook.
(Rao Shusheng,
Examination Item: Brain MRI Plain Scan)
Hello?
Zhang.
Rao Shusheng, if you don't pay
back the money,
I'm going to corner you at your house.
Say something!
Hippocampal cerebral infarction.
The doctor said
I can't take any more shocks.
Liangliang,
(Rao Shusheng)
it was you who told me
to buy those houses in Linwei Alley.
You have
to help me settle the money I owe.
Otherwise,
I'm a dead man.
Don't you know
what has happened, Mr. Rao?
I know.
Between you and Yuci,
there might be a misunderstanding.
There is no misunderstanding
between Rao Yuci and me.
Do you want to hear our story?
No need.
I just want you to help me.
I'm truly at the end of my rope.
You really don't care
about your daughter at all.
That Rao Yuci and I
have come to this point,
you've been a huge help, Mr. Rao.
You've always thought she was a monster.
But have you ever considered
that the biggest monster
is you?
You failed in your futures investment.
I used Chuxia's clients
and funds to help you
just to drive a wedge
between you and Rao Yuci.
You thought she was a lunatic
and agreed to let her
enter the treatment center.
But you didn't know
that the knife she used to stab Mrs. Rao
was placed under the printer
in advance by Bai Muran on my orders.
Zhaohe,
I was wrong.
Your failed investment in Linwei Alley
was because
I sought you out intentionally.
The purpose
was to aggravate the conflict
between you and your daughter
to make the resentment run deeper.
Zhaohe,
I regret it.
I've failed our daughter.
I've failed Yuci!
Did you really think
I was helping you make money?
- You were just the first step
- I was wrong.
in my plan to strike at Rao Yuci.
I was wrong.
Now, your daughter hates you to death.
She won't save you.
And I won't save you either.
No one will save you.
Look, what happened to him?
Someone fell over there!
Call an ambulance, quick!
(Waiting Area)
(Emergency Room)
The doctor said
he had a hippocampal
cerebral infarction.
The chances of him
waking up are unknown.
How is he?
Out of danger.
But we don't know
when he will regain consciousness.
The score I'm going to settle
might end up hurting me too.
If anything happens to me,
I can't let my mother
face all this alone.
(Stocks: Sell All)
(Baiying Business Investigation)
I called you all here today
to calculate exactly how much
Rao Shusheng owes.
How much do I need to pay back?
The loan agreement we have
states it very clearly.
Here, give it to me.
Give me the IOU first.
It's been six months.
The interest has piled up.
If you don't pay now,
we will take legal action.
Please rest assured.
Once Miss Rao and I
have verified everything,
the payments will be transferred
successively into each of your accounts.
(Paying the debt)
(is not for Rao Shusheng)
(but for my mother.)
Was my acting okay?
You played the part very well.
It was completely
beyond my expectations.
Thank you.
Ms. Bai Xia,
I've leased this house
for three years.
You and Mr. Xu
can live here with peace of mind.
Don't worry about the rent or anything.
No, no.
That won't do.
How can we take advantage
of you like this?
This is what I owe you.
You owe me?
You've been helping me all along.
How can you owe me?
Ms. Bai Xia,
there are some things
I can't tell you right now.
Soon,
I'll be away for a while.
You and Mr. Xu
just live here comfortably.
Yuci...
While you're out there,
remember to eat on time.
Thank you, Ms. Bai Xia.
Does your situation
have something to do with Liangliang?
Finally, we meet, Ms. Bai.
I am an actuary
of the Beauty Pearl Society.
There are so many rumors
about the Beauty Pearl Society now.
How do I know you're not a fraud?
As proof,
not only do we know
what's on your mind, Ms. Bai,
but we also know the answers you want.
In fact,
we also know everything
between you and Rao Yuci.
The Beauty Pearl Society
wants to make a deal with you.
Place the bug
in Jiang Dongchao's office.
You want me to betray Mr. Jiang?
Betraying Jiang Dongchao
is something you've done before,
only you didn't succeed.
Isn't that right?
Finish this task,
and the Beauty Pearl Society will help you
find the person in the photo.
Rest assured, Ms. Bai.
If this is successful,
it will certainly help improve
your status in Lysen.
You don't trust me?
Bai Liangliang,
your good friend Rao Yuci
is smarter than you.
Bai Liangliang...
You're so much like I was
when I was young.
Your ambition is showing.
Especially you, Bai Liangliang.
Why do you always want
to be the one waiting to swoop in?
Hello, Miss Gao.
The acquisition plan
for those green building
materials companies has been concluded.
Mr. Jiang, you don't need to worry.
What do you mean?
I want to resign.
I think what you need
isn't me,
but a bargaining chip
to break free from Baiye,
steady Mr. Li,
and continue
to control Lysen.
Yes.
You are my greatest bargaining chip.
Rao Yuci,
I know your character.
You wouldn't resign rashly.
As for the reason behind it,
if you don't want to say, I won't force you.
I'll keep this for you for now.
(Lysen Group)
Go and take a long vacation
with peace of mind.
Mr. Jiang, why don't you
take a look at this?
I think Mr. Li
would also be very interested.
This is Li Qiang's
capital flow record
(Haoyu Shengbo)
on an offshore gambling platform.
I traced
the system architect of the platform,
and by following the trail,
I found a linked
private bank account.
This is the name
of the account holder.
(Muran Bai)
Bai Muran.
These are the contracts
for those green building
materials companies.
They've all been processed.
Review them when you have time.
You were right about one thing.
Bosi just announced publicly
that their strategic direction
has shifted
to existing housing renovation.
Unexpectedly,
this Beauty Pearl Society
suddenly appeared.
Have you thought of
how to help Lysen out of this trouble?
If it were you, what would you do?
You've been at Lysen for so many years,
you must have your own judgment.
I believe you know what to do,
even if one day
I'm no longer at Lysen.
What do you mean, you won't be at Lysen?
Dept 3
used to be
the underdog in Lysen,
but now everyone
is in their proper place.
And Director Ren is looking out for us.
I am very much at ease.
Since I'm at ease,
I can go and settle
some of my own affairs.
What are you going to settle?
Yuci.
Didn't I say it before?
I said very soon,
everyone and everything
will return to their rightful owners.
I know you don't care,
but the position
has always been yours.
I have some business.
I won't be back today.
Alright, Mr. Jiang.
Hello, Ms. Bai.
Are you a woman of your word?
After it's done,
all the money
will be cleanly
transferred to your husband's account.
Mr. Jiang won't find out.
Besides,
by the time he does,
we will have already succeeded.
Helping Mr. Li get rid of Mr. Jiang
is the outcome
everyone wants to see.
Fine.
It's a deal.
(Li Qiang)
Dad,
(Six months ago)
I just wanted to prove
myself to you.
You know
that my uncles look down on me.
If I didn't have
a strong teammate right now,
I really couldn't hold on.
If I were to give up now,
I'd truly have no more chances.
Please accept my condolences.
I've been very saddened
(Li Qiang)
by Li Qiang's passing too.
But this matter
has always been
a mystery in my heart.
Now, the truth is right here.
What a coincidence.
Mr. Chen has been
on leave for many days.
From the time Mr. Chen
arrived five years ago until now,
this is his first time taking leave.
As a volunteer teacher,
it's not easy at all.
He has always
stayed with the children.
He came here five years ago?
Yes,
five years ago.
Actually, Mr. Chen's parents
were also deaf-mutes.
When he was little,
his parents both passed away
in an accident.
But Mr. Chen
didn't give up hope on life.
Not only did he heal himself,
but he also helped and healed
the children here,
allowing them to grow up happily.
(Nuan, Rao Yuci)
(Linwei Alley Snack Street)
Hello, Yuci.
Mr. Chen didn't come today.
I think the two of you
are quite alike.
Every time Mr. Chen comes,
just like you,
he looks around everywhere
to see if you're here.
Nuan is really smart
and sensible.
Was Nuan
born this way?
When she was first born,
we all thought
we were blessed with
an exceptionally well-behaved child.
She didn't cry or make a fuss.
♪And wash away
the mud that stains your soul♪
All these years,
Nuan has always followed us,
running around everywhere.
Fortunately, thanks to you and Mr. Chen,
we've been able
to do business here peacefully.
Nuan
can also stay by our side for school.
♪Wander freely through the thorns♪
♪Keep walking through the light♪
♪Fate is absurd, don't stop for anyone♪
What does Nuan want to tell me?
She says it's Mr. Chen's birthday.
Being alone makes him
very lonely and sad.
She wants to draw a heart for Mr. Chen.
♪I'm sorry,
I still owe myself these words♪
♪This pathetic kindness♪
♪Is the last shred of human heart♪
♪When the cold wind passes
it takes the past away♪
(Reminiscence Alley)
(Trademark Registration: Nuan's Sweets)
It's all processed?
Registration is complete.
From now on, Nuan's Sweets
will be your brand name.
Now that you have a brand,
if anyone wants to collaborate later,
(Business Proposal for Financing)
just show them this.
♪I will stay behind
and wait for your eyes♪
♪To rebuild
the same flesh and soul again♪
What about you?
I might have to go on a long trip.
I don't know if I'll be back.
♪Fate is absurd, don't stop for anyone♪
Please help me give this
to Mr. Chen.
Won't you give it to him personally?
I'm afraid there won't be time.
Are you ready?
Friends from Dept 3, give me a smile.
Good.
Three,
two,
one.
Keep it up!
(After leaving Xinkang,)
(the most meaningful thing I've done)
(was helping these people
create a more stable life.)
(It fulfilled my small ideal.)
(It's them)
(who let me feel warmth and beauty.)
♪Will finally bloom forever♪
I've already done as you said.
Tell me where he is.
Have you thought it through, Ms. Bai?
Facing the past
might not be
what you imagined.
Tell me where he is.
(Chongguangli Lane 2)
(Why is it here?)
(A secret of mine is hidden deep here.)
(This is Professor Han's home.)
(How could the actuary)
(from Beauty Pearl Society
know this address?)
Have you thought it through, Ms. Bai?
Facing the past
might not be
what you imagined.
As for us,
from the theoretical application
of financial mathematics
(Five years ago)
to practical work analysis,
(Han Dehai)
we still have a long way to go.
My defense is over.
(School of Economics and Management-
Financial Maths. Thanks for watching.)
Professor Han,
my grades are good enough.
Why can't I do research?
(Macroeconomics)
Liangliang,
financial mathematics
is a theoretical science.
It requires one's full devotion.
Given your current
family situation,
can it support you
to continue on this path
of theoretical research?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
Perhaps
I was a bit too direct.
But your advisor
has already told me
about your family situation.
Your father had a stroke.
I think you should find a job
as soon as possible
to help ease the pressure at home.
Liangliang, have some fruit.
I saw Professor Han here just now.
He wanted me
to apply for his grad program.
He brought me this book, "Macroeconomics."
It has his notes inside.
I haven't had time to look at it.
Why don't you take it
and read it first?
No need.
Liangliang, come on in.
Yes?
Yes, Professor Han.
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
You...
What do you think?
You're trying to frame me.
No one will believe you.
In this environment,
it's just the two of us.
As long as I have these clothes,
no one will believe you.
This is a false accusation.
Professor Han!
Mr. Han, what are you doing?
You pervert, stay away!
Bai Liangliang, you're framing me!
(Finance Department Office)
Hello?
I want to report a teacher.
Professor Han,
are you okay?
I didn't do anything.
I... I...
I didn't do anything!
Just leave.
Liangliang,
they say Professor Han resigned
because someone reported him.
Reported him for what?
Something inappropriate
between a man and a woman.
I was supposed to be fast-tracked
as his graduate student.
Then, this suddenly happened.
I always thought Professor Han
was a very good person.
What do you think?
Do you think it's true?
You are...
Are...
Are you Liangliang?
It's Dad.
Dad!
Where...
Where are you?
Are you alright?
I thought something happened to you.
Dad.
Liangliang.
Why didn't you want me anymore?
Do you...
Do you know how I survived
the days after you left?
Do you know
that my life has completely changed?
You were the only one
who gave me happiness,
but then you abandoned me.
Do you know how much I've suffered?
I'm sorry.
I don't want you to say you're sorry.
I don't want to hear it.
I don't!
You are my father.
Come.
Cheer up.
Look over there.
At the most important moment of my life,
where were you?
When I decided to become a bad person,
all covered in thorns,
where were you?
When I should have
learned how to love others,
where were you?
All these years,
if you had just given me one call
and contacted me once,
I could have let go of the past.
I could have put everything down.
I could have forgiven
everyone who hurt me
and forgiven all the injustice.
But you didn't.
You were the only person
in this world who loved me.
You were the only one who loved me.
Even you didn't want me.
Why didn't you want me?
Liangliang,
it's not that I abandoned you.
It's that your mother and I
were doing our best to find a way
to bring everything back
to the right track.
The right track?
What do you mean by the "right track?"
Actually,
I am not your biological father.
I could never have children.
I...
I really wanted to adopt one.
Later,
someone brought over a baby.
It was you.
The first time I saw you,
your little hand
just grabbed onto me.
At that moment, I felt
that you were a daughter
sent to me by God.
So I kept you.
But who knew that six years later,
your biological mother
would find me with the police.
She said you
were abducted by a neighbor.
You had been trafficked several times.
Come home with me.
Your mother had also been
looking for you for six years.
Liangliang.
I couldn't bear to let you go back then.
I was heartbroken, too. I...
But you
were someone else's child, after all.
That's not right.
It's Rao Yuci.
It's Rao Yuci who sent you
to say these things to me, right?
I don't know her.
I don't know this person.
It's Rao Yuci.
It's Rao Yuci and Bai Xia.
They've teamed up against me.
They're the ones who sent you here!
It's Rao Yuci!
They sent you here!
Liangliang.
It's Rao Yuci!
(Bai Liangliang,)
(I just want you to taste)
(this kind of heart-piercing pain)
(because you once inflicted)
(the same pain on me.)
(Everyone has an old dream
they'd rather not remember.)
(But in your old dream,)
(there lies your cruelty)
(and your resentment.)
(After I was discharged,)
(I chose to start over here)
(just for today)
(so that here,)
(you would have no choice but to face)
(the karmic consequences you've hidden.)
That knife is still here.
It's just that
it's not meant for you.
=Episode 15=
(Inner Demon)
(All animals in this production
were treated humanely)
♪Take a breath and swallow
the words you couldn't say♪
♪No need to force your heart anymore♪
♪Searching for the season
we once missed♪
♪Leave this place,
though wounded still stay strong♪
♪You must believe
one day the rain will fall♪
♪And wash away the mud
that stains your soul♪
♪Find your freedom in the wild♪
♪Take your stride and move ahead♪
♪I will stay behind
and wait for your eyes♪
♪To rebuild
the same flesh and soul again♪
♪Wander freely through the thorns♪
♪Keep walking through the light♪
♪Fate is absurd, don't stop for anyone♪
♪What you dare to lose
will one day be your own♪
♪I'm sorry, I still owe you these words♪
♪An apology that came too late♪
♪Yet it's also the path
that saves my soul♪
♪When the cold wind
passes it takes the past away♪
♪You must believe and stand unwavering♪
♪There will be hands
to pull you from the deep♪
♪Find your freedom in the silence♪
♪Let your wounds be mended♪
♪Gray is not the past
and pain is not a shame♪
♪Sometimes the sunlight
makes the world look crueler♪
♪Wander through the echoes of regret♪
♪Be forgiven and be sheltered♪
♪After everything shatters,
hold my hand♪
♪A flower reborn
will finally bloom forever♪