In the ancient
Mesopotamian plains,
there lived the beautiful
goddess Inanna.
Legend says
she was the goddess of love and justice.
Then, one day,
Inanna, high in the heavens,
suddenly heard
a wail from the underworld.
It was the voice
of her younger sister,
Ereshkigal, Queen of the Underworld.
So,
Inanna passed through
the narrow Seven Gates of the Underworld
to visit her suffering sister.
But unexpectedly,
Ereshkigal screamed frantically,
"I will grind her
into dead ashes!"
She repaid Inanna's kindness
with pure rage.
After that,
Inanna remained
forever in the painful
underworld.
While the furious
Ereshkigal
wore her sister's crown,
relishing the glory
that once belonged to her sister,
along with the power.
Your hand is injured.
Does it hurt?
How could you
hurt yourself like this?
Your wound
looks much better.
Xinkang is a qualified
and professional treatment center.
We adopt
a relatively systematic approach.
Don't worry,
this treatment is very safe
with minimal side effects.
For Rao Yuci's current condition,
it's the most suitable.
Thank you, Doctor.
Listen,
would it be possible for me
to visit her every day?
The patient's condition
is very unstable right now.
We don't recommend that family members
stay with her in her current state.
But...
I'm still worried.
Look at her.
I suspect
she...
She won't be able
to adapt to this environment.
Yuci,
I want to show you something.
This is your boyfriend,
Bai Muran.
We lied to you.
Your first boyfriend
liked me
long before he was even with you.
If it weren't for exploiting
your bit of genius,
how could he ever have fallen for you?
A girl who's never been in love
is really naive
and easy to fool.
Let me tell you some good news.
The company you led us to start,
Chuxia...
We successfully
sold it to the Lysen Group.
Public companies are great.
They gave us a huge sum of money
and even let me take
the Investment Director position.
Listen up.
Come to the meeting room.
This position
originally belonged to you.
But it's such a pity
that you
can only stay here now.
No telling how long you'll be here.
Your father and I
went to a lot of trouble
just to get you in here.
It seems the line
between genius and madman
is truly a thin one.
Let me go!
You're a lunatic.
You're just a lunatic!
Why is this woman tied up?
There's no other way.
The patient, Rao Yuci, has shown
severe mental abnormalities.
Her behavior is out of control,
and she has been violent.
So we must resort
to forcible restraint measures.
Calm down!
Tie her up.
Quick, hold her down!
Don't move.
Stop!
Be gentle with her!
No!
Listen to me.
I will definitely help you
take care of your parents.
Yuci...
My dear,
just rot in here.
Get up.
Let's go.
Yuci's mom, please calm down.
Mom!
Let me go!
All of you, let me go!
No! Let me go!
Let her go!
♪It's a sordid story that you've made♪
♪Up to fill my mind
with doubts and pain♪
♪Blood I shed, and tears I wept,
are you satisfied?♪
♪Enjoying what's mine♪
♪Have you found a way
to bury guilt and shame♪
♪I'm coming back to life♪
♪Through the seven gates of death♪
♪I'm coming back survived♪
♪Feeling great to see you fall♪
♪I'm taking back what's mine♪
♪Bringing horror to the battlefield♪
♪Lay it to waste♪
♪Til the day my kingdom is reclaimed♪
=Her Blaze=
=Episode 1=
(Three years later)
I was wondering, you know?
For two years,
someone has been paying the rent,
but no one has lived here.
Come on in. Welcome home.
Do you want me to find someone
to help you clean up?
No need, thanks.
Then, I'll be going.
Hello,
security office?
The milk tea
Ms. Bai from
Investment Dept 1 ordered is here.
(Lysen Group)
It's great to be in Investment Dept 1.
Ms. Bai is so generous,
buying milk tea for the whole team.
- Thanks for the tea, Ms. Bai!
- Thanks, Ms. Bai!
- Thank you.
(Bai Liangliang)
We get Ms. Bai's milk tea every Monday.
(Lysen Group Investment Dept 1)
(Xinkang Treatment Center)
Hello?
Miss Bai,
you asked me to keep
an eye on Rao Yuci, right?
She was discharged yesterday.
She left by herself.
No one picked her up.
Alright.
I understand.
Thank you, Doctor.
Goodbye.
Congratulations!
- Congrats on the founding of Chuxia!
Come on, let's take a photo.
One, two, three, yell "Chuxia!"
- Chuxia!
Many people ask me why
"Chuxia Business Investigation"
(Chuxia Business Investigation Sharing Conference)
sounds a bit strange
and perhaps a bit informal.
But they don't know
that the word "Chuxia"
holds a very special weight in my heart.
Today's agenda
is to come up
with a name for our company.
Right.
We need a good name
with a good meaning.
How about Chuxia?
Chuxia is right now.
In my life,
I have friendship...
And I have love.
- It's when I feel most complete.
- It's also our best time.
- Cheers!
Congratulations, Rao Yuci.
You are discharged.
Actually,
I've always had a question for you.
Based on our observations,
quite a long time ago,
you met the criteria for discharge.
But you kept finding
all sorts of excuses
to avoid the evaluation.
Why is that?
(I don't need to tell you the answer.)
(Three years.)
(The only thing that's changed
is the rules of the game.)
(As for me, I only need to
turn around and look back)
(this chessboard.)
(Black pieces, white pieces.)
(Kindness or evil.)
(Everything will return to my board.)
(Lysen Group.)
(During these three years,)
(I've gathered every piece
of information I could find.)
(Shareholding ratios of the four Li brothers.)
(Bai Liangliang is aiming for a high position at Lysen.)
(The higher she climbs,)
(Total investment)
(the harder I will make her fall.)
(I'm waiting.)
(Waiting for the right moment.)
(When all the information
comes together...)
(Li Wancheng)
(Jiang Dongchao)
(And then,)
(Bang.)
(Explosion.)
(Li's Restaurant.)
(Chuxia, Baiye Group)
(Investment Depts 1, 2, and 3,
Human Resources Department)
It's time for me to be discharged.
(Bai Liangliang.)
(The "blessings" you gave me,)
(I have always kept them in my heart.)
(For these past three years,)
(you were the reason
I was able to persevere.)
(I believe that one day,)
(I will be able to use those same words)
(to "bless" you back.)
(At 26, she sold the company to Lysen.)
(Chuxia was acquired, Bai Liangliang became a Lysen executive.
What is the underlying logic of her life?)
Three, two, one.
- Cheese!
Okay, we're done here.
Come over here.
(Thanks to Lysen Group for donating supplies)
Okay, easy, easy. Slow down.
Don't rush.
Hey there, kiddo.
What are you doing?
Ma'am, it's dead.
I want to take it home.
What a kind child.
This is for you.
Remember to clean your hands.
(Li Qiang)
Hello?
Liangliang,
I can't get in touch with Bai Muran.
And Mr. Jiang
isn't answering my calls either.
What should I do?
My dad might have found out.
Please, help me think of something.
I'm just a low-level employee.
What can I possibly do?
If you could help me
talk to Mr. Jiang,
maybe there's a way.
Otherwise, with a mess this big,
I...
The only thing left is to die.
Sounds like
that's the simplest way
to solve this.
(If I want to take down Bai Liangliang,)
(my first step)
(is to find)
(a breakthrough within Lysen Group.)
(And among Lysen's ruler,)
(subject,)
(father,)
(and son,)
(of all these people,)
(the one easiest to break)
(is Li Qiang.)
(A scandal involving Li Qiang)
(will definitely cause)
(a huge uproar at Lysen Group.)
(Li Qiang)
Welcome, everyone.
(Jiang Dongchao, CEO of Lysen Group)
The speech was well-written.
(Venture Capital Sharing Session)
It's my duty to serve you, Mr. Jiang.
And please believe
that the surprises I can bring you
go far beyond this, Mr. Jiang.
(Hello, the user you are calling
is currently unavailable.)
(Li Qiang)
(Please try again later.)
Let's go, let's grab a bottle of water.
Let's go.
Quick, quick!
Hurry up! Call the police!
Okay, okay.
(Jiang Dongchao)
(Farewell Hall)
Mr. Jiang.
I'm sorry.
(Li Wancheng, Chairman of Lysen Group)
Mr. Li is devastated
after losing his son.
He said he doesn't want to see anyone.
Not even me?
Mr. Jiang,
Mr. Li specifically instructed
that this is an internal memorial.
Only those who received an invitation
can attend to pay their respects.
So,
I'm truly sorry.
I understand.
Please convey my condolences to Mr. Li.
Take care.
He's gone.
Do it.
Yes, sir.
(The power struggle between Li Wancheng)
(and Jiang Dongchao at Lysen Group)
(is my best chance)
(to get in.)
Mr. Jiang!
Mr. Jiang, a question, please.
Will the negative impact
of this incident affect your position
as CEO of Lysen?
Do you have any new thoughts
on Lysen's stock price?
(Lysen Group)
How much of the family
office's money did he touch?
Some of it was dividends.
As for the rest, I really don't know.
How could you not know?
Mr. Jiang put you in charge
of the family office.
(Li Mingxuan, Lysen Group Investment Dept 1)
But there were several times
when Mr. Jiang met Li Qiang alone.
Li Mingxuan,
from now on,
keep your mouth tightly shut.
Ms. Bai, Mr. Jiang is looking for you.
We'll talk later.
Mr. Jiang.
(Notice to All Shareholders)
It seems you've seen it too, Ms. Bai.
It's dated before Li Qiang's death.
Li Wancheng and his brothers
had this planned all along
to push me out.
Am I right?
Mr. Li hasn't been involved
in operations for a long time.
What does he gain
from getting rid of you?
I assigned someone
to manage the family office funds.
The money may have been
misappropriated by his son,
but since his son jumped to his death,
isn't this debt
going to be pinned on me?
Do you think
there's a problem with Li Mingxuan?
But he told me...
He said what?
He just said
that Li Qiang used his shareholder status
to take the dividend money.
He's an adopted son, after all.
Even in death,
he's still being used.
They're determined to use this incident
to force me out.
However,
(Notice to All Shareholders)
who wins and who loses
is still undecided.
This major turn of events has triggered
an internal crisis for the group.
Lysen Group, listed in Hong Kong, China,
has seen its stock price
fluctuate wildly,
worsening an already
sluggish performance.
Although the man at the helm,
Jiang Dongchao,
leveraged his deep
Wall Street background
to lead the company's expansion
over the past decade,
even creating a stock market legend
three years ago,
it seems he too is struggling to reverse
the current predicament.
The market is now asking.
Is the golden age of Lysen Group
coming to an end?
We can meet now.
Who is coming?
The head of HR
is greeting them personally.
That's quite a reception.
I heard they're meeting someone
very important.
Mr. Jiang, I'm here to see you.
I only have one thing to tell you.
Today, Lysen's stock price
will plummet.
Li Wancheng is the one
trying to oust you.
Only I can help you.
Get in.
Given Lysen's current situation,
I think only you
can save it, Mr. Jiang.
I have a gift for you.
The Kelly Criterion.
(The Kelly Criterion is a math formula used)
(to determine the optimal size
of bets or investments.)
(Its core idea is
to optimize investment decisions)
(by maximizing the long-term capital growth rate.)
That casino tactic?
Wasn't Wall Street
once your casino too, Mr. Jiang?
I think
you should know better than I do
what needs to be done.
Today, the price of LT
will rise from 26,300 USD
(EST 10:30 AM)
to 70,000 USD.
Mr. Li.
Hello, shareholders.
Is Jiang Dongchao here?
Mr. Jiang hasn't arrived yet.
Let's go inside and wait for him.
(Li Wantian, Shareholder of Lysen Group)
Wancheng.
Let's get to work.
From now on,
no one is allowed to leave that door,
and no one is allowed to enter.
- Yes, Mr. Jiang.
Find the LME,
look at all our open positions.
I want all the copper and tin.
As long as the recent trend is stable,
find them all.
David,
give me
the cost prices
of all our positions.
Small fluctuations are fine.
Understood.
Hurry up!
Update
the fundamentals of all
our open positions.
Based on industry feedback,
recently in China...
The earlier flooding accident
at a Chilean copper mine
directly reduced supply.
Move aside!
Hello.
Mr. Jiang,
Mr. Li and three other shareholders
are waiting for you in your office.
Mr. Li said,
no matter what you are doing,
please go to the office to see him.
Otherwise...
Keep that door guarded for me.
Understood.
Everyone, listen up.
Close all
these positions now.
What are you waiting for?
Mr. Jiang,
many of these commodities
are currently bullish.
If we close them all now,
the potential profit
will drop significantly.
Was I not clear?
Clear.
Close everything!
Mr. Li.
Open the door.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Jiang ordered
not to open the door.
Get out of the way.
I said get out of the way.
Open the door.
The key.
Mr. Jiang took the key.
I don't care how you do it,
open the door.
Aluminum 2630
sold.
Lead 2220,
all closed.
A large number
of sell orders are appearing.
Copper has dropped to 8978.
Shall we continue?
Continue.
Keep selling. Sell it all.
Lead 2212,
I've dumped it all.
Aluminum 2629,
all sold.
Copper 8978, all dumped.
Everything on my side is closed.
- Closed.
I'm closed here too.
Mr. Jiang,
all positions have been closed.
(LT)
Every order on the market,
we take them all.
Mr. Jiang,
everyone has been bearish
on LT for six months.
You... You want to go long?
Put the word out.
We want the spot too.
We want it all!
Last week,
the LT international futures closed
at 26,300 USD.
Last month, it was still 31,500 USD.
The price is trending down.
We...
We are going against the market.
If we lose this bet,
our margin
could be wiped out.
This is gambling with our lives.
Mr. Jiang, please think twice.
Please reconsider,
Mr. Jiang.
- Yes, Mr. Jiang.
- Please, Mr. Jiang.
I'll say it once more!
All the LT,
buy it all for me!
Smash it harder.
Smash it harder!
Open the window for me!
Jiang Dongchao,
what on earth are you doing?
He's trying to save Lysen.
How is he saving it?
Mr. Jiang is going long on LT.
He's a madman.
Buying on three accounts at 26290.
Buy everything at 26316.
Two accounts at 26300,
buy it all.
If he loses this bet,
how much will we lose?
It's impossible to estimate.
Mr. Jiang, trades complete.
- Trades complete.
Trades complete.
Mr. Jiang,
all 43 members of the trading room
have completed their trades.
The battle is over.
Mr. Jiang,
how much do you expect
LT to rise today?
You expect it to rise that high?
Yes.
This is what I've calculated.
70,000.
70,000...
Right at 10:30 AM
Eastern Standard Time.
10:30 AM
Eastern Standard Time,
which is 10:30 PM
Beijing time.
So what do we
do next?
Wait.
Get out of my way!
(Beijing 22:28)
Two minutes left.
A minute and a half left.
Wancheng.
- Mr. Li!
Mr. Li, please calm down.
Mr. Li, don't be impulsive.
(Beijing 22:29)
(Beijing 22:30)
It's already 10:30.
Why isn't it rising yet?
It's up.
LT is up!
- It's rising!
It's up! Look!
Watch
the miracle happen.
(70,000 USD)
Mr. Jiang, you're amazing!
So incredible!
Mr. Jiang!
That's impressive.
Close all positions.
- Yes, sir!
- Good.
(Dr. Dai, five hours ago)
Dr. Dai,
I'd like to ask...
Regarding your academy's research report
on the rare metal LT,
(LT, time?)
is it confirmed to be released
at 10:30 AM Eastern Time?
Thank you very much.
Based on LT's current trading
and position status,
for every 3,000 long lots added,
the price will be pushed up
by at least 10,000 USD.
If 14,000 short lots
face an extreme short squeeze
and are fully covered,
LT
could indeed reach 70,000 USD.
(Portal Finance)
At 10:30 AM Eastern Time,
MIT
released a major announcement.
Significant progress
has been made in the highly anticipated
room-temperature
superconductivity experiments.
Previously, these materials
were primarily copper-based oxides,
but scientists have just discovered
that LT materials
exhibit excellent performance
in areas such as high magnetization
and broad temperature ranges.
Mr. Li,
I believe the market's commercial rating
for Lysen
will certainly satisfy you.
Let us all
congratulate Mr. Li together.
- Congratulations, Mr. Li!
Mr. Jiang!
Congratulations.
Well done.
Well done, well done.
Let's keep up the momentum.
Good, keep it going.
Keep working hard.
Go, go.
Forgive me, Mr. Jiang,
I was a bit slow to realize.
Come.
Go to the observation deck
and meet someone for me.
I want this person to join Lysen.
Yes, sir.
Have fun, everyone. Have fun.
Let's celebrate!
At Lysen,
under me, Jiang Dongchao,
every harvest
is earned through effort.
Your hard work and loyalty,
I see it all.
Please look up
and tell me what you see.
- Balloons!
Those are no ordinary balloons.
Inside each balloon
is a note.
On every note,
a dream is written.
I'll give you ten seconds.
Try your best to grab
as many notes as you can.
Every dream you capture,
I will fulfill personally!
Good!
Thank you, Mr. Jiang!
Are you ready?
We're ready!
Ready,
go!
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Hello.
I'm the Vice President of Lysen
and head of Investment Dept 1,
Bai Liangliang.
Welcome to Lysen.
Two!
One!
Congratulations, everyone.
May your dreams come true.
(Do you remember the myth)
(you once told me?)
(I am Inanna, who was dragged
from heaven to the underworld.)
(Inanna)
(I was once so desperate)
(and helpless.)
(You took everything from me.)
(Do you feel any guilt?)
(Or do you think it was your right?)
Congratulations
on joining Lysen Group, Miss Bai.
My dear,
it's my turn to say to you...
It's been a long time.
(Even though you once)
(pushed me into the abyss,)
(I have always believed)
(that I can...)
=Episode 1=
(Rebirth)
(All animals in this production
were treated humanely)
♪Take a breath and swallow
the words you couldn't say♪
♪No need to force your heart anymore♪
♪Searching for the season
we once missed♪
♪Leave this place,
though wounded still stay strong♪
♪You must believe
one day the rain will fall♪
♪And wash away the mud
that stains your soul♪
♪Find your freedom in the wild♪
♪Take your stride and move ahead♪
♪I will stay behind
and wait for your eyes♪
♪To rebuild
the same flesh and soul again♪
♪Wander freely through the thorns♪
♪Keep walking through the light♪
♪Fate is absurd, don't stop for anyone♪
♪What you dare to lose
will one day be your own♪
♪I'm sorry, I still owe you these words♪
♪An apology that came too late♪
♪Yet it's also the path
that saves my soul♪
♪When the cold wind
passes it takes the past away♪
♪You must believe and stand unwavering♪
♪There will be hands
to pull you from the deep♪
♪Find your freedom in the silence♪
♪Let your wounds be mended♪
♪Gray is not the past
and pain is not a shame♪
♪Sometimes the sunlight
makes the world look crueler♪
♪Wander through the echoes of regret♪
♪Be forgiven and be sheltered♪
♪After everything shatters,
hold my hand♪
♪A flower reborn
will finally bloom forever♪