♪It's a sordid story that you've made♪
♪Up to fill my mind with doubts and pain♪
♪Blood I shed, and tears I wept,
are you satisfied?♪
♪Enjoying what's mine♪
♪Have you found a way
to bury guilt and shame♪
♪I'm coming back to life♪
♪Through the seven gates of death♪
♪I'm coming back survived♪
♪Feeling great to see you fall♪
♪I'm taking back what's mine♪
♪Bringing horror to the battlefield♪
♪Lay it to waste♪
♪Til the day my kingdom is reclaimed♪
=Her Blaze=
=Episode 8=
I've always known that Lysen
has a genius.
She helped Jiang Dongchao out twice.
Now that I've met you in person,
you really do look like
the Little Genius
I imagined.
Don't worry.
Jiang Dongchao won't find out we've met.
I'm not worried.
Mr. Pengyu, don't you also
keep your plan
under wraps?
What do you mean?
The feud between the Xian family
and Jiang Dongchao
isn't hard to trace.
If you think
I'm a genius,
then it shouldn't surprise you
that I know what you're planning.
But don't worry.
I came here today to talk
about cooperation.
If your commercial building
had a proper snack street inside,
it could actually cover up
some irregularities.
Hold on.
Irregularities?
What irregularities?
A commercial building this big
has been empty for more than a year.
Wouldn't that attract attention?
The reason a building this big
hasn't been leased out
is that we're waiting for
the right businesses
and the right people.
Those small vendors
you're proposing
have no brand recognition,
and you want me to cut the rent in half?
Little Genius,
or are you actually a Little Dreamer?
If this is about Lysen's
so-called city plan,
I'm not interested.
It's not that.
(Linwei Alley Snack Street)
This is about the financing plan
(Renewal Financing Plan)
of the snack street I'm working on.
Jiang Dongchao asked you
to handle the Linwei Alley renewal,
but you're only pushing
the snack street project.
Looks like Jiang Dongchao and you
have a disagreement.
Linwei Alley Snack Street
has been around for many years.
A lot of people grew up
eating snacks there.
So,
for many people,
it's not just an ordinary alley.
It's a landmark.
It's a kind of sentiment.
(Linwei Alley Breakfast Stall)
Landmarks and nostalgia
are huge draws
for consumers.
(Linwei Alley)
So
the name "Linwei Alley" itself
(Lysen Group, creating a better life)
already carries commercial value.
If the transformation
of the Linwei Alley Snack Street
succeeds in your building,
we'll use it as a model
to expand and replicate it.
And of course,
Mr. Pengyu,
you'll be
our preferred partner.
To be honest, I don't really care
about making money.
But if this keeps Jiang Dongchao
in check,
I'm in.
Come on.
Pass these around.
We brought them from Linwei Alley.
Thank you.
Boss,
this is for you.
You eat it.
The best mixed fruit bowl
from the snack street.
Here's your ice cup.
Rao Yuci,
how much digging have you done on me?
Everything.
Including this.
And
your hairstyle, which hasn't changed
in over twenty years.
Should I take
all that effort
as a way
of buttering me up?
So, I'll help you
and approve your plan.
I never asked you to help me.
But I did say
if Dept 3 wants to move up,
we'll have to stick together.
Tian Tian, start.
Over the past few days, Yuci and I
visited several districts
and put together
a more detailed market survey.
Please take a look.
(Linwei Alley Snack Street
Renewal Financing Plan)
Our city
has a large number
of mobile street vendors.
(Project Overview:)
Compared to
(Around 30,000 mobile street vendors)
vendors
with fixed storefronts,
mobile vendors do bring
some negative impact
to urban sanitation.
But at the same time,
because they exist,
our city
has more warmth
and a real street-life atmosphere.
Just like Confucius Temple in Nanjing
and the Muslim Quarter in Xi'an,
these places carry generations
of food memories.
I came to this city
when I was eighteen.
It was my first year of university.
I'd go there with my coursemates
every night
for late-night snacks and a stroll.
A lot of my old customers
and old friends are here today.
I remember
when you were in college,
you used to come here
for malatang
and have secret dates.
And now look at you,
you're all married with kids.
Yuci's plan
is to bring these vendors together,
register and manage them uniformly,
from branding and logo design
to site planning, and eventually move them
into a commercial building.
(Mixed Fruit Bowl)
That way, we can create
a new indoor market model.
We've also finalized the location
for the first phase.
(Linwei Alley)
(Xianxian Malatang,
A'ertou Food Store)
This city is huge.
(Demolition)
All of us are trying to find
a place that belongs to us.
But along the way,
(Demolition)
it's easy to forget to ask ourselves
what all this hustle and bustle
is really for.
In the end,
it comes down to this.
"Warmth on a cold night,
and the comforting aroma of a hot food."
Well said!
Great job, Tian Tian.
Mr. Yu, you understand this better
than I do.
Money itself is never a bad thing.
But when money
goes to the people who need it,
that's even better.
Right?
How much funding are you asking for?
Ideals always sound beautiful,
but reality often turns out otherwise.
Boss.
(Project Overview)
Mr. Yu.
It's fine. Let him go.
(Even if no one helps me,)
(I'll still carry out my plan)
(step by step.)
This is a joke, don't you think so?
A company worth tens of billions
helping a few street vendors?
People would think
we're crazy.
This is absurd.
Maybe geniuses
think differently from us.
Genius?
Looks more like an idiot to me.
Mr. Yu,
I feel like she's a lot like you.
Are you saying I'm an idiot?
I wouldn't call you an idiot.
At most, it's idealism.
I still remember
when you went
to see Mr. Jiang to raise funds for
that rare disease project,
you said,
"If this project
has no commercial value,
I'll run around the whole company naked."
Thinking about it now,
I must've been sick in the head.
Actually,
we all know
you didn't give up,
even though Mr. Jiang rejected you.
All these years,
you've still been out there
trying to raise funds for that project.
(Seven years earlier)
Where's Ren Jing?
Still thinking about my Ren Jing?
She's in a meeting.
She'll come after work.
What's the point?
My illness
has no cure.
Looks like
the medicine won't come in time.
You... Sometimes,
you're just too pessimistic.
Peidong,
can you promise me one thing?
Please take care of my wife and kid.
Don't worry.
When she finds a new boyfriend one day,
I'll vet him for you.
First thing I'll do
is take him to the hospital
for a check-up.
She can't keep ending up
with sickly guys.
If you ever make it big,
besides helping me,
please help the other patients too.
In the end, this disease
is nothing
but money.
I've plenty of ways to deal with money.
Don't end up like me,
buried deep in debt.
Director Liu,
(Rare Disease Center)
I haven't come here much
after my friend passed away.
Right. Recently, I've been in contact
(Compassion of a Healer)
with a few foundations in this field.
But nothing has worked out so far.
So you're short on funds again...
The number of patients has increased?
A few days ago,
a volunteer
contacted us.
She brought some donated funds
and supplies.
But
she had one condition.
When the donation was made,
you had to be present.
I had to be there?
Please come in.
Mr. Yu,
long time no see.
Careful with that.
Chen.
Boss Yu.
Excuse me?
Peidong.
Thanks.
All the supplies are here.
You can double-check them later.
If there's any issue,
contact me.
It's so hot today.
Thank you for your hard work.
I should be thanking you instead.
Because of the money and supplies
you donated,
my son can finally
receive treatment here
without worry.
One from the parents' group chat
says they want to thank you properly.
No need for that.
I should get going.
Go on.
Boss Yu,
the money you donated saves lives.
What is this, a wake or something?
Drive safe.
It feels great when your mind
isn't distracted.
After I left, there must've been
rumors everywhere.
Some said you went crazy.
Some said you ran away.
Some even said...
What are those?
Rao Yuci donated them.
Who?
Rao Yuci.
I'm just
acting as a liaison.
Before,
my cowardice and greed
made me do a lot of wrong things.
I couldn't even face
who I really was.
It was Rao Yuci who woke me up.
After leaving the company,
I focused on working,
paying off my debts,
and taking care of my sick father.
That kind of life
made me feel grounded.
I came here to repay a debt.
I owe Rao Yuci too much.
Many patients here
are younger than me.
They need help.
Those outsiders
may think this industry
is only about making money,
but investing in an ideal
and helping people who need help,
someone has to do it.
A few years ago,
you raised charity funds
for these patients.
You were full of passion back then.
Nothing could stop you.
You were happy, weren't you?
(Linwei Alley Snack Food
Renewal Financing Plan)
(Yu Peidong: After careful consideration,
the snack street project can proceed.)
(Sima Yang: !!! Boss is the best!!!)
(Tian Tian: That's great!
Thank you, Mr. Yu.)
(Tian Tian: @RaoYuci Yuci!)
(Wang Meng: We'll follow your lead.)
Come on.
Something just struck me.
(Rao Yuci: Thank you.)
Water, electricity, and fire safety.
Make sure you coordinate with them.
Especially the old electrical wiring.
That needs extra attention.
Don't take it lightly.
Hello?
Also,
another thing.
Make sure to emphasize
food safety with them.
From sourcing raw ingredients
to processing to storage,
every step
must strictly follow regulations.
If we want to build this
into a strong brand,
we can't cut corners.
Follow the rules.
Don't worry, Miss Meng.
Yes.
We got this.
Rao Yuci does have some charm.
Even Yu Peidong was convinced by her.
It's not just Yu Peidong though.
Mr. Jiang,
you didn't stop her either, did you?
Why would I stop her?
This project
doesn't cost much money.
I just want to see
what she's trying to do.
Aren't you curious?
Oh, right, Mr. Jiang.
Regarding
the Linwei Alley City Plan,
I went to the construction site
a couple of days ago.
I ran into
our old friend.
Who?
Zhou Lufeng.
Mr. Jiang.
(Baiying Business Investigation)
The prices are posted on the entrance.
Reports and investigation fees
are all listed.
We'll talk after you read it.
Mr. Zhou.
Long time no see.
Mr. Jiang, please don't mind the place.
It's a small office.
Here.
Not at all.
Back then, if anyone wanted to have tea
with you,
they had to line up for it.
It's been many years since we last met.
Yes.
I suppose
it was after Lysen's second
Boundary Forum
that you
disappeared.
Yes.
After that public speech
when I criticized
Lysen's reckless expansion,
I was forced to disappear.
Right.
Lysen's strategy back then
was to move forward step by step
in a careful manner.
That explains
why people misunderstood.
Mr. Jiang, you've got the wrong idea.
I barely remember
those things anymore.
I'm doing fine now.
What happens in the big market now
has nothing to do with me anymore.
Big or small,
those are labels outsiders use.
People in the industry know
that small things decide big outcomes.
Mr. Zhou, you say you don't care about
big matters anymore,
but it seems
otherwise.
I heard
you visited our construction site
for the Linwei Alley City Plan.
If Bosi
hired you
to investigate us,
you could've come straight to me.
Someone did ask me
to investigate this project.
It wasn't Bosi.
They knew you were coming
and asked me to hand this over to you.
(Investigation Report on
Green Building Materials Firms)
Take some time to read it.
There's something very interesting
in there.
This client you mentioned
is Rao Yuci?
Rao Yuci.
Morning.
You look pretty happy.
To be honest,
I haven't felt this happy
in this building for a long time.
Thank you.
You helped me get back
the drive I had when I first joined Lysen.
I have a gift for you.
Go to work already.
Once you walk through this door,
you can't smile.
Put that smile away.
Look around.
Everyone in this building is sick.
Can't smile or make friends.
There's something I don't understand.
You could've taken over
the Linwei Alley City Plan.
It doesn't conflict
with the snack street project.
Aren't you basically
handing the opportunity
Mr. Jiang gave you right back to him?
Who said I handed it back?
The opportunity is still in my hands.
Alright.
Mr. Rao.
Liangliang.
The money I'm putting in here
isn't just mine and my wife's,
it's also money borrowed
from relatives and friends.
Some of it is a bank loan.
Are you sure
this plan won't go wrong?
Ever since Mr. Jiang joined Lysen,
acquiring Bosi
has been his dream.
Now that the opportunity
is finally right in front of him,
there's no way he'll give it up.
If you're worried,
you can take your money back.
No, that's not what I mean.
It took me a lot of effort
to convince those then households
in Linwei Alley.
After we buy those ten properties,
Lysen has to take over them.
The contract of this project is signed
under my company's name.
I can cover
the initial funding.
But if Lysen
refuses to take over later,
my cash flow
will collapse.
Don't worry, Mr. Rao.
Nothing will go wrong.
Mr. Rao, the contract has been checked.
Everything looks good.
You can sign it now.
Alright.
I'll take the gamble.
I trust you.
You won't bring me bad luck
as my daughter does.
Sign on the last page
of the contract.
Alright.
Over here.
(Rao Shusheng)
Okay.
(Five years earlier)
I told you before.
I investigated that company.
It's a scam.
Rao Shusheng, you're too greedy.
What did I do wrong?
I did nothing wrong.
I was just unlucky.
All of this happened
because of you, jinx.
Rao Yuci.
What happened?
He invested in futures
and lost a lot of money.
He even took my mom's savings.
How much did he lose? A lot?
The problem is,
every decision he makes
always ends up dragging my mom down.
When I was little,
his factory caught fire.
Two workers
died in the accident.
The compensation
was all paid with money
my mom earned through hard work.
And him?
He never even apologized.
Yuci,
he's your father.
If you expose him like that,
he won't be able to take it.
Sometimes when you're too serious,
it puts pressure on him
and makes him fear.
Do you understand?
Liangliang,
I wish Yuci
could be more like you.
I really envy your dad
for having an understanding daughter
like you.
Mr. Rao, I understand you.
All you want is for Yuci
to support you unconditionally.
After all, she's your daughter.
I'm doing all this for this family.
I don't get
why she always
doubts me.
No father and daughter are born enemies.
But she and I...
Ever since she was little,
everyone said
she was smart and sweet.
But I can only see
that judgmental look
when she looks at me.
(Rao Yuci,)
(you're not gaining a foothold)
(with Jiang Dongchao.)
Do you need any help?
No.
I can manage.
(These ten property deeds)
(are my proof of loyalty.)
(I'm going to completely destroy)
(Jiang Dongchao's trust)
(in you.)
(Demolition)
Didn't we agree
to move out in three days?
We haven't finished
packing yet.
Look,
we've known each other for years.
Can't you cut us some slack?
Yes, give us a little more time.
We don't have a choice either.
Right.
Please try to understand us, okay?
The building doesn't belong
to us anymore.
It's not ours now.
The ownership has been transferred.
The new landlord
wants the place vacated immediately.
There's nothing I can do.
Exactly.
But if you make us move out now,
where is my whole family
supposed to live?
Live wherever I want.
Why are you asking us?
How would we know?
Don't fight. Stop it.
What's going on here?
Thank goodness you're here, Mr. Chen.
What are we supposed to do?
The landlord suddenly told us
to move out.
Why such short notice?
Hello, Tian Tian?
Ms. Chen.
Submit this through OA.
But Ms. Chen, there are ten house owners
in Linwei Alley
who suddenly demanded
that the tenants move today.
The system takes time,
so I brought the document
directly to you.
This is something
the Dept 3 is working on.
We don't have the budget for it.
And besides,
we're not a charity.
It was Dept 3's idea
to help these street vendors
in the first place.
But Ms. Chen, you're also in charge
of the Linwei Alley project.
If you disagree,
you can talk to Mr. Jiang.
Ms. Chen...
Right now.
At once.
Please leave my office.
Notify every moving
and logistics company
in the name of Lysen Group.
If any company helps with the move
in the Linwei Alley today,
Lysen will never work with them again.
We've contacted all the moving companies.
Even when we offered more money,
none of them would come.
Why?
They didn't give a reason.
Uh,
we tried contacting a few ourselves.
They all said
they had no trucks available.
What do we do now?
We're asked to move out today.
We've tried everything.
We can't get a truck.
Alright.
Let's make use of the time
we still have.
You all
go pack everything up.
Go ahead.
Let's start moving.
We'll figure out the trucks.
Alright?
Alright.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
We'll solve it.
(Group chat (3)
Rao Yuci: This is a temporary group.)
(The vendors at Linwei Alley can't find
any trucks. @Chen, we need your help.)
(Chen: No problem. I'll do everything
I can. How many trucks do you need?)
(Rao Yuci: Thank you, Chen.
@Mr. Yu, please coordinate with Chen.)
(Yu Peidong: Roger that.
You call the shot now!)
I didn't get anything done this morning.
Just making phone calls.
What's wrong, Liang?
It's about the Linwei Alley.
Didn't the announcement say
they would move out in three days?
No idea
why it has to be today.
Ms. Chen is furious.
She told everyone
that if any logistics company
steps in,
Lysen will never work with them again.
Chen.
Alright.
Done eating?
If you're done, let's go.
- Where?
Linwei Alley.
Yes.
We're going to Linwei Alley.
Do you mind sitting in one of them?
Of course.
That's awesome, Boss.
Let's go.
Time to get to work.
I'll take the truck at the back.
Okay.
I'll take this one.
♪What's playing on the TV
another annoying heartbreak song♪
♪Maybe I just woke up too early♪
♪This pointless rain
washes all my color away♪
♪Your message shows as read♪
Give it a moment.
Don't worry.
♪Maybe my passion burned too hot♪
♪Boiling over till it lost its flame♪
♪We always pass each other by♪
♪Then dive back into the crowd again♪
♪Who would listen to
my sleepless nights♪
♪Who cares about
the stars or the weather♪
♪None of it has anything to do with me♪
♪The little shop down the street♪
The trucks are here!
They're here.
They're here!
♪Good night, world♪
♪The moon has risen♪
♪How could the lonely fall asleep♪
So many trucks?
♪The silence of the world
feels just right♪
There are plenty of them.
♪Good night, world♪
♪It's time for my own lonely celebration♪
Here we are.
Yuci, we're here to help.
We're here to help.
We have so many helpers.
Thanks, everyone.
Let's get to work.
Come on.
Come.
Let me carry this.
I'll take it.
Let me.
Careful.
Give me that one. I'll carry that.
Slow down.
Watch it.
Come. Slowly.
Don't bump it.
Put the big ones down first. Right.
Here, have some water.
♪Who would listen to
my sleepless nights♪
♪Who cares about
the stars or the weather♪
♪None of it has anything to do with me♪
(Nuan and I will never be apart)
We're leaving now.
Alright.
Take care.
Slow down.
Bye.
Careful.
Looks like you've found new friends.
Seems like it.
♪The moon has risen♪
I'll help them get settled first.
Don't worry.
Off we go.
♪The silence of the world
feels just right♪
Get in the car.
The first one.
♪Good night, world♪
♪It's time for my own lonely celebration♪
♪A hopeless insomniac♪
We might as well
start a moving company tomorrow.
♪Half drunk before I wake again♪
Thanks for the hard work.
It wasn't that hard.
I'm just a little hungry.
Hungry?
Let's go grab something to eat.
Who's paying?
I'll treat.
Sounds good to me.
No expense claims allowed.
♪Leave me with myself♪
♪Just the noise, no more heartbreak♪
Liangliang,
several properties in Linwei Alley
have been transferred.
You must make sure
Lysen's acquisition goes through
without a hitch.
I'll give it everything I've got.
Please don't worry.
I've staked
all my money on this.
There absolutely can't be any mistakes.
Of course not.
Good.
Then I'll leave everything
in your hands,
Liangliang.
Bye, Mr. Rao.
(Rao Yuci,)
(you probably never expected)
(that it was your dad who helped me.)
(Ever since you were little,)
(you've always been the lucky one.)
(Fate has always favored you.)
(Five years earlier)
(But)
(I've had nothing.)
(I had to fight for everything
for myself.)
You're dining with
an important guest.
Would it be convenient if I came along?
Why wouldn't it be?
My mom asked you to come.
By the way,
how's your thesis defense preparation
for the next couple of days?
I still need to cut some parts.
I feel like
my argument has some problems.
It's just
analyzing some data.
It's basically a formality for you.
Don't be too nervous.
I'm not nervous.
Let's eat first.
Mom.
-Ms. Liu.
-Yuci.
Liangliang, have a seat.
Bai Liangliang
is Yuci's good friend
from university.
This is Ms. Liu.
A good friend of Mr. Rao's and mine.
Hello, Ms. Liu.
Hello.
Yuci's friend is very pretty.
Where's your family from?
Her parents are diplomats.
They've been working abroad for years.
During the four years of university,
she has lived here by herself.
Sometimes,
she stays at our house too.
Time flies.
I thought it was just your parents.
I didn't know either.
Come on, let's start eating.
Yes. Let's eat first.
Liangliang, please have more.
Thank you, Liangliang.
Yuci, you're going to graduate.
What are your plans?
I haven't decided yet,
Ms. Liu.
Why don't you come work at my bank?
We're recruiting through
campus hiring right now.
You should give it a try.
Your parents
would prefer you
to find a stable job.
Besides,
jobs are hard to find these days.
Right.
The bank is great.
The benefits, the conditions,
and the career development
are all very good.
Liangliang, didn't you say before
that you were very interested in
bank campus recruitment?
Yeah.
Right.
Liangliang and Yuci
are in the same major.
Her grades are also very good.
How about this?
You can both try applying
to Ms. Liu's bank together.
Please help them out.
I'll appreciate that.
Then I'll thank you in advance, Ms. Liu.
We'll talk about it later.
Let's eat first.
We'll talk about that later.
Right.
You didn't even
discuss it with me,
and suddenly suggested that the girl
apply for
my bank's campus recruitment.
Youming, you saw
how hesitant Yuci was.
I just thought
if the two good friends
could work
in the same place,
maybe Yuci would feel more comfortable
saying yes.
So I...
Zhaohe,
you're thinking
too simply.
With my position,
I can only help Yuci.
When we recruit,
we don't just look at grades.
We also consider
many other factors.
Liangliang told us about
her parents before.
They have decent jobs.
What does that have to do with me?
Zhaohe,
like what you said,
her parents
are already so successful.
Why are you worrying about her?
Miss, your receipt.
Thank you.
Liangliang,
I'm really sorry.
Why did you pay the bill again?
It's okay, Mrs. Rao.
We're like family.
It doesn't matter who pays.
Well, I'm your elder.
I feel really embarrassed.
It's fine.
Yuci, why are you just sitting here
eating by yourself?
You should learn from Liangliang.
Look at her.
She's very considerate.
She paid the bill again.
Yuci has always been protected
by all of us.
She doesn't need to learn
those social tricks.
By the way, Mrs. Rao,
you mentioned
the campus recruitment earlier.
I actually have my own plans.
I'm not applying for that.
I'm planning to apply for Professor Han's
graduate program.
Thank you for your kind offer.
A master's degree
in financial mathematics
must be very hard to get into.
I'm not like Yuci.
I don't like following rules
or having my life arranged for me.
I like to take control of my own life
and my own future.
For me,
a stable job
isn't important.
Mrs. Rao,
didn't you also work hard
when you were young?
Parents are just worried
that we'll get hurt.
But getting hurt
is part of life.
So,
even though work is important,
I hope to push myself harder
and grow more
during the best years
of my life.
Young people really are bold.
We really are getting old.
That's true.
Liangliang
really has her own ideas.
Liangliang, I hope you don't mind.
I didn't expect my mom
to suddenly bring that up
yesterday.
Why would I?
Your mom was just being concerned.
Good to hear that.
Oh right.
My mom
really likes the duck.
She asked where you bought it.
I'll buy it for you.
Don't worry about such small things.
Alright. Bye.
Bye.
(Linwei Alley)
(Linwei Alley Salted Duck)
One moment.
Madam, the money's here.
Alright.
Thank you, madam.
Please come again.
Sure.
Hello, half a duck or a whole one?
A whole duck.
Done.
Here you go.
(Linwei Alley Salted Duck)
She didn't pay yet, right?
That's my daughter.
=Episode 8=
(Proof of Loyalty)
(All animals in this production
were treated humanely)
♪Take a breath and swallow
the words you couldn't say♪
♪No need to force your heart anymore♪
♪Searching for the season
we once missed♪
♪Leave this place,
though wounded still stay strong♪
♪You must believe
one day the rain will fall♪
♪And wash away the mud
that stains your soul♪
♪Find your freedom in the wild♪
♪Take your stride and move ahead♪
♪I will stay behind
and wait for your eyes♪
♪To rebuild
the same flesh and soul again♪
♪Wander freely through the thorns♪
♪Keep walking through the light♪
♪Fate is absurd, don't stop for anyone♪
♪What you dare to lose
will one day be your own♪
♪I'm sorry, I still owe you these words♪
♪An apology that came too late♪
♪Yet it's also the path
that saves my soul♪
♪When the cold wind
passes it takes the past away♪
♪You must believe and stand unwavering♪
♪There will be hands
to pull you from the deep♪
♪Find your freedom in the silence♪
♪Let your wounds be mended♪
♪Gray is not the past
and pain is not a shame♪
♪Sometimes the sunlight
makes the world look crueler♪
♪Wander through the echoes of regret♪
♪Be forgiven and be sheltered♪
♪After everything shatters,
hold my hand♪
♪A flower reborn
will finally bloom forever♪