♪It's a sordid story that you've made♪
♪Up to fill my mind with doubts and pain♪
♪Blood I shed, and tears I wept,
are you satisfied?♪
♪Enjoying what's mine♪
♪Have you found a way
to bury guilt and shame♪
♪I'm coming back to life♪
♪Through the seven gates of death♪
♪I'm coming back survived♪
♪Feeling great to see you fall♪
♪I'm taking back what's mine♪
♪Bringing horror to the battlefield♪
♪Lay it to waste♪
♪Til the day my kingdom is reclaimed♪
=Her Blaze=
=Episode 28=
If Rao Yuci leaves Lysen,
is there anyone
in Dept 3 more suited
to lead this team than you?
If you handle this well,
Mr. Jiang
will treat you well.
You should go get checked out too.
You're crazy.
Go take your meds.
Ms. Rao.
The coffee machine is broken.
I told Admin,
but they haven't fixed it yet.
Ms. Rao.
I'm just heading down for coffee.
Can I get you one?
Thanks.
(Jiang Dongchao)
Sima,
where in Jiangxi are you from?
Nanchang, Mr. Jiang.
I'm from Shangrao.
We're practically neighbors.
It hasn't been easy for you.
No connections, no backing,
you've fought for everything
on your own.
Look,
in all of Investment Dept 3,
you're the only one left standing.
That proves you're a real fighter.
Thank you, Mr. Jiang.
Last night,
Ms. Bai was telling me about you.
She said Sima Yang
has a lot of potential.
But I think
you're still missing
one final edge.
Here,
help me with the blinds.
You got it.
You've been at Lysen for years.
I should have brought you up here sooner
to see this view.
How high
a person can climb
usually depends
on the choices they make.
When making a choice,
if you can't see
what's truly in your best interest,
where it lies,
you'll never reach
the top floor of life
to look down on the world.
To do great things...
You have to burn your bridges.
Sir, your coffee is ready.
Thanks.
No problem.
Sir,
your to-go coffee is ready.
Sir?
Your coffee is ready.
Oh, thanks.
Come in.
Thanks.
No problem.
The sky looks ominous.
Something big is going down
at Lysen Group tonight.
(Chen Mo)
(One day ago)
This is the file on Chen Mo.
I'm sure you'll find it interesting.
If I give this
to Rao Yuci,
how do you think she'll react?
For everything Rao Yuci did to me,
I'll make her pay a hundredfold.
When I want something done,
no one can stop me.
I want her to rot in hell.
She's been there before.
But this time,
I'm never letting her out.
Your girlfriend's lost it.
She's at Lysen Group.
Get over here and see her.
Look at you.
You're in even worse shape
than you were three years ago.
And I love it.
Fragile.
Helpless.
Broken.
You managed to get out
after I sent you away last time.
But this time,
you won't be as lucky.
You're never getting out of here again.
My dear.
Your end is nigh.
I'm afraid I'm going to disappoint you.
Ms. Rao.
I've already called the police.
Let me introduce you to someone.
(One year ago)
He's a student I've been sponsoring.
He's at Lysen Group now.
At Lysen Group, you need
an ally who looks like an enemy.
He'll always be against you,
but he'll help you.
You have to trust him.
Hello. I'm Sima Yang.
I found this on her computer.
It's being delivered tomorrow.
How do you know
she isn't just using it for fruit?
A fruit knife?
Why would she keep staring at it?
Besides,
Rao Yuci and Manager Yu's
recent conversations
have been all about you.
Be careful, Ms. Bai.
She already has the photos.
Dept 3 should have finished
the project proposal long ago.
Send it to me.
I haven't had the chance.
Only Manager Yu,
Rao Yuci,
and Miss Meng have it.
I don't care if you have it now.
I need it before the bidding starts.
Yuci,
Bai Liangliang wants to get
our project proposal early.
I know.
We'll beat her at her own game.
You managed to get out
after I sent you away last time,
But this time,
you won't be as lucky.
Stop!
Rao Yuci, you lied to me!
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Let go of me!
Calm down.
Let go!
Calm down!
Just calm down!
Sima Yang, you can head out.
You were my best friend.
I shared everything
with you.
(Even the warmth of a home.)
Mrs. Rao, you should have seen
Yuci's defense today.
It was brilliant.
Brilliant, both of you were brilliant.
You are both my daughters.
(Chuxia)
(Our dreams for the company.)
(I held nothing back.)
I never did anything to hurt you.
I don't understand why
you hate me this much.
I just do.
I hate that everyone thinks
you're so kind.
everything you have
is just your birthright.
You talk about
pursuing fairness in this world,
but in reality,
you've just been riding
the wave of your own privilege.
I worked hard too.
I'm just as good as you!
So why did Professor Han
choose you back then
and not me?
The things I have to bleed for
just to obtain,
you get without effort.
It just falls into your lap.
How is that fair?
Everyone...
Everyone calls you a genius.
You're everyone's treasure.
But what about me?
I've had to
crawl in your shadow.
You even dragged Bai Xia into this.
My own mother.
I didn't even get a chance to know her
before she was gone.
And it's all because of you, Rao Yuci.
I hate you.
Hating you
is all I can think of!
Bai Liangliang, you're twisted.
And honestly, you're pathetic.
But your life
didn't have to be like this.
Neither of our lives
had to end up this way.
I've prepared
a little something for everyone.
I hope you all keep up
the hard work.
Thank you, Ms. Bai.
This seat
should have been yours.
(Please be safe, Rao Yuci.)
(Please be safe.)
Do you regret
the choices you've made?
Losing your family.
Losing everything.
You betrayed everyone you loved
just to get what you wanted.
Now, it's time for you to face the law.
Do you regret it?
I don't regret a single thing.
Sima Yang.
Where's Rao Yuci?
She's with Bai Liangliang.
Are you okay?
To the hospital, now.
I'm fine.
She's fine.
We were all fools.
She already had
this whole thing planned.
She doesn't need
anyone's help
or your protection.
Rao Yuci.
Even if I'm gone,
you'll never find peace.
Even with me out of the picture,
you'll never be happy.
You two really are a perfect match.
You act like
you're so devoted,
but the truth is
you're both just living a lie.
You'll never be happy together.
What's going on?
It must be something big.
Look! Look over there!
Isn't that Bai Liangliang
from Lysen Group?
This looks terrible.
What did she do?
Why are the police taking her away?
What's the story?
It's just...
Move.
What is it, Ren Jing?
Mr. Jiang.
Bai Liangliang
drugged Rao Yuci at the office
and was arrested.
What about Rao Yuci?
Rao Yuci is fine.
Okay. I understand.
Yes.
I understand.
Dongchao,
the financing conference
will proceed as planned.
(Workplace Compensation Agreement)
(Deaf couple killed
in old city factory fire)
(Responsible Party: Rao Shusheng
Family of Party B: Chen Mo)
The deaf couple in the newspaper
were your parents?
When the fire broke out
at Rao Shusheng's factory...
They passed away.
(Deaf couple killed in factory fire.
Compensation sparks controversy)
(Twelve years ago)
Can you hurry it up?
Hold the umbrella.
This child, honestly...
Mom,
who is that girl?
The factory manager's daughter.
She's two years older than you.
She's a quiet little girl.
Her dad just lost his temper with her.
It's none of our business,
so don't go asking around.
Now, eat.
(Happy Birthday, Mom)
Hello?
Shusheng, where are you?
Get home, quickly.
What's the matter?
The voltage here is acting up.
I'm just fixing the wiring.
You need to come back.
It's incredible news.
Yuci has a surprise for you.
(Vehicle Registration Certificate)
A surprise from her?
I'm content with her
not being a troublemaker.
Yuci told me to keep it a secret,
but she opened a stock trading account.
She made some money on the market.
And since she knows you love cars,
she bought you a brand new one.
Hurry back.
Fine. I'm on my way.
Two workers
are trapped inside!
Get them out!
(Workplace Compensation Agreement
Operations Manager: Rao Shusheng)
Hey, kid.
Why don't you have an umbrella?
It's pouring out here,
and it's already dark.
You should head home.
Here, take mine.
Go on, take it.
I said take it.
Be a good girl.
Hurry home now.
Listen to me.
(Xinkang Treatment Center,
Duty Room)
(Patient Medical Records,
Name: Rao Yuci)
Hurry home now.
Listen to me.
No! Wait, wait!
Don't hit me! Stop!
Why are you following me?
I'm Chen Mo, a psychologist.
Rao Yuci.
Rao Yuci, can you just
let me finish what I have to say?
Rao Yuci,
I kept quiet for our sake.
What's the point of the truth?
What would it
actually change?
Do you know how long
it took me to let this go?
Who was I supposed
to tell about my pain?
You get to go home
and have dinner with your parents.
But what about me?
I want to have dinner with them too.
I'd give anything
to have dinner with them.
Listen closely, Rao Yuci.
I've stood on that line between
good and evil.
But I don't want to
lose the ability to love.
So I fought so hard
to be someone dependable.
But you don't think
I understand anything.
You never once bothered to ask me
if I was actually hurting.
But I'm human too.
I feel wronged.
I have emotions.
Now, I want to think for myself.
I don't want to die
in this emotional dead end.
I want to do everything I can
to protect all that I still have.
I couldn't let go
of my parents.
Now, I can't let go of you.
Rao Yuci.
I want to protect you.
When will you stop
pushing me away?
You know me so well.
But I barely know you at all.
You're right.
I am a selfish person.
I never considered your feelings.
I never cared
what was on your mind.
But since the day we met,
that's just how we've been.
I've always lived in the dark.
Now that you've found the light,
stay there.
I don't need your protection.
This ends here.
♪It's a sordid story that you've made♪
♪Up to fill my mind
with doubts and pain♪
♪Blood I shed, and tears I wept,
are you satisfied?♪
♪Enjoying what's mine♪
♪Have you found a way
to bury guilt and shame♪
♪In this dismal dream
where I've been trapped♪
♪you fabricated all these twisted lies♪
♪You could pray, but won't be saved♪
♪Cuz your soul is walking down
a path of destruction♪
(But I'm human too.)
(I feel wronged.)
(I have emotions.)
(Rao Yuci.)
(I want to protect you.)
(When will you stop)
(pushing me away?)
♪I'm coming back survived♪
♪Feeling great to see you fall♪
♪I'm taking back what' s mine♪
♪Bringing horror to the battlefield♪
♪Lay it to waste♪
♪Til the day my kingdom is reclaimed♪
=Episode 28=
(Fury)
(All animals in this production
were treated humanely)
♪Take a breath and swallow
the words you couldn't say♪
♪No need to force your heart anymore♪
♪Searching for the season
we once missed♪
♪Leave this place,
though wounded still stay strong♪
♪You must believe
one day the rain will fall♪
♪And wash away the mud
that stains your soul♪
♪Find your freedom in the wild♪
♪Take your stride and move ahead♪
♪I will stay behind
and wait for your eyes♪
♪To rebuild
the same flesh and soul again♪
♪Wander freely through the thorns♪
♪Keep walking through the light♪
♪Fate is absurd, don't stop for anyone♪
♪What you dare to lose
will one day be your own♪
♪I'm sorry, I still owe you these words♪
♪An apology that came too late♪
♪Yet it's also the path
that saves my soul♪
♪When the cold wind
passes it takes the past away♪
♪You must believe and stand unwavering♪
♪There will be hands
to pull you from the deep♪
♪Find your freedom in the silence♪
♪Let your wounds be mended♪
♪Gray is not the past
and pain is not a shame♪
♪Sometimes the sunlight
makes the world look crueler♪
♪Wander through the echoes of regret♪
♪Be forgiven and be sheltered♪
♪After everything shatters,
hold my hand♪
♪A flower reborn
will finally bloom forever♪