Hey.
Let me explain what happened.
No need to explain.
"No need?"
That's right.
As you know, we're nothing now.
Right.
It's over...
between us.
What?
We're nothing now?
(Episode 12: Love, the Miracle of the Universe)
I'm coming in.
Hey, my goodness.
What is all this?
You should be writing with a clear mind.
Do you really want to depend on dopamine?
- You'll die at this rate. - Do you now know how I felt...
when beer cans were lying all over the house?
You should just have a drink.
Alcohol is the best remedy for a breakup.
It's not about that.
The contest submission deadline is this week. That's why.
Sure, whatever.
Hey, here.
I know I can't cook, but I tried my best.
I appreciate it,
but can you please get out?
Make sure you eat it.
- Okay? - Yes!
We'll really be leaving for the US in just three days.
Yes, that's right.
It feels like a dream, us going to Corning University together.
Right, I told my landlord today...
that I'd be moving out.
Good.
Hey, we should have dinner together this evening.
- My treat. - Sorry.
I have plans for the evening.
You do? With who?
Don't tell me... No, right?
With my family.
It's the last weekend before I leave.
I see. Then I should let you go.
I'll see you every day from now on anyway.
(Love Four Cuts)
Yes.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Hey, come and sit.
Honey, that's enough. Just come and join us.
There's no space left on the table.
Dad's right. That's enough, Mom.
Yes, I'm done. Here.
All right, let's pray now.
My eldest child, Park Yoon Jae, will be leaving...
for the US very soon to study at Corning University.
May the Lord be with him...
and watch over him so that his new journey...
will be safe and free from any problems.
Amen.
- Amen. - Amen.
All right, let's eat.
Should I have a cup of coffee?
I got this.
It's fine.
- I'll do it, Mom. - Goodness.
Stop it.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Thank you very much for everything.
I must admit, I'm sad, which isn't like me.
Where in the US will you be?
I'll be attending Corning University in Maryland.
Corning University?
You're that smart?
I never thought so.
Me neither.
Anyway, good luck with everything.
Here's your parting bonus.
What?
What employer gives a mere part-timer a parting bonus?
Please, it's fine.
Just do what your boss says and accept it.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thank you.
Oh, Min Hyuk. Can you spare me a minute?
(Lee Min Hyuk)
Ji Hoon, the clothes you borrowed from me at the club.
When can I get them back?
Oh, right.
I really wanted to talk to you...
about something before leaving for the US.
So, you decided...
to go to the US after all.
Yes.
That's great. When do you leave?
Tomorrow.
Really?
That's really great. Congratulations.
And you...
You're doing well, right?
Yes, of course.
I'm doing really well.
I've been busy preparing for the contest,
but I'm still eating and sleeping well.
Yoon Jae.
Make sure you eat well in the US too.
And study hard.
I have something urgent to take care of, so I should get going.
Goodbye.
I...
That day,
I couldn't hold back any longer,
so I went to see you for the first time.
I heard I was drunk...
and passed out in front of your place.
I held out...
as long as I could.
I swear, it was the first time.
You said I didn't need to explain,
but I really wanted to.
Should I really go?
Ji Eun.
Do you really want me to leave?
What's up?
I came to say farewell.
I'm flying out to the US tonight.
I see.
With Yoon Jae.
Have a safe flight.
Don't worry about Yoon Jae.
All right, I won't.
Ji Hoon, you take care...
I mean, you take care of yourself too, Ji Eun.
You too.
Tonight at 9:20pm. It's Hana Air.
Hey, what are you doing?
Good luck with everything, Park Yoon Jae.
Don't worry about Mom and Dad. I'll take care of them.
All right.
I trust you'll take good care of them while I'm away.
Son.
We all believe in you.
I'll be fine, Mom.
How about a hug?
- Don't go. - Don't go.
Don't go.
(Spoon Worm)
- Hey. - So, did you submit it?
What?
Oh, right.
"Oh, right?"
Hey.
The deadline is in an hour.
I'm working on it.
It's in an hour. You're still writing?
Read me the last three sentences you wrote before I called you.
Three sentences?
(At 9:20pm, Hana Air)
"At 9:20pm, Hana Air."
- What? - "At 9:20pm, Hana Air."
What are you saying?
What?
At 9:20pm,
Hana Air.
I guess he's not coming.
What?
What? Oh, nothing.
We should head in now.
All right, let's go.
Goodbye,
Park Yoon Jae.
My gosh.
What is this?
Goodness.
My gosh!
Hi.
Hey, I'm not Kim Ji Hye.
Hi, Hong Young Seok.
Good luck on your exam. Good luck!
(Exam Site 4)
- Well done. Bye. - Thank you.
- Well done. - Thank you.
Hi, bye.
Well done!
Hi, well done
(Rooting for You and Your Dream)
What's this?
(Dear test takers)
(Written Exam Held Here)
My gosh, I can't see.
How come I can't see a thing now?
I could see just fine earlier.
Oh, no. What's going on?
My goodness.
Where did you rent this from?
Hi.
Kim Ji Hye, seriously...
Did you do well on the exam?
Oh, it's totally fine even if you didn't do well on the exam.
I think I did pretty well.
Really?
Hey! That's amazing!
Anyway, how did you find me here?
How did you know I took the exam here?
Oh, you know I'm close with the President of Noryangjin.
- Auntie? - Yes.
Gosh, you.
Well, I should get going.
What?
(Exam Site 4)
- Gosh. - Hey.
Let's go eat something.
What?
I'm hungry.
You're...
You're hungry?
Yes.
Oh, you're hungry. That's not good.
Yes, let's eat something.
Yes, let's go. Let's grab a bite to eat.
Wait, then...
It's on me. I'm treating you.
Hey, Kim Ji Hye. You're so funny.
Where did you even find these things?
Where did you get this?
Yes, that's it.
I didn't know Hong Young Seok smiled so much.
Like this. Keep going.
What's so funny?
Kim Ji Hye, you're really something.
Actually, he looks ugly when he smiles.
Do you want something to drink?
Oh, you have something?
(Kim Ji Hye)
Come on. This is nothing.
- What do you feel like eating? - What shall we eat?
- What shall we eat? - Oh, this...
- What shall we eat? - This is red ginseng.
That's right. Red ginseng is good for you.
(Congratulations on Mom and Dad's 30th wedding anniversary.)
Congratulations, Mom and Dad.
Here's my gift to you.
- Matching pajamas. - Oh, my gosh.
Thanks. My goodness.
And thank you, Ji Hye. We will enjoy this meal.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
Hey, Mom, Dad.
I'm 33 this year, you know.
So, how is it that this year marks your 30th anniversary?
What?
The answer is obvious. Do you really have to ask?
Oh, that...
Your mom was against having a wedding.
She said she didn't know what to expect, even after you were born.
I can understand why.
Honey.
Do you regret marrying me?
I plucked up the courage to stay with you,
and it turned out to be the best decision of my life.
Thanks to that decision, we had our two daughters, Ji Hye and Ji Eun.
My gosh, that's cringey.
Hey, Ji Hye. Has something good happened to you lately?
- You're looking great. - What?
- I am? - There's someone she likes.
Really? Who?
Well...
It's someone you two know.
Who?
You know...
Hong Young Seok.
He sat next to me back in high school.
Yes, I remember him, of course. Your first love, right?
Hey, how did you guys meet again?
It happened somehow.
But we aren't officially dating yet.
I'll tell you more later.
And you.
Your grandma kept praising...
that friend of yours and went on about how reliable he is.
Really?
But Yoon Jae and I broke up.
There's a happy ending like yours,
but since I made the best choice for Yoon Jae and myself,
it's still a happy ending too.
My dear daughters.
When did you grow up like this?
Now, I can really put my worries about you two to rest.
All right, guys.
How about we say "Love you, cheers" and clink our glasses?
- Love you. - Love you.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
(3 months later)
I'll enjoy this meal.
Don't steal glances at me like that.
All right.
You're looking great these days.
I can't get sick, you know.
Hey, do you want to go watch a musical with me?
I still have a lot to do.
It's because you're volunteering to do things that you don't need to do.
Are you just going to study and do nothing else?
Yes.
I came here to study, you know.
You're annoying.
Let's go for pho.
I was just going to grab a sandwich.
Again?
I have to send this to the professor by 2pm.
I really am busy.
Brother. Are you doing okay?
I read an episode of something that Crystal Shoes recommended,
and the male lead reminds me of you...
that I can't get into it.
Am I the only one to find it weird?
(The first blind date of my life.)
(Crystal Shoes' Recommendation!)
(My Girlfriend is the Man! Episode 1)
(Publish on a portal, not a blog.)
(Why do our days off go by so fast?)
(When will the movie or TV drama come out?)
(I'll keep reading starting today.)
"Jellyfish. I'll keep reading starting today."
I'll treat you well and honor you,
Jellyfish.
You got quite a few comments this week.
Right?
I owe that to you, Crystal Shoes.
No need to thank a friend.
You won't go home?
What?
I'm going to eat dinner with you.
I...
ate dinner.
It's 2pm, and you had dinner?
I was hungry, so I ate ahead of time.
Didn't you hear something just now?
No.
The air is dry.
So dry.
Where are you going? No, wait.
What do you want?
- Step aside. - No, there's nothing in here.
You can't...
Oh, my gosh.
What are you doing here?
Hi, Ji Hoon.
It's Min Hyuk. Hey.
Are you all right?
For some reason, you always show up when Min Hyuk is here.
Yes.
Today, I'm here to change come light bulbs.
You guys are dating, right?
- Yes. - No.
No?
Why would you hide when I'm not her parent?
- You're dating, aren't you? - We're not.
"We're not?"
I rush over when thunder strikes, fix your boiler,
change your light bulbs. Am I some janitor?
We never said we were dating.
Do you have to?
Of course, you do. It's important to define stuff.
Ji Hoon.
Why do you keep visiting her?
- She lives here alone. - What?
It's because...
I write better when I'm here, and it's quieter too.
It's quiet here?
I see.
Come with me.
I'll show you the quietest place in the world.
Boss. I can vouch for him.
Pass.
See? I was right.
It's not about you.
It's his face.
What?
Your face vouches for you.
It's perfect.
I was reluctant to leave Min Hyuk in charge.
Do your best for me.
I will. I'll work hard.
Are you going somewhere?
I'll travel for a few months.
You can start today, right?
Yes, I can.
Here.
(Park Yoon Jae)
Yoon Jae's old apron is the only spare we have.
It's fine.
Go sleep at home.
- What time is it? - Three o'clock.
What?
- Come home with me. - What?
I'll finish reading this.
Do you want a biography written about you?
I can't stay any longer. I'm going home.
Okay.
Take care. See you tomorrow.
(Crystal Shoes' Recommendation!)
(My Girlfriend is the Man!)
(Episode 12)
- Hello. - Hey.
That evening,
I waited for Yoon Su, perfectly prepared.
I sweated a lot during my workout.
I got...
so hot.
I will make you fall for me even as a man.
It's dangerous.
Stay away.
The ointment. Where is it?
I'll do everything from now on.
Just sit still.
Since you're here,
why not stay the night?
My sister's away.
I need permission to stay out.
(Jellyfish)
How did you think of that?
That went down as the worst day in Ji Yeon's life.
(Spoon Worm Angel)
(Jellyfish)
Yoon Su would've felt flustered,
but I think he would've found it cute.
(Yu Rim's lips touched mine.)
The kiss with Yu Rim.
Even at that moment, Yoon Su was all I could think about.
Hey!
I was afraid Yoon Su saw,
but I was relieved to see how calm he was.
(Spoon Worm Angel: I was afraid Yoon Su saw,)
(but I was relieved to see how calm he was.)
Who says Yoon Su was calm?
(Jellyfish)
Me, because I'm the writer.
That's not right.
I bet Yoon Su was furious.
How dare you?
Die!
The hanbok date with Yoon Su.
I'd imagined this day for so long.
But what am I even doing?
Even if it were just for show,
I think Yoon Su would've felt really hurt.
Do you think Ji Yeon wanted to play the guy?
She looked forward to the palace date with Yoon Su.
It was on Ji Yeon's bucket list.
(Spoon Worm Angel: She looked forward to...)
(the palace date with Yoon Su.)
(It was on Ji Yeon's bucket list.)
(Jellyfish)
I see.
(Jellyfish: I see.)
"I see?"
I mean, I guess so.
(Gaseo-dong Community Center)
Thank you.
(Look out for neighbors in need.)
(Code of Conduct for Child Protection)
Number six.
I'll take your number tag.
What can I do for you?
I'm here to report a death.
Is it yours?
They have to come in person?
Oh, dear.
My husband died a while ago.
Oh, gosh, no.
I'm sorry.
(General Complaints)
Number 12.
(Number 12)
What do you need today?
I need a resident registration certificate.
It's 60 cents, right?
One, two, three, four, five, six.
You come here for one every other day.
Yes. It's a hobby of sorts.
Give me a moment.
Here.
- No? - No.
Okay.
How would you want a guy confess his feelings?
Did you dream of something?
- You're asking that now? - Yes or no?
I did, actually.
What do you want?
It's a dream I had since I was a kid.
- All the lights are out. - All the lights are out.
At the amusement park.
- An amusement park? - Yes.
The moment I step into an empty amusement park,
the lights on the carousel turn on, and you...
No. The guy's standing there.
You're a writer after all.
Did you watch too many movies?
That's impossible in reality.
An amusement park isn't like a playground.
I shouldn't have asked.
That's just a dream I have.
In real life, you can just say it.
- Come on. - That hurt.
I'm embarrassed now.
Don't be upset.
(Episode 23)
(How much longer will you hold him back?)
(Ji Yeon decided to stop clinging to Yoon Su.)
("Should I really go?")
("Ji Yeon, Do you really want me to leave?")
("Ji Yeon, do you really want me to go?")
("Don't go. Please don't, Yoon Su.")
(Then Yoon Su ran back to me and embraced me.)
(I'm glad I told him. I'm glad I asked him to stay.)
But are you sure you won't regret this?
Yes, sir.
My universe is not here.
Your universe is not here?
No.
I'm sorry.
Well, I don't know what to say, Yoon Jae.
It's very disappointing.
Hold on.
Yes. So you have to hurry up and come here.
What? Are you hurt badly?
No, not really.
It's hard for me to move.
Okay. Wait for me there.
- Yu Ri. - What?
By the way, you should consider freshening up before coming here.
- What? - Nothing. Hurry.
Hey! I'm here.
Where is she?
What's going on?
I couldn't rent the amusement park.
But will you still go out with me?
Yes. I'd like that.
My gosh.
It's snowing.
I'm sorry, but we're closing now.
Excuse me, sir?
(Passport, Republic of Korea)
(Park Yoon Jae)
It's me.
Park Yoon Jae.
I'm back.
What are you doing here?
I got cut from the program.
You got cut?
We sacrificed our relationship for it.
You can get back into the program, right?
I can't.
Open it.
"Yoon Jae is a student who has brought me great disappointment."
"However,"
"he is also someone who has reminded me..."
"of the meaning of the universe and love."
"The universe is so vast that..."
"I have to rely on mere probabilities."
"So I have decided to support your happiness..."
"that is closer to certainty."
"Yoon Jae's universe isn't here,"
"but it is where you are."
"John O'Connor."
Oh, this? I didn't ask him to write it.
He wrote it all on his own.
What do I do now?
Right.
Do you want to go and watch some stars?
- What? - We never got to go to Chuncheon.
Let's go now.
Aren't you cold?
You're not hungry yet?
These are so good.
I'm in Chuncheon with you.
I'm not dreaming, right?
It's a dreamlike reality.
It only took an hour for us to get here.
But how long did it take us to come here?
There are so many stars.
This is it.
I love it.
What a fool.
What?
Nothing.
Oh, right. How's Min Joo doing?
Oh, right.
Yoon Jae.
Give this to your girlfriend.
- What's this? - It's not a bomb.
Just give it to her.
Okay.
Thank you for everything, Min Joo.
Be honest. You're a bit disappointed, aren't you?
You thought I'd break down and beg you to stay,
but I'm letting you go without any drama.
I won't take you back even if you come back.
Okay. Never take me back.
Since this is it for us,
I want to end it on a good note.
So I'd like to ask you...
Give me a hug before you go.
Be healthy.
Don't get sick.
Take care.
Bye.
"I thought Kim Ji Hoon who stayed with Yoon Jae was the worst."
"But I was wrong. Yoon Jae without Kim Ji Hoon was the worst."
"I said I'd take care of Yoon Jae, but I'm taking that back."
"I'm returning him to you. Kang Min Joo."
What's this?
She's returning me?
Yes. Even you think this is crazy, right?
Yes.
By the way,
let me tell you this in advance. You can't trade me in.
You have to take care of me until the end.
What?
When my mom finds out that I'm in Korea,
she might want to return me too.
Oh, right. The unit next door.
Did someone take the unit?
If it's available, I'd like to rent that unit.
Right. Money.
How much is the deposit?
How much is the rent?
I think the cafe owner just might lend me money.
Does she still have the same phone number?
Does the cafe get busy? What about Min Hyuk?
How's he doing? Is he skipping work?
Be honest. I'm better than him, aren't I?
- What are you doing? - Did you not miss me?
What?
Did you not miss me?
I missed you.
Should I have fought for you harder like Yoon Su?
To impress you?
Or you should have been more honest like Kim Ji Yeon.
I could have hugged you harder.
Did you...
read my novel?
Jellyfish.
Who do you think that is?
I'm sorry I took so long.
Just five hours ago,
I believed that our breakup was the happy ending of our story.
When I was missing you like crazy and having the toughest time,
I pictured you being happy somewhere in this world.
That's how I put up with it, but...
But?
But I think I know now.
Our lives won't be all sunshine and rainbows.
But all the moments...
we spend together will remain as happy memories.
It's me.
Ji Eun.
From the first moment I turned into a man...
Remember.
- It's Yangpyeong. - Yangpyeong.
Yangpyeong.
Yes, sir. I was stationed in Pyeongyang.
- Up in... - I drove a tank...
and trained hard!
I could only get through this...
because you were by my side.
As long as I was with you,
it didn't matter if I were a woman...
or a man.
I was just happy.
I'm back.
That's why you came back too, isn't it?
Yes. That's right.
Precisely.
From now on,
it doesn't matter...
whether you are Kim Ji Hoon...
or Kim Ji Eun.
I just want you.
Come on. Hurry. We'll be late to the movie.
You'll still look pretty even without all that effort.
There are so many things I want to do today.
Please?
Hey, Kim Ji...
I'm ready.
My gosh, you and your nagging.
I'm not nagging you. We're running late.
Let's hurry.
I forgot to put on earrings. Hold on.
Let's just go. They aren't that important anyway.
Of course, you'll look pretty with earrings.
Hurry up and put them on.
You've changed.
How could he say that?
I didn't do anything. She's always running late.
It's been 98 days...
since Yoon Jae came back and I changed back.
Luckily, we are happy together...
in our own universe.
Here.
What? What is this?
- It's finally out. - Yes.
You're the first one to get it.
Thank you.
"To my love, Jellyfish."
"Spoon Worm Angel and Jellyfish."
- Look at this. - It's funny, isn't it?
- Our lives aren't quite like... - This is funny.
everyone else's.
Our daily lives, far from ordinary,
actually became even more special.
It looks nice.
- It looks nice, right? - Yes.
I must dress better than Min Hyuk.
So cute.
Ji Eun.
Oh, hey.
- Who is this? - Oh, him.
Say hello. This is my boyfriend, Park Yoon Jae.
And he's from my department. Jang Jin Young.
Gosh, did you get a boyfriend when you were taking a break?
I'm disappointed.
We've been dating even before my break.
- You didn't know. - I wasn't in school then.
As if that would have made a difference.
They're waiting for us. Let's go.
What was that?
You're acting weird.
My gosh.
She doesn't know how to pick the right one.
I'm better than him. Darn it.
- Isn't that funny? - Yes.
That's so funny.
That's hilarious. Hey.
My gosh. Seriously.
- I'm tearing up. - I'm going to use the restroom.
- Let me come with you. - Go ahead.
Okay.
Yoon Jae.
What do I do?
What? Is something wrong?
I think Yu Ri is quite sick.
She's sick? What's wrong with her?
Her head.
Don't tell anyone.
Not even your girlfriend.
Why don't you explain to me what's going on?
She must've been devastated when Ji Hoon suddenly left.
She's been saying weird things lately.
Like what?
She said Kim Ji Eun and Kim Ji Hoon were the same person.
She said they went back and forth between Ji Eun and Ji Hoon.
I cut her some slack...
for having a creative mind since she's a writer.
But is this a delusional disorder or something?
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure about that.
Please reassure your girlfriend...
that she's not a weirdo.
Hey.
- And that she's a nice person. - What?
Okay. I got it.
Yoon Jae. Look over there.
My gosh.
Ji Hye.
Continue that inside.
Ji Hye. Continue that inside.
You guys...
If you guys are going to be together all the time,
you should start paying rent too, Yoon Jae.
Yoon Jae?
What? Hey, Yoon Jae.
What? Young Seok!
- How do you know him? - What?
Yoon Jae...
Hey, your face.
Oh, no. Is the lipstick stain that bad?
It's all over your face too. Oh, no. Let me wipe that.
- It's all over your face too. - Oh, no. What do I do?
Then... My gosh.
What? You two know each other?
Yes. I introduced him to the cafe owner.
- Things didn't work out, though. - Both of us.
He's my sister's first love.
Don't tell my sister about that.
Okay.
A life shared by Kim Ji Hoon and Kim Ji Eun.
We embrace miracles...
like they're part of our daily lives.
(Kim Ji Eun, Kim Ji Hoon)
- Are you ready to go? - Yes.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- All right. - That must be heavy.
It's fine. This is nothing.
Let's go.
- What should we eat? - What should we eat?
Oh, right. What time are we arriving in Chuncheon?
At 5pm.
- Our day-to-day lives... - It's going to be so tasty.
are miracles from the universe.
It's also love.
(Special thanks to Jinyoung for his appearance)
(Thank you for watching My Girlfriend is the Man!)
(My Girlfriend is the Man!)