[The Glory of Queen]
[Episode 20]
Who are you brave people
that dare to trespass
into the Pei Manor?
State your purpose.
Brave people?
Are you blind or what?
Can't you see we live on the streets?
That means we are beggars, understand?
I've never seen such arrogant beggars.
Everyone, grab your weapons
and throw them out!
What should we do, Chief?
Split up and scatter.
What do you mean by that?
Run!
- Over there!
- Quick! Over there!
- After them!
- You go there.
Ping, I've got some good news.
Soon,
we'll be able to be together openly.
Now,
no one can stop me anymore.
When the time comes,
I will see to it
that you marry into the Pei family
with all due honor.
You'll be my wife,
and I'll be your husband.
Then we'll have
a few children of our own,
and our whole family
will live together happily.
Eldest Master!
Bad news. A lot of beggars
have broken into the manor,
claiming they're here
to save Song Zhiyao.
There are just too many of them.
We can't stop them at all.
Useless!
That wretched woman!
Eldest Master,
something has happened at the annex.
A bunch of incompetents!
Follow me!
Where's Pei Jingheng?
He went to save Aunt Ping.
Aunt Ping?
Don't worry, he knows what he's doing.
He mentioned something about directions.
A division tactic.
No, a divergence tactic.
What he really said
was a diversionary tactic.
Let's go.
Zhiyao.
Aunt Ping is asleep.
Miss,
you are so fair and lovely.
You remind me of my niece,
whom I watched grow up.
If she were still alive,
she would probably be
just as elegant and poised as you are.
Perhaps
she's still alive.
If she's still alive,
having spent all these years
without her parents
and family by her side,
she must have suffered greatly.
Miss.
Miss, what's wrong?
There, there.
It's all right now.
Why didn't you tell Aunt Ping
who you really are back there?
Aunt Ping is still alive,
and she's here by my side.
That's already enough.
None of the rest matters.
Pei Jingheng,
I'm no longer an orphan.
I have a family now.
It's just… Pei Jingheng,
I won't let the suffering
my aunt has endured
all these years go unavenged.
But that person is your father,
and I don't want to put you
in a difficult position.
Zhiyao,
ever since I was a child,
I've lived carrying my father's hopes
on my shoulders.
I never complained.
But now,
his obsession runs too deep,
and he's hurt
far too many innocent people.
So even though I know
he's suffered a lot all these years,
that cannot justify
his wrongdoing.
Ping...
Ping.
Pei Qingshan.
Have you recovered?
Have you remembered everything?
That's wonderful, Ping.
Yes.
I remember everything now.
Why did you hire people
to kill my sister and her entire family?
No, I didn't.
Ping, listen to me.
I was just afraid of losing you.
All I wanted then
was to keep you by my side,
so I could take good care of you.
I never once intended to harm
your sister or her family.
I truly didn't know
that the people who took you away
would do something so cruel
to the Song family.
Now, it doesn't matter anymore.
Let it all go, all right?
You no longer need to concern yourself
with the matters that once troubled you.
My wife passed away long ago,
and the Pei family
is now under my control.
I can have you marry into the Pei family
with dignity, openly and honorably.
You're terrifying.
For the sake of your own interests,
you'd even kill your own mother
and younger sister.
How many times do I have to tell you?
They left me with no choice!
And...
And that meddlesome Pei Xiuning.
She had already uncovered
the counterfeit workshop.
If she kept digging,
she would've found you next.
I had no choice but to kill her.
And as for my mother,
as long as she lived,
we could never truly be together.
Look how perfect things are now.
All I need to do
is offer her some incense
and finish her funeral rites,
then you can marry into the Pei family.
Also, I swear to Heaven
that the Pei family
shall belong to you and me alone.
You brute!
You wretched brute!
How dare you commit matricide
and murder your own sister?
Song Zhiyao,
this was all your doing, wasn't it?
Jingheng,
are you really just going to stand there
and watch that vile woman
scheme against your father?
Don't forget, you're a man, too!
Are you really willing
to spend your whole life
being trampled under these women's feet?
This has nothing to do with gender.
Wrong is wrong.
Father,
turn back while you still can.
Jingheng,
do you really think
I can still turn back?
Father.
Don't worry, Jingheng.
I'm not going anywhere.
I am the Eldest Master
of the Pei family, after all.
You expect me
to bow and scrape,
to kneel and beg for mercy, don't you?
You expect me
to grovel like a dog, don't you?
You vicious women!
Don't even think about it!
Never!
It's...
It's all over.
Jingheng,
there's no turning back for me now.
Father!
Watch out!
[Sihe Fragrance Shop]
- Congratulations.
- Thank you. Please step inside.
Congratulations, Madam Song.
- You are too kind.
- Thank you.
- Please step inside.
- You've been on our minds all along.
- Thank you.
- Please step inside.
You're too kind.
But Yao
is the true owner
of this Sihe Fragrance Shop.
From now on,
she'll be relying on your support.
Please, come in.
This is the grand opening
of Sihe Fragrance Shop.
Where could they have gone?
Forget about Chief.
Have you seen her husband?
Please, come in.
Hope we won't miss the auspicious hour.
What exactly are they doing?
Thank you. Please step inside.
You know how a hungry dog
won't let go of a meat bun, right?
That's exactly how it is.
♪We first met♪
♪The wind blew softly♪
♪Our eyes met♪
♪And the heart was stirred♪
♪That tender affection♪
♪Shone through the eyes♪
I'm hungry.
♪Your smile captured my heart♪
Then I'll get you something to eat.
No.
♪Night and day, we stay close♪
I'll eat you.
♪The scent of sweetness♪
♪Floats high in the clouds♪
Pei Jingheng,
I am your wife.
How dare you act this way before me?
Cross me, and I'll divorce you.
♪You alone hold my heart♪
Who was it that told me
she would always be mine
and never betray me?
I was saying that to the little fool.
Are you him?
♪Making memories together♪
♪I only wish your feelings mirror mine♪
♪I'll never betray this love♪
♪I won't forget the moment
my heart skipped a beat♪
♪My heart skipped a beat♪
♪I won't forget every day and night♪
♪Every day and night♪
♪I dream of romantic moments with you♪
♪Wondering how you feel about me♪
♪Whenever I close my eyes,
all I see is your smile♪
♪Under the stars, we meet♪
♪The secret about you
is buried deep in my heart♪
♪I draw near, then pull away, fearing
I might yield to this attraction♪
♪I like to think I'm keeping my cool♪
♪But my instincts
keep pulling me closer♪
♪Unwittingly,
I've fallen completely for you♪
♪Can the sacrifices of this life
measure the depth of love?♪
♪It's too late to summon the courage
to hold you once more♪
♪Having witnessed
all the world's splendor♪
♪I've felt joy and sorrow
for one soul alone♪
♪For our kindred souls,
all I can give is this humble heart♪
♪If I encounter you in this life♪
♪Fate is already fulfilled♪
♪Let this chapter become a memory,
breaking free from destiny♪
♪In the next life,
may the course of time lead me to you♪
♪With a sincere heart,
I shall carry our love forward♪