Today's Webtoon
Can you give that to me?
How did you come here, Jun Yeong?
That gift, give it to me.
Episode 10: A star doesn't disappear. It reappears someday.
I heard that Young Toon's next editor-in-chief will get an amazing offer.
They're contacting Ji Hyeong.
Going home?
Do you want to grab a drink?
Why not?
On Ma Eum!
Your boyfriend?
No, no. He's just a coworker.
I guess you had a friend coming.
I'll take my leave.
Why are you leaving already? Let's drink together.
Yes, you came this far. Let's drink together.
It's okay. You two have a good time.
Come on.
Where do you think you're going?
Then, I'll stay for a bit and leave.
Okay.
Could we have some glasses, and you're drinking beer, right?
One beer and one Sprite, please.
Okay.
- Do you want to switch seats?
- It's fine as is.
You said you were having a hard time,
but you had a reason for having a good time at work.
What do you mean?
I got a call from Mom.
I'm going to catch this call, but you're dead meat if you say weird stuff.
She knows me too well.
Oh, thanks.
Hello, I'm Ma Eum's friend, Lee Eun Yeong.
Hello, my name is Gu Jun Yeong.
I'm working as a webtoon PD with Ma Eum.
If you don't mind me asking, your age is...?
- I'm 26.
- We're the same age.
Let me pour you a glass.
- Thank you.
- Wait, wait, wait.
He can't drink alcohol.
You can't drink, you know.
Drink Sprite.
Here you go.
Thank you.
What is this?
You two are coworkers and the same age.
Why so polite?
I thought she was your seonbae.
Is that so?
I want to be friends.
Is it uncomfortable?
No. I like it.
We should also skip the honorifics.  Shall we?
Okay.
You asked first, okay?
Okay then, shall we start for real?
Okay. Shall we all drink?
"Shall?"
Have... a drink... let's?
It's not going to work. You drink, too.
Here.
Shall... Let me pour you one?
"Shall? Let me?"
- Shall we?
- I will. I will pour you a glass.
Good, good.
- You're home.
- Where's Ma Eum?
Not here yet. It looked like she was having a drink with Eun Yeong.
I see.
Dear. Try some watermelon. It's so sweet.
Yeah, Dad. Try some. It's very sweet.
- You move.
- Why?
I'll wash my hands first.
Why pick on me?
Ma Eum's Room
Then, Artist Ma Hae Gyu went to a rehab center?
Small Cart Bar
Yeah. He said he'll come back after getting treatment.
He asked us to look after Yu Na while he's gone.
Good for him.
What exactly do you want to tell me?
What do I want to tell you?
I was offered the chief editor position at Young Toon.
Really? Hey!
Wow! That's great news!
You should've been one a long time ago.
It's actually a bit late for you.
Hey, congrats!
Your time to shine is finally here.
Nice.
I was just offered. Just an offer.
I'm telling you only because I don't want you to hear from someone else.
With this kind of stuff, you can accept it first and then tell me.
These chances don't come by often. Especially from that Young Toon.
Also, it's not like anyone can be a chief editor.
You can do it with this perfect timing and an incredible opportunity.
I'm so happy for you.
Congrats, man.
It's not perfect timing for us.
Just think about yourself.
It's here.
Hyeong.
Ji Hyeong. Even if...
I change my mind and cling to you,
you just make sure
to think about only yourself until the very end.
I'm saying to decide with yourself as the top priority.
That's the only advice I can give you as your
long-time hyeong and as your colleague.
I'm going now.
Take care, Hyeong.
I mean, you still should've set up a future meeting.
What can I do when Artist Ha doesn't even let me talk about a meeting
saying, "Why do you need to put my cartoon on the internet?"
How can he send me away at the door when we've known each other for so long?
But you did set a meeting with Artist Yeom tomorrow, right?
Yeah.
Hyeong, this is seriously an employment fraud.
I mean...
you brought someone who was set to transfer to another publishing hous—
What do you mean fraud?
The future is opening for the webtoon.
The Golden Age.
Golden.
Th-That conman...
Fun Maru
Funny Toony
Webtoon Bottle
JinjyeoriToon, Ginger Toon?
(Jinjyeori, sounds like "Gingery," means sick and tired of.)
- Ji Hyeong.
- Yes?
How is this for the logo?
GingerToon?
- You said to go with GingerToon.
-  Hyeong.
But it's still a company name.
Isn't JinjyeoriToon and this picture too much?
You said you don't like Jinjyeori, so we're going with GingerToon.
But the only thing GingerToon reminds you of is the gingerbread man.
GingerToon
Can you just help with organizing these?
We have to go now. We're late!
Wait, wait!
- Why?
- The contract is missing.
Didn't you leave it there before?
-  It's not here. Where did it go?
- U-Unni, it's here.
Oh, yes. Thank you, thank you!
Hurry and go now.
We'll be back.
I'm going, going. I'll be back!
- Take care.
- We'll be back!
Everyone!
Finally, Artist Hae Su also signed the contract with GingerToon!
Hurray!
As soon as he saw the contract, it was a done deal!
I knew it!
We need to take a picture on a day like this.
- A picture.
- Okay.
- Ten seconds.
- Hurry! Come, come!
- Same pose, everyone.
One, two, three.
When is it?
Just keep smiling.
Ginger
Toon
Deputy Editor.
Yeah?
This is the OST production proposal.
- Please confirm.
- Oh, okay.
Is this... confirmed with the artists?
Yes. I'm planning to meet Artists Pomme and Sin Dae Ryuk today and tell them.
I see, okay.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
By the way...
What are all these?
Stuff from GingerToon days.
You're here.
- Hello.
- PD On Ma Eum is here, too?
I came because I missed you.
Come this way, please.
They are my assistants.
They are Neon Webtoon PDs. Say hi to each other.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm PD On Ma Eum.
Hello, I'm PD Gu Jun Yeong.
In the midst of all this, I'm glad that the assistants are nearby.
We won't be falling behind the schedule, thanks to you two.
Right, Artist Pomme?
PD Gu here is always worrying about deadlines.
As I told you before, I'm always worried about you, above all.
I don't know. You don't sound sincere.
Say something for me.
What?
About my sincerity.
I don't know about that.
Just once.
Well, yeah...
I said I don't know.
I'll do my best.
Artist Sin. I told you this last time.
Yes, your cartoon is important
but it's not as valuable as people.
You're also included in that "people."
Eat well and sleep well.
This is great!
It's definitely distinct from existing characters.
What do you think?
The facial expressions are good.
However...
she seems oddly familiar.
Really?
I don't think any of the characters remind me of anyone.
If it's okay, I'll add the colors and finish.
Okay.
Did you review the OST-related paperwork?
I think Ji Hyeong will go to Young Toon this time.
Excuse me?
Geez, you scared me.
Deputy Editor is...
Wh-Why to Young Toon?
He always has a lot of offers.
But he already rejected Young Toon once.
He came here with us instead of going to Young Toon when GingerToon was being dissolved.
This time is different.
It's an offer for the chief editor position.
The chief editor position is not an easily found opportunity, right?
Right. He'd be called a fool to reject
the terms that come with the offer of being a chief editor.
Young Toon?
Where are you going? A meeting?
To see Artist Oh Yun.
- You decided?
- Yes.
I still don't think it'll be easy.
I'll be back.
Should I get you a pep pill?
The door is closing.
Fighting.
Nice.
Okay.
Two remaining.
What the heck? I'm winning right now.
I texted you several times yesterday that I'll be visiting,
but you didn't answer.
I also called you in front of your house,
I didn't know because it was hectic.
It's tough on you these days, right?
Your manuscript isn't progressing, either.
It's always tough.
It's not like this is my first or second year in the field.
There are times when things don't work out like this.
I'm sure it'll work itself out.
Will it really?
This is your first time staying in the low rankings for so long.
You did get tired a little bit here and there.
But you were never lost like this.
I'm not lost.
I'm going my way, but the people are not recognizing it.
That's what gets me frustrated.
And I suddenly start thinking,
"Did I go the wrong way in the first place?"
Did I really start off on the wrong foot?
What is this?
You also said it was interesting after listening to my explanation.
You said it's all fine. You said let's go with the series as is.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
What?
If I could turn back time, if I could have another chance,
I would've mustered up more courage and opposed it strongly.
I wanted to follow your opinion as much as possible.
I was also afraid that you might go somewhere else if I opposed you.
But I think that was a dereliction of duty on my part.
When I saw the first synopsis and storyboards for "Origin of Mankind,"
it was very difficult and obscure.
I also thought it was a genre where your forte wouldn't come through.
What is my forte?
Silly jokes?
Making people happy, whoever that is.
A comedy webtoon, huh...
I'm not in the mood to laugh at all.
Don't lose, don't lose.
I was sure that I had met a genius then.
Why?
What is it?
Th-This is so... Aigoo, aigoo.
I'm fine, fine.
What is he doing?
Do you remember the first thing I said when I met you?
I'm going crazy.
"This world needs your webtoon."
"Because at least while someone is reading this webtoon,
he will be genuinely happy."
Okay.
That was true.
I heard you say that then, and I got so excited.
I thought I had kissed my debut goodbye when GingerToon vanished.
But I was able to make a grand debut with you at Neon.
You trusted me back then.
Please trust me one more time.
Your humor is warm, not cynical or on edge.
It has humanism.
I also know that you planned "Origin of Mankind" because you wanted to show humanism.
It's not just because of the revenue.
For your own good, I realized that it's right to decide quickly,
after much consideration as the PD.
If my decision turns out wrong, you can reprimand me all you want.
However. I, Choi Du Hui,
think that it's about time to fold "Origin of Mankind"
and prepare a new work as our next hand.
I was going to trample on all those people
who said my success only happened because of my looks and the media,
saying that my work is shallow.
I was going to shut up all those people who said
that I can only make people laugh.
Artist Oh.
Making other people laugh...
is the hardest thing to do.
No one does it better than you in this country.
I hope that you'll take pride in that.
PD Choi...
I never once thought about Deputy Editor not being here.
Your total is 5,000 won.
- One more of the same thing, please.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Thinking that Deputy Editor Seok might leave,
I just can't focus on work.
Is it to that point?
I mean, changing jobs is quite common these days.
Especially since he was offered the position of chief editor,
- I think it's a congratulatory thing.
- Yes. That's true.
It's congratulatory for him, a hundred times over.
I just feel sad about it.
Since he's my first immediate supervisor.
I guess you relied on him a lot.
Yeah.
I did.
I did learn a lot from him, too.
I only troubled him thus far and came up with lots of hassles.
I should've learned the trade faster
had I known that he was going to leave so soon.
Is it hot?
No, no.
Answer Right Away
Excuse me.
Yes.
Do you also work out, Mr. Gu?
Taking care of yourself is important these days.
I sometimes jog to ease my mind.
My, my. Doing cardio alone is not enough exercise.
Real men should lift some weights.
I see.
- Pardon?
- Towel.
Thank you.
Do you have something else for me to do?
I think I sent you all the information you needed.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
You don't even know what I'll need.
I noticed last time that
PD Kwon's revenue portion was a lot larger than everyone else's.
I'd like to see his artist candidates or a list of researched information.
Well, that's PD Kwon's personal documents...
That's what I want to see.
While it's a risk for a single PD to take up a majority of the revenue pie,
he also keeps the core info to himself.
It's also dangerous to let him do as he pleases.
There's nothing bad for me to know about it in advance.
What is this?
Raise your arm.
You said you only jog. Yeah, right.
It's a charm. Lucky charm.
You gave me this on the day I had an interview.
Oh, that's right.
But you got rejected then.
But eventually, I got in, and I'm sitting here now.
Deputy Editor!
Oh, my God!
What are you doing over there?
But why are you like that?
Did something happen?
- Yes.
- Why? What is it?
I heard that you're getting a promotional transfer.
Where did you learn a word like that?
Before when I was doing judo,
my seonbaes used to say that when the coaches
or the directors transferred to better positions.
I see.
Anyway, who told you that I'm being promoted?
PD Kwon told us.
That you're going to Young Toon as the chief editor.
That it's the talk of the town in the industry right now.
PD Kwon did?
Yes.
But that's not true.
- Sorry?
- I didn't decide yet.
Of course, I did get the offer.
Then you might still r-reject the o-offer?
Yeah.
Why, do you not want me to go?
Well, this is shameless and selfish of me, but
I don't want you to go, of course.
But everyone is saying that it's a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity you can't refuse.
So, I can't really talk to you about it...
Well, it is a good opportunity.
Lots of people covet that position.
But why couldn't you decide yet?
Just because other people want something,
I don't have to want it just like them.
I'm in the process of studying my heart carefully.
Trying to figure out what I really want and
what kind of decision I wouldn't regret later.
♫  Even today when I'm tired, my day is shining.  ♫
♫  Everyday is my birthday.  I am like an awkward kid.  ♫
Cheer up. It's okay.
♫  Everything feels new as though I were reborn  ♫
♫  The little whisper of wind and the warmth of the blazing sun  ♫
- One moment.
- Okay.
♫  greeted tired be with a "great job."  ♫
Yeah, what's up?
♫  greeted tired me with a "great job."  ♫
♫  In the dark night when everyone is asleep  ♫
Okay, I got it.
No, I'll go there.
Okay.
♫  I'm the only one who forgot to sleep  ♫
♫  Like the star passing through distant time   ♫
Well, then.
♫  which reached me  ♫
Go on home and see you tomorrow at the office.
- Okay.
- All right.
See you.
♫  Will I also be able to shine?  ♫
D-Deputy Editor!
♫  How is your night? How is your heart  ♫
♫  How is your night? How is your heart?  ♫
Yeah?
♫  Even though the day was intense, the night shines  ♫
Nothing.
Please take care.
♫  For me every day the star greets me "Good day"  ♫
♫  It shines on my fading wish  ♫
♫  The whisper of a quiet night, the starlight cast on my room  ♫
♫  greeted tired me saying "great job"  ♫
♫  In the dark night when everyone is asleep, I'm the only one who forgot to sleep  ♫
♫  My heart which shines like that far away starlight  ♫
♫  Like the star passing through distant time which reached me  ♫
♫  Will I also be able to shine?  ♫
♫  How is your day?  ♫
♫  A night dreaming dreams  ♫
♫  which cheers for your heart  ♫
Neon Mail
From Seok Ji Hyeong: August - This is homework!
Then, what is a genuine editor?
In one word.
That's what you have to find out.
Oh, me?
Me… I see.
Starting next month, send me your answer each and every month, you got it?
♫  My heart which shines like that far away starlight  ♫
♫  Like the star passing through distant time which reached me  ♫
♫  Will I also be able to shine?  ♫
♫  How is your day?  ♫
September: What is a genuine editor?
♫  A night dreaming dreams  ♫
An editor is
♫  will shine on your day  ♫
♫  and cheer for your heart  ♫
Why are you still conflicted?
Where else will you get a better offer than this?
Everyone has a place that suits them.
And everyone is attracted to different terms.
No matter how I think about it,
I think you're a better fit for that position.
Why me of all people?
Because I want to be with you.
I need to learn more from you, Oppa.
Just like how you chose Chief Editor Jang Man Cheol and went to Neon.
I also chose you as my chief editor.
Didn't you ever regret
your decision then?
This might be your last chance to reverse that decision.
R.I.P. Gu Ae Ri, Sophia
Why the heck are you refusing to go?
Shouldn't you be thankful that it's Young Toon that you're switching to?
Especially under the circumstances?
Oppa.
Let's think realistically.
I don't care if they trash talk about me.
I just need for us two to be together.
Oppa...
It's all an excuse.
What excuse?
You just chose Chief Editor Jang Man Cheol.
Instead of me.
Search Result: Seok Ji Hyeong
Deputy Editor.
Hey.
Did you see the email I sent you yesterday?
Yesterday, I sent the homework,
"What is a webtoon editor?" that you told me to do.
Well, the meaning behind that homework is not about
me checking it, but you doing it every month.
That's true.
Just because I don't check, don't do it half-a**ed or skip on it. Okay?
Of course not.
I always think of that homework as my priority while working.
You're doing well.
One second.
Yes, Artist.
Have you been doing well?
Deputy Editor, are you going to Young Toon by chance?
You are.
You worked that hard to stop me from going to Young Toon.
Now, you're going to be their chief editor by yourself?
Whoa. Isn't this totally a betrayal and a stab in the back?
Come on now. I told you I haven't made up my mind yet.
That is what I had first thought.
But on second thought, it's about time you become a chief editor.
Also, if you become Young Toon's chief editor,
it would be more convenient for me when I move there as well.
So, I thought it wasn't such a bad thing.
Are you going to move to Young Toon?
No.
But you can never be sure about anything in life.
This field is changing so fast these days.
And honestly,
it's a good thing if an ally like you is a chief editor of any platform.
Isn't that true?
Okay, then please contact me right away.
Okay.
Publishing Rights Contract for OOO
Neon Webtoon Rankings
Copyright, Company, Publishing Rights
What are you peeking at?
Your daughter is just so adorable.
That's my son.
I'm kidding.
She's lovely, right? My Ji Ho.
I'm thinking of debuting her in a girl group later.
Why?
Curious about these files?
I'll show you when you grow up a little more.
You won't understand anything now.
Just get to work.
Okay.
Kwon Yeong Bae, 2022-2023 Expected Artist Data
2022-2023 Expected Artist Data
I need to go to the bathroom.
- PD Kwon.
- You won't get it but take a look. Look all you want.
And if you have an idea that can help us, then think about that.
This is why my hoobaes fall for me.
Look at this.
See right here.
You can do stuff like this, too.
- Isn't it neat?
- Whoa, yes.
Lately, I'm deep into applying new effects.
Because I can work in separate layers,
it's so much fun because I can try out different variations.
It's so crazy that there's still more to learn even at this age.
It's hard, but I'm still glad.
You're great, sir.
Anyhow, are you concerned about something?
Do I look that way?
I don't know what the problem is, but
try to separate the layers of your thoughts carefully.
You turn off the layers that are on top and
look at each one separately,
then you can see the true nature of the issue.
I see.
You're by yourself today.
Chief Editor also came alone last night.
I see.
- Please have a good time.
- Thank you.
Young Toon CEO
Deputy Editor Seok Ji Hyeong,
you'll give me an answer by the end of the week, right?
Did you see the email I sent you yesterday?
On Ma Eum
An editor is a webtoon artist's cheer squad.
Artist Baek, your drawings...
I mean, your comic drawings are not sagging.
Yes, so when you are drawing, sir...
if being hunched over was the issue,
you can adjust the drawing board angle
and if you can draw from the frontal view...
Then I can draw webtoons that I'm not embarrassed about?
Yes, that is right.
You must always breathe energy into the artist, telling them that they can do it
and also encourage their confidence.
An editor is a troubleshooter for webtoon artists.
No, we can't suspend!
Wh-Where are you right now?
I'm on my way to find Artist Na's girlfriend.
What?
Promise me.
Promise!
- Great!
- For the artist to meet the deadline,
do whatever you must do.
An editor is a webtoon artist's running mate.
One, two. One, two.
You gladly join on the lonely marathon
of the artist as another leg and
- One, two!
- finish the race together.
Peeve Weapon.
Then you are Artist Sin Dae Ryuk?
An editor is Columbus.
To discover a new continent called "Rookie artist,"
you willingly embark on long adventures.
Pretty good.
An editor is a gardener.
Eat well and...
sleep well.
You trusted me back then.
Please trust me one more time.
Fighting, Ma Yu Na.
I'm sorry.
A gardener who looks after and cares for numerous trees and flowers called "Webtoon artists."
Sometimes you get pricked by a rose's thorns and get wounded.
Sometimes, you can't do anything else but cut off some overgrown branches or grass.
On Ma Eum.
Think carefully.
Without readers, there's no reason for us to exist.
Even this department each and everyone.
The gardener must
care for the trees and flowers responsibly until the very end,
so that they can bear the best possible fruits.
So that many people will visit the garden and fully enjoy its beauty.
Webtoon/Web Novel
Top 10: 1. The Girl's Rule, 2. Gumiho Princess,
3. Peeve Weapon, 4. Full Count, 5. Dragon's Dream
This is my garden.
Ma Eum.
Deputy Editor.
- You're still here?
- Y-Yes.
You've been diligent with the homework.
You saw it?
You did well.
- You were better than me.
- Gosh. No way.
I'm serious.
A long time ago,
when Chief Editor gave me that homework for the first time,
I think I gave him maybe about two answers.
I think I'll only be a bother here.
I'll leave first.
No, it's okay.
I'm going. See you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
2022-2023 Expected Artist Data
Story Artist List
Received Pay, Desired Pay
Hello.
It's me.
Who...
I said let's see next time, Uncle.
Why? So you can change your number and disappear again?
How can you treat a person like a debt collector?
What is it you want?
Chip in on the living expenses.
How long did we even stay at your place?
Honestly, we barely kept ourselves from starving while walking on eggshells.
- Aren't you being too shameless?
- Hey.
You can't be doing this to me.
While you were staying abroad,
who do you think took care of Ae Ri's funeral?
When your noona died, I was the most sorrowful person.
The one who cried sincere tears? I was the only one.
That's why I came to see you for the last time.
Enjoy your food and don't ever come by my workplace again.
S**t. You ungrateful a**hole.
I worked so hard to raise the two of you,
considering my younger sister, who passed away first.
You took all of my parents' insurance money.
On top of that,
you constantly took my noona's part-time income she made as a student.
You were sorrowful when she died?
You must've gotten angry because your money source died.
Damso Ox Bone Soup, Blood Sausage, Hot Spicy Meat Stew
Hey, PD Gu. Have you eaten?
Hot Spicy Meat Stew is not for me.
See you later.
Jun Yeong! Hey!
How do you know that person?
He's the one! The one who caused Ae Ri's death.
What brings you all the way here?
Because I decided.
I thought I should give my answer quickly.
What is it? Is something wrong?
No. There's nothing special.
Jun Yeong.
We have a sudden company dinner later.
And it's at a premium beef place. Isn't that great?
Yeah.
You don't care for it? A beef place?
- No.
- Right? You like it, right?
What do you like about it?
Today is Deputy Editor's farewell dinner.
You're so clueless...
I'm going to eat a lot later.
Why are you like this today? It's scary.
Why? What? Why?
PD Kwon, you never join on company dinners.
It's premium beef. Korean beef.
He came because this is Deputy Editor Seok Ji Hyeong's farewell dinner.
Farewell party, my foot. It doesn't even cost the base fee to get there in a cab.
You guys always overreact.
We all know.
Even if you say that, we know that you're saddest about him leaving.
PD Kwon. You're trembling, right?
Because you might be forced to take the deputy editor position.
I already said it. I'm never doing it.
Why not?
I think you'll be good at it.
Am I crazy? That position is a lot of work, a lot of stress,
and the only thing left in the end is meaningless flattery.
You don't even know anything about it.
You still get a raise, though.
You really don't know anything.
That tiny increase.
That's nothing compared to the incentives that he's getting right now.
You know well.
There's probably no way Deputy Editor won't leave, right?
How would I know that?
It would be right for him to go
from his perspective.
Whoa, wh-what's going on? Are you pouring yourself?
Gu Jun Yeong.
Give it to me.
You two now skip the honorifics, huh?
Yes.
On Ma Eum, you're sprinting from the beginning?
She must be upset. He was her first immediate supervisor.
Aigoo, you all love to overreact.
Hyeong, what's this sudden company dinner about?
On top of that, Korean beef?
I just want to feed you some meat before you go.
Hyeong, I have something to tell you.
Tell me there. They're all waiting.
Hurry along.
Th-That's not it.
I'm so full. I ate too much.
- Oh, you're here.
- Hey.
It's fine. Don't get up.
The main character is here.
What main character?
Don't bother. We all know.
Know what?
About your job change, Deputy Editor.
It seems that everyone knows about my business besides me.
Yes, it's that kind of a gathering.
All right.
Today is, as you all know,
Deputy Editor Seok Ji Hyeong, who has been with us...
through the highs and the lows since Ginger Toon to Neon today,
- will be going to Young Too—
- W-Wait! Chief Editor, wait.
You want to say it yourself?
Yes. I'll tell them.
- Well, right no—
- One moment.
- What are you doing?
- Let me be.
You're scaring me toda—
One grand farewell, please.
I know very well what all of you're thinking right now.
As well as what kind of talk is going around within the team.
- Howeve—
- I'm so sorry, one moment, please.
I really tried not to cry...
What do I do?
What's wrong with her?
Deputy Editor.
I'll do better! Could you not go anywhere?
What do I do?
Aigoo. I've never seen her drunk.
I'm not going.
Please don't go.
That's what I said. I'm not going.
What?
Don't worry.
Really?
Yeah.
- I decided not to go.
- Huh?
Wait, are you really?
W-Wait, why?
Are you crazy?
Do you mean it?
Yes. I mean it.
I thought about it through and through.
About the reason why I'm so hesitant to leave this place.
As you said, is it because of an unnecessary sense of obligation?
Or is it some kind of fear about a new challenge?
I constantly looked dep into myself.
However, I just want to...
take responsibility of the new projects that I started here and
the people that I have become acquainted with to the end.
I want to see the trees that I planted and the flower seeds that I sowed,
all grow up well
and bear fruits in this garden called "Neon."
Well, that's too bad.
Your desk might be gone come next year.
What do you mean?
The Neon executives intend to acquire Young Toon.
I think I still have a lot of work to do in Neon.
Also, it seems that I have a friend I need to look after.
Anyhow, stop saying unnecessary stuff now.
Ma Eum, stop crying.
Let's enjoy ourselves and feast on meat.
Okay, okay! Drink, drink.
Shall we have a toast?
Cheers to Deputy Editor Seok Ji Hyeong!
Cheers!
Stop overreacting.
- I love it! Cheers for Deputy Editor Seok Ji Hyeong!
-  Cheers!
Hey, Ji Hyeong.
Okay, then w-wait, wait.
Okay, then.
Let's say, "Cheers for the Neon Webtoon Editorial Department."
Sounds good.
- For the Neon Webtoon Editorial Department!
- Cheers!
Yes, we're all together again!
Why did we even come?
Thank you, CEO.
You gave me a really good opportunity, but I still fall short of the position.
Deputy Editor Jang Hye Mi will do a good job.
Yes.
Thank you, CEO.
Why did you come out?
Deputy Editor.
I want to ask you something.
Sure. What is it?
Do you know this person?
How do you know Ae Ri?
♫   Life doesn't go the way you want. Things happen which you never expected   ♫
♫  When I suddenly lose my footing, grab me.  You know everything.  ♫
♫  I feel alone that. Of all things you should ignore a rough relationship.  ♫
Today's Webtoon
You know Ae Ri we used to work with back in GingerToon days?
Did she have any other family members?
Now that you moved into a new place, I hope only good things happen for you in this new house.
They tossed her bait, saying that they'll hire her as a full-time employee.
Excuse me, you've met me before at a webtoon artist's apartment, right?
What brings you here to the headquarters?
I had some documents to deliver.
She was the best person to let us know why we should create webtoons.
This person is Jun Yeong's older sister?
♫  Whoa, whoa, whoa, open your eyes  ♫
♫   Someday you will stand again.  ♫
♫  Whoa, whoa, whoa. Think. I think you will smile brightly.  ♫