=He Kills It=
=Episode 11=
(From here on out,
I'll live for my family.)
(But right now,)
(just let me be myself,)
(even if it's for a little while.)
Sister,
I saw nothing.
You guys continue.
Do not marry Shen Guohao.
Give me some time,
I'll surely...
Wu Ming.
Stop.
No one said he'd protect me before.
I don't know whether you really mean it.
I'm touched anyway.
Leave here now.
With all your stuff.
(You're right.)
(Except medical skills,
I've got nothing.)
(But I'll never let anyone
touch my girl.)
(Never.)
That's enough.
Sister, who's that person?
I'm finally having a brother-in-law?
Expecting a husband?
I'll find you one.
Dishes ready.
Hey, Boss.
We didn't order these two dishes.
(Shan Ye)
They're on my wife.
Come around more often.
Hey, Boss,
your wife always has a stone face.
What's got her so cheerful today?
Hey, Bro.
You got any more of that med
you gave me last time?
Boss,
as long as you don't overdo it,
one pill is enough.
That med is
seriously potent.
I'm still feeling it, no joke.
Not for me. For my buddy.
You know.
Some meds
are priceless.
(Shan Ye)
Alright, got it.
Enjoy your dinner.
It's all on me.
Boss, so generous.
Enjoy.
I'm at your service.
Mr. Ming,
what med did you give him?
Can I have a try?
Not now.
Well,
how's that thing going?
Found a place.
200,000 in rent per year.
Good.
Tomorrow, ask Lei Changhe
about Shen Guohao from Jinling.
Why bother?
Shen Guohao,
one of the Four Young Masters.
What's this about?
He stole my girl.
He can steal any woman
he wants.
What did you say?
Let's see
who comes out on top.
(Ling, trust me.)
(You will be a mom.)
(I'll protect you.)
(I believe)
(you'll make the smart decision
for the Yang Group,)
(since it's on the brink.)
Send me a contraceptive pill now.
Come on, Mr. Ming.
Grandmaster!
Such a coincidence.
Low-key, please.
Sounds like you're begging for alms.
Begging for alms?
Grandmaster.
Benefactor!
I'm not begging.
Order whatever you want.
It's on me.
Hey, Beauty.
You call him Grandmaster.
I'm his bro.
So I'm your granduncle?
Want me to call you Granduncle, huh?
Depends on what gift you're offering.
My gift
is this big,
and this long.
Are you messing around?
Hey! I'm a decent guy.
I'm talking about...
It's the thought that counts.
Don't mind it.
Grandmaster,
where's your greeting gift?
You skipped the kneeling ceremony.
Grandmaster,
my respects to you!
Alright, get up now.
It's my insights
(Acupoint Map)
about complicated illnesses.
Thanks, Grandmaster!
Mr. Ming,
this book of insights
is worth a fortune.
You just gave it away?
It's a copy.
I have plenty.
Mr. Jin.
Doc, great to see you here.
But today I've got other stuff today.
Are you here looking for them?
Yep.
For him.
Bro,
come with me.
Mr. Jin,
you claimed to break my legs,
and make me lay your foundation.
How dare I go with you?
Brat,
watch your mouth!
Tired of living?
Keep it down.
Grandmaster,
need my help?
You just need to pay a bit.
No worries.
I'm not that rich.
Hey, you! I'm talking to you!
Are you deaf!
I said, keep it down.
Just keep it down.
You're talking so loud.
People will think you're the boss.
Let me put it this way.
A big shot's been asking after you,
by name.
You, eating at this cheap street stall,
got no business talking to me.
I'm being nice. Don't be a fool.
Nice?
Fine.
You should
look the part.
What's wrong with you?
Take him.
Who dare harm him!
(Why does he smell like my sister?)
(Her perfume is unique.)
(It's him!)