=He Kills It=
=Episode 4=
What's wrong?
Afraid I'll poison you?
This is your place.
Would you dare?
Mr. Long, stop beating around the bush.
It's becoming boring.
Chairman Yang
is now gravely ill.
The Yang family business
is in a precarious situation.
Your second uncle
wants to rise to power.
I think
you've figured
all these out already, haven't you?
If Mr. Long
came today just to tell me these,
there's no need keep talking.
Calm down.
Let's put it this way.
The Yang Group's success
was mostly made by your dad.
But he passed away so young.
You and your sister
are too new to the game.
Not enough clout.
But the shares you hold
are the most
besides your grandpa.
So,
if your grandpa
really
passes away,
and something happened to you two,
what would happen?
What do you mean?
Alright.
I'll be straight.
Your second uncle asked me
to collaborate with him.
He wants to take you down
so that he can take power.
After that,
I'll get some shares of the Yang Group.
Long Gang.
Do you think your petty tricks
could bring chaos to our family?
We have power struggles,
but we will not kill each other.
Miss Yang, you may be smart,
but I think
you're a little too naive.
I can't handle this matter myself.
Only if your Long family takes action,
will it be foolproof.
Do you believe now?
Why do you tell me
about this?
Let me be honest with you.
For me, whether working
with you or your uncle,
it makes
no difference.
Don't be delusional.
Working with you
is like partnering with a tiger.
Our family's own matters,
I will handle them.
I knew you wouldn't give in.
But I
don't want to be cruel either.
Well, doing one thing
with different approaches
will yield different results.
And my method
is to keep you and your sister
in my own hands.
You drugged the wine?
Sha!
Go ahead, scream.
Scream.
Scream all you want.
They are already under my control.
But don't worry.
I won't lay a hand on you tonight.
Unless you beg me.
Then I won't be able to refuse.
Run!
Hurry up.
How about it?
Are you in a lot of pain now?
Long Gang.
I'd rather die
than let you succeed!
Aren't you always lofty
like an ice queen?
Tonight, I want you to see
what you
look like
when you fall!
Excuse me.
Are you Lei Changhe?
Who are you?
How did you get in?
Through the window.
Nonsense!
This is the thirteenth floor.
I don't care that.
Get out of here!
So you are Lei Changhe?
You're Lei Changhe!
Are you crazy?
This is Lei Changhe's room.
The person in the photo is him.
Where is he?
Your whole family is nuts!
Don't want to die?
Get out now!
Mouth stinks.
Burning inside.
You're all about desire.
I'll help you cool down.
I see.
You really do have a death wish.
I...
I sealed your Niwangong
to make you calm down.
The drug is strong.
If not treated soon,
you'll die.
(Seal the acupoints now.)
(How can I help her detoxify?)
(This drug is so powerful!)
(She broke the seal through?)