=He Kills It=
=Episode 17=
To awaken a vegetative patient
is so difficult.
Such medical miracles are very rare.
But I believe in you.
Your blind trust like this
puts a lot of pressure on me.
Wu Ming, give me a definite answer.
Does my grandpa have hope?
Traditional Chinese medicine
calls it as "Shi Jue".
It means the evil displaces the spirit,
and damages the brain.
The spirit is displaced.
The mind is injured,
leading to a loss of cognitive function.
To restore, the 12th
of the Divine Thirteen Needles,
Risky Life-saving Trick,
may bring the spirit back.
As you mentioned,
do you master
the 12th one?
Yes.
But I never did it.
Its success rate is super low,
like 10 to 20 percent.
Wu Ming,
don't even talk about one in ten.
Even if it's one in a hundred,
I've still got to try.
Wu Ming,
please do it for Grandfather.
Even if it fails,
I won't blame you.
The risk is just way too high.
The last two
of the Divine Thirteen Needles
are seriously dangerous.
It's life and death.
A couple of things first.
Might boost my odds by 30%.
What is it?
Ghost Needle.
Professor Song, how's it going?
We've pinpointed the exact location
of this bone needle
using the marking method.
Can this be removed?
Yes.
Great.
The probability of death is 99%.
Professor Song.
The probability of death is 99%?
What does this mean?
This bone needle is now entangled
with the brain nerves.
Almost integrated.
So, I'd say
don't forcefully take it out.
Mom.
How come nobody found it sooner?
It has been in the brain
for at least three years.
Three years?
Such a pity for a good girl.
At least three years.
Was it the Wu family that put it in,
Mom?
That terrible Wu family!
It's all his fault.
Miss,
calm down.
What I'm about to say,
please listen carefully.
Alright, please go ahead.
Miss Wang
passed out a few times lately
for no apparent reason.
It's very likely
that her brain nerves
are being compressed.
Maybe Miss Wang will
faint more often.
And the chance of dying is really high.
Very high?
You mean,
whether or not she gets surgery,
she will definitely die?
Is that so?
You could say that.
I suggest,
if you've got unfinished business,
you should probably get to it.
Dr. Song,
please!
Save our Hui.
She's only 20.
Not even had a boyfriend.
Dr. Song, you can't let her die.
You're a leading brain expert.
Please save Hui.
I am begging you!
What are you doing?
Please get up.
Please.
I do want to save her.
But I just can't do anything.
Mom, get up!
Mom.
I'm just useless.
It's my fault.
Mom.
Not your fault, Mom.
It's my fate.
I don't blame anyone.
No.
This isn't your fate.
It's the fault
of the Wu family. Of Wu Ming.
If anything happens to you,
I'll just destroy him with my life.
I'm settling this with him.
- Right now!
- Mom.
Hui, are you alright?
Mom, I feel dizzy.
I want some rest.
Alright.
Considering Old Mr. Yang's
health condition,
now, the biggest shareholder,
Mr. Yang Tingjian
will step in as the temporary chairman.
Next up, we'll announce the CEO changes.
Ms. Yang Ling is dismissed as CEO.
Mr. Long Gang is the new CEO.
My dear Ice Queen.
You left the business empire
built by your grandpa and dad.
I'd really like to interview you.
Do you regret your choice back then?
Sorry to disappoint you.
Whether up on a mountain top
or down in a valley,
I'd never pick a filthy bug like you.
You!
Hey, don't forget.
Even if I get fired now,
I'm still one of the main shareholders
of the Yang Group.
You won't make it.
(Wretch!)
(Sooner or later,
you'll come begging to me.)
Come on.
Congrats to Mr. Yang
on taking over the Yang Group!
Teaming up closely with the Long family.
Dominating Loong City.
You're too kind, Mr. Jin.
Thanks to Mr. Shen for stepping.
We then managed to crush
those minor shareholders
siding with Yang Ling.
From now on,
my Yang Group is doing
whatever Mr. Shen says.
Honestly, the Yang Group
is peanuts to my Shen Group.
I'm helping you just to get Yang Ling.
Yes.
She's really getting squeezed right now.
If Mr. Shen shows her a life raft,
she'll be grateful and, you know,
give herself to you.
That's a sure thing.
Mr. Shen,
Yang Ling is a pretty tough woman.
I heard she's pretty close
with that Wu guy.
To win her over,
I'm afraid
it's not that easy.
Wu Ming?
Just a tiny ant, nothing more.
I have a ton of ways to handle him.
A ton, indeed!
Cheers to Mr. Shen!
Come on, cheers!
Here.
No need.
You need it!
You're a patient now.
Should eat more.
What are you doing?
Your arms and legs are broken.
You're stuck.
Yue, you've got a lot of guts.
Any respect to me?
Grandmaster.
You're a patient now.
Make your acting feel real.
Others will then believe.
Mr. Wu, all ready.
We won't mess up.
But
does this method really work?
Of course.
Some just see me as an ant,
a thorn in their eyes and a real pain.
But others see me as a treasure,
and a lifeline.
So,
leveraging strength is crucial.
Grandmaster.
I'm the one
who sees you as a treasure.
Yue,
you're getting
pretty bold lately.
Don't you know about personal space?
Back off.
You're a patient.
You should be nice.
Back off.
Doctor.