=He Kills It=
=Episode 7=
Stop!
Great you're here, Manager.
We got trouble.
It's you!
Still got that temper, huh?
Want more needles?
Where's Xu Zhengchun?
He's in seclusion
to master the art of healing.
I've got his phone.
Seclusion?
He's probably just hiding away
because he knows
he's not good enough.
Scared of me.
You're really enjoying it, aren't you?
Is there no end to this?
You made that call just now?
Yes.
How come you know my master's number?
Because he is my disciple.
Bravo!
Talk about having some nerve!
Dr. Xu looks to be in his fifties,
maybe even sixties.
And you? Still teething?
Kid,
you dare call yourself Dr. Xu's master!
You think
we're all idiots?
You're not saying
you were born a genius, right?
Beauty doctor.
If
this guy is Dr. Xu's master,
then he should be your grandmaster.
Seriously, you didn't even
recognize your grandmaster?
Honestly, I didn't know him before.
Miss,
what an embarrassing moment.
Dr. Xu's disciple
doesn't even know Dr. Xu's master!
Why is Wu Ming so stubborn?
Let's see how he will settle this.
Who's
got the nerve
pulling scams at Baozhi Clinic?
I will break his leg for Dr. Xu.
Miss Shen, I'll be right back.
That's Mr. Jin from
Jintong Construction.
His status is on par with Lei Changhe.
Hello.
I'm Yang Jinbao from the Yang Group.
Yang Jinbao?
Never heard of you.
Are you with the eldest sister
or the second brother?
I'm Uncle Yang's nephew.
A far distant relative.
No far.
Can't you speak Chinese?
Go play yourself.
Mr. Yang,
aren't you a direct descendant
of the Yang family?
How's some random guy
yelling at you like that?
Yeah, I am.
But the old master
specifically told me to
keep it low-key
when I'm out.
Low-key.
Oh, low-key.
Got it.
Hey, Doc.
I'll take care of this
for you today.
My construction site just started up.
We're short on bricks.
So I'm making him
into a brick.
Mr. Jin,
appreciate your kindness.
But it's our internal matter.
We'll take care of it.
Congenital ghost-faced nevus?
Nope.
Not congenital.
H-how do you know?
Grandpa!
Dad!
Look at this mess you caused!
If anything happens to my grandpa,
you won't get away with it!
Doc,
please.
Please save my grandpa!
Get him to the treatment room!
Yes.
I'm going too.
He probably won't make it
if I don't go in.
Wu Ming,
what has our family ever done to you?
Why are you always against us?
Now you're cursing our master?
What do you want?
I'm telling the truth!
Miss Shen,
Dr. Xu will take action.
Let's go in and see what he's got.
Whatever happens to the Wang family
is none of your business.
Just get out of here.
Now!
The Wangs made it perfectly clear.
You're not welcome here.
If I don't go in there today,
just kiss your Baozhi Clinic signboard
goodbye.
Still not your business.
Get lost.
Mr. Ming,
let's go.
Even clay figures get angry.
The King of Hell
couldn't save this wretch.
I don't like the Wangs either.
But Grandpa was fond of Wang Meihui
back then.
Can't die.
Miss.
Wang Meihui would die?
What's going on?
Isn't it her grandpa?
Hurry up.
Grandpa!
Dad!
Dad, are you okay? Dad.
Hold on, Dad.
Li,
go get Master. Fifth floor.
Got it.
Don't worry.
She is awesome.
And now she's going to get Dr. Xu.
Dad!
Stop it!
If this needle goes in,
he'll be dead.
If it doesn't,
he's also dying.
One shot is all I get,
but it's worth a try.
Doc,
no time for us.
My dad's dying.
Just try it.
Whatever the outcome,
we won't blame you.
Do it.
Stop.
Wu Ming, what exactly do you want?
Get lost!
Wang Meihui,
trust me this time.
Get lost!
Doc,
do it!
Quick!
Trust me.
Go.
Dr. Xu is here.
He had an attack.
I blocked his acupoints with needles.
But he...
You're just rambling!
Get to the point!
You...
He's nearly gone.
Why waiting?
Dead.
Grandpa!
Dad!