The killer didn't leave footprints
anywhere in the house.
We didn't find the killer's fingerprints
or saliva on the scene either.
All we found
was her family's fingerprints.
Most importantly,
those with the clearest motive
for murdering her
are her family members.
Everyone in the family
except for Ms. A-jin Woo
will be questioned as witnesses
starting today,
so your cooperation is required.
GANGNAM POLICE STATION
The time of death is presumed
to be around 2 a.m. on February 28th.
The first call to the police
was made at 9:17 a.m. that day.
Now, I'll go over
who's on our list of suspects.
Tae-dong Ahn.
Ji-yeong Park's husband who certainly
has enough motive to kill her.
Jae-gu Ahn.
Tae-dong Ahn's eldest child
who was even charged
with attempted murder in the past.
He's definitely one of our prime suspects.
Jae-hui Ahn.
She's Tae-dong Ahn's second child.
Even though she was
in the same space with the victim
on the day of the incident,
but she lied in her statement
by saying that she wasn't with her.
Ju-mi Park. She's married
to Tae-dong Ahn's eldest son.
She has no alibi for the day
of the murder, and the statements
we received from people around the victim
make her one of our prime suspects.
She died from TBI.
There's nothing that shows she was raped.
There are no signs of resistance either.
The killer hit her here twice
with a blunt weapon.
The artery ruptured right away.
We don't even have any space
to store the body.
Please get her transferred soon.
Okay.
Who do you think did it?
I thought it was her, but I was wrong.
She's the only one with a firm alibi.
So, Bok-ja Park.
I mean, Ms. Ji-yeong Park.
You said you met her for the first time
when you interviewed her
for the caregiver position,
but we did some digging and found out
that the two of you go way back.
Do you really not remember?
Can I be born again?
If I can,
I don't want to live as Bok-ja Park.
I want to live as the woman
who watched the moment
I became a handful of ashes
even if it's just once.
We all want to be happy
and covet the things that we don't have.
From the intense pressure and belief
that it's the only way to happiness,
our lives begin.
But we can't control anything in life
from how it begins to how it ends.
This is a story about me
and the woman who dreamed
of becoming like me.
Residents of Gangnam-gu pay 15 percent
of the taxes that the city collects,
but receive no benefit.
I understand why people are saying that.
That amounts to a trillion
and 700 billion won.
It rightfully belongs to Gangnam.
Plus, the residents will have to put up
with all the noise from the redevelopment.
It's all because people are insecure.
They want Gangnam out of Seoul.
I'd actually appreciate that.
Then, Gangnam can become
a self-governing district.
Hello.
Hi!
Hello, ladies.
-Am I late?
-We'll cut you some slack.
A-jin, is that clutch a limited edition?
-No.
-I think I've seen it.
-No, it's not.
-Right.
Have you checked out
the new high-end shop in Bupyeong?
That shop. You know Gyeong-hun Park
in Class Four, right?
Isn't his mom the one who gave me
the lash extension lady's number?
That's right.
The class president's mom
got her eyebrows tattooed through his mom,
and they look so natural.
Her husband owns that outlet.
He must have a coinvestor, right?
I mean, they don't seem that well-off.
Do you know her number?
-Why do you need her number?
-I want the eyebrow tattoo place's number.
-Do you want to get it done?
-Not me. It's for my husband.
The tarot reader in Apgujeong told me.
You're in trouble.
Your husband will cheat on you.
-Pardon?
-Your husband is weak-willed,
and he even has two earth
in his natal chart.
It represents his spouse, which means
he's destined to have two wives.
That's crazy. So?
You're not about to tell me to slip
a talisman in his underwear, are you?
I'm not a shaman.
I guess you don't know.
Even shamans come to me for readings
to find out when their abilities
will start wearing out.
So, what should I do then?
You need to change his physiognomy.
Through plastic surgery?
That'd be the best,
but it looks like he's handsome.
He doesn't need any work done.
Do the cards even tell you
about his looks?
Of course. He's rich and handsome.
Plus, you have him wrapped
around your finger.
Then, why would he fall for another woman?
That's just his fate, okay?
So, what should I do?
Try making his eyebrows look thicker.
His brows are quite wimpy and sparse,
aren't they?
Don't they look like foxtails?
Thicken them.
Make them look like caterpillars.
That will block another woman's energy
flowing in.
Caterpillars, okay?
That's absurd.
But you can't just ignore it
when you hear something like that.
Goodness.
If thickening your husband's eyebrows
can prevent his affairs,
every husband in this country
should have heavy caterpillar brows.
Gi-ok, do you think
that your husband will never cheat on you?
Well, I probably wouldn't care
if I never find out about it.
Ms. Baek, you said you'll change
the kids' math study guide, right?
A new in-depth study guide
for the math competition just came out.
The questions will likely be based on it.
I'll get all the kids on it.
Math is definitely the determining factor
for which university kids can enter.
Those who give up on math
basically have to give up on life.
But Ms. Baek,
you should make kids take a test
and only accept those who pass it.
If you continue to accept
academically incompetent kids,
moms in prestigious families
won't send their kids to you.
I'm running a math institute
because I have to earn a living,
but I don't want to discriminate
against a certain group of kids.
The smart ones will excel
even without my lessons.
Those who are struggling in school
need my help.
That is so true.
You're a true educator.
JIN-HEE
-I have to take this.
-Okay.
A-jin?
I told Ms. Bok-ja Park, to come at 3 p.m.
She's so different from other candidates.
She can use smartphone apps
without any difficulties.
She said she just needs the address
as she can use the navigation app.
Also, her voice sounded honest and kind.
Yes.
I'm at the store now
to change strings on Ji-hu's violin.
I'll go to the gallery after this
and pick up the painting.
Even this teacup is so pretty.
It's pretty, isn't it?
We must have similar taste.
I like this teacup too.
It looks like one
of Henri Matisse's paintings.
It is his painting.
I knew it.
Do you like art?
I just enjoy looking at paintings.
Life is tough.
Looking at paintings
gives me peace of mind.
Maybe we were meant to meet.
I'm a big fan of Matisse's works too.
Is that right?
I do like his paintings,
but I actually like Manet more.
This is amazing.
We should go to a gallery together.
I'd be honored.
Gosh. Did you go to art school?
I studied fashion design.
I see.
Well, Ms. Woo.
Yes.
I'll take great care of him.
I've worked as a caregiver
for a number of patients.
When people are physically ill,
they actually suffer more emotionally.
Even those who were openhearted
become apathetic and unkind.
Doctors will use medicine
to cure him physically,
so I'd like to help him heal his heart
by doing my very best.
Please give me a chance.
I'll do my utmost
to take great care of him.
Please help him
so that he can become happier
and healthier.
I'll give you a raise
if his condition improves.
Please help us out.
Then, does that mean I'm hired?
Yes, you can start tomorrow.
What are my hours going to be like?
Father usually goes to bed at 10 p.m.
and wakes up at 7 a.m.,
-so I guess...
-How about
you hire me as a live-in caregiver?
I mean, I'm sure he has to drink water
in the middle of the night.
He'll want to go to the bathroom as well.
Will that be okay with you?
We'd really appreciate it.
Goodness. What can I do?
Caregiving isn't a nine-to-five job.
May I take a look at your china?
Of course, have a look.
Did you pick this out too?
Yes, I did.
Do you like Piet Mondrian?
Yes. Do you like his three primary colors?
I actually have a deeper appreciation
for Wassily Kandinsky's style of work.
I'll bring my stuff tomorrow
and start working right away then.
Sure. Just bring what you'll need
for about a week.
We'll send a car to your place
to move heavy things.
Just focus on looking after Father.
We'll take care of the rest.
Thank you very much.
Then, I'll get going.
Okay, goodbye.
Well, Ms. Woo.
Yes.
You're really beautiful.
Thank you.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Our destiny is predetermined at birth,
and it's too cruel to some of us.
Our social class is decided for us,
and moving up in the hierarchy
is not allowed in most cases.
About the artist, Gi-yeong Jeon,
you recognized his talent
before anyone else did five years ago.
Everyone else thought that Sun-ji Choi
would be the next big star,
but you supported Gi-yeong Jeon's works,
saying that he'll become
the greatest contemporary artist.
Now, he can practically charge
however much he wants for his works.
You have such a good eye.
What's this artist like?
In what aspect?
In the association alone,
there are over 50 artists who mimic
Andy Warhol or Roy Lichtenstein's works.
Will she keep her own distinct style?
I can guarantee that.
Her unique perspective
and strong self-esteem
already supersede that
of Julian Opie and Damien Hirst.
Isn't that why you chose her?
Gosh, that hurts. The needle
pricked my skin. It hurts so much.
Why on earth do I have to get this done?
It'll make you become successful.
It'll help you lock in cash flow.
Jeez, do you actually think
that makes sense?
Yes, I do.
You and your friends
believe in superstitions too much.
Please be gentle.
Have you done a background check on her?
Not yet.
I'm sure you'll like her though.
But still, ask her social security number
so that we can vet her.
Don't worry.
By the way, she sent
her resume via e-mail.
Really? She sure keeps up with technology.
How old is she?
She was born in 1972,
so she's 45 this year.
-Isn't she too young then?
-Is she pretty?
Why do you need to know that?
Looks matter to me a great deal.
She seems to have a great personality.
-That means she's not pretty.
-You'll like her.
I'll fire her if that's not the case.
Are you wearing makeup?
-No, I'm not.
-Your brows look like furry caterpillars.
It looks like Dad needs new hearing aids.
He's getting louder and louder.
I want to pee.
Did you get your ballet shoes
from Aunt Jin-hee?
My feet must've grown. My toes hurt.
She said I need to get new ones.
Then, how about you just quit ballet now?
I don't care either way.
Your legs will get muscular
if you keep doing it.
I just wanted to fix your figure.
The plan was to learn it
for only two years anyway, right?
Ballet is all right, but I actually want
to stop learning Chinese.
Say that in Chinese.
"I want to stop learning Chinese."
Just keep taking the lessons
until you can say that in Chinese, okay?
Bye.
I can't believe Dad still goes on
about women's looks at that age.
I think that lady will be great
for the job.
She has worked a lot as a caregiver.
But she seems very intelligent.
She even knows Matisse and Kandinsky.
What's that?
What do you think?
Matisse and Kandinsky.
Are they dog breeds?
New whiskey?
They're artists.
They sound too generic.
Artists' names should be more unique
like van Gogh, Gauguin, and Picasso.
By the way, how does she know
about those artists?
They have nothing to do with caregiving.
It's okay that you don't know
who Matisse and Kandinsky are,
but the way you think
makes you look so ignorant.
What? Ignorant?
Gosh. Aren't you taking that back?
I never take back what I already said.
Forget about it if it bothers you.
-Ji-hu.
-How can I forget?
You said I'm ignorant.
How can I forget hearing it?
Take it back already!
HISTORY OF 20TH-CENTURY ART
Hello?
Don't you worry. I'll do a good job.
Keep your lips sealed yourself.
Yes.
All right.
MS. A-JIN WOO
My gosh, Ms. Woo.
Yes. You need a copy
of my social security card?
Yes, that's no problem.
I'll bring it tomorrow.
Gosh, please don't worry about it.
Yes.
Hiring the right person is so important.
You have to be careful
about whom you hire.
Would you need my family register too?
Okay. I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
Push out. All the way.
Please try to hold it when you go down.
I heard that both of his sons
are helpless.
He sent his elder son to the States
after he beat someone to death.
His younger son is the big shot
in the company,
but even he's not that capable.
Is he seriously ill?
He's had a stroke, and he's even suffering
from diabetes complications.
His hearing is bad too.
Did you tell him
that he should hire a caregiver?
I told him again today. He said
he'd talk to his daughter-in-law about it.
-I'll head out first.
-Oh, wait.
Buy whatever you want to get.
-Okay.
-Bye, Min-su.
I'll see you next time
we play golf, Seong-ju.
I didn't know
that there was a way you can change
your name without a court visit.
Then, there are people who are dying
to make their name known
as soon as possible.
Romantic French-girl style
What's the difference
between waiting and longing?
And there are also people
who are trying to keep
their children's names in the dark.
Ms. A-jin Woo, who was formerly named
the best flight attendant in the company
will give a special lecture for us today.
They're now used to being addressed
as someone's mom
instead of by their own names,
but some of them are lucky enough
to get opportunities
to use their names from time to time.
-Please take him to the hospital.
-Yes, ma'am.
I don't want to get that injection today.
You're not getting
any injection today, Father.
Dr. Jo said that he'd just like
to see how you're doing.
That jerk looks like a con man.
That's not true, Father.
What are you talking about?
You trust people too much.
That's why you married
that idiot, Jae-seok.
ONE MISSED CALL
CURATOR EUN-SEO PARK
Ms. Park, I just saw
that I missed your call.
The artist, Seong-hui Yun
really would like to meet you.
May I give her your number?
No, you can just give me her number.
I'll call her.
Thank you so much, Ms. Woo.
I'm honored that you're my first client.
It's my pleasure.
A close friend of mine is married
to the president of Hawon Group.
She has a gallery and is on the lookout
for a talented rookie artist.
I'll introduce you to her.
I'd be honored to meet her. Thank you.
Please produce good work.
I'm investing in you.
It's rude to say such things
to artists, isn't it?
Not at all.
Art can't be separated
from the commercial world.
It's not like money will fall into my lap
so that I can buy paints.
By the way, you're so beautiful.
I'm flattered. Thank you.
I can't beat your youth though.
Do you have any children?
I have a daughter. She's in third grade.
I bet she's so pretty
if she takes after you.
I can't deny that.
How about I teach her art
whenever I have some time?
Are you serious?
You call that a painting?
It looks like a cartoon.
I've seen things like that in web comics.
She'll become the most renowned pop artist
in Korea in ten years from now.
You just watch.
You know
we're playing golf tomorrow, right?
Gosh, I hate those guys.
Do we have to play golf with them?
Try to get along with them, please.
Do-hyeon's dad helped Father
with the site for the factory.
Everything starts
from human relationships.
I bet they're no match for me.
What are you talking about? Yun-jae's dad
is an ex-professional golfer.
You're just a beginner compared to him.
Who is Yun-jae's dad?
What does he look like?
-Good shot!
-The one who looks like a weasel.
You remember him, right?
What's the score now?
Jae-seok: 4, Bong-sik: 0
Seong-su: 1, Mun-tak: 1
Oh, no. It went out of bounds.
Nice, you got par.
It looks like she's been
practicing golf day and night.
Out of bounds.
Shall we ask Yun-jae's dad
to tutor all of us together?
Women have affairs
with their golf instructors.
-Sorry?
-What if one of us do that?
Gi-ok, stop joking around.
He makes my heart flutter.
I'd be nice to date a younger guy.
Then, shall we swap husbands?
Hey, I'd obviously love that.
You'll regret it.
What's the matter with her?
-Let's take a short break.
-Okay!
I'm so embarrassed.
SCORECARD
I found it.
Jae-seok, your ball is here.
That's not mine.
It's really not mine.
-The one I just hit is a bit different.
-How is it different?
I made a mark on it with my fingernail.
Do you know what the 19th hole mean?
It refers to where those
in extramarital relationships go
after the 18th hole.
My goodness.
Raise your hand
if you have a secret lover.
Right, who'd actually raise a hand?
You're really something.
Did you actually make your husband
get his eyebrows tattooed?
I should prevent it, you know.
If it actually happens,
the aftermath will be such a headache.
Right. Your father-in-law
used to be a total philanderer, right?
That runs in the blood too.
Don't say that, please.
It's so horrendous.
There are two types of men.
Those who cheat on their wives
and those who want to cheat.
Ponder on which category
your husband may belong.
Hey, is he doing well these days?
The binary species is swarming over here.
We're here.
Gosh, I'm tired. Hello.
Hello.
Shall we have dinner together
when we're done?
-Sure, meet me in front of the clubhouse.
-Okay.
-Good job.
-I'm not hungry though.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Bok-ja Park.
Thank you in advance for all of your help.
A-jin has a golf get-together today.
I already spoke to her on the phone.
I should get to work now.
Wait.
Did you bring a copy
of your social security card?
Yes.
I'll give it to Ms. Woo.
Hello, Mr. Chairman.
Did you have a good sleep?
Let me help you.
Careful.
Please be careful.
Please try to sit up like this.
Ms. Park.
Did you go
into my father-in-law's room already?
Well...
What do you mean?
When Ms. Woo and I were going over
my contract together,
we decided that I'll start
at 7 a.m. today.
It's 10 a.m. now.
I'll use Mr. Chairman's bathroom
in his room.
To look after him all day...
No, you can't.
There are six bathrooms in this house.
Please use the one upstairs.
Well, ma'am.
I'd like to take excellent care
of Mr. Chairman.
If you're too condescending toward me,
I won't be able
to look after him wholeheartedly.
Everything is relative, you know.
Do you not care about him sincerely?
You and Ms. Woo are very different.
Ms. Park.
Where is the bathroom upstairs?
I'll just use that one.
Don't you understand hierarchy?
Who is above whom in that hierarchy
you're speaking of?
I don't really know
what I've done to deserve hearing
such a remark from you.
I have to relieve myself.
I need to use the bathroom now.
I guess it's somewhere upstairs.
What is going on?
I'm sorry, sir.
I went upstairs
to use the bathroom, but ended up...
There's a bathroom inside my room.
Why did you go upstairs
and cause this rumpus?
Father, it's actually...
I should use the one upstairs.
Not many people would be understanding
about those under them
sharing the same bathroom with them.
I'll use the one upstairs.
I'm sorry about the noise.
Everyone is equal.
And why would you tell her
to use the bathroom upstairs
when there's one on the main floor?
Well, that was...
Age wisely, please.
Aren't you hungry, Aunt?
Why do you always feed me and eat nothing?
I told you that I'm trying to lose weight.
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
I forgot that you're on a diet.
The smell filled the whole car. Sorry.
You know that you'll meet
your art teacher today, right?
-Yes.
-But
I think you're taking too many lessons.
Your brain might be burnt out soon.
My brain probably looks like this now.
Just tell your mom
that you want to cut down.
I'll do my best before I give up.
I just quit ballet, and she already filled
my schedule with art lessons.
My schedule is completely full.
What do you hate the most?
Chinese.
Chinese!
You know your grandpa's factory
is in China.
Wouldn't that be
why you're studying Chinese?
How is that relevant?
Who do you think will inherit the factory?
It's obviously you.
There's Dad and Un-gyu.
What are you talking about?
That's true.
I guess I've been watching
too many American TV series lately.
One of them
is about a 17-year-old girl inheriting
several hundred thousand dollars.
Aunt Jin-hee, I'll tell you a secret.
Do you know what I want to be
when I grow up?
A stationery store owner.
Goodness. Your mom will faint
if she hears that.
Considering my general aptitude,
I think that'd be the best job for me.
Why?
Because all of my customers would be dumb.
I wouldn't need
to treat them like royalty.
We're here.
It's on the third floor, Unit 306.
Let's go up together.
-Hello.
My gosh, are you Ji-hu?
Hello, I'm Ji-hu Ahn.
Wow, you're so pretty and polite.
Well, what time should I pick her up?
I'll call you when we're done.
By the way,
what's your relationship with A-jin?
Well...
I'm just helping her out.
I'm like her secretary.
Oh, her secretary?
Yes, you can think of me
as her personal assistant
that manages her day-to-day things.
I didn't know that there was such a thing.
I don't know about that.
It's just what the two of us do.
Anyway, please call me when you're done.
Okay, I will. Come in.
See you.
What do you think of Dr. Jang?
-What?
-Gosh.
Oh, no. It went out of bounds.
He talks way too much,
and all he does is brag about himself.
Most people know that he hires brokers
to get patients and that all procedures
are done by other plastic surgeons.
And that guy, Bong-sik Kim.
Jae-seok, your ball is here.
That dude looks a little dumb.
And that man, Mun-tak Seo.
The CEO of the hotel.
He bragged
about having a secret girlfriend.
What's he going to do if I tell you?
Right, you shouldn't be telling me.
Why shouldn't I?
It's such scandalous news.
Did Dr. Jang mention anything like that
by any chance?
-What do you mean?
-Well, things like having a girlfriend.
No, he just said that he'll tell me
about a stamina-boosting supplement.
That means he has a girlfriend, right?
Why would it mean that?
Why would he take it for his wife?
I'm sorry that I have to say this,
but you're honestly
so much like your father.
Gosh, hey. Take back what you just said.
I never take back what I already said.
Just forget about it.
That caregiver is starting today, right?
Yes.
Hello?
Yes, today must've been
exhausting for you.
Okay, I will. You should hurry home.
You're off tomorrow, so get some rest.
If Ji-hu texts you,
just ignore her messages.
All right.
Jin-hee has to hurry home now.
Her brother will bring
his fiancée home tomorrow,
but her mom got the date mixed up
and haven't even started cooking yet.
You should pick up Ji-hu.
I need to go to Father's place
to sort things out.
-Where am I going?
-I told you.
Pick Ji-hu up from her art lesson.
Oh, that web comic artist.
Dear, you better not say
anything inappropriate or ignorant.
If you do, you'll end up
massively humiliating yourself.
But wouldn't it be better
if I go to Dad's place,
and you go there?
No, things must be
pretty tense there by now.
I'll sort it out.
You'll only make things worse.
Oh, right. Don't forget to pick up
Father's hearing aids tomorrow, okay?
All right.
Where's Ms. Park?
Ms. Park!
Yes, sir.
Eat with us.
I'll eat with Ms. Jo later.
Just join us.
-Father.
-It's okay, Mr. Chairman.
I'll eat later.
I don't want to feel uneasy
when I eat because I won't be able
to digest the food.
I'll go prepare your bed for you.
By the way, I noticed
that your bedsheets are pilling.
I'd like to change them.
I think it's the 100 percent
natural bed linen that A-jin bought
directly from a manufacturer overseas.
All-natural fabrics
are more prone to pilling.
It must be very uncomfortable.
I'll buy new sheets tomorrow.
I can just use that one myself.
Hello, Ms. Woo.
I'm sorry, Ms. Park.
I know it's your first day,
but I had other plans.
Gosh, please don't worry about it.
It's not like I'm a kid.
Everything is going well, right?
I hurt my back a little,
but I think I'll be fine soon.
You hurt your back?
There was a bit of a situation.
I'll talk to you later.
You should have dinner.
Ms. Woo, would you like
to have dinner now?
It's okay. I already ate.
Father.
Do you like her?
She's not that good-looking,
but it looks like she has
a good personality like you said,
so I'll see how things go.
What about you, Ju-mi? You don't like her?
We can talk about it privately.
Unit 306.
My gosh, are you Ji-hu's dad?
Yes. Hello.
I'm here to pick her up.
It looks like we'll need
about 30 more minutes.
Then, I'll wait in the car.
Please come in.
You can look at her drawing too.
-No, it's okay.
-Jin-hee said that A-jin would be coming,
so I made some light snacks
to eat with her as well.
Okay. Ji-hu.
Ju-mi, you don't like her that much?
A-jin.
I don't think she's right for the job.
Why?
She totally creeps me out.
Is that the only reason?
I have exceptionally good instincts.
Even the day when Jae-gu
got himself in trouble,
I got chills down my spine for no reason.
That's exactly
how she's making me feel now.
Let's fire her, okay?
If you feel that way, we should.
All right.
I'll speak with her tomorrow.
Is it good?
It's so good. This tteok-bokki
literally melts in your mouth.
Ji-hu doesn't want to eat it because
she had a sandwich on her way here.
She said that tteok-bokki has 300kcal
and that anything she eats after 7 p.m.
makes her put on weight on her thighs.
She's very expressive.
She gets that from me.
Here.
No, it's here.
I didn't get it?
Hey, Ji-hu.
She learned the basic techniques well.
I think she has the talent.
-Oh, really?
-Do you like paintings?
-I love paintings.
-Who's your favorite painter?
Matisse and Kandinsky.
Who's your favorite?
I'm a fan of Damien Hirst.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
He's my third favorite artist.
Matisse, Kandinsky, and Damien Horst.
-Really?
-Yes.
My Matisse and Kandinsky
were making history like that elsewhere,
and this frozen persimmon dessert,
which Ms. Jo had worked so hard to make
became my Matisse
and Kandinsky of the day.
Wow.
I can't believe that I'm seeing
such incredible work right before my eyes.
You're making me blush.
All I can say is that it's incredible.
Painters have been criticizing pop art,
saying that it's not
a form of pure art.
They often say it's like cartoons.
How ignorant. Cartoons? That's crazy.
I can understand.
Even the illustrator and painter,
Norman Rockwell was treated
like a magazine illustrator in the States
at the beginning of his career.
Don't even worry
what those art illiterates say.
They think this looks like a cartoon?
Unbelievable.
Dad, let's go home already.
All right.
Dad, let's go.
Okay. Hey, isn't your teacher
so impressive?
You deserve a thumbs-up.
I remember the calm
the day before the storm.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
NAME: BOK-JA PARK
SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER: 720813-2423124
SEONG-HUI YUN
Seong-hui Yun.
MIN-SU
When you hear the sound
of thunder at home,
being safe from the possible danger
gives you a strange sense of relief.
SEONG-JU
However,
when you're standing outside
without an umbrella, that sound
gives you fear.
That day, all of us
were standing outside
although we were the only ones
that didn't know.
ELEMENTARY LEVEL
MATH COMPETITON
Life is a repetition of tests
where we're required
to choose the right answers,
but the answer I chose
was wrong every single time.
I truly hoped that this one
would be the right answer.
Henri Matisse.
Does that mean his surname is Henri?
Just like how Ji-hu's dad was hoping
that Matisse and Kandinsky
would be the right answer.
-Isn't the result coming out on the 12th?
-Yes.
Last year's competition ratio
was eight to one.
I know. It keeps on getting
more competitive.
They must be putting more emphasis on math
because there's barely any gap.
A-jin, you must feel at ease.
Math is the subject
Ji-hu excels at the most.
You know she's not thorough at all though.
She always gets
the easiest questions wrong.
Jeong-hyeon.
I told you to call me by my name.
Why do you keep calling me
by my kid's name?
Anyhow,
I want to get Derma Toxin and Restylane
Vital injections at your husband's clinic.
How about I go with you
when you get your Botox?
I got it done three days ago.
I knew it. I was thinking
that your smile looked awkward.
Should I get the Beyoncé injection?
I heard that it's pretty good.
The Venus injection is better.
You need to get fillers
for your nasolabial folds.
Oh, the kids are coming out now.
EXAMINATION ROOM
-Mom!
-Be careful, guys.
-Hey.
-Ji-hu!
A-jin...
I mean, the wife of Daesung Pulp
Chairman's younger son.
How did she meet her husband?
Why do you ask?
Well, I'm just curious as to how he won
the heart of such a beautiful lady.
She used to be a flight attendant.
You know those standing signboards
you see at travel agencies, right?
She modeled for the company.
Her husband fell in love with her
as soon as he saw the signboard,
so he stole it.
My gosh, that's so funny.
I heard that her husband
is a bit of a character.
JI-HU'S DAD
I'd like to thank you
for the delicious tteok-bokki.
-What's this fabric?
-It's microfiber.
It's great for blankets.
Hello.
-Let's see. It's 100,000 won.
-Yes.
CHAIRMAN AHN
-Hello?
-What's taking you so long?
You should've just sent someone.
Why did you go there yourself?
This is important.
How can I let someone else do it?
Anyway, come back quickly.
I have a kinesiotherapy session today.
You have to come with me.
Yes, of course.
Please wait for me.
Okay.
Excuse me.
-Another serving of pork rinds, please.
-Yes.
A bottle of soju too.
DIMWIT BONG-CHEOL
Yes, it's me.
Chairman Ahn has a kinesiotherapy session
with you today, right?
Move it to tomorrow.
Just call him and tell him
that you need to reschedule it.
Okay.
This is high in collagen,
so it's good for the skin.
You already look much younger
than your age though.
You think I look younger?
Gosh, you look at least
ten years younger than your age.
Please get better soon.
You should enjoy everything
that young men do.
I've actually been craving this.
Back when I was going through a hard time,
I used to eat this all the time.
He said he's craving pork rinds.
He can never eat it at home
because his family says
it smells up the house.
-Thanks.
-Yes.
I'm telling you.
She's definitely talented in painting.
Ms. Yun did a lot of it.
She painted two out of ten petals
to show me how I should do it.
Anyhow, it looks very promising.
Yes. I should visit Dad
before I head to work
to meet the caregiver.
There's no need
because we need to fire her.
Why?
Ju-mi really doesn't like her.
Gosh, I just can't say it to her.
I even arranged a room for her
and got her to move her stuff in.
Ju-mi doesn't know her place.
If she remembers what Jae-gu did,
shouldn't she keep
her complaints to herself?
That's not right.
Your brother is the one
who made that mistake, not her.
How a man behaves
depends on how his woman treats him.
She's always so negative.
Maybe that's why Jae-gu
ended up like that.
Gosh, I need to go to Father's place now.
Where am I going to find
another caregiver?
Let's try to have a good day, everyone!
-Have a good day!
-We can do it!
Wow. Good shot!
By the way, shouldn't we have checked
everyone's pockets before we got started?
He looks totally normal.
How could he try to trick us like that?
How embarrassing.
You guys will need to watch
what you say in front of him.
He looks like a bigmouth.
He's not my cup of tea.
-Good shot!
-Great.
How about we talk honestly
since none of us is a bigmouth?
You have another woman, don't you?
Gosh, of course.
What about you?
You must have a mistress too.
I don't want to say, "Of course,"
but I do have one too.
Only losers don't have one.
There are two types of outcasts.
Those who don't care
as long as they don't know about it
and those who have to tussle with others
to prove themselves.
Ms. Jo.
Ms. Park.
You haven't heard about it from A-jin yet?
What about, ma'am?
I slept like a baby
thanks to the new blanket.
Mr. Chairman.
Did you have a good sleep?
Give me breakfast. I want rice.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Jo.
From now on,
I'll prepare Mr. Chairman's meals.
I'll take care of his laundry too.
We should get a new fabric softener
with a different scent.
I'll hand-wash his clothes.
Ms. Park!
Hand-washing is a lot of work.
You're a good judge of character
even though you made a mistake
with Jae-seok.
The scope of the things
that an outcast can do
becomes narrow each day.
One of the reasons I became fond of her
was the fact
that she doesn't have the malice
that I see in most rich people.
The grace that enables her
to offer a hand to a devastated outcast.
That was the reason why I thought
that she was special.
FACULTY OF HUMANITIES
Father, please forgive him just this once.
It was a mistake.
Jae-gu is not that kind of person.
I don't want to hear it.
I'll disown him as of this moment.
He betrayed me
in order to eat up my company.
How dare he kill a person whom I hired?
It means he's capable
of killing me as well.
No, Father. Please don't get
the wrong idea. It was just an accident.
Anyway, I'll take care of Un-gyu,
but I've already decided
to cut ties with Jae-gu.
Let A-jin take care of everything
in this household from now on.
I won't give you any financial support.
If I do, my money will obviously
go to that punk.
Father...
So? Will you keep that caregiver?
I should. What else can I do?
She's Pungsan CEO's mistress.
She's gorgeous. Why is she living
as a mistress, not as his wife?
I can understand men.
Even I'd want to be with young,
fresh-faced women like her.
Gi-ok, I bought 10kg
of cherries yesterday.
Do you want some?
It's okay. I still have some too.
Hello, delivery for you.
-Okay.
-Enjoy your food.
I wasn't able to find a tart
that's as sweet
as your smile.
From Jae-seok Ahn.
Pork belly and soju.
Fried chicken and beer.
Burger and cola.
Every kind of food that exists
has the most ideal pairing.
And there's one thing
that beats the pleasure
given by the sweetest food
in the whole world.
It's sweet, isn't it?
It's really sweet.
I couldn't resist it.
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR JAE-SEOK AHN
I see.
My gosh.
Hello, Ms. Baek.
Hey, A-jin.
There's good news and even better news.
Which one do you want to hear first?
Good news.
I heard that a hot guy will come
to our meditation class tomorrow.
We can all pair up now.
That's great.
Now, I want to hear the better news.
Ji-hu is the only one
who got perfect score
on the math competition.
Really?
Ms. Baek, you're being serious, right?
My goodness.
The association that organized it
wants to take a picture of you and Ji-hu.
I can say yes to them, right?
Ms. Baek.
I'm really happy right now.
I'm too excited at the moment.
I'll call you again in a bit.
Okay.
The sweetness she was
thoroughly enjoying at that moment
could've been a gift from God.
But the conclusion I've come to
is the fact that God always bestows
such a gift on us
before he gives us
extreme pain and suffering.
He can be so mean at times.
-Ms. Park.
-Yes.
Bok-ja.
Know your place, Bok-ja Park.
You're just a maid here.
My father-in-law's caregiver.
I have to fire her.
I have no choice because
Ju-mi absolutely can't stand her.
A-jin is actually more simple-minded
than you think. I bet she has no idea.
I'll make sure she never finds out.
Just trust me.
We have a new member
who is joining us starting today.
-Meet Lawyer Gi-ho Kang.
-You're pretty.
-Father, she is...
-Sir.
Please do as Ju-mi says.
She still is the lady of the house.
Even I don't own a high-end designer bag.
Why should a caregiver have one?
Don't
provoke me, please.
If you don't behave yourself,
you'll get kicked out.