Everyone should watch this.
What is it?
JIN-HEE
Father, there's something
I have to tell you.
I have something to tell you guys too.
All of you are here,
so this is perfect.
Do you mind waiting upstairs with Ms. Jo?
That's not necessary.
I...
have decided to marry her.
-Dad!
-Father.
What are you talking about?
Father, this is unacceptable.
Father, you can't!
You're not serious, are you?
I want to get married
and who are you to refuse?
So, do you dare to stop me?
Dad, you barely even know her.
You can't take marriage lightly.
Who says that I'm taking this lightly?
You're disgraceful.
Father, your marriage affects us too.
Can't you all just shut up?
Goodness, Mr. Chairman.
Marriage is a big deal.
It affects the others' lives.
Instead of being angry at them,
you should at least hear out
what your family has to say.
She'll take the place
of our deceased mother-in-law.
She'll be your wife, but she'll also be
one of the elders in this house.
You shouldn't make this decision alone.
Moreover,
we can't let someone who had been
convicted of fraud and embezzlement
be part of this family.
Fraud and embezzlement? Is that true?
No way. He must be out of his mind.
Her child had leukemia,
so she embezzled money from her company.
You all have children, don't you all?
If Ji-hu or Un-gyu had
such a terrible disease
and you had no money,
wouldn't you steal for your own child?
That's what any parent would do.
You all have no sympathy.
JIN-HEE
This is a video taken
at your birthday party.
Who is this?
As you can see,
someone made the canopy collapse.
What happened that day
was not a mere accident.
It was intentional.
We should think the marriage through.
-And Father...
-You should call the police.
I also felt that something
was fishy that day.
When the canopy collapsed the way it did,
I had a feeling that someone
with bad intentions
was behind it all.
So, you're saying that someone
did that to hurt my dad?
That's what I've been thinking,
but I couldn't be sure.
Now that we have
the video as proof,
we should find out who the culprit is.
After what happened, I knew that
I had to protect Mr. Chairman.
I was positive
that this house was dangerous
for him to be alone.
What are you suggesting?
Are you implying
that one of his children did this?
Judging from the situation, it's possible.
Shut your mouth!
Or maybe it's not his children.
What?
How dare you speak like that
to my future wife?
There's no order in this place!
Telling her to shut up and all.
You have no shame.
There is another video that's clearer.
We should put the discussion
about your marriage on hold.
Why?
We should find out who is behind this.
Don't you want to know?
What does that have to do
with my marriage?
Why does it not?
She is one of the suspects.
What?
If she claims that one of
our family members is a suspect,
she can be a suspect too. Don't you think?
That's right.
Do you think she's crazy enough
to do such a thing?
After all, this was the incident
that led you to want to marry her.
If that was her motivation, it's possible.
I'm disappointed in you.
Tell me.
Did you see this coming?
See what coming?
That you'll end up marrying Father.
I had no idea.
Is that so? I guess I am mistaken.
It's such a shame
that all the evidence is pointing to you
when you have no ulterior motive.
If you don't want to be misunderstood,
tell him that you won't marry him.
I will always
protect Mr. Chairman.
If marriage is what it takes,
then I'll do it.
You are already protecting him
as a caregiver.
Stop trying to be more than that.
Don't cross the line.
Father, she's the one
who forced Un-gyu outside in the rain.
Do you expect me to treat her
as my mother-in-law?
If you don't want to,
take Un-gyu and leave this house!
You shouldn't say that.
Okay then. I'll leave.
-Ju-mi.
-Dad.
Dad, do you like her
more than your grandson?
-How can you say that?
-You stay out of this!
I'll bite my tongue and kill myself.
If you don't want an old man
to get married, then I should just die.
If I do,
don't ever come to my funeral.
I don't regard you as my children.
Happy now?
I'll leave.
That will solve everything.
Unbelievable.
Wash up and sleep.
Okay. Don't overthink it.
They'll get married eventually.
What? I can't believe you.
If they do, there's nothing
we can do to stop it.
The problem is that she didn't
end up here for no reason.
She came here
to seek something for herself.
Goodness, Mr. Chairman.
We don't have to do this.
All I need is to be with you,
that's all.
Those brats.
Who are they to refuse?
Are you going to the second floor?
I'll come back after I wash myself.
I'm so cold.
Go to sleep. I'm not in the mood.
Okay.
Wake up. You need to exercise.
-Go on!
-I don't need to go today.
-Where are you going then?
-We had a fight...
Stop being weak. Act normally.
Both you and I.
We need to be strong to get through this.
Just give up. Those two will get married.
-What?
-Not me. I'm talking about Dad.
What are you talking about?
This raspberry juice gives me energy.
I'm going out to exercise!
Namaste.
The Pungsan woman
settled for one billion won.
At least, she didn't have a child.
One billion won is too unfair.
The amount is too small
compared to his wealth.
I heard she attempted suicide.
Is she okay?
I heard she lost her voice.
A man really ruined a pretty girl's life.
Yes.
But I don't think the man
is the only one to blame.
It takes two for an affair.
-The woman probably seduced him.
-Probably.
Is your husband doing all right?
Yes.
What about your husband?
My husband is doing perfectly fine.
I see.
Every woman thinks
that her husband never cheats on her.
But it's the husbands of those women
who cheat on them.
I agree.
I heard a new salad restaurant opened up
around the square. Let's check it out.
Yes.
Did you want to tell me something?
Yes, I do.
I guess that you're having a hard time
because of the caregiver.
It's worse than it seems.
I can't find a solution to it.
There is no solution.
It's a never-ending fight
between a parent and child.
It would be easier to spank and teach him
a lesson only if he were a kid.
I know that your father-in-law
has you occupied,
but pay attention to your husband.
Normally, I would let
things like this slide,
but I think I should tell you
because you're special to me.
Okay, I know.
I think your husband is cheating on you.
-You're here.
-Did you finish your exercise?
It's so refreshing.
I didn't know cycling
was such a good workout.
You never miss a single day.
Impressive!
Yes.
He bought the medicine
and said it's not for you.
I see what's going on. You're mistaken.
He rides his bike every day,
so he probably bought that medicine
for his own health.
The medicine isn't for health improvement.
He takes all kinds
of supplements and tonics.
He's under a lot of stress
because of the new product launch.
He likes food that increases his stamina.
-Is that so?
-Of course.
My gosh.
Even if he did, there's no way
that he would tell Dr. Jang
that he's cheating.
You're wrong.
Men do share things like that
with each other.
They know each other
through the kids' gatherings.
He'll know that telling Dr. Jang
will eventually reveal his secrets.
He says ridiculous things like that often.
Sometimes, it's hard to tell
if it's a joke or a lie.
Then, there's nothing to worry about.
Still, you should keep an eye on him.
I wish that you're right.
What about your husband?
What about him?
I'm just wondering.
He's so handsome and fine
that he attracts a lot of pretty girls.
That's very true.
Doesn't he get handsome as he gets older?
He's still very loyal to me.
Yesterday,
he kept on going.
I see.
Good for you.
It stinks.
What is this smell?
Why did he have to say such things?
He doesn't think when he talks.
I'm planning on making pickles for Ji-hu
since we ran out of them.
Okay.
How long has it been
since your husband started cycling?
I don't know. It's been a while I guess.
Well, he never went
riding on one until today.
-What?
-He hasn't been cycling every morning.
Keep a watchful eye on him.
MR. YUN
TURN OFF
Am I working alone here?
The number you have dialed
is switched off...
I always thought that it was strange
how his clothes wouldn't smell of sweat.
But today, his clothes stank.
That means that he never
went cycling until today.
I saw your husband
at Take Two in Cheongdam-dong yesterday.
He was with a woman.
Oh, I heard that you had food
with a young girl at a café.
I caught you red-handed!
What?
How are you, partner?
Hi, partner.
I'm not good at all.
Goodness. Don't be too disappointed.
You're too obsessing over it.
Those brats.
They are useless.
Let's get married by ourselves.
Maybe you'll get a child
who is not like them.
Mr. Chairman.
I want to have your baby.
Father, she's the woman
who forced Un-gyu outside in the rain.
Do you expect me to treat her
as my mother-in-law?
If you don't want to,
take Un-gyu and leave this house!
ACCOUNT BALANCE
She got pregnant against her will.
It was clearly a case of rape.
I understand that they can't find out
who the rapist is.
But expecting me to pay
for the hotel fees is absurd.
Of course. It is absurd.
The contract says that the hotel
must protect the dog from any harm.
But she got pregnant,
so I will sue the hotel
and I refuse to pay the hotel fees.
It is possible to sue the pet hotel,
but are you sure
that she got pregnant there?
Are you saying that she's a whore?
That's not what I mean,
but since the hotel says
that no such thing happened...
How is it going with the caregiver?
She is about to be my mother-in-law.
Going mental. Emergency situation.
Depressed.
How much can you give me for all this?
Never mind.
Leave it.
How long will it take?
We can do everything,
but we don't make Korean ramp pickles.
Angelica and Cedrela pickles
are our specialties.
Make Korean ramp pickles.
Mr. Chairman would like them.
I told you we don't make them.
You run this place illegally, don't you?
You certainly are not paying any taxes.
To make someone side with you,
rather than persuasion or appeasement,
acting upon their weakness
is a powerful strategy.
Everyone has secrets and weaknesses,
which are only to be revealed
by someone who will take advantage of it.
He's in a good mood.
He's buying her a car.
I'll try all of these on.
Okay. I'll get them ready for you.
You have one just like that.
Are you buying another one?
Dad. I like this car the most.
-This car suits you best.
-Really?
That will be eight million
and 32 thousand won.
Goodbye.
-Goodbye.
You should greet them back.
Don't you have manners?
I guess I don't.
Look who's talking!
-Have you gone mad?
-Watch what you say.
If I don't have manners,
neither do you.
Bitch.
Hey. Are you crazy?
-Bastard.
-What?
Hey. Get out.
Get home and take a beating.
-No.
-You need a beating.
Come.
Do you want to meet tonight?
Don't you miss me?
Come to my room.
I feel insecure in other locations.
Okay. See you then.
What was that?
That sounds like you're talking to a man.
That's right.
I was right. Is that who I think it is?
-Yes.
-Way to go.
He's so young.
I live with an old man,
so my lover should be a young one.
-Don't you think so?
-Of course.
Just like how we like new cars.
Be careful not to get caught.
She says that her husband isn't cheating.
Is that true?
I guess it was just a rumor.
He doesn't seem like a guy
who would cheat on his wife.
You should look out for your husband too.
No man should ever be trusted
in this world.
Especially
the husbands.
I said that there's another video.
Then? Was she shocked?
Yes.
She definitely seemed a little shocked.
But we don't have another video.
What do we do?
Now I know the feeling of detectives
who know who the suspect is,
but doesn't have proof.
This morning, a friend told me
that my husband is cheating.
And the housekeeper told me she thinks
he doesn't go cycling every morning.
When you put that together,
that means your husband
is cheating on you in the morning.
No way.
This is coming off.
It's not sticky enough.
People normally don't wear this
upside down and shake around.
That's true.
Yes?
I'll leave.
You must have urgent matters.
Yes.
You don't answer my calls.
Why did you call?
-I am sorry about yesterday.
-Go away. I have nothing to say to you.
-Sorry.
-Hey.
There's something you need to know.
I'm not insanely in love with you.
If you pull something like that off again,
it's goodbye.
Am I
just a hookup to you?
Give me money then.
At least, I'll get something out of it.
Then, I'll get over you.
What kind of person do you think I am?
You were my love and destiny.
Me too.
Who said you weren't?
Let stop seeing each other for a while.
I don't think
we're in the same emotional page.
Ma'am.
Hello, Manager Park. You must have
a lot of work these days.
It's the same as usual.
-Is he inside?
-He's with a visitor right now,
I'll go and tell him.
I think he was
in a serious discussion.
Okay then.
Ms. Woo is here now!
Hide. Go under the sofa.
-Wait.
-Hurry!
Get underneath.
Why won't this open?
-Where did she go?
-Desk!
All right. Hurry. Go!
The guest has left.
-You can come in, ma'am.
-Okay.
This...
OFFICE OF EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR
Welcome. What's the matter?
I want to have lunch with you.
Lunch sounds great! Very good!
Why are you in such a good mood?
Because you are here,
of course.
Do you want to stay outside
until I wrap things up?
Why? I can just wait here.
Really?
You can indeed.
I thought you were going to finish.
I'm starving. Let's go.
Let's go.
-What do you want to eat?
-I...
I'll buy you something delicious.
Mr. Park, I'll come back after lunch.
Okay.
And as for the adhesion,
I think it is good enough.
If we make it stickier,
it would be too sticky.
Have a nice lunch.
Mr. Chairman, you're walking fine.
You'll soon be running around.
I'm doing well, right?
Astonishingly well.
We should call it a day. Let's go.
What a joke.
Good for you.
This is spicy.
Did you get medicine from Dr. Jang?
What?
What kind of medicine?
-Do you mean Balporin?
-Seeing you surprised makes me suspicious.
Why did you ask for such medicine?
Dr. Jang recommended it to me.
You know how much I like medicine.
That's why I tried...
Then, why do people around Dr. Jang
think that you are cheating?
And why are people telling me this?
What have you been up to?
I was just a joke.
I shouldn't hang out with people
who don't have a sense of humor.
You shouldn't joke around with
stuff like that.
I'm sorry. You must have been worried.
Not worried. Just embarrassed.
Even if I did cheat, how could I
tell people something like that?
You're certainly capable of doing so
since you're out of control at times.
A-jin, I have only one woman
in my world and that's you.
Are there two suns in this world?
There's only one sun in this world.
You're my sunshine, all right?
What's with you?
From now on,
I'll buy medicine
from a certified pharmacy.
You're out of control again.
Are you joking again?
Okay. I'll behave from now on.
-Don't embarrass Ji-hu.
-Okay, ma'am.
Should I just live here?
Go home now!
I can't. I won't!
Promise me your inheritance, and I will.
This brat...
Dad, I need money.
My husband lost it all.
If I want to divorce and go my own way...
Enough! I won't give you a penny!
Money should go to those
who can take care of it.
It isn't worth a shit
to those who waste it like you.
I won't give you a penny.
What? Did you say, "shit"?
If she gets married,
I'd have to call her "Ma'am," right?
Then, Ms. Woo would have to
call her "Mother."
They say that you never know
what tomorrow may bring.
What if she really marries
the chairman of Daesung Pulp?
That could be.
-Is there a way to stop the marriage?
-No.
Thank you.
How old was she again?
Six years younger than me.
So, she's 45 years old.
Then, she's probably fertile.
What if she gets pregnant?
No way.
Can Mr. Chairman...
He probably could.
That's probably why he's getting married.
I don't think he could.
It's already up.
What?
You've been recording a video of me
eating, right? Stop it already.
I saw someone lurking around our house.
I wondered who it was at first,
then remembered
it was the man
from the video sent by A-jin.
How kind of him to walk
in front of the security camera, right?
I should call the security services
right away.
Hey. What were you doing,
you dumb bastard?
Why didn't you answer my calls?
I told you not to call me.
This is an untraceable phone.
I told you no calls or texts are allowed.
I heard that there was another video.
It's been keeping me on edge.
Is that why you revealed your face
to the security camera, you idiot?
If you get caught, tell them.
What?
-That Ms. Park told you to do it.
-What?
If you do, I'll give you
that fitness center you wanted.
That's not fair.
Do you want to tell them that I did it?
Then, we both go down.
Tell them that it was Ms. Park.
They will stop the investigation.
Use your brain, you punk.
This will end by simply making her
leave the house.
And get rid of that phone right away.
If there are records that we spoke
on the phone, we'll be screwed.
That's him. The man in the video.
Can you focus on his face?
Yes.
Do you know him?
No, but he does look familiar.
I can't remember where I saw him.
You draw well.
JAE-SEOK
Hello?
Why did you call?
I'm not interested.
I am teaching your daughter
how to draw. Why?
You don't need to come. We're not at home.
Ji-hu. I know you're very good, but look.
The basics of drawing
a landscape are trees.
The ratio should be three to two.
So, if you divide it into five areas,
make the ratio three to two.
Color it with bright and light colors
as a base color...
Why? Is there something on my face?
Who was on the phone just now?
Why?
Because you seem happy all of a sudden.
Three to two...
JAE-SEOK
I bought two. One for your father-in-law's
and one for your house.
Ji-hu is in art class.
I'll bring her home after she finishes.
-You're here.
-Yes. You seem busy.
Hey.
I'll be waiting on that bench.
You can color it, can you?
If you want to make it brighter,
just use more water
instead of white paint. Okay?
Why are you painting outside in the cold?
You can paint inside
with two apples on a table.
Are you still angry at me?
I told you that I'm sorry.
There's a camel!
It's not funny?
There is a monkey too!
Is that funny to you?
What's that?
An unpredictable future is worrisome.
You don't know what you will discover.
You don't know what will happen.
Your husband is seeing another woman.
You don't know what is real or fake.
DIAGNOSIS
GYEONG-HUI OH
BRUISING OF FACE AND CHEST
SPRAINING OF SPINE
You don't know what you will end up doing
at that time.
As you come up, stretch!
Hello?
Jin-hee, I found out
who that man in the video is.
I found out who he is.
I'll talk to you later.
Ji-hu, aren't you listening to music?
Why are you staring at me like that?
Dad, are you cheating on Mom?
SEOUL GANGNAM POLICE STATION
Who beat you up like that?
Someone came from the shop and did this.
He could be the same person
who attacked your husband.
Yes.
But why didn't he attack you the same?
I screamed and he fled.
There are security cameras
everywhere these days.
I'm sure we can find him easily.
There were no security cameras
in the area where I was attacked.
Pardon?
Don't you think I'd know that already?
Hello.
Let's talk.
Okay.
Let's take a look at the security
camera footage of this morning.
The police already took it, ma'am.
No, not that one.
The one in the elevator.
I need the video of the person
who attacked me.
Don't show this to the police.
I will keep this for myself.
It will only distract them
from the investigation.
Have a drink.
ADMINISTRATION OFFICE
-Are you all right?
-Yes.
Who did it?
Wasn't it you?
Why would I do such a thing?
You told me that you would kill him
if he lays a hand on me.
Yes, but it wasn't me.
So, it wasn't you.
That bastard must have a lot of enemies.
Good.
Let's go.
I don't want to go home today.
It was me, ma'am.
I was so worried that I visited the place.
Sorry.
-You should be totally honest with me.
-Of course.
I will not lie.
-Who told you to do it?
-Bok-ja Park.
She wanted Bok-ja Park to leave the house.
She despised her.
-Who did?
-The wife of Mr. Chairman's oldest son.
The professor.
So,
you're saying that Ju-mi
told you to do this?
Yes.
She wanted me to hurt Bok-ja Park,
not Mr. Chairman.
Do you expect me to believe you?
She had much hatred towards Bok-ja Park.
She even
told me that she wanted her dead.
How do you know Ju-mi?
She came by one time
because of Mr. Chairman's therapy.
That's true.
She came by during vacation.
Sorry, ma'am.
I urgently needed money.
She told me
to take this secret to the grave.
I am terribly sorry.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
Ji-hu, let's eat.
The art teacher helps me with my work.
That's why we've become close,
but it's nothing inappropriate.
Dad. Have you read Hansel and Gretel?
I think so, but I don't remember.
Do you think
that their stepmother abandoned them?
No. The real bad person is their dad.
The stepmother tells him
to abandon his children, so he does.
He's a really bad person.
But I bet he wasn't originally
a bad person.
The stepmother made him like that.
Men in fairytales are seduced
not by good women, but by evil women.
Same happened to Cinderella's dad.
Ji-hu, I am totally different
from those assholes.
-Dad is...
-I will not forgive anyone
who breaks Mom's heart.
Even if it is you.
I love you, Dad.
Me too.
-Yes, Ju-mi.
-A-jin, how did it go?
Did you find out who it was?
About that...
-No, I have no idea.
-Then, you should call the police.
Simple as that.
If rumors spread and become news,
it will be bad for the company's image.
I'll be home soon. Wait for me.
Jin-hee,
Ms. Woo is worried enough.
Don't tell her and pretend that
you didn't see anything.
How can I pretend? She needs to know.
Sometimes, things are better kept
as secret.
The atmosphere here is as if a
nuclear bomb dropped in this household.
Also, you don't know for sure.
Physical contact and laughing doesn't mean
that they're having an affair.
That wasn't all.
What?
He always picked up Ji-hu
after her art class.
Also, he told me not to tell Ms. Woo.
Is that true?
So, that's where he went in the morning
instead of cycling.
I can't believe him.
There's no trustworthy man.
Their penises are what controls men.
We need to chop them off.
Well, about telling her...
-Ms. Woo.
-You're here. What about Ji-hu?
-Your husband took her.
-Okay.
Did you want to tell me something?
No. I figured it out.
What was it?
The video.
I filmed Ji-hu playing the violin.
All right. Eat dinner together
and go home. I need some rest.
You told me that you found
the man in the video.
Who was it?
Seems like you're having a tea party.
You're back.
Enjoy. Let's go, Ji-hu.
Go on.
Is the problem solved?
Yes. I think it is.
In the meantime,
don't ever call me until I call you.
If it's utterly important,
call me with someone else's phone.
How will you contact me?
I will use someone else's phone too.
Whose phone?
Ms. Park's.
Where are you going?
The place I used to live.
I need to bring a few things.
Congratulations on your marriage!
It's still early.
Goodbye,
and wait for my call.
Where is the caregiver?
She went to her hometown.
Did she quit?
We're going to have
a small wedding this weekend.
She went home to say hello
to her relatives.
Dad, are you really going to do this?
Don't you guys want me to be happy?
Then, just give your blessings.
Just the two of us will do the ceremony.
Don't try to stop us.
Anyways, I had to tell you all,
so I did.
I will help you prepare, Father.
What can I do other than to support you?
I'll help you prepare.
You are
quite not like the others.
-Ms. Heo.
-Jin-hee.
-Ms. Woo.
-Why are you here? What's the matter?
-We need to talk.
-Okay. Let's go in.
No. Let's talk outside.
Just the two of us.
Okay.
Let's go.
What's the big deal?
You look so tired.
Things don't happen the way I want it to.
Father will proceed with the marriage.
Who can stop him.
Just let it be.
Tell me already.
What's the matter?
Ms. Woo,
your husband is suspicious.
-The thing is...
-Stop!
I'll look into it.
I don't want to hear it from someone else.
I'll look into it,
and if I am mistaken...
Okay. You can figure it out.
I'll tell you if things go wrong.
Okay.
All right.
Cheer up, Ms. Woo.
Okay.
Is that what you wanted to tell me?
Thank you.
You hesitated because of how I may feel.
-Yes.
-I appreciate that.
I know how that feels.
JEONG-A, BEER AND LIQUOR
-My gosh.
-What a surprise.
Is it you, Jeong-a?
Cho-hui!
-My gosh.
-Hey!
Hey, it's been a while.
You look the same.
Nonsense. I've gotten older.
But you look really good.
Who's the guy?
-Let's have a drink.
-Before a meal?
-Have you eaten yet?
-I don't need food.
Just bring some pollack and soju.
Here it is.
Smells good.
What have you been up to these days?
I am getting married.
Is that so? Good for you!
He must be rich.
Yes.
I am tired of working here.
I...
tried to find you.
You're the only one
that I can trust.
You're the only one who knows
that my real name is Bang-soon Cheon,
not Jeong-a Lee.
And you were the only one who knows
that my real name is Bok-ja Park,
not Cho-hui Park.
But I live by my real name nowadays.
Damn.
We must be tied by fate.
Who knew we'd meet again?
I hope we can
see each other more often.
Dad.
What do I do?
He told me that I am his sun.
He'd never stress me out.
Cheer up.
This shall pass too.
We need to stop her
from taking control over Father.
It's your prenuptial agreement.
You told me that you only care about
protecting Mr. Chairman, didn't you?
Tell Jae-gu to come back.
He's the only one
who can trample Bok-ja Park.
It looks like my dad is marrying
one special lady.
Get lost! Get out of my sight.
I feel insecure though.
I'm just not sure if I deserve
to be this happy.
She's a new maid who'll be working for us.
Say hello. This is the younger son's wife.
Ms. Woo, whose orders should I follow
from now on?
From now on, I will make all decisions.