Subbers Rian , Katherine, Sophia
Co- parsing a story
ın an
anonymity
is
we
are
a
appear
as
one
Love with Princess
Episode 18
Lin Yiteng, are you crazy?
How could you do this for Jiang Xiaoqi?
I told you, I didn't do it for her.
I did it for the kitten.
The kitten is so cute, right?
Don't be stubborn.
Even if you have a heart,
do you dare to admit that
the kitten's meaning
has changed because of Jiang Xiaoqi's existence?
I...
I'm here to see you, not to be criticized.
Help me find a clean place.
Otherwise, my mom will be worried about me when she comes back.
I'm just looking for the same place
that I bought with my mom.
What's most important now is
to have a good attitude with Jiang Xiaoqi.
A clear attitude.
Does she still want to be your friend like when you were a kid?
If she keeps being so distant,
you'll let her go as far as possible.
You're not getting close to her.
I'm not getting close to her.
I'm already far enough away from her.
Why are you yelling at me?
If you have the guts,
go find Jiang Xiaoqi.
You're useless.
Let's go.
Ah Li, make me breakfast.
Go and find someone really interesting.
She's your girlfriend?
I don't understand what you mean.
Stop pretending yourself.
You and Ceng Xiao Fan
shouldn't be good friends
with Lin Yindao.
It couldn't be.
It's impossible.
What are you talking about?
Wait a minute.
Well,
You should go now.
It's hard to explain in school.
He hasn't gone far.
Little Qixi.
Uncle, we changed cars.
Changed cars?
Yes.
Ying Tao.
I haven't changed.
I want to be your good friend.
Ying Tao.
You are leaving.
Bud.
Produce requirement is good.
I think it's pencil ink.
Let me see your completing paper.
Then I'll...
It says yes.
My pen has already been pink in some points.
I'll take it to see it later.
Alan food.
I'll show theて.
ок 옏
It's perfect now.
Here.
Jiang Qiao同 risu.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Do you know that it was very dangerous just now?
It's very dangerous.
You're dying.
And you're laughing.
Are you silly?
It was really dangerous just now.
Stop laughing.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm here.
Who wants to do your job?
Come on.
I'm sorry.
If you're ready,
just tell me
why you didn't contact me
during the New Year.
All of this
has to be said
after I went back to Shen Chen.
After I went back to Shen Chen,
I would be
sent to work at the police station.
I couldn't finish my homework every day.
But I studied very hard every day.
I thought
as long as I finished school early,
I could call you
and go to the mountains to see you.
But I found out when I got home
that my mom cut off her phone line.
Then on the New Year's day,
I asked my mom
if I could call Shen Chen
and tell him that
after I got home,
I would go back to work at the police station.
You lock your heart
and keep it in the clouds
if your dreams
don't leave traces.
We are small
and$ill retain the year that no wells home.
I want you
to forget that I'm desolate in the starlight
Jiang Xiang Si.
cicada colour is warm
I'm going to look through the Native Heat
the palm light is warm
ebd Huling
We'll retreat into the tide
And follow you
To the end of the cycle
You're the reason us to burn
Suspicion
Enter the unknown
Turn around and dive into your love
You're the reason us to shine
Suspicion
St45
Change into the first leaf in the wind
It's full of you
Stop
Go! Go home
Are you very fat?
You can't even stand on your own.
I'm almost fat.
I'm fine. It shouldn't hurt.
What should I do?
Are you stupid?
You did so many things,
but I didn't know anything.
I kept blaming you.
Even if you reply to me
and call me,
let me know you didn't forget me.
That would be great.
Let me go.
I want to go back to Mount Jun.
How can you be so selfish?
Your brother has never been like this.
Jiang Qiao Xi.
Why are you like this?
Because I'm Jiang Qiao Xi.
If you dare to have any contact with those people in Mount Jun,
I have a way to get them all out.
You can try it.
Okay.
Are you 2 not talking yet?
I don't want to disappoint you.
I want to give you the final answer.
What final answer?
Don't give me the math answer.
I don't have it.
I promised you to come back during the winter vacation.
But I didn't do it.
I hope I can do everything you said.
Like my Hong Kong cousin, Peng.
He can do anything for me.
But I know that I have nothing now.
I have to listen to my mom.
And you are a relative.
I don't want you to do everything for me again.
I don't want to disappoint you.
I'm also very helpless.
I don't know what I can do for you.
Why do I have to talk about you?
Jiang Xiaoxi.
Actually, I just wanted to help you.
Why didn't you reply my letters?
Why didn't you call me?
Why did you disappear suddenly?
So what I want is not something you can return to me.
I just want to know your news.
I want to know if you are doing well.
I know.
I also want to send you a message.
But even if I send it to you,
you can't solve any problems.
It will only cause you trouble.
But what about you now?
You are sitting here and running after the car.
You are obviously throwing it at me.
Isn't this a conflict of mind?
Not conflict of mind.
There is a change now.
I didn't expect you to come to me.
I didn't expect you to value me.
I didn't expect you to misunderstand me and Zeng Xia.
Then blame me.
Blame me for being a bad person.
Let's go.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
Did I make myself clear?
If you want to ask me if I forgive you,
I haven't thought about it yet.
So this is the way to get married.
So his mother didn't let him marry me.
Does it still count that Jiang Qiao Xi is a little heartless?
I always think that Jiang Qiao Xi is not a heartless person.
But a little heartless coward.
What coward?
You don't understand their situation.
You change too fast.
You only know the truth for a few days.
You just protect her like this.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm protecting her.
Yu Qiao.
What are you laughing at?
What's wrong?
Why are you always laughing?
You look happier than Lin Yintao.
You have such a good relationship with Jiang Qiao Xi.
I...
And you're laughing so ugly.
No.
I just heard a joke.
It's so funny.
One day, the steamed bun was fighting with the noodles.
Then the noodles were beaten by the steamed bun.
The noodles were not convinced.
The next day, they found their good friends.
It's convenient to help them get their heads.
The next day, the steamed bun was beaten by the noodles.
Don't be so stubborn.
You can't recognize it by looking at my head.
I'll beat you.
It's really funny.
I'm sorry.
Jiang Qiao Xi.
What's this?
Why are you yelling?
Why is this you guys did,
Why are you dressing like this?
Whose
clothes is that on?
Mine.
Although I had no idea if it's your clothes.
Do you think it's all on your clothes?
But just look at this.
Is this really your clothes?
Don't follow me.
Do you think it's pins and needles?
Do you know?
What?
Once, the pain is gone,
Or, tonight.
You guys can discuss it.
Jin Yan Yun!
What are you doing?
How about this?
From now on,
let's have lunch together every noon.
Like this afternoon.
So boring.
Who wants to have lunch with you?
You just smiled so happily.
Yu Qiao.
From now on,
you'll be responsible for telling a joke to Qin Yan Yun every noon.
I just saw you two smiling so happily.
A
Can we Islam work with you for a few minutes?
Do you know how to do the這樣問題?
か
I told you.
Do you know how to do the things in this GDM?
Do you know how to do it?
So you can discuss it
by separated the two scenarios of government.
Then, solve the equation.
Let me help you write an example.
How is it?
Can you see it clearly?
I see.
This solution is quite clear.
Good.
If you have this, why did you copy my handwriting so bad?
I soPHOMAN O plein tree
What are you holding in your hands?
I'm listening to music.
Where's the other hand?
My diary.
It's all about Jiang Qiaoxi.
It's not about you.
You can't keep it.
What can I keep?
You can't keep it as a feeling.
If you keep it, you'll be the bottom.
What do you know?
I just want to tell him
when he misses me,
I miss him a lot
I miss everyone.
We miss him too.
Are we the one?
Or do you want to say
you miss him a lot
when he misses you?
I'll go.
Well,
look at my outfit.
Am I really not too short?
No, believe me.
It looks much better.
Don't forget.
I'm showing my belly.
It looks much better.
That's it.
Don't open it.
It's so late and someone is playing.
Who cares?
I guess he's a fool.
Who?
Huh?
Are you going to see Jia Qiao Xi or not?
Hmm.
Yu Qiao.
Why are you here?
Are you still up?
I couldn't sleep and I came out for a walk.
I didn't expect to meet you.
You're out for a walk in the middle of the night
and you're dressed so well.
You must have been in love with someone.
It's not funny at all.
Then, the joke I told you today
was made by you.
You're the same as me.
I think that joke is funny.
It's not funny.
You're laughing at me?
I think you're funny.
I think so.
I think so too.
So, what are you laughing at?
I think you're funny.
Really?
I think so too.
I wish you could wake up
and get rid of your sorrow.
I wish you could turn around
and melt the ice in your dreams.
I wish I could see your smiling face
from the other side of the stage.
I wish you could tell me
how much you love me.
I wish I could tell you how much I love you.
How many times have I told you
that red is not for you?
I like red.
You're still young.
You don't know what you really like.
I think I'm too young
to know what I like.
Do you want to talk to me
about this?
I've been on a business trip for a few days.
You're not at ease.
Why are you so reluctant to let me go?
Are you on a business trip
or going to see your brother at the park?
Every time I get a good grade,
you'll notify me
about my brother
right away.
You want him to be my good brother.
I also want him to be your good son.
If you dare to go today,
if you dare to go today,
you're forcing me to go to Lin Haifeng's house
and ask them how they educate their daughter.
The boy they asked to meet in the evening
I want them to know
that something is wrong with their Jiafeng.
What's wrong is our family.
The construction site in Fujian
is also missing a engineer.
Let them go to the place they should go.
You go to the place you should go.
Isn't that just right?
You think I'll never grow up?
You think you can trap me forever?
I hope you'll grow up soon.
Only when you grow up
will you understand my pain.
I'm tired.
I don't want to talk about these anymore.
Let's go.
Pack your things.
I'll send you to the training camp tonight.
You can't take part in business outside.
Math is the most important thing now.
I'm not going.
I want to get back to school.
Qiao Xi!
I heard it outside.
Why are you yelling at Qiao Xi?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
If it wasn't for your promotion,
and you took her to the mountains,
she wouldn't be like this.
Liang Hong Fei,
why are you making up stories again?
What's wrong with me taking care of her?
I'm in trouble.
When Qiao Xi was little,
you didn't take care of her,
and you didn't want to take care of her.
If I had a job,
what would I do if I didn't take her to the mountains?
What do you mean I don't care about her?
I have a job, too.
Then I'll take her to the mountains.
Little girl,
you're so pitiful.
Put it here.
Since Qiao Xi was in grade five,
we rarely see
such a smile on Ying Tao's face.
Tonight,
she mentioned Qiao Xi.
I think
she's become
a child again.
You know what?
I thought you wouldn't let her go.
But look at her.
It's late.
She won't come back so late.
What a child.
Now,
even if you don't let her go,
she'll try her best to go.
Besides,
if she really has something to worry about,
she won't tell us.
The friendship between them at this age
is the cleanest
and most needed protection.
Yes.
Who is it?
Why is it so late?
Cai.
Manager Sun.
Why are you so late?
Li Na.
Mr. Jiang is fighting with Mr. Liang at home.
The cadres are all lost.
It seems that
it's because of Ying Tao and Qiao Xi.
What?
If you don't let her go,
when will you stop being so weak?
Do you want to
let both of them go back to their families?
This world is so strange.
You're not the only one.
You're the one who's wrong.
What do you want?
What do I want?
You're the one who's always
in the wrong.
I'll be with you
no matter what happens.
I'll be with you.
This is the end of the world.
Aunt Juan.
You're the one who's wrong.
Li Na is still
the one who's not used to seeing her son.
If you want to go back to Zhengzhou,
you should go to your family first.
Tell them
to let their daughter
and Qiao Xi go to the capital.
If you want to go back,
just do it yourself.
No one will be with you.
Why are you here?
I...
I was just passing by.
I saw
you're here alone.
Qiao Xi hasn't come here yet.
Did you tell her
what time it is?
I did.
I told her
that I'm here alone.
She's not here yet.
I told her
that I'm here alone.
It's already such late.
She's not here yet?
So
why don't you go home?
Talk to you tomorrow.
Let's go.
I'll walk you back home.
If the family was still
one of us,
пон eye wouldthey not notice
how怕 andIouard
that we are
no one but each other.
Mm.
I'm sorry.
Jiang Taoxi.
I'm going to win the Taekwondo competition.
Well,
Lin, Shengjuan,
it's normal for kids to go to school
and communicate with each other.
It's late.
I'm sorry for making you come here
for our family matter.
Is it just our family matter?
Mom,
let's go now.
I'll do what I promised you.
I believe you for the last time.
Ying Tao.
What?
Don't lie to Ying Tao.
Ying Tao.
Where is Ying Tao?
Mom.
Aunt Juan, Uncle Haifeng.
Ying Tao didn't do anything wrong.
She didn't.
Thank you.
Yuqiang,
it's late.
Go back now.
You go back first.
I'm sorry.
I...
All right.
Don't worry.
Mom and Dad
didn't think you did anything wrong.
Go back.
Come on.
Go.
Go back.
It's...
It's getting cooler.
Right?
It's autumn.
Wait for me to make some rock sugar water.
Take it to school and drink it, okay?
Mom.
Did Jiang Qiaoxi's mom
say anything bad to you?
Ying Tao.
Don't forget who your dad is.
I'm the owner of the shop.
No matter how big the job of Jiang Qiaoxi's mom is,
she's always
polite when she talks to me.
Right?
You...
But I've caused you a lot of trouble.
When you grow up
and become a parent,
you'll know
that a child
is born in trouble.
I...
Well...
Is Jiang Qiaoxi okay?
Ying Tao.
Qiaoxi is a good girl.
She cares about your love
as much as you do.
But people
are hard to change their attitude
especially when they're young
and rely on themselves.
He'll only like youت
but he'll always think that
he loves you.
I support your idea.
Although
people often can't change theirgrounds,
their friendship
can't be changed either.
Right?
Then you can blackmail me.
Goodbye.
We should fight together.
Yun Yue.
It's Jiang Zhengnuan.
Steaming hot HTML
Is there anything else you need?
Yes
Yuan yuan
You and children very familiar
You look
Can you tell him
that the most important thing
in your current stage
is learning?
Besides that,
you have to build
a healthy relationship.
Including the relationship between friends.
And the possible love relationship
that will happen in the future.
It all needs to be done in the right time.
It's a critical stage.
We'd better not affect each other.
Uncle Jiang,
if we really do,
it's also Jiang Qiaoxi who will affect Ling Yimang.
If I don't discuss it with Ling Yimang's family,
they won't write the mas Latinis' prepare notes.
So I have to hope that
Dad can interfere with the operation.
Well,
Ling Yimang's company
did put a lot of effort into the arrangement.
What is it then?
It's AZ.
You see.
It's AZ's places.
cuál?
Right now,
we streamrow movie together.
You're by my side
The sun will rise and set, we'll say goodbye
A little cat and I are walking on the road
Many years have passed, the appearance of the past has been blurred
I'm more than a dog that's been bitten by a dog
I'm going to sing with you on the hillside
We accidentally bled
I want to run to the top of the hill, holding you in my arms
The sun is about to turn red
You're in my eyes, I'm looking at you
You're the only one in my eyes
It's you that I finally understand peace and freedom