canonical
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Miss à la Shouldn't know
Shota
Hurry up
Can you
No.
Then,
if you need anything,
I won't ask you.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Wait.
It's fine.
I'm on my way.
I'll call you if need me.
You've been preparing
for your internship at the college.
How's it going?
Not bad.
I told you
I'm taking a 11-year-old class.
I think
they must still like
I'm old enough to listen to fairy tales.
So today, I'm going to watch a fairy tale episode from different countries.
I want to find something interesting and fresh to listen to.
Did you see anything interesting today?
Can you tell me about it first?
Do you have to listen to fairy tales with your friends?
Yes.
I read a book called The Window of the Fox.
If you put your hand together into a fox's window,
you can see anything you want through this window.
Anything I want?
Yes.
How should I compare this window?
It's a bit complicated.
Left hand on the back of the hand, right hand on the heart.
The middle finger of the right hand and the ring finger of the left hand are pressing the index finger.
It's a bit like a tongue twister.
You have to put your fingers together, and there's a window in the middle.
It's really complicated.
I'll teach you when we meet again.
Okay.
Are you sure you can see what I want to see most?
Of course.
Do you believe in Mr. Lin?
I believe.
What about you?
What do you want to see most now?
Do I have to ask?
Jiang Qiaoxi.
Come to the balcony.
With your fox's window,
you may see what you want to see.
The wish you said
The shadow of familiar is getting longer
Your outline is so gentle beyond the sight
The world is turning
The breeze is blowing
The scenery in the window
Is like yesterday's morning
The past is in front of you
The future is in your hands
You're the key to who I am
Be with me and become myself
The night sky is long
My strong wind is so loud
I can't stop running
The dream in my heart is calling
You're the spark in all my dreams
Be with you and become yourself
The wind is blowing
The future is in your hands
The past is in your hands
I'm going to dance.
Jiang Qiaoxi.
You scared me.
You're up so early.
I smell the fragrance.
You're not getting thinner, are you?
I feel like you've lost weight.
Really?
Yes.
I didn't feed you well.
I didn't feed you well?
Look at what you ate.
I'm full.
I'll go first.
How is it?
Okay, you eat first.
I have to go to the office.
You're going to the office again?
The market is better these two days.
So the boss wants to steal more companies.
I happened to meet a small company this morning.
I have to go over and talk.
I'm a little tired.
You remember to tell me when you slept last night.
4.30 p.m. last night.
Now? 8.30 p.m.
You slept for four hours.
Hello.
I read the email. I know everything.
OK.
I'll come over when I'm done.
I understand.
If their founders are all college students,
don't make the atmosphere very serious.
Listen to their ideas.
Yin Tao, I'm going out.
Wait, wait, wait.
You just graduated and you say you're a college student.
When will you come back?
At night.
I'll come back as early as possible.
At night?
Bye.
Qi Yue.
Yin Tao, you're 25 years old.
Aren't you ashamed?
You and Jiang Qiaoxin are in the same place.
Jiang Qiaoxin didn't come.
We're on the same boat.
Don't mention it.
She said that the investment market is good recently.
Her company asked her to go to meetings every day.
Now she's with Mr. Shang.
She's so focused on the financial market.
She has no time to care about that.
Jiang Qiaoxin doesn't even care about her own wedding.
She doesn't come home every day.
Is she in trouble?
What are you talking about?
Yes.
You called me for the first time four years ago.
Four years ago?
Four years.
It's time.
What are you talking about, Qin Yeyun?
What?
The truth.
A man.
Thank you.
Don't you know what kind of person he is?
Every time he comes home late from work,
he comes back to make breakfast for me.
Sometimes he comes to work before I wake up.
But the food in the pot is hot.
What are you talking about?
What did he say?
He said you like to cook.
Who would he cook for when he made you breakfast?
You can't talk about it, can you?
I'll throw it away.
I don't believe it either.
You actually started to do the game industry.
I know that this financing is a great risk for our company.
But once I succeed,
I can turn all the impossible in my mind into possible.
If we fail,
I won't give up anything.
You've read the contract with Mr. Yang.
Have you read it carefully?
Contract?
Actually, I don't know much about contracts.
My colleagues are reading our contracts.
But they said they wanted to make an agreement.
You mean we have to sign a contract with them
to lower their sales price by providing us with discounts.
As an exchange, the company will increase their investment.
If we really do that,
their shares will be overestimated.
That's what they should consider.
I think it's important.
A small company with core technology
and a new game industry
can also make a lot of topics.
In the future, we can be the first to sell high-end.
These companies are here to cooperate with us.
It must be a better development in the future.
If we really do that,
will it be unfair?
It's the best result at all costs.
As a financial person,
this is the simplest rule.
Winson,
you should know what's most important.
It's good for you and me.
He forgot about the wedding venue.
He went to work overtime today.
Jiang Xiaoxi is so insensible.
Ning Tao, wait for him.
When I see him,
I'll teach him a good lesson.
Okay, you can talk to him.
Xing, I'm back.
Come here.
I'm talking to Jiang Xiaoxi.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
Come here.
I bought vegetables.
I'm talking to Jiang Xiaoxi.
Dad.
You're back?
Yes, I just got off work.
Dad,
how are you in Africa?
I'm fine.
I'm fine, too.
You're fine, too, right?
Dad, I'm going to cook.
Hurry up and cook.
Make some delicious food for Ning Tao.
Take care of yourself.
Okay, I got it.
What are you in a hurry to cook?
I'm not hungry.
Hello, your flowers are here.
I didn't buy you flowers.
This is my favorite cherry blossom.
I'm not happy with the flowers I gave you.
I know what day it is today.
Today is the sixth day we met.
Sixteen years.
Let's eat.
Ning Tao, what's wrong with you?
Actually, I'm not in a hurry to get married.
You've been saying that
Aunt Juan's breakfast is only for the family.
Is it the family that calls the aunt Juan's mother?
She forced me to get the certificate at my age.
Then she asked me to hold a wedding.
But it's too late.
You forgot it yourself.
Oh, sorry, I forgot.
Today is the day we choose the wedding venue.
I really forgot.
I'm too busy.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I remember now.
I promise you that if there is such a thing next time,
I will definitely not forget.
I'll come back and sing with you as long as I have time.
You have time to come back and sing with me.
You're not going to work.
Isn't this deeply reflecting your own mistakes?
Big powder water.
Is it sensitive again?
If you want to make a good moisturizing, you can use it to reduce the redness.
This big bottle can handle it.
Okay.
Blue button, all-new big powder water.
Pink water, white red rice.
Hello, Mr. Li.
Slow down.
Ready for class.
Hello, Mr. Li.
Mr. Li, where did you go on the weekend?
I went to the castle.
I went to my good friend on the weekend.
The teacher said you were getting married.
Is that true?
Mr. Li, look.
This is the new gift box my mom gave me.
It's so pretty.
It's beautiful.
Teacher, I remember the big green one.
I remember the big green one.
Okay, okay.
Hurry up and get ready.
We're going to class in a minute.
What are we doing here?
Mr. Fan is here with you.
Tell me if you want to do it.
Do you want me to protect you from the chair?
But look around us.
There are our classmates and the sun.
The teacher will teach you in a moment.
Do you want to come out and listen to the story?
Have you done your homework?
Come to school tomorrow.
Don't forget to bring your textbook.
Goodbye, Mr. Li.
Goodbye.
You're up.
Chen Xiaoman.
You're here to pick up the kids?
No, no, no.
I'm here to pick up my boss's kids.
You don't know yet, do you?
I worked at a magazine after I came back from school.
That's great. It suits you.
I didn't expect to meet you today.
What's your boss's name?
I'll help you find it.
Xu Hao.
Xu Haolei.
Class one, Class one.
Our class.
Lei Lei.
I'm here to pick you up. Let's go.
Let's go. It's snowing.
Actually, I haven't seen Lei Lei a few times.
But every time I see him, he's like this.
My boss is a career-oriented woman.
He doesn't usually stay with the kids.
It's normal for him to be introverted.
He may not be introverted.
I think he's sensitive.
And he's very imaginative.
Sometimes he imagines himself as a little mushroom in the corner.
I think you can pretend to be a mushroom.
And chat with him more.
Is that how you got Jiang Xiaoxi?
Actually, there weren't any of those things.
I think we were good friends in high school.
Lei Lei.
Let's go. I'll buy you some candy.
See you with Mr. Lei.
Bye. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
See you tomorrow.
Look at the news.
Something happened to Yu Qiao.
A black bird hit her plane's engine.
Yu Qiao.
A flight from Hongyang Airport
was hit by a flying bird during the takeoff.
It only took a few seconds for the plane to take off.
The lights went out immediately.
Yu Qiao.
Qin Yeyuan.
Are you scared to death?
Why didn't you make it clear?
Why are you running?
I'm not going to eat you.
Don't eat. It's getting late.
I'm fine.
I'm so hungry.
I'm so full.
I'm fine.
Let me see you in person.
Don't hide.
I'm fine.
Can't you make it clear?
Why are you scaring me?
You're back.
Drink some water.
Don't be angry.
You're young.
Find something else to do.
Qin Yeyuan.
Let's not talk about this kind of
unspoken words.
Think about it from another angle.
I've accumulated valuable flight experience
through this sudden situation.
How many pilots can have such flying experience?
Besides,
pilots like me who are awarded by the Ministry of Foreign Affairs
leaving the position is a loss to our private bank.
You're right.
You made the decision yourself.
You won't change no matter what others say.
I heard Qin Yeyuan say
that the anti-cancer drug you're studying
has been reduced to a substance of cancer.
How is it?
Is it going well recently?
It's still the same.
I've known since I decided to be a doctor.
Being a doctor must be a difficult thing.
Especially now I've decided to study the anti-cancer drug.
If it's not difficult,
then it will be a problem.
Moreover,
Yuqiang has been struggling in the sky.
I can't overcome such a small problem.
It's so embarrassing.
Right, Yuqiang?
Yes.
This is the role of the front-line internet.
When my pre-medical design came out,
the pattern of this meal was pulled up.
You're good.
Come on, the role of the front-line internet.
Cheers.
The role of the front-line internet.
Today,
we finally get to meet here.
Do you remember
that we didn't do anything before?
I think today is a good opportunity.
What?
Help me.
Okay.
You're so heavy.
Yes.
Suddenly I feel
that I'm waiting for this moment
to buy this car.
Okay, let's go.
Get in the car.
Qianyue, are you driving?
Of course.
Okay, I'll be the assistant driver.
We can be the guide.
I want to hold the steering wheel
in my own hands.
Listen to my favorite songs,
and I'll show you
many beautiful scenery.
I want to sit on the cherry blossoms
on my assistant driver's seat,
sit on the roadside of the vegetable garden,
and also sit on the bridge.
Who wants to get off the bus?
The plane is taking off.
The sun is setting.
Come on.
I'm not afraid to say
that the next year will be better.
We just got married half a year ago.
Now we're giving the money to the fans.
It's too early.
This is not the money from the fans.
This is the letter.
I wrote it to you when I was in the first grade.
The letter I took down.
I sent it to you.
Don't worry.
You've got the correct message.
It's not up to me
whether I believe it or not.
I've kept this letter
for so many years.
I've always wanted to open it.
But I never opened it.
It's enough to test my moral level.
Now it's good.
I finally threw this stone egg to you.
Thank you.
Lin.
What else do you want to play?
I want to play that.
Are you done?
Yes, I'm done.
Yuqiao.
I thought
I couldn't tell you
something for the rest of my life.
But after you got out of the interview,
I'm afraid I'll regret not telling you.
I don't want to regret it.
Tell me.
I don't know
which class you're in every day.
Every time I look up
and see some flying objects in the sky,
I'll think
that's you.
Okay.
But when I look up
in the sky,
I'll think
that's you.
I'm done.
Let's go and play.
Let's go.
Run, run.
Be careful.
Go.
So beautiful.
Today,
there are major adjustments
in the food supply.
The main point is the decline in the stock price.
The market is moving more.
The supervision department said
they will continue to pay attention to the market
and maintain the market steady operation.
This is the market steady operation.
The market is going up to 3000.
I even misjudged my eyes.
Isn't this a beautiful woman?
I and my wife
have been living well.
We've been saving a lot of money.
We've been earning a lot of money.
Teacher Chen, this...
You don't know about the stock price.
Today is the day of the moon.
The stock price has fallen.
The main point has fallen to 3000.
The stock price has fallen by 40%.
You know it.
Why are you here?
Have you contacted Jiang Qiao Xi?
No. What's wrong?
Her boss was taken away for investigation.
Feiling just told me.
Jiang Qiao Xi told Feiling
that the contract given by Simu is very problematic.
They are at risk of being caught up in the market.
After Feiling knew it,
she didn't cooperate with Simu anymore.
Today, the stock price has fallen.
Her boss was taken away.
Feiling called her but she couldn't get through.
I've been thinking about it.
I have to come to you.
I'll call her first.
I'll go home to see her.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Stop talking nonsense.
Go ahead.
Jiang Qiao Xi,
I've told you so much.
But I forgot to ask.
Do you still remember Chun Lu?
Do you still remember that you are Chun Lu's father?
Do you still remember me?
I always remember you.
When I think of you,
I think of our childhood.
At that time,
time flies so fast.
It was almost the time when the ice cream was just in my hand.
It started to melt.
It was almost the time when I started climbing the mountain.
When I saw the sunset,
the night came and it was dark.
I was about to go down the mountain.
But without you,
without my friends,
time flies so slowly.
It's like a sleepless afternoon.
What about you?
Are you living a fast or slow life?
Is it because you have new friends
that you like them more?
Did they make your time go faster?
If that's the case,
I would be a little sad.
But only a little.
You are doing well.
I would also feel that I am doing well.
But
you have to tell your new friend
that your name is Jiang Qiaoxi.
Your name is the most beautiful sunset in Qunshan Mountain.
Jiang Qiaoxi wrote you this letter.
I used a lot of courage.
I was afraid that you had forgotten me.
But I also felt that if it was you,
you wouldn't forget me.
Can you tell me the answer?
I know you are busy.
You have to do a lot of math.
But if you are not that busy one day,
can you go back to Qunshan Mountain?
I want to see the sunset of Qunshan Mountain with you.
I want to hear you tell me
how are you these five years?
Is your time fast or slow?
I want to go to Qunshan Mountain with you
to see the sunset of Lingyin Tower.
Jing Shang.
It's okay, Jiang Qiaoxi.
It's okay.
As long as you are okay.
I am fine.
Why did you say that I am fine?
I know it.
Chen Xiaoman just came to me
and said that your boss was taken away for investigation.
You didn't make a mistake.
Don't worry.
Sit.
I resigned before I made a mistake.
Why are you crying?
I...
Are you crying because of the stock market?
It's okay.
You can make money again.
As long as you are fine.
It's okay, Jiang Qiaoxi.
It's because of the stock market.
I have sold all the stocks.
You have sold them?
Why didn't you tell me that you sold them?
You didn't tell me that you resigned.
You didn't tell me that you sold the stocks.
You didn't tell me anything, right?
Come.
What are you doing?
I am crying.
What?
Did you buy the ring with the money from the stock?
Jiang Qiaoxi, what are you doing?
Don't worry.
It's enough.
Director Lin.
I know it's a little unnecessary for me to say this now.
But I want to ask you again.
Would you like to live with me?
I have lived with you before.
That's different.
Would you like to?
Hurry up.
I'm so embarrassed.
Enough.
Don't show off.
You are so beautiful.
No.
Close your eyes.
Jiang Qiaoxi.
How long are you going to stay this time?
We will stay for a weekend.
I have to go to school.
I have to go back.
Okay.
You are busy.
You are promoting.
It's okay.
They both grew up.
They have their own career.
You can stay for two days.
Just stay for two days.
Qiaoxi.
I will make you more steamed buns and lotus root this time.
You two can take it back and eat it.
Don't bother.
You can leave it to me.
When I go back to Hongyang, I can make a cherry.
No.
Leave it to me.
He is cooking now.
If he is bored and wants to play with me,
I will have a sister.
You are so smart.
Uncle, aunt.
I want to say something.
Although I haven't had a wedding ceremony with Ying Tao,
I want to call you dad and mom from today.
Call me if you want.
Dad.
We have been looking at you as a son since you were a child.
It depends on how you behave.
Dad.
They will agree.
Okay.
Dad.
We will live trauma-free.
Not anymore.
Actually,
my relationship with Jiang Xiaoxi
is not that serious.
I've always been.
I was kind of necessary.
Now,
I'm very expected
to be a professional both wholesale andatures.
That's great.
You're a little stingy.
Ping Tong,
you'll be living with Qiang Xi in the future.
You two are a family.
You have to make more plans for your little family.
No.
Even if I have a little family,
I still love my parents the most.
How can you two be happy?
You two will live together in the future.
You have to take good care of each other.
If you need anything,
remember to call me.
What did you ask?
Do you understand what I mean?
Let me explain.
My dad means
you must not bully me.
If you bully me,
call my dad.
My dad will go.
You're so good at it.
You ruined it.
You're in pain.
Of course.
You broke it.
I broke it.
Let me see.
Okay, it's fine.
It's fine.
This one looks good.
It's pretty.
You'll get used to it.
Thanks.
Ming Tao.
Does Qiao Xi still
contact her parents often?
I guess so.
You know about her family.
She can talk to Uncle Jiang
for a while now.
But she can't help it.
Aunt Liang
will call her
and ask about the situation.
But she'll hang up in less than a minute.
There's something
her mom didn't let me tell you.
But now you're married to Qiao Xi.
I think
I should tell you.
What is it?
Two years ago,
Qiao Xi's mom came to our house
after she was sent back
from Nigeria.
Do you know what she came here for?
What?
She did
the same thing
you're doing now.
No one can change Industrial Council
so easily.
When I saw her back then emails,
you know where I got myắp.
That kind of encounter
no matter who you choose to work for,
nobody can get through it.
I still can't live without you.
You...
You're so nice.
Yin Tao.
You're the best daughter in the world.
You're also the best mother in the world.
You're so nice that
I don't want to be separated from Jiang Qiaoxi.
What?
What do you mean by that?
The End
I'm 16 years old, Lin Yin Tao.
Hello.
I'm 25 years old, Jiang Qiaoxi.
I'm sorry.
My letter has been returned to you for nine years.
But I still hope you can receive it.
It's a good thing to return the letter.
I can tell you
about our nine years of life.
Would you like to hear the ending first?
That's a good ending.
We're getting married soon.
Now we have the same parents
and live in the same house.
We eat the same food
and use the same bath.
I really want to know
what kind of words you would like.
But you
wouldn't think so much at that time.
In these nine years,
those times when I was alone,
I was dreaming
and I was with you.
We were looking at the sunset of Qun Mountain
and I could bear it.
I was also dreaming
about everything that happened in life.
So I could feel
that there was a future.
When I just left Qun Mountain
and couldn't find you,
I would dream
that I was still with you.
I would leave the chocolate
that my teacher gave you.
I would bring your favorite peanut milk.
I would go to see the sunset with you and Chunru.
Yun Tao,
do you remember
when we were kids,
we used to
watch Harry Potter together?
You're talking nonsense.
You didn't even watch Harry Potter when you were a kid.
I had to tell you.
Besides,
we never watched Harry Potter
on the mountain top.
Did you remember it wrong?
Of course I did.
But you didn't know.
When we were in middle school,
I would imagine
that we never separated.
We were still in school
and watched Harry Potter together.
But Yun Tao,
I don't have to
imagine anymore.
At this moment,
you're by my side.
The sunset today is beautiful.
I really want to
give you the sunset
and let you wear it with you.
Just like
you gave me
the broken heart you've been carrying.
But what can I do, Yun Tao?
I can't give you the sunset.
Besides, I'm more greedy
to eat the early steamed buns
you made yourself.
Do you think
Yun Tao will make it for me
nine years later?
I think
you'll agree
nine years later.
I'm watching the sunset with you
on the bridge of the evening sunset.
Be careful.
Yun Tao.
You've grown up.
Today,
you're going to be a bride.
Yes.
I'm going to be a bride.
Is it the same as you imagined?
I've never imagined
I'd be a bride.
I've never thought about it
when I was growing up.
Do you feel satisfied
now?
Are you not afraid of anything
like before?
Of course.
But
when I was an adult,
I sometimes
had to pretend to be a coward.
Do you like people who marry you?
I don't have to like the one I like.
I like the one you like.
The one you like.
How do I look?
Am I handsome?
Are you really me?
Why can't I be you?
You're a laughing stock.
The real you
has been awakened.
Is the person who woke you up
a eagle?
Who else
can it be?
In the fairy tale,
it's the princess and the prince who get married.
From then on,
they live happily together.
But the story is over.
Is it true?
Will their lives
continue to be happy?
Are you asking
whether Jiang Qiao Xi and I
will be like this forever?
Always be happy
is a difficult thing.
In the future,
we will face many difficulties.
We will face
the bad weather
and the rain.
But as long as I'm by her side,
she's by my side,
I'm not afraid of anything.
What I want to do most now
is to be by her side.
Let you
be my guide forever.
Then you have to work hard.
Don't worry.
I will.
I'm very satisfied.
Very satisfied.
I like you when you grow up.
You're not afraid of anything.
Look.
This pair of shoes.
Why are you wearing this pair of shoes?
Aren't white sand red shoes
just for jumping?
I like to jump.
I just want to wear this pair of shoes
and walk into the life with you.
Jiang Xiaoxi.
Now you can marry your bride.