And who are you?
I've never seen you before.
You've got a lot of guts.
Hey, move it. Go on.
Damn, move.
Hey, Gotak, are you alive?
- I'm dead, dumbass.
- You okay?
Just go.
Go where?
- Go to him, fucking assholes.
- You should be training with the team.
What is all this?
What? Training?
Hey, we can't even compete
in the tournament because of you.
What are you saying, dumbass?
We can't compete
because you got suspended.
You stupid dumbass. Fuck.
Fuck! Really?
Are you sure?
Man, I shouldn't have dyed my hair.
- This won't come out for a while.
- You asshole!
What? Are you that happy to see me?
You too?
- My arm!
- Hey, you too?
Fucking asshole!
I don't care if you act out
and bully other kids,
but no fighting
while wearing the Eunjang uniform.
No fighting, okay?
Repeat after me. No fighting!
No fighting.
That's it! Now beat it. Scram.
Go!
- You started it.
- Let's go. Go on.
- Let's go.
- Hey, you said Hyo-man would win.
I didn't know.
Si-eun, here you go.
Are you okay?
Thanks.
Hey, Si-eun.
I'm sorry.
I think I might have got the wrong idea.
Hey.
You don't sound sincere
when you start with "I think."
I'm sorry! My dear Gotak is very flawed!
- But--
- Let go of me, man, please!
He's not a bad kid!
Si-eun, where are you going?
Oh, I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
Si-eun, you can't just leave.
Oh wow. Such courtesy
is rarely found at Eunjang.
Hey, dumbass.
Who are you impersonating now?
My dad. Didn't you get it?
Anyway, that timing was crazy.
I mean,
if Hu-min hadn't shown up…
You ruined someone's life.
Don't pretend you're a nice guy.
You fucking hypocrite.
I guess…
you must have felt bad
after Hyun-tak said that weird stuff.
Everyone just likes
to talk behind other people's backs.
Don't worry about the rumor.
It's not a rumor.
What?
That's why I decided never to fight.
Never again.
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 2
11TH GRADE, CLASS 7
09 - PARK HU-MIN
- Baku!
- Hey there!
Hey, nice to see you! Hello!
Hey, put out that cigarette! You punk.
- Baku!
- Hey there!
How have you been?
I'll see you at the canteen later.
Hey, what's this? You lost weight!
How's it going?
Everyone, freeze!
Baku.
- Leave these kids alone.
- It's Baku.
Is this the World Cup Stadium?
You kick balls outside.
What are you doing?
You're right. We should be outside.
- Right, guys?
- Yeah.
- We should go outside.
- Right.
Okay! Let's all get along, yeah?
Hey, man, isn't that right?
Go to class now.
Hurry back to the classroom.
Get ready for class. Go on.
Baku!
You son of a bitch. Baku!
Ganghak High doesn't play basketball.
What they do is closer to martial arts!
Why do we have to play a practice game
with those assholes?
There are all kinds of teams out there.
A true master
doesn't care who he plays.
If there are all kinds of teams out there,
then we can play a different team.
Let's avoid causing problems.
If someone gets hurt--
You chicken.
You moron.
You scored 99 on the IQ test.
Are you a monkey?
- Or a dolphin?
- I'll kill you.
I just couldn't finish
the test in time, dumbass.
This punk ran out of time!
You ran out of time, did you now?
Only idiots run out of time on an IQ test.
Mr. Gotak. You're all grown up now.
All grown up? I've always been taller.
I'll kill you, you jerk!
- Hey!
- Hey, you're killing him.
Stop it!
What's this?
Are we under attack?
We're wanted in the teachers' office.
You're right.
That did happen at the underpass.
But that's an exaggeration--
Everyone who hangs out
with Choi Hyo-man is absent today.
Don't you think that's strange?
There were some kids who saw the fight.
That's news to me.
- "That's news to see," dumbass.
- That's news to see, idiot.
Man, you really have an IQ of 99.
- How dumb are you?
- Shut it, dumbass.
- Moron.
- Hey, be quiet.
Take it.
YOUTH CULTURAL VOLUNTEERS WANTED
You're going to do some volunteer work.
And you'll still get demerits.
Hey, this isn't fair.
What about Hyo-man and the others?
They started the fight!
Hey!
Does this sound like a debate to you?
You punks.
It's true.
Hyo-man and the others started the fight.
We were just--
Yeon Si-eun.
Did these kids rub off on you?
You punks have got to be kidding me.
We're so sorry, Teach!
We'll work hard volunteering!
I'll keep the basketball team
out of trouble from now on.
Once again, as team captain,
I sincerely apologize!
Damn, volunteer work?
Aren't you pissed?
Is it okay to let Hyo-man off the hook?
When I breathe the air in that office,
I get dizzy. I almost threw up.
And you did get in a fight.
What did I say about fighting?
Those punks started it, Baku. Damn.
Hey, friend.
Tell him, Gotak.
Right now?
You should say something.
He sided with you
in the teachers' office, right?
Well,
I'm sorry
about yesterday.
For saying weird stuff and getting angry.
I'm sorry too.
What?
For yesterday.
I'm also sorry.
What's this?
It feels like you've made up,
but then again, not really.
Hey.
I'm not on your team.
And don't touch my head.
What are you going to do? Huh?
What are you going to do about it?
What now? What will you do?
What the hell?
Dude, what's so annoying about this?
Like this, yeah? You can do this to me.
- Hey!
- Like this.
Baku, what's with you today?
Know when to stop.
- Damn.
- Hey, man.
You try being suspended, kid.
It's fucking boring.
I wanted to eat pizza so bad
that I almost cried.
- Why did you get yourself suspended, then?
- Let's go get pizza!
Hey, let's go together, guys.
Gotak is buying today!
- Over there!
- Mark him!
Okay!
- He seems kind of odd, doesn't he?
- Save some energy!
But it's peaceful, thanks to Baku.
Baku protects all of us.
There's this thing.
It's called the Union.
All the schools near ours
belong to this union of delinquents.
There's a rumor that
Na Baek-jin of Yeoil High,
Geum Seong-je of Ganghak High,
Do Seong-mok and Baek Dong-ha
of Yeonsung High,
and many others
have been operating like a real gang.
Choi Hyo-man has been stealing phones
so he can get into the Union.
But Hu-min said he wasn't interested
in things like that anymore.
So Eunjang was the only school
that didn't join.
After that, Union kids would go after
anyone in an Eunjang uniform,
picking fights or taking their money.
So Hu-min got pissed off
and beat up everyone in the Union.
I heard the Union members
didn't stand a chance and were smashed.
Baku did that to protect all of us.
As the king of Eunjang.
Anyway,
he fought, didn't he?
Hey, Si-eun! Jun-tae!
Come play with us! Come on!
Hey, dumbass, leave them alone.
I don't want to nag you,
but you should behave
so the teacher doesn't have to call me.
It's not that I don't trust you.
I'm just worried.
What happened before
should never happen again.
Tell me you're not
hanging out with bad kids again.
- Great job.
- Thank you.
- I told you to meet the quota.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
- How can I face Baek-jin like this?
- Don't have enough?
- Thank you.
- Make up the rest by stealing, assholes.
Sorry, sir!
Hey, move it.
These Eunjang sons of bitches.
We should just kill them all.
Baek-jin wants to see you.
Let's go.
GEUM SEONG-JE
What was his name?
Choi Hyo-man.
That idiot didn't bring in enough cash
and lost all the phones he collected.
I heard he was beaten by Baku.
I shouldn't have trusted that punk
in the first place.
With Baku there, Eunjang is a no-go.
Baek-jin.
I'll do whatever I can to fix this.
Just give me a little more time--
Shut the fuck up, dumbass!
You got rejected by the Union.
If we gave you more time,
what could you do?
Baek-jin, how should we handle this?
Baek-jin, please.
Don't do this. Baek-jin, please wait.
- Baek-jin, please!
- Hurry up. Let's go.
- Baek-jin!
- Hurry up!
Seong-je.
Let's check up on Park Hu-min.
Baku?
Sounds good.
I could use some action.
Okay.
SEOUL MUSEUM OF HISTORY
- Look over here.
- Smile.
- One, two, three.
- Show your teeth.
How about a peace sign?
This king's expression is weird.
I don't like it.
Could you angels give me just one chance?
I've heard there are precious treasures
hidden somewhere in here,
and I think I've found them.
They're you!
What? What's with him? Seriously.
Why don't you just let my heart rest?
It's racing.
Stop stuffing your face.
You didn't even work that hard today.
Hey! Listen up.
Hey.
Some girls from Buil Girls' High
gave me their numbers.
Should I ask them out for dinner?
Give me a break.
There's no way they'd go, idiot.
Then how about this?
If I set up dinner with them,
you have to pay for it. Deal?
- Deal! If you fail, dinner is on you.
- It's a deal.
- Okay.
- No take-backs!
- Pick something to eat.
- You're dead.
It'll be expensive. You're dead, man.
Hey, damn.
The number you have dialed
is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
Cell phone numbers
are usually eight digits, aren't they?
But what's this? One, two, three…
It's nine digits!
Hey, give it back, punk!
"Hey, give it back, punk!" Are you mad?
This seven is a mistake.
She put two sevens instead of one.
- Sure.
- That's it.
- You're really dead now.
- Sure, try again.
You are seriously dead!
- Do it, then. Go ahead.
- I knew it was odd.
No, you jerk. Put it on speakerphone.
You've reached Seonheung Finance--
I'm sorry. Wrong number.
You've got a mouth on you.
- Hey, man.
- I'll…
I'm really fucking sorry…
Buldak sauce is really hard to get out.
Hey, Jun-tae.
Take the chopsticks from Si-eun.
I heard he stabs people
with chopsticks and stuff.
Si-eun, put it away. It was an accident.
It's not my fault.
I'm going to the restroom.
Are you Baku's friend?
You know, you'll screw up your life
if you hang out with the wrong crowd.
Here it is.
Now, look here.
One, two, three.
You have sad eyes, don't you?
Do you know who I am?
Man, this punk…
won't look away.
You're not bad.
What?
You want to bash my skull in?
I just came to say hi today,
so let's stop here.
I'll see you later.
I'll beat the shit out of you next time.
My stomach hurts because of you!
- No way.
- I'm off to the can!
- Go ahead.
- Hear me out.
What's up with him?
How many dumps do you take in a day?
I'm going to die.
What?
Hey, Baku.
What? Are you a fucking woodcutter?
Why are you here?
Why do you think?
I wanted to see how you were.
But I ran across an unfamiliar face,
so I said a little hello.
What?
I'll kill you.
Keep laughing
if you want to die.
You still don't want to join the Union?
Every school is in it
except fucking Eunjang.
Fuck this.
Aren't you tired of this?
I am.
I am tired of this.
But it seems Baek-jin isn't.
Anyway, I get it.
End your lovers' quarrel with Baek-jin
and try to get along.
Hey, are you okay?
Did you meet some weirdo?
Damn, I'm sorry. It's my fault.
What is?
What's your fault?
Nothing. Never mind.
AWARD FOR OUTSTANDING ACADEMIC ABILITY
Next, we will present the award
for outstanding student achievement.
This student excelled
in the Academic Evaluation
for the second semester
of the 2023 academic year…
What? Why does he get an award?
What was his score?
His score? He only missed number 30
on the math portion. The trick question.
Wow, that's insane.
We hereby present this award
to Na Baek-jin of Yeoil High School.
DONGMYEONG BANK
DEPOSITED: 12,435,000 WON
DEPOSITED: 7,435,000 WON
Baek-jin, we took care of
the collected phones.
As you know, only Eunjang was left out.
But that loser somehow
managed to meet his quota.
And he called and said
he wanted to talk in person.
It's a hassle, but you should meet him.
I'll send the address.
- Hey, what is this? Where is he?
- What?
Find him.
Damn, it's locked.
He's not there?
Where is that son of a bitch?
Are you sure he came this way?
What the fuck?
- Not there?
- Nah.
- Fuck, where did he go?
- What the hell?
- Seriously?
- Shit.
What the…
Hey.
What is it?
"What is it"?
Hey.
Do you just fucking use people
and toss them when you're done?
I fucking did what you told me to,
you son of a bitch.
Hey, Baek-jin.
I know about you.
I hear all you fucking do is study.
You hide behind Geum Seong-je
because you can't fucking fight.
The only punching you do
is on a calculator.
Are you listening?
A petty trickster like you
doesn't deserve to lead the Union.
That's what I'm saying.
A set of brass knuckles. Two steel pipes.
The loudmouth is last.
What are you waiting for? Get him!
You asshole!
Shit!
Hey, you son of a bitch!
Come better prepared next time.
SEONG-JE: NEW FACES APPEARED.
ONE'S A WUSS, AND ONE'S NOT BAD
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
Why did my energy run out so fast?
I'm hungry.
Man, let's go eat! It's on me!
- Yeah!
- Awesome!
Bullshit. He isn't buying.
- He said he would.
- He won't.
Hey, knock it off.
It's a good place. Really good.
- You heard of Michelin?
- Bullshit!
- It's all good!
- He isn't paying.
- He won't pay, really.
- I need to go.
What?
Why? You said you'd eat with us.
I did? When?
No, but…
Oh, he's right.
But you should come. We worked hard today.
I have plans.
I see.
Man, you'll regret it.
You can go, but next time is on you.
Take care!
- Go on.
- See you.
Anyway, he isn't paying.
Seriously, what is going on?
Hey, it is my treat!
BAKU CHICKEN
This comes out of your allowance.
These are your son's friends. Can't you--
Then you fry the chicken, punk.
Freeloader.
Hey, it's fine. Dig in.
Eat! Jun-tae, have a drumstick.
- Okay.
- Let's eat.
Oh yeah.
What did Jun-tae do?
What?
What happened at school?
Oh, right. You know Hyo-man was
stealing phones and money from the kids.
Then Jun-tae
got it all back and returned everything
to all the kids in school.
Hey, isn't that fucking dope?
Jun-tae, this guy here.
He's got some guts.
Hey, Jun-tae! You're really cool.
Oh no, I just
followed Si-eun's advice.
What? What did he say?
Well, it was…
Do you know Newton's third law?
…Newton's third law.
The law of action and reaction.
For every good action,
a good reaction follows.
Oh! U-turn's law! Yeah!
No idea what that is, but it sounds cool.
- I'm going to use that later.
- Sure.
That Si-eun guy,
I heard he had to transfer to our school
for causing serious trouble.
But he seems all right to me.
When I was getting beaten up
by Hyo-man, Si-eun saved me.
Si-eun is really nice.
Man, that bastard.
I hope he got home okay.
PATIENT'S NAME: AHN SU-HO
VISITOR: YEON SI-EUN
RELATIONSHIP TO PATIENT: FRIEND
Hello?
Yeon Si-eun? It's me, Hu-min.
What's up?
Nothing's up, man. Just checking
to make sure you got home okay.
So, nothing happened, right?
No one followed you or anything?
No, I just went home.
Really?
Hey, anyway,
you know how I was turned down
by those girls today?
Well, it occurred to me
that girls might be
into guys like you these days.
So what do you say?
Why don't we pick up chicks
together next time? Deal?
Why would I do that?
Okay, fine. Asshole.
I did some volunteer work today.
Once I got there,
it wasn't as bad as I thought it would be.
The weather was nice too.
More than anything,
it took my mind off things
for the first time in a while.
I wondered how that happened.
I think it was
because of the guys I was with.
So that's Ahn Su-ho.
Your friend.
The one whose life you ruined, right?
Why are you here?
What?
What are you gonna do?
Come with me for a second.
You shouldn't interrupt
your friend's sleep.
Damn, you have a real punchable face.
Just my type.
Hurry up, you fucking asshole.
Subtitle translation by: James Webb