Hey, move! Out of the way!
Hey, Yeon Si-eun!
Is it true that you're staying?
Yeah.
I heard Hu-min joined the Union.
And he's not answering his phone.
It's because of us, isn't it?
He felt bad for us.
He thought we were suffering
because of him.
But still,
we should bring Hu-min back.
Hey, Baku, Baek-jin told you
to make it quick and simple.
Is that him? From Hyeongshin?
He's a fucking poser.
This is gonna be fun.
Fuck, he's tall.
What the hell is up with his eyes?
He's acting tough.
Do you have a smoke?
- Hey, he hit Baku.
- It's a clean hit.
All done?
Fuck.
Shit, we're fucked.
Hey, what do we do?
Hey! Wait!
It's over.
Why?
What's over?
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 2
Great job.
What's this?
Give it to your father.
Are you a fucking charity?
I told you before.
He'll have to pay a fine.
You give me this…
to make me do more fucked-up stuff?
You'll take it anyway.
Does it feel better
when you talk like that?
How on earth…
did you end up like this?
Baku, where are you going?
What's with that punk?
Hey! Baek-jin!
Enough! That's enough!
You'll kill him, man!
Why did you stop me?
I learned it all from you.
It must be tough for Baku
to climb this every day.
That's why Baku's stamina
is so fucking high.
Hey, Baku!
Hey, Park Hu-min!
I told you he wouldn't be here.
Seriously, where is Baku?
Hey, brats.
What the hell?
Hello.
Mr. Park, how have you been?
How do you think?
Why are you here?
Oh, well--
When did Hu-min stop coming home?
Goodness, that senseless fool.
He didn't get enough beatings as a kid.
He's just like his mom,
so I never know what he's thinking.
Hey.
If you see him,
tell him to die out there
or come back and learn how to fry chicken.
Damn, that fucking imbecile.
Did Hu-min do something to you?
What?
Hu-min isn't a senseless fool at school,
nor a fucking imbecile.
He really cares about his friends,
and they like him a lot.
I don't think that
Hu-min is the problem.
I think you're the problem.
Hey, you little punk.
Get out.
Get out, you damn punks!
Yes, sir.
Get out now!
Let's go.
Please excuse us.
See?
I told you we shouldn't have come.
Baku used to stay at my place
whenever his dad got drunk.
Mr. Park was scary.
Na Baek-jin.
Why does he need Hu-min?
Didn't they used to be friends?
Yeah, they were fucking BFFs.
Back in middle school,
Baek-jin did nothing but study.
He couldn't even look kids in the eye.
And?
Baku taught Baek-jin
how to fight.
I no longer teach anybody
Yeah, it's lunchtime!
EUNJANG HIGH SCHOOL
You know Hu-min joined the Union, right?
So what?
I can't reach him.
Do you know where he is?
How should I know?
Even if I knew, why would I tell you?
I don't like the way you fucking talk.
Answer him while he's still asking nicely.
Goddamn it! You're just Baku's lackey.
You want to go? Now?
Okay.
Sorry.
So just tell us where Baku is.
You're nothing.
Well, he's probably polishing balls
at the bowling alley.
If not, he might be
at Daesung Motorcycles.
"Daesung Motorcycles"?
Man, you don't even know that?
Now…
First off, the bowling alley.
- Who's next?
- It's me!
Na Baek-jin is a manager
at the bowling alley.
But it's just to launder money.
Launder money?
Money laundering.
The owner is some kind of gangster,
so he uses it to launder money.
He manipulates the sales
and hires Union boys
so he can inflate their pay.
The money from Daesung is also illegal,
so he launders that money there too.
Daesung Motorcycles. What do they do?
Those crazy punks…
They steal motorcycles, scooters,
basically any type of bike.
They repaint them, change the plates,
change the parts to make them untraceable,
and then sell them, yeah.
They also keep a list of everything…
make copies of the keys,
then steal the bikes back later.
Wait. That doesn't make sense.
Won't it get reported?
Reported? You're nuts.
Hey, there's no use reporting it.
They only use cash or burner accounts.
The gangsters might be
in on it as well.
And the police?
I hear they turn a blind eye to it all.
Why do the Union boys work for Baek-jin?
That's so simple.
The pay is fucking good.
Just think about it.
Fuck, they do a few errands
for a few million won.
That's why those punks lose their minds.
And you know Baku is fucking poor too.
Fucking asshole!
What do you know? I'll kill you. Shit.
Let's go.
Hey.
What are you up to?
Are you going after Baek-jin?
I mean, you know,
I have some unfinished business
with that son of a bitch.
We could fucking join forces, yeah?
Get him when he's alone, yeah?
Gang up. Gang up on him, yeah?
Let's find and kill him.
Hey, should I make some calls?
Hey, Si-eun! Seriously, man.
Fuck, should I round up the boys?
We don't need your help.
What?
What a fucking idiot.
Hey, should we get a Union guy
and find out where Daesung Motorcycles is?
I think that's where Baku would be.
So… we can fight again and get hurt?
No.
Don't do anything yet.
I have a plan.
Please.
Hey, what's your plan?
Am I supposed to just sit around?
Who knows what
Baku might be up to right now?
Whatever.
USE THIS
BAEK-JIN SENT A PHOTO
76 YEONGDEUNGPO-RO 10-GIL,
YEONGDEUNGPO-GU, SEOUL
What is this?
Go to that address and pick it up.
What?
Go steal it.
If you want to protect
the people you care about.
AWARD FOR OUTSTANDING ACADEMIC ABILITY
JUNIOR, NA BAEK-JIN
We're just…
childhood friends.
Damn, so close! Fuck!
You can't organize those, fucking idiot.
- Why not?
- Because we'll get in trouble.
It's fine.
Hey, isn't he that punk?
- What?
- Who is he?
Just a minute.
Hey.
What do you want?
Where's Na Baek-jin?
Hey!
- That punk is looking for Baek-jin.
- Why?
He's the guy that beat up
Geum Seong-je last time.
That guy?
Hey, are you the fucking lunatic
that beat up Seong-je?
I've been fucking curious about you.
Nice to meet you. Put it there.
Where's Baek-jin?
Why do you want him?
I have something to say to him
but nothing to say to you.
This guy really is a fucking lunatic.
Well, Baek-jin is coming soon.
Just wait a bit.
You can play a round if you're bored.
Hey, turn off the signs.
- Sure.
- We aren't open.
DAESUNG CORPORATION
Tak, should we really be doing this?
Hey, let's just find it first.
I think this is the right place.
Is it that way?
No, I think this is it.
Daesung Corporation.
YEONGJIN INDUSTRIES
Then we can just go in.
- Come on.
- Hey, wait.
Is this right?
There is no Daesung Motorcycles.
This was the only place I found.
Don't you think
we should listen to Si-eun?
Hey, if we wait around like this,
will Baku return on his own?
We have to do something.
Hey.
Just a minute. Hey. Slowly.
Motorcycles!
- Motorcycles?
- Tons of them!
Just a second.
Hey. Shit, why are you so heavy?
You're so heavy, man.
DAESUNG CORPORATION
This is it! The Daesung Corporation sign!
- Is this the right place?
- I think so.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Hey, did you see it?
- Yes, the sign said "Daesung Corporation."
- Good job.
Then let's wait nearby.
I'm sure if we wait long enough,
we'll see Baku.
Good job. Okay.
- Okay.
- Nice job.
WESTERN SEOUL HIGH SCHOOLS' UNION
ROADS WITHOUT CCTV
GOTAK
The number you have dialed…
He won't pick up?
Nope.
Son of a bitch.
This device is switched off.
Please leave a message…
Man, that freaking jerk!
What is it?
Hey.
What's gotten into you?
Hey, Park Hu-min! I know you're in there.
Come out, you punk!
Union guys might be inside.
No way. We haven't seen anyone for hours.
Hey, Baku!
Park Hu-min! Hey, Baku!
I don't think he's here.
Let's get out of here and rethink this.
Let's go in.
Go in here?
No, Tak! What are you going to do?
Hey, this guy has some freaking balls.
He fucking came here alone.
Hey, Baek-jin.
Yeah. All right.
Okay. Understood.
Let's go.
Hey, let's go.
- Keep an eye on the place.
- Yes, brother!
Just wait a bit.
Baek-jin will be here soon.
You really need to lose weight.
- You got it?
- Wait.
Hey, I did it!
I did it!
Hey, are you okay?
- I'm coming.
- Okay.
What's all this?
- Go see what's up there.
- What?
Hey, Baku.
Park Hu-min!
Tak, he's not over here.
- That's Baku's underwear!
- What?
The tiger briefs. There!
- Baku's briefs.
- Those are Baku's?
- Yeah, they are.
Shit.
- So he really was here.
- Tak.
- What is it?
Those papers there.
Isn't that what Hyo-man was talking about?
Evidence of Na Baek-jin's crimes
or something?
Yeah, I think you're right.
- Hey, Jun-tae.
- Yes?
I can't let this go.
What are you doing?
Move over a bit.
- No, don't do it!
- We have to look.
- It's fine.
- Hey!
- Hello, brother.
- Hello.
- Go outside.
- Yes, brother.
I didn't expect to see you again.
There's one thing I don't get.
I don't know why
a top student with scholarships
is caught up in Union stuff
and commits crimes to earn money.
There must be a reason.
I don't know the reason.
But Hu-min does, doesn't he?
Do you think I'm doing this
because Baku knows everything,
and I'm scared of him talking?
No.
Hu-min knows everything about you…
so you think of him as your only friend.
However…
would Baku consider you his friend too?
My boys… will get there soon.
You said I had to separate
the variables, right?
But I realized there's an even better way.
If you remove the variables,
it's much faster.
Last time, Baku left here
to go save all of you.
Can you do the same?
Why?
Are you scared?
What are you doing?
I said, what are you doing?
Come on.
What the hell are you doing here?!
Hyun-tak and Jun-tae are
at Daesung Motorcycles.
Union members are on their way.
We need to hurry.
Fuck!
Park Hu-min.
Si-eun, you should go.
I'll be fine, so go.
And the goods?
"The goods"?
The bike?
I didn't steal it.
Do what you want…
to the people in my life.
What?
Do whatever shitty things you want.
This time, I realized that…
you and I will never get along.
So…
don't contact me again.
Let's go our separate ways.
Have a nice life.
- Find something, Jun-tae!
- Okay.
Do you really think we'll find anything?
Shit.
BIKE PURCHASE RECORD
DATE, PLATE NUMBER, BUYER
NUMBER OF TIMES SOLD
- I found it.
- What?
- You did?
- Yeah.
Let me see.
This looks like
a list of the stolen bikes they sold.
Won't the Union collapse
if we take this to the police?
Then all of Baku's problems
will be solved.
Hot damn, Jun!
Nice. Hey, take it. Let's get out of here.
- We aren't missing anything, are we?
- No.
- Hey.
- What's going on?
These punks got in through the window.
Hey, close the back door.
Hey, little rats. Did you have fun?
Jun-tae, stay back.
Come on, guys.
Get them.
You fucker!
Shit.
Damn it.
Hey, that's him, right? Baku's lackey.
Go Hyun-tak.
Jun-tae, are you okay?
Man, this punk.
Hey, move it. Move.
This fucking piece of shit.
Look at this fucker's eyes.
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Fuck.
- Jun-tae.
- Yeah?
- Stay right behind me.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Run, Jun-tae! Open the door!
- Okay!
- This fucking lunatic!
Get him!
Hey, hurry!
- Get them.
- Get the door open!
- Come here, crazy fucker!
- It's open!
- Gotak!
- Jun-tae, run!
- Run!
- You son of a bitch!
- Come here, asshole!
- Hey, you son of a bitch!
Hey, stop right there!
Hey! You fuckers! Son of a bitch!
I'll kill you once I get you!
- Come here, asshole!
- Hey, Jun-tae, run!
Those fuckers are fast.
What are you doing?
- Hurry up! Go over it!
- Fuck!
Hello?
Hello? Is this Mr. Yeon Si-eun's phone?
Yes, that's me.
I'm calling
from Sungang University Hospital.
Patient Ahn Su-ho
is in critical condition.
I couldn't reach anyone
and found your number in the visitor log.
What?
Do you know how to reach his guardian
or any other family?
Or maybe you can come instead?
Hello?
Subtitle translation by: James Webb