[ominous music plays]
[Brianne] That's him in the green.
We gotta go now. Let's go. Let's go.
Now, now, now. Go, go, go.
[Cecilie] We need to go.
Shit, is that him?
Looking your tormentor in the face
and showing them
that you're not scared of them anymore
is a great way to take your power back.
Hi, Ricky.
Hi. I'm Bri.
Um, Bridget said
you stole a lot of money from her.
-Is that true?
-I think you have the wrong person.
-You're not Ricky?
-No.
[Bridget] Hi, Ricky.
-You guys get the cameras away from me.
-No, what happened to the money?
-You guys can get away from me. [laughs]
-No. What happened to the money?
Seriously. What happened to the money
you stole out of the ATM?
[Ricky laughs]
[Bridget] I caught you on video.
You think it's funny?
[Ricky] Yeah, I do.
Did Clarence save your life?
100%. We were stationed
in El Paso together.
[Brianne] Clarence's family said
he died in an IED attack.
He didn't take a bullet for you.
[Bridget] I gave you money.
-To send to Clarence's family.
-You never. You never.
[Brianne] We've met Clarence's family.
We know they don't have the money.
Clarence doesn't even have
a wife and kids.
I'm not admitting anything.
Have a good day.
[Bridget] How about Zeus?
-Zeus is your war dog, right?
-[Ricky] And?
-Please, tell me.
-I don't need to tell you anything.
[Bridget] Do I deserve how you treated me?
Stole from me?
-[Ricky] I'm not answering anymore.
-Took advantage when I was at my lowest?
Do you? Do you feel bad at all? No.
You're going to jail
if I have anything to do with it.
[tense music plays]
[Brianne] Come on, sweetheart.
[dramatic music plays]
[line ringing]
[Brianne] Hello?
He fucking didn't show.
-Wait, what? He didn't show up?
-[Cecilie] Yeah.
-He's gone.
-I really thought this was the moment.
[Cecilie] Bridget thinks he has left.
-And now--
-[Brianne] Yeah.
We're back at square one.
[dramatic music continues]
[Cecilie] When a suspect goes on the run,
they can evade justice for years.
With limited resources and no leads,
it's not like the police will go
actively out to hunt them down.
But I'm gonna be
a thorn in their side forever.
Doing the legwork that no one else will.
And they should be scared.
[music fades]
[intriguing music plays]
[woman] Hi, I'm--
I'm calling from Orlando.
My name is Jeannie O'Donnell.
I just saw your post.
I was dating this guy.
He was in the military.
He's taken me for thousands.
And he goes by the name of Ricky Morrisey.
[chimes]
[suspenseful music plays]
[Brianne] When a perpetrator
has crossed state lines,
it's clear that they don't wanna be found.
They know the risks.
And they're willing to do anything
to avoid being prosecuted.
It really bothers me
how easy it's been for Ricky to get away.
Like, there's an arrest warrant
out for him.
Seems like
the police aren't doing anything.
When we get a new lead,
it's imperative that we act on it quickly.
'Cause every minute that we wait,
it gives them time to clean up, regroup,
and move on to a different location.
I think Ricky is just hoping
that Bridget is gonna give up.
-We have to get eyes on this guy.
-[Cecilie] Yeah.
[Brianne] If we can find him,
we can get him extradited
back to Rhode Island.
[suspenseful music continues]
[line ringing]
This is Mindy.
[Brianne] Hey, Mindy.
Look, I need you to help me find this guy.
His name is Ricky Morrisey.
He's ex-military.
[Mindy] Just send me all his information
and I'll update you as soon as I can.
[Cecilie] Jeannie?
Hi. Cecilie.
-Nice to meet you.
-[Cecilie] Hi, so nice to meet you too.
When you got in touch,
I couldn't believe it.
'Cause we've been on the hunt
for Ricky for months.
[Jeannie] Really?
Can you just take me back to the start?
[straining] The start of it all was
Ricky and I matched on Tinder,
and he basically told me
that he was a cell phone reseller.
He was from the Boston area.
One of the reasons
why he was leaving Boston
is he did have an ex-girlfriend there.
It just didn't work out.
He did tell me that
she was a little bit, you know,
on the crazy side
and that he tried to make it work.
But it was just… It was really tough.
[soft music plays]
First time we met,
he was in some type of hot ride,
kind of like,
Fast and the Furious type of, like, vibe.
And as soon as I walked out my front door,
he came up right to me.
He gave me a hug,
opened the car door for me, let me in.
It was… a great feeling.
Like, it was just…
I don't-- Just-- I got a little bit
of, like, the butterflies in the stomach.
I mean,
the first date we spent all day together.
So, I feel our connection
just got so strong,
just on that first date.
-How long were you together?
-[Jeannie] Maybe two months.
He talked to me like I was…
the most beautiful woman in the world.
Mm.
[Jeannie] This is what I've always wanted.
He wants to plant roots.
He wants to have a house.
He's… He's doing everything
that he should be doing in his thirties,
and it's sexy.
I felt that Ricky was it.
-Mm.
-[Jeannie] Like, he was the one.
Everything was great
for the first part of it.
And
then it turned into… the nightmare.
[tense music plays]
[Cecilie] When did he start
to defraud you?
[Jeannie] After we were seeing each other
for a month.
He basically told me that he had
a big cell phone deal that was happening.
He does a lot of overseas sales.
Since he was in the Army,
he met a lot of people.
Okay.
There was a partner
coming in from Saudi Arabia,
to buy off these cell phones for $50,000.
The deal does not go through.
He has some old friends
from Boston that loaned him the money,
and now he's in a lot of trouble
because they were loan sharks.
And he needed to pay this loan back.
[chimes]
[Jeannie] He would call me upset.
He says, "I thought somebody was
following me. I was trying to run away."
And I'm like,
"Why don't you just come over?"
"Jeannie, I can't come over to you.
They know… They know where you live."
Were you scared?
I still have nightmares.
He said the loan sharks
were gonna attack us.
I think of somebody getting into my house
and it scares the shit out of me.
And that's what I asked him. "Can I help?"
'Cause I wanted to do something.
And I said, "What if I take out a loan?"
And he drove me over there during lunch,
walked out with $12,000.
[exhales]
[Jeannie] And literally handed it to him.
Like, it was, like…
It was 20 bucks in my pocket.
[chimes]
The next thing I know,
he doesn't speak to me for, like, a week.
[chimes]
-[Jeannie] He's busy.
-[chimes]
[chimes]
[Jeannie] Finally, he let me come over.
New address.
He had, um, a brand-new laptop,
one of these gaming computers.
The car was new.
It was gorgeous.
I'm looking at it like, this is…
Ricky, this is a brand-new car.
And I'm like,
where the fuck did this money go?
I just handed you $12,000,
and now you have stuff.
He's like, "No, I traded in the old one.
Remember I didn't like the old one?"
Looking around
and seeing all these pieces put together…
And then I knew it was a scam.
[ominous music plays]
Your life just kind of blows up.
And the worst, I think one of the worst,
and this is probably when it gets hard,
is that I don't have anybody to go to.
-Aw.
-[Jeannie] And it's…
[sniffles] It makes it difficult
because I had it… held it in.
-[Cecilie] Yeah.
-For so long.
And I couldn't tell my parents.
I didn't want my friends to think
I was absolutely crazy
for doing something so stupid.
-You need to stop saying that it's stupid.
-[Jeannie] I know.
We're doing a disservice
towards ourselves when we're doing that.
'Cause it's not true.
[gentle music plays]
[Cecilie] When you mix fear and love,
that's very powerful.
If you love someone
and care about someone,
and they come to you
and say that they're in danger,
you would want to help them.
The fraudsters
are targeting that kindness.
To steal money.
There's a warrant out for his arrest.
-Do you have any idea where to find him?
-As of where he is currently? No, I don't.
But I can give you the address for
where he was staying
the last time I saw him.
-That would be amazing.
-Okay. I agree.
-Thanks. I really appreciate everything.
-[Cecilie] Thank you so much.
Thank you.
[dramatic music plays]
[cell phone ringing]
Hello?
[Cecilie] Hi, Bri.
He's moved on from Bridget.
It seems like he has a whole new scam.
She doesn't know if he's still here,
but she gave us
the address where he's been staying.
It just looks like he's never gonna stop.
So we need to stop him.
[tense music plays]
Fraudsters have the ability
to go underground for a very long time.
This is their job.
And they're damn good at their job.
My fraudster definitely did things
to stay under the radar.
He used different names, fake passports,
and other people's credit cards.
He made sure
that nothing ever traced back to him.
But the thing is that
once you realize what they've done
and how many lives
they've wrecked, you don't stop.
[curious music plays]
-[Brianne] Let's see if anybody's home.
-[knocking]
Hi. I'm so sorry to bug you.
I'm looking for help
seeing if anyone who lives here
knows this guy.
-[man] I don't know. I'm sorry.
-[Brianne] Okay, thanks.
Quick question.
I see you guys walking the neighborhood.
Have you seen this guy around here?
Does he look familiar?
-I don't think so.
-[Brianne] No?
[Cecilie] I'm sorry to bother you,
but I am looking for a man
who used to live in the neighborhood.
His name is Ricky Morrisey. No?
We're looking for him.
-[Cecilie] And he looks like this.
-[man] No, I have no idea.
[Brianne] This is just dead end
after dead end.
[cell phone ringing]
-Hello?
-Hey, Bri. It's Mindy.
Hey, Mindy. What you got?
I might have found him.
-I have a video for you to look at.
-That's perfect. Can you send that to me?
Hi.
Mindy might have spotted him,
but she's not 100% sure.
[Cecilie] Is that him?
[Brianne] It looks like him.
-That's him.
-[Cecilie gasps]
[Brianne] Clear as day.
He's in freaking Orlando. Look at his ass.
Here's the best part.
Got his damn license plate.
The police can run the registration
and pick him up.
Now just the police needs to do their job.
-Yeah.
-[Brianne] We got his ass.
That's what we're hoping.
[music fades]
[intriguing music plays]
[radio beeps]
[officer] I have a white male, 10-15,
for signal 18 out of state, 10-27.
[officer 2] Oh, stand by, hold on.
There's a car over here.
Yeah, it is occupied.
Put a bumper on it if you want.
[radio beeps]
[officer 3] All right. You ready?
[officer 4] Yep.
Show me your hands. Do it now!
Put your hands up. Put your hands up.
-[Ricky] They're up. What am I doing?
-[officer 4] Step out. Step out.
Turn away from me.
You have a felony warrant.
-[Ricky] For what?
-[officer 4] Failure to appear for theft.
You have another one
out of Rhode Island for fraud.
-You have one out of--
-Same chick, yeah.
[officer 4] So…
-You can bring it.
-[Ricky] Yeah.
Fuck, man.
What are you doing up here?
You're meeting somebody or something?
That's the game you wanna play?
Just go up against the car.
Bro, I just had my life torn from me.
This girl's making up lies.
[officer 3] That's not our problem.
You have a warrant. That's why we're here.
[officer 4] You can take a seat.
You're gonna be extradited.
[Ricky] Fuck, man.
My whole life's just got turned up over
a fucking disagreement with a girlfriend.
It's fucking crazy.
[melancholy music plays]
-Oh my gosh, good to see you.
-[Bridget] How are you?
Hi.
[Brianne] I've been doing this
a long time,
but there's nothing like
seeing a bad guy get arrested.
-How are you?
-[Bridget] Good, you?
[Cecilie] We wanted
to just bring everyone together.
[Jeannie] Hi, how are you?
It's just good to hold him accountable.
[Ricky] Fuck, man.
I just had my life torn from me.
[officer 3] That's not our problem.
You have a warrant. That's why we're here.
[Brianne] Love it.
They just did not
put up with his shit. [chuckles]
I feel like I'm getting my life
back together, but it takes time.
The past few months, I met a new guy.
He's the complete opposite of Ricky.
He's wonderful.
He, I can see a future with.
And for all the pain and suffering
that Ricky caused me,
I ended up with Zeus.
He's a great dog.
No, no, Zeus!
[music fades]
[tense music plays]
Hi, Cecilie. I'm Shareza.
I married a man called Dorian Wilkerson.
He was a successful medical doctor.
I helped him start
a cosmetic surgery center.
He left me in almost $2 million of debt.
I really need your help.
That is insanity to me.
And I felt like I lost a lot
when it was, like, $250,000.
She has over $2 million in debt.
What did he say to her
to make her do all of this?
How does it get so bad for her?
[Shareza] I met Dorian
back in high school.
I was actually a freshman,
and he was a senior.
He was a great athlete.
Very popular.
He was great at football,
and he also ran track.
He was a ladies man,
you know, very charming.
I was kind of a bookworm.
We had brief interactions,
but not so much.
We lost touch for several years.
I was a teen mom,
so I actually had two daughters
by the age of 19, but I was still working.
I was going to college
and, um, just taking care of my girls.
Because I did grow up in the inner city,
I didn't have a whole lot.
So I wanted to provide
a better life for my daughters.
I had a successful career,
climbing the corporate ladder
as a business consultant.
I was doing pretty well for myself.
Then one day…
[chimes]
[Shareza] Dorian reached out to me
on Facebook.
"When you have a minute, put me in it."
At this point, I'm in Florida.
He lived in Atlanta.
He was working at Emory Hospital
as a medical doctor.
I was very impressed.
You know, Black man doing his thing,
you know, very proud of the man
that he has become from high school.
I had a business trip.
It was going to be in Atlanta, Georgia.
And I was like, "Oh, Dorian lives there."
I reached out, and I said,
"Hey, maybe we can have lunch?"
And he was like, "Oh, sure."
The first date, you know,
I was very nervous.
He picked me up
in this nice Bentley coupe.
He had on his medical scrubs,
and he told me,
"Hey, I have to go back and change."
So we went back to his loft,
a beautiful…
I think he was on the 21st floor,
which is very, you know, very nice.
And then we just went out on the town.
He seemed to be very into me
as far as asking questions,
very interested in, you know,
my life and things that I did.
I had a great time.
He was over-the-top romantic,
made me feel like a princess,
a queen that night.
This is someone who matches your drive.
This person is, you know,
everything that I would want.
[tense music plays]
I've never, ever had a case
where I'm meeting up with the victim now
where she's actually been married to him.
So he's gone to that length.
Then you are
a true professional in the game.
You're a hard-working fraudster,
I have to say.
-[Shareza] Hi.
-[Cecilie] Hi. Cecilie.
-Shareza, right?
-Give you a hug? Yes, Shareza.
[Cecilie] Hi. So cute.
It's beautiful here.
-Is that…
-[Shareza] Those are my daughters.
-[Cecilie] Beautiful.
-Thank you.
[Cecilie] Thank you for reaching out.
I saw the video where…
Yeah.
And I was like, "Wow."
It's scary.
-[Cecilie] Yeah.
-I have no idea what's going on.
-I'm hoping you can help me figure it out.
-[Cecilie] Yeah.
So tell me about Dorian.
What was your impression of him back then?
Very, um, loving.
-Yes.
-[Shareza] Right?
I literally get flowers
three times a week.
It wasn't just the average dozen roses.
He would just go all out
with rose petals, candles,
and walking in on flowers.
There was always something.
Just doing things
that you see on movies and TV.
He told me I was this perfect woman,
wrapped up in all of the qualities
that he was attracted to.
So, what did your daughters think of him?
They really thought
that he was a good guy.
Like, their mom was happy.
[soft instrumental music plays]
[Shareza] I am definitely not someone
that falls in love easily.
I always said that I trust backwards.
Like, you start at zero
and you have to earn 100.
I introduced my daughters to Dorian.
It was a big deal for me they'd get along.
Neither one of their fathers
were, you know, in their lives.
I found it very difficult to find someone
who wanted to be that father figure.
He was very attentive.
You know, he seemed to be very into,
you know, their well-being,
and who they were as young ladies.
They started building
a pretty decent relationship.
-So you were heavily invested in--
-[Shareza] Everything. Right.
And your entire family
was invested in this, yeah.
Oh my God, this is Mr. Right.
-[Cecilie] Yeah.
-This is the one.
[camera clicks]
[Shareza] It was off and on
for about a year,
and then he said
he wanted to be exclusive.
[camera clicks]
[Shareza] He says to me,
"What do you think
about me moving to Florida?"
"And moving in with you and the girls?"
I-- I was a little taken back.
And he said, you know,
"I need to be with, you know, someone
that really cares about me and loves me."
So he moved to Florida.
The girls were very happy about the move.
It was a new chapter.
Dorian told me
he wanted to open his own practice.
Here in Florida.
He said, "This is a dream for me.
Something I've always wanted to have."
And I was excited about it.
It felt like a new beginning
for the both of us.
[music ends]
[Cecilie] When did he first ask for money?
He asked me about
taking out a $100,000 business loan
for his own practice.
He said that his credit was horrible
from taking care of his mother
and the medical bills.
And I told him
I wasn't comfortable with doing that.
We're not even engaged.
Then he proposed maybe like a month after.
Well, that was quick.
-I still have the engagement video.
-[Cecilie] You do?
[upbeat music plays]
[Shareza] I was in the kitchen
just kind of cleaning up
because I had family over for dinner.
Next thing I know,
he comes in with flowers and balloons.
[women squealing]
[Shareza] Oh my God!
He had my friends and family over.
Dorian had even contacted my dad
asking for my hand in marriage.
So everybody except me knew
that he was going to propose that day.
Oh my God!
I can remember my godmom saying,
"Are you gonna answer?"
-So I finally just say yes.
-[Dorian] Yes.
[women squealing]
And
I was engaged.
[woman] Let me see that!
But I feel like
you seem in complete kind of shock.
The way he came about it was almost like
making you not be able to say no.
Like, I see this so often
with romance fraud.
Like, the victims are put under
such huge amounts of pressure.
Yeah, in hindsight.
-It's like that was very manipulative.
-Yeah.
[soft music plays]
The wedding day was very exciting.
I was nervous, of course.
Family and friends,
maybe about 150 to 200 guests.
And we just had a great time.
It was awesome.
This is it.
Like, now I'm building my forever.
[Cecilie] So let me guess, it wasn't long
before he asked for that loan again.
Yeah.
And then I end up
taking out a $100,000 loan
'cause he promised
that this would be great for our future.
So this new business was set up.
It was called the Best U Now
where we had cosmetic surgery procedures.
Being that the Best U Now
was in South Florida,
and I know that South Florida is,
like, the hub for cosmetic surgery,
I was really excited about it.
Dorian was over the day-to-day operation
of the business.
I was really just an investor.
I was still working
for a Fortune 500 company.
He would hire surgeons
that would perform tummy tucks,
liposuction, Brazilian butt lifts,
facelifts, rhinoplasty.
You name it, they did it.
But there was a lot of expenses
that came along with it.
Dorian said that his credit
still wasn't where it needed to be.
I took out a lot of loans
just to fund this business.
He had me put my name
jointly on everything.
I felt a bit overwhelmed,
but Dorian said that I would definitely
be able to get my money back.
I felt like I had to do that,
you know, as a wife.
That's what it's about, partnership.
When it started,
the business, it was doing well.
-It was, yeah?
-It seemed like it. Things were lucrative.
[gentle music plays]
[Shareza] The Best U Now became known
based off of word of mouth.
And it started bringing in money.
So I felt that
this was gonna be something great.
So Dorian felt
that my house was too small.
He had always said
he never liked townhomes.
And he wanted something bigger.
So he talked me into
purchasing a new home that cost $800,000.
It was a beautiful five-bedroom,
four-bathroom home.
Gated community,
very prestigious community.
I mean, it was gorgeous.
It was a dream home.
Because Dorian's credit
still was not where it needs to be,
I qualified for this home by myself.
I felt like
everything was falling in place.
We had the Best U Now clinic.
I had the husband.
I had beautiful daughters.
So this is perfect.
And then all of a sudden, things weren't.
So how did things unravel?
Um, things got bad
when the business just kind of flopped.
[suspenseful music plays]
After about a year and a half
of the Best U Now opening,
Dorian told me that
the landlords wanted us to pay more money.
And the Best U Now had to move
to get this new location up and running.
There's more money that has to be spent.
A lot of things started going wrong.
I noticed that staff
started leaving abruptly.
Dorian had lost surgeons.
Patients were coming back
with surgery horror stories.
Botched Brazilian butt lifts.
Lipo gone wrong.
The clinic was just going down.
There was no money coming in.
The debt is piling up,
and we can't afford it anymore.
I asked Dorian what happened
to the money that we were making.
What-- What's going on?
And he was never able
to give me a real definitive answer.
We're in a position
where we're literally maybe
two, three payrolls away
from losing it all.
I have so much to lose at this point.
I have to make this work.
So I took out a loan…
[keyboard clacking]
[Shareza] …for $500,000.
Just to get the business back afloat.
But now I have all this debt in my name.
I begin to get very worried.
I don't have a handle on this.
[Cecilie] There's something called
sunk cost fallacy,
which means that
the more that you put into a relationship,
and the further in you get,
the more difficult it is to admit
that something's wrong
'cause you've already spent
so much time, so much money.
Like, you go deeper and deeper into it
instead of retracting.
[Shareza] Eventually, the business closed.
It was close to, like, $2 million
in debt and loans that was owed,
that I was ultimately responsible for.
[soft music plays]
[Shareza] I wasn't sure how I wanted
to move forward at this point.
After the business closed,
once I said I wasn't taking out
any more credit in my name,
Dorian began behaving very irrationally.
We got into argument after argument.
Then one day, I came into his office.
He wasn't there,
and I just happened to look on his desk.
I found this text message
that he wrote to a friend
that basically said,
"She's broke.
She's not gonna use her credit,
so I'm basically done."
[music intensifies]
[Shareza] As I read that message,
my heart literally
just sunk to my stomach.
After five years together,
it was sickening.
And that's when
I decided to file for divorce.
[foreboding music plays]
[Shareza] Dorian just left.
And I have no idea where he's gone.
I'm in so much debt,
I filed a civil suit to try
and get at least some of my money back.
But Dorian's tactics
was to file a lawsuit against me.
He was basically saying that
it's my fault that the business failed.
He has actually filed
multiple police reports against me.
One of those saying that
I signed a check
that he didn't give me permission to.
Dorian was trying to silence me.
[Cecilie] Did you go to the police?
I went to the police,
and they said, um, this is a civil matter.
They didn't even take a report.
The police don't even care
to look into it, and I think that is what…
It-- It angers me so much.
Yeah.
-What do you need our help with?
-I need to find out everything.
-I wanna get to the bottom of this.
-Yeah.
Um, I want justice.
[Brianne] Hey, girl.
-Hi.
-[Brianne] Hi.
Good to see you.
[Brianne] Good to see you too.
So where do we go from here?
The case is insane.
[curious music plays]
[Cecilie] Shareza claims
he was asking her to co-sign for loans,
making her legally responsible
for the debt.
And now he's disappeared.
So the ultimate goal
with this investigation is
establishing whether or not
this dude was legitimate.
-Yeah.
-[Brianne] Or not.
Was he really in love with her,
or was he really trying
to take her for everything he could?
A common tactic among fraudsters
is to get the victims
to take out loans in their names.
That way, the victims are the ones
who are responsible for the debts.
If we can prove
that the perpetrator lied to the victim
in order to get these loans taken out,
that's loan fraud.
We need to dig up
some information on Dorian.
[keyboard clacking]
[Brianne] Look at him
with his little business suit.
How many businesses does this guy have?
I wonder why he has
so many different businesses and personas.
He's got, looks like,
the doctor lab coat
with the stethoscope around his neck.
And then there's another one.
"Dorian Wilkerson, PhD,
Statistics Professor."
[Cecilie] Looks like
two very different careers, you would say.
"Dr. Dorian Wilkerson, PhD,
Director at Body Renue."
[keyboard clacking]
Facebook, Facebook,
good morning, good morning.
-[Brianne] He's got some Facebook videos.
-Yeah.
I'm just here laying at Body Renue.
[Dorian] Non-surgical Brazilian butt lift.
-[woman] Introduce yourself, Doc.
-Yep, Dr. Wilkerson, Dr. Wilkerson.
Who goes on a Facebook Live
with a patient laying there?
Yeah. Yeah, definitely.
[Dorian] I'm actually tagging a name
that, uh, you're gonna hear me
use and, um, and post a lot.
That name is Dr. Body.
Did you hear this guy
call himself Dr. Body?
[sniggers] Yeah, Dr. Body.
A week from today would just give us
a pretty good, um, ideology of how…
Not even an ideology,
a pretty good assumption
of how well
her lymphatic system is draining.
He's trying to sound
like he knows what he's talking about.
But he totally sounds, like, uninformed
about what it is he's trying to explain.
Yeah.
[Dorian] Some of the things
that I wanna talk about is two words. Um…
Well, actually, it's one word.
Liposuction.
[Brianne] Something's not adding up
with this.
We need to see what information
is out there on those clinics.
We need to do a little digging around
on Dorian and the business itself.
And I think
that's a very good starting point for us
to work out
what's fact and what's fiction.
When marriage is involved,
it could complicate things.
You share bank accounts.
You share contracts. You share mortgages.
It's not as easy to separate
responsibilities.
And it's hard to isolate wrongdoing.
All right.
Y'all just hang there for a minute.
Might be a little weird with the cameras.
[tense music plays]
[Brianne] Hi, how are you?
Just wondering if you've heard
of a business called Best, uh, U Now.
-Does that name ring a bell?
-[woman] Yeah, it does.
That's the gentleman who was
across the street doing--
[Brianne] Yeah.
In that building over there, right?
[woman] He was a former athlete
or something.
[Brianne] Yeah.
[woman] That's what I heard.
So he appeared to be reputable.
[Brianne] Yeah. So what have you heard
about him or what do you know about him?
Well, we just heard
that there were some kind of
unscrupulous things going on over there.
-[Brianne ] Yeah.
-Shady stuff, yeah.
-[Brianne] Yeah.
-I have to say it's unusual for this area.
-[Brianne] Yeah? Thank you. Bye.
-Yeah.
[tense music plays]
[Brianne] Hi.
I was wondering about a business,
Best U Now, um, Dorian Wilkerson.
-I don't… Gosh, this was a while ago.
-[Brianne] Yeah.
I remember something
along the lines of him, like,
jumping out of state
because of something funky that went on.
-[Brianne] Oh wow.
-Yeah.
[Brianne] Did you remember where he went
when he left state? Do you remember?
[man] Georgia. I don't know
if that's where Emory is…
-[Brianne] Oh!
-[man] Where he graduated from med school.
-That's the only thing I remember.
-[Brianne] Possibly going to Georgia.
-Maybe. I don't know.
-[Brianne] Potentially.
Thank you so much for your time, okay?
All right, bye.
It seems like Dorian
has jumped state lines with this.
He used to work at Emory Hospital.
Maybe he's gone back there.
I've gotta get to Atlanta.
[music fades]
[Cecilie] We are now headed
to see Shareza's daughters.
I have tons of questions
about how their life with Dorian was.
How involved were they in the business?
What did they know about it?
What has been the aftermath?
-Hi, Cecilie. Nice to meet you.
-Hi, Nykki. Thank you.
[Cecilie] Sit down.
Thank you for meeting up with me.
-[woman] No problem.
-[Nykki] Of course.
Yeah, as you know,
we've been speaking to your mom.
-[Nykki] Yes.
-[Cecilie] Um.
I don't know how much she's told you,
but we're doing an investigation.
You know, I can imagine
what you guys have been through…
-Yeah.
-…as well.
So how close were you guys to Dorian?
We were pretty close.
[soft lively music plays]
[Nykki] We pushed the family narrative.
If someone referred to us as his stepkids…
[Cecilie] Oh.
Oh, he's going off, like,
"Who gives you the right to call?
These are my daughters."
[Nykki] The little girl in me
appreciated it.
[Jynah] It was undeniable
that when you would see all four of us,
we were in a family.
-There was no one I've ever called dad.
-Dad.
'Cause my biological father,
I never got a chance to meet him.
-It did make you feel special in a sense.
-Yeah.
Thinking back,
and that's one thing I grieve.
That family unit
that I was so proud to be a part.
-We changed our last name legally.
-Oh wow.
[Shareza] We are the Wilkersons!
[Nykki] And we framed it and everything.
That's something
that kind of makes me tear up because
when we made that decision to do that,
that came from, like, our soul.
-And he cried, he bawled to the point…
-[Jynah] He bawled.
[Nykki] My granddad held him.
He bawled. They were both crying.
[Cecilie] Did you guys know
that your mom was taking up loans?
We didn't know exactly
what was going on behind the scenes.
[Nykki] That's all we knew
as far as my mom's involvement,
was pushing his narrative and helping
his business get off the ground.
What did you know about, like, him
as a doctor and what did he say?
Yeah. Okay, so they called him Doc-Doc.
-Yeah.
-Why'd they call him Doc-Doc?
-Because he was a double doctor.
-Doctor.
He was a medical doctor
and a PhD, hence the Doc-Doc.
When you say "they." Who were they?
-That's how he introduced himself.
-So, he said it?
[Nykki] He said that.
That was his Facebook name.
"I'm Dorian. You can call me Doc-Doc.
Doc for short." Everyone called him Doc.
You didn't say the doctor,
it was a problem.
[Nykki] Now we're starting to learn
that we were living with a stranger…
-…this whole time.
-[Jynah] Whole time.
How have you seen
this whole situation affect your mom?
It was unbearable at a point.
The hurt I felt and we felt,
I know my mom feels that times a thousand.
I never want another woman
to feel this ever again.
And just to think about us now,
us growing up as young women.
-You think about love a different way.
-Yeah.
A completely different way, because…
To know that you were in love
with somebody who was just using you.
-That hurts.
-[Nykki] That hurts bad.
Like, how do you do that?
-It's crazy.
-Yeah.
I'm just happy we still have her mentally,
'cause that can take a toll on somebody.
Especially, like, you know, being in love,
being defrauded.
So to still have her
being the strong woman that she is…
If she can do it,
it kind of gives me hope.
[tense music plays]
[Cecilie] What he's done to this family
is just unforgivable.
They thought they had a father figure,
like what a lot of teenage girls
you know, would want, you know.
It's like he's coming in,
making their mom happy.
Like, "I'm here, we have a future,
we're a proper family unit now."
But it isn't just only one victim,
it's a ripple effect.
It's a huge devastation.
For the people around.
They changed their fucking last name.
And this is what he does?
[music intensifies]
[Brianne] I do not come to Atlanta often,
so… I'm just trying
to navigate these streets.
Dorian told Shareza
that he worked for Emory Hospital.
So, I'm just gonna go to Emory
and see if there's a personnel office,
human resources,
someone who would be
willing to talk to me.
And see if any of that's true.
[background chatter]
[Brianne] I need to verify, like,
an employment status.
I'm a licensed private investigator.
How do I do that here?
-[woman] Let's find a private space.
-[Brianne] Yeah. Let me grab my stuff.
Perfect.
[female] What is this person's name?
[Brianne] His name is Dorian Wilkerson.
[Shareza] When we were
just getting to know one another,
Dorian told me that
he was working at Emory Hospital,
and he was an emergency room doctor.
And when I would go to Atlanta
for a visit,
Dorian would go out to work
at about 10:30 p.m.
and get home at 7:30 a.m.
He had on his medical scrubs,
looked very studious
and very, you know, attractive.
He was very impressive.
At one point
Dorian said that President Obama
came to Emory Hospital,
and he just went down the line
shaking their hands.
He was like, "Good job, Doc."
And I was like, "Oh wow."
I said, "That's awesome."
[Brianne] Thank you so much.
I appreciate it. Y'all have a good day.
[line ringing]
-[Brianne sighs]
-[line continues ringing]
[Brianne] All right.
[Cecilie] Hi, Bri.
Hey, Cecilie. So…
I'm at Emory Hospital.
-And guess what I found out.
-What?
So, I got someone to give me information.
And turns out they don't have
a record of him at all in their database.
[sighs]
These people have never heard
of Dorian Wilkerson at Emory.
Fuck. This is big.
[Brianne] It's huge.
All right. Well, I just wanted
to give you a brief update on that.
-[Cecilie] Sure.
-[Brianne] Okay, bye.
It's not looking good for Dorian.
So Dorian is claiming to be a doctor,
and I wanna dig up
some information into his credentials.
[Shareza] When Dorian and I first met,
he seemed very compassionate,
that he wanted to help people,
no matter what.
But after a while,
it really just started changing.
Search.
[Brianne] No records found.
[Shareza] We got into
argument after argument.
He became more distant
and just basically disappeared.
Here's something
from the Department of Health.
Oh, this sounds serious.
They issued this guy a cease and desist.
They said that he is not licensed
by the department
or the board of medicine,
and is practicing medicine
and leading the public to believe
he is a medical doctor.
Oh my God.
[tense music continues]
I don't know
who this person is that I married.
This person was turning into a monster.
[music ends]
[eerie music plays]