♪Time flies and your soul is escaping♪
♪With chaotic breaths, you strive to fight♪
♪Yet you keep being labeled♪
♪Crushing your last bit of courage♪
♪The storm leaves you defeated♪
♪Emotions are pushed to the edge♪
♪With endless words, who takes a stand♪
♪Join me in my dreams♪
♪In the long night, I'm waiting for a chance♪
♪Have you seen the tomb's secret?♪
♪Where does the person in my dreams go?♪
=Sadistic Love=
=Episode 3=
What do you want to do?
Let me go!
Let me go, He Zheng.
My dear sister,
do you know
the harm you've caused me
is no less than what your father did?
But your current pitiful appearance,
for me,
is extremely hypocritical.
Either sign the paper
or let your father die.
Choose one.
I forgot to tell you.
Before I agreed to this marriage,
I hid the gold mine map.
Except me,
no one knows where it is.
If you can't fully investigate the case
and clear my father's name,
I promise
you can't even get any gold.
(Marriers: Helian Zheng; He Anran)
Can you let me go now?
(Even if this is the only way)
(that keep you by my side.)
♪Turning the last page♪
♪Only then did I realize♪
♪We have been apart for fifteen years♪
♪Going through the rain of bullets♪
♪Living on the edge of life and death♪
No snow fell in five years in Luan City.
♪Similar silhouettes♪
How ironic!
♪Take it as destiny's mercy, time's gift♪
(In the heavy snow that year,)
(you saved me.)
(He Anran,)
(do you regret this?)
♪A pen dipped in honey
can seek a trace of life♪
You're an illegitimate child.
How dare you come to the He Family?
He's still a mute.
Please, stop fighting.
- Mrs. He said
- He knows he was wrong.
if he can't learn to eat properly,
then make him stay outside overnight.
Zheng.
Mother...
- How dare you!
- Please stop.
A bad woman has such a bad child.
Stop it. What are you doing?
♪In the dead of night♪
Someone. Help her go back to rest.
Don't let her freeze.
Save him.
Zheng...
He's He Zheng, my father's son,
my brother.
Who's trying to harm him?
First, ask if my father agrees.
Let's go.
♪A blank sheet of paper♪
♪For a love poem without words♪
♪Among the crowd, only I grasp his will♪
♪Wearing matching suits and rings♪
♪Attending a special ceremony together♪
Are you okay?
I know.
You did it for your mother.
Your mother did it for you too.
You are my brother,
my only brother.
I'll protect you from now on.
♪Let names be buried in history♪
♪No need for grand praises♪
♪Just hope future know my steadfast will♪
♪Devote myself to chaotic times♪
♪My heart also given to the fervent red flag♪
(Even if you regret,)
(I will never let go.)
(The one who first provoked me)
(is you.)
♪Those words that were never spoken in life♪
♪I will say them myself after I die♪
♪The news of victory comes to my ears♪
♪An old friend stands close before me♪
♪I raise the gun♪
♪To meet him in prosperity♪
(Luan City's First Prison)
Governor.
(File)
Here are the info for all 20-year-old men.
But we still haven't found the person.
It's been so many years.
Could it be that he has...?
As long as I don't hear from Tang for a day,
it means he is not dead.
Keep searching.
Yes.
After she finishes visiting,
take her back to the Governor's Mansion.
I've already given the instructions.
Governor,
do you want to take a look at the case
of the spy being killed last night?
No need.
Lu Sheng Tower just wants to tell me
he can take the people
that I can capture.
So what should we do now?
He's gone to such lengths to involve me.
How could I not give him some face?
Bravo!
You sing so well.
Let me tell you.
I heard the governor is coming today.
Really?
Yes, it's true.
I heard he is as handsome as in the photo.
Yeah.
Bravo!
Governor, forgive me for my incompetent.
I couldn't identify the Master's identity.
I don't even know the gender.
How could he compare to you?
Lu Sheng Tower
relies on selling intelligence,
which is a tough one to deal with.
As long as they're not opposing me,
it doesn't matter who they are.
- Great!
- That's great.
I haven't come back in years.
When did the darts in Luan City
become the reward in Luan City?
Whoever hits the colored ball on stage
will receive prize money from loyal fans
and will be awarded to the day's star.
- Tell the head here
- Great!
if the Master doesn't appear,
then he'll have
to accept my gift.
There are ten minutes left.
Understood.
- Bravo!
Beauty, have a drink with me.
Go away.
Have a drink.
It's all gone.
Does this help him out?
Don't be shy.
Get lost.
You're the governor.
Helian, Helian Zheng.
How are you?
A place that harbors dirt and filth.
It's closed.
Go away.
Please, let me go.
It's all because of you.
He views me as worthless.
Want me to have a drink with you?
Good.
Drink it
while it's hot.
Here's a toast to you.
Drink it! Drink!
Drink!
I'm asking you to drink!
Drink it up.
Drink it!
Drink!
♪Like a drowning whale♪
♪Falling into you♪
♪Into every inch of your body♪
♪Then it fell apart♪
♪Without a trace♪
♪Like a warm winter♪
♪Running barefoot to you♪
♪Spreading in your cold palm♪
♪Vanishing in your warm breath♪
♪Because nobody knows♪
♪Can't ever go back♪
♪You touch my heart, my heart♪
♪Why is it so calm?♪
♪Cause everybody knows♪
♪Can't ever go back♪
♪I have long lost myself♪
♪And lost you too♪