♪Time flies and your soul is escaping♪
♪With chaotic breaths, you strive to fight♪
♪Yet you keep being labeled♪
♪Crushing your last bit of courage♪
♪The storm leaves you defeated♪
♪Emotions are pushed to the edge♪
♪With endless words, who takes a stand♪
♪Join me in my dreams♪
♪In the long night, I'm waiting for a chance♪
♪Have you seen the tomb's secret?♪
♪Where does the person in my dreams go?♪
=Sadistic Love=
=Episode 14=
Governor,
if we provide both porridge and medical aid,
our supplies won't suffice.
Moreover,
the new refugee settlement is also an issue.
Open the soldier's training ground,
and place the refugees there for now.
Use the budget from the Governor's Mansion.
But our expenses are already...
I'll find a way.
Give me the water.
Go ahead.
The Chu Family
is willing to help the refugees.
After all, such acts that build public trust
shouldn't be monopolized by you alone.
I'll remember your kindness today.
I'll repay it.
Thank you.
Helian Zheng,
I want to talk to you.
Mr. He has returned home now.
What's your plan with Anran?
This is my personal matter.
I don't need outsiders to interfere.
I just want to know your feelings about her.
This will determine
whether I should tell you a secret.
He Anran is my wife.
In my lifetime,
I'll never let her go.
When Mr. He found out about you two,
he insisted on driving you away.
Anran, to keep you there,
was forced to agree to meet me.
Later, she confessed to me,
saying that she would never
marry anyone else in this lifetime.
Though I'm reluctant
to admit it,
I don't even qualify as your rival in love.
What were you talking about?
Nothing.
Just some usual conversations.
Ming'an and I...
Anran,
you must be exhausted today.
Come up, I'll carry you.
Take a look.
Sir,
following the style of this merit ring,
make an exact copy for me
as soon as possible.
The materials must be precisely the same.
This must remain a secret from everyone
to avoid causing any unnecessary trouble.
No problem.
How's your brother-in-law lately?
Five years ago,
a concubine in our family died.
He helped with the autopsy,
proving it was suicide.
Help me arrange a meeting.
Let's have tea together.
Thanks for thinking about us.
I'll pass the message along.
Let's not delay, get to work quickly.
Alright.
Goodbye.
Hello?
Anran.
What?
You want to hand over the key to the mine.
(So you've kept it all along.)
(I misunderstood)
(that you already discarded our token.)
I know you're not asleep.
Go to bed quickly.
Or are you...
waiting for me to carry you?
Who said I'm not asleep?
I just woke up now.
Thank you.
I can handle this minor injury myself.
I'm your husband.
It's only natural that I care about you.
(He Molin)
Wait.
Deposit slip for the gold mine map.
Here you go.
(He Molin)
Why give it to me?
Because I trust you.
To settle so many refugees,
you'll need funds.
Why trust me?
Rumors outside say,
I'm a ruthless warlord.
But I do trust you.
You're not heartless,
but a governor who cares for the people.
♪Silent sentiments, shattered colors♪
♪All withered to dust♪
♪Shrouded in gloom, ideals are destroyed♪
Don't trust me too much.
(Helian Zheng,)
(I'll never leave you again.)
(He Anran,)
(I won't let you slip away again.)
♪Time flies♪
I raised him for nothing!
No wonder
he wanted to release He Molin.
He plans to take the gold mine alone.
Doesn't he want to be the hero of Luan City?
Fine.
Go,
spread the news
about those orphans.
Yes, I'm on it.
It's me.
I said,
there will be no cooperation between us.
You want Helian Zheng to apologize,
and I want the gold mine.
Isn't it worth teaming up once?
Sounds interesting.
It's a good deal.
Tell me your plan.
I know,
you've hidden those orphans
in the Death Squad
as bait for me.
This time,
I will make sure Helian Zheng dies.
Wait for the news.
Rong Yin.
Yes.
Investigate
what Zhao Zhiqian is up to.
Cooperate in secret.
Remember,
never use our Death Squad.
Identify bandits linked to Zhao Zhiqian.
Have them target Helian Zheng.
This way,
I can make their relationships...
(completely break apart.)
Yes.
Governor,
we found that the missing orphans
fell into the bandits' hands.
The bandits made one of our spies
deliver a message,
demanding you to go to
the abandoned warehouse at 3 PM today.
Otherwise,
no orphan will survive.
Prepare explosives from the armory.
Place them around the warehouse.
Governor, you mustn't.
These explosives are more powerful
than before.
Once I rescue the orphans,
I'll detonate the explosives.
These bandits are heinous.
I won't let them leave Luan City alive.
Master,
Zhao Zhiqian has taken action.
He Anran has also been taken
to the warehouse.
What about Helian Zheng?
He's been lured there.
It seems like
he's doomed.
The Helian Zheng I know
is definitely not foolish.
He must be using this event
to remove Zhao Zhiqian's men
and to intimidate Zhao Zhiqian.
But Zheng still underestimated
his foster father's deceitfulness.
♪Like a drowning whale♪
♪Falling into you♪
♪Into every inch of your body♪
♪Then it fell apart♪
♪Without a trace♪
♪Like a warm winter♪
♪Running barefoot to you♪
♪Spreading in your cold palm♪
♪Vanishing in your warm breath♪
♪Because nobody knows♪
♪Can't ever go back♪
♪You touch my heart, my heart♪
♪Why is it so calm?♪
♪Cause everybody knows♪
♪Can't ever go back♪
♪I have long lost myself♪
♪And lost you too♪