♪Time flies and your soul is escaping♪
♪With chaotic breaths, you strive to fight♪
♪Yet you keep being labeled♪
♪Crushing your last bit of courage♪
♪The storm leaves you defeated♪
♪Emotions are pushed to the edge♪
♪With endless words, who takes a stand♪
♪Join me in my dreams♪
♪In the long night, I'm waiting for a chance♪
♪Have you seen the tomb's secret?♪
♪Where does the person in my dreams go?♪
=Sadistic Love=
=Episode 16=
I recently learned a new herbal cuisine.
Eat it while it's warm.
Honey,
the doctor said I've fully recovered.
I don't need to have this.
You need to nourish your body.
I've just stewed it.
Let me feed you.
Does it taste bad?
♪Blurry silhouette, dark soliloquy♪
How about I feed you some too?
♪Silent emotions, shattered colors♪
♪All withered to dust♪
It really doesn't taste good.
Then,
how will you make it up to me?
♪You're like a ghost♪
Well...
♪Trapped in the sea of people♪
Eat me up then.
♪Time flies and your soul is escaping♪
♪With chaotic breaths, you strive to fight♪
♪Yet you keep being labeled♪
♪Crushing your last bit of courage♪
♪The storm leaves you defeated♪
♪Emotions are pushed to the edge♪
♪With endless words, who takes a stand♪
♪Join me in my dreams♪
♪In the long night, I'm waiting for a chance♪
♪Have you seen the tomb's secret?♪
♪Where does the person in my dreams go?♪
♪Do you still remember my footsteps♪
Open your eyes.
There's nothing here.
It's beautiful!
Look.
Do you like it?
I like it.
This is my happiest time
in the past five years.
Thank you.
(I once thought)
(that in this lifetime,)
(we'd only be entangled by hatred.)
(But heaven heard my prayers)
(and granted me a reunion with you.)
(He Anran.)
(Thank you)
(for willing to fall in love with me.)
The assassin who silenced Li Yang
and the bandits who kidnapped Anran
used weapons from your old troops.
Since they were my old troops,
what do they have to do with me now?
From the kidnapping case of wealthy children,
He Molin's imprisonment,
Anran's abduction,
to the bandits trying to blow me up...
The only goal
was to clear all obstacles.
So the person behind all these
can claim the gold mine without hesitation.
That person
can only be you.
Helian Zheng.
Don't forget,
when you were at your lowest,
I was the one who took you in.
Is that so?
I survived a pile of corpses on my own.
To you,
I'm just a sharp and useful blade.
The reason I made it through alive
isn't because of your mercy.
It's because my will to live is unyielding.
Even if...
you truly formed troops with the bandits,
it doesn't matter.
But now you can rest easy,
because I've worked with neighboring cities
to launch a major purge.
The last remnants of the bandits
won't survive this time.
Zheng,
it seems I should step down.
everything here
will belong to you from now on.
Zhao Zhiqian.
This is the last time I'll see you.
We are no longer bonded.
Helian Zheng,
you really have a tough life.
I couldn't kill you even with such a trap.
And it cost me
so many pawns I trained painstakingly.
I won't forget
this debt.
This studio is truly unique.
Compared to the mansion,
this studio
is where Anran loves to stay the most.
Come on,
try the afternoon tea I made myself.
How is it?
It's really good.
It's Zheng's favorite green tea.
As long as you like it.
Zheng, here's your favorite
Sweet Tofu Pudding.
Tang,
the Spicy Tofu Pudding Zheng said you like.
Since when did Zheng like sweet foods?
I remember he only liked spicy ones.
Anran likes it,
so now I like it too.
Seeing you and Miss He so close,
as his younger brother,
I feel truly pleased.
I carved these by myself.
Consider them a wedding gift for you two.
Thank you, Tang.
They're truly exquisite.
Are they a butterfly and a bead?
The hollow bead symbolizes unity.
The butterfly represents
happiness and health.
I hope it brings you good fortune.
What a wonderful blessing!
Tang, you're really handy.
Zheng, I'll attach it to your gun holster.
Alright.
The pudding is getting cold, drink it.
Then feed me.
It's delicious.
(He Anran, Helian Zheng,)
(why do you get to be happy?)
(While I live alone in a nightmare.)
Losers!
If it weren't for your selfishness,
he would've been dead
and you wouldn't have to sulk here.
The governor seems to
truly care about you.
I heard he even gifted you
a private residence.
But honestly, I still think you
look even more stunning
with your makeup on.
Zhao Zhiqian,
stay away from me.
I can't stand the filth.
Mo Yutang.
Don't you forget,
everything you have now
was given to you by me.
Old man,
take a good look.
I'm no longer that Mo Yutang
you could manipulate.
Take your dirty hands off it.
(Helian Zheng, May 29th, Year Seventeen)
Mo Yutang.
You hate me.
But haven't you become just like me?
I'm the one who understands you the most.
So,
don't even think of going against me.
If I were to die,
before my death,
I'd make sure to expose your darkest side
to the public.
Finished?
Then leave now.
What?
Don't want me to bring up the past, huh?
Alright.
Just think of it
as my final deal with Lu Sheng Tower.
You have to take it.
Yutang,
your body
still smells as fragrant
as before.
Rong Yin, I need to bathe.
Stay back!
Don't come over!
- You have a face
- Let me go.
- even more beautiful than an actress.
- Please let me go.
You even smell nice.
I didn't expect
to reach this move so soon.
This moment...
I don't want to wait anymore.
♪Like a drowning whale♪
♪Falling into you♪
♪Into every inch of your body♪
♪Then it fell apart♪
♪Without a trace♪
♪Like a warm winter♪
♪Running barefoot to you♪
♪Spreading in your cold palm♪
♪Vanishing in your warm breath♪
♪Because nobody knows♪
♪Can't ever go back♪
♪You touch my heart, my heart♪
♪Why is it so calm?♪
♪Cause everybody knows♪
♪Can't ever go back♪
♪I have long lost myself♪
♪And lost you too♪