♪Time flies and your soul is escaping♪
♪With chaotic breaths, you strive to fight♪
♪Yet you keep being labeled♪
♪Crushing your last bit of courage♪
♪The storm leaves you defeated♪
♪Emotions are pushed to the edge♪
♪With endless words, who takes a stand♪
♪Join me in my dreams♪
♪In the long night, I'm waiting for a chance♪
♪Have you seen the tomb's secret?♪
♪Where does the person in my dreams go?♪
=Sadistic Love=
=Episode 17=
(Wen Hsin Gallery)
♪Like a drowning whale♪
♪Falling into you♪
♪Into every inch of your body♪
(Anran,)
(did you paint them
in the past five years?)
♪Like a warm winter♪
(Someone has missed me)
♪Running barefoot to you♪
(so deeply these five years.)
♪Vanishing in your warm breath♪
♪Those things about you♪
♪Beautiful things♪
♪Deep as breathing♪
♪Pause and breathe♪
♪Hold tighter♪
♪But I've already♪
♪Decided to forget you♪
♪But♪
♪Because nobody knows♪
♪Can't ever go back♪
♪You touch my heart, my heart♪
♪Why is it so calm?♪
♪Cause everybody knows♪
♪Can't ever go back♪
♪I have long lost myself♪
Master,
I've dealt with
the death warrior related to Zhao Zhiqian.
The governor and madam
share a deep affection.
They released sky lanterns
for blessings tonight.
Buy all the sky lanterns in the city
and burn them all.
Understood.
Master,
this is the peace talisman I got for you.
Keep it for me.
Consider it as keeping me safe.
What wish did you just make?
I know what wish you made.
(together forever)
How could you have it?
Does that mean my wish didn't make it?
Give it back.
♪Blurry silhouette♪
Anran and Zheng will be together forever.
You said it out loud.
Will it still work?
I'll help you make it come true.
♪All withered to dust♪
My wish is...
♪Your soul is escaping♪
to fulfill all of He Anran's wishes.
♪Yet you keep being labeled♪
♪Crushing your last bit of courage♪
♪The storm leaves you defeated♪
♪Emotions are pushed to the edge♪
♪With endless words, who takes a stand♪
♪Join me in my dreams♪
♪In the long night, I'm waiting for a chance♪
♪Have you seen the tomb's secret?♪
Father, the strawberries are so sweet.
Then have some more.
You're the best to me.
Wouldn't all the fathers
treat their daughter well?
But I worry someone will treat you poorly.
Father.
Zheng treats me very well.
Really?
He almost got you hurt in an explosion.
I shouldn't have agreed back then.
Father.
I can't even describe how good he is.
All you need to know is
he's someone
who would risk his life for me,
whom I can entrust everything to.
I've decided he's the one for me.
Father, you'll give us your blessing,
won't you?
Father.
Come here.
Take a look.
Father, what is this?
This is the He Family's property deeds
(Deed)
and the shop contract.
Don't tell He Zheng about this.
This is my private property for you.
Even if he treats you really well,
I hope you can live well
even without him.
Father.
(No wonder when I first met him,)
(I felt his ring looked familiar.)
(I didn't expect)
(it to match the mark on Concubine Liang.)
(I need to tell He Zheng about this.)
(Let him investigate.)
Hello, connect me to the Governor's Mansion.
He Molin wants to tell them something.
He Zheng, tonight at ten,
meet me near the mining area
in the outskirts.
Don't tell anyone about this.
It's about the cause of your mother's death.
(Anran,)
(I'll be back soon.)
(It's already 10:30.)
(Why hasn't He Molin shown up yet?)
Why did he leave so early?
Hello?
Miss, you should go home quickly.
The Master has been harmed.
What?
Anran.
Don't be too upset.
Father.
Ming'an.
My father is just injured, isn't he?
Tell me.
My father is just injured, right?
Say something! Tell me.
He's just injured,
- isn't he?
- Anran...
Mr. He, he...
He has passed away.
No, that can't be.
Father.
Father!
Father...
Wake up, Father!
Father!
Please wake up.
Anran, calm down!
Father, wake up.
Don't leave me alone.
Please get up, don't scare me.
Mr. He was murdered.
Someone strangled him with a fishing line.
This...
is a button
from Helian Zheng's governor uniform.
Why is it in my father's hand?
Helian Zheng.
Miss... Miss.
I... I saw it.
I had just delivered breakfast to Master.
Then I saw someone
climbing into the backyard,
and heading straight to Master's study.
At first, I wanted to call for help.
But then I realized
it was Mr. Helian.
Impossible.
It can't be.
Where is the governor?
The governor went out this morning,
and hasn't returned since.
Even Lieutenant Li doesn't know.
The governor went out this morning.
But then I realized
it was Mr. Helian.
Anran.
Zheng,
what's going on?
Tang,
find me a doctor.
I got shot in the arm.
Zheng.
♪Like a drowning whale♪
♪Falling into you♪
♪Into every inch of your body♪
♪Then it fell apart♪
♪Without a trace♪
♪Like a warm winter♪
♪Running barefoot to you♪
♪Spreading in your cold palm♪
♪Vanishing in your warm breath♪
♪Because nobody knows♪
♪Can't ever go back♪
♪You touch my heart, my heart♪
♪Why is it so calm?♪
♪Cause everybody knows♪
♪Can't ever go back♪
♪I have long lost myself♪
♪And lost you too♪