Cardiology outpatient clinic,
number 14, You Xiaoli,
please proceed to Room 2.
Hello, Dr. Ye.
Hello.
You Xiaoli, right?
What's your current condition?
A 1.5-centimeter ventricular septal defect.
Currently with pulmonary hypertension
and bidirectional shunting.
When was the pulmonary hypertension discovered?
When I had an echocardiogram as a child
and they found this condition,
my pulmonary artery pressure was already quite high.
My family didn't take it too seriously.
Let me listen first.
Okay.
Later, when I was twenty-seven or twenty-eight
and became pregnant,
my pulmonary artery pressure
rose even further.
Over the years, whenever I exert myself,
the chest tightness and shortness of breath
have become more and more obvious.
I've been taking medication all along.
You've been using targeted pulmonary vasodilators?
Yes.
This new drug has worked pretty well.
My previous doctor said
I might
have a chance at surgery now.
Strictly speaking, in your current condition,
there is no indication for surgery.
I heard
Dongli Hospital's Heart Center
is excellent,
and has performed many operations
other hospitals couldn't do.
That's why I came specifically to see you.
Please wait a moment.
Hello?
Hello, Director.
I have
a patient with pulmonary hypertension.
Her case is unusual.
A 1.5-centimeter VSD,
with bidirectional shunting.
She strongly wants surgery.
Could you come take a look?
Right now?
Okay. I'm coming.
Ask Director Lin too.
Have him come over if he's free.
Okay, no problem.
Thank you, Director.
Hello?
Hello, Director Lin.
We admitted a patient with a large VSD,
pulmonary hypertension, and bidirectional shunting.
Director Zhou asked
if you could come take a look.
Okay. I'm on my way.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay.
Dr. Xiaoran,
didn't you already report
to Critical Care?
Why are you here?
Beds 5 and 10
were a little unstable last night.
I came back to check on them.
They're stable now.
Don't worry.
Director Lin came by
to examine them early this morning.
He just left.
Right, Xiao Du. Come here.
This patient has diabetes,
so the wound
will heal more slowly.
Check and palpate the lower limb often.
Director Lin told me too.
He also said
that during this period,
if anything comes up
on our side,
we should tell him immediately.
He'll handle it.
Xiaoran,
although none of us
wants to see you go,
still,
go do your best without worrying.
You've only taken this medicine for three months,
just three months,
and both the tricuspid regurgitation
and pulmonary regurgitation
have already improved.
Director,
can I have surgery?
My previous doctor said
both Cardiology and Cardiac Surgery
had ways to treat my VSD.
How old are you this year?
Seventeen.
I'll be an adult next year.
It's okay, Director Lin.
For my mother's condition,
I've always accompanied her to appointments.
I know her condition very well.
You can tell me anything.
All right.
I
don't recommend surgery.
Since
the targeted medication is working,
you can continue conservative treatment.
My previous doctor told me
surgery was possible.
They could close my VSD
or patch it.
Your pulmonary artery pressure is very high.
Considering your blood gas results
and the clinical finding
of cyanotic lips,
the surgical risk is very high
and the potential benefit is very small.
So I don't recommend surgery.
I came all the way to your hospital
because I wanted surgery.
Have you had cardiac catheterization?
Not yet.
How about this?
We'll admit you first
and arrange some tests.
We'll make a decision after a thorough evaluation.
Okay?
Okay.
Write the admission order.
Mom, see? What did I tell you?
Don't underestimate young doctors.
Young doctors
can still summon the real experts, right?
And she summoned two at once.
Coordinate with the cath lab.
You Xiaoli's cardiac catheterization—
expedite it if possible.
Okay.
Director,
in You Xiaoli's current condition,
does that mean neither medication
nor surgery
can fully solve
her problem?
Yes.
And her condition
will only keep worsening.
She's only forty-five,
but her VSD
could have been treated
in a timely manner years ago.
How did it end up
progressing this far?
Everyone
has their own difficulties.
Maybe when she was young,
her family couldn't afford treatment,
or they lacked
the necessary medical awareness.
That's how it was delayed until now.
What a shame.
Ask
Director Duan from Thoracic Surgery
to join the consultation too.
Okay.
But the results show your pulmonary vascular resistance
is at the borderline
and you're not suitable for surgery.
Whether it's VSD closure
or surgical repair,
we don't recommend either.
If you have surgery,
your condition could very likely
become worse than it is now.
I agree with Director Zhou.
I understand.
But since the targeted medication is working now,
shouldn't I seize
this rare window for surgery?
Judging from
the current degree of pulmonary vascular remodeling,
the benefit of surgery
is uncertain.
And you'd be facing
enormous risk,
trauma, and expense.
But
if I don't at least try,
I won't be able to accept it.
Let's say this is your heart.
There's a defect here.
Normally,
we would patch the hole,
and then the pulmonary artery pressure
would come down.
But your case is special.
If we simply
close this defect,
the blood flowing
from the left ventricle to the right
would stop,
but the pathway allowing blood
from the right ventricle to the left
would also be closed.
The blood in the right ventricle
would then have nowhere to go but the pulmonary artery.
If your pulmonary hypertension is irreversible,
that could cause acute right heart failure,
with very serious consequences.
I understand how you feel.
But every medical decision
requires us to weigh
the benefits against the cost.
If there is clear benefit at little cost,
then of course we should proceed.
But in your case,
the evidence of benefit is insufficient
and the cost is extremely high.
So why force it?
Continue the medication for now.
Xiao Lin.
Director.
Just finished surgery?
I heard
there's a patient with pulmonary hypertension
who strongly wants surgery,
but you refused
to repair her VSD.
Cardiology performed
cardiac catheterization
and found her pulmonary vascular resistance
is already at the borderline.
If we repair it now,
there isn't enough evidence of benefit.
What a shame. She's only in her forties.
Exactly.
So for now, we'll have her continue
the targeted medication.
Director Zhou,
you all want me to keep taking medication.
In my current condition,
can I last another year?
I honestly can't guarantee that.
I understand.
I had a fellow patient before.
She had been doing fine,
then suddenly deteriorated off a cliff.
She was gone within months.
Director Zhou,
could you help me?
As long as I can live one more year,
even just one year.
So the reason you're insisting
on surgery
is to gain one more year?
Why?
It's a promise I made to my daughter.
You don't have to
be so pessimistic.
Take your medicine on time,
keep the disease under control,
and maintain a positive mindset.
Another year
isn't impossible.
Thank you, Director Zhou.
Where is your daughter?
She went to deliver some books.
I hope you'll like them.
Your mother is a writer?
My mom writes children's books.
I know this book.
I saw it in a bookstore a few days ago.
It was on the bestseller list.
Really?
For my precious daughter, Linlang.
This is a gift
from your mother.
Yes.
When I was little,
my mom told me
bedtime stories every night.
The Little Mermaid,
Snow White,
Black Cat Detective, Calabash Brothers...
I got tired of all of them.
So she'd make up stories on the spot.
The stories she made up
were my favorites.
So she simply wrote all of them
down.
That's so loving.
Yes. It's wonderful.
Then... I'll get going.
Thank you, and thank your mother.
We'll read them carefully.
Thank you.
Those two are really close.
You Xiaoli is so seriously ill,
and these past few days,
it's only been that young girl
looking after her.
It doesn't seem like
there are any other family members.
What does she have?
Pulmonary hypertension.
And it's already severe.
Imagine
if something happens to her mother...
what will that girl do?
Xiaoli.
My Xiaoli!
Mom.
Xiaoli.
Why are you here?
The moment I heard you needed major surgery,
my vertigo
flared up from the fright.
I haven't slept
a wink all night.
I can't even eat.
And it rained two days ago,
so my old arthritic leg hurts badly again.
I was counting on my daughter to care for me.
What a miserable life!
My life is so bitter!
Grandma.
Linlang.
Family member,
please keep your voice down.
There are other patients here.
Mom.
Grandma's life is so hard.
Let go of Linlang.
Let her go.
Linlang,
go to the convenience store downstairs
and buy some wet wipes for hands and mouth.
And get Grandma
some heat patches for her knees.
Okay.
Go on.
My life is so miserable.
Miss Nurse,
I'm going downstairs to buy something.
My grandma is inside right now.
If anything happens
to my mother,
call me anytime.
I won't go far.
Okay. Don't worry.
Thank you.
You saw that just now, right?
You Xiaoli is so sick,
but from the moment her mother walked in,
she didn't say a single caring
or comforting word.
Every tear was about her own suffering.
Isn't that just making the patient feel worse?
You made money writing books,
didn't you?
Why did you sell your home?
I'm seriously ill.
I need lifelong medication,
and I'm planning to have surgery.
My savings aren't enough.
How much did you sell it for?
It must've been several million.
No matter what,
there's still Linlang,
your father and me,
and your sister and brother-in-law.
If anything really
happens to you,
leave the money with me.
Linlang
can be raised by your sister.
It's just one more pair of chopsticks.
Raising a child
isn't just adding another pair of chopsticks.
Besides,
what gives you the right to decide for my sister?
She's our own family's child.
We wouldn't mistreat her.
You wouldn't treat her well either.
What do you mean by that?
Your father and I raised you for twenty-three years,
all the way through college.
Did we ever let you go hungry
or freeze?
How was that mistreating you?
My illness—
if you'd taken it even a little seriously back then,
it never would've progressed
to this point.
We didn't understand.
We thought
you were just being a spoiled little girl.
I wanted to study the humanities,
but you forced me into science.
You made me major in accounting
because you wanted me
to work at your supermarket after graduation.
My sister had excellent grades.
She could've studied engineering
at a top university.
But you secretly changed her application
to preschool education.
What's wrong with preschool education?
She'd know how to raise children.
What in-laws wouldn't like that?
Exactly.
You're always right.
I don't want to argue with you.
You came a long way.
You must be tired.
Go home early.
I have nothing else to say to you.
I'll wait for Linlang to come back.
I'll explain things directly to her.
You don't need to wait.
Everything was my decision.
You are not allowed to bother her.
I'm her grandmother.
Do I not even have
the right to talk to the child?
You're far too overbearing.
Now you remember
you're her grandmother?
Since the day she was born,
have you ever held her once,
or changed a single diaper?
Have you bought her one piece of clothing,
or even one piece of candy?
In your hearts,
you've only ever cared about yourselves.
Now you're settling accounts with me?
You made so much money from your books,
and yet your father and I
hardly enjoyed any benefit from you.
I'm sorry.
I've disappointed you.
My abilities are limited.
I can only look after myself and Linlang.
We can look after Linlang.
We've already planned it all.
She does reasonably well in school.
She can study nursing in college
and become a nurse.
Look at your health now.
You...
and your father and I are getting older.
Mom.
If we have
a nurse in the family in the future,
wouldn't that be useful?
What's wrong?
Are you having trouble breathing?
Do you feel unwell?
What's happening?
How did she suddenly get like this?
Doctor!
Doctor, hurry!
Family, step back.
The patient is unstable.
Watch what you say around her.
I didn't do anything to her.
You Xiaoli had a pulmonary hypertensive crisis today.
She stabilized for now after resuscitation.
But her condition
is still very poor.
What's her oxygen saturation now?
Around 90.
Keep her on strict bed rest
for the next two days.
Avoid any activity.
Keep her emotions as stable as possible.
I'm sorry, Director.
I originally thought
that if she stayed in the ward,
she could see
her daughter every day
and might feel better.
But I didn't expect
her mother...
I understand.
This isn't your fault.
Let's observe her a little longer.
If necessary, transfer her to the ICU.
That would also shield her
from unnecessary disturbances.
Okay.
Director Wei.
All right. I'm coming now.
And the baby?
He has received standard treatment,
and we've observed him
for two weeks.
But the diameter
of his ductus arteriosus
hasn't decreased,
and there is no sign of closure.
Also,
he still requires mechanical ventilation
for respiratory support.
His blood pressure
still depends on medication.
At present,
his kidney function
is mildly impaired.
His creatinine is somewhat elevated,
and his abdomen has started to distend.
That suggests his intestinal function
isn't very good either.
Then
how should we treat him next?
The most important thing now
is to find a way
to close the ductus arteriosus.
There are two options.
One is surgical ligation.
But the baby is too small.
Open-chest surgery would be very traumatic.
He may not tolerate it.
The other option
is a minimally invasive catheter intervention.
Through a blood vessel in the leg,
we would advance an occluder
and close the opening.
But the baby currently weighs
just over 800 grams.
His vessels are extremely, extremely small.
So the intervention
would be very difficult.
There are very few successful cases
worldwide.
If the opening is closed,
will he be like
other children in the future?
If closure succeeds,
the cardiac prognosis
should be fairly good.
But after all,
he is an extremely premature infant.
He may still face
other challenges in the future.
These days in the incubator
have already cost tens of thousands.
And now another procedure...
Director Zhou,
will the operation
cost tens of thousands more?
What about social insurance?
Have you enrolled the baby
in newborn medical insurance?
Don't cry.
Our household registrations are back home.
We can't enroll the baby
in Dongjiang.
We have to return home to do it.
You can register for cross-region coverage,
then settle the bill directly in Dongjiang.
That way you won't have to pay first
and claim reimbursement later.
Also,
did you know many places
offer financial aid and subsidies
for extremely premature infants?
How do we apply?
Leave that to me.
I'll find out
the exact procedure
and help you get it done as soon as possible.
Thank you, Sister Ouyang.
Don't cry.
If you really want to thank me,
take good care of yourself first.
Have you named the baby?
You'll need a name for the insurance application.
While I was pregnant,
we considered a few,
but never decided.
Thinking about it now,
nothing matters more
than health.
How about Gong Youkang?
"You" as in blessing,
and "Kang" as in health.
And his nickname can be Doudou.
That's a good name.
Wait for my update.
I'm going to ask about it now.
Take good care of her.
Thank you.
Thank you. Don't cry.
Thank you. Thank you.
Continue straight for one kilometer, then turn right.
Most of the time,
we follow up at the Children's Hospital.
Today we specifically booked
an expert at Dongda University Children's Hospital.
It's good to hear from different doctors.
Yes. Cross-checking
can't hurt.
Uncle Zhou,
why did I get sick?
Why did I just sneeze?
See?
Uncle Zhou caught a cold too, right?
Senlin,
everyone gets sick.
Being sick is normal.
You're no different
from anyone else.
Also,
what does Uncle Zhou do?
He's a doctor.
He treats illnesses.
Exactly.
So you don't need to be afraid when you're sick.
Mom will protect you,
and doctors will help you too.
My mom said that too.
She also said
Uncle Zhou is an excellent doctor
who's really good at treating people.
That's right.
And he's very handsome.
Your mom has good taste.
Why do Uncle Zhou's clothes
smell so nice?
Lane guidance activated.
Do they?
It's the same scent
as Mom's.
Why are you so talkative today?
Take a little rest.
I put too much on.
This one works well.
Hello.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Senlin.
This is the supreme pizza you ordered.
Isn't this
your favorite restaurant?
Eat a little more today, okay?
Thank you.
Mu Hongxia told me
you were helping her arrange
newborn medical insurance.
I've already asked about it.
It isn't that complicated.
It should be processed soon.
They can settle the bill directly across regions.
That's great.
That'll ease
a lot of their financial pressure.
It's all thanks to you.
It's just making a few calls
and running a few errands.
I'm happy
if I can help them.
They've decided to proceed with surgery,
so I also wanted to ask
whether you have a product
suitable for their baby.
Actually, we do.
But it's only indicated
for a ductus arteriosus
3.5 millimeters or smaller.
What if it's larger than 3.5?
It isn't absolutely impossible.
I've also seen
a few isolated reports.
But it would involve
off-label use.
I had been considering
asking my mother to help.
She'll soon be back from Chengdu.
Only she has enough experience
and skill to complete this procedure.
But if the product
isn't indicated,
I'll be frank:
As for this matter,
if it succeeds, of course that would be great.
But if it fails,
using a device off-label
could invite criticism.
Professor Fang
would be falling into
the same trap twice.
Exactly.
After what happened with Xuemei,
I don't know whether Dongli
would be willing to work with her again.
Yes.
We terminated our collaboration with Professor Fang.
If we restart it now,
less than a year later,
would it
raise objections
from other colleagues?
Of course,
I'm not saying this
from the hospital's standpoint.
about this.
An intervention this difficult
would be
a major challenge even for Dr. Fang.
Yes.
But during this period,
Professor Fang has performed similar
high-difficulty interventions elsewhere
and accumulated more successful cases.
And as you know,
if a hemodynamically significant
patent ductus arteriosus
is left untreated,
the baby may die very soon.
President Wang,
you're a veteran.
You've weathered many storms.
You know very well
that if either a hospital or a doctor,
once bitten,
shies away forever,
patients will never
see any hope.
Here.
Professor Fang already knows
about little Doudou.
Really?
Someone posted about it on the congenital heart forum.
There's no skim milk.
That's okay.
Right.
He's been in the incubator
for four weeks already.
Medical treatment hasn't worked.
This procedure is indeed very difficult.
You're the only one who can do it.
I'm willing.
What do the parents want?
I knew
if I asked,
you'd agree.
The parents' wishes are very clear.
Can you send me
the patient's records?
He really is
a suitable candidate
for transcatheter PDA closure.
He's been alive four weeks
and has gained only twenty grams.
Without intervention,
there's truly no hope.
Let's assess him as soon as possible.
Have you spoken with hospital leadership?
We've discussed it with them.
Mom,
for this procedure,
I want to operate with you
as your assistant.
That would be beneath your ability.
How could I miss
such a valuable learning opportunity?
How about this?
This time,
I'll assist Professor Fang.
That way, internally and externally,
we can say I led the procedure.
If anything happens,
I'll take responsibility.
And the device?
No problem.
You two...
what's going on?
You noticed that quickly?
How could you hide it?
When did this start?
Not long ago.
We planned to tell you
in person when you came back.
I'm back now.
So tell me.
But given your positions,
will the hospital and company be okay with it?
We'll deal with that.
Don't worry.
We'll be very clear
about separating our personal lives
from our work.
I'm not worried.
I actually find it rather amusing.
The hopeless bachelor
in our family
wandered around for over a decade
and still ended up with you.
Hopeless?
How hopeless?
Come on, let's celebrate.
I truly didn't expect
the great Professor Fang to step in again.
That kind of courage...
I genuinely admire it.
Professor Fang's procedure
will still use
a product supplied through our company.
This product
may be rather niche.
I wonder whether you have
the courage to take it on.
Don't try to provoke me.
We're open for business.
We never turn customers away.
Whatever product she wants,
we'll find a way to supply it.
Good.
I'll send you
the detailed information later.
Also,
I want to help little Doudou apply
for financial assistance from a foundation.
His family really is struggling.
No problem. But
there's a condition.
I knew it.
What condition?
Wang Zhifeng called me
a couple of days ago.
Ouyang,
I don't interfere
in your private life.
And if you're close to a department director,
that's something I'd welcome.
But since President Wang asked,
we can't afford to offend the leadership.
Let's move you to another region.
What region
can you even move me to?
Fushan Hospital.
They've opened a branch
in Dongjiang's suburbs.
They invested heavily.
It's far away,
but it's backed
by a major tertiary hospital.
The market potential
is enormous.
And you can also work
the Kuncheng Hospital account.
You can make some rounds there.
So I'm the one who expands new territory?
I go out hunting,
bring the meat back for everyone,
and in the end,
I'm left gnawing the bones.
Look at you.
That mouth never gives anyone a break.
I won't shortchange you.
We can renegotiate
the weighting of your performance bonus.
I'll raise it substantially.
Whatever other support you want,
just ask.
Just don't leave me caught
between you and the client.
I only hope
you can understand my difficulties.
This is wonderful.
With you involved,
little Doudou has real hope.
I also looked into it.
For a 3.5-millimeter
PDA in an extremely low-birth-weight premature infant,
transcatheter closure
there are very few
international guidelines available.
For this intervention,
there really is no suitable occluder.
But a fourth-generation vascular plug
can be used instead.
I've already done three cases.
None was
as extreme as little Doudou's,
But if we
complete a few more cases,
we can provide more
evidence-based support,
and also put forward
Chinese experts' views and recommendations.
Yes.
We absolutely can't let foreigners
have the final say on everything.
You'll scrub in too, right?
Of course.
I've already applied
to attend with the manufacturer's technician.
Thank you for your help.
I heard
that last time the mother had an emergency
with fetal hypoxia,
and you handled it urgently too.
Yes.
Hongxia was terrified that day.
As a mother,
I understand how she felt.
Professor Fang,
you know I have a child, right?
Is he doing okay?
At present, it hasn't affected
his normal life.
He's already in elementary school.
Regular follow-up is enough.
Thank you.
It was nothing.
Ever since I learned
that little Senlin was ill,
all I wanted was to earn money,
spend more time with him,
and raise him well.
I hoped he could grow up safely.
Later, when I met Xiaofeng again,
at first, I didn't have
any other thoughts.
Later...
I never expected things to turn out this way.
It must be fate.
That's good.
Yes.
But don't worry.
As for little Senlin,
I've already made plans for him.
He will never become a burden to Xiaofeng.
There's no question of burden.
Xiaofeng has always known his own mind.
If he chose to be with you,
he must have thought it through.
As for me,
you have even less reason to worry.
I understand everything.
Thank you.
Thank you for understanding.
When the procedure is scheduled,
I'll let you know.
The product is readily available, right?
Yes.
I've already prepared it.
The baby's overall condition
has remained relatively stable,
and there are no other
cardiac malformations.
The femoral artery and vein
are both normal.
So I think
the puncture
has a high chance of success.
Based on the overall assessment,
I believe
transcatheter PDA closure
is worth attempting.
Looking at it this way,
the baby is still fairly fortunate.
I hope he gets through this.
But for an
extremely low-birth-weight premature infant like this,
even the trip
from the NICU to the cath lab
is dangerous.
If hypothermia occurs,
a whole series of complications
could follow.
Leave that to us.
Neonatology
and Anesthesiology
will ensure safe transport.
As for the operating table,
we'll use a warming blanket
and preheat it to above 37 degrees Celsius.
For the surgical team,
I can assemble
top specialists from every department
across the hospital.
But no matter what,
we must ensure
the procedure is safe and successful.
If you need
anything else,
just let me know.
Thank you, President Wang.
A true master is still a master.
It hasn't been that long,
The C-arm
doesn't faze her at all.
So bold, Professor Fang.
I never thought in my lifetime
I'd see Professor Fang
and Director Zhou operating together.
My God, a baby this small...
His heart
must be about the size
of a little quail egg.
The femoral vein may be
only about two millimeters.
Operating under these conditions
is truly pushing the limits.
It's like placing a raw quail egg
inside a straw cup,
then using only a guidewire
to pass through a winding straw
thinner than a toothpick,
pierce the shell,
and deliver a plug inside
to close a hole in the yolk membrane,
without damaging the egg
or the straw.
And remember,
the heart is still beating the whole time.
C-arm, left lateral view.
Let's take a measurement.
Just as we predicted.
Use a six-millimeter vascular plug.
The occluder is in position.
Director Liao,
check with ultrasound.
No residual shunt.
No obstruction of flow
in the left pulmonary artery or descending aorta.
There's a tiny amount of flow
through the vascular plug.
That's not a problem.
The key is stability.
We need to perform a push-pull test.
No displacement.
Xiaofeng, look.
The vascular plug
is slightly deformed
inside the ductus arteriosus.
What does that mean?
Slight deformation of the vascular plug
means it's seated
with just the right amount of compression.
The size is appropriate too.
That makes migration unlikely.
We can release it.
Director Liao, check again.
No displacement.
The residual leak is decreasing too.
We did it.
The weather is really nice today.
We pulled off something huge.
I feel completely refreshed.
Do you still have to go back to the company?
Or do you want to come to my office
for a cup of coffee?
No coffee.
Are you free tonight?
Let's have dinner.
There's something I need to tell you.
What is it? Why the mystery?
I'm being transferred.
Where?
Fushan Hospital.
They opened a new branch in the suburbs.
It's fairly large.
And I was also given
the entire Kunshan region.
Those areas are so remote.
Qin Xiong has gone too far.
He didn't force me.
I agreed to it.
Why would you do that?
Didn't we already agree?
I said I would handle it.
You didn't need to move.
This isn't only
because of you.
President Qin
helped secure funding
for little Doudou.
He kept his promise.
So I'm keeping mine.
I switch regions.
Everyone gets what they want.
But this is unfair to you.
Do you remember
what I told you
when I was in college?
I said that in middle school,
I had already decided
I would get into medical school.
Integrated bachelor's, master's, and doctoral training,
internship,
residency, specialty training,
and then clinical practice...
It was exhausting.
But I never shed a single tear.
Last year,
on the day I was about to leave
clinical medicine,
I cried alone
the entire night.
The excitement I felt
when I received my medical school admission letter
was immense.
And when I took off my white coat,
the pain was just as great.
More than a decade of dreams and hard work
abandoned in a single day.
That feeling...
you must understand it.
So
I don't want you
to feel the same regret I did.