You haven't stopped moving all night.
Your WeChat step count
must be over twenty thousand.
I'm honestly scared.
The old gentleman
really can't afford
any more setbacks now.
We'll all keep a close eye on him.
Don't worry.
When I first started working,
during my very first week,
I made a terrible mistake.
The catheter from a PICC line
broke off
inside the patient's body,
and I didn't notice it right away.
The fragment drifted through the vessels,
which was extremely dangerous.
What happened after that?
Later,
the patient had to undergo major surgery
and suffered a great deal
before the catheter could be removed.
Fortunately,
the patient's prognosis was good.
The patient and family
also forgave us.
I still remember
what she said to me then.
She said,
"You've just started working.
Newcomers are bound to make mistakes.
But
the earlier you make one,
the earlier you must learn from it,
so you don't make
an even bigger,
irreversible mistake later."
Head Nurse.
I'll never forget
the lesson from this time.
In clinical work,
many of our hardest lessons
come from patients.
Every profession has a beginner stage.
But ours is too special.
Even the smallest
mistake on our part
can be enormous
for a patient.
Remember the lesson.
Turn guilt into action.
Show more care
in your daily work,
and work twice as hard.
Ms. Jiang.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Peng suffered because of me.
I'm truly sorry.
This was my mistake.
I really was
too hasty at the time.
My technique wasn't good enough.
I won't make excuses.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Jiang.
Xiao Du is still in specialty training.
He made an operational error,
and as his supervising physician,
I bear primary responsibility.
So I want to formally apologize
to you again.
I'm truly sorry.
Our department
has deducted one month's
performance bonus from Xiao Du.
I will also strengthen
his training.
More importantly,
we'll monitor Mr. Peng more closely
and make sure this never happens again.
Poor Mr. Peng.
He was already so seriously ill,
and now
he's suffered even more.
Tell us,
is there anything else you need?
We'll do our best to accommodate you.
I really want to blame you.
But
the informed consent form said
these complications can occur.
And you already
warned me
that prolonged intubation without tracheostomy
could lead to complications.
Mr. Peng suffered this time
partly because of my choice too.
I won't pursue it.
I don't have any other demands.
But
Dr. Fang,
I still want to ask:
if we don't do a tracheostomy,
will Mr. Peng get better?
All I can say is,
if we simply maintain the status quo
and do nothing,
Mr. Peng will face
even more
difficult challenges.
So
regarding the tracheostomy,
I'd still like you
to think it over carefully.
We've paused the sedatives
to let him wake for a while.
Try communicating with him.
He can nod or shake his head,
or write
on a board to answer you.
Mr. Peng.
I'm here.
It's me.
Mr. Peng.
Listen to me.
Don't panic.
The doctors are all
trying to help you.
To help you breathe better,
they need to
open your trachea.
D-Don't get agitated.
Listen to me. I remember.
I remember our agreement.
But I still want to ask you:
why don't we
listen to the doctors, okay?
Mr. Peng Mao,
based on your current condition,
we have to perform a tracheostomy.
Of course, we also respect
your own wishes.
If you agree,
put a check mark here.
If you don't,
put an X.
Mr. Peng.
Listen to me.
Only by opening the airway
do you have a chance.
What if one day,
you can't even
speak anymore?
Then how would you
express your wishes?
We agreed in advance.
But I heard
the closer someone is to death,
the stronger the instinct to live.
What if, by then,
we change our minds?
Then
let's agree on a signal.
When that time comes,
I'll blink three times.
You'll know what I mean:
don't let me
keep suffering like this.
Even if I can't speak then,
I should still be able to blink.
Then
blink for me now.
No.
Listen to me.
Don't get agitated.
Ms. Jiang.
I'm going to sedate him.
Midazolam, four milliliters per hour.
Don't get agitated.
Please don't get too upset.
I remember. I remember.
It's all right.
It's okay. It's okay.
I knew it.
I haven't forgotten.
I haven't forgotten our agreement.
I just can't bear to let go.
I can't bear it.
Ms. Jiang.
May I speak with you for a moment?
Two weeks
is basically the limit
for endotracheal intubation.
If you're certain
you don't want a tracheostomy for Mr. Peng,
then soon
I plan to switch him to nasotracheal intubation.
But nasotracheal intubation
is painful too.
And his infection
may still worsen.
I understand.
Thank you for all your work.
Remove it.
I understand that Mr. Peng
wants to live with dignity.
But if—
Dr. Fang.
Mr. Peng and I have been together
for thirty full years.
In all those years, it seems
we were never apart for even a day.
We are partners,
and, more than anything,
each other's closest confidants.
We lived together,
and also wandered together
through the ocean of literature.
Over these thirty years,
we've walked hand in hand
through the scenery of many lifetimes.
I understand him completely.
So even though
it's incredibly hard to let go,
I still respect
his decision.
Yes.
It is wonderful.
Actually,
our journey
wasn't easy either.
We went from teacher and student to partners,
and carried a great deal of misunderstanding and criticism.
Because of that, Mr. Peng lost
every chance of administrative promotion.
He remained an ordinary teacher all his life.
His health was poor and he needed care,
so I also gave up many career opportunities.
But what comforts me is
that we were always certain of each other
and never regretted it.
I asked both of you here today
mainly to discuss
Mr. Peng Mao's family.
The Medical Affairs Office has repeatedly
tried to negotiate a settlement,
but the family ultimately
refused mediation.
They insist
on pursuing legal action
and are asking the hospital
to hold both
of your departments responsible.
She's really that determined?
I heard Mr. Peng
developed a pneumothorax from the puncture,
yet she didn't hold the ICU
or Du Wenzheng responsible.
She seems quite reasonable.
Director Zhou,
why don't your side step forward
and apologize to her?
It's best to turn a major issue
into a minor one.
Our diagnostic and treatment process
was evidence-based.
We just need to cooperate with the procedure.
There's no need
to apologize simply for the sake of apologizing.
I respect her decision.
The family also said
that if the hospital believes
the doctors' actions
were appropriate,
then they'll wait for the court's ruling.
I'm telling you,
if I were Ms. Jiang,
I'd ignore everything else
and have the tracheostomy done directly.
What if there were still a miracle?
That's easy for you to say.
Do you think Ms. Jiang
can bear to let him go?
And everyone
has the right to decide
how they leave this world.
No matter how reluctant loved ones are,
they can only respect that choice.
People like Mr. Peng
and Du Yan
are so hard to read.
They leave me completely at a loss.
Du Yan's condition
has stabilized somewhat.
Also considering the financial burden,
we can begin weaning him
from ECMO.
But the underlying disease remains.
This improvement is only temporary.
We saved him this time,
but next time
he may not be so lucky.
We've only returned to square one.
He still needs surgery.
As for a donor heart,
there's been no news.
So the most direct and effective option
is still an artificial heart.
You've always known
Du Yan's position.
I'm worried that after ECMO withdrawal,
he'll remain just as determined.
What are we supposed to do then?
He may not talk much,
but that child is stubborn.
Otherwise,
we wouldn't have sent him there.
Whatever we say,
he never listens.
You keep saying he never listens.
But what about you?
Have you ever listened to him?
Your child
refused the artificial heart.
Couldn't you see
that he was using his life to fight you?
We know we were wrong.
Doctor,
please help us persuade him.
As long as he agrees to surgery,
he can do whatever he wants from now on.
We'll go along with anything.
As long as he lives.
What do we do, Dr. Fang?
His parents are no help at all.
Dahuo.
Why are you here?
I said
I'd come see you in a couple of days.
You two talk.
We'll be next door.
Call if you need anything.
How are you?
I didn't want you to see me
like this.
Fine.
Then I won't come again.
But I'll wait for you
to come find me.
Do you remember this place?
Let's go.
Where?
Run.
Get out of here.
Are you crazy?
What if the instructors catch us?
Forget them.
Come with me.
Go.
Hurry.
Quick.
Go.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for the mark.
Found it.
Jin Miao.
This is the place.
Look.
I made a mark here.
What kind of mess did you draw?
Keep going forward.
After walking for a while,
we'll reach a road.
We can hitch a ride and escape home.
You found the route,
then came back?
Of course.
I had to take you with me.
Metal, wood, water, fire, earth—we agreed.
We can't split up.
Come on. Hurry.
Okay.
How are you?
Jin Miao.
Stop! Don't run!
I can't go on.
I'll stop them.
You go first.
Jin Miao.
Come find me after you get out.
You told me before
that the academy had been demolished
and you wanted to see what it looks like now.
I've been there.
It's now
a field of rapeseed flowers.
Lots of people go there to take photos.
But they don't know
there's still a forest behind the hill.
Two people once
wandered into that forest
by accident.
Even knowing it was dangerous,
they were still willing to break through together.
Dahuo.
Let's play a game.
I put your birthday present
in that forest.
When you get better,
go find it yourself.
What age are we in?
You're still playing
children's treasure hunts?
You scared?
Kid.
Jin Miao asked me to give you this.
He's my only friend.
I had planned
to say goodbye to him and then...
I know.
I know how suffocating
your life used to be.
And I know how badly you wanted
to escape your parents' control,
even if it meant
using your life to resist them.
I'm tired, Dr. Fang.
Now I don't even
have the strength to fight anymore.
My life has become airtight.
This is the only path left.
To return everything they gave me,
including
my life.
Who said
this is your only path?
You're already eighteen.
You're an adult who can choose
your own treatment plan.
You can live
in the way you want,
and choose the road you want to take.
If you don't like
the pigeon soup your mother brings,
then don't drink it.
If you don't want to forgive them,
you don't have to force yourself.
You can go find Jin Miao
and continue
your story of metal, wood, water, fire, and earth.
You still have a very long road ahead.
Don't give up on yourself so easily.
I believe you can
find your own direction.
He agreed.
Director Lin.
You'll perform the surgery.
There should be
a consultation tomorrow about the plan.
I'll let you know then.
Director Zhou.
Dr. Fang is amazing.
Du Yan is such a stubborn kid,
yet she still found a way
to change his mind.
I also heard her say
Director Lin will be the lead surgeon.
Now Du Yan's surgery
has real hope.
Lin Yi's surgery
should be ending soon.
Let's wait for him.
You brought an extra model?
Yes.
The other one is an overseas product.
It only entered the domestic market this year.
Mr. Qin asked me to bring it
for Director Zhou and Director Lin
to consider as well.
I'll urge him.
Director Zhou.
Director Sheng.
Manager Ouyang.
Let's begin.
I'll be the lead surgeon
for Du Yan's artificial-heart operation.
Any objections?
Manager Ouyang.
Go ahead.
We've prepared two products.
The first is domestic.
What's the situation?
It's larger,
but provides relatively stronger output.
It's more suitable for critically ill patients
who need greater circulatory support.
The other
is a Spanish product.
It has been on the overseas market
for several years
and only entered China this year.
Its advantage
is its smaller size.
I remember Du Yan
is relatively thin.
Wouldn't this
smaller and lighter model
suit him better?
Let's use this one.
Director Sheng.
Du Yan
looks thin,
but he's tall,
so his body weight is still considerable.
Once he recovers,
the amount of support
he'll need will also be substantial.
And he has only just
been weaned from ECMO.
His condition is critical.
The higher-flow domestic pump
can support him better
through this immediate danger.
Besides,
he's still young.
He has a chance to wait
for a heart transplant,
though donor hearts are hard to come by.
Precisely because he's young,
he'll probably need the artificial heart
for longer
than an elderly patient.
Then why not choose
the more portable model
that would better support
his future life?
Director Zhou,
aren't you considering his future?
If he can't survive
the immediate crisis,
what future is there to discuss?
This new imported device
doesn't provide enough flow
for a critically ill patient
and lacks sufficient
domestic clinical data.
I'm the lead surgeon.
I know which device to use.
Director Zhou,
are you planning to pick up
a cardiac surgeon's scalpel?
If that's your attitude, Director Sheng,
is there any point
in holding this consultation?
To be blunt,
Cardiac Surgery's operations
never required
Cardiology's involvement in the first place.
All right. I understand.
Xiao Du said Sheng Nian
temporarily assigned Lin Yi
an emergency operation.
He couldn't get through to him.
Director Sheng is going to do this surgery.
You definitely didn't know that.
No.
Then did Qin Xiong know?
I'm not sure.
But when I left today,
I had only prepared the domestic brand.
Just before I left,
he suddenly stopped me
and told me to bring
the Spanish product too.
As far as I know,
that manufacturer
has been looking for a chance
to complete a procedure in China.
At present,
they have no domestic use cases.
None.
If it's used this time,
it will be the first case in China.
And if I remember correctly,
wouldn't it also be Dongli Hospital's
first artificial-heart operation?
Put together,
that can't be a coincidence.
In Du Yan's current condition,
the more important thing
is getting him through
the immediate crisis.
The domestic artificial heart
clearly matches the data better.
Director Sheng couldn't possibly
be unaware of that.
Right.
Some medical decisions
aren't made
solely for the patient's sake.
Dongli's first.
China's first.
Put those two together
and the publicity alone is enough.
What is it?
Why did you call me here so urgently?
Why didn't you tell me
you couldn't attend Du Yan's consultation?
I was operating.
You still could have
sent me a message.
You left us
completely unprepared for Director Sheng.
I didn't know he'd go either.
Lin Yi.
As for Du Yan's surgery,
I still want you to perform it.
Why?
Director Sheng chose
an overseas product.
But my brother and I both believe
the domestic one
better suits Du Yan's current condition.
He has only just
been weaned from ECMO.
Director Sheng is the lead surgeon.
He has his own reasons
for choosing that product.
But the one he chose
has only just entered China
and has never been used here.
We both think he put hype
and publicity
ahead of the patient.
His motives aren't pure.
What do you want me to do?
As long as you agree to operate,
I can go with you
to talk to Director Sheng.
Say what?
"Director Sheng,
we suspect your motives aren't pure,
so don't do this surgery.
Let Lin Yi do it"?
Then how should we say it?
We can discuss it further.
You know
how much effort it took
to restore Du Yan's will to live.
I truly hope he receives
the safest and most reliable treatment.
Like Xiaorui,
he's a child who's had a very hard life.
How is he like Xiaorui?
How exactly is he like Xiaorui?
They share a birthday.
They're about the same age.
Are you insisting I operate
to make up for the regret
of not saving Xiaorui?
That's not what I mean.
He's not the same as Xiaorui.
He's lying right there.
Xiaorui is already dead.
This surgery has nothing to do with me.
And I don't need this kind of redemption.
Thank you, Director Sheng.
Here's to the success
of this operation.
A pleasure working together.
It's a great honor
that you will be the one
to launch our product's first case in China.
We truly feel privileged.
When the time comes, we'll also
build publicity for our product,
for Dongli Cardiac Surgery,
and for you, Director Sheng.
I remember you're also
a strong candidate
for chair of the Heart Failure Committee
of the next Dongjiang Medical Association.
With this operation
strengthening your record,
your victory should be assured.
These empty titles may matter
to you,
but for Director Sheng,
the surgery
and the patient always come first.
Of course. Of course.
We certainly hope
for what's best for the patient, Director Sheng,
and for all of us.
Exactly. Exactly.
Come.
A toast to Director Sheng.
Come, let's toast Director Sheng.
To Director Sheng.
Director.
Mr. Qin.
Lin Yi.
I still want to talk to you.
Another day.
I have surgeries all day tomorrow.
Zhang Zhen.
Director.
You look well.
How is it?
Are you settling into the new company?
Pretty well.
It really took some time
to adjust.
I ordered you coffee.
Insurance claims review
is basically doing a doctor's work
from a different perspective.
My clinical experience
and academic background
are useful too.
That's good.
Thank you, Director.
And please thank Manager Ouyang for me.
I'll cherish the opportunity
and work hard.
Do your best.
The company has just started.
Keep it up.
If you run into any other difficulties,
you have to tell me.
No more being polite with me.
It's okay.
I've recovered now.
Enough about me.
I actually asked you here today
because there's something else
I wanted to tell you.
What is it?
I only heard this
through other people.
I don't know whether it's true. Just hear me out.
A group of us
went to Europe together, right?
The senior directors
didn't accept cash gifts directly.
But I heard
accounts were opened overseas
for some directors.
Future product kickbacks
would be transferred directly
into those offshore accounts.
The accounts
aren't under the directors' names,
but the funds inside
can be remotely controlled by them.
Remotely controlled?
For overseas spending,
children's tuition, property purchases,
international medical care,
insurance, and so on.
And if they need
to move the money back,
they can probably find a pretext.
Which directors?
Either
directors with purchasing authority,
or people like
Director Lin,
who exclusively handle difficult, critical,
high-end procedures.
They decide which products get used.
I don't really have evidence.
And I don't want people thinking
I'm making random accusations now.
I've already suffered
such a major fall.
I...
I'm genuinely worried about Director Lin.
Maybe
you should verify it with him.
I'm here to see Xiaoran.
She isn't back yet.
I'm here to see you.
What do you want to say?
Make it quick.
I still need to go out.
The offshore account—
it has nothing to do with you, right?
Who told you?
Zhang Zhen.
Just tell me openly.
Say you don't have one, and I'll believe you.
I do.
Director Lin.
This
is a small token of our appreciation.
We mainly wanted you to—
I can't accept this.
No, don't misunderstand.
Business is business.
Use our product
when it's appropriate.
If it isn't,
we would never pressure you.
Don't worry.
We've considered everything for you.
This is a bank account
our company opened for you.
The password is inside.
It's not under your name.
Please take it.
Xiao Cheng, right?
Yes.
I appreciate the gesture.
All right.
We'll talk later.
Here's your bill.
I'll pay by card.
Zhang Zhen really is something.
He fell into the water himself
and still insists on dragging someone down.
Are you drinking or not?
What about the envelope?
Did you return it?
No.
The envelope.
It's in the bag.
Here.
Good thing you didn't open it.
There's still time.
Return it immediately.
Why should I?
What are you thinking?
Do you understand
what an offshore account means?
Do you know how serious this is?
How serious can it be?
A warning?
Dismissal?
At worst, I'll become another Zhang Zhen.
I'll return it for you.
Put it down.
I'll answer for my own actions.
You don't have to clean up after me every time.
Or are you planning to report me?
If you want to ruin yourself,
that's your business.
But what you're doing
will implicate Xiaoran.
What happens between Fang Xiaoran and me
is none of your business.
How is it none of my business?
I know perfectly well
what I've done.
What are you talking about?
What account?
Lin Yi.
Did you take money you shouldn't have?
Return it immediately.
I won't.
That money is for you.
If something happens
in the future,
at least you'll have something left.
I don't need your money.
You're crossing a red line. Do you know that?
Are you insane?
Fine.
I'm wrong again.
Everything I do is wrong,
isn't it?
I wanted to do the right thing too.
I devoted myself to saving patients.
And what happened?
That donor heart
went to Lu Dadong.
Xiaorui collapsed at home.
I put him in the ambulance.
In the general ICU,
I watched him die
right in front of me, unable to do anything.
So that was the right choice?
That is how it ended for me.
We know
you need time to process it
and adjust.
But you can't remain
trapped in it forever.
Xiaorui's death
hurt us just as much.
It's not the same.
You have a brother. You have a sister.
You don't understand me.
You don't know
how dark my world is.
the kind of life
I face every day.
You don't understand me at all.
Right.
It really isn't the same.
We've always treated you as family.
And I want to become your family.
What about you?
My entire family is dead.
Lin Yi.
Do you really believe that?