We need to put him on ECMO.
Director.
Severe heart failure, recurrent ventricular fibrillation.
We have to start
ECMO now.
You're his legal guardian.
Do you consent?
Sign here.
Lin Yi.
Sign? Where?
For ECMO.
Come with me.
How did it suddenly get this bad?
I don't know.
I... I got home,
and he was already like this.
This afternoon,
he looked fine on the monitor.
He took his medicine
every day too.
Lin Yi.
Listen to me.
Xiaorui's condition is very serious.
Even with ECMO,
we don't know how long it can sustain him.
Use a donor heart.
We've been on the waiting list for a long time.
We can use a donor heart.
There isn't enough time.
His right heart function is very poor.
An LVAD won't work either.
No. You have to save him.
You have to save him.
Please save him.
I'm begging you.
Please.
You have to save him.
He...
He can't end like this.
He can't.
I'm begging you.
Think of something.
Please save him.
The only possible option now
is biventricular assist support.
But Dongjiang can't do it.
Okay.
Biventricular support. Fine.
Implant the device.
I have money.
How much? How much does it cost?
I... I've saved a lot.
Any amount is fine.
We'll do biventricular support.
Please help me.
Help me.
Please.
I'll try.
Director Zhou.
Biventricular artificial heart support
has not yet been formally
approved for routine clinical use.
But several major hospitals
in China
are authorized for clinical trials.
I've contacted a few.
A hospital in Shanghai
is willing to accept him.
I don't know
how Xiaorui is doing now.
Can he be transported?
He's on
ECMO for now.
If he stabilizes,
we can find a way to transfer him.
I'm coming over now.
It's too far.
An ambulance won't work.
We need a helicopter.
Does Dongli Hospital
have any agreement
with general aviation services?
The emergency medical center
may be able to coordinate it.
Okay.
I'll contact them.
I'll also ask
private rescue organizations.
Let's split up.
All right.
The blood gas results are back.
The lactate is even higher.
It's over 25.
His blood pressure is falling too.
A hospital in Shanghai
will accept Xiaorui for biventricular support.
We're contacting a helicopter.
Prepare for transfer.
We found one.
Director Xiaofeng
arranged biventricular support.
We're going to Shanghai now.
The helicopter is already...
Can... can it still fly?
Yes.
Transfer him.
Um...
Dr. Qiao.
Take the ECMO team
and equipment with you on the flight.
Beibei.
You come help too.
I'm transferring him.
Everyone, help.
Director Lin.
Is there still any point
in flying now?
Of course there is.
He can't die.
Can we please not give up?
I'm begging you.
Please.
Help me.
Then we'll fly.
I'll go with you.
Director Zhou.
But...
Brother.
He hasn't given up.
We can't leave him with regret.
President.
President Wang.
Director Lin
still wants the transfer,
to Shanghai.
Give me the penlight.
Both pupils are fully dilated.
No light reflex.
He is likely brain-dead.
The transfer stretcher is here.
The stretcher is here.
Xiao Lin.
The patient
is already brain-dead.
If we go through all this
to transfer him now,
there's no point.
As his family,
I understand
how you feel.
But as a doctor,
you need to be rational.
Don't touch me.
I'm not a doctor right now.
And you're not my superior.
I'm family.
I'm his family.
I demand a transfer.
I demand
that the hospital transfer him immediately.
Will you cooperate or not?
Forget it. I'll do it myself.
Lin Yi.
If you won't help, I will.
This is also the choice you should make.
A matching donor is rare.
It should be reserved for your own family,
so your loved one can live.
That is also your responsibility.
This is the choice you should make.
Let him go.
Director Lin.
Director Lin! Director Lin!
Xiao Lin.
Lin Yi.
Xiaorui.
Yi.
Brother.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't keep my promise.
You've already done so well.
You've worked hard.
Do you remember
the book we read together?
When someone leaves the earth,
a new star appears in the sky.
Why do all of you
have to become stars?
Why do you have to go to the sky?
Why leave me behind?
Why did you have to leave?
To shine a little light
shed a little light
I want to say goodbye to him.
He said a butterfly
could create a whirlwind of love
with every flap of its wings.
But today,
he tied my shoelaces
with a surgical knot.
It looked awful.
If he can't even tie a bow,
how am I supposed to flap my butterfly wings?
Fine. Next time I'll tie you a bow.
I'll get your clothes.
Why did you dig out
this shirt?
Did Yi wash it?
The colors all ran.
I thought you'd never wear it again.
I'll let him off this time.
Because I think it looks good.
And everyone's colors
are all on it.
That makes it meaningful.
Fine.
It's one of a kind.
No one else will have the same shirt.
I've already decided.
On Dad's birthday,
I'll wear this
and take the spiriranthes to see him.
Okay.
And I'll complain to him
that Yi is still unreliable
and has gained weight again.
Remember to take a nap.
I know, you nag.
Bye-bye.
You still can't say goodbye properly.
Are you home?
Did you get everything?
Lin Yi.
As the first cold wave
of 2024 sweeps through,
powerful cold air
is pushing the warm, humid air southward.
It's only November,
yet Dongjiang has welcomed
its earliest first snow in ten years.
According to the Dongjiang Meteorological Center,
today's high
will be around one degree Celsius.
Winds will be strong,
with northwesterly winds at Force 5
and gusts at Force 6 to 7,
and even stronger along the coast.
The snow is so heavy.
Let's go.
It's snowing. Look.
You really didn't need
to come all this way.
I thought it would be better
to come in person.
How...
how are you?
Are you okay?
If there's anything
I can help with,
please tell me.
Director Zhou is here.
Sorry I wasn't there to welcome you.
You two talk.
Director Zhou.
Have some fruit first.
Here, have some water.
No need to be so polite, Mr. Qin.
I mainly came today
to thank you in person
for helping arrange
the helicopter.
Director Zhou,
please don't mention it.
I didn't manage to help in the end.
It still makes me feel
pretty awful.
He was so young.
Such a shame.
How much did you spend in total?
I'll transfer it to you.
I didn't spend anything.
The flight never happened.
But arranging the aircraft
and the personnel
must have cost something.
Honestly,
it really wasn't much.
I asked a friend for help.
It was a personal favor.
He didn't charge me.
If I took your money,
what kind of person would that make me?
No, but...
Director Zhou,
there has never been
any financial transaction between us,
right?
If you suddenly
transferred me money,
I'd have a lot of explaining to do
if anyone investigated later.
That's true.
Then I'll settle it directly with them.
Director Zhou,
really,
I deeply admire
the kind of person you are.
Even if we weren't
in a client-vendor relationship,
I'd still hope
to have a friend like you.
You did it for your brother.
I did it for my friend.
It's the same principle.
Having the chance
to do even one small thing for you
is an honor for me.
So let's not
stand on ceremony.
Come on.
Have some fruit.
Director Lin, that's enough.
It looks all right.
Has he had
an echocardiogram and 24-hour Holter monitoring?
Yes.
There were no major problems.
But genetic testing shows
he carries a pathogenic mutation.
And the probability
of developing the disease is unclear.
Actually,
you don't need to worry too much.
For now,
we can rule out dilated cardiomyopathy.
His current insomnia,
chest pain, and palpitations
are probably
mainly psychological.
But this can't
go on indefinitely.
You're right to take it seriously.
This kind of grief-related stress
is harmful even
to an average person.
Let alone someone
in Director Lin's condition.
We really can't be careless.
He needs regular follow-ups.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
He fell asleep
in such a noisy place.
Maybe
he should see a psychologist.
Director Lin.
Should I schedule the next follow-up
for six months
Six months.
Six months, just to be safe.
Okay.
Thank you, Director Wang.
You don't need to be too nervous.
Let's get him admitted first.
Thank you.
Come with me.
I'll help you with the admission.
Are you okay?
You didn't sleep again last night, did you?
I couldn't.
Why don't you take annual leave
and get some proper rest?
If I stay home,
I won't know what to do.
Maybe
we should finish this week's appointments
and suspend the joint clinic for a while.
Zhang Zhen and Liu Dong
have opened their own clinics anyway.
The slots for the European summit
have all been finalized.
They're already
starting the visa applications.
Dr. Zhang told me
he never expected to get a slot.
He's thrilled.
He usually has it hard.
He works tirelessly and conscientiously.
This is a good chance
for him to recharge and relax.
That's good.
And this summit
is highly valuable.
It's a great opportunity
for him to learn and gain experience.
It'll help him.
With a director
as considerate as you,
he'd probably work himself to the bone
without complaint.
Cardiac Surgery
is definitely sending Director Sheng himself, right?
Yes.
See? Both are department directors,
but at critical moments,
you can tell who's better.
How is
Director Lin?
Not very well.
Maybe he doesn't want us to worry.
He refuses to tell us anything.
He keeps everything bottled up.
Honestly, it might be better
if he cried or made a scene,
and let it out.
If he keeps it all inside,
even if he looks calm,
his heart
may already be shattered.
He'll make himself sick.
I urged him to take some time off,
but he wouldn't listen.
How about
I apply for
a summit slot for him?
It could give him a change of scenery.
That's a good idea.
It is.
Right now, only
professional matters
can get him energized.
But I'm not sure
he'd be willing to go.
I'll talk to him first.
If that doesn't work, I'll ask Director Sheng.
He'll listen to Director Sheng.
As long as he's willing,
I'll do whatever it takes
to secure that slot.
You get back to work.
I'll ask about the slot.
By the way,
is Senlin due
for his checkup this month?
If it's convenient,
I'd like to arrange
an MRI for him
and review it personally.
That's very thoughtful.
Thank you.
No need to be so polite.
I'm leaving.
As you know,
the European summit slots
are extremely competitive this year.
I truly had to pull
every string I could
to get one more.
After all,
Director Lin is in a special situation.
For such an important summit,
Cardiology
is only sending Zhang Zhen.
Had I known,
we might as well have given this slot
to Lin Yi directly.
Had we known...
No one could have predicted
this would happen.
All right.
It may be good for him to get away.
I'll talk to him.
Thank you, Director Sheng.
Manager Ouyang, you really think of everything.
What I'm thinking is,
if we can help Director Lin
move forward sooner,
that also helps ease
your burden, doesn't it?
Not only mine, I imagine.
I'll get you another hoodie.
These regular medicines
will go in
this little white pouch.
Be careful.
Don't catch a chill.
And your toiletries—
I've packed them separately
so they're easy to take.
Xiaoran.
I want to sell the old house.
Okay.
Think about whether
there's anything there
you want to keep.
Tell me.
I'll go sort through it
and bring it over.
No need.
When I come back,
I don't want to live here either.
Let's move.
Okay.
We'll look for a new place.
This time,
we'll find a home
you like.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
Not one I like.
One we like.
This
was given to us by Xiaorui.
I told him his craftsmanship was bad.
Lin Yi.
Let's get married.
I want a wedding by the sea.
We don't have to wait until spring.
The sea is beautiful in winter too.
Let me be your family.
Xiaorui and I designed countless
ways to propose.
I just never thought it would happen like this.
I do.
Give me some time to recover.
I'm leaving.
Ouyang.
Mr. Qin.
There are five revisions.
I've compiled them
into an editable document
and sent it to your WeChat
and email.
Okay, okay.
Mr. Qin.
Did everything go smoothly there today?
Today?
The meeting
is over.
I just
talked with Sheng Nian for a while.
He's still somewhat unhappy
that you helped Zhou Xiaofeng
with the fourth-generation vascular plug.
But fortunately, I calmed him down.
Don't worry.
I know.
I'll keep things balanced.
Ouyang.
I get the feeling
Sheng Nian is determined
to move into transcatheter valve procedures.
He mentioned it at the forum today too.
It looks like
a war between Cardiology and Cardiac Surgery at Dongli
is about to break out.
Isn't that exactly
what you wanted to see?
When the snipe and clam fight,
the fisherman profits.
All right, all right.
The fisherman is going to dinner with them now.
I'm hanging up.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
I truly learned a lot
from your talk at the forum today.
It was extremely enlightening.
Mr. Qin, thank you for your hard work.
It's what I should do.
I must toast you with this glass.
Take it easy. I'll finish mine.
Thank you, Director.
If it doesn't work well,
we'll never force it.
Take your time using it.
Here.
Director Lin.
Let me pour you some wine.
I don't drink.
Just one glass.
I can't.
Mr. Qin.
I'll drink with you.
All right, all right. No pressuring anyone.
Drink as you like.
Sorry.
No, no, no.
What is it? Still jet-lagged?
A little.
Then drink less.
One glass is fine. It'll help you sleep.
Director, I barely drink.
Everyone knows alcohol isn't good.
But it can make people happy.
In clinical practice, I've met
people with congenital conditions
who had no idea what they had
and lived without restrictions,
yet still reached their seventies or eighties.
As long as there's moderation,
don't make life too hard on yourself.
That's true.
No amount of caution can keep every storm away.
A little drink won't hurt.