=To Fly With You=
=Episode 9=
Coach Zhuang,
the nurse asked us to pay the bill.
How is it going?
We asked a few more experts,
and they have the same opinions.
What do you mean?
I'm afraid his hand...
But Coach Zhuang,
I don't think
he should know about it at the moment.
I'm afraid he can't accept it.
You mean
he can't play Pairs Skating anymore?
He is young after all.
If he can recuperate well,
he may probably recover, right?
Well, did he mention
which ward?
No. 39.
Did he mention how bad it was?
- I have no idea.
- Xiao Qing,
why are you here
alone?
Where is Shao Beisheng?
He is in the ward.
How is he?
Where did he get hurt?
Is it bad?
He got his hand injured.
Probably
he can't play the game anymore.
How is it possible?
He just got injured.
Why can't he play the game?
Where is he?
Take us to him right now.
Wait.
About the fact that
he can't play anymore,
does he know about it?
No, he doesn't.
Don't tell him for now
when we're up there.
Let's go.
OK.
Hurry up!
(Outpatient)
Let me help you.
What are you doing here?
It's fine. I've opened it.
Are you okay?
Quite free you are.
Still have the time to check on me.
You stood us up today.
We agreed to check
whether you were pretending or not.
Look at me now.
Am I like pretending?
He looks good now, doesn't he?
Yes.
Why?
I'm not that sick.
Are you disappointed?
We are not that bored.
Then why are you empty handed?
We haven't got the time.
What would you like to eat?
I'll buy it now.
I want some tangerine.
Let me.
It's fine.
Let Shen Zhengyi do it.
I'll do it.
Peel the tangerine, right?
Hang on a second.
It's a little bit...
Hurry.
I can peel faster than you
even with only one hand.
Right away.
Almost done.
Take a seat.
It's okay.
Why are you looking like this?
I'm fine. Really.
Almost done. Almost done.
Here you are. The tangerine.
How can I eat it like this?
Then what?
Are you expecting me to feed you?
I get it.
Well, the boyfriend got injured.
He needs his girlfriend to feed him,
so he acts coquettishly.
It is very reasonable.
Well, we will
leave you two alone.
We gotta go now.
Who is acting coquettishly?
I mean...
This is a whole one.
I can't swallow it.
Break it. Break it.
Come on.
Peel it.
Don't stop.
Come on.
Don't bother. I'm good.
Come on. Open your mouth.
I'm good. I'm good.
It'll be good for you
to have some tangerine.
I know. I know.
Come on. Come on.
Did I do it well?
Enough. One is enough.
No, no, no.
You can have more.
Have more.
Okay. Enough.
I know.
Whatever you want to eat,
we'll buy it for you.
Take it. Come on.
Thank you, nurse.
It's late now.
How about you go back?
There are classes tomorrow.
Fine.
Take care of yourself then.
Stay put.
Then stay and supervise me.
I have no class tomorrow.
Let me stay and take care of you.
Don't bother.
I'm not so hurt
that I need special care.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Hold on.
I've changed my mind.
You stay with me.
Me?
But I... I...
I think it makes a lot of sense.
At this time
Zhengyi is needed to stay
and take care of him.
Right, Zhengyi?
But tomorrow we...
Yes. Tomorrow,
we only have project homework
to hand in.
And you have finished it already.
So it doesn't matter.
Just stay
and take care of Shao Beisheng, OK?
Okay.
Then we made the deal.
Why did you say yes for me?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you wanna stay
and take care of me,
the injured one?
So poor of him.
Fine. Fine.
How about this?
Xiao Qing, please stay
and take care of him together with me.
OK.
Just go.
Hurry up. Go!
Well, we're leaving now.
Have a good rest.
Okay.
Bye.
Well, I'm leaving too.
Would you like some water?
No, not for now.
Do you want some water?
No, I...
Let me get you some hot water.
I'm fine.
Xiao Qing, I've got it here.
Thank you.
Brother, you are here.
Coach Xiao.
Let me take it for you.
Thanks.
Let me give you some hot water.
Coach Xiao.
How are you doing? Does it hurt badly?
For a man,
it's nothing.
Thank you.
Thanks to you today.
I have no idea
what would've happened to Xiao Qing
to fall like this.
No worry.
She is my partner.
It's what I should do.
Anyway, thanks to you today.
If in the future
you need anything,
just say it.
Don't bother.
It's nothing.
I'll recover in two months.
Never mind.
Well, then.
Brother,
why did you pull me away?
Shao Beisheng's girlfriend is there.
If you stay there and take care of
Shao Beisheng,
it's not appropriate.
Why not?
He got injured because of me.
It is my responsibility
to take care of him.
Xiao Qing,
things constantly change
on the skating rink.
It's not your subjective wish
that got him injured.
You don't have to blame yourself.
Do you know Coach Jiang Hua?
Are you referring to
that winning coach Jiang Hua?
She thinks highly of you.
I showed her your videos,
and contest materials.
If you've got something in your mind,
I can help you make the contact.
What do you mean?
I didn't say I will change teams.
Xiao Qing,
Shao Beisheng
can't play Pairs Skating anymore.
But he
doesn't know about it yet.
He'll know it sooner or later.
Yes!
For him,
it's probably a little bit cruel.
But you have to
face the problem sooner or later.
The only thing you can do
is to separate.
Coach Jiang
is your best choice.
What about Shao Beisheng?
He can't do it anymore.
There might be a miracle.
It's hard to say.
There might not
be any miracle.
Are you going to wait all along?
He got injured because of me.
I can't leave him alone.
Please press here.
Okay.
I...
Like this?
Yes.
Thank you, nurse.
Why are your hands so cold?
It may be a little cold.
How about this?
Hold on there. Hold it.
Your chin.
Okay. Wait a minute.
Here.
Feel better?
If on that day
I gave the last coin to you,
it won't be like this now.
What are you thinking?
My injury
has nothing to do with that thing.
Besides,
even though I can't play in
the College Student Ice League,
and I can't play in Ling Yun Cup,
when my hand gets recovered,
I'll still win the prizes
as much as I want.
Don't worry.
Shao Beisheng,
no matter what happens in the future,
I'll be there for you
and get you back.
What do you mean?
Just... Just encourage each other.
Well...
Are you hungry?
What would you like to eat?
I'll buy it now.
It's fine. I'm not hungry.
And there is
bone soup someone made for me.
You have bone soup?
Why didn't you drink it?
You should have a lot of them,
the nutritious food.
Here. Let me.
Drink it.
Hurry.
Is it good?
Here.
One more.
Your left hand can work.
And you asked me to feed you?
You made the offer.
I can't say no.
Take it yourself.
If you don't feed me,
I won't drink it.
I'm not hungry, anyway.
Don't be such a baby.
Hurry. Take it yourself.
You have to take it now.
It's nutritious. Hurry.
Fine.
I will hold the bowl for you.
Drink it by yourself. Okay?
Hold on.
What are you doing?
My back.
- What's wrong with your back?
- It's a little itchy.
But I can't reach there.
What should I do?
Let me help you.
Help me.
Not here.
I can reach it myself.
A little bit right.
Right. Right.
Up. Up. Up.
You missed it. Down a little bit.
OK now?
Wait a minute.
It suddenly comes
to the left.
(Wind Chaser Ice Sports Team
of Lingbei University)
Isn't there
any possibility to recover?
We asked a few more experts.
They all agreed that
it was irreversible.
Beisheng is
an ace player of our Wind Chaser.
Such a pity!
What's your plan next?
I mean
since the kid can't play anymore,
we, as the adults,
should plan for him
as early as possible.
Talk to him.
Ask him to retire at this time.
He can have more choices.
He can't retire, Director.
He can't.
I can understand you.
Beisheng is indeed a good player.
You've worked very hard.
I've seen it all.
However,
it is for his own good.
Think about it.
Since on this way,
the kid can't make it.
Why would we
hold him up?
Director, I think
it's too early to talk about this.
No, it's not.
The sooner we talk about it,
the better it will be for him.
He is still young.
There are more choices
and opportunities for him.
Director, I don't think
it's necessary to talk about it.
Unless he talks first,
I can't make him retire.
What's wrong with Ma?
Ma,
it's been more than a week.
How is Beisheng?
You asked me every day.
If one's bones and muscles are hurt,
it takes one hundred days to recover.
It's impossible for him to recover
in such a short time.
It takes so long.
Shall we go to
visit him?
Don't bother.
If so many people go to him,
he'll bear more pressure.
How about
the College Student Ice League?
Can Beisheng still take part in that?
Probably.
When he is absent,
train them well.
Don't relax.
Okay. Don't worry.
Then I'll go training.
Come here.
Can you stop
asking me questions?
I'm done.
(Doctor's Office)
Come in, please.
I will break through the dark clouds,
cross the raging waves,
and face the wind, the rain,
and the lightning.
Lele,
I think it would be better
to add some actions here.
Why not give it a try?
How?
Let me show you.
I will break through the dark clouds,
cross the raging waves,
and face the wind, the rain,
and the lightning.
Have a try.
Let me give it a try.
Okay.
I will break through the dark clouds,
cross the raging waves,
and face the wind, the rain,
and the lightning.
Where does the music come from?
My ringtone.
Why don't you answer it?
I can't move.
You're stepping on my foot.
I can't get away.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Hello.
That was close indeed.
Well,
are you going to
practice Triple today?
I feel great today.
Take a look.
Beisheng is back!
Beisheng.
You haven't seen me for days.
Do you miss me?
We do miss you.
We miss you so much.
It's been a while.
How's your hand?
Right. Are you OK?
My hand is OK.
It's nothing.
When you're not around,
we have no confidence.
What are you doing here?
How can you discharge yourself
in such a short time?
The doctor discharged me. So I'm here.
Go training. Go.
We gotta go now.
Okay.
See you later.
Why don't you behave yourself?
Why can't you just stay in the hospital
for a few more days?
I'm not badly hurt.
I can eat, sleep, and jump well.
If I lie in the hospital,
it's a waste of
precious medical resource?
Right?
When you were discharged,
did the doctor say anything?
No.
The doctor just asked me to sleep early,
sleep well, and stay away from water.
Nothing else.
Right.
Take good care.
Fine. I gotta go.
For what?
Back to the dormitory.
Stay put.
Don't... Don't toss around.
If you get injured again,
you'll get yourself into a big trouble.
Fine. So rambling.
How dare you!
Take care!
♪So I can see you are afraid♪
♪The body is broken apart yesterday♪
♪But I can show you one new face♪
♪If you let me touch your heart again♪
‍♪Baby, I will let you go♪
‍♪The way that you want to♪
♪But I want to hold you close♪
Shao Beisheng. Shao Beisheng.
Shao Beisheng.
♪I'm carrying all the pains♪
♪For one more time, one more time♪
♪Before it's too late♪
Shao Beisheng, what are you doing?
Why didn't you reply my messages?
Why?
What?
I heard from them that you are back.
So I'm here to check on you.
What's the point?
Well...
Have you eaten yet?
Why are you so nervous?
I'm not... not nervous.
I'm concerned that
your hand hasn't fully recovered.
What if
you get yourself injured again?
What's next when I get recovered?
If I get recovered,
can I lift dumbbells?
can I do the lifting?
Stop pretending for me.
I've been skating
for more than ten years.
Since I could walk,
I've been on the ice.
Beisheng.
Here.
Come to mommy.
What a good play!
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Wonderful! Let mommy play with you.
OK?
OK.
Mommy, don't let go of my hand.
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
Mommy
will always be with my Beisheng.
OK?
OK.
When I was little,
I admired my mother the most.
Like your mother,
she was a short track
speed skater.
But my mother was a coach.
So your mother was a
short track speed skating coach.
When I was little,
she led
her team to train all day
on the ice.
She looked so cocky.
But she was too busy
to take care of me.
So every day in order to
stay with her for a while longer,
and spend more time with her,
I said I wanted to play skating.
Why didn't you
play the short track speed skating?
I intended to.
I thought I can train with my mom
when I grow up.
But I didn't expect that
the coach of figure skating said
I was a good player
for figure skating.
And my mom agreed.
Then I went to play figure skating.
That coach was right.
Since I started to play figure skating,
I like this sport more and more
day by day.
When I was fifteen,
I won my first gold medal.
As I won more and more awards,
I felt more and more that,
for me,
like eating and sleeping,
skating has become
a very important part of my life.
What about your mother?
Did you spend more time
with you mother?
No.
Don't talk
the nonsense to me.
I'm telling you.
I don't want to listen to that.
Look at you.
No mom will behave like you.
You left our sick child behind
and took care of your injured player.
No.
This game is really important.
Fine. Important.
If it is important, just go!
Live your life with your games.
Mind your own business.
I'll take care of the child.
Go!
Mom.
Sorry, son.
Don't go.
Mom, stay with me!
She was at work on my birthday.
When I was sick,
she was also at work.
Every time it was my dad
to attend parents' meeting.
Then she divorced my dad,
and went abroad.
For me actually,
having a mom or having no mom,
there is no big difference.
I always believe that
for anything,
as long as you don't give up
in your heart,
some day
it will come true in a certain way.
Yeah.
Just like you.
After more than ten years of practice,
you finally made it
to the professional team.
I'm almost recovered.
I can have my stitches removed tomorrow.
(I always believe that)
(for anything,)
(as long as you don't give up
in your heart,)
(some day)
(it will come true in a certain way.)
Leave me alone.
You...
What are you doing here?
Qu Zhi told me to
come straight to your room.
Finally, you're awake!
Look at this. And this.
These are all
inspirational books for you.
Take a look.
Which one do you prefer?
Three Days to See.
Yes. That's right.
And these movies.
They are all good for you.
Which one do you prefer?
Alright.
Stop it.
It doesn't work for me.
Hang on a second.
I know you're very upset now.
But you can't give up.
So is there anything you can do
to allow me to play Pairs Skating?
No.
Good night.
Get up!
I'll take you somewhere.
For what?
Get up!
Fine.
Let me get dressed, OK?
Hurry up!
Why are you taking me here?
Hurry up.
Don't you think
it feels like skywalking
when
walking on that rainbow bridge?
Hurry.
So?
So let's start.
Start what?
Isn't it obvious? This runway.
You asked me to change into sportswear
so that I could run with you?
Yeah.
Are you afraid of heights?
I...
Do I look like I'm afraid of heights?
Well, it is your hand that got injured.
Your feet didn't.
No.
It's been a while
since I did exercise last time.
I feel pain all over my body.
I can't make it.
Let's sit for a while.
I think it's quite good to
take a sun bath.
Muscle soreness?
Come here. I'll give you a massage.
Here?
It hurts!
OK. OK. Take it easy.
Muscle soreness? Here.
Is it here?
Muscle. Where are the muscles?
Alright, alright.
Running requires music.
I need music.
OK. Let me check out
your taste of music.
Are you okay now?
The theme song of the Wind Chasing Boys?
What? You also like it?
This is my favorite animation.
What a coincidence!
It is my favorite animation too.
I know.
Your phone case is the same as mine.
Cut the crap! Hurry up!
Come on.
OK.
Last request.
Say
the classic lines of the Wind Chaser.
I will not surrender.
I will not give up.
No.
You have to follow the original version.
I will not surrender.
I will not give up.
Quickly.
I will not surrender.
I will not give up.
Enough?
Not loud and clear enough.
Loud and clear?
I'll give you loud and clear.
I'll give you the original version.
I will make you scared.
Shao Beisheng is a big fool.
Freak! Narcissist!
Shen Zhengyi!
♪I ask you♪
♪When♪
♪Can I forget the absurd me♪
♪The meaningless question♪
♪How to live through this life♪
♪I cannot only live in dreams♪
♪No one can answer♪
How is it going?
Why are you all sitting here?
Didn't I ask you
to apply for the venue?
Forget it.
So the school didn't approve it.
It got approved!
President,
rest assured
to let three of us do the job.
Good for you.
President,
you have no idea.
There is also
the popular band in our school
who made the application.
They have sheer numbers.
But we three fought so hard
to get the venue.
You're so good!
They also assured the school leader that
on the day of performance,
it can reach 90% attendance.
And then?
We of course assured that
our attendance
can reach 100%.
Good gracious!
The leader heard us,
and he made the decision at once
to give the venue to our club.
What if we can't make it?
If we can't reach
100% attendance,
our club
will dismiss on the spot.
Well...
Let's go over the script.
So awesome you are!
Good job!
(Return and Love)
Beisheng,
I want to talk to you.
For what?
Let's find a place,
sit down and have a talk.
Don't bother.
Just over there.
Beisheng,
there's something I've been
thinking about for a long time.
I decided to tell you.
The doctor said
your hand
couldn't do the lifting anymore.
You told me this.
Aren't you afraid that I can't bear it?
I'm afraid.
But I'm more afraid of that
you're kept in the dark,
and take a hopeless road.
Beisheng,
don't run away from difficulties.
As long as we face it,
we will figure out how to solve it.
Don't worry.
Mom will be with you.
You finally realized
you should be with me.
I needed it before.
But I don't need it now.
I knew it all along.
I'll take care of it myself.
Don't worry about me.
Brother,
where are you taking me?
You'll find out when you're there.
Where exactly are you taking me?
Tell me.
I'm taking you to meet Coach Jiang.
Stop.
You shall meet her,
and have a talk.
Maybe you'll change your mind.
I won't meet her.
♪Hold me tight♪
♪Before the sky's blue fades away♪
♪There are still sunsets we can see♪
♪It doesn't matter if we are♪
♪Drowned by the river flowing backward♪
♪Or wet in downpours for a starry night♪
♪Remember I'll always be there for you♪
♪If the whole universe is gone
after the big bang♪
♪And we become the wanderers
of the Milky Way♪
♪Stay strong
because I'll always be there for you♪
♪I'll always back you up♪
♪As persistently as ever♪
♪Like when the sunset
stretches our shadows♪
♪and everything behind♪
♪My heart beats only for you♪
♪Looking into your eyes♪
♪And falling in love with you♪
♪Right at the moment♪
♪When time has stopped♪
♪It's a world of you and me only♪
♪I'll always back you up♪
♪As persistently as ever♪
♪Like when the sunset
stretches our shadows♪
♪and everything behind♪
♪My heart beats only for you♪
♪Looking into your eyes♪
♪And falling in love with you♪
♪Right at the moment♪
♪When time has stopped♪
♪It's a world of you and me only♪