Good thing Boying
and Mael were here.
And the cops came too.
We might need
to move out again.
- Where's Arissa, Ma?
- She hasn't come home yet.
Maybe she's still at work.
I'm getting worried
about that kid.
- Where are you?
- I'm still at work.
There was a problem
with the inventory.
I won't be coming home tonight.
Do you think the money
that Mike took
is actually with Samuel?
That's the only
logical explanation.
But if I'm right,
will Samuel help us?
Or will he run off
with the money?
I could tell
he's a good person.
I'm sure he'll choose to do
the right thing in the end.
Mike Trinidad
and his son...
They're the ones
responsible for this.
They killed you.
They killed you, son.
Maybe that's why
the police found me.
Because of Mommy.
She's my guardian angel.
But I wish she were
still here
so I could hug her
whenever I'm scared.
I'm here.
Daddy's here.
My family's already been
hurt too many times.
Even King can't sleep properly
because of trauma.
Bro, how about the money?
I'll still return the money
to the victims.
I just need to make sure
my family's safe
from the hands of Roldan.
We need to get far away.
I need a clean escape.
No screw-ups.
No noise.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Ma.
- Dear.
Ma, I'll get going.
Oh, okay. Take care.
I'll come home early
to help with the packing.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Miss Lolita,
where do I put these?
Just leave it there.
Thank you, Boying.
Uh, dear, this is Boying.
He's the tricycle driver
I asked to drive me around.
Boying, this is my son, Samuel.
Sir.
[LOLITA] He's a victim too.
He also invested
in Yayaman Tayo.
Stop talking!
Give us our money back!
I remember you.
- Boying.
- Sir.
- Alright, Ma. I'll get going.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh, come with me.
Let's talk outside.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Boying, I want to apologize
on my father's behalf.
Oh.
I understand, sir.
Plus, you didn't do
anything wrong.
Thank you for understanding.
And thanks for helping us when
someone broke into our house.
My conscience couldn't take it
if I did nothing.
And I know you're going through
a lot right now.
That's why I'm not
looking for anything in return.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
How much money
did Papa take from you?
10,000 pesos.
I was going to use it
to buy a new tricycle.
I know 10,000 pesos
isn't much,
but I worked long and hard
to save that money.
Here.
Perfect.
10,000 pesos.
Take it.
- Bu--
- Just take it.
[HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- I'm sorry--
- Thank you, sir.
[HOPEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Go look for passengers
so you can earn more.
Uh, I'll give you a ride.
- Hop on.
- No need.
It's fine. Go on.
- Get going. Yeah.
- Are you sure?
[HOPEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
We're still lucky, dear.
Boying is not like your father's
other victims.
Ma, those victims
are not our enemies.
My bosses were the ones
who took advantage
of people like Boying.
They need to pay
for what they did.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Welcome to Mug Co--
Oh.
I thought you
were customers.
You're early.
No.
You two are just late.
Wow, you closed last night
and opened the store.
Amazing.
That's what it's like
when you love your job.
You're excited to work.
Right?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Who are you?
What do you want?
Your father ruined my life.
I had nothing to do--
You always say that
you had nothing to do
with what your father did!
But scammers like you
know how your actions
affect the lives of people
you've hurt!
It's not just about the money
or humiliation.
It's not just about
the future.
You destroyed lives!
You destroyed lives
and relationships!
I'm sorry,
but I promise you
- I'll return your money.
- I don't care about the money!
My son killed himself
because of that money!
[SOBBING]
Can that money
bring back my son?!
You monsters!
Look at me and remember
this face, Samuel Trinidad!
This... This is the face
of all your victims!
[SOBBING]
A father who lost his child...
because of you!
Because of all of you!
- [MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SOBBING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[ANTON]
I don't care about that money!
Because of that money,
my son took his own life!
Money can't bring back
my son's life.
You're evil!
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CABINET THUDS]
[CABINET DOOR OPENS]
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
Wait--
[BOXES THUD]
Thank you. Order for Jonah.
Here, ma'am. Thank you.
What's your order, ma'am?
Iced latte, please.
- Okay. One iced latte.
- [PHONE BUZZING]
[LINE RINGING]
[PHONE BUZZING]
[PHONE RINGING]
What's the matter
with this child?
[BREATHING SHARPLY]
Iced... Iced caramel latte.
- Your name?
- Kim.
Kim.
Here. Iced. Thank you, ma'am!
[PHONE BUZZING]
Black coffee. Iced or hot?
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [BREATHING SHARPLY]
Arissa, why aren't you
answering the phone?
What's the matter
with this child?
Okay, let's start updating
each other.
Len, let's start with you.
- How are you?
- Trying to make ends meet.
It's true what they say.
You have to tighten the belt
if needed.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh, Anton's not here yet.
He usually comes in early.
You're right.
Why isn't he here yet?
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHISPERING] One, two, three,
four, five, six.
- [PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PHONE BUZZING]
[PHONE BUZZING CONTINUES]
[BOX THUDS]
Arissa.
Miss Lolita is calling.
- Aren't you going to answer it?
- Uh, I didn't notice.
I'll call her back later.
Arissa.
Maybe she's worried about you
or there's an emergency.
Don't sweat it.
She knows that if I don't
answer, it means I'm busy.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JACOB] Okay. Just tell me when.
- No problem.
- Let's go.
I have to go. Bye.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Agnes, we're going
to a lunch meeting.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DRAWER THUDS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Get out of there.
They came back.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYPAD CLACKING]
[MESSAGE WHOOSHES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE BUZZES]
Uh, sir, can I talk to you?
It'll be quick.
- Sir, please. It'll be quick.
- Yes.
Uh, I... I have some new ideas,
uh, for our next project.
I'd like to run it by you,
if that's okay.
- I have lunch in 30 minutes.
- S-Sir, wait.
Hold on. This will only take
a few minutes.
Sir, we can do it here.
Son of a-- Can we do this later?
You're showing off again.
- Let's do it later.
- Sir, wait.
Please.
What?
Sir, I... I promised you I'd
increase our profits
to 50 million by the fourth
quarter, remember?
What if I tell you,
I can do uh...
I can raise it to 100 million.
[JACOB SCOFFS]
Yes. 100 million.
Okay, fine.
Prepare the proposal,
then email it to me.
- Okay?
- Yes, sir.
- But, sir--
- He told you to email it.
Didn't you get that?
Okay, sir. You're right.
Uh, I'll just email it to you.
- Okay.
- Yes, sir. Thank you.
- [SCOFFS] What an idiot.
- Thank you.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLING]
Okay, let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
I'll email it to you.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing?
Are you trying to get yourself
in trouble?
I saw an opportunity,
so I took it.
I was hoping I could find
some evidence against them--
What if they catch you?
Agnes, you know
what they're capable of.
They could kill you!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You think I didn't know that
before I accepted this mission?
I know it's dangerous,
but I have to do it!
For every day
that I don't bring them down,
more victims suffer.
More lives are destroyed.
My conscience
can't take that, Samuel.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ANTON] You know
the impact of what you did
to your victims' lives!
It's not just about money,
shame, or the future!
It's lives...
...lives and relationships!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I really didn't think
Anton was capable of doing that.
We are building a case.
So we can trace where
that money actually went.
You have the nerve
to come here?!
How do you sleep at night?!
Do you have the money?
How dare you leave me at night
and flirt with him!
Samuel! Samuel!
That's enough!