[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm the only one in our class
with an incomplete family photo.
I don't have a picture
of Mommy.
Maybe it's time for King
to know the truth about his mom.
Son, my heart can't handle
telling him the truth
that his mom left him.
Samuel,
I saw how much it affected you
when Mike left us.
I don't want my grandson
to go through that.
You still don't want to go home?
Arissa, if you think
you're an outsider,
Miss Lolita wouldn't cook
for you if that were the case.
If she didn't care about you.
It's not enough to
make me go back.
What about King?
That's exactly why I left.
I'm the reason
King got kidnapped.
He's better off without me.
I made a reservation
for you and Sir Jacob.
I just want to ask if
I should cancel it or...
No. I'll be there.
Ah, Sir Jacob!
I've made a reservation at
your and Ma'am Lea's
favorite steakhouse.
Alright. Very good.
Thank you.
I saw how much money
you have.
I want a piece of that.
Now you want a cut
of the money?
I want to join your group.
I'll prove that
I'm better than my father.
I'm done struggling.
I'm ready to do anything.
You don't understand--
Think about it.
Argh!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma.
Ma, I'm fixing our problem.
Is this the plan
you mentioned?
I hope it works.
I need it to work.
Once I've fixed everything,
I'm telling King the truth
about his mom.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
To the most beautiful
woman in the world.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I thought we were just
having dinner?
You didn't say we were
celebrating Valentine's Day.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Do you like it?
I wish did more.
Some fireworks.
A marching band.
But this will do for now.
I noticed that
we're the only people here.
Don't tell me you rented
the entire restaurant.
Oh, honey...
You didn't have to do this.
We spend so much
of our time working
and taking care of the kids.
So I just thought,
I should spoil my wife.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Thank you.
You're everything I prayed for.
Beautiful,
strong,
smart,
kind.
Sometimes I wonder,
what if...
What if I lose you?
Why would you think that?
Because I know how
rare someone like you is.
And I won't let it slip through.
Not now.
Not ever.
Well, good.
Because I'm irreplaceable.
Exactly.
[POIGNANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Dad, I wish she were still here.
So I could hug her.
I'm the only one in our class
with an incomplete family photo.
I don't have a picture
of Mommy.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SAMUEL ON VIDEO] Love.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAMUEL ON VIDEO] Love! Love...
[SAMUEL]
You're so beautiful.
Love...
Look over here.
[SAMUEL] Love, look here!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Lea!
Oh my goodness.
You look so beautiful, my love.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS, CREAKS]
Dad.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Son. [SNIFFS]
Hey, why are you still awake?
- Hmm?
- I woke up
because you weren't by my side.
What are you doing here?
Aren't you going to sleep yet?
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's go back inside.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SMOOCHES]
Let's go for another round.
Are you seeing someone else?
That's why you can only
do one round with me?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I really don't trust
that Samuel.
He's a criminal
just like his father.
He's just good
at hiding his rottenness.
You're talking
about Samuel again?
I won't leave him alone.
I'll get to the bottom of this.
I'll find the people
who kidnapped his son.
Because that's where
I'll find out his involvement
in that syndicate group.
Where are you going?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES SENSUAL]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Roldan.
Is it true? Really?
He wants to join our group?
[CHUCKLES WRYLY]
That bastard is ambitious.
Jacob,
we have to play his game
to get the money.
What?
Are you serious?
We're going to accept him?
We already let him join
our company, remember?
Why would we let him
join our group?
I disagree.
Of course not!
Are you okay?
Jacob,
We'll just let him think
that he's part of the group.
But...
once we get our money...
we're going to kill him.
That's what I want to do.
Kill him!
I'm going to kill him.
Shot, Jacob.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR] Agnes!
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Johnny, you're drunk again.
Stop!
Stop it!
Come on.
[GRUNTS]
Johnny, what are you doing?!
Ow!
You're hurting me!
[GRUNTS, EXHALES DEEPLY]
Agnes...
Agnes!
[GRUNTS]
[JOHNNY EXHALES SHARPLY]
Agnes...
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Help me! Help me!
It's my baby!
My baby's not breathing!
My baby!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PLATE CLATTERS]
[PLATE SHATTERS]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUNSHOT]
[BANGING ON TABLE]
- [SCREAMING]
- [LOUD THUDS]
[GUNSHOT]
[GOON] Give me the seed phrase,
or your son won't see
another sunrise!
[GUNSHOTS]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ANTON] Remember this face,
Samuel Trinidad.
This is the face
of all your victims!
[GUNSHOTS]
[AGNES] If you're not planning
to use the money,
what will you do with it?
[SAMUEL] I'll use it as leverage
to get into their group.
From the inside,
I'll destroy them all.
[GUNSHOTS]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I know...
we're going through
a difficult time right now.
But I hope that...
no matter how heavy
it all feels,
we can still have
each other's backs.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Please don't give up on life.
He's right.
What happened to Anton
and his son
must never happen again.
We're the only ones we've got.
Sorry!
I'm sorry I'm late!
There were so many passengers,
I couldn't pass on the chance.
Just what the hell are
you doing here?!
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
What's the problem?
Are you still upset that I tried
to stop you
from going after
Samuel's family?
You're a traitor!
You were defending
those scammers!
It's funny.
I remember you used to be
so fired up about them.
Why the sudden change of heart?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Two-faced bastard!
Let me guess.
They already bought you.
How much are we talking?
Is that where the new tricycle
came from?
Wow, that's harsh.
Do I look like someone
who can be bought?
Tell me!
We have all the right to be mad
after the stunt
Mike Trinidad pulled.
But his family didn't do us
anything wrong!
They've been dealt one card
after another!
[CHAIR SCRAPING]
And they deserved all of it!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you seriously think
they even feel sorry for us?
For Anton?
What about his son?
[MUSIC BECOMES SOMBER]
They can keep all their flowers
and condolences.
If you've fallen
for their theatrics,
then we're definitely
not the same!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
If you're choosing their side,
I suggest you stay away.
If you're not one of us,
you don't have a place
in this group.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Just go.
You may leave now.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SIGHS]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CITY NOISE IN THE BACKGROUND]
[DOORS SLIDING OPEN]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELEVATOR BELL CHIMES]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[ELEVATOR DOORS SLIDING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BUILDING UP]
"How's the wife?"
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNICKERS]
I'm just making small talk.
Because if you ask me,
we're happily married.
We have a beautiful daughter.
Oh, we're happy.
You?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
My wife is gone.
Really?
You mean, she's dead?
Or she left you?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What made you say that?
So she left you, huh?
Sorry.
I see it's still
a sensitive topic.
Actually, I get it.
It really is hard
being left behind.
Especially when she leaves you
for another man.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
A man you could never be.
[BUTTON CLICKS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You mad?
You're shooting daggers at me.
You want to punch me?
Let's do it.
I won't back down.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
How do you plan to get
into Roldan's inner circle?
I won't be staying here
for long.
What opportunity
are you talking about?
Why are you letting
your husband abuse you?
It's a long story.
I'm willing to listen.
I wonder if my mom has
more pictures.
Grandma, who's this?
It's time for King to know
the truth about his mother.
- Coward.
- I'm not a coward.
She belongs with me, Samuel.
You have no chance against me.
Sins of the Father.