Trinidad!
[KNOCKS]
Who's that?!
We've known each other so long,
you still don't know my voice?
What do you need?
I just want to talk to you.
I'm working.
You don't want to?
I'll really tear this down. One!
Two!
Three!
[PHONE RINGING]
Johnny, where are you?
What is it, Agnes? I'm busy.
There are men following me,
please help me!
I already drove Johnny
away from there.
He's gone.
Thank you.
By the way,
where did you send Trinidad?
I sent him to our model unit.
He's handling the money alone?
Yes.
And once he does it right...
he'll be able to clean
the money,
for acquiring Crownlitéra.
Once we get our hands
on that casino,
our group will become
even more powerful.
I can help too.
Arissa, there's something
I want to know.
About my father?
Because he's a scammer,
is that it?
- Never mind.
- You don't make sense.
You're the one
who doesn't make sense.
You said the two of us
would help each other,
and now you left me behind?
We're both not making sense,
that's why we're fighting.
You need to clean that money.
But it's too much.
That's where it'll be proven...
if you can handle the job
you accepted,
that you can be trusted
with even more important ones.
I know, but if I get
caught by the police...
You have no choice, Samuel.
Find a way as soon as possible.
Hello, bro?
Do you know anyone
trading cryptocurrency?
Of course,
is this part of your mission?
Yes.
That's why I need to act fast.
Are we talking millions here?
Hundreds of millions.
Okay, come here.
I already know who to call.
Alright, bro.
Thanks.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- Mael.
- Hey.
This is the friend
I was telling you about
who's good at crypto trading.
Just call him Captain Brunch.
For security reasons.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
30 million.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
That's all I can manage.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay, fine. That'll do.
Thanks.
- Thank you, Cap.
- Alright.
Samuel, how much more
do you need to clean?
A lot more, bro.
Jeez.
I really need to find a way
to get rid of all this cash.
Wow.
This is the first time
I've seen that much money.
I thought money's a problem
only when it's lacking,
but even too much is a problem.
Thanks.
Take care.
[PHONE RINGING]
- Johnny?
- Agnes.
Make sure I see you at home
when I get back.
Why are you talking like that?
Because you keep going
everywhere,
that's why you're always
in danger!
Who did you meet?
Who's your lover?
[HUFFS]
What nonsense
are you saying again?
Behave yourself!
You're always fooling around.
That's why you lost your child.
[AGNES] I've been holding it in
for so long.
I endured all your accusations.
Even your abuse.
Don't you dare
turn your back on me!
Go ahead!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
Is it your schedule today?
To flirt with my wife?
Overtime with Samuel!
Samuel again?!
- Enough!
- What?
You're defending your boyfriend?
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm so disgusted with you!
You killed our child!
I have limits too.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're in trouble.
I'm sorry.
For how I acted earlier,
I shouldn't have fought
with you.
You were only trying to help me.
I'm sorry too.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Sorry if I'm pushy.
Although...
I just wonder, Arissa, why...
...why you left me.
Why you let me go.
I thought we were supposed
to help each other?
Before I got shot,
weren't we okay?
Then what?
Suddenly things changed.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're Enzo's dad?
Yes, I am.
My father.
I know him.
He's my employee.
I appreciate that
you're trying to help me, Enzo.
But this is too personal for me.
What I'm doing
is too dangerous,
and I don't want you
to get hurt.
Please try to understand.
Well, I can respect that.
But Arissa,
please also understand
that I just want to protect you.
Enzo, I told you,
you don't have to do that.
I don't have to,
but I want to, Arissa.
I don't want you to get hurt,
you're important to me.
Because I like you!
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sorry.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
What nonsense is this,
who are you?
[JOHNNY GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLOW LANDS]
[BLOWS LAND]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [JOHNNY GRUNTS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JOHNNY GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[BLOWS LAND]
[BLOW LANDS]
[GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Less 30 million.
Still a lot left.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Perfect.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES SOFTLY]
[GRUNTS, EXHALES HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Johnny,
what happened to your face?
It's nothing, really. I just...
Fought off those guys
who harassed you.
Oh, really? You caught up with
them? I'll get some medicine.
Of course.
I really caught them
and taught them a lesson.
- Poor you.
- Hmm.
Why's it this bad, though?
There weren't that many, right?
What, were there more?
Like five of them?
Five? What five?
You think five guys
could do this to me?
There were ten of them!
- Huh?
- They ganged up on me!
- Oh, ten.
- Watch it.
Good thing you got away.
Why would I run?
I don't run from things
like that. I face them.
I took them all head-on.
Hit them, punched them...
See these bruises?
Their faces looked
ten times worse.
Fifty, even.
Ah, fifty.
I bet you brought them
straight to jail after.
Sure, I'll visit them tomorrow,
maybe give them a few more!
They're not in jail.
I didn't take them in.
I felt sorry for them,
so I let them go.
- [AGNES] Ah...
- They said sorry, anyway.
Wow, you felt sorry for them.
Just... ow!
Don't press too hard.
It doesn't hurt,
but when you press,
- Feel a bit...
- What?
You keep moving. Come closer so
I can put the medicine on right.
There, is this okay?
Ow, ow, uh...
I'll take a shower first.
Okay.
Poor you. But good job!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BLOW LANDS]
[GRUNTING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES,
THEN FADES]
[MUSIC BECOMES PENSIVE]
Hon, are you still mad?
You understand why I'm
mad now that we're finally okay.
[CHUCKLING]
Okay. If...
that's the case, then I know
how to make you feel better.
No.
I'm tired.
Let's sleep.
[SCOFFS]
Tired?
Really?
Tired from what?
Taking care of Trinidad's son?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you being serious right now?
You're getting
too full of yourself.
Want me to tell your dad you
and Samuel Trinidad have a son?
Just tell me!
Huh? You'd really tell him?
Be my guest.
You think I'm scared?
I've built a life and
a name for myself.
I'm not that little
girl anymore.
So what if Dad finds
out about our son?
One mistake won't erase
all my accomplishments.
[SCOFFS]
Well?
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LINE RINGING]
[JACOB] Xenon,
where's that damn Trinidad?
He went into the
gallery with the money.
Don't worry, I'm tailing him.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, hello!
Welcome to Panagimpan
Collective Art Gallery.
Here, we keep works exclusively
from National Artists,
which are very rare
and very expensive.
Is this everything?
Well, we rotate the
pieces on display.
The rest are in safekeeping.
Sir, what do you need here?
- Everything.
- [CHUCKLES]
The whole collection is worth
about 350 million pesos, sir.
And I guess you
don't have the right--
[UNZIPPING]
That's exactly what I brought.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR ALARM BEEPS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAMUEL]
Is someone following me?
Why?
What are you up to now,
Jacob?
[ENGINE REVS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Stop!
Where are you going?
You're running away?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAMUEL] They can't see
these bags of money.
I cannot screw up this mission.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is that a gun, sir?
"POL. GEN. DIEGO RAMIREZ"
[DIEGO] Just in case
you remember something
or you change your mind,
this is my card.
You can call me anytime.
So...
Do I have to call
General Ramirez?
Do you want to discuss
this with him?
Hmm?
That won't be necessary.
Go on.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Proceed.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Give this to me!
No, please!
This is all I have!
- Help me!
- Let go!
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- [CRASH]
[BODY THUDS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Miss, what are you doing?
- Salted...
Um, where's your boss?
I am the boss.
Oh, well,
if that's the case,
here's my resume,
and consider this
as my job interview.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Give me a chance
to win you over.
You can't get hurt.
You're important to me.
Because I like you.
[SIGHS LOUDLY]
What's wrong with me?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Wow! Flowers!
Who gave these?
- Huh?
- Uncle Enzo?
King, you scared me.
No.
Those are from Luke.
Is that what's bothering you?
Because Uncle Enzo
didn't give you these?
[HUFFS] What?
How could you think that?
You're just a kid, King.
Isn't Uncle Enzo courting you?
Well... Yes.
Then what's the problem?
Don't you like him too?
King, you're just a kid.
You won't understand.
I just don't like
seeing you sad, Aunt Ari.
If you're sad, I'm sad.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Come here.
[ARISSA]
I wish it was that simple, King.
I wish loving someone
was as easy as liking them.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SAMUEL]
This is your fault, Jacob.
Damn you.
Why would you
endanger your operations
just to set me up?
Why do you hate me so much?
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
He used my calling card?
[SCOFFS]
So basically...
Trinidad got away again.
[POLICE OFFICER] Yes, sir.
My men let him through.
They thought
he had authorization.
I see.
Alright. Keep me posted.
I cannot believe you used me.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You really know how
to play your cards right,
Mr. Samuel Trinidad.
Well, you might actually be
worth keeping an eye on.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
This Wednesday...
Luke gave those.
I thought you liked Uncle Enzo?
I wish loving someone
was as easy as liking them.
She's Samuel's sister.
They're moving in full force.
Welcome to the group.
I am sure they are
involved in human trafficking.
Be alert.
This is your fault, Jacob.
Why do you hate me so much?
No secrets, hon.
Why did Jacob
have me followed?
Is he really risking
losing all of your money?