Dear, this is Boying.
He's the tricycle driver
I asked to drive me around.
He's a victim too.
Boying, how much money
did my father take from you?
10,000 pesos.
I was supposed to use it
to buy a new tricycle.
Just take it.
I'm sorry--
Thank you, sir.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Miss Lolita is calling.
Aren't you going to answer it?
Uh, I didn't notice.
I'll call her back later.
Your father ruined my life.
I promise you
I'll return your money.
I don't care about that money!
Because of that money,
my son took his own life!
Remember this face.
This is the face
of all your victims!
Agnes, we're going
to a lunch meeting.
Okay, sir.
Get out of there.
They came back.
Uh, sir, can I talk to you?
It'll be quick.
Prepare the proposal,
then email it to me.
- Okay?
- Okay, sir.
You're right.
Uh, I'll just email it to you.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to get yourself
in trouble?
I know it's dangerous,
but I have to do it.
For every day
that I don't bring them down,
more victims suffer.
My conscience
can't take that, Samuel.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[ANTON] You always say that
you had nothing to do
with what your father did!
But scammers like you
know how your actions
affect the lives of people
you've hurt!
It's not just about
the money or humiliation.
It's not just about the future.
You destroyed lives!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- I'll return your money.
- I don't care about that money!
Because of that money,
my son took his own life!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAMUEL]
We need to get far away.
I need a clean escape.
No screw-ups.
No noise.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ANTON] Remember this face,
Samuel Trinidad.
This is the face
of all your victims!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
[ANTON]
I don't care about that money!
Because of that money,
my son took his own life!
It's not just about
the money or humiliation.
the future.
You destroyed lives!
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[MUSIC FADING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh my god. Do you know him?
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh...
It's just that...
What? What's wrong?
Come on. You can tell me.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
He's one
of your father's victims.
How do you know?
You know him personally?
Hmm...
I just met him.
A friend.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I never imagined
Anton would do that.
That explains how much pain
he was carrying.
Of all of us,
he was the calmest.
I thought he wasn't
as desperate as we were
to get our money back.
Each of you
is going through something.
You have different problems.
That's why
this group was formed.
And despite everything,
let's keep listening
to one another
and, most importantly,
supporting each other.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't lose hope.
I can assure you
that Police General Ramirez
won't stop
until he resolves your case.
I even keep reviewing it myself.
And you can help us
by staying informed.
So if you have any evidence
or any relevant information,
let us know right away.
Your affidavits are important.
We are building a case
not just to put those
involved behind bars
but also to trace
where the money actually went.
And if we can recover
even a small amount,
we'll fight for it.
This won't be easy.
I can't promise we'll recover
every single peso you lost.
But what I can promise...
...is that I will fight for you.
You are not alone.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma, I was just talking
to him earlier.
He was furious.
He kept blaming me
for what happened to his son.
Samuel, dear.
Many people were really affected
by what your dad
and his accomplices did.
We had nothing
to do with it, but...
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
...we've been dragged into it.
We also can't help but...
...blame ourselves
for all the bad things
that happened to them.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ARISSA]
I need to do something.
I need to find
Dad's secretary.
So I can figure out
who else got scammed
by Yayaman Tayo.
I still have something to do
to help them.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Got it.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What happened to him
is really heartbreaking.
Sir Anton, I hope you're
at peace now with your son.
[CAR HUMMING]
[MURMURING]
You've got some nerve
showing up here!
How do you even sleep
at night?!
[WOMAN] Exactly!
So many people died
because of you!
[CLAMORING]
Calm down!
They're here to pay
their respects.
- Respects?
- What kind of respect?!
If you're mad at them,
this isn't the
right place for it.
Let's not fight here.
If they really came
to show respect,
they should return our money!
- That's right!
- Give us our money back!
Return it!
We're not forcing you
to believe we're innocent.
We just wanted to offer
our condolences.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN] Shameless!
They shouldn't even be here!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
Hello, Agnes?
Let's meet.
I'm ready to work with you
to take down
Roldan Rivera!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bro, why didn't you
tell Arissa about our group?
[SIGHS]
She's already dealing
with so much,
especially with her family.
I just don't want
to add to her burden.
I don't want to remind her
of the problem anymore.
Besides...
she's already blaming herself
for the kidnapping
of Samuel's son, King.
I heard about that news.
I feel bad for their family.
Many from our group
are still furious at them.
But from what you've told me,
it sounds like
they really are innocent.
Don't worry, bro.
I'll do what I can to calm them.
I'll talk to them and
clear Mike Trinidad's name.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BUSY LINE TONE]
[STIRRING MUSIC RISES]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC INTENSIFYING]
Do you have the money?
I knew it!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Johnny!
Samuel!
- You bastard!
What are you doing?!
Stop it!
- Johnny! Samuel!
- [SMACKS]
Samuel! Samuel!
Johnny! Stop it, you two!
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- [AGNES] Enough, Samuel!
- Johnny! Stop it!
- [SAMUEL GRUNTS]
Enough! Samuel, stop it!
- [KICK LANDS]
- Stop, please! Stop!
Johnny, stop it!
- [GRUNTING]
- Guys, stop!
- Samuel, please!
- [BLOW LANDS]
Samuel! Samuel!
- Stop it!
- [SAMUEL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[AGNES] Stop it!
Samuel! I said stop it!
Enough! Stop fighting!
[JOHNNY PANTING]
[AGNES]
Just go, Samuel!
- Go-- Ah!
- Defending your lover, huh?!
She's not doing anything wrong.
Don't hurt her.
She's not doing anything wrong!
That's enough, Samuel!
Just leave, please! Leave!
Go!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- What, huh?
- Johnny! Johnny!
Enough!
Why on earth did you do that?!
Now it's my fault?!
And why not?!
You're out here flirting
this late, and it's my fault?!
I told you it's just for work!
Work my ass!
I'll kill that Samuel!
- Stop!
- I'll kill you!
Johnny! I said stop!
- Hey!
- We'll talk at home. Come!
Come with me!
- [AGNES GRUNTS]
- Caught you in the act!
- [JOHNNY GRUNTS]
- [AGNES WHIMPERS]
You're lucky I didn't blow
that guy's brains out!
How could you do
this to me, huh?!
How?!
What, you're not happy with me
anymore so you cheated?!
Between the two of us,
you're the cheater.
- [SCOFFS]
- You are the cheater.
You've got some nerve!
You killed our child!
Did you forget that, huh?!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATH QUIVERS]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
I hope I'm doing
the right thing.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Go home.
We're worried about you.
You don't need
to worry about me.
I should be a scam buster.
Time to toughen up.
Watch every move you make.
I won't hesitate to kill
your whole family.
Until I'm sure you won't touch
my family again,
you're not getting the money.
Sins buried by time...
Love, look over here.
...will be exposed.
Maybe it's time
for King to learn
the truth about his mother.
Hold on tight.
- I want to join your group.
- That's not happening.
Their secrets are about
to be revealed.
I'm ready to do something bad
if it's for my family.