Revo Diaz,
son of renowned businessman
and alleged leader
of a scamming syndicate
Emerson Diaz, was killed
during a shoot-out.
During the investigation,
it was discovered that
the father and son
were involved in the kidnapping
of the son of Samuel Trinidad,
son of the infamous scammer,
the late Mike Trinidad.
So that's why you took him
out of the equation.
You don't want anyone
messing up your plans.
Thank you so much.
That's what friends are for.
I forgot my phone upstairs.
Let me just go and get it.
Arissa, wait.
The house key.
I have my own key, remember?
And you say
you're just friends, huh?
Samuel!
[GUNSHOT]
Enzo! Enzo!
Samuel...
Samuel?!
Oh no, Enzo!
Arissa, just go!
Enzo!
Somebody!
- Samuel...
- Help!
Samuel!
Come back!
- Samuel!
- We need help!
Somebody, please!
Find out how he's doing.
Spend a crazy amount of money,
I don't care.
We can't afford
to lose the money
Trinidad would take
to his grave.
Enzo? Enzo?
Enzo.
Slow down! I'm his father!
- Sir, it's an emergency.
- What happened?!
What happened to my son?!
He was shot, sir.
We need to take him
to the recovery room.
He needs to be monitored.
You're not allowed inside.
I'm sorry.
Please wait for further
instructions from the doctor.
He'll be transferred to another
room once he's stable.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[LOLITA] Lord Almighty...
please allow my son to survive
yet another tragedy
that's befallen him.
Give him the strength
he needs
to return to us.
My grandson still needs
his father.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KING] Lord Jesus...
please save Daddy.
I still want more time with him.
My mommy's already in heaven.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Can my daddy please stay
with us?
Pretty please?
[SEAT BELT UNBUCKLES]
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [CAR DOOR OPENS]
- Yes, honey?
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[JACOB]
Are we still on for later?
We can reschedule
if you're busy.
- Don't worry.
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
I'll make sure the meeting
wraps up fast.
We made a promise
to Chloe, remember?
Okay, I'll see you later.
Okay.
I'll see you then.
Bye.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Alright.
Let's make this quick.
I'm a very busy woman.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[MUSIC FADING]
Sir.
- Dr. Gonzalez?
- Yes?
You're the director
of this hospital, right?
Yes.
I'm Jacob Rivera
of Oriental Ridge Estates.
- Okay.
- Uh...
Samuel Trinidad, one of
our employees, was rushed here.
He's in the third
operating room.
Now, if you ever need
a piece of equipment,
financial support,
or a blood donor,
just let me know.
I just want the best care
for him.
I'll see what I can do.
Thanks.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROLDAN EXHALES DEEPLY]
Excuse me.
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you Enzo's dad?
That's right.
I'm Arissa.
- I'm his--
- Girlfriend?
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Friend.
I was there when it happened.
Did you happen to see the person
who shot my son?
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
There was a guy.
And I think Enzo was his target.
Fortunately, my brother
was there, too.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
They fought over the gun,
but...
he ended up getting shot too.
He's in critical condition
right now.
I hope your brother
gets well soon, Arissa.
What's his name,
by the way?
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Samuel.
Samuel Trinidad.
I'll be on my way.
I'll stop by to check
on Enzo another time.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Alright.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
"SPO2 Policarpio is so amazing!
And handsome, too!"
"Handcuff me, officer! Kidding!"
"Cutie cop."
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DISTANT TELEPHONE RINGING]
"What a muscular, strong,
and handsome cop!"
Sir.
- What?
- Have you heard the news?
What do you mean?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Trinidad took a bullet.
What?
Last night, we got confirmation
that a scammer group
kidnapped his son.
And now you're telling me
he got shot?
That's strange.
[INDISTINCT CROWD CHATTER]
[BEKKAH] Yes, sir. The agency.
I'm on my way.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[AGNES] Where is he?
Girl.
Crane your neck all you want,
but you won't find Samuel
in his office.
And possibly, he'll never be
in there again.
Huh?
What makes you say that?
Haven't you heard?
Cutie pie was rushed
to a hospital.
- What?
- Got shot during lunch break.
What happened?
I guess all the rumors are true.
That he got mixed up
with some shady people.
So be careful.
I noticed that you two
have been getting close lately.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Is it true?
Was Enzo really shot?
The gunman had him
as the target,
and then Trinidad intervened.
Just his luck.
That bastard got shot as well.
He saved my son.
Who could've done this?
Think!
Who has the capacity to do this?
Who has the motive?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROLDAN BREATHES SHARPLY]
Diaz.
Tell me what I have to do.
Moron!
I'll handle it.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAR DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LOLITA SOBBING]
[KING CRYING]
[LOLITA] Doc...
...how's my son?
The operation is done.
He is somehow
in stable condition.
He lost a lot of blood.
But Doc,
he's going to be okay, right?
We'll keep monitoring him
just in case there are
post-op complications.
We'll do everything we can
for him to recover.
[LOLITA SOBBING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm already
at the hospital, Colonel.
I'll keep you updated.
Okay.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Johnny?
Uh, what are you doing here?
I went to see the scammer.
Heard he got shot.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I was going to interrogate him,
but he's still unconscious.
You?
What are you doing here?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Visiting him?
Some of our other officemates
are coming too.
Liar.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I already took care
of his fellow scammers.
So tell him when he wakes up...
...he better be careful.
He might be next.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Go ahead.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUNSHOT]
- [GRUNTS]
- Enzo! Enzo!
- Samuel!
- Help!
Samuel--
[GRUNTING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't move too much.
Your stitches might open.
[ENZO] Dad.
You're here.
Next time,
can you put me
as your emergency contact?
You're acting like
you're mad at me.
I'm not mad at you.
[SCOFFS] It feels like
you're distancing yourself.
I just want to be alone
and independent.
That's it.
I understand that.
But I'm your father.
Enzo, I want to know
if you understand.
I want to hear it from you--
do you understand?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ECG MACHINE BEEPING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[KING SOBBING] Dad!
Daddy... Daddy...
- [AGNES PANTING]
- [KING] Daddy!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
How's Samuel?
Daddy hasn't woken up yet.
[KING CRYING]
Daddy...
[KING SNIFFLING]
[SOBBING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
Hon?
[SIGHS] Where are you?
Chloe and I have been
waiting for her movie night.
[JACOB]
Sorry, something came up.
There's just an emergency
at work.
Oh, I hope it's nothing serious.
No, no, no.
Nothing I can't handle.
Don't worry,
this will be quick, okay?
Okay.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHLOE] Mommy, come on!
Okay, dear.
I choose?
Why won't you choose?
Okay...
Ready.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
If only he knew
this would happen to him,
he should've just run away
with the money!
Then he'd be safe right now!
What will happen
to Auntie Lolita and King
if he's gone?
Hey, what's wrong with you?
We're not even sure
Roldan's behind this, right?
And it's like you don't even
know Samuel.
You know he's the toughest
and strongest among us.
That's why he always wins
in sparring.
He'll wake up.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Stay alert.
I'm sure Roldan already knows
I had his son shot.
And most likely...
...he's on his way here now.
[WHISTLES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- [RAPID GUNFIRE]
- [DIAZ] Shoot him!
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[GUNSHOTS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ready, set, go!
[GUNSHOTS]
[JACOB GIGGLING]
- [DIAZ] Go ahead, shoot!
- Alright, noted!
[GUNSHOTS]
Jacob, you bastard!
Go on, shoot me!
If that's what you want.
[GUNSHOTS]
Hurry!
Bastard!
[GUNSHOTS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JACOB GRUNTS]
Stand up!
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Go ahead!
[GRUNTS]
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
- [JACOB LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
- [DIAZ GRUNTING]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES] Daddy....
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Daddy?
[LOLITA] Son?
[SOBBING] My God.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Daddy.
Bro.
You really scared us there, huh?
Glad you're okay now, sir.
[MAEL]
Told you Samuel's tough.
He's a fighter.
You almost gave me
a heart attack
worrying about you.
I was scared, Dad.
I thought you were
going to leave me.
[KING CRYING]
[SAMUEL] Son?
Remember what I told you?
[EKG BEEPING STEADILY]
I'll never leave you.
["HINDI AKO MAWAWALA"
BY LA SANTOS PLAYING]
[KING, LOLITA CRYING]
["HINDI AKO MAWAWALA" CONTINUES]
This Thursday...
How are you feeling now?
You made me worry.
Crushing them wasn't enough.
I burned them down to dust.
Honey, what happened here?
A wrench was thrown
into their plans.
Meet my dad.
Thank you very much
for saving my son, Samuel.
I know what you must've felt.
The fear of almost losing
your own child.
You mentioned that
someone saved Enzo.
Well, I was hoping to meet them.
To personally thank them,
you know.
Sins of the Father.