Human trafficking is one
of the major sources of income
of the Bakunawa Group.
They have a large
scam warehouse somewhere.
They must be
holding people there too.
Don't worry.
We have a lead.
Their staff caught by the police
can point out where
the scam warehouse is.
- [SIREN WAILS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LAND]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [WAILS, GRUNTS]
- [GUNSHOT]
[GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GUN CLATTERS]
[GROANS]
Enough! Surrender!
[GUNSHOT]
Ah!
Why did you kill him?!
I kept him alive
so he could be a witness!
Didn't you see? I saved you!
He was going
to shoot and kill you!
This can't be!
Our clients in Cambodia
will be very upset
that the new girls
didn't arrive on time!
What went wrong
with the shipment?!
My goodness!
I'm sure whatever's on that
hard drive is important to them.
That's why they killed Rainier.
It's my fault.
I'm the one to blame.
I'm the one to blame
for Rainier's death.
That's why we have
to finish this mission.
We can't fail, okay?
We need to work together...
to get justice for Rainier.
For Rainier.
[SOBBING]
Who do you think is behind this?
I don't know.
- It's Trinidad!
- What?
Haven't you noticed?
Ever since he got
into our group,
we've been in disarray.
Explain it to me.
How would he do that
if he doesn't even know
who the Bakunawa members are?
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- [SIGHS SHARPLY]
Sir.
- Sir--
- You bastard!
- [BODY THUDS]
- [GRUNTS]
You bastard!
I know you're the one
who sabotaged
our shipment to Cambodia!
Where were you last night?!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Answer me!
Where were you last night?!
I don't know
what you're talking about.
If you have proof, show it.
If not, then I know nothing!
You bastard! Liar!
- I don't know!
- Admit it!
I know you're behind it!
- That's enough.
- You bastard!
- Enough!
Stop it, Jacob.
What are you doing here?!
- What do you want?!
- The money!
You can get the money now!
I heard that
Johnny Policarpio got shot.
No one's spying on me anymore
about where the money's hidden!
You can have it all now.
Mm?
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ROLDAN BREATHING SHARPLY]
Alright.
- Alright.
- No!
No. I'll get it.
- Why you?
- Because you're useless!
I'll get it, but make sure
there's no trace!
Do you understand?
Alright.
Jacob will get it.
Enough.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why are both Arissa
and Enzo not here?
Arissa has an important errand.
And Enzo...
I don't know.
He didn't inform me.
Maybe they eloped.
Guys.
Guys, look at this.
Boss, look.
[REPORTER ON VIDEO]
A young man was killed.
Isn't that the guy Arissa
was talking to last time?
The victim has been identified
as Rainier Cruz, 22 years old.
It's still unclear who
is responsible for the shooting
or what the motive might be.
The police are reviewing...
Maybe that's why
Arissa's absent.
...the CCTV footage
from nearby establishments
and taking statements from
people near the crime scene.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Two of our revenue streams
have already collapsed.
Our clients in Cambodia
might cut ties with us.
What a waste of a partnership.
We'll suffer huge losses
if that happens.
[BECCA] I agree, Mother!
Don't you worry. I'll mobilize
the recruiters right away
so we can compensate
those Cambodians.
- Not enough!
- [BECCA] What?!
We need human blood sports
to boost revenue!
- Don't bring that up here!
- Why not?
At least I'm doing something
to bring our money back!
- You're just spitting nonsense!
- Shut up!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you even hear yourselves?!
Look at yourselves!
You all look like amateurs!
All you do is fight
and point fingers!
None of you
are thinking of a solution
to fix our problem!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let me remind you.
We still don't have
the Crown Madera!
And we can't let
our plan fall apart
just because you're all acting
like a bunch of fools!
You think you're so great?!
You think you've done
nothing wrong?!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
See?
You pissed off the old man.
Because you keep fighting!
Well, at least I'm bringing
something to the table. And you?
You're just leeching off
my business!
[CHUCKLES]
You're too careless
that the truck got ambushed!
Look who's talking!
Just because you act all holy
in a white suit
doesn't mean you're pure!
You make me sick!
- Hey. Watch your words.
- [VALENTINA] Hey, Pastor!
You're a real pain!
Don't blame me!
You're getting on my nerves!
That's enough.
Enough. Calm down.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come in.
[LEAH] Yes?
What can I do for you?
Aljon, what--
Enzo.
What are you doing here?
Uh...
Miss Leah, I'm sorry
for dropping by so suddenly.
Are you okay?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
You're here
because you have a problem.
I guess so.
What is it?
You can tell me.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENZO BREATHES SHAKILY]
I don't know how to put it
into words, Miss Leah.
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ENZO BREATHING SHAKILY]
Is it about your dad?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh... [BREATHES HEAVILY]
I feel like...
I don't really know Papa
that well.
It feels like
he's keeping so many secrets.
Like...
Like what kind of secrets?
[SIGHS] Miss Leah...
Too many.
Miss Leah, it's maybe because
we hardly talk these days.
Maybe...
...you should find out
what those secrets are.
So you won't have
to bear the burden.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FRUSTRATED SIGH]
Miss Leah,
I feel like knowing the truth
will just add to my burdens.
[BREATHES SHARPLY, SIGHS DEEPLY]
Sorry, Miss Leah.
Sorry if I'm not
making sense. [SNIFFLES]
I'll go now.
Enzo.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I understand.
I know how hard it is
when you know your family
is keeping secrets from you.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
But I want you to know
that I'm here for you, okay?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you, Miss Leah.
Thank you.
I'll go now, Miss Leah.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC SWELLS]
- You should always smile.
- [FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Be confident.
You shouldn't let the customers
sense that you're nervous, okay?
- You can go now.
- Thank you.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you trying
to steal my job here?
Huh?
What are you saying?
Don't play dumb!
You're such a show-off!
Remember, Naomi,
you're just new here.
I've been working here longer.
I even taught you
the ins and outs, right?
So, don't be smug with me!
Why?
Is it my fault
if I'm better than you now?
In case you've forgotten,
I go by the name Shanaiah now.
[SCOFFS]
And by the way,
why are you scolding me?
Are you my mother?
[MUSIC BECOMES SULLEN]
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LINE RINGING]
So, have you found it, bro?
Yes, bro.
I'll put it on now.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
All done, bro.
Okay, bro. Thanks.
[GRUNTS]
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
[JACOB] Damn that Trinidad!
I'm sure he's the one
sabotaging our group.
Go find his car
and put a tracker on it.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Understood?
- All done?
- Yeah.
Okay.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROLDAN]
Jacob, what are you up to?
[JACOB] I want to know
Trinidad's every move.
Because I want to prove to you
that damn Trinidad is the one
sabotaging all of
our group's operations.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNICKERS]
Whatever, Jacob.
Suit yourself.
[CAR LOCK BEEPS]
Let's go.
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bro... Are you okay?
I'm just chilling here, bro.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
[GRUNTS]
Did you hear that, bro?
Yes, bro.
They also put a tracker
on your car.
We can use it to our advantage.
Alright.
Okay, bro. Be careful. Thanks.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
- Paeng.
- Hey, Samuel.
You're back.
How have you been?
Well, I'm swamped with work.
I heard what happened
while I was gone from Mael.
I missed a lot.
You sure did.
Why did you suddenly go to Cebu?
You know I have cases
to tend to.
- Right.
- It's fine. I understand.
How's it going over there?
Where's Jacob now?
At home. He didn't go to
the address you provided.
What's this address
pointing to, Samuel?
The model unit where
the money is hidden.
If he went home, it means he
hasn't cleared it yet.
I'm sure the next time he does,
he'll collect the money.
Alert me when that happens.
Is that clear?
Crystal.
You can count on us.
Yeah, we're monitoring
the tracker 24/7.
Okay.
What about the tracker
on your car?
He himself gave me
a smokescreen.
He won't find out
where I am.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Arissa! Who were those people?
I don't know!
But I think they're the reason
your sister is missing.
[RAINIER] Arissa, this way!
[MAN] Hey!
- [ARISSA WHIMPERS] This way!
- Arissa! Arissa!
- No!
- Get her!
Hey, you!
[ARISSA] Rainier!
[RAINIER] No...
No!
- No!
- [GUNSHOT]
No!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRYING, BREATHING ERRATICALLY]
Arissa? Arissa...
What is it?
It was just a nightmare.
Arissa.
It's okay.
Auntie Ari?
King.
[ARISSA CONTINUES
BREATHING ERRATICALLY]
Inhale...
Exhale...
- [BREATHING EVENS]
- Inhale... Exhale...
Inhale... Exhale...
[WHIMPERING]
[ARISSA SOBBING LOUDLY]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Policarpio, hey.
- Hey.
Sir, we've got a new case.
Okay. I'll look into it later.
- Sir.
- Hey.
So, how are you?
Are you okay now?
- Of course.
- Hey, sir.
Hey.
I'm tough as a tank.
That's good to hear, sir.
Looks like I need to
keep a close watch...
Hello, sir.
...on our men.
Think about it.
Sir.
How did those goons
manage to escape?
Weren't they all
in handcuffs?
And the sole potential witness
I spared to make use of
was killed by Gallaga.
What are you trying to say, sir?
I'm saying there are protectors
of criminal syndicates
among our ranks.
We can't trust anyone.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Policarpio.
- Welcome back.
- Thank you, Gallaga.
Here's the file
Chief is looking for.
- I'll leave it to you.
- Yes, sir.
How's the lead
for the new case?
[GUN CLATTERS]
- [GUNSHOT]
- Hey!
Why did you kill him?!
Didn't you see? I saved you!
He was about to shoot you!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Grandma, Daddy,
is Auntie Ari okay?
Yes, Auntie Ari is just
going through something.
- What is it?
- Son...
You're too young
to understand.
For now,
let's just show
Auntie Arissa our support.
Take care of her.
Make her laugh.
Of course, Dad!
I love Auntie Ari!
[SAMUEL] I know.
Here's your lunchbox.
[LOLITA] Mm, here's your bag.
[DIEGO] Alright, sweetie.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Yes.
- Come on, sweetie.
- Welcome.
Well, I really didn't
expect you to join us.
Are you sure we are not
interrupting your schedule, Dad?
No, don't worry.
I told you,
I want to meet my grandson.
Chloe!
Hello, King!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
King, this is my Grandpa Diego.
Grandpa, this is King,
my best friend.
- Oh... Hi.
- Hello!
King, if we can share my mommy,
we can also share my grandpa.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DIEGO] Hi, King.
I am your Grandpa Diego.
And I am very,
very glad to meet you.
Really? I can treat you
as my grandpa?
[DIEGO] Of course!
You can be my grandson.
Yay!
- Hi, Grandpa!
- [DIEGO CHUCKLES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Help me escape.
Let's work together.
Those who don't perform well
are sent to Cambodia.
Every move is calculated...
Good luck on
your new assignment.
I'm looking forward
to working with you.
Why don't you look
for the hard drive
to find out the truth?!
I was right.
He's behind
the scam operations.
I'll prove Samuel
is the one ruining the group.
...to strategically
take down their enemies.
Are you just
going to stand there?
Take off your helmet.
This week,
the scammers will be in chaos.
We lost the money
because of you!
It's Trinidad's fault!
He's the guy
on the motorbike.
My money is gone!
Sir, I have a proposal.
- Trinidad--
- Not now, Samuel!
This is a game changer!
I'm the old man's favorite now
because their group's in chaos.
Hello, Samuel Trinidad.
[DISTORTED VOICE]
I have an assignment for you.