Now,
we are not just
welcoming a colleague.
We are celebrating Samuel.
A loyal, brave, and kind man.
You risked your life for my son,
and I will be forever grateful
to you.
Thank you, sir, for those, uh...
kind words.
That's enough talking.
Come on, let's have a toast.
Cheers!
Everyone, meet Danny.
He's one of the many scam
victims of Mike Trinidad.
W-What's the problem, Danny?
The loan shark
I owed money to--
You thought you could hide
from us?
- Oh my!
- Goodness!
I'm working myself to the bone
just to pay you back!
- Oh no!
- Good grief!
I'll repay you soon!
Watch your back, Danny!
We'll get you one of these days!
Dude, to be honest,
I'm not sure I feel comfortable
with your plan.
This was the only way
I could think of
to scrounge up enough evidence
against them.
Don't worry.
I've got people backing me up.
"It's ready."
Uh, sir?
We received a mission order
from the National
Revenue Authority.
They will be conducting an audit
at Oriental Ridge.
What?!
An audit?
When?
It's confirmed
for tomorrow, sir.
Alright.
I'll just have a talk
with Jacob.
Not all of these records
are clean.
You think that's news
to me, Jacob?
How could you drop the ball
on this?
We need someone
to launder our money!
If Mike were alive,
he would've figured it out!
Uh, excuse me.
Is there a problem, sir?
I heard the NRA will conduct
an audit here.
Sir, taxation is one of my areas
of expertise.
I can help you.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Taxation is one of my areas
of expertise.
How can you help us?
Well, first,
I need to know whether they'll
uncover any discrepancies.
[SNICKERS]
If so, you need to show me
your books.
[JACOB CHUCKLES DRYLY]
He's lost his mind.
Is this a joke?
Sir, I'm not going to find
anything they won't.
If there are any discrepancies,
it's better that
I see them first.
So I can fix them.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What are you hiding?
Whatever it is, I can help.
I can protect you.
You just need to trust me.
I'm on your side, Sir Roldan.
Sir, you can trust me.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Remember, I took a bullet
for your son.
And I will take a bullet
for you.
I can clean up any mess.
[HUFFS]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Land acquisitions,
project expenses,
list of contractors--
- Everything's on your desk.
- Okay.
This one.
Three disbursements for
land development in Tanauan
but no supporting permits
or progress reports exist?
This book has inconsistent
posting of entries.
The auditor might
become suspicious
of the overlapping dates.
And regarding this contractor...
They received a hefty sum,
more than a hundred
million pesos,
but the details of their
supposed project are missing.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir, I've just begun scratching
the surface here.
And I'm sure tons
of discrepancies
are waiting to be uncovered.
So what?
Can you fix them or not?
- Of course I can.
- There we go.
[ROLDAN SIGHS IN RELIEF]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KNOCKING ON THE DOOR]
Sir?
Here's the list of transactions
that might be flagged.
Each has its own memo.
A narrative, a justification.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
This one includes the report on
the land acquisition in Tanauan.
I reclassified it as
speculative development.
I also prepared
a feasibility study
and an internal appraisal.
This folder contains the delays
in the books.
I justified them as part
of a system transition.
We'll say we changed
our accounting software,
which caused a mix-up
in the entries
during migration.
I created reconciliation tables
to make it look more believable.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, and sir, here's the one
regarding the contractor.
I filed it as a CSR project.
Corporate Social Responsibility.
We'll present it
as if we hired them
for a community
development initiative
where Oriental Ridge
pledged a donation.
I also prepared a project brief
and a Memorandum of Agreement
to support it.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir,
I've discovered numerous
unexplained earnings
amounting to hundreds
of millions.
It could become a major issue
if the NRA uncovers them.
But don't worry,
I'm already working on it.
I'm currently creating
paper trails.
Contracts, records of donations,
dummy projects.
Everything to make it appear
they came from legal sources.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Good. Carry on.
[SAMUEL] Okay. Thank you, sir.
[SAMUEL GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[ROLDAN] Samuel.
Aren't you going to ask where
all that money came from?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
No, sir.
It's not my place to ask.
I'm here to fix the problem.
Excuse me, sir.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[PRINTER WHIRRING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEKKAH] So where is
the morning tea coming from?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir, everything's ready.
I've written memos
explaining every discrepancy.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Are you sure?
- Yes, sir.
You have nothing to worry about.
Crisis averted.
I'll get going now.
- [SIGHS DEEPLY]
- Roldan.
[JACOB INHALES SHARPLY]
Do you think he actually
pulled it off?
Swept everything under the rug?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I guess so.
But if he actually did,
then he's even better
than his dad.
[SCOFFS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [BEKKAH] Sir, excuse me.
Um...
The people from the NRA
are here.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
We're here to collect
your books.
Sure. We are ready.
We have nothing to hide.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Please send my thanks
to Colonel Enrico.
For contacting his assets
in the NRA.
It's been a huge help.
Roldan and his brother
are absolutely rattled.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
You created a problem
just so you could come in
and fix it.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you think this will work?
That you'll become one of them
after this?
Yeah.
I'm in.
Roldan doesn't know it
yet, but...
I'm already in.
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENRICO BREATHES DEEPLY]
How was it?
All good, sir.
Samuel can now
join Roldan's inner circle.
Thanks for your help
with the NRA.
[CHUCKLES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I have to say...
[CLICKS MOUTH]
I'm impressed with Samuel.
He's smart and resourceful.
And above all,
he has a true criminal mind.
Sir, do you think...
that's an advantage?
If you aim to catch a criminal,
you must think like one.
You need...
a criminal mind, too.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
- Hello, Samuel?
- [UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
You didn't come home last night.
Are you okay?
Yes, Ma.
Uh...
I just had a lot of work to do.
Son, I'm still not comfortable
with you working
at that company,
especially with
your criminal bosses.
I know, Ma, but...
don't worry.
I've got this.
I know what I'm doing.
Are you safe, son?
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I am, Ma.
That's what...
I'm working on right now.
[WHISPERS] So they won't be
a danger to us anymore.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Samuel.
- Sir?
- [LINE DISCONNECTS]
- Hello? Hello?
[SAMUEL CLEARS THROAT]
The NRA called.
They're requesting
supporting documents
for the issues you flagged.
Yes, sir. It's...
all sorted out.
You're good, Samuel.
Thank you, sir.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Everyone at the cafe misses you.
I miss them, too.
I've been wanting to come in,
but Luke insists I rest.
I'll be reporting tomorrow.
Oh, I guess I didn't need
to bring food.
You've got so much here.
Papa brought that over
yesterday.
We were supposed to eat it,
but he had to rush out
because of an emergency.
So...
he made time for you, but...
he ran out of time?
Yeah, pretty much.
At least...
he's trying.
But...
I had to get shot first.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Enzo...
How well do you know
your father?
[CHUCKLES]
What kind of question is that?
Obviously, I know my father.
He's been my father since birth.
Just asking.
I never knew my father,
you see.
That's all.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're weird.
Let's just eat.
Why didn't you heat up
the food from the fridge?
Because I knew you were coming.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE BUZZING]
[SAMUEL] Agnes?
[AGNES]
Samuel, where are you?
I just went out for air.
I need to clear my head
for my next step.
[AGNES] Is that so?
Alright, take care.
- [BODY THUDS]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hey!
- Hey! Stop!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
My landlady
just wouldn't let me.
I can't even go to my parents
because they're mad me.
You can stay with us if you
still haven't found a place.
- Really?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Our struggles never seem to stop
because of that Mike Trinidad.
If I run into any
of his family...
I'll make them pay!
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll give them a 360-degree
head spin when I see them!
[ARISSA] Hi again, Ms. Cruz.
I'm sorry if I'm bugging you
but please reply
once you see this message.
[PHONE CHIMES]
Especially that Arissa.
That Arissa who went viral!
[ARISSA] I want to fix
the mess Dad caused.
I know you've been dragged
into all this.
I also want to help you.
- Oh!
- That's her!
That's really her!
- She's pretty, huh.
- The nerve!
See? That girl looks so good
because of our money!
[WOMAN] She's wasting our money
to look that good!
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENZO] She's a good person.
I feel sorry for her
because she's been dragged
into her dad's mess.
Why didn't you tell Arissa
about our group?
She's already dealing
with so many problems.
I don't want to add more
to her burden.
[WOMAN] I just want to pull
her hair, beat her up
and drag her off!
[BEBINA] I'll squeeze her nose!
I'm dead serious!
- Look at her other video!
- That spoiled brat!
Hey. Why are you
just standing here?
It's just hot. Uh...
Take a seat, Pa.
Go on.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh my god.
She's seen my message.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ARISSA] Ms. Cruz, I know
you've read my message.
Please reply.
Please. I want to know
about my father's victims.
I want to help them.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Hey!
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GRUNTING]
Stop!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come here!
You can't run away from us!
You think someone
will defend you here?!
Please have mercy on me.
- Have mercy?!
- [BLOW LANDS]
[SAMUEL] Stop! That's enough.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Enough?
You also want a beating?!
[MAN 1] Get lost.
This is none of your business.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS LOUDLY]
[GRUNTS LOUDLY, WAILS]
- [MAN 2] Who's that? Hit him!
- [GRUNTS IN PAIN]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTING IN PAIN]
Enough!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's talk calmly.
What's the problem?
Talk calmly?
That guy owes us so much!
And he's telling us
he has no money to pay?!
I didn't know Yayaman Tayo
was an investment scam.
I put all the money there.
Investment?
- You bastard!
- Stop!
That's enough!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GROANING WEAKLY]
How much does he owe you?
Half a million pesos.
Half a million pesos?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Call me.
I'll pay off his debt.
With interest?
Yes.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is what I have for now.
Now, go.
Go. Just call me.
Go!
That's enough.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you okay?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
You and your father
are to blame for this!
Because of you two,
I'm neck-deep in debt!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Even if you pay off my debt...
[SNIFFLES]
You can no longer fix the mess
you and your father caused.
You ruined my life!
And everyone else's lives.
Yes!
There are many of us!
All our lives got ruined
because of you!
I'm meeting them today.
Now, what do I tell them?
"My problem's over!"
"Samuel Trinidad
will pay off my debt!"
Like that?
- [MUSIC BECOMES EMOTIONAL]
- [SNIFFLES]
How about them?
How about them?!
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Mm.
- Help yourselves.
Thank you.
[GASPS]
- Danny! Oh my gosh!
- Danny! Danny!
Did those goons catch you?!
What happened to you, huh?
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
- What are you doing here?
- Please calm down.
I didn't come here
to cause trouble.
I know you're angry
with me and my family.
I don't blame you.
But I just want to apologize
for what my father did to you.
[SCOFFS]
Oh, he apologized,
so I guess we can
all just move on, huh?
It doesn't work like that!
Take a look at
what happened to Danny!
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
I know it doesn't
fix everything.
I get it if you don't want
to forgive me.
But please believe me,
all I want is to fix
what my father did to you.
I can't return
all of your money yet,
but I'll do whatever I can,
step by step,
until I make it right.
Write down all your names
and the amount
my father took from you.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Write it all down.
Every cent.
Go ahead.
List your names.
Well, if you said so.
There's nothing left
to lose anyway.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you.
I give you my word,
I will give back
all of your money.
I just hope
you won't let us down.
I'll get going.
I'm sorry.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAMUEL]
They are your victims, Roldan,
along with the countless others
you've deceived.
I can't give
their money back yet.
Not now.
I need this chance
to get inside your circle
and destroy it from the inside
to make sure
you can't ruin another life.
And when my mission is done,
I'll return every cent you took
and help them rebuild
the lives you destroyed.
If it weren't for Samuel,
we'd be done for!
You want to bring him
into our circle?!
Samuel can work around
the law for us.
A new scam is
about to be launched.
Who didn't hit the quota?!
- [WHIMPERS] Have mercy, sir!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
Samuel's got Roldan
by the throat.
I know you ordered
the kidnapping of my son.
What do you want?