Please, I'm busy.
Why are you so grumpy?
I just wanted
to give this to you.
Thank you so much.
The second batch of words
for the seed phrase.
"Violin, erupt, yellow."
There's the next clue.
"Where you stumbled and learned
to get back on your feet."
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[DIGITAL TRILLING]
[ROLDAN LAUGHING]
Right, Jacob?
I didn't move the mouse.
- Is that possible?
- I think they planted an agent
before they gave it
to you.
But bro, I can get
rid of it.
No need, bro.
They'll find out.
But I bet
they're doing this
because they don't know
the seed phrase,
and they need me
to find it.
You're not like
your father,
and you're making
an honest living.
I hope you mean that.
I can drive you home
if you want.
Thanks, but no.
- You can drop the act.
- Whatever.
Johnny--
Is it your turn to flirt
with my wife?
Your wife and I
are just coworkers.
Stay away from my wife.
Is that the money Daddy stole?
You had it all this time?
Go to bed, Arissa.
Sure, I can sleep now.
But I'll ask again tomorrow.
Don't expect me
to shut up about it.
Sit down.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
And you're only
telling me this now?!
I didn't want to involve you.
You have your own problems.
I have the right to know
because he's my father!
- You won't understand.
- Then help me understand it!
- Arissa--
- [DOOR OPENS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What's wrong with you two?
My grandson is asleep.
If you two are going to fight,
do it outside.
Does she know?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Know about what?
- About this.
Yes, I knew.
Oh my god!
That's enough.
Now that you know, let me find
the seed phrase
so I can return this money
to Papa's victims.
No.
I want to be part of this too.
Let's talk about the clue.
Where did you first stumble?
Ma...
Ma, do you remember a time
when I stumbled as a kid?
You stumbled many times
when you were a kid,
especially when you had
just started walking.
No, Ma. Um...
It has to be the kind
that is very memorable.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I do remember one memory.
Your father and I
had a big fight
when he was teaching you
how to ride a bike.
You fell really bad,
and got that scar.
Where did he teach you
how to ride a bike?
Maybe we can start there.
It was at the park.
Which park?
- [OBJECTS CLATTER]
- [DOG BARKING]
What was that?
It's probably a cat.
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [DOG BARKING]
I'll go and have a look.
[DOOR CREAKING OPEN]
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DOG BARKING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC SWELLS]
Samuel, what was that?
Uh, it was just a cat, Ma.
It was a cat.
I'm going back to bed.
Alright.
Good night.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
It wasn't a cat, was it?
Don't tell Mama.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Fine. I'll be quiet.
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Good morning.
I just need you to sign these.
You can start with this one.
Um... Okay.
Just come back
for it later.
Oh, of course.
Alright.
Hold on.
What happened to your neck?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
How did you get that?
Uh, this? Uh...
It's nothing.
It's just a graze.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I'm fine.
Hold on.
Stay here.
I'll be quick.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PHONE RINGING IN DISTANCE]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Worthless jerk.
You think you can mess
with me?
- What are you doing?
- Oh.
- Uh...
- Huh?
Uh, sorry.
I couldn't find a seat.
I spaced out
while looking at your laptop.
I didn't know.
Is there something important?
I didn't see anything.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Alright, I need
to get back to work.
Thank you.
I'll leave the papers
that you need to sign.
- Thank you.
- Come back for it later.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
[ENZO] Auntie!
Enzo!
Wait.
You're my driver?
At your service.
Hmm.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Let's go.
Okay.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mr. Trinidad.
You're going home?
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
Sir.
Yes, sir. I'm going home now.
Take care.
Oh, sir, by the way...
I'm done with one
of my proposals.
You can check it out
if you want to.
We have a meeting
for that tomorrow, right?
Yes, sir, but in case you want
to do some advanced reading,
I have here the--
[LAPTOP THUDS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sorry, sir.
The laptop you issued to Samuel
is mirrored.
So, everything he types there
will show up
on your screen, too.
- Got it.
- [CHUCKLES]
[SAMUEL] Sir, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to drop it.
Just bring it to
the IT department.
Uh, alright.
This is kind of laggy anyway.
Sometimes, the cursor
moves on its own.
Anyway, sir, I'll go
to the IT office.
You can go home first.
Take care.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAMUEL] Do you think
you can still fix it?
I need my presentations
and proposals.
There are lots of important
documents on that laptop.
Well...
I can still fix this,
but it will take some time.
How much time will it take?
- I urgently need those--
- Ow! Ah!
It's so hot!
I'm really sorry, I didn't
mean to spill it on you.
Are you okay?
Wait, I'll just go
to the restroom.
I'm really sorry.
It was an accident.
Ah!
I hope you're alright.
I'm so sorry.
You'll sneak into
your boss's office?
- Yes.
- How will you do that?
There are security cameras
in every corner of his office.
Hmm. [MUNCHES]
That's where Mighty Mael
comes in.
This contains a payload.
If you plug this into the CPU,
it will install
a remote access trojan
in about 30 seconds.
And because of that,
you can enter the CCTV stream
of your company.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAPTOP THUDS]
This is kind of laggy anyway.
Sometimes, the cursor
moves on its own.
Okay.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on, download faster.
Hurry up, please.
I don't have much time.
This needs to install quickly.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
How are you?
Did you get burned?
Uh, just a little bit,
but it's okay.
I'm really sorry.
Anyway, how soon can you fix it?
Do you think you can finish it
by tomorrow?
I'll try my best to
get it fixed by tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Alright. You see,
I need my files there.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Yeah.
I'm really sorry.
Do I need to sign anything?
No, since I was the one
who issued this to you.
Thank you.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
I saw your name
on the ride-hailing app.
I was in the area anyway,
so I accepted your booking.
By the way, Auntie,
where's your driver?
Well, I had him pick up
some documents,
but he got stuck in traffic
and I can't wait for him.
But it's fine since I got you
as my ride.
I know that I'm in
good hands.
Of course, Auntie.
Besides, I've got
a five-star rating,
- so you're safe. [CHUCKLES]
- Mm-hmm.
So you went with your plan to
be a ride-hailing app driver.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're very hardworking.
Thank you, Auntie.
Um...What about you?
How are you?
Well, I'm back.
I just got back from Switzerland
for a Global Legal Summit.
- Wow.
- I'm going straight...
to the hotel
for a lecture.
Plus, I'm handling cases
on the side.
Wow, Auntie. You really
are a busy person.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- Yes.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
But I find it very fulfilling.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yes?
Is there anything
you want to tell me?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Auntie, have you heard about the
Yayaman Tayo investment scam?
Yeah.
I'm aware.
It scammed a lot
of people.
Wait. What about it?
Don't tell me you're one
of the victims.
No, Auntie.
But the father of my friend,
Gavin, was also scammed.
Earlier...
I was at their meeting.
I feel sorry for them, Auntie.
So, I was hoping that you
could give them...
Only if it's okay with you.
Maybe you could give them
legal advice.
If you're not busy and you have
free time.
Yes, of course.
Well, please tell them that I'd
love to meet them.
I'll see how I can help them.
Thank you, Auntie.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Sit down, sit down, sit down.
Okay, um...
Bullet updates.
Make it fast.
Sir, we got a total
of three arrests
related to the
Cebu crypto scam.
All of their accounts
have been frozen.
And sir, we also arrested
Pastor Elvin Reyes.
We tracked him in Tagaytay.
[DIEGO] Good.
Make sure to freeze
all accounts
linked to that fake charity
of Harvest of Hope.
- Okay?
- Yes, sir.
I have filed a request
with AMLC.
As for the online
lending app, sir,
we already have more
than 100 complainants.
[MOUTH CLICKS] Good.
But that's not our main
agenda today, right?
What's the update on
Yayaman Tayo investment scam?
We still don't have
any leads, sir.
Mike Trinidad covered his tracks
before committing suicide.
Despite continuous
public pressure,
Samuel Trinidad still
wouldn't budge.
It seems we won't get
anything from him.
Is it really that or is he just
unwilling to yield?
I don't believe
that he is innocent.
I'm sure that Samuel
is hiding something.
Well, anyway, keep on pressing.
He'll break eventually.
Yes, sir.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Oh. You're still here, sir.
Yeah. I just need
to finish something.
I'm working overtime.
- Should I turn off the lights?
- Yeah.
- Alright. Sorry about that.
- It's okay.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[MUSIC BECOMES SUSPENSEFUL]
[LINE RINGING]
Hello, Mael?
Hello?
Just a sec, bro.
Let me transfer the call.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hello? Do you hear me?
It's me, Mael.
I hear you.
Ma-- Oh, okay.
Everyone in the office
left already.
Okay.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[TRILLING]
Alright. I'll loop
the footage now.
Just sit there...
and keep typing.
Don't move too much
so they won't notice
that the video is looped.
Wait for my go signal, okay?
Okay, bro.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[EXHALES LOUDLY]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[TRILLING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mael?
Okay. I'm done
looping the video.
You have 15 minutes. Go.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[CLICKS]
- "ROLDAN RIVERA"
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC STING]
Who are you?!
[THUD]
[GRUNTS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GROANS]
- [KICKS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GROANS]
Who are you? Who are you?!
- [THUD]
- [GROANS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTING]
[THUD]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GASPS]
- Who are you?! Who are you?
- [GASPING FOR AIR]
[GRUNTS, SHOUTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
This Wednesday...
Why were you
in Roldan's office?
You work for him?
We're not enemies.
We're on the same side.
[GRUNTS]
Secrets will explode.
This search for the money
is taking too long.
This is taking too long.
We need to level up our game.
Who are you?
What are you-- Aah!
- Let me go!
- Argh!
I won't stop until
I get the truth out of his son.
I can't let my family be
in that kind of danger.