You can't just scare
that Jacob guy off easily.
You finally met your match.
And he's dangerous.
And if he's that intense,
what more Roldan?
So be careful, man.
Agnes is waiting for me.
These are the keys
to our new house.
Remember this,
you have a home.
That Jacob is
out of his mind, isn't he?
I'm sure King will get worried
when he sees that.
Agnes, I'm so-- I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry too.
This shouldn't have happened.
It's unfair. You know almost
all my problems with my family
but you've never opened up
to me.
My dad and I aren't close.
And he's too busy
with his work.
I'm really sorry, Enzo.
I'm really sorry.
I'm getting sleepy.
Uh, will you sleep
in your room?
It's already late.
Did he really talk
to you like that?
Just say the word, Roldan,
and I'll take him out.
People like Diaz
aren't worth stressing over.
Diaz might still get
that deal.
Can you trace where
that call came from?
Yes, it's matched
to the Green Mile.
Come on.
Let's head to the warehouse.
I think we'll find
the answer there.
Damn it. I knew it.
This is a scam hub.
Hey!
- What are you doing?!
- Sir!
Cops!
[GUNSHOTS]
Revo!
- Son! Revo!
- Sir!
We need to leave!
Let's go!
You okay?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Revo Diaz, the son
of Emerson Diaz,
a prominent businessman
and alleged leader
of a scamming syndicate,
died in a police encounter.
The shooting happened
inside the Green Mile warehouse.
The raid took place
in a warehouse
that is suspected
to be a scam hub.
The police found
fake IDs,
passports having the same photo
but different names, SIM cards,
and other paraphernalia
used for digital scam.
While the operation
is under investigation,
authorities also found out the
involvement of the Diazes
in the kidnapping
of the son of Samuel Trinidad,
whose father was the infamous
scammer, Mike Trinidad.
Authorities are
still identifying
the motive for kidnapping.
Meanwhile, Emerson
has reportedly escaped
and is currently
being hunted down.
The operation is headed
by PO2 Johnny Policarpio,
who was also responsible for
the rescue of Trinidad's son.
The investigation
is still ongoing
to uncover the extent
of the syndicate's operations,
and to determine the names
of other people involved.
[JOHNNY] I will not stop
until the mastermind,
Emerson Diaz, is behind bars.
We also have a lead
on the other people
behind this scam syndicate.
But we can't disclose
that yet to the public
because it might preempt
our investigation.
This is a call for the
conspirators in Diaz's group.
You know who you are.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Your days are numbered.
I'll make sure you rot
in jail.
I'm coming for you,
you damn scammer.
You know what,
this cop is really something.
I'm grateful to him
because he saved King,
but he's too smug, right?
You're right, Ma.
Yet he doesn't know he's going
after the wrong guy.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you connected
to them, Roldan?
Or are they an enemy
you're trying to take down?
If my suspicions were true,
they're getting powerful
and becoming a threat to you.
That's why you got rid of them
in the equation.
So they wouldn't be able
to interfere
with whatever you're planning.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[ROLDAN] Sir.
Roldan, any news?
Give me some good news.
If you haven't heard yet,
I already took care of Diaz.
He's no longer a problem.
That's what I want to hear.
That's the Roldan Rivera I know.
Logical, efficient,
and smart.
From now on,
I want you to keep
the good news coming.
Yes, sir.
That way, you'll make up for
all those mistakes you made!
- [SCOFFS]
- [PHONE THUDS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROLDAN BREATHES SHARPLY]
Roldan, you really did
a great job handling Diaz.
I told you we shouldn't worry
about those kinds of people.
Plus you also fooled Policarpio
to kill them.
- Good work, bro.
- Jacob.
Think of the people
around you.
Think of them
as chess pieces.
You have to know
when to move them.
Now, if you want to earn
that old man's trust,
you can't keep using
an iron fist in your battles.
Just like what
we did now,
we have to think
carefully.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS]
Bro, did you hear
the news last night?
The shootout
at the Green Mile factory.
Yeah.
The warehouse that was used
as a scam hub. Why?
Does Roldan own that?
It doesn't seem like it.
But my gut tells me that Roldan
was responsible for that.
They're eliminating
competition.
They're killing groups
they can no longer control.
They don't want them
to get ahead.
Makes sense.
Do you think they're working
with the cops?
Bro, I don't think so.
I know that cop.
He's smug, arrogant,
and a show-off,
but I don't think
he's corrupt.
I think Roldan
is taking advantage
of how show-off he is
to target their enemies.
They're using him.
He needs to be pointed
in the right direction.
Your enemies
are smart, bro.
That's why I need
to outsmart them.
That's the only way
to take them down.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
Enzo, thank you for
offering Arissa a place to stay.
I know you've only met
each other recently,
but you've already
helped her so much.
Not just her,
but our family too.
Enzo, thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
That's what friends do.
Are you guys
really just friends?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, don't make this
a big deal.
Well, whatever it is
you have going on,
I just hope you have
good intentions for her, Enzo.
Okay?
Uh, I forgot my phone upstairs.
I'll just get it.
Ah, Arissa, wait.
The keys.
I have my own key, remember?
Just friends, huh?
Samuel!
My god!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
She's grumpy, isn't she?
[MUSIC BECOMES UNSETTLING]
[LINE RINGING]
Sir, I'm already here.
[MAN] Take care of it.
Sir, he's with someone.
I don't care!
Do as I say!
Copy, sir.
[GUN COCKS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUNSHOT]
- [GROANS] Ah!
- Enzo! Enzo!
Samuel! Ah!
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- [ENZO GROANING]
Samuel!
- Enzo!
- Arissa! Run!
Enzo!
[ENZO GROANING]
Oh my god!
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [SAMUEL GROANS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [MAN GROANS]
Help! Help!
- Help!
- [GUNSHOT]
- Samuel!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Samuel!
- Enzo!
- Arissa! Run!
- [GROANS IN PAIN]
Oh my god!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING]
Help! Help!
- [GUNSHOT]
- Help!
- Samuel!
Samuel!
[BLOWS LAND]
[GUN CLATTERS]
Hey! Stop!
- [GROANS IN PAIN]
- Enzo!
Enzo!
Help! Samuel!
Samuel!
- Samuel!
- Help us!
Someone call for help!
Samuel!
Enzo!
Help!
[SOBS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WEAKLY] King...
Ma.
[ARISSA] Samuel!
Enzo!
[SOBBING] Samuel!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir, this is our proposed budget
for this project.
Roldan, Trinidad was shot.
He's in critical condition.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, guys, I have to
cut this meeting short.
Jacob and I have
an urgent matter to discuss.
So everybody, please?
What happened?!
Trinidad cannot die!
If he dies,
all the money we worked hard for
goes with him!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [EKG MACHINE BEEPS]
- Bleeder found.
It's deep but manageable.
Tie please.
Vitals?
BP 80/40.
Heart rate, 120.
He's losing a lot of blood.
Let's prepare for
blood transfusion.
- [ENZO WHIMPERS]
- Stay still.
- Nurse, give me some gauze.
- [MUMBLES]
Doc, let's sedate the patient.
Prepare to intubate.
Yes, Doc. Intubating.
Samuel.
[GAGGING, COUGHING]
- Doc, vital signs?
- Doc, vital signs are stable.
- BP 110/80.
- Cutting.
[EKG MACHINE BEEPING]
Seems like the bullet
didn't go in too deep.
No vital organs were hit.
Okay. Stabilize the patient.
Run a fast drip, double line.
Hook up RBC.
Retractors?
[EKG MACHINE BEEPING]
We're not out of the woods yet.
Blood transfusion ready.
[EKG MACHINE BEEPING]
Hemostasis done.
Packing.
[EKG MACHINE BEEPING]
Bro?
Yeah. He's still in surgery.
We're all worried out here.
King's been crying nonstop.
Yes--
Alright, alright.
Just finish what you're doing
then head over here.
I'll update you later, okay?
Alright.
I hope Sir Samuel
gets better soon.
It's just heartbreaking.
His child was just kidnapped
and now this happens to him.
Arissa, what really happened?
I don't know!
[STAMMERS] I only left them
for a bit, then--
T-Then when I got back,
Enzo had been shot.
And Samuel was wrestling
for the gun...
- ...with some guy and--
- What?!
Auntie! [SOBS]
Auntie, I'm sorry.
Auntie, I'm sorry. [CRIES]
If I had known
this would happen,
I wouldn't have gone
to see Samuel. [SOBS]
Something bad always happens
when I'm around.
F-First, King got kidnapped,
then--
Now this happened to Samuel.
[CRIES, SOBS]
Auntie, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Auntie.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
[CRIES, SOBS]
[BREATH QUIVERS]
[VOICE BREAKS] It's not you.
This isn't your fault, Arissa.
[CRYING, SOBBING]
It's the people who did this.
Those criminals!
Those monsters!
They took King! [SOBS]
They hurt your brother!
- Not you.
- [SOBS]
It's not your fault
so stop blaming yourself.
I raised Samuel
to be a fighter.
He'll get through this.
I know he will
get through this.
[CRIES, SOBS]
Once all this is over...
...he's coming home.
He'll come home to us.
We'll all come home together.
[WAILS, SOBS]
My son will come home.
[CRYING, SOBBING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Find out how he's doing.
I don't care
how much it costs.
We'll lose more
if Trinidad dies.
Got it?!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I was just thinking...
if Samuel saved Enzo...
then what was
the shooter's motive?
Could've been a robber, bro.
It's dangerous these days.
There's so much evil
in the world.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Doc, how is he?
He's going to be fine.
We'll take him to the
recovery room for monitoring.
Excuse me.
Arissa, where's his family?
Why don't you go see Enzo?
Try to find a way to contact
his parents when he wakes up.
- Go on.
- Alright.
Keep me posted about Samuel.
Arissa.
Address him with respect.
He's your older brother,
so you should address him
respectfully.
Okay.
I hope...
...Samuel gets better.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAEL SIGHS SHARPLY]
[PHONE RINGING]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Hello?
What is it now, Roldan?!
You just tried to impress me,
And now this?
Another problem?
And worse...
we might lose the
money completely!
You want that?!
Sir, we won't let that happen.
Sir, Jacob's already
making a move.
He won't let...
...Trinidad die.
[CHUCKLES WRYLY]
Damn it!
All talk, no action!
The person you should've
killed long ago...
...you're now desperate
to save?!
Why?!
Because he
outsmarted you, huh?!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BANGS]
Enzo? Enzo?
Enzo?
Enzo!
What happened?
What's wrong with him?
Wait a minute!
I am his father!
- [NURSE] Sir, hold on.
- Tell me!
[NURSE] Please calm down, sir.
What happened to my son?
Sir, he was shot.
We're taking him to
the recovery room.
The patient requires
critical monitoring.
You're not allowed inside.
We're sorry.
Let's wait for the doctor's
further instructions.
He'll be transferred to
another room once he's stable.
Please stay here.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know, sometimes
dads really are a problem.
[ARISSA] What about your father?
Uh...
My father?
He's busy with work.
I think he has
forgotten about me.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
This Wednesday...
Samuel is in the hospital.
What are you doing here?
Are you mad at me?
I'm your father.
There was a man.
Enzo was his target.
But my brother was there.
What's your brother's name?
- Enzo was the target.
- I'll take care of it.
It's payback time.
Roldan knows now that
I tried to have his son killed.
He's going to retaliate.
- [GUNSHOTS]
- Run!