[GUNSHOT]
Rainier--
Who were those people
and why did they kill Rainier?
Because of your father!
Why don't you look for
Rainier's hard drive
from your father
so you'll know the truth?!
What do you need?
We can get the money!
That Johnny Policarpio was shot!
No one will follow me anymore.
We can finally get the money!
No, I'll do it!
Why you?
Because you're useless!
I'll get the money.
You clean it.
My secretary met an accident.
Unfortunately,
she didn't make it.
Do you have anyone
you can recommend
to be my new
executive assistant?
Our EA, Agnes.
I'm looking forward
to meeting this Agnes.
I see it, bro.
I'll attach it now.
All set, bro.
That damn Trinidad!
I'm sure he's sabotaging
the group!
Here's what you should do.
Find his car.
Put a tracker on it.
You heard that, bro?
He got you bugged.
And we can use that
to our advantage.
Hello, King!
King, this is my Grandpa Diego.
Grandpa, this is King.
He's my best friend.
Hi, King!
I am your Grandpa Diego
and I am very,
very glad to meet you.
Really?
Can you be my grandpa?
Of course!
You can also be my grandson.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't know if you knew,
but Leah is my daughter.
And I just recently
found out that...
...the two of you had a child.
Anyway,
my offer still stands.
Especially now that I learned
your son is my grandchild.
So, I believe
it would be best
if you tell me what you know
about your bosses.
General, is this true?
You are Jacob Rivera's
father-in-law?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Because, General...
I don't know anything
about what you're saying.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
You don't need
to get worked up, Samuel.
I'm just worried
about my grandson.
That's all.
And I also have one request.
Please allow me
to be close to my grandson.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You don't need
to tell him the truth.
Just let me be his grandpa.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
General, the truth is...
...I'm angry.
I'm angry at Leah.
Because she left us.
I don't know why.
I don't know where she went.
And now suddenly
she comes back into our lives?
Then I find out
I never really knew her at all.
I didn't even know
you were her father.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
General, I want to tell you
that I don't want to.
I don't want to grant
your request.
But I saw your connection
with my son.
With his sister and with Leah.
My son is happy now.
And I don't want
to take that away from him.
So fine.
I'll agree.
But I have one request.
Please don't tell him
the truth yet.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm looking for the right time
to tell him everything.
To tell him...
...that his mother
didn't really die.
That the truth is...
...she abandoned him.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's all I ask.
Don't tell him the truth yet.
Thank you, Samuel.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KNOCKS]
Sir, Agnes is here.
[JACOB] Yes. Thank you, Bekkah.
Uh, sir? You called for me?
Yes, Agnes.
Starting today,
you will no longer be working
here at Oriental Ridge.
S-Sir?
Why? Am I being fired?
Did I do something wrong?
Nothing like that.
I'm just transferring you
to General Ramirez.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
To General Ramirez?
Yes.
He's looking
for an executive assistant.
And since you're good,
I recommended you.
You know General Ramirez?
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Of course.
He's my father-in-law.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DIEGO]
I don't know if you knew,
but Leah is my daughter.
And I just recently found out
that the two of you
had a child.
My offer still stands.
Tell me what you know
about your bosses.
[SAMUEL] Diego Ramirez
is a scam buster.
And his son-in-law
is a scammer?
How could this happen?
And Leah doesn't know?
What are you staring at?
Nothing.
You're the one staring.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE BUZZING]
Hello, bro.
[MAEL]
Bro! Jacob's car is moving.
This might be
what we've been waiting for.
Alright, bro. Thanks.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEEPING]
You're done for.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TRACKER BEEPING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[GATE CREAKS OPEN]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're an idiot, Trinidad.
You couldn't do
one simple thing.
[DUFFEL BAGS THUD]
[CABINET DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[MAEL] Wow! Looking good!
Bro, are you sure about this?
Don't worry, bro.
This is insured, just in case
you want to wreck this.
And I switched the license plate
with a fake one.
[BANGING]
[KEYS CLINK]
Okay. Bro, thank you.
Take care, bro.
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE STARTS, REVS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DUFFEL BAGS THUD]
[TRUNK DOOR CLOSES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE STARTS, REVS]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS, REVS]
[SAMUEL] Tonight, you'll
experience real sabotage.
After tonight,
even your own brother...
...won't trust you anymore.
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE RUMBLES]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROLDAN]
This isn't the bathroom.
Didn't Enzo tell you?
Uh, Pa, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ARISSA]
You don't believe me?
Why don't you try to find
where your father
hid Rainier's hard drive
and discover the truth
for yourself?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES UNSETTLING]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUNSHOT]
[ARISSA] They killed Rainier!
They killed Rainier!
They killed him!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SOBBING]
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
[SNIFFLES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Enzo?
What are you doing here?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
How did you get this? Huh?
Answer me!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What?
What's in there?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Does it...
contain a picture of my mother?
[SCOFFS]
No.
Enzo!
Didn't I tell you not
to touch my stuff?
What part of that don't you
understand? It's very simple!
Don't touch my stuff!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is there anything else
you want to say? Huh?
Why are you
still standing there?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING]
[GUNSHOT]
- [MUFFLED SCREAMING]
- Arissa, be quiet.
[ARISSA SOBBING]
They killed Rainier!
They killed him!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING]
You're letting their praises
get to your head.
If you don't do well,
they'll send you to Cambodia.
You're a criminal, Pa.
You were the reason
why Mama died.
We need to
make him realize
that he has no one
to rely on except me.
The tempest that will
bring down the thieves
is already
lying in wait.
Idiot! Do you want
to get killed?
Why are you
still standing there?