- [THWACKS]
- [GROANS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [COUGHS]
- [THWACKS]
- [GROANS]
Our men intercepted it.
We'll find out where
our money is with this.
His father fooled me.
So I should kill him myself.
- [YELPS]
- [GRUNTS]
Sir! Let go of him!
My credit card got declined.
I tried to withdraw some money,
but it got declined too.
I heard that
the government will freeze
all accounts under
your dad's name.
I'm trapped here.
I love you, dear.
I trust you.
Thanks, Ma.
- Give me your bag!
- Help!
- Help me! Aah!
- Give me that!
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [CRASH]
[THUD]
I think this is yours, miss.
You think?
How about you help me
stand up?
This is you, right?
I have nothing to do with
that, if that's what you mean.
You benefited from it.
You helped me,
but you judged my character.
That amount of money can make
people kill each other.
What if they kill you?
What about your son?
What about King?
What's taking you so long
to find that damn seed phrase?
Even Mike's son doesn't have
access to the crypto wallet.
You're Mike Trinidad's
daughter!
She's the daughter of Mike
Trinidad, the scammer!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Miss, wait!
Don't be scared.
Perfect timing.
I just finished making adobo.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[PLATE CLINKS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
She eats a lot.
What a glutton. Don't they
feed her at home?
She got held at the airport
on her flight back to America.
The government froze
all Papa's accounts,
so she couldn't access
her allowance from Papa.
She hasn't eaten a proper meal
since yesterday.
Your dad is unbelievable!
Think about it.
He provided for his other
family, but left us starving.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where will she stay, huh?
Ma, she doesn't have
a family here.
- You mean she's staying here?
- We can't abandon her.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I want to kill your father
over and over again.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Who are you?
What about you?
I live here, so I should be
asking you that.
Sorry. I don't talk
to strangers.
You know, you're weird.
But I like you.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[ARISSA] Well...
I kind of like you too.
My name is Arissa,
but you can call me Ari.
I'm King.
Ow! Ouch!
Why is your hair
so messy?
And your hands are dirty too.
You look filthy.
[ARISSA LAUGHS]
You're so cute.
[ARISSA] And smart, too.
How old are you?
- I'm seven.
- Seven?
I thought you were
30 years old.
Seriously?
[ARISSA CHUCKLES]
Have you eaten?
- Um... Not yet.
- Oh, not yet?
- Well, let's eat.
- Look at her.
She's taking my grandson
away from me.
Ma, come on.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
She's Ellen's daughter.
Ellen was your dad's mistress
when he left us.
He left us for that
Miss Caloocan.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I've accepted the fact
that your dad abandoned us.
And that he cheated on me.
But Samuel, bringing that girl
to my house...
reminds me of the pain
your father caused me.
I'm sorry, okay?
It's...
[SOBBING] It's hard for me
to process this.
[LOLITA SOBBING]
Ma.
But okay then.
[SNIFFLES] She can stay here.
I won't make her leave
because I'm not like her mom,
who is a bad woman
and a flirt.
You mean Miss Caloocan?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Stop it. Say that again
and I'll hit you, Samuel.
I'm just kidding.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's okay. It's okay.
- [MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING]
[NORLAN] Dear.
[ECG MACHINE BEEPING RAPIDLY]
- Nurse!
- Call for help!
Nurse! Nurse!
[NURSE] Excuse me,
ma'am and sir.
- Where's the doctor?
- Call the doctor.
Call him now!
[NORLAN] Mikay.
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ECG MACHINE BEEPING RAPIDLY]
- Mikay.
- Please move aside.
[NORLAN] Mikay, dear.
Please be strong.
Doc!
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ECG MACHINE BEEPING RAPIDLY]
[DOCTOR] Her condition
is getting worse.
[MILDRED SOBS]
I don't think we can
wait for four months.
She has to undergo surgery
within the week.
[MILDRED SOBS]
Excuse me.
- [MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MILDRED SOBBING]
Love, what are we
going to do?
[SOBS] I told you not to invest
all our money in that fund.
That way, we'll still have
some money left
instead of having nothing.
- [MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ECG MACHINE BEEPING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Is the room comfortable?
Yeah. It's comfy.
Don't worry.
I won't be here long.
Stay as long as you need.
You're welcome here.
You're my sister.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Thanks.
Alright then. I'll--
I'll buy some supplies.
If you need anything,
just let me know, okay?
Even to King.
Looks like you two
have become close already.
I'll go now.
And... your mom?
She's nice.
Don't worry.
I'll go now.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir, good news.
We already know
where the money is.
We also have the laptop
which is the key to getting it.
[MAN] That's good news only
when you actually get the money.
Until then,
there is no good news!
You're still a failure!
It was under your watch
when Mike got that money.
The person you trusted.
You did this, Roldan!
You! So you fix this!
Roldan, what do you
want me to do?
Mike's son...
We can't let him
access it.
He can't beat us to it.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
[ENGINE HUMMING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GATE SQUEAKING]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[LOLITA] Are you back?
You've already bought it?
[ARISSA]
Hey! Wait for me!
Don't cheat!
[KING] Chase me, Auntie!
Chase me!
Catch!
- King!
- Stay back!
- No! Don't!
- [MAN] Be quiet!
I'm begging you!
Don't hurt the boy!
[MAN] Be quiet, or I'll
blow his head off.
[LOLITA SOBS]
No! Please don't! [SOBS]
Don't hurt my grandson!
Don't hurt him!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR ENGINE STOPS]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GATE DOOR SCRAPING, RATTLING]
[METAL RATTLES]
[PAPER, PLASTIC RUSTLING]
- [FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [PAPER, PLASTIC RUSTLING]
[METAL RATTLING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES UNSETTLING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GLASS CLINKING]
[GLASS CLINKS]
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
[GLASS CLINKING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUTTERING]
Please don't hurt us!
[MUFFLED SOBBING]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[MAN] Hey! Don't move!
- I said don't move!
- Hold on!
Please calm down.
Please let's talk
about this calmly.
I don't know what you want,
but please,
let's not resort to violence.
Please leave
my family out of this.
[SOBS]
[MUFFLED SOBBING]
- You want to save your son?
- [SOBBING CONTINUES]
I need to save my child too!
Give me back all the money!
Give it back!
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
[SAMUEL] Calm down.
You might accidentally
pull the trigger.
Please don't point it
at the kid.
Point it at me!
Please!
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
You monsters!
You and your father!
Monsters!
If this is about
what my father did,
I had nothing to do with it!
I had nothing to do--
- Liar!
- Listen to me!
My son didn't do
anything wrong to you.
- Let's talk about this calmly.
- [CHILD SOBBING]
- Please stop--
- That was supposed to pay
for Mika's surgery.
But you stole it!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
My child's going to die,
but I can't do anything!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING CONTINUES]
Because of you and your father!
Please--
Bro, please listen to me.
If you think I did something
bad to you, fine.
Fine. I'll admit
I made a huge mistake.
You're a scam victim.
Your kid got caught in it.
That money was
for her surgery, right?
- Don't test my patience!
- Listen.
Hear me out.
You're putting the blame
on yourself now.
Your child shouldn't
have been dragged
into the mess you got involved.
I feel you, bro.
I regret it too.
Even my child's
getting affected.
That's why I'm begging you.
Please. I'm begging you.
If you need someone to blame,
blame me.
- Blame me.
- [SOBBING CONTINUES]
Don't make the kids pay
for their father's mistakes.
Bro, please.
Put the blame on me.
Please, let's settle this
between the two of us.
Please stop
pointing the gun at him.
Point it at me.
Please, point it at me.
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING CONTINUES]
[NORLAN WAILING]
[SAMUEL, NORLAN
GRUNTING LOUDLY]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS LOUDLY]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [GRUNTING LOUDLY]
[SQUEALS]
[SAMUEL, NORLAN GRUNT]
That's my son!
They're my family!
- [NORLAN WAILS]
- [SAMUEL GRUNTING LOUDLY]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS LOUDLY]
[GRUNTS]
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
Are you okay? Ma?
Dear, are you okay?
[TENSE MUSIC FADING]
[COUGHING, GAGGING]
[NORLAN GRUNTS, GROANING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
You bastard.
You and your father
will rot in hell.
[GROANS LOUDLY]
Untie me.
[BREATHES SHARPLY,
GROANING LOUDLY]
I tied you up
so we could talk calmly.
We have nothing to talk about.
You're a fraud.
Let me go!
[GRUNTS LOUDLY]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
I said let me go!
[SAMUEL] "Norlan Gonzales."
I know you're not a bad guy.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[NORLAN BREATHING HEAVILY]
Your gun's fake.
You had no intention
of hurting my child.
I really can't point
a real gun at a kid.
I know.
I understand why you did that.
You're a desperate father,
trying to save his child.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
But please believe me.
My father left us
when I was just a kid.
That's why
I had no idea what he did.
[SNIFFLING]
I'm already tied up.
The police are on their way.
Why are you still lying to me?
No one's coming.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
But I hope...
...you don't do that again.
I'm tired of defending myself
all over again
just to prove I'm innocent.
So next time...
[SNIFFLES]
...I won't even try
to understand you.
You understand?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
How much did my father
steal from you?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
One hundred twenty
thousand pesos.
[ARISSA]
Samuel!
What are you doing?!
Why are you giving him money?!
After what he did?!
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Idiot! Stupid!
- Let's go. That's enough.
- So stupid!
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[SNIFFS]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I had nothing to
do with what he did.
But...
it still weighs on me if...
something happens to your
child because of my father.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Take this.
"One Hundred Twenty Thousand
Pesos Only"
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't have a job right now,
so...
believe me,
I need that money too.
So take it.
Before I change my mind.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Go ahead.
Maybe...
...you're not like your father
after all.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry.
[SNIFFLES]
[DOOR OPENS]
- [SNIFFLING]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
[SNIFFLES]
[SAMUEL] Son...
How are you?
I'm okay.
But I got scared earlier,
Dad.
Very scared.
Did you get hurt?
Just a little.
But it's okay.
Because like what
Aunt Arissa said,
I'm a big boy now.
I'm strong.
- Yes.
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
You are very strong.
Son...
I'm so sorry
about what happened.
Daddy will make sure...
that will never happen again.
I know.
But, Dad, even though
I got scared earlier,
I knew we would be saved.
I knew you would come.
Because you're always there
for us, right?
You won't leave us.
I won't leave you, son.
Never.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Love, why did he give you
that money?
Do you think he'll ask
for something in return?
No.
All he wanted was
for me to believe...
that he wasn't involved
in his father's scheme.
Do you think
he was telling the truth?
Next.
I think...
what matters is we get money
for our daughter's surgery.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Oh, sir.
- [CLAPS]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[BEEPS]
Jaguar Six,
Eagle Two is coming.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you doing your job properly?
Don't waste your time
watching nonsense stuff.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Oh.
So, have you cracked
the seed phrase yet?
Uh, sir...
- We are 80% done.
- Hmm.
We're just checking the files
on the laptop one by one.
Sir...
We just need more time.
[SCOFFS]
You need more time?
How much more time
do you need, huh?
You've been working on that
for so long.
Or maybe...
you need a little push.
Sir...
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
You're here for a reason.
Right?
You're getting paid
a lot here, right?
Stop disappointing me.
You wouldn't want
to get me upset.
- Get back to work.
- Sorry, sir.
- Alright.
- We'll work faster.
I want results today.
Do you understand?
Today! [CLAPS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAMUEL] Is this just a clue
to help me find the laptop?
Or is there another reason
why you sent this to me?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
Nice picture.
[MUG CLINKS]
- Sorry I called you an idiot.
- [LIQUID POURING]
It's just that...
it wasn't your fault,
so why did you have to pay him?
It's not even
your responsibility.
Plus, you're unemployed, right?
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I didn't want
his child to die...
just because of what
was done by my father.
Our father.
Well, I never really knew him.
Dad.
I was 12 years old when
Mommy and I moved to the US.
But even before that,
I didn't see Dad often either.
He and Mommy separated
when I was eight.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Because he was always away.
I was seven when
he and Mama separated.
Looks like Daddy's behavior
had a pattern.
He left his kids early on.
That way, he wouldn't
grow to love them.
Kids could get in the way
of his affairs, you know.
But sometimes,
I'm still wondering.
Did Daddy ever love me or...
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Did he keep giving me
financial support
because he really cared for me?
Or was his secretary just
really good at her job?
I guess I'll never find out.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
Our technicians have been
thoroughly searching
the laptop, but...
they still can't crack
the seed phrase.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[ROLDAN] Jacob.
Mike left that laptop
for his son.
It contains the instructions
on how to access the wallet.
Tell your technicians...
to look harder!
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
Jacob.
We can't let him
get ahead of us.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
About the picture
you're looking at,
is that your favorite?
Not really.
Why?
It's kind of pixelated.
Seems like the file
is corrupted.
Maybe you should rescan it.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SAMUEL] The picture
in his house is clear.
But this one has errors.
Could something be hidden?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[LAPTOP BEEPING RAPIDLY]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I...
I.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ivory.
Ivory...
L.
T.
Lizard.
Okay.
Ocean.
What comes next?
Come on!
What's next?!
Come on, what's next?!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on.
This is a seed phrase...
Yeah!
This is it. This is it.
This is the seed phrase.
Okay. What comes next?
[SNIFFLES]
Come on.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
"Where..."
"Money..."
"You..."
"First..."
"Value."
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
"Where did you first learn
the value of money?"
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Where did you first learn
the value of money?
[STIRRING MUSIC SWELLS]
Out of twelve,
he only gave me three.
He left a clue to find
the next ones.
Money is power.
Pressure Samuel Trinidad
and his family.
Don't leave him alone
until he releases the money.
His enemies will
spy on him.
The CEO is waiting for you
inside for your interview.
You're my new
asset manager.
Our new barista, Arissa.
Enzo.
- You again?
- Are you stalking me?
It's like you're bringing
a snake into our territory.
Miss?
Who are you flirting with
in the office? Who?!
The people's anger
is about to erupt
into violence.
I only know one thing.
He can't beat us to it.
He needs to die.