You're Enzo's dad?
Yes, I am.
We were with him
when he was shot.
Who did this to my son?
There was a man.
It looked like Enzo
was his target.
But my brother was there.
He fought with the gunman,
but he was shot too.
What's your brother's name?
Samuel Trinidad.
Have you heard?
Heard what?
Trinidad was shot.
Huh?
We just confirmed last night
that his son was kidnapped
by a scammer.
And now he was shot?
Unbelievable.
What are you doing here?
Came to visit Samuel?
Our other officemates
are coming.
Liar.
I killed his fellow scammers.
So when he wakes up,
tell him to watch out.
He might be next.
Enzo was shot?!
What happened?!
Enzo was the target,
but Trinidad was hit too.
Who would do this?
Who do you think?!
Who else could've done this?
Diaz!
Tell me what I need to do.
Take him down!
Leave it to me.
Roldan knows that
I ordered his son to be killed.
He's going to retaliate.
[GUNSHOTS]
Get him!
- [KICK, BLOW LAND]
- [GUN CLATTERS]
- [FLESH SQUELCHES]
- [GROANS]
- [FLESH SQUELCHING]
- [LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
The surgery is done.
He lost a lot of blood.
We'll do everything we can
for him to recover.
Daddy?
Thank goodness!
I was so scared, Daddy!
I thought you were
going to leave me.
I told you,
I'm not going anywhere.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Miss Lolita?
- Hmm?
I'm going home.
Oh, okay.
Just give me a call
if you need anything.
Yes. Thank you.
- Thank you, too.
- Take care.
[AGNES] How do you feel?
You scared me there.
Are you hungry, son?
Are you in pain?
Ma, I'm okay.
Don't worry.
Get well soon, Samuel, okay?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Enzo.
[EXHALES LOUDLY]
Samuel.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
He's my father.
I know him, son.
He works for me.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you very much
for saving my son, Samuel.
You're welcome, Sir Roldan.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You are...
my son's boss?
Yes, ma'am.
[ARISSA ON CALL]
Auntie, King is missing.
What?!
[KING ON VIDEO]
Help me! Save me!
Dad, help me!
[PAENG] Maybe it's
one of your father's victims.
No. Those people are desperate
but not evil.
A criminal did this.
Only Roldan and Jacob
could've done this.
I'm glad you were able to visit.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
By the way,
don't worry about
your hospital bill.
I'll cover it.
Sir...
Sir, that won't be necessary.
No. I insist.
[PAENG] Auntie.
Let's step outside.
Excuse us. We'll leave you
two alone to talk.
Let's go, Auntie.
Come on, Auntie. Let's go!
[MAEL] Let's go, Auntie.
Ma.
Samuel, we'll be outside.
Come on, Auntie.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't know how
I could repay you
for what you did
for my son.
I don't know what I would do
if I lost him.
I know how it feels...
to almost lose your son.
I know exactly how it feels,
sir.
My son was kidnapped.
Enzo helped me find him.
That's why
when I saw Enzo in danger,
I didn't think twice.
I did what I had to.
For that, Samuel,
I can't thank you enough.
Sir, I would do it again.
Not because he's your son,
or because
he's my sister's friend.
Sir, Enzo is like family to me.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIQUID SLOSHING]
[LIQUID TRICKLING]
[PLASTIC CONTAINER THUDS]
[LIGHTER CLICKS]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Samuel, what did
that jerk tell you?
Dear...
[WHISPERS] King is here.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh, King, do you want
some ice cream?
- Yes!
- Come, let's buy some.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
That monster!
He kidnapped my grandson!
The nerve of him to offer
to pay your hospital bills!
What for? Did he think he could
bribe us?
[PAENG] Fortunately, I was
able to stop Auntie.
Roldan would've ended up
in a hospital bed too.
Oh, that's for sure!
And to think he has a son!
How could he stomach taking
other people's children?
Does Enzo know
what his father does?
I don't think so, Auntie.
They're not on good terms.
It's because his father
is evil.
He's not close with his dad.
That's why he works two jobs
to support himself.
[SAMUEL] Arissa.
Don't tell Enzo
what you've found out.
I'm sure that he's unaware
of his father's crimes.
Of course.
It's just going to be hard
because he's my friend.
I don't like keeping secrets.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Dear, what's your plan now?
What are you going to do?
[INHALES DEEPLY, SIGHS]
Ma, I think it'd
be best...
if you don't know
about it.
I'll take care of it.
Just trust me.
I hope you understand.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE HUMMING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Roldan.
Any news?
[SNICKERS]
It's done.
I didn't just crush them.
I turned them to ashes.
Great.
[LEAH] Hey!
What happened?
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
Daddy!
- What took you so long?
- Hi. Darling, come here.
[GRUNTS]
I'm sorry. I had a lot
to finish at work.
But I'll make it up to you.
I'm sorry.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hon, what happened here?
[GROANS] Argh!
- [JACOB GRUNTING]
- [FLESH SQUELCHING]
Must be the shaving.
Yeah. It's okay.
It's just a small cut.
Be careful next time, okay?
Yeah. Come on.
Let's get your ice cream.
- Come on, hon.
- Mmm!
- Ice cream!
- What flavor?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Chloe--
- [LOLITA GASPS]
[JACOB] Darling, here you go.
Hon.
Who is it?
Um...
I just thought I saw someone.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's go.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What time
did the incident happen?
Around 10 in the morning.
Did you recognize the gunman?
I fought him
for his gun, but...
I didn't recognize him.
Have you been receiving
any death threats?
Have you gotten into
a fight recently,
aside from the ones
happening to you
and your family currently?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I can't think of any.
How's your father's case going?
The investment scam?
Has it been resolved?
I don't know.
I don't have any updates.
Weren't you involved
in his transactions?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I had nothing to do with that.
You are one tough cookie.
So glad you're okay.
Thanks, Auntie.
We live in dangerous times, huh?
What if you stay
with your dad for now?
Auntie, I'm fine staying
in my condo.
Fine.
If you don't want to live
with your dad,
why don't you
stay with us first?
Honestly, Auntie...
I'm okay.
Enzo, don't be stubborn.
Let us take care of you.
Pa, Auntie...
I appreciate your concerns...
but this time,
trust me on this.
I'm all grown up.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
If you were to ask me,
I'd assume you got
into a fight with someone.
Maybe one of your father's
scam victims
or one of your victims.
They're the ones
who might have a motive.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Is this still about
the shooting?
Your line of questioning
sounds a bit odd.
Relax, this is just the routine.
I'm just asking some--
It sounds like
you're accusing me of something.
I'm just doing my job,
Mr. Trinidad.
But if you are hiding something,
you can tell us now.
It's a waste of an opportunity.
Are you finished?
If you are, you can go
so that I can rest.
Unless you want to suggest
that I'm involved in the scam?
I don't have any more questions.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I don't know, but I feel like
there's some distance
between Enzo and his dad.
By the way, hon,
you said someone helped Enzo?
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
Well, I want to meet him.
Uh, I just wanted to thank him.
Do you know
what his room number is?
He's resting.
They thanked him
a while ago.
He's asleep.
Chloe.
Let's go.
Come on.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma?
- Ma? Are you okay?
- Hmm?
It looks like
you've seen a ghost.
I'm okay.
Do I not look okay?
You look very serious.
It's nothing.
It's just...
Hi, Sir Samuel.
The doctor signed
your discharge papers.
You're free to go home.
- Oh, thank goodness.
- Yay!
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SOBBING]
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- What's going on?
- Sir.
We have another
missing person.
He was recruited
as a programmer.
And then he suddenly vanished.
How long has it been
since your son left?
[SNIFFLING]
Around six months, sir.
At first...
he would constantly update me.
He would always send me
his paycheck.
But we would only talk
through messages.
Whenever I try to call him,
he won't answer.
How long has it been
since you two last talked?
[SOBBING]
It's been 3 weeks, sir.
I have a bad feeling about this.
My son would never do that.
Miss, come here.
Let's look over here.
[SNIFFLING]
Not to scare you
or anything, miss.
But we've been getting a lot
of missing person cases.
They all suddenly vanished
after accepting a job offer.
As you can see,
most of the missing men
are programmers.
As for the women,
they're mostly models.
We think they're victims
of human trafficking.
[SOBBING] My poor son...
- [SNIFFLING, SOBBING]
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
But don't worry, miss.
I'll help you
find your son, okay?
Thank you so much, sir.
You are heaven-sent.
I'll go now, sir. [SNIFFLES]
[SAMUEL] Roldan is also
targeting fellow criminals.
A lot of money is at stake,
so they're all ready to fight.
Dude, this situation
has gone overboard.
Are you sure you want to
infiltrate Roldan's group?
[MAEL] Yeah, dude.
You might...
end up with more than just
some bruises and a bullet wound.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe you can...
get some of the money and use it
to hire a hitman for those two.
100 million might be enough
as a reward.
[SAMUEL]
I doubt that would work.
Their operations
have a huge reach.
There is someone
bigger in charge.
Even if those two disappears,
someone will replace them.
Which means their schemes
will have no end.
This will only work
in their favor.
Because we won't know
who'll replace them.
That's true.
So dudes,
even if it's dangerous,
I need to finish my mission.
I need to uncover
all their secrets.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
What I am offering you
is a chance for a fresh start.
Help me.
Clean your name.
You didn't just risk your life
for someone.
And I will be forever
grateful to you.
Sir, I see you all
as my family.
Now I'm worried about
what you're planning to do.
We just received
an initial order.
They need to conduct
- an audit at Oriental Ridge.
- What?!
This is our only way to get
enough evidence against them.
Sins of the Father.