I want to prove to my father
that I can do it.
Sorry, I'm getting emotional.
Do you notice the patterns,
cuts, and designs?
They're the same as the ones
you see on the racks,
the same clothes
worn by female victims
of human trafficking.
That's not true! Cut that out!
Cut it!
That's a lie!
General Ramirez
is really my idol.
But General Ramirez said
he doesn't see the similarity.
After all these years,
he still can't accept
that I'm his son.
You're General Ramirez's son?
That jerk is my father.
You're still in denial?!
[DIGITAL TRILLING]
Mael!
Someone's trying
to enter our site.
[DIGITAL TRILLING]
Bro, they're about to catch us!
Uh, divert it right away!
[INAUDIBLE] ...server in Russia!
Huh?!
[DIGITAL TRILLING, BUZZING]
What's happened?!
Aah!
Aah! [GROANS]
- You bastard!
- Jacob.
- Jacob! Jacob!
Here's what we'll do.
You both want to fight, right?
Then go for a human cockfight.
You can kill each other
in that bloodbath.
But we have
to make money out of it.
- [GRUNTING]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
I need to beat Trinidad.
But I can't do that
with a useless sparring partner.
[GRUNTING]
Ah!
Your fight's already hyped up.
People are just sharing the link
and spreading it
by word of mouth.
But so many
are installing the app.
So many bets on you guys.
Eighteen million dollars?
Be careful in that fight
with Jacob, okay?
I'm sure Jacob
isn't going to fight fair.
He'll make sure you lose,
maybe even get killed.
This is his shot to make you
disappear from his path
and from Bakunawa.
As long as my mission
isn't finished,
that won't happen.
If I die,
I'll make sure they fall,
that they never rise again.
I'll make sure of it.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Samuel, what is this?!
This is you, right?!
And your opponent
is Jacob Rivera?!
- Arissa, quiet!
- Answer me--
- Arissa, keep it down!
- [STIFLED SCREAM]
[SAMUEL] Mama might hear you.
- [ARISSA] Oh my god.
- Keep quiet.
Oh my god, Samuel!
- So, it's true?!
- Arissa.
You'll fight Jacob Rivera
to the death!
- Arissa.
- Shut up!
- What if you die?!
- I won't die.
And how can you be so sure?!
Arissa, I already promised you
that I won't die as long
as my mission isn't over.
Are you a psychic or something?!
What makes you so sure?!
Arissa.
They're close to falling apart.
But for now,
I just need to roll
with their games
and to entertain them.
When the time comes,
they won't even realize
what hit them.
[ARISSA SOBS]
I'm sure it'll happen
very soon, okay?
[ARISSA SOBBING]
Arissa.
Everything will be fine.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[ARISSA SOBS, SNIFFLES]
- [SOBBING, SNIFFLING]
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELECTRIC BUZZ]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[ABEL CLICKS MOUTH]
This can't be happening.
I need to find a way.
They can't catch me.
[SWITCH CLICKS ON]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES STIRRING]
[ABEL] I don't know
who's attacking us.
But I need to hide all this.
No one must find out.
If they do,
this could be strong evidence
against me.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LEAH HUFFS]
Well?
Well, what?!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Turns out I have a brother.
When were you
planning to tell me?
I was not!
Because he's not important.
[LEAH SCOFFS]
Not important?
You kept that from me
all this time, Dad?
You kept it a secret!
Leah.
Cut it out
with all those secrets.
- Have you forgotten?
- Oh!
Oh, no.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
Don't you dare
turn this on me!
I came to you willingly
and told you my secret.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
Why don't you tell me, Dad?
Were you planning to take
this secret to your grave?
No.
I'm your daughter.
If he really is my brother,
I have the right
to know the truth.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay, fine!
I don't even know
if that person's really my son!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
His mother was a bar girl
I had a relationship with.
Oh, and that was before
I met your mom.
Then I got reassigned,
and we lost contact.
And that was it!
It was like just
another chapter in my life
I'd already forgotten.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
No.
Hmm...
Actually, it was more like...
just another
unimportant subplot.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I can't believe
you're saying this.
Now...
After two years,
she suddenly showed up again.
She introduced someone to me,
claiming it's my son.
Why would I waste my time
on a bar girl's son?
Even if he says he idolizes you?
Oh! [LAUGHS]
Good for him!
At least he has someone
to look up to!
Do I have to be
a part of his life?!
Listen to me, Leah.
Stop wasting
your time and energy...
on someone like him.
Do you understand?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LEAH] Why do all the men
around me have so many secrets?
And you, Dad.
If you can't even tell me
something like this,
what bigger secret
are you still keeping from me?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[REPORTERS] General,
we have a few questions!
Just a moment, General!
General, we just have
some important questions!
General Ramirez,
please answer our questions!
Is it true that PO2
Johnny Policarpio is your son?
What's your reaction
to his statement?
How come he's your son?
I will not dignify that
with a reaction.
Because it's totally ridiculous.
[REPORTER] General, there's
a video of you two together!
- Wait, General!
- Please answer our questions!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir.
It's okay.
[SULLEN MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
Dad, I want the same haircut
as yours.
You want the same haircut
as mine?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Hmm?
Why did you suddenly decide
to have King get a haircut?
No particular reason, Ma.
I just wanted to
spend time with King.
It's our bonding time.
Right, son?
Yes, Dad.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SAMUEL] Son...
I'll come back to you.
Nothing bad will happen
to Daddy.
That's a promise.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Samuel.
Ma?
Is there a problem, son?
No, Ma.
None at all.
Are you sure?
Yes, Ma.
- [UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MAN 1] Hey, dude.
I already placed a bet
on Light Saber.
[MAN 1 CHUCKLES]
The minimum spend
is only 50 pesos.
Even if you don't have
that much money,
you can still place a bet.
You're right, dude.
[MAN 2] Good thing I placed a
bet on Light Saber yesterday.
A lot of people are
betting on him, too.
The amount of bets on him
is almost equal
to that on Shadow Striker.
And guess what, dude?
They both have 1.8 now.
- [MAN 1] 1.8?
- We're going to win big!
[MAN 2 CHUCKLES]
How about you, sir?
Have you placed a bet?
If you want, I can send you
the download link of the app.
I heard they're going
to fight to the death, sir.
- What's that? Let me see--
- I don't gamble.
Mama doesn't like it. Right?
Of course.
Especially since you said
they would fight to the death.
Only criminals would do
something like that.
You shouldn't get yourselves
involved in that!
My goodness.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
They would fight to the death?
That's crazy.
Alright, King, he's going
to cut your hair now.
Okay.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
There's a lot of money riding
on Samuel and Jacob's match.
So far, the total bets
have reached five billion.
And before the game
starts later,
it will probably double.
[MOUTH CLICKS]
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
And while the match is ongoing,
the betting will still be open.
People can still place bets
based on what's happening.
If Samuel is winning,
they can place
their bets on him.
If Samuel is losing,
they can place
their bets on Jacob.
They'll keep placing bets
on their pick
in order to win bigger.
Or...
they'll bet on the opponent
to recover their losses.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is addictive.
Exactly!
We can get the amount
we need for Crown Madera
just from this event alone.
I told you, General,
human cockfight can be
a big revenue stream.
So, let us push through
with this!
We can make this
a regular event.
No.
Samuel already explained
why we can't do that.
And my decision stands.
Just focus on
those pesky hackers who've
been sabotaging our operations.
Alright, General.
I almost caught them.
I won't let them get away again.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Good.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNICKERS]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Johnny?
- Hmm?
- You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just...
I just want him to accept me.
I want him to see
that I'm good too.
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
But that bastard,
no matter what I do...
[SOBS, BREATH SHAKING]
No matter what I do,
I'm still trash...
Just trash in his eyes.
[AGNES SIGHS DEEPLY]
- [GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING]
[WATER TRICKLING]
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLING]
[BREATH QUIVERS]
[SNIFFLES]
- [GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SNIFFLING, SOBBING CONTINUES]
Babe! Here's the
porridge you asked for!
Agnes.
Guess you don't need
me anymore, huh?
- She'll take care of you now.
- Agnes.
Agnes.
Agnes!
Babe!
- Johnny!
- Agnes!
Babe, come on, let's go!
You're just drunk!
- Agnes!
- Babe!
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
- You okay?
- Agnes!
Want me to clean you up?
I'm fine. Just leave me.
Please... just leave me.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[BELL CHIMES, DOORS OPEN]
Hey, Benj! Hurry up.
What's that?
If Sir Luke sees you...
- What are you even watching?
- Oh, look.
I bet fifty pesos
on Light Saber.
Should I add more?
What the?!
"HUMAN COCKFIGHT:
LIGHT SABER VS. SHADOW STRIKER"
No way.
Get that phone away from me.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Benj, what's that?
- Let me see.
- Look.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's Samuel, he's
joining the human cockfight.
His life's in danger
again, Enzo.
[MUSIC BECOMES DRAMATIC]
Arissa, that's--
That's Uncle Jacob, isn't it?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
What the hell are you
planning this time, Pa?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CROWD CHEERING, CLAPPING]
- [INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CHEERING CONTINUES]
[MAN 1] Whoo!
- [MAN 2] Come on!
- [MAN 3] Fight!
- Go, go, go!
- Bring it on!
- [CHEERING CONTINUES]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MEN WHOOPING, CLAPPING]
[MALE HOST]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the night
we've all been waiting for
is finally here!
The fight of the century!
One time only!
Lightsaber versus Shadow Strike!
Human Cockfight!
- [CROWD CHEERING, CLAPPING]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHISTLING, LOUD CHEERING]
- [CHEERING, WHISTLING]
[MALE HOST]
In just a few more minutes,
we will witness
the no-holds-barred
fight-to-the-death match
between Lightsaber
and Shadow Strike!
- [CHEERING, CLAPPING]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PAENG] Man,
sorry we can't make it.
[MAEL] Sorry, bro.
You don't have anyone
in your corner.
I'm sure Jacob's with Roldan.
It's fine, guys.
You're still
supporting me anyway.
Just watch me, okay?
[PAENG] Alright, good luck.
You can do it.
[MAEL] Be careful, bro.
Alright, guys.
Thank you.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SIGHS SHARPLY]
[PHONE RINGING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hello?
[OLD MAN] Samuel.
I just placed a big bet
on you again.
Actually, it's even bigger
than my last bet on you.
So...
Make me proud.
And make me a lot of money.
Remember...
you're my guy in this fight.
Alright, sir.
I will not disappoint you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROLDAN] Remember our strategy.
Don't be intimidated.
[PHONE BUZZING]
"OLD MAN"
[BUZZING CONTINUES]
Sir.
Jacob!
Good luck on your fight.
Thank you.
You really need it.
Because just so you know...
my bet will beat you
to a pulp.
[SCOFFS]
Really, sir?
You called just to tell me that?
You think I wouldn't know, huh?
You recommended Agnes
to work for me
knowing full well that
her husband's a cop.
Are you really throwing me
under the bus, Jacob?
Sir, no.
I didn't think--
Oh, really?
Enough!
I don't want to hear
your excuses.
Now, I want you
to keep this in mind:
While you're on that ring,
I'll be rooting
for your opponent.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINISTER LAUGHTER]
[BREATHING DEEPLY
IN FRUSTRATION]
Come here. Get up, Jacob.
Quit thinking about
pointless things.
Give me your hand.
Take a deep breath.
- Relax.
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
The old man's just
messing with your mind.
Remember, you shouldn't waste
your energy on him.
He's probably just wagered a lot
in Samuel's favor.
Now, if you let that
get to you,
you will be beaten to a pulp
by Trinidad.
I will be the one
to beat him.
I'll make sure
that after tonight,
the old man will regret
betting on him.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SPECTATORS CHEERING]
[ANNOUNCER] Ten! Nine! Eight!
Seven! Six! Five! Four!
Three! Two! One!
And now, let's welcome
our first contender!
Standing at 170 centimeters,
weighing in at 160 pounds,
an expert in Jiu-jitsu,
Krav Maga,
Capoeira, Karate, Muay Thai,
Aikido, and boxing...
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's welcome Shadow Striker!
- [SPECTATORS CHEERING]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jacob.
Take out all you anger
towards Trinidad here.
Pour it all out here!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Shadow! Shadow! Shadow!
[ANNOUNCER]
And in the blue corner,
standing at 178 centimeters,
weighing in at 178 pounds,
and expert in Kali.
Yes! Just in Kali!
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's welcome...
Light Saber!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
- Saber! Saber! Saber!
[BLOW LANDS]
[TENSE, DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
You cheater!
Jacob's something else
for pulling such dirty moves.
I don't know
what you're saying.
It's Papa.
Place your bets.
Ten million for Sir Jacob.
- Five hundred million.
- For who?
Samuel!
Are you ready to fight
to the death?
It's starting.
...blood will spill in the pit.
Finish him!
- Jacob!
- [SCREAMING]