- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [METAL CLANKS]
Hey!
You reckless driver!
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
[GUNSHOT]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARING]
What's up, Jacob?
Sir, what happened here?
Someone hit my car
and shot my tire.
Stupid Jacob!
You're useless!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS IN PAIN]
If Samuel had handled it,
he could've gotten
through this situation
without having to call me
asking for help!
Aah!
I'll do it my way.
Human blood sport.
We'll kidnap players
and make them
fight to the death.
Our subscribers
will bet on them.
You bastard!
Don't you dare
invade my territory!
That's my best friend's uncle.
Idiot. He's the leader here.
If he's bold enough
to come here,
he must be confident
we won't be able
to get out of here.
I thought Papa and I
would finally make up.
I know what
you're going through is hard.
I know how it feels.
I want to help you and Samuel.
I want to put an end
to what Papa's doing.
General Ramirez
keeps a strict schedule.
I can only offer limited help.
But...
I'll still find a way.
Agnes, good luck
on your new assignment.
We have time for ice cream.
Would you like
to come along, King?
Monster! Monster!
I've lost my money
because of your stupidity!
Sir.
Trinidad,
we're on a phone call.
Sir, I have a proposal.
This is a game changer!
Let him speak!
Sir, once the casino
has been built,
it'll be easier to launder
not only our money
but also the money
of the other syndicates.
[CHUCKLING]
You really are clever,
Samuel Trinidad.
We think the same way, Trinidad.
You're truly my pawn.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
What happened?
Why did the old man
talk to him?!
That can't happen, Roldan!
You know that!
- [ROLDAN] I don't know.
- What?!
He's the old man's new pawn?
You know he can't get in!
- Don't let it happen!
- I don't know, Jacob!
I don't have control
over the old man, right?!
This is your fault! [HUFFS]
If you hadn't screwed up,
there wouldn't be a problem!
[JACOB] It's my fault again?!
Goddammit!
Tsk!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[AGNES] Ah...
Good morning, sir! I'm--
- Agnes Policarpio.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You were highly recommended.
Um, I'm looking forward
to working with you.
It's an honor, sir.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
- [UTENSILS CLINKING]
[SIGHS]
I want to go home, man.
Me too.
I wish I'd listened to Papa
and stayed away from that Abby.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm planning to escape.
But I can't do it alone.
It's possible
if we work together.
We'll come with you.
We'll do anything
just to get out of here.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
- [ROLDAN BREATHING SHAKILY]
Tsk.
[MOUTH CLICKS]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [PANICKED BREATHING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
"Enzo, how are you?
Please answer my call."
"Son, how are you?
Let's go have dinner."
"Let's talk. Are you okay?
Call me, please."
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LEAH GIGGLES]
- Hi, Mommy!
- Hi, darling!
- [KISSES] Hi, King!
- Hi, Miss Leah!
[KISSES]
How are you feeling?
Are you still having
panic attacks?
Not anymore, Miss Leah.
I'm okay.
That's good.
Do you know
why you had a panic attack?
I saw Xenon wearing a hoodie.
He reminded me of the one
who kidnapped me.
That's exactly how he looked.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LEAH] Oh my god!
Who did that to you?
Samuel Trinidad.
What?
Why would he do this?
I don't know. Samuel's crazy.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES STIRRING]
Welcome to--
Oh! It's you again!
Yes. Do you have any new stocks?
- For you, yes! [CHUCKLES]
- Okay. Same as before.
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
I've already cleaned up
the last batch of their money.
And while you're doing that,
they keep getting closer
to take over the casino
they're planning.
But on this day,
we claim a victory.
I spoke with the old man.
I barged into Roldan's office
while he and Jacob were talking
to the old man on the phone.
I pitched my casino idea to him.
But that's their plan
all along, right?
Yes. But they don't know
that Samuel knows about it.
Ah... Since you pitched that,
he'd feel you're both
on the same wavelength.
Right, man.
I made him feel
that I'm his pawn.
That's cool!
This is indeed
a great victory for us.
And I know that I impressed him.
I'm sure it's just
a matter of time
before he lets me
into Bakunawa's inner circle.
I'm sure of that.
But while I wait...
I'll give them
a lot more problems.
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on, baby.
Show me.
I want to see all of you.
Uh... I'm shy.
Why would you be shy?
You're perfect.
You're beautiful and sexy.
You should be proud.
Besides,
it's just the two of us.
You first.
[CHUCKLES]
Me?
Okay.
So you'll be in the mood.
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Here.
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GIGGLING]
More!
You want to see everything?
Yes, Henry!
More!
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
I want you so much!
I can't wait to see you!
There!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GIGGLING]
We'll be together soon.
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOANING]
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES,
THEN FADES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Mr. Afilada.
We've got your sex tape.
If you don't want it to spread,
give us 10 million pesos.
Otherwise,
we'll destroy your reputation.
[HENRY]
Boss...
Please don't.
Please.
Please don't leak the video.
That would ruin me.
Just keep your end of the deal.
I'll text you where
to bring the money.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Ellen.
Lolita.
Can I talk to you?
Where's my daughter?
Where's Arissa?
You know,
I've been telling her to come
home for the longest time.
But what?
She won't leave that place!
So? What now?
[LOLITA] Ellen, I didn't call
to argue with you.
I called to tell you what's
happening to your daughter,
because she needs you
right now.
Not your nagging,
not your sermons,
not your blaming her.
You. She needs you.
Your support.
Your understanding.
What happened?
If you're thinking
she got hurt, no.
But Arissa saw...
...something terrible happen
to her friend,
and she was traumatized.
She blames herself.
She's been crying nonstop.
Oh my god!
She didn't want you to know
because she didn't
want to worry you.
But as a mother,
I understand
that you have to know
what's going on with her.
Oh... So what now?
You can't come home?
I don't even know who I
could leave my kids with here.
And I don't know if my
husband will let me go.
And we're...
We're cash strapped right now.
- We don't have the mon--
- I understand.
- You don't have to explain.
- Besides,
I know the reason
she doesn't want to leave.
And I've never seen
Arissa this happy.
I just want to thank you
for welcoming her
into your family.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
For being a mother to her.
Honestly, it's not easy...
to love the child of your
husband and another woman.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
But Arissa isn't hard to love.
She just needs understanding.
[ELLEN]
And Lolita...
I'm sorry for getting
involved with Mike,
and for ruining your family.
[LOLITA]
That's all in the past.
What matters now
is Arissa's well-being.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ARISSA]
Auntie...
Wait, hold on.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where are you going?
Headed to
work already?
Are you really okay?
Yes.
Otherwise, I'll go crazy
if I just stay here.
I understand.
That's why I packed you
some food.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Your Favorite.
Your adobo.
My favorite.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you.
Very, very much.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [PHONE RINGING IN BACKGROUND]
- Sir.
- Hm?
- Is there a problem?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Everyone involved in
the operation last night...
...is a possible suspect.
For what?
For the robbery
involving the goons,
during our
human trafficking bust.
I don't buy that they were
just some crime syndicate.
Everyone in the operation, sir?
They seem like decent officers.
It doesn't matter
what they look like.
People will do anything
for the right price.
What about you?
Can you be bought?
[SCOFFS] Of course not.
I'm my father's son, right?
Mm, scam buster.
Exactly!
[CHUCKLES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir, tomorrow at 9 AM
you have a meeting
with Detective Ajero
and Atty. Pangilinan
over lunch.
Then at 2 PM--
Please clear
my schedule for the afternoon.
Noted, sir.
May I know what
your schedule is for tomorrow?
I just need it
for the calendar, sir.
[SCOFFS]
That won't be necessary.
It's classified.
Alright, sir.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Arissa, are you alright?
Trying to be.
What about you and your dad?
Well...
I'm ignoring him.
I have nothing to say to him.
I'm still mad at him, Arissa.
Enzo.
Mister Roldan
is here to see you.
[ROLDAN SIGHS HEAVILY]
You're not responding
to my messages or calls.
I'm just busy with work, Pa.
I'm always on the road too.
There are a lot of customers
in the café as well.
We don't have breakfast
together anymore.
Can we do that again?
Mm... Yeah.
Tomorrow.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
Or whenever you're free.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
So, are you ready?
- Ready!
We manipulated the algorithm
to make sure he'll read it.
Okay, good, good.
Alright. Let's go. [CLAPS]
- Game!
Come on, come on.
Let's go.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Execute!
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[CLACKING CONTINUES]
"HUMAN COCKFIGHT
COMING SOON"
"Human cockfight"?
"From Nepal here,
very excited for this."
"Finally, something exciting
for us here in Switzerland."
- [GRUNTS ANGRILY]
- [LAMP CLATTERS]
Damn it!
They stole my idea!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Enzo.
If you need help,
I'm here.
I know.
Don't worry Arissa,
I'll be fine.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Hey, Benji!
- Hmm?
You're using your phone again.
You're gambling online, huh?
No, I'm not!
I'm not gambling.
I'm just watching.
I have a crush on the dealer.
Look.
Isn't she beautiful?
[DINGING]
Place your bets!
Let's go, guys!
- Benji! Can I see that?
- Hmm?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Shanaia?
This is Naomi.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CARINA] She sent money.
Then when I wanted to call
to check up on her
and thank her for the money,
she said not to call her.
She only wanted to talk
through text messages.
Now, she doesn't
update me anymore.
She no longer
sends photos either.
I know my daughter.
This isn't like her.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Sir.
Matthias called.
He's asking
for an emergency meeting.
Do I have to make a call?
Okay.
[LINE RINGING]
Becca, call everyone.
Tell them we're having
an emergency meeting.
Bro!
[DOOR CLOSES]
Bro, I'm sorry.
But...
the cancer cells have spread
all over your body.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
How long do I have?
If you're lucky...
six months.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know what's funny?
I've faced so many battles.
Demonstrations,
riots,
shootouts...
We've even been
bombed multiple times.
But not once
did I get taken down
Who would've thought the
thing that would kill me...
is already inside me?
Bro...
Maybe you should tell Leah now.
So she can prepare herself.
Don't worry about my daughter.
Leah was born ready for anything
You know what I'm worried about?
Bakunawa.
I built this group
from the ground up.
And until now,I
haven't found...
...a single person
who can replace me.
They're either
incompetently stupid...
or goddamn greedy.
Except for one.
Except for one person.
Someone...
smart,
skilled,
brave,
and he has the
strength of character.
A natural-born leader.
Who?
Are you talking about
Samuel Trinidad?
Yes.
I think I've finally
found my successor.
And I think it's about
time I prepare him.
[PHONE BUZZING]
Hello?
Hello, Samuel Trinidad.
This is Old Man.
I like your proposal
about the casino.
You have foresight.
You think outside the box.
I'm impressed.
Thank you, sir.
And now, I have an
assignment for you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
This Thursday...
We found Naomi.
She's working there
as a casino dealer.
If I hadn't fallen
for those scams,
I wouldn't be in this mess.
Alliances will be shaken.
- What are you doing here?
- Old Man sent me.
He'll speak for me.
Whatever decision I make.
That human cockfight
can't happen.
You're sabotaging me!
You want to fight, right?
Then fight each other.