[English subtitles are available]
♫Fall in love with your uniqueness♫
[Perfect Mismatch]
[Episode 23]
Morning, Mr. Zhou.
Good morning, Zhifei.
Zhi'ang?
Chi?
Why are you in my place early in the morning?
Look, Zhifei.
I talked to Chi last night.
We customized
a treatment plan for your blood phobia.
Why does it sound familiar?
Huahua.
Zhifei, don't worry.
Zhi'ang and Chi don't know anything about medicine.
They won't force you to take medicine.
You can try their treatment.
First of all, the red substitution method.
If you can adapt to a large area of red,
when you see blood again,
just consider it's a red dye spill,
and you'll be fine with it.
Mr. Zhou,
let's put on some music.
Mr. Zhou, do you feel anything?
Chi Miqi,
do you think I'm a bull?
It's okay.
Wrong music.
Let's change it.
Mr. Zhou,
can you feel it?
Chi Miqi, enough.
Useless.
Next.
Fear comes from insecurity.
If you're afraid of something,
you have to face it,
feel it,
and defeat it.
So I prepared this for you.
Sensory stimulation therapy.
Zhifei,
this might be slightly uncomfortable.
But no matter what, you must not run away.
Remember, we're all here for you.
What are you doing?
Zhifei,
this is fresh pig blood.
Straight from the slaughterhouse via air.
Look, how fresh.
I don't need it.
You do.
I don't.
Zhifei,
look,
I'll demonstrate for you.
Mr. Zhou,
don't mind Zhi'ang.
It's okay.
Let's move on to the next.
There's more?
Yeah.
Zhi'ang, it doesn't work very well.
It seems that we have to find another way.
No matter what,
I have to cure my brother.
Guys, enough already.
No.
Get some rest today.
We'll be back tomorrow.
Chi,
let's go.
See you tomorrow.
I didn't know Zhi'ang's creative.
Chi is quite something, too.
I'm exhausted hanging out
with them today.
Zhifei,
there's something I want to tell you.
Do you have to say it now?
Want to come to my room
and have a good chat tonight?
You…
All right.
Just kidding.
Let's talk tomorrow.
I'm really tired.
Okay.
Sorry, Huahua.
You must've been disappointed
by my cowardice.
Zhifei,
wake up.
Huahua.
Are Zhi'ang and Chi here?
I talked to Xiaoxiao
and we decided
to stop this unreliable treatment.
Why?
How will we know unless we try?
I think Zhi'ang must have many ways
to cure me.
I want to try them all.
But do you think that's going to work?
I see.
You're getting upset.
From now on, only you get to heal me.
Other people won't have the chance.
All right, Huahua.
Don't be upset, okay?
Why don't you teach me kung fu?
Didn't you say
Shi's kung fu can cultivate our body and mind?
Or
let's just go back to the mountains.
You've been out for so long.
You must miss home.
Zhou Zhifei,
do you mean it?
Go back to the mountains with me
and hide?
Is this the life you want?
I think it's good.
Didn't you tell me to get out into nature?
If I go home with you
to a picturesque place,
maybe it's good for my health.
You have no physical problems at all.
Zhou Zhifei,
what exactly are you escaping from?
Can you afford to lose Feiran?
Are you willing to spend the rest of your life hiding
and have everyone mocking you,
admitting you're just a sick person?
I know
what Zhiran did was a big blow to you.
But now you have to pull yourself together
and find the man you used to be.
You can't just run away from it
like what you do now.
The man I fell for
shouldn't be like this.
Huahua,
I'm useless, aren't I?
I've been
running away from it till now.
You used
to be afraid.
You were afraid of facing it alone.
But now it's different.
I'm here for you.
You can rest assured that
whatever problems you'll have,
we'll deal with them together.
Zhou.
Ji Qing,
no one's on my side now,
I hope you can help me.
I'm glad you came to me.
You see, there's always a way out.
I know what happened to me
was a shock to everyone.
But I have never made any mistakes
throughout my years running Feiran.
As a major shareholder of the Zhou Group,
you should
know better than anyone about this.
You don't have to explain that much to me.
I have every faith in your ability
and I know why you came to me.
I can give you
all my shares in the Zhou Group
on one condition.
Let's get married.
Sorry.
The person I love is Shi Huahua.
I can't accept
your condition.
Seriously?
You don't get to refuse.
Shi Huahua can offer you nothing.
I'm the only one who can help you now.
I'm serious.
So am I.
Zhou Zhifei,
when you took over Feiran,
I also took over the Ji Group.
Step by step, we get
where we are right now together.
Are you really willing to let Zhiran
steal the company you built?
Feiran is owned by Zhiran and I from the beginning.
No matter what,
"steal" should never
be used on my brother.
And,
Huahua is never
a bargaining chip.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Zhou Zhifei.
[Feiran Capital]
Mr. Zhou?
Right.
You're not the president anymore.
Guess now I can
just call you Zhifei.
Shen Jun,
I don't have time to waste.
Hold that thought.
I know
you're going through a hard time.
It could've happened to anybody.
But, as your senior,
I'd like to help you out.
Are you upset
about the shares?
Just 2.5 percent,
keep it for yourself.
Better than nothing, right?
If you want to get back on top,
there's only one way.
You have to conquer the small shareholders one by one.
If you'll return
Professor Yu's sweetener patent
to me,
I'll give all my shares to you.
What do you think?
It's a win-win.
I want you to understand two things.
First,
learn some manners.
It's not your place to remind me.
Second,
I don't believe
you'd be so kind to help me.
So, just drop your act.
Zhifei,
stop being patronizing, okay?
You're like a stray dog with nothing left to lose.
What's the point?
[Feiran Capital]
You have nothing left.
You're selling your car
and your property in a couple of days, right?
Please tell the one who's barking downstairs
to come up for a chat.
Zhiran,
how did you know I'm here to see you?
Don't be paranoid.
I'm not interested in you.
What did you say to my brother?
Nothing much.
I'm just curious.
What is it
between you and your brother
that you run him to death?
Uncle Shen,
loose lips sink ships.
All right. All right.
I couldn't care less.
I'm here today for business.
Now you are the only one in your family.
Are you worried that
Zhou Zhifei will come back one day
to destroy you?
I've been waiting for him.
Let's not put it like that.
A bit of advice.
The thing about shares is
the bigger piece, the better.
I don't have much.
But it's better than nothing.
If you'll return
Professor Yu's sweetener patent
to me,
I'll transfer all my shares to you.
It's the same speech you gave my brother, right?
No way.
You got rejected
and gave me the same offer?
What's wrong, Uncle Shen?
You don't want to get into the Zhou Holdings now?
I've seen enough drama of your family,
and I want to withdraw my investment.
Let me say it for you.
You want to use Professor Yu's free tech to cash in
and cheat Zhou Holdings out of its shares.
Well,
if Professor Yu knows about this,
how do you think that will make him feel?
How do you know?
[Authorization Contract]
You know,
word always gets out.
I think
Professor Yu's legal team
is on their way now.
What?
Shen Jun, I'm telling you,
no outsiders are allowed
to get their hands on our Zhou family's stuff.
My brother
will never be insulted by people like you.
Anyone who does harm to my brother
won't end well.
Zhou Zhiran, you psychopath!
You and your brother are both psychopaths!
Zhifei,
I know you don't have a stake in the group now.
But you don't have to eat this.
This is too shabby.
Don't laugh. I'm serious.
I'll support you.
You gotta eat meat.
Huahua's still growing.
Zhi'ang, you're overthinking it.
We're not that broke.
You see,
Zhifei's been running around for the company stuff.
I don't want him to get inflamed,
so I prepared this
mushroom soup pot today.
These are all healthy vegetables.
No meat.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You should've told me earlier.
Let's eat.
Well, how's the equity thing going?
Getting anywhere?
Zhiran holds all the shares of Feiran,
let alone of Fei'ang Group.
Now, among the company's major shareholders,
Ji Qing is our only hope.
But I can't
accept her condition.
It's okay. Take your time.
I'm here for you.
What time do we have to wait?
I can't believe my parents.
I wonder when
they'll change their minds.
Speaking of which,
they have done
many private transactions in the dark.
Do you think
it could be a bargaining chip for us?
Where do people usually put this kind of evidence?
Mom, I'm home.
What's the code to the safe?
It's your birthday.
Okay.
What are you looking for?
Just some stuff.
[File Cover]
Mom, I got to go.
I'll go have dinner with my friends.
Drive safe.
Zhifei,
have you really decided?
I'm Zhiran's brother.
His mistake has a lot to do with me.
Of course I should be the one to solve it.
I just need to untangle what is tangled.
Then let me recharge you.
Since you decided,
just go all out.
I'll be there for you.
Zhifei, you're here.
I've been waiting for you.
Zhiran,
at this point of time,
you still think you're doing the right thing?
What did I do wrong?
These days,
everything's been under control at Feiran.
I'm waiting for you to come back
so we can share
what belongs to us together.
Okay.
If that's the case,
let's go.
Why is this outsider still here?
Grandpa asked me to come.
Zhiran,
you called a board meeting
with several major shareholders
and had my position removed.
I'm worthless now.
To you,
am I an outsider now?
Zhifei, you know
that's not what I want.
Have a seat.
What's all this?
It seems it's a crusade against me.
You really threw me under the bus.
That's why you came home that night.
Shame on you.
Uncle,
Aunt,
I have nothing to lose now.
But you are different.
If these internal transactions in Fei'ang
get exposed,
the consequences
should be more than just a drop
in market value, right?
I don't think
you want that, right?
You're threatening me, too?
I wouldn't dare.
Let's get it straight.
Feiran and Fei'ang have different priorities for development.
I have no intention of competing with you for resources.
I just want to get back what belongs to me,
and I don't think you're going to sit back and do nothing.
Mom, Dad,
you were always going against Zhifei
and has done so many unethical things.
I have seen it all these years.
I'm doing this now
not only for Zhifei,
but also for you.
I want you to stop before it's too late
and get back on the right track.
After all, we're family.
Zhiran,
why did you say that?
We're family.
How can this be a crusade?
Yeah.
You and Zhifei are brothers,
and you were brought up by Zhifei.
Is that really necessary?
Uncle,
Zhi'ang and I are brothers, too.
Are you saying
I have a share of Fei'ang's dividend, too?
No, you…
Cousins are different from brothers.
No wonder
you wanted to see my brother fall before,
but now you're so dedicated to defending him.
If it's not for interest,
you wouldn't have done that, right?
Zhiran,
I've been indulging you for a long time,
yet you never know to dial it back.
When will you
stop making a scene?
Grandpa, I'm not.
Zhou Holdings is the hard work of your life.
I know you think highly of my brother
and you wanted him to take over the chairmanship.
But you saw it last time.
People will doubt
if he can take over the job
with his blood phobia issue.
I agree with Zhiran.
Ji Qing, you're a stockholder.
Of course you have the right to object.
Zhou Zhifei,
I gave you the chance.
And my answer is clear.
Zhou Zhifei has a serious mental illness.
He'll act like a kid at the sight of blood,
and people will take advantage of that.
So,
I object that Zhou Zhifei rejoins the board.
It seems
many people have the same concerns as me.
What do you say?
At the last shareholders' meeting,
my grandfather vouched for me with the reputation of Zhou Holdings.
My brother made me swear
out of concern for the reputation
of Zhou Holdings.
I will give you an answer
to the vow I failed to fulfill
on that day.
As you can see on that day,
I did once suffer from
a strange illness.
I faint at the sight of blood and would act like a kid
with only memories before I was seven.
The reason for this is that
I witnessed the death of my parents
when I was young,
which traumatized me severely.
Until now, I still can't face it.
It was like
a nightmare,
bringing me painful memories over and over again.
It's still difficult for me to talk about that.
But today I'm telling this story
because I found a way
to fight this illness.
When I was young, I was afraid of being abandoned,
but now,
I have found the person who's always there for me.
She let me know that
I'm no longer alone in the world,
and I'll never feel lonely again.
Wake up, guys.
It changes nothing.
Zhifei,
I don't want to go against you.
But do you think you can convince everyone
with just a few words?
I'll show them.
Zhiran.
If you still think of me as your brother,
stop hurting yourself,
okay?
Zhifei,
you're scared?
I do not want to see you
repeatedly revealing your scars.
It breaks my heart.
So why can't it be me?
Why can't I be
the one who stands by your side?
Because I never wanted to leave you behind!
Liar.
Zhiran,
if you want to prove it,
I hope you're not the one bleeding today.
Zhifei.
You've recovered?
Huahua has cured me.
Since Zhifei has been cured,
I agree that Zhifei should come back
and continue to be the president of Feiran.
Agreed.
Zhifei is our best choice.
Yes, that's right.
You're all crazy.
And you, Zhifei.
Remember your choice today.
I hope you don't live to regret it.
Zhiran!
Zhifei.
Let him be.
Zhifei,
I thought you were young
and still need more experience.
Today, it seems
I was overthinking it.
You have
Huahua with you in the future.
I'm relieved.
Zhifei,
come here.
I would like to announce that
from today,
I step down as Chairman of Zhou Holdings.
Zhou Zhifei will take over the position
and be in charge of all matters in the group.
Zhifei,
you did it.
Because you are
the cure I need.
I know you have something on your mind.
I'm here for you.
Huahua,
I'm so lucky to have you.
Mr. Zhou. Mr. Zhou.
Congratulations!
You guys…
Congratulations on your promotion.
[Staff Card]
You're now the Chairman of Zhou Holdings.
Mr. Zhou's awesome. You made a grand a comeback!
Together you can do so much as a couple!
Get married! Get married!