Ms. Dentist?
Your clinic closed hours ago.
You shouldn't be out so late--
Excuse me.
You dropped your phone.
I'll leave it here.
Continue what you were doing.
It didn't break.
Really?
Our country sure makes sturdy phones.
Of course. After all,
we are an IT powerhouse.
-I should go.
-Okay.
Get home safe.
Okay. Thanks.
No problem.
You were just startled.
That's all.
Gosh, it's hot.
Why am I feeling so hot?
Is the feng shui bad here?
Taekwondo!
EPISODE 9
Please touch the anti-static pad
for your safety.
-Please select your method of payment.
-How will you pay? Credit? Cash?
-Credit, please.
-Just press this.
Please select the fuel of your choice.
-It's diesel, so press this.
-Right.
You selected diesel.
-Input the amount of fuel you want.
-How much?
-Fifty thousand won.
-Fifty thousand won. All right.
Please insert your credit card facing up.
-Insert your card.
-Right.
-Checking your fingerprint.
-Press "confirm."
It worked.
You can refuel now.
-Make sure you touch the anti-static pad.
-Right.
Thank you, sir.
Don't mention it. This is a problem.
They're replacing everything
with computers now.
The elderly have no time
to adjust to this change.
Yes?
Right now?
Is it the standard size?
Okay, I'll stop by.
All right.
Are you done?
Yes, almost.
We should've gone
to a regular gas station.
By the way, didn't that guy
speak down to me?
Did he?
I think he did.
Hello, Dr. Yoon.
Working out early in the morning?
Yes. My body felt a bit heavy,
so I went for a run.
I see. Are you sure
it wasn't your heart that was heavy?
Sorry?
I know.
-Know what?
-Mr. Ban told me.
He said you and Chief Hong
passionately embraced last night.
What?
Don't worry. I didn't tell anyone.
That's not what happened.
I understand.
You spent the night with Chief Hong,
but you're also interested in Director Ji.
You're torn between those two. I get it.
You got it all wrong.
Don't worry. I get it.
I totally understand how you feel.
Don't worry. I haven't told a single soul.
I'm rooting for you.
Good luck.
Seriously? She's awfully excited
for someone with a secret.
Don't you worry about a thing!
I won't tell anyone!
-That hurts.
-Trust me!
Gosh.
Dad.
Had you told me you were coming,
I would've cleaned up a bit.
I didn't want to come.
Unbelievable.
He's lying.
We were nearby, and he wanted to stop by.
I told him
we should call you first, but he insisted.
I see.
Where's the bathroom?
It's over there.
-Have a seat.
-Okay.
Goodness!
Chief Hong.
-"Chief Hong"?
-What? Yes.
What are you doing here?
I came to fix your shower.
The showerhead burst,
so I got completely drenched.
The new head is stronger.
Why would you do that in an empty house?
Ms. Pyo just left.
She told me to fix it
since you'd be home soon.
I can't believe her.
Okay, then. You should go.
-Pay me.
-What?
I need to get paid.
Okay. I'll wire it.
-Leave.
-Come on.
Don't push me. My bag's still here.
Fine. I'm leaving.
-Gosh.
-Stop!
Will you pay me instead?
So you're Chief Hong?
That's right.
I'm her father.
I thought so.
Did you refuel your car all right?
Yes, we did. Thank you.
-It was my pleasure.
-You met him?
Yes. I helped him out at the gas station.
Do you frequent her house?
Well… I do come by
more often than every now and then.
Dad. Let me explain--
What's your relationship with her?
-What?
-From what I heard,
you two even spent
the night together. Am I wrong?
Well…
-Dad. Let me--
-I'm afraid I can't answer that
with a simple yes or no.
I also heard you two
embraced each other last night.
There's actually a good reason.
Gosh, will you continue holding…
Right. You have
no intention of letting go of it.
Dad, I can explain. So please let go--
There's no need. I already heard it all.
Besides, I even caught him at your house,
so don't try to make excuses.
-I said I'd explain--
-No, let me.
You're right. I'm Ms. Dentist-- I mean,
Hye-jin's boyfriend.
Goodness.
Oh, dear. Come on, honey.
Why did you say that?
I had to survive.
What?
That's your reason?
Then what? He was about to crush my hand.
And I figured
that this was the simplest way.
He wasn't going to be convinced otherwise.
Explaining myself wouldn't have worked,
so I decided to just pretend
to be your boyfriend for today.
And then?
And then you can say we've broken up.
What can he do about it?
So you're making me clean up the mess.
Consider this a part-time job for me.
I'm your boyfriend for the day.
And you want to get paid?
I'll only charge you for the showerhead.
Unbelievable.
"Unbelievable"? Why? Do you not like it?
Then I'll tell him the truth.
Continue what you were doing.
What is this? A rabbit?
Yes. Isn't it pretty?
I have a fruit plating certificate.
Hop, hop.
Oh, my. You sliced them so well.
It's so pretty.
It's nothing. Enjoy.
Hye-jin, go to your room.
No.
All right, then.
You. Let's talk over there.
No.
-She says no.
-He's quite obedient to her.
Women know what's best, right?
He already knows the truth.
He's better than you.
Be quiet, will you?
Was that an order?
No, it was a question.
What's your name?
I'm Hong Du-sik.
-Sir.
-Age?
Thirty-five.
Sir.
How long have you two been dating?
For about three months.
How could you have gotten
so close in such a short time?
Honey. Calm down and breathe. Okay?
Times have changed.
Don't be so old-fashioned.
Fine.
What do you do for a living?
I just have many part-time jobs.
Are you saying
you're unemployed?
I'm currently experiencing
all the jobs in the world.
But if you want to limit that
to having one specific job…
Then no.
Are you dating an unemployed man?
I guess you could say that.
Well…
Why does it matter
when I make enough money?
He's a good guy.
What did you say?
And he's not the incompetent man
you're making him out to be.
I mean, he's handsome, tall,
and graduated from SNU.
-SNU?
-Yes.
Besides, he got in
with the highest grades.
Was it chemistry?
-Engineering.
-Right.
-I see.
-Anyway, he's just taking a rest
in his hometown.
Right?
Is that true?
Of course, Dad.
I am a good judge of character.
She's right. I'm sure
she picked the right one.
Let's go check out her dental clinic
and look around the neighborhood.
Sure, then.
Then let's let him go first.
-I'll guide you after.
-You should do it.
Me? Sir?
What? No?
Let's go, honey. Come on.
Are you insane?
People will see us together!
Don't worry. I have a plan.
Let's go.
I can't believe this.
Here.
Eat slowly and enjoy.
Eat up.
-Thank you for the meal.
-My pleasure.
This is an announcement
to our dear Gongjin residents.
-Due to some unavoidable situation,
-No way!
-Chief Hong is pretending
-Look at this.
to be Dr. Yoon's boyfriend.
We ask for your cooperation
in this role-playing.
Whoever contributes the most
will be rewarded
a 30-percent discount
at our dental clinic.
-Thirty percent?
Let's go!
Cut.
You're in a food coma, aren't you?
Yes. I'm extremely drowsy.
How about we take a two-hour break?
-Seriously?
-Yes.
I don't want the staff
to get heat stroke in this scorching heat.
We deserve to work in better conditions.
-Awesome.
-But promise me you'll stay inside
and rest up.
-Okay.
Let's take a break
and come back by 2 p.m. Go.
-Okay. Good work.
-Good work.
-See you later.
-Bye.
-Hello.
Goodness, you're going to spill it.
No, I'm fine.
That must be very heavy.
Let me take it.
-Goodness.
-It's nothing much.
We just made some potato rice cakes.
We've worked since early
in the morning to make them.
How could you say that?
My back is about to break in half.
-Goodness.
-Are you not filming now?
We're taking a break.
-I see.
Thank you so much for this.
We'll have them later.
Try some now.
-Should I? Okay.
-Yes.
My gosh.
Check out this color.
Here I go.
It's scrumptious!
It's so chewy.
Are they beans inside?
To be exact,
-they're kidney beans.
-I see.
I'm afraid they'll go bad quickly
-in this scorching heat.
-I'll take them indoors.
-Put them in front of the fan.
-Gosh. You fool.
-They'll harden in the fridge.
-Wait.
It's sweet and salty.
And the texture is just perfect.
JUNE, try one.
By the way, are you still on a diet?
No, ma'am. Thank you for this.
Try it.
It's delicious.
-Is it?
-It's so good.
-Have more.
-It's so tasty.
Eat more.
Isn't the ocean beautiful?
-Yes, I love it.
-That's right.
Isn't the neighborhood cozy and nice?
It's nothing special.
Gosh. Hye-jin, why is your dad so boring?
Sorry?
It's impossible to have
a conversation with him
since he's so indifferent
about everything.
I have no idea what's on his mind.
I know how tough it is to deal with people
like him. Does he sulk often?
Of course, I don't.
-He does. He sulks all day long.
-What?
He sulks when his egg yolk breaks,
-when we run out of toilet paper--
-That's not true.
You have it rough.
Then you must've frowned a lot,
but how come you don't have any wrinkles?
Your boyfriend is humorous.
What a lucky girl you are.
-Don't worry.
-Don't go overboard.
Go ahead.
Hello.
Gosh! It's Dr. Yoon and Chief Hong.
No other couple can hold a candle
to them in the neighborhood.
They're the best couple ever.
I agree.
My good friend Du-sik
looks as handsome as always.
I thought you had a plan.
-He can't act to save his life.
-You're so awkward.
Hello, you must be Dr. Yoon's parents.
-I'm Oh Yoon,
-What's up with his voice?
the singer who sang
"Exercising in the Moonlight."
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
I guess you don't recognize me.
That's fine.
Chief Hong and I are pretty much brothers.
And Dr. Yoon and I
often share thoughts on music and culture.
-I see.
-I've prepared a present
for you two. It's my autographed CD.
-Don't!
-Here you go.
And this is my poster.
It may not seem like much right now,
but it could be a remarkable gift
for your future generations.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
Hey, Du-sik.
Wow, have you been working out?
-You're--
-Hello,
sir and ma'am. I'm the zone chief here.
Hello.
Thanks to Dr. Yoon, we finally have
a dental clinic
and can get our teeth treated.
That's right.
She's the owner of both my place
and the clinic building.
-Goodness.
-I see.
I finally get to meet you.
Thank you for your help.
Goodness. I should be
the one thanking you.
You should bring them to our restaurant.
I'll prepare a nice lunch.
No, bring them to my restaurant. I'll--
Okay? Bring them to my place.
Sure.
-That way.
-Come by for some coffee.
That way.
-Goodbye.
-That's okay.
See you, my friend.
-Bye.
-Don't do that.
This neighborhood is a bit odd.
And how do they all know about me?
Let's hurry.
-Goodbye.
-This way.
-Goodbye, Du-sik.
-Good luck!
Goodness.
-That was awkward.
-We did well.
What's with the CD?
-I was most natural.
-Why gave it to them?
Because I'm a singer.
-You were most awkward.
-That's not true.
-I did well. What?
-Unbelievable.
Are you crazy? Tell me you are.
That's our precious cue sheet.
I wanted to see
if it'd make a good paper plane.
Are you kidding me?
Just go take a walk and get it together.
-Fine.
-I ought to smack you.
Gosh, you're so strong.
What?
Looking for JUNE?
No. We Hackers respect our stars' privacy.
Are you seriously not here to see DOS?
Is JUNE in there?
No, he's taking a rest somewhere else.
Darn it. I should've come earlier.
Then I would've seen him leave.
Darn it.
-Hye-jin?
-There's a harbor.
Why is she with Chief Hong?
-There's a fish market too.
-You can't go.
-Why not?
-Dr. Yoon's parents are here,
so he's acting
as her boyfriend. Awesome, right?
What? That can't be. Why?
-I don't know.
-Hye-jin!
Seong-hyeon. Aren't you supposed
to be filming?
Do you know him?
Hello! I'm Ji Seong-hyeon,
Hye-jin's senior from college.
I see. Hello.
Your name sounds familiar.
Goodness. Aren't you that famous director?
Thank you for recognizing me.
Wait. Do you know him?
Of course. He directed
all my favorite shows.
Really? It's nice to meet you.
It's an honor to meet you, Father.
"Father"?
That's wonderful to hear.
How formal.
Aren't you busy? Shouldn't you be filming?
-Filming?
-Sir, we're taking a break right now.
Would you like to come in?
I'll give you a tour.
No, there's no need.
-That's okay.
-May we?
Wouldn't we be a nuisance?
Not at all. Come on in.
-This way.
-Let's go.
I'm actually their crew's guide.
Seong-hyeon.
-Yes?
-Let me explain.
It's okay. I heard.
Don't worry. I won't put you in a pickle.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
-This is the living room.
-I see.
There's another camera here.
Gosh, how many cameras are there?
I saw how these cameras followed
your movement.
-Are they filming us?
-No, we turned them off.
-Please sit down.
-Okay.
Would you like some iced coffee?
That'll be great.
Coffee on an empty stomach?
Then how about some tea?
No, coffee is fine. Thank you.
Why did you have to say that?
Hye-jin, isn't it hot out there?
Come inside.
No, it's okay. I'll stay here.
Let her be. She works indoors all day.
She needs some sunlight and vitamin D.
I'm already taking supplements.
Why, when you can get it naturally?
Give your liver a break.
Don't worry about me.
-All right. Hye-jin, sit down.
-Gosh.
Here you go.
All right.
Here.
-Hye-jin.
-Thank you.
Cover your legs with this.
Thanks.
I brought these from Seoul. Try some.
Since they're vegan-friendly,
they're not sweet and easy to digest.
Don't vegans refrain from eating meat?
Bread doesn't have meat in it, does it?
Well, you see, the bread--
That's not what he meant.
There are levels to vegetarianism.
Flexitarians occasionally consume meat.
Pescatarians consume fish but not meat.
Vegans are the strictest
and even refrain
from consuming milk or eggs.
So simply put,
this bread doesn't contain milk or eggs.
Please enjoy them.
They're light and tasty.
Dad, let's leave
after eating this. He needs to work.
Right. He must be busy.
That's okay.
She just doesn't want to inconvenience me.
She's been like this ever since college.
By the way,
we met through an elective course.
I see.
She prepared really thoroughly
for our group project
and even did the presentation.
She gave an outstanding presentation.
-She left everyone was speechless.
-Really?
-Did you know she's good at arguing?
-Yes, she's a feisty one.
I was never like that.
Please tell us
what kind of student she was in college.
Let's see.
She was studious
and worked hard for the scholarship.
And she was a terrific dancer.
She was?
How could you tell them that?
I only danced once.
-That's enough.
-You were good at this.
I won first place.
Mother, please visit our TV station
next time. I'll give you a tour.
-Do you mean it?
-Of course.
We shouldn't bother you anymore.
If you want, I can get you tickets
to Gag Big League.
Really? I love that show.
It's so strange
how nobody ever eats the last piece.
-Oh, dear.
-Oh, no.
-Are you okay?
-I'll bring some tissue.
It's okay. I have some wet wipes.
You should've been more careful.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Sir.
Sir, we should get back to the shooting.
Sure. I'll be there soon.
Okay.
I'm sorry we have
to make you leave like this.
That's fine. Thank you for the tour.
I'll tell my friends to watch your show.
Thank you, ma'am. Have a safe trip.
I'll officially introduce myself
next time.
-Okay.
-Sure.
-I'll call you later.
-Bye.
I know you're just part-timing,
but treat them well.
Of course. I'm going to be true to my role
as Ms. Dentist's boyfriend today.
That little… God, I never pegged him
as such an annoying type, but he's so…
You surprised me too.
I was wondering where our lucky charm was,
and she has it.
Director Ji, I bought a house
with a 30-year installment plan.
And I need to feed my cats.
Let's do well.
Okay.
-I'll do my best.
-No, do well.
I'll do well.
Ms. Pyo.
Hey!
What are you doing here?
Me? I was just killing time here.
Because I don't think
I should go home right now.
What do you mean?
It's nothing important.
Aren't you working? Where are you headed?
I was just patrolling.
Now, I'm delivering lunch
to the elderly living alone.
Me. I'll help you. Let me volunteer.
What? There's no need for that.
It's okay.
I have nothing better to do anyway.
This is wonderful.
I'm helping those in need.
Can I get in?
What are these?
They're lunch boxes.
I see.
This is my first time riding a police car.
The seat feels different.
It's coated with enamel
to make it waterproof.
Because drunk citizens often throw up
or relieve themselves in the car.
They do what?
Don't worry. There was an incident
last night, but I cleaned up after them.
I see.
-Give me a minute.
-What?
License plate 8736,
you made an illegal U-turn.
Please pull over.
-Wait here.
-Okay.
He looks even more handsome when working.
Thank you.
He's driving me crazy.
-Sorry about that.
-No, it's fine.
Did you just give him a ticket?
He went over the centerline. That's
30 penalty points and a 60,000-won fine.
I see.
You should be penalized too.
Sorry?
You see, you invaded my heart.
As for the penalty, let's call it even
with the chicken you bought.
Let's date.
I think you're being rash.
Sorry?
You still don't know much about me.
I understand that people these days
easily fall for each other
and date casually.
I'm aware of how easy it is
for people to start dating.
However, I'm afraid
I'm a bit old-fashioned.
I hope you understand.
Sure.
Wait. I just remembered
that I have somewhere to be right now.
I promise I'll help you
deliver the lunch boxes next time.
This is driving me insane.
Rear doors of police cars
don't open from the inside.
I see. Darn it.
Okay. Thank you.
Hye-jin, does Seong-hyeon
have a girlfriend?
Seong-hyeon? Probably not.
Really? He seemed like a decent guy.
-I see.
-Over here.
It's nice and cozy.
It's neither too big nor too small.
-Right?
-Really?
I chose this place
and took care of the renovation myself.
What a show-off.
What? Did you say something?
Hye-jin, take good care of the orchids.
I will.
You're one to talk.
You've let a few die yourself.
What kind of orchids did you have?
Oriental orchids. You wouldn't know.
Those are noble orchids.
To make them bloom, you need to maintain
the temperature well during winter.
How did you do it?
What do you take me for?
I kept them in our living room.
Oh, dear. The temperature
must've been too high.
During winter, they should stay
at temperatures between 5°C or 15°C
for 60 consecutive days to bloom.
Is that so? I thought they'd freeze.
I see.
By the way, how do you know
so much about growing orchids?
That was my job in the military.
Sir.
Is that actually a thing?
Yes. I grew trees and flowers
that were used for events.
I see.
Look.
I'm also growing Jeju Island boat orchids.
Boat orchids… Let me think.
Boat orchids live in shaded forests.
The environment needs to be warm.
And give them enough water and fertilizer.
-They shouldn't receive too much sunlight.
-I see.
-Hello.
Do you want to go upstairs?
Sure. It has the best view.
-Okay.
-This way.
Does he like to play go?
I don't know.
He loves it. He spends
his free time looking at game records.
-Hey.
-Hey, Chief Hong.
-Hey. Who won?
-Hey.
It was a close match, but I won.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
Why are you still here?
Buy him some jjajangmyeon.
Fine. Let's go eat it.
-Well done.
-Okay.
Come.
-Order some tangsuyuk too.
-Got it.
I won't go easy on you next time.
Goodbye.
Care for a game?
Can you even play?
Find out for yourself.
-All right.
-Bring it on, then.
You're going to do that right now?
-Aren't we here to eat?
-Oh, dear.
All right. Let's see.
Here.
We'll order after they're done playing.
Sure. I should've just opened
a board game center instead.
I can't believe
I-jun knows how to play go.
He even does traditional painting.
If he were born during the Joseon Dynasty,
he would've made a name for himself.
I bet he'll be successful.
You're the successful one.
You must be very proud of your daughter.
Right. I am.
By the way, you look very young.
-I'll let you guys be.
-Okay.
Are you feeling unwell?
No, it's nothing. Don't worry about it.
You keep drinking water.
Are you parched?
Actually,
I met with a doctor.
Apparently, I have burning mouth syndrome.
I see.
Then is your mouth feeling hot?
Does it burn?
A bit. I'm sure it'll go away.
Have this.
Thanks.
You need to keep your mouth
hydrated at all times.
Suck on candy or chew gum often.
You should also drink a lot.
Right. I'll get you some warm water.
No, that's okay.
I think you should know that
I've always had free jjajangmyeon.
I was able
to feed myself with my go skills.
Can you take that back?
Come on. What do you take me for?
Old age has been messing with my sight.
Shouldn't you respect your elders?
I believe it's unfair
to mention your age during a match.
Forget it.
Father, are you sulking?
No, I'm not.
And why do you address me that way?
Then what else should I call you?
Fine. I'll take it back.
-But just this once.
-Forget it.
Here. I took it back. It's your turn now.
It's your turn. I took it back.
Oh, dear. So that was your plan.
In that case…
Yeong-guk.
Cho-hui.
I just came by to see
how you were doing. I wanted…
Take this.
Vitamin C is good for your health.
You didn't have to do this.
I don't think I can invite you in,
so can we talk outside?
Just the two of us?
-I'd love that.
-Okay.
I'm bored out of my mind.
How could you say that
when I even grilled that fish for you?
You see,
snacks taste the best
when you're gossiping.
Anything interesting to talk about?
You need to fix that bad habit of yours.
Now, that's interesting.
It's Mr. Chang and Ms. Yu.
Look at that.
This is going to be interesting.
-Hey, you're here.
-Sit down.
Don't do that!
What would you like…
All right. Got it.
All right.
-Are you guys done?
-Yes.
So who won?
Do you want some food?
Sure. Please prepare a feast for us.
I'm counting on you.
Okay. I'll prepare a lavish meal for you.
Thanks. Is there anything you want…
Come on. It's not my fault you lost.
Will you keep sulking like that?
Wait up, Father. Gosh.
Wait for me.
NAM-SUK
-The person you have called…
-Why isn't she picking up?
I can't hear them
since they're too far away.
You see, Cho-hui.
There's something I want to tell you.
Listen carefully.
"To the love of my life.
I will never forget you
until my very last breath.
I know my chance will never come."
-Can you hear them?
-He's reciting a poem.
He's reciting a poem? That lunatic…
"Please stay beautiful as you are."
That's a poem by Yi Sang.
Gosh, Cho-hui. You and I click so well.
I think we're soulmates.
The reason
I recited his poem
is that I still like--
Yeong-guk.
Yes?
He's confessing his love,
but I can't hear that well.
Me neither!
You've been so good to me
ever since we first met.
I'm always grateful for that.
-Don't mention it.
-However…
I've never had any romantic feelings
for you.
I hope we can continue being good friends.
Is this because of Hwa-jeong?
What?
You're turning me down
and drawing the line
because of her, aren't you?
That's not true.
This has nothing to do with her.
I should get going.
Gosh, she has prepared
all kinds of seafood for us.
Father, try this.
These sea squirts are known
for their scrumptious aftertaste.
No, thanks.
Honey, are you upset you lost the game?
Gosh, you're too competitive.
What? Ms. Dentist is the same.
She's also impossibly stubborn.
You take after him.
I'm not like him.
Of course, she does.
Like father, like daughter.
Gosh. I've noticed this
from the beginning,
but you guys aren't close at all.
What does it matter when you're family?
It does matter. It's still a relationship.
Mother, this won't do.
There's this ice breaker game
called Two Truths and One Lie.
They should play that.
-Cut that nonsense.
-They should--
When it's awkward like this,
it's best to just eat.
Father, try some of this.
Here. Open up.
I don't eat anything slimy.
He doesn't eat seafood.
Goodness. You're all about the sauce
when having raw fish, aren't you?
Just trust me and have a bite.
I promise you that
you'll appreciate the taste of seafood.
Why should I trust you?
Because
we played go together.
My grandfather used to say,
"Playing go brings good friends.
Being able to play the game together
means you're already good friends."
What? Does that mean you two are friends?
Don't be ridiculous.
All right, open up. Come on.
Open up.
Good.
Chew well. It'll taste salty at first,
but then you'll get a hint of sourness.
It seems like you like it.
How is it? Doesn't it taste fresh?
Well, it's not bad.
Okay. You've mastered
sea squirts now. Next up are spoon worms.
That's too disgusting to eat.
I know, but the texture--
-No way.
-Come on.
-I don't want to.
-Try it. Come on.
-Try it.
-Never!
-Give it a go!
-Come on!
-Try it. It's tasty.
No, I don't want to.
-Please.
-It's strange.
-Try the spoon worm.
-This is their first time meeting.
-If she cans, so can you.
-So how does he seem
to blend in so well?
-How is it?
-How does he make us
-It's not bad.
-feel so comfortable?
Now, the spoon worms.
How does he warm our hearts like so?
-I really can't eat that.
-The texture is--
No. It disgusts me.
I don't like raw food.
Gosh, I can't believe
you finished two bowls.
This is surprising
for someone who eats like a bird.
It's because I'm eating
with my entire family.
The best meal is one
that you have with your family.
You're right.
By the way,
it seems that this is your hometown.
Does that mean you live with your parents?
No, sir. They both passed away
when I was little.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Then do you have other family members?
Dad, that's a private matter.
It's okay.
My grandfather passed away
when I was in middle school.
Now, it's just me.
Goodness. You must've been lonely.
The people here have treated me
like family and taken great care of me.
Shall we go?
-How about some coffee?
-Sure.
That sounds good.
That's okay.
Why not?
Let's have some coffee before we go.
We should go now
if we want to avoid traffic.
You're right. It's the weekend.
Then I'll get some coffee to go.
-You can drink it on your way--
-No, thanks.
There's no need for that.
Dad.
Let me go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Dad, what is the matter?
Were you aware
that he was an orphan?
"Orphan"? How could you say that?
He had a family as well.
He just lost them when he was little.
-It's not a sin to have no parents.
-It is.
What?
I have nothing personal against him,
-but you shouldn't be seeing him.
-Dad.
No parent in this world
would be supportive
of their child dating an orphan!
Honey!
Break up before it gets any deeper.
You haven't been dating for long.
I don't want someone with a flaw like that
to be my family.
In that case, I have a flaw as well.
What?
I also lost my mom when I was little.
On top of that, I have a stepmom.
Yoon Hye-jin!
I have a flaw too.
So why do you think
he's the only one with a flaw?
Damn it.
You even smoke?
You do everything that's unhealthy.
Even Hye-jin never nags at me.
I'm sorry.
With or without you present,
I shouldn't have said what I said.
She sure does take after you.
She also admits to her mistakes quickly.
This may sound like an excuse,
but she was also lonely growing up.
After her mother died,
I relied on alcohol for a long time.
I was a neglectful father.
JIHYE ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Never once did I pack her backpack.
Thanks to my negligence,
she grew up too fast.
I'm going to school.
I'll carry that guilt with me forever.
It's not that I don't like you.
And I know it's selfish of me to expect
someone else to do what I couldn't.
But I hope she marries into a big family
so that she never gets lonely again.
Finally receiving the love she couldn't.
You got it all wrong.
Hye-jin…
received tons of love growing up.
If not, she wouldn't be able
to give others so much love.
The weather's so nice.
I apologize for what I said earlier.
It was wrong of me.
That's okay.
Your dad crossed the line first.
Hye-jin.
That's just how parents feel.
To be frank,
what he said was downright unfair.
But you see, it's hard
to be objective about your own child.
It's easy to spot other people's flaws,
but not your own child's.
You just want to turn a blind eye to it.
I promise to tell him off big time,
so don't resent him too much.
That'd be too harsh of a punishment
for someone who dotes on you.
He does?
We visited a dozen flower shops
before finally buying those orchids.
I'm looking for something
meaningful and rare.
Something that brings
success, good health,
and luck.
The wallpaper on his phone
is you as a little girl.
I heard it's pouring in Gangwon Province.
I'm worried about Hye-jin.
Give her a call if you're worried.
I heard there will be a typhoon too.
He doesn't care
about the weather back home,
but he always knows
how the weather is down here.
That's not all.
He's quiet at home.
But he becomes chatty
and boasts about you when he goes out.
Soon, he's going to have no friends left.
Hye-jin.
At times, you guys may bicker
because you don't always see eye to eye,
but he always has
nothing but love for you.
Do you like her a lot?
Yes.
But…
I like her as a friend.
What do you mean?
We're actually just friends.
I had no choice but to lie
since there was a misunderstanding.
Nothing you might worry about happened.
-I'm sorry.
-So you're telling me
that you're not my daughter's boyfriend?
Yes.
But I meant what I said.
She's a warmhearted person.
So I…
truly hope that she'll find
someone good that she deserves.
And that…
could be you.
HWAJEONG RAW FISH RESTAURANT
Oh, you came out.
Let's go eat something.
We just did.
Right.
Then how about some coffee?
I prefer tea.
We seriously don't get along.
What an awkward relationship they have.
Really? I think it's nice.
Wait up.
Let me take you
to a place that serves good tea.
But to be frank, I make the best tea.
All right.
Gosh.
Okay.
All right.
I can't be late again.
Aren't you tutoring today?
Yes.
They're brother and sister,
and they never listen to me.
Really? Call me if you need help.
I'm good with kids.
I once aspired
to become a preschool teacher.
Don't lie.
I'm serious.
-Really?
-Yes.
Okay. I'm going to the restroom.
Sure.
ROMAGNA
"I have a free ticket.
Would you like…
I heard this musical is fun.
Let's watch it together
if you have time, Hye-jin.
They sing like this."
Hye-jin.
-Gang-uk.
-What are you doing here?
I'm having coffee with my friend.
Hey, Seong-hyeon.
Hey, Gang-uk.
What a small world.
I was going to introduce her
to you next time we met.
Say hi. This is
my girlfriend, Yoon Hye-jin.
Wait. Do you two know each other?
Oh, I see.
He's my high school friend.
Didn't I tell you?
I see.
No way. This is crazy.
-This is amazing.
-You're right.
Gosh. You guys look good together.
I can't believe this.
Here.
-Done?
-Yes.
Gosh.
-Here you go.
-Goodness.
-It doesn't fit.
-Should we make it again?
-No, it's too late.
-It's not too late!
I'm just saying that it's not too late
even though you think it is…
What are you doing? Make it again.
Don't look at me.
-Don't.
-What's wrong with you?
A dog is barking.
We had a blast today thanks to you.
It was my pleasure.
I also had fun thanks to you.
About that coffee stain,
rub it with some baking soda,
detergent mixed with vinegar,
or carbonated water.
You'd make a better housewife than me.
What do you not know?
Dad, drive safely.
All right.
Father, pull over if you get drowsy.
It can be dangerous.
You. Can you come over here?
Me?
Goodness. I wonder
what he wants to tell me.
-Closer.
-What is it?
Wait. I get ticklish
when someone whispers in my ear.
Fine.
Why do you talk casually to me?
Oh, that? It's sort of
a philosophy of mine.
Simply put, it sounds
more friendly that way.
Not to me, you bastard.
-We'll get going then.
-Okay. Drive safely.
-Bye.
-What did he say?
-Pardon?
-"Pardon"?
-Pardon? I…
What did…
What did he say to you?
You like him, don't you?
What?
How about we get some snacks
at a rest area if the traffic gets heavy?
I know you have a sweet tooth.
It's okay. I already have a snack.
What?
Why did you follow me
all the way here? You're being a nuisance.
Well, you see,
I tend to be the curious type.
You're not answering my question.
I've always been curious.
Is this your boat?
Yes.
Why did you bring it up here?
I mean, how did you even bring it here?
I looked for a helicopter
and even rented a truck.
It was quite difficult.
But in the end, I succeeded.
So why did you do such a thing?
Boats belong in the ocean.
I wanted it to appreciate a different view
since it had been sailing all its life.
To tell you the truth,
this was my grandfather's.
I see.
You're definitely not normal.
You wasted money and time
for such a sentimental reason?
I was expecting to hear
some grand explanation.
Why do you live here like this?
Are you picking a fight with me?
No, I'm asking out of pure curiosity.
What did you do
after graduating from college?
I mean, during those five years.
Fine. The past is in the past.
What's important is the present.
You're just taking a break now, right?
I get it.
You get tired.
You can't run a marathon forever.
You came down here
to refresh yourself
and plan for your future.
This is temporary, right?
You're wrong.
I'm going to live like this forever.
I'm content with this life.
You must be kidding me.
That's a total waste of resources.
It's like playing Minesweeper
on a high-tech computer.
You're driving a sports car
across the rice paddies
instead of the highway.
Don't look down on the beauty
of simplicity Minesweeper has to offer.
And rice paddies look magnificent
on a summer night.
You have no idea.
Right.
I was crazy to think I could actually
have a conversation with you.
Do you want a flower in your hair
to look like a pretty lunatic?
No, thanks.
It's going to be a long walk.
Goodbye, then.
Darn it.
I'm mortified that I had
some kind of hope even for a moment.
Mi-seon, why did you call Chief Hong over…
Why are you crying?
I asked Eun-cheol out,
but he said no.
Don't cry.
YOON DENTAL CLINIC
Take the call. I'll take it from here.
I'm sorry.
Mom, I'm working.
What? Is it serious?
Where did you hurt yourself?
She put her hand down as she fell.
Yes, it's a compound fracture.
Would she be able to have surgery
as soon as possible?
Okay. Thanks.
Thank you.
Fortunately, my friend had
some time today,
so I scheduled the surgery.
Don't worry. The surgery will go well.
Thanks.
Let's go to Seoul right now.
You're coming?
Of course. We should cancel
our afternoon appointments.
But Ms. Lee Jeong-yeon
is coming by in the evening
because her makeshift tooth fell out.
She needs to get that treated.
You should stay here. I'll go by myself.
Just go straight to Seoul in this.
My dad and Hyeon-seon already arrived.
I can just take the bus
at the terminal. I should get going.
Call me as soon as you get there.
-Okay.
-All right.
Oh, my goodness.
What are you doing here?
Is she going somewhere?
Well…
Ms. Pyo!
Officer Choi.
Get in. I'll drive you to Seoul.
What?
Come on.
Thank you. How did you know?
You're going back to Seoul today?
Yes. I'm coming back next week.
Try to focus more on the subtitles.
Your show tends to lack in that area
compared to the other shows.
Thanks for the advice.
My pleasure.
Did Hye-jin's parents go home safely?
I think so.
Look, I'm just asking out of curiosity.
You're done with that job, right?
Yes. I worked 7 hours and made 61,040 won.
It was a great success.
Really? Then why does it seem
the job is still ongoing?
Then maybe it is.
Have a safe trip.
Gosh.
I came out for a quiet walk.
Why are you tagging along?
What are you, a leech?
Hey, I'm also just trying to exercise.
It's not easy
to maintain this figure, you know?
Oh, my. Isn't that Yeong-guk?
Yeong-guk!
You. Take a detour.
Why?
Why are you drinking here alone
when you can't even hold your liquor?
I've only had one sip so far.
Two sips, and you'll die.
Just go home and sleep.
It's all your fault.
Cho-hui turned me down because of you.
I'm sorry you failed to win
your first love's heart once again.
But don't you think
it's so unfair to blame that on me?
That's rich coming from you.
Did you forget
what you did three years ago?
You wanted a divorce just because
I took off my socks inside out.
I promised that
I wouldn't do that ever again.
I begged and asked you for forgiveness,
but you kicked me out that day.
I was downright dumbfounded.
But I accepted it. Do you know why?
Because you said
you couldn't live with me anymore.
I did everything you wanted.
So why do you keep getting in my way?
You'll never know why I wanted a divorce.
Fine. Let's keep it that way forever.
Just live your life.
Hey, Hwa-jeong.
What did you mean by that?
Why are you insinuating
that there was another reason?
You can't just leave like this.
Do you want me to suffer forever?
-Hey!
-Gosh.
What are you doing?
You can't grab her like that.
You're a civil servant.
She may be your ex-wife,
but you have no right to do that.
I only grabbed her
because I wanted to talk.
Besides, I've always had a weak grip,
so she's beaten me
in arm-wrestling every single time.
-Right?
-Yes. He's weak as a kitten.
Don't forget that I have eyes everywhere.
I know.
And why did you have to mention
Cho-hui to her? You're pathetic.
Hwa-jeong!
Gosh.
Wait up.
I'll pretend I didn't see that.
As if.
Right?
I can't promise you that.
It's better to talk about it, you know?
If you keep bottling up your emotions,
you'll get sick.
Talking is like pooping.
You need to relieve yourself
regularly to stay healthy.
You're unhealthy right now.
Hey, Seong-hyeon.
Hey, where are you?
I got off work.
I'm on my way home.
I see. I'm on my way to Seoul.
I had to leave right away,
so I couldn't even say bye to you.
That's fine. You were busy. I understand.
You're coming back anyway.
Right.
Hye-jin.
Yes?
When I go back down to Gongjin,
can you meet up with me?
Meet up?
Of course, I can.
I really hope you can.
I have something to tell you.
What?
They fixed the streetlamp.
It's finally working.
Are you happy
that you could fix it today?
Yes. I feel great.
You put off such a simple task.
An IT powerhouse
should always keep the people safe.
I'll get going.
Where are you going?
I have a ton of complaints.
Listen carefully. Number one.
How could there be
no Wi-Fi at the community center?
The elderly enjoy watching videos online.
Number two. The garbage bags…
Hye-jin, are you there?
Yes, I am.
Let me know when you're back.
I'll treat you to a meal.
Okay. I'll see you soon.
Okay. Drive safely.
I will.
No. I can't be late again.
She's a warmhearted person.
So I…
truly hope that she'll find
someone good that she deserves.
And that could be you.
MEDICAL CHART
It seems you're sleeping better now.
At this rate,
I think we can lower the dosage.
Okay.
Great.
Today,
we're going to get
to the root of your fear.
Do you still feel that…
those around you…
Goodness. What an unfortunate boy.
As if losing his parents early wasn't
enough, he lost his grandpa too.
Goodness.
I guess it's true that some people
bring death to those around them.
So everyone you loved
has left you?
Yes.
And I'm to blame.
It's because of me.
Gosh, I was so scared.
Chief Hong.
-Would you like to say hello?
-Hello.
I'm Yoon Hye-jin.
Gosh.
You keep talking about Gongjin
as if all roads lead there.
Du-sik, life may seem long,
but it really isn't.
Chief Hong.
I've been regretting
not telling you how I felt 14 years ago.
The conclusion I came to is this.
I like you.