(First Choice Episode 12)
I want to sleep...
on the sofa.
Zhao Zhao's bed is too small. I can't sleep in it.
Don't blame me if you get a cold.
And you said you don't care about me...
Zhao Zhao!
Wake up.
We're going to be late. Put on your shoes.
Zhao Zhao, let's go.
We're going to be late.
It's the weekend. Why didn't you sleep in?
Weekend?
Weekend...
Zhao Zhao.
I forgot that today is Saturday.
There's no kindergarten today.
You must be sleepy.
Sleep some more.
It smells good.
Doesn't it?
Go wash up. It will be ready soon.
You're quite talented.
You have no idea how many rubber bands...
I broke during practice.
Luo An.
Thank you for taking such good care of Zhao Zhao.
It's been tough on you...
all these years.
From now on,
I'll work hard to be a good dad.
Zhao Zhao.
Let's eat.
Daddy Prince has magic.
He can make heart-shaped eggs.
This is all we have in the fridge.
Let's make do with this.
If you like it,
Daddy Prince will make it for you every day.
I like it!
Daddy Prince cooks better...
than Daddy Long Legs.
Zhao Zhao.
You have a dad now.
You can't call others Dad.
Do you understand?
Shouldn't I explain to Zhao Zhao...
about my relationship with her?
She can't just call...
someone else Dad.
Okay.
Zhao Zhao.
Let me tell you something.
I know.
Daddy Prince is my dad.
That's right!
That's my daughter. You're so smart.
Zhao Zhao. You're too young.
You might not understand.
This man...
is your dad.
But he's different from Daddy Long Legs.
That means...
I know Daddy Prince is my real dad.
Daddy Long Legs isn't.
You're smart like me.
Zhao Zhao, don't forget...
you have a dad now.
You can only call him Uncle.
Call me Dad. Let me hear it.
Dad! I have a dad now!
Good girl. Here.
Here.
This one... Look, there are four of them.
Zhao Zhao and I don't eat bean paste.
Why are you buying so many of them?
It's for Wen Shi.
Wen Shi is going on a tour abroad.
I'm afraid he won't be used to the food there.
So I thought I'd buy him some.
It's hard to find it when he's abroad.
Abroad?
That's good.
Get him more.
- Childish. - Ma'am, congratulations.
You're the 10,000th customer...
to patronize our store!
We've prepared a three-day, two-night...
Hot Spring Park package just for you.
Thank you for your support all this time.
Really?
Thank you.
Zhao Zhao, Mom won a prize.
That's great! Zhao Zhao can finally...
go on a trip with Dad and Mom.
That depends on Dad.
Please show me your ID.
I'll register your information.
Is an ID number okay?
I lost my wallet a while ago.
Why do you have it?
That night,
you left it at the hotel reception.
Thank you.
I'm coming.
Why are you here? Come on in.
Come on, Zhao Zhao.
Come.
Zhao Zhao heard that you were injured.
She kept saying she wanted to see Daddy Long...
I mean, Uncle Chen.
Isn't that right, Zhao Zhao?
Uncle Chen.
Is your hand better?
It was all Zhao Zhao's fault.
You got hurt because of me.
Of course not.
I recovered a long time ago.
I just couldn't bear to remove it.
It's a medal for protecting Zhao Zhao.
Isn't it cool?
Yes!
Here. I have a small gift for you.
Here.
You're living such a messy life,
but you're still in the mood to please some man.
Some man?
Wen Shi is my friend.
What am I to you then?
You...
If my hand is crippled,
Xiao Bai will feel guilty for the rest of her life.
Perhaps she'll soften up and marry me then.
You're not skilled enough.
You can't blame it on your small injury.
No, it's torn.
- Hurry. - Are you all right?
Xiao Bai, no. I need bandages.
This... This is acting!
It's a shame he didn't become an actor.
Why's he playing the flute?
What's going on between you and Huo Ling?
He's Zhao Zhao's biological father.
This is something I can't give Zhao Zhao no matter what.
I just want to know...
if you two are back together.
Of course not.
We're just like...
an ordinary divorced couple.
For the sake of their children, they co-exist in peace.
That's understandable. It's understandable.
I understand.
- It hurts. - How did you get hurt too?
Wen Shi, get the alcohol disinfectant and gauze.
Okay.
How blatantly lovey-dovey.
He really has no respect for you and Uncle Shen.
Apart from being sarcastic,
what else can you do?
Don't be impatient.
I already have a plan.
I'm just waiting for your approval.
Mr. Huo.
Ms. Bai knows how you feel.
She'll definitely say yes.
Luo An is so stupid.
If I don't make it clear,
she'll think I'm with her...
because of Zhao Zhao.
Mr. Huo.
I've got bad news.
Something happened at the Healing Gallery.