(First Choice Episode 4)
Bai Luo An.
Are you worried about me?
You're Dejia's investor.
If anything happens to you,
Yuexin will go down with you.
Let go.
I said, let go!
Let go?
You disappeared for five years when I let go.
You even got married and had a kid with someone else.
Bai Luo An. You're so cruel.
When did I...
We've each started our lives over.
Let's not pester each other.
First, it was Gu Xiao Yu. Now, it's Chen Wen Shi.
What do they have that I don't?
I said let go!
Let go!
Let go of me!
Huo Ling!
Let go!
Let go of me, Huo Ling!
Any news from Shen Qing Yi?
(Six years ago)
Mr. Huo.
Have some water.
Xiao Yu's corneas...
were donated to him.
I'm blind.
If the Shen family wants to call off the engagement, so be it.
I, Huo Ling,
will not be controlled by anyone!
- Mr. Huo. - Let go!
I want to hear it from her!
Mr. Huo. The doctor said you just had surgery.
You need to rest. You can't do strenuous activities.
Mr. Huo!
Who are you?
- This is... - I'm...
a caregiver Ms. Shen hired...
to take care of you.
Shen Qing Yi hired her?
Xiao Yu.
I just want to see your eyes one more time.
Just one more time.
Then I'll leave.
She did.
Here, Mr. Huo. Here.
Come slowly. Be careful. Come.
Mr. Huo.
Ms. Shen still cares about you.
Your eyes...
You can see?
It's just that the swelling has gone down.
But...
it's enough for me to see some people's true colors.
Bai Luo An.
When are you going to stop lying to me?
You know everything?
- I... - Shen Qing Yi kicked me away...
when I needed help the most.
Why would she hire...
a caregiver to help me?
So...
why did you stay with me?
I...
- It hurts. - Are you okay?
Don't move.
You like me.
Mr. Huo.
Since your eyesight has recovered,
I don't think there's a need...
for me to stay with you anymore.
I'm officially resigning...
from now on.
After all,
you don't pay me.
I don't think I need to report to you.
Then, take care.
Goodbye.
Who said you can leave me?
From the moment you lit up my dark world,
I decided then...
to spend the rest of my life loving you...
and protecting you.
Will you give me this chance?
Xiao Yu.
Although our relationship didn't start out in a genuine manner,
I think I'm really in love with Huo Ling.
I do.
Huo Ling.
Huo Ling?
The person who donated the corneas to me...
was your first love, Gu Xiao Yu.
Yes.
That's why you approached me.
All the care and concern you showed for me...
was because of him.
I...
I've always wanted to explain this to you.
But I haven't had the chance.
- Actually... - You're such a good actress.
I was so blind.
I thought you really loved me.
So all of this was fake.
Let me explain, Huo Ling.
Forget it!
I won't be fooled by you anymore.
Yes, I admit it!
I got close to you with an ulterior motive.
But...
But then I...
I have sincere feelings for you.
We've been together for so long, Huo Ling.
- I... - Keep your phony sincerity!
What makes you think...
I'd be willing to be a substitute for a dead person?
You're so cruel.
When I was in despair,
you were the one who gave me hope.
And you're the one who took it all away.
That's not what happened, Huo Ling.
The doctor said your eyes weren't healed yet.
You weren't supposed to be agitated.
- So I... - Enough!
The divorce papers have been drafted.
Don't let me see you again.
(Pregnancy test report)
Don't forget, Huo Ling.
Five years ago,
you were the one who ended our relationship.
Since that's the case,
please move the Healing Gallery...
out of the Art Center as soon as possible.
Don't let me see you again.
Huo Ling, calm down.
Mixing art with life...
has always been Dejia's philosophy.
What Yuexin Healing is doing now...
is allowing special children from ordinary families...
to use Dejia as an art platform...
to heal their bodies and minds.
I didn't buy Dejia for charity.
I thought because you've been in the dark,
you'd know better...
that you need to light the way for others as you move forward.
I was wrong about you.