(First Choice Episode 18)
I've got a piece of good news...
that I haven't had the chance to tell you.
Luo An and I are getting remarried.
She'll be Mrs. Huo soon.
Does she have the right to stand here now?
Uncle Gong?
Mr. Huo.
Are you admitting that you're doing this for personal reasons?
I admit that I stopped Dejia's development,
but that was not because of Bai Luo An.
It's because during my time at Dejia,
I saw its purpose for existing...
and its vitality.
Here,
people can feel the charm of art.
And through art,
they can relieve mental stress and illness.
If it weren't for Dejia,
none of this would exist.
This is a business.
We're not running a charity.
Don't you know...
you're affecting the company by repeatedly delaying it?
Don't worry about that.
Shareholders,
Junyue and Ningxin...
have reached a strategic agreement.
They're investing in the company.
This is the collaboration agreement.
I think this result...
will satisfy everyone.
As for you,
I asked you to take over Dejia's development.
But what have you done?
You asked Uncle Gong to sell it...
to relieve the deficit you caused.
Don't think that just because you're careful,
no one would know about it.
Where's the proof of that?
I suggest you sort yourself out first.
You are blind now.
Do you still want to take over the company?
Here.
Let me see.
Who would want a blind man as their chairman?
What are you talking about, Huo Wei?
Why do you always hide behind a woman?
Be a man,
Huo Ling.
Huo Wei.
You're my brother.
You shouldn't be used by outsiders...
to hurt your own family.
Stop with the nonsense.
If you can, prove that you're not blind.
If I remember correctly,
this blue shirt...
was my gift to you last year, right?
Although his eyes were injured previously,
the main cause of his blindness...
is the pressure on the nerves caused by the blood clots in your brain.
I just checked.
Mr. Huo's eyes seem to be reacting to light.
Perhaps after the surgery,
the blood clots are starting to dissipate.
Doctor.
How long will it take for me to fully recover?
I'm not sure about that.
It depends on your condition.
Get some rest first.
That's great.
I'll inform Ms. Bai.
There's no need.
The fewer people know about this, the better.
Since they all think I'm blind,
I'll keep up the act.
That way, they'll let their guard down.
I know what to do.
You're not blind.
How is that possible?
If I don't do this,
how can I draw you out?
Uncle Gong.
These are your men, right?
They've all been caught.
If I call the police now,
Huo Wei,
what will happen to you?
You're also involved in my mom's fall, right?
Uncle Gong.
What do you think?
Min Yan, call the police.
Let her go.
All of you, get out of here!
What are you doing, Huo Wei?
I'm sorry, An An.
Drive.
- Huo Ling. - Luo An.
Luo An!
Xiao Wei.
An An.
It's time to eat.
It's noodles with tomato and egg.
When I was at the orphanage,
didn't I often make this for you?
Yes. but no matter how I made from then on...
I couldn't make it taste the same.
You had just arrived at the orphanage.
You were so skinny.
As for me,
I didn't know how to cook.
I only knew how to make this.
I thought...
I could make you eat more,
grow bigger and taller.
That way, when other kids bully you,
you can protect yourself.
If it were possible,
I'd rather not grow up.
If I weren't the Huo family's illegitimate son,
I could have stayed in the orphanage...
with you forever.
What happened to you in the Huo family all these years?
Why did you turn out this way?
Let's eat.
Xiao Wei.
From now on,
I'm your mother.
After they brought me back to the Huo family,
at one point, I thought I had a home...
and a family.
But when I found out who I really was,
I realized...
Fu Wan Pei had never truly accepted me.
She was just afraid.
She was afraid I'd take everything from Huo Ling.
That's why she raised me away from the family.
It wasn't until Huo Ling lost his sight in a car accident...
that she brought me home.
It's funny.
At that time,
I treasured even the slightest bit...
of fake warmth.
Here, Xiao Wei.
Have some more.
Thank you, Mom.
How do you like living at home?
- Eat more. - Okay.
You're too skinny.
Ling.
Eat up.
You too, Mom.
Okay.
But it didn't take long for Huo Ling to recover.
So I became a pawn,
a pawn...
that was hated by others.
Mom.
Ling.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It was not like that, Xiao Wei.
They've never accepted me!
They've never loved me!
Why did they bring me back?
I had just lost my mother.
And then I lost you.
Why do they get to take away...
everything I have?
It's because I have the blood of the Huo family.
That's the meaning of my life.
Xiao Wei.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Don't punish yourself for other people's mistakes.
You don't understand anything.
I'm sorry.
An An.
You're not me.
How can you feel my pain?
How can I let them off so easily?
I'll make them know...
what it's like to lose everything.
Xiao Wei, that's not true.
It's not like that!
Say goodbye to your teacher.
Bye.
Xuan Xuan, I'm here.
Come, Bei Bei.
Grandma is here, right?
Okay.
- Bye. - Okay.
Mr. Huo.
How did it go?
The car was abandoned...
in an old parking lot.
There are no security cameras.
I don't know where their final destination is.
But I've sent people...
to look for them in all the possible places.
I'm sure we'll find something soon.
I failed to protect Luo An.
I didn't think Huo Wei would do that.
Mr. Huo. It happened so suddenly.
Don't blame yourself.
Besides,
Mr. Huo and Ms. Bai...
have known each other since they were in the orphanage.
I don't think he'll let anything happen to Ms. Bai.
I hope Huo Wei...
won't go to the point of no return.
I'll call Huo Ling later.
Think carefully before talking.
Or I'll kill you.