(First Choice Episode 13)
We trusted you!
How could you let our children use toxic paint?
Parents, please calm down.
This must be a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding? My Xiao Bao took your drawing class...
and pooped all night.
Now he's in the hospital with an IV drip!
If anything happens to our Liang Liang,
I'll haunt you from beyond the grave!
Yuexin has repeatedly challenged...
Dejia's bottom line...
and played with children's lives.
I hereby announce...
that from today onwards,
Yuexin's partnership with Dejia is terminated.
We also reserve the right to sue Yuexin...
for damages to Dejia's finances...
and reputation.
The matter hasn't been investigated.
You're jumping to conclusions...
based on the parents' words.
Mr. Huo.
- Isn't that too arbitrary? - Arbitrary?
Bai Luo An.
Haven't you implicated Dejia enough?
We've put up with you for a long time.
Is it Dejia who doesn't want to put up with me...
or is it you, Ms. Shen?
You...
Ling.
Many reporters are already getting wind of this.
If we don't shut it down now,
we'll be implicated for sure.
Also,
Junyue will hold a board meeting soon.
We can't afford any mistakes.
Ms. Bai.
Dejia will send an investigation team to investigate this.
In the meantime,
cooperate with the Art Center's investigation.
I'll be honest with you.
Dejia's acquisition...
was not done for the sake of art.
It was because of this land.
Huo Ling wants to demolish the Art Center.
Dejia has taken over...
the most desirable spot in Ning City.
I don't think anyone...
would do that...
just for art or charity.
It's the chance to build a business district worth 10 billion.
What a pity.
The project you've worked so hard on for so many years...
will be torn down...
along with this building.
I didn't acquire Dejia for charity.
From now on,
I'll try my best to be a good dad.
Dad! I have a dad now!
Here.
I'll feed you.
I want this.
Don't buy her too much.
Kids need to eat more.
It's okay.
I've made it through these years.
I can do it.
Find out...
who instructed the parents...
to make a ruckus.
Shen Qing Yi is so aggressive.
I think someone doesn't want me to go back to Junyue...
and is using the Healing Gallery...
as an excuse.
Understood.
Who is it?
Liang Liang's mom? Please hold on.
How dare you come here? If it weren't for you,
Liang Liang wouldn't have to suffer like this.
Liang Liang's mom.
Don't be mad.
I'm here to explain the situation to you today.
Look at this.
This is our work log.
I brought it with me.
It has the kids' sign-in sheet.
This day,
which is 10 days ago,
Liang Liang had a low fever...
and couldn't attend our therapy class.
He took the day off.
The next time he came to our therapy class...
was a week later.
In this class,
Liang Liang already had small rashes...
on his mouth and hands.
Coincidentally,
the kids in that particular class...
also claimed to be allergic to the paint.
That's because they used your toxic paint.
What? Are you turning the blame on me?
No. That's not what I meant.
Regarding the paint,
we have an explanation here.
Look at this.
This is the production and operation license...
for the paint we use at the Healing Gallery.
It says it's all-natural.
It meets the criteria.
As for the rest of the paints,
we've already sent them to the relevant department...
for quality testing.
If anything happens,
we'll be responsible to the end.
So the reason I'm here today...
is I'm hoping...
that you can take your child to the hospital...
for a checkup...
to see if the cause of the allergy...
is our paint,
or if it's hand, foot, and mouth disease.
What are you talking about? Get out of my house!
Liang Liang's mom, you...
Have you cried enough?
Do you have the energy to carry luggage?
I don't.
Didn't you want to avoid suspicion?
Why are you back?
As the people in charge of Dejia and Yuexin,
we should avoid suspicion.
But I missed you two.
Don't move.
I'm the one who's hurt.
Why are you yelling at me?
You're injured, but you're still acting tough.
I shouldn't have placed it directly.
It might be a bit irritating.
The gallery was framed.
I know.
It all started because of me.
I've already sent Min Yan to deal with it.
I need more time.
Huo Ling.
Are you hiding something from me?
No.
Mr. Huo.
When were you going to tell me...
about Dejia's land development project?
What did Shen Qing Yi say to you?
That Junyue acquired Dejia for its land...
and will demolish the Art Center overnight?
Bai Luo An.
Don't you know how I feel about you?
Are you suspecting me?
Don't you have a conscience?
I'm nothing.
How can I compare...
to a multi-billion-dollar real estate project?
Besides, you were in cahoots with Shen Qing Yi that day.
Who's the one without a conscience?
Are you jealous...
of me and Shen Qing Yi?
I'm not.
Fine.
You are not.
Luo An.
I did come to Dejia...
for the land development project.
But when I saw...
what you did...
for Zhao Zhao...
and the children at the Healing Gallery,
I gave up on...
tearing down the Art Center.
And because of that,
Junyue's board of directors are dissatisfied with me.
What happened at the Healing Gallery wasn't simple.
The true culprit...
isn't Shen Qing Yi.
Give me some time.
I can handle it.
I can find out the truth on my own.
But if Shen Qing Yi is involved,
don't worry too much about her.
Silly girl.
I only feel sorry for you and Zhao Zhao.
Luo An.
I know you're capable.
You can take good care of Zhao Zhao on your own.
But I just hope...
that when you need help the most,
I'll be the person you rely on the most.