"REIMU TAXI"
This woman dies with me.
"PAY"
Hi there.
Oh, really?
Good.
Rather tomorrow.
In the afternoon.
Yes.
Okay.
He has to apologize to
Bruce and Roman. Seriously.
Yeah, go ahead.
Not for me.
Right?
What a waste.
How I wanted to take her life
and end mine.
Fine. My search continues.
"VACANT"
"HIRED"
"PAY"
We live in a dystopia.
A living hell.
That was fine with me.
I was happy.
But now that's gone. Taken.
I long for death.
But I won't die alone.
I'll kill a woman.
My revenge on society.
My love was taken from me,
so it's my right and duty...
do the same to someone else.
"VACANT"
"HIRED"
Are we there yet?
Hey!
Why are we on the freeway?
Huh?
Stop that shit!
I said why the fuck
are we on the freeway!
Stop the car!
Get off the freeway!
You fuck.
You better kill me.
Are you stupid?
I said are you fucking stupid? Hey!
From time to time, I think,
screw vengeance. I just want to die.
So I let some fuckers try to kill me.
But it doesn't work.
Humans are built tougher
than you think.
My wife was hunted.
Like an impala chased by a lion.
Like a baby penguin
eaten by an albatross.
The murderer cornered her,
then slowed down.
He played with her.
My wife hated to be scared.
She couldn't even watch horror movies.
I lost my mind just thinking about
how scared she must have been.
Stop!
Stop! Stop! No! No! No!
My wife was captured. Gagged and bound.
Then she was placed in a tub.
Water filled it slowly.
Her fear and despair were unimaginable.
I lost so much blood and all
I could do was to watch her die.
I will never forget the laughter,
I heard from under the helmet.
My wife was killed mercilessly.
Then the murderer took
his own life in front of me.
That is why I must kill someone,
without mercy,
and then die.
It's my retribution, my mourning.
Bon appetit.
"HIRED"
Mister, you can look.
But no accidents, okay?
Enemy of women. Die now!
We are all masochists.
We like to be tied down
and stripped of our freedom.
Maybe this is the reason,
why we gravitate toward populists
and fascists.
Then self-destruct. It's our fate.
Male chauvinism is the dumbest concept.
For most things,
women do it better than men.
Just think, even if you don't
know your mother's face,
you were given birth by a woman.
Women should handle politics
all together.
Things would be better
than now for sure.
Women on the top. I like it that way.
Even when I fuck. That's right.
I'm not an enemy of women.
Forgive me. Justice is obsolete.
"PAY"
I love you.
Me too.
Never let me go.
I can't take it anymore.
I need my victim now.
"VACANT"
"WAITING" "RESERVED" "HIRED"
If you kill a person or two,
you'd be charged with murder
and put away for about 20 years.
If you kill five or more,
you'll be executed.
But in a war, if you kill one
or two, you'll get a bonus.
Kill 10 or so, you're given a medal.
Reaction to murder is subjective.
"VACANT"
The corner of 7th please.
Oh, yes.
Spitting image,
mirror image,
carbon copy,
doppelganger,
dead ringer...
-It's 1220 Yen.
-Yes.
I have exact change.
Here.
Yes. Thanks.
Thank you very much.
Please take all your belongings.
Oh. I'll open the trunk.
Yes.
Thank you.
Your loved one will be taken
with no reason.
Sadness, anger,
despair...
How will you handle them?
Where to?
Didn't I ride in your cab yesterday?
Huh? That's not possible.
I was off yesterday.
Where to?
I'll get off at Show a Street.
"PAY"
Finally, I found a perfect offering.
She even looks like my wife.
I will take her life, then mine.
Die with her.
Finally end my existence.
I've made my wife wait too long.
Are you talking to me?
You talking to me?
Well, I'm the only one here.
For three nights and days,
I will have her.
Then I will kill her and kill myself.
Kill myself.
What are you wearing?
No! Stop! Let me go!
See? Your leg. It's cursed.
You have not paid proper
respect to your ancestors.
Your agent not renewing
the contract was a curse too.
From your ancestors.
But how come I need to have sex
with this man? It's absurd!
How many times do I have to say this?
Sensei's penis has the
spiritual power to lift the curse!
It's not sex, it's a sexual exorcism!
I had it many times with Sensei
and my stocks are doing tremendously!
Unreal.
Go. Both of you.
Never come back!
The demon is strong with this one.
You, hold her down.
Yes sir!
Stop! Let me go! No!
The exorcism will start
with her vagina,
then her anus,
and ends in her mouth.
Yes Sensei! Please!
No! Let me go!
Help Ma yumi.
Stop! No!
Sensei!
Go to hell! Under the bed fucker!
Who are you?
Ma yumi! Take the gun!
Shoot!
Who are you?
Don't die...
Mr. Fujinaga?
Are you there?
He went back to work
the day before yesterday.
Really?
His doctor told me he should still
be recovering at home.
He had to start driving again...
said he can't be still any longer.
He's very strange.
I see...
Mr. Fujinaga saved my life.
Oh! You were in the paper!
Do you want to know something weird?
I went out with him once.
He told me
that he joined the French Foreign Legion
when he was 18.
Do you know why?
Because he wanted to kill people.
Fucking weird, right?
France! Unbelievable!
He wanted to kill people...
Fucking manga shit right?
He must be lying.
Oh, do you happen to know
where his wife's cemetery is?
His wife?
Yes. She was a murder victim.
Do you really think someone
would marry that dude?
He's been alone forever!
No one would marry such a creep.
I don't think you should go in.
What? I shot this 2 years ago...
"HIRED"
Thank you for choosing to ride with us.
"If the world considers hatred
and lies are virtues,
then the villains
will go on unpunished."
C.A. Torrance