Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
✨ The Marvellous ✨ Team @ Viki.com
What scholarship percentage can you get this semester?
Just seeing her eat like that will give me indigestion.
Gosh, is she determined or foolish?
Doing as much as others
won't let me live like others.
I knew that early on, but...
Let's start the operation.
Scalpel.
- What's this?
- Why did she faint?
Are you okay?
Hyo Ri!
Ms. Lee Hyo Ri.
Are you here alone?
Yes.
The CT and MRI scans detected a brain tumor.
"Tumor"?
It's not metastatic. It appears localized.
We'll know the details after a biopsy.
So, you need surgery first.
But as much as I tried,
exactly as much,
I thought I'd get a chance, too.
It's Patient Kim Min Ji, 27 years old.
She was hospitalized due to sudden quadriplegia.
The test revealed a tumor in her brainstem.
Gosh! Hello, Doctor.
How are you feeling?
She doesn't eat because she's worried.
She's such a troublemaker, Doctor.
Mom.
Don't say stuff like that to the doctor.
While caring for her,
we're telling her to be strong.
I said she can count on you.
Yes.
Don't worry, and relax your mind, as your father said.
Eat the food your mother gives you
and care for yourself.
- Yes, thank you.
- Thank you.
With this misfortune that's on another level,
I hopelessly...
became afraid.
I became sad.
I'm home!
Have you eaten?
How old are you?
You should feed yourself if I'm home late.
It'd be nice if you made some for me, too.
Let's see what we have.
There it is.
I...
- need to tell you—
- You know I live for you, right?
Become a great doctor soon,
so I can retire before 50 and enjoy life while shopping.
Hey!
You can't break the door like that.
Guilt mixed with sadness
became a childish tantrum,
anger, and tears.
And it hurt us more.
Ms. Lee Hyo Ri's guardian, please come in.
Okay.
Awake surgery is appropriate
when you cut out a tumor
that's melded into the brain.
Her tumor is small,
but it's located near a highly functional part of the brain.
So, through the awake surgery,
we'll safeguard important parts of the brain
and remove the tumor.
Yes. She'll receive all necessary treatments.
We trust you and will get all the treatments you mentioned.
Please schedule her surgery sooner.
Well,
I will schedule it as soon as possible,
and move it earlier if I can.
Thank you.
Doctor,
as for the treatment cost...
How much will it be?
Don't you want to visit Hyo Ri?
I'm going to HQ now.
You can't even work because of the audit. Why go?
You heard the doctor, right?
I must pay for her treatment. I can't get fired.
Will you beg the owner or something?
That piece of work?
No matter what it takes, I'll survive at work
and give her all the good treatments she can get.
I'll go now.
Hey, please call Hyo Ri. Okay?
Sir.
My sister-in-law is a nurse at Mungyeong Hospital.
- Should I ask her?
- Yes, if I need help later.
How are things with the Audit Team?
They seem to think it was Manager Jang based on the circumstances.
But the owner is so unpredictable.
- Let's try talking to him.
- Yes.
Here he comes.
I see you often lately, Manager Lee.
Are you feeling anxious?
I get to see you often because of it. It's so nice.
Hey,
try harder when you lie.
You can't be successful because you can't do that.
Come on. Fill it up with Spam.
You can't even tell Spam and sausage apart.
Just give it to me. Give it to me.
Give it to me.
Sir, regarding Manager Lee's audit—
Yes, the audit.
I spoke with the Audit Team.
You must take some responsibility.
Pardon?
Sir, you're joking. Right?
It's your fault for not catching it.
Just accept it and be done with it.
You went through a lot. Go on and eat.
Sir, it's so unfair for her—
Why are you butting in again?
You don't know when to butt in or not, do you?
It's not that, Sir.
Based on her circumstances, if she can't work—
"Circumstances"? What circumstances?
Who in this country doesn't have circumstances?
Manager Lee is still young. She can quickly find another job.
Right.
You said your daughter goes to a top medical school.
You seem to have no luck with a husband.
Let your daughter pamper you and play rich.
Gosh, I'm jealous.
- Gosh, Sir.
- Did I just get fired?
- I'll give you severance pay—
- Whatever.
- Did you just fire me?
- What did you say?
How can you come into work at 11:00 a.m. every day? Do you know the work hours?
Even kindergarteners need to arrive by 9:00 a.m.
You show up late, and you bully the employees
who left home while it was still dark out.
You call whomever's below you "this bastard" and "that bastard."
You'll pay me severance pay?
Wake up.
That's my right, not your charity.
You...
You're crazy, right? Oh, right.
It's because you got fired, right?
Listen carefully. Okay?
Do you know why people tolerate your overbearing behavior?
It's to protect something.
It's because they have something to protect.
But I'll quit with no regrets.
I can't afford to waste my time on people like you anymore.
If the severance process doesn't go smoothly,
you'll see me in court with shackles.
Sit.
Come here.
Hey!
I'll no longer tolerate it.
You know how difficult a life Hyo Ri had, right?
Why should she be sick?
This is too unfair.
Thinking about it now,
I worked desperately to protect her.
But I couldn't be...
by her side when she needed me.
So, I'll stop living like that.
I won't be a pushover.
I'll fight all the injustices
and protect Hyo Ri right by her side.
Good job, Lee Ji An.
You know I'm a blue collar diner conglomerat, right?
I have no parents, siblings, or a husband.
I saved up a lot since I had nothing to spend on.
If we combine our savings,
we can easily pay for Hyo Ri's treatment.
Don't worry. You did a good thing.
Did you think I'd be moved by this?
Whatever.
I couldn't call Hyo Ri.
I just couldn't for some reason.
Bring her back quickly because I miss her.
Okay. Hang up, Bitch.
Dad, hand me the wrench.
Okay.
- Here.
- Thank you.
You make me uncomfortable by being here.
Why don't you check out the neighborhood?
Okay.
Dad,
go downtown. I bought the wrong wire.
It's the wrong size.
Why tell me that so secretly?
Because I would've looked lame.
Right. Men can't look lame.
I'll go without anyone noticing.
What's the deal?
It only took 30 minutes to circle around.
It's so hot.
The empty fields get filled with stray dogs at night.
Sometimes, they get into fights with boars.
Boar. Boar.
Hey.
She looks very skillful.
These are basic skills you learn in school.
Are you okay?
Why am I here?
You overdressed to work in the field in this heat.
Of course, you have heat exhaustion.
To tan the right amount for my physique,
I can't expose my skin to the sun.
But I can't give up on our garlic, either.
So, I had no choice...
but to work overdressed like this.
Gosh, my image was ruined.
You have no image to protect around here.
Don't try to save face and
try not to inconvenience others. Okay?
If it weren't for her,
you would've been eaten by stray dogs.
Do you feel dizzy or nauseous?
Drink water often, little by little,
and rest a while before moving.
Okay.
But you know...
are you a doctor or a nurse?
I was in medical school, but I quit.
I'm nothing anymore.
Go to the hospital if you feel sick after 30 minutes.
Okay.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Good work.
Is she pretty and smart, too?
Your eyesight is good at times like this.
It's no good.
Hello. How much are the apples?
They're 10,000 won for four.
- I see.
- Help yourself. They're tasty.
Hello, Sir.
I'm looking for electrical wiring.
Will the 5-meter one work?
Goodness...
Oh, it hurts!
Gosh, you're so out of touch.
Look. Anchorwoman Baek Ji Yeon was on the news with this hair.
Gosh, when? When?
Your faces are different.
You'll look pathetic if you try to copy her.
What are you saying?
Hey, look.
"As the recession continues,
the market prices have been going up."
Hey, that's your problem.
You don't understand the basics.
A newscaster needs a mic.
You must do it properly.
Fine. If I held this...
"As the recession continues..."
Are you okay?
He doesn't have an accent.
He said, "Are you okay?"
Go in there!
Jeong Seok!
Jeong Seok! Jeong Seok!
Hey!
I thought the transfer student was a bookworm.
When did you steal a girl's heart?
Wow!
Look.
- Hey, hold on—
- Hey!
Jeong Seok's girlfriend is here! Oh my gosh!
What's she doing there?
Geez, stop.
♫  The sky is open toward us  ♫
♫  And you're by my side  ♫
♫  You're standing smiling brightly  ♫
♫  Yes, you're the blue ocean  ♫
♫  You're the blue ocean  ♫
♫  I love you  ♫
Ryu Jeong Seok?
Lee Ji An?
What a small world.
We ended up meeting again like this.
I know.
You haven't...
changed much, Ms. Lee.
"Ms. Lee"?
Talk to me casually, Oppa.
I don't talk casually to random people.
"Random people"?
Anyway, you became a lot more handsome.
Well, I aged a lot—
You used to wear huge glasses
and those drab clothes. What was that?
You wore only depressing colors.
Your nickname was Pity Party, you know.
I was going for minimalism.
- Minimal—
- But I still liked you.
My friends said I had poor taste, but I didn't care.
Hey, Lee Ji An!
You're talking casually!
It seems you can do it with any random person.
I'm joking because I'm happy to see you.
It's so interesting that we met like this.
By the way, what brings you here?
Are you here to get someone, too?
- What?
- I'm here to get my daughter.
She's pretending to be on a trip, but she ran away.
Does your daughter drive a camper, by chance?
Did you become a psychic?
Let's go.
Isn't it heavy?
Wow, is this your house?
We must have a special connection.
Please don't read too much read into it.
Let's call it a coincidence, not fate.
Lee Hyo Ri!
Hey, Lee Hyo Ri!
Hyo Ri!
Lee Hyo Ri!
Hyo Ri.
Didn't you understand what I said?
I told you to leave me alone, even for just a moment.
I went to the hospital today.
I got a treatment plan. The treatment fee...
Anyway, let's go to Seoul. Let's properly—
Why do you get to decide everything? I asked you...
to wait just a few days.
I'm worried your condition will worsen—
I'm trying to live right now.
Do you know what the diagnosis means?
It means I need to change the way I live.
I don't know how much time I have.
So, what I should live for and how,
I need time to figure that out.
What about me?
Am I not...
one of your reasons to live?
I'm sorry,
but I have no energy to care for you now.
I'm overwhelmed just thinking of myself.
So, you care for yourself.
Why weren't you there...
when I needed you?
Why me?
What did I do wrong?
Why just me?
What did I do wrong, exactly?
Hey!
It stopped raining.
Thank you so much.
I'll leave with my daughter tomorrow.
You know the rule of brattiness, right?
There are kids who behave until high school,
but then go through puberty late in their 20s.
I'm a known brat myself, too.
Menopause beats puberty.
Fighting.
What's wrong?
Don't fuss. I fell into the ocean.
What? H-How did that happen?
It's okay. I'll do it.
Why did you do that?
It was an accident, right? A mistake, right?
I was standing on the beach,
and the waves suddenly became intense.
Why would you go to the beach?
The waves were too strong,
and I had no energy to withstand them.
It's okay. Let's go to Seoul tomorrow.
The waves were much stronger than I was.
Of course, they were. The ocean is dangerous.
Should I no longer go to the beach because I might drown?
Is that what I'm supposed to do?
No.
I won't do that.
I'm not going to Seoul.
Not seeing the ocean, even though I want to,
because of the fear of drowning,
and waiting until things get safe,
I won't do that anymore.
Hey.
Come to our house.
She must be in shock.
Let's feed her a warm meal.
Okay!
I haven't eaten, either, Hyung.
Hyung, I was so shocked, too.
Earlier at the beach,
I was so shocked. My heart is still racing.
I need a warm meal, too, Hyung.
Hyung, we must have a telepathic connection.
- Come.
- Okay.
Hello.
Hyung, I'll move this and be right there!
Wait, Hyung!
Gosh, let me finish it.
You're so good at cooking meat.
Invite me sometimes, Hyung.
You have a healthy appetite.
I've been told that I was a good eater since I was a kid.
They must've meant it sarcastically.
Pardon?
Never mind.
Thank you for today. I heard you saved her.
Not at all.
By the way,
it's hard to run into a hometown friend like this.
It's meant to be. Right?
Hyung...
was really handsome back in school, right?
Your father...
well...
got very good grades.
He was a good student and...
h-he was a good student.
No.
Not that. Wasn't he totally
handsome and super popular?
Girls lined up in front of his school to see him, right?
Excuse me, I repeatedly said he was a good student.
Don't you think there is a reason
and you should stop?
I fed meat to these people, and hear this?
You got funnier, Ji An.
Yes. I got really funny.
You have a beautiful home.
I've always wanted to live in a house like this.
- "A house like this"?
- Yes.
A house with a picturesque view.
You see the seasons changing.
It has stairs, a high ceiling, and a garden, too.
It's like a house in dramas.
Hey, I said I'd build us a nice house.
When I was little,
I found it ironic that we didn't have a house
when you build houses.
But not anymore.
I just...
want you to not lend money to others, save modestly,
and get a small apartment soon.
Mom is a construction site manager.
A "site manager"?
I know a lot of good lots to build houses.
Discuss it with your husband and let me know if you really want to build.
I'll recommend a few lots I've been keeping secret.
I'm a single mom.
- If I tell you about raising Hyo Ri alone—
- Thank you for the meal.
I'm not feeling well. I should rest.
Let's go, Mom.
Why are you suddenly doing this?
Are you in pain, by chance?
- Is that something to brag about?
- What?
Are you proud that you're a single mom?
Should you get an award or something?
Hey, should I be ashamed then?
I chose to have you and raised you so well.
I should be proud. Is that a shame?
You can be proud since it was your decision.
What about me?
I was born as the daughter of a single mom. I didn't get to choose.
- Hey.
- Do you think you should be proud?
Then, why not say you adopted me?
Wouldn't that make you prouder?
Why bring this up now?
What does it have to do with anything?
When you have meals with people,
they always ask where your dad is and what he does.
I'd rather come right out and tell them—
That's why you blabbered to everyone throughout my school days
when we made introductions.
Did you find that embarrassing?
Why did you pretend you were okay when I told people?
You should've told me not to say anything.
I wasn't okay with it.
I had to pretend that I didn't care
to feel less embarrassed. So, I acted okay.
Because I didn't want other kids talking about us,
I studied desperately.
Because grades equal power,
I studied desperately so they couldn't say a word.
So, don't say that to people in front of me anymore.
If you really want to brag about it,
do it when I'm not around to people who have nothing to do with me.
Is that why you looked down on me,
dropped out without discussing it,
and refused to go to a hospital in Seoul?
- I'll manage myself.
- Manage what? You can't manage this alone.
Will you keep treating me like this?
Fine, I get it.
I-I made no accomplishments,
and I didn't do much for you.
Now, I know I blabber my mouth, not knowing when to shut it.
Fine. We're going to Seoul tomorrow.
Let's stop.
Who's that?
Is she someone's sister?
Don't you know? She's Hyo Ri's mom.
Gosh, did she have her in high school?
She must've been a partyer.
I heard she divorced her husband.
If I stayed with my first love,
my son would've joined the military by now.
Not everyone can do that.
You have to have the knack for it.
She must've lived up to her pretty face.
Hey, if it's about looks,
she can't beat me.
You're so silly.
Seriously. You're pretty.
Hello.
I'm Hyo Ri's mom.
We kind of know.
What is it?
I know that you "kind of know."
I want to provide facts.
It's true that I was a partyer in high school.
But I had her after graduating.
I'm not a divorcee. I never married.
I'm a single mom.
And you...
are nowhere near my competition.
Why is there nothing easy in this world?
I always attacked first because it was tough to hear murmurs.
But that wasn't the solution.
How could I have known that it made things harder for you, Girl?
Excuse me.
I think there was a deal between us.
Just like I'm trying my best to fix the camper,
I want you to do your best to work here, too.
I don't ever do anything half-assed.
Whenever I do something,
I always get the perfect score.
- "Perfect score"?
- Perfect score.
Okay, then.
I'll expect a thorough job.
Give me your hand.
Another fragrant day!
- Nice, nice, nice!
Nice, nice, nice. Okay?
One more time.
Another fragrant day! Nice, nice, nice!
- This is Korea.
- Go.
So, let me repeat myself.
Cut the stem at a 45-degree angle like this.
The cross-section needs to be large so it absorbs water and grows.
- Here?
- No, no. A little lower.
- "Lower"?
- Yeah.
At a 45-degree angle.
You're good.
45-degree angle...
That's right.
You did it right.
Are you tired?
No, not at all.
Really?
Yes, I'm fine.
You must've worked for a long time.
Has it been six years?
I started when I dropped out in 11th grade.
It's been about six years.
I see.
It was nice to see.
Huh?
You seemed happy.
You're right.
I really love this job.
By the way,
why do you act so rude?
Why are you rude to your mom?
I saw you arguing with your mom yesterday.
- You—
- That doesn't make you feel less victimized.
You don't love her less, either.
So, I am curious why you keep behaving rudely to her?
It's not something you should care about.
Don't overstep boundaries, please.
You're right.
I overstepped boundaries.
I'm sorry.
Hyo Ri.
Your mom must've left this yesterday.
It kept ringing.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Don't look at me like that first thing in the morning.
Get ready to go to Seoul.
Hey, it's Chief Hwang's mother's 80th birthday today.
His family lives in Cheonghae.
Go and see him. You need your 30 million won back.
The address is...
Again? Did you lend money again?
Why...
Will you always be a pushover?
- It's not that. It's not that.
- It's not?
Chief Hwang's mother is sick.
I told you,
monetary exchange is for those who can afford it,
or for people who don't mind burning bridges.
I said you aren't qualified!
I'll get it back. He promised to pay it back.
Follow me.
Hey, where are we going? It hurts.
Auntie Seon Yeong sent you the address. You have to go there.
Will you lose 30 million won?
It's okay. I'll go. You stay.
You're not well.
Where is it?
You shouldn't have given a loan if you cared about me so much.
It's not far from here. Take a taxi.
Hey, Lee Hyo Ri, I said I'll take care of it.
And it's hard to get a taxi here.
- Hello.
- Hi.
What?
It takes about 30 minutes. Should I play music?
Okay. Play NEXT, please.
Let's drive quietly.
You're so inconsiderate.
He's suggested playing music because it's awkward.
- Right?
- Pardon?
- Well...
- He wants to drive quietly,
but after seeing your face, he wondered if he should play music,
to be considerate of his elder.
- Right?
- Huh?
- Yes.
- Hey, hey, did you say "elder" just now?
If I get dolled up, people still think I'm a college student.
I haven't heard such a silly joke in a long time.
Wow, seriously.
Bo Hyeon, when you first saw me,
glancing from afar, you thought I was in my 20s. Right?
Why do you keep pressuring him? Don't do that.
It'd be pressure if I were unreasonable.
I'm just doing a fact-check. That's not applying pressure.
I think this is it.
I won't let him get away with it. I'll flip everything upside down.
Do it right. Don't argue pointlessly.
Swear, scream, roll eyes, and fight.
- Otherwise, you can't get the money back.
- You just watch.
I worked at a construction site for years.
We'll take a taxi to go back. You can leave.
Thank you.
Mr. Hwang Yeong Ju!
Don't say "Mister."
Gosh, got it. This girl...
Hwang Yeong Ju!
Chief Hwang!
Are you home alone?
No.
Where's dad? Where's he?
Dad is at Grandma's hospital.
It's a nursing hospital.
Who are you?
Huh? Gosh, thank you.
Thank you.
We don't know...
where Dad went.
Oh, I see.
Where's Mom?
Your siblings are so healthy.
- Don't say stuff like that.
- Ouch!
Gosh, are you okay?
Are you okay?
It hurts.
Sis, I'm hungry.
Okay.
I'll make you food and go to work.
Do you work?
I clean griddles at a barbecue restaurant.
There's nothing more fun than watching fights.
I'm not going anywhere.
They should start screaming soon.
Huh?
One, two, three.
- One, two, three.
Two, three.
There.
- Thank you.
Smile.
Here.
- A heart.
- So pretty.
- Eat.
- Thank you.
Let me help you.
Put ketchup.
Enjoy.
Say "ah."
Eat this.
Do you want to try this?
Gosh, you acted all tough and smart.
Since when did you care about humanity?
Geez.
Excuse me!
Huh?
Well...
It's Grandma's 80th birthday.
He's treating Grandma and her friends to a meal.
Wow, he's having a party instead of paying me?
Can you do it properly?
Stay here. I'll take care of it.
♪  Deep within the waves of the Samakdo  ♪
♪  The young bride standing at the dock  ♪
Mom, happy 80th birthday!
Applause.
Be healthy!
Gosh, so frustrating.
Manager Lee!
Gosh, Mom.
You're 80 but still so pretty.
Mom, I will make a lot of money and
show you around Seoul.
You wanted to see the 63 Building.
It's not so hard to do, but I still haven't taken you there.
Mom, wait just a little. Okay?
Mom, eat well.
I'll visit you soon.
Manager Lee,
I'm a jerk, aren't I?
I know how hard you worked for that money.
But I...
I'm sorry.
When I lent you that money,
do you think I thought that
I might not get it back?
I didn't.
I still don't.
Chief...
you don't know how hard I worked for that money.
How dare you act like this?
Why do my wife and daughter always drag me down?
Why?
Honey, this is Cho Rong's funeral!
Come to your senses!
It's your fault!
What are you doing?
Who said you can demolish and redevelop?
I...
lived a lot more depressingly
and devastatingly than you think.
So, I know.
When a person is struggling too much,
you think, "I want to stop living."
You can barely breathe at some point.
But...
you know what makes you go on?
People.
Cho Rong.
My mom...
My mom left me.
What kind of mom abandons her daughter?
Don't cry.
You have me by your side.
Stop crying.
Ji An.
I learned that people let you breathe.
Your kids are sweet.
You're enduring your hardships well.
Gosh, my daughter called me a pushover.
I'm not a pushover.
I'm a romantic.
So, I believe in miracles.
A miracle isn't anything special.
People with no connections and nothing, like us,
let each other live briefly,
even though they call us pushovers.
That's a miracle.
I lent you a miracle worth 30 million won.
Make sure to return it.
You must recycle miracles.
Since I need it back, take your time...
surviving until the end, and give it back.
Manager Lee.
Manager Lee, you know...
Here.
What's this?
I got a text from Chef Kim from the diner.
I heard about your daughter.
Even if my life depended on it, I have no money.
This is a small house my mom owned.
Well, no. It's not much of a house.
It's just a shabby farmhouse at the foot of a mountain.
Selling it won't get you much.
But...
I just wanted to do this.
I'll go.
Hey,
young lady.
Well...
Your mom...
isn't a pushover.
She's a good person.
She saves lives.
It might take time,
but I'll make sure to survive and...
Miracle? I'll return it to you.
Okay.
Take care.
- I'll get going.
- Okay.
- Thank you for today.
- Sure.
Excuse me.
I'm over here.
I thought maybe you forgot to care for me.
By the way,
my life is...
so hopelessly dark.
Isn't that a foul?
I'm trying to live right now.
Do you know what the diagnosis means?
It means I need to change the way I live.
You have a beautiful home.
I've always wanted to live in a house like this.
"A house like this?"
Not seeing the ocean even though I want to,
because of the fear of drowning,
and waiting until things get safe,
I won't do that anymore.
Oppa,
I'm so sorry,
but do me a favor.
I can't see anything.
If we fall into a rice field,
no one will save us since we're in the countryside.
We'll freeze to death.
Who freezes to death in the summer?
I'm saying that's how dangerous it is.
You have poor comprehension skills.
Okay, go further. Go further.
Have you always been this supportive?
Huh? Over here.
There's something. Look, look.
It's here.
Stop, stop.
Wow, what's this?
Is it a haunted house?
It's not a haunted house.
It's Hyo Ri's house.
The ceilings are high,
it has stairs,
and it has a garden.
It's Hyo Ri's house.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
✨ The Marvellous ✨ Team @ Viki.com
♫  Somethings are leading now  ♫
♫  We’re looking through the stars  ♫
♫  and the sun
♫  No need to talk or prove  ♫
♫  When you're one that I admire  ♫
♫  Live for rather than me  ♫
♫  Breathe in, let the ocean flow in  ♫
♫  I'll never hear a sound  ♫
♫  For you, it leads to where I’m meant to be  ♫
♫  My lover, lover  ♫
♫  It’s not about the greed nor a bitter mind  ♫
♫  You won't know anything  ♫
♫  'Cause you're my privilege  ♫
♫  Live forever in me  ♫
♫  Honey, and let the ocean flow in  ♫
♫  I’ve never seen it whole  ♫
♫  But it’s all I’m meant to be  ♫
You're afraid of me dying.
You're making me want to right now.
Don't be surprised about how dogged I am.
I'll do something instead of crying.
The belly button is bigger than the belly.
- You'll build it, Oppa.
- I said I can't! I won't!
I looked for you desperately.
It's for my roots, not the wave.
Have I been approved?
Good boy.
Why are you trying to fix that house?