I'll be going on a date with
Dad, so wash up and sleep.
=Episode 13=
Yoon Jeong Eun, 30 years old.
It's Daehan First Party's Chairman Yoon
Seong Woo's one and only daughter.
Dad!
The license plate number Seoul 3
Ga 3126. Type of car Chet TF30.
Color of the car, red. Totaled
soon after the accident.
You there!
Stop there!
Thank you.
Take one. Thank you.
Who are you to be ordering me around?
So arrogant. Why am I not getting
drunk no matter how much I drink?
The CCTV at the hit-and-run
site was broken.
Three witnesses... as if
they promised each other...
they changed their testimonies.
No witnesses. No evidence.
Probability of appeals
request to be made, zero.
What did you do earlier?
A test recording for the movie.
Why, so suddenly?
I've made up my mind.
I heard the new team leader of that
investing company is a beauty.
So... you didn't change your mind because the
investing company's team leader is a beauty?
You're right.
-Please!
-Geez!
I forgot to take my blood
pressure medication today.
Let's try to minimize such upsetting
jokes, alright, Jun Young oppa?
Do I look like a joke to you?
No.
That Team Leader Yoon Jeong Eun... I hear
she'll become KJ Group's daughter-in-law.
She's not the type for you to hit on...
She plans to, but she's not yet.
Man Ok, give me some Chung shim hwan...
Take what's good for you.
There aren't any. No more.
Say it ain't so. Please
tell me you're joking.
No, I don't want to.
You said they started taping Seo Hyeon Woo's
portion. Let's hurry up and go meet them.
Wait. Kim Soo Chan is supposed to play that role.
They already published articles saying that.
I know. According to the coordinator
unni over there, their team...
is going as well.
That case...
call the agency and tell
them to take their pick.
Will they take Kim Soo Chan who barely
starred in one independent movie or
will they take Sin Jun Young, a top notch Hallyu
star and 10 million audience driving actor?
I'll go after meeting with the director.
You're really not doing this movie because of Team
Leader Yoon Jeong Eun, right? You lied, right?
It's true. She's rich from an amazing family.
On top of that, they say she's a beauty.
Since when did you go after women
with money and family background?
For a long time. You just
never caught on, Hyung.
But still...
She has a fiancé and is
about to get married.
Hey! If it's that KJ,
Assemblyman Choi Hyeon Joon...
Team Leader Yoon will become Choi
Hyeon Joon's daughter-in-law!
Stop lying.
It's true. KJ Group only has one son.
You didn't think that far?
What a relief you found out now. You would've
been in big trouble if it wasn't for me!
Well, now that it's come to this,
let's do your best in acting.
In any case, it was a movie you
didn't want to miss out on.
Yoon Jeong Eun. Choi Hyeon Joon and
Lee Eun Soo's daughter-in-law to be.
Choi Ji Tae's fiancée.
I mean... what's wrong with that Oppa?
Didn't Jun Young oppa like PD No Eul?
I don't know. Who'd decipher
that crazy guy's heart?
I'm okay.
Lots of people can see us. This
is one of our company's resort.
There are lots of people from KJ here.
Kim Soo Chan, they'll
start filming tomorrow.
Oh, really? That's good.
Days remaining for statute of
limitation to expire, 46 days.
Days remaining for me, minimum
30 days, maximum 60 days.
There's no one.
Is someone talking bad
about me over there?
What are you doing here?
I came to film the movie. Your
counterpart. The psychopath role.
You dropped it saying you
don't want to do it.
I'm not that irresponsible. I should
wrap things up if I dropped the ball.
See you again, Jeong Eun. I'll call you.
The reporters are all over.
Be careful, Hyung.
Excuse me at our first encounter.
Alright then.
This isn't our first encounter.
I wasn't going to acknowledge that.
I'm Yoon Jeong Eun.
I'm Sin Jun Young, even though
you probably know it already.
-Long time no see.
You haven't changed your phone number?
You're ignoring my texts and
not answering the phone.
I thought you changed your number.
I wanted to change it,
but didn't get to.
Why aren't you picking up?
And ignoring my text?
-Just because.
-Just because?
Sorry, I'm busy. I have nothing to say.
Why don't you have anything to say?
I have a lot to say.
I don't want to listen.
Jun Young...
I'll see you soon.
I'll go back, please rest.
I'm sorry.
-Is that all?
-If you could get married soon,
it would be a bit less confusing.
I'm really sorry.
Ji Tae...
Wanna drink together?
What kind of trouble am I
going to cause while drunk?
CEO! What are you doing?
Would you like to party with me tonight?
Did you come because
you wanted to see Eul?
-I was shooting a movie.
-I thought you refused to do it.
Oh, that. Well, the team leader was
very beautiful so I changed my mind.
I have a bit of a soft
spot for beautiful people.
I'm sorry, it slipped my mind. You shouldn't
be drinking, right? Because you're sick.
I'm not sick.
Brain cell glioma, the tumor has spread
too much to even consider surgery.
Life expectancy is estimated...
at 2 months.
Am I right?
I will take care of Eul, so why don't you
focus on taking care of yourself first?
The way I see it,
you don't have much time left to waste.
You won't even be able to take
responsibility because you'll be gone soon.
Stop shaking her up.
I will take this.
-Let's have one more drink.
-You'd better move!
Hey, are you not even going to say hi?
Go away, please!
Wow, you're so cool!
You won't even look into my eyes.
Long ago, Man Ok used to bother
me so much saying she likes me.
She was all like Oh, oppa,
let's go out just this once...
Stop it! Aren't you going to step aside?
You... your accent...
playing hard to get...
Man Ok, you're the cutest when
you speak with your accent.
Stop talking like you're from Seoul, because
it doesn't suit you. And keep in touch, okay?
Are you really not going to move? If
you keep this up I'll be calling oppa!
What? Ok then! Call him.
Come on, I'm dying to see him.
Call him, come on!
I'm not scared one bit!
Just move already!
She said to let her go! Are your
ears rotted away, jerks!
Yes, Joo-Jun Young.
-Where are you?
-Well...
These jerks!
You brat! Hey!
I'm going crazy...
If you want to drink, drink nicely!
You're dead.
Hey!
What are you doing? Are
you guys gangsters?
It's not like that. They were
being like this to our Man Ok...
Shut up.
Jang Gook Yeong, Jang Man Ok, get out.
Ah, really. Why for me?
-This brat!
-No!
Why are you calling Gook Young by name
when he's 2 years older than you?
You're not even sorry?
Mr. Jang is innocent.
Those punks were the ones
who picked on Man Ok first.
So what?
What do you mean so what? It's that...
It's that what?
I'm hurt.
I was scratched here
and I've had some hairs pulled out.
Those guys also hit me here
and now I have a wound here too.
And I can't show you, but I have
a bruise this big on my butt.
I think I might have broken a rib too...
Or is it this one?
That's why you have no right either.
You have no right to be by Eul's
side and make her happy either!
Just like me, you...
have no choice but be
Choi Hyeon Joon's son.
Excuse me.
Yes? What is it?
Do you know any hospital nearby?
Yes, there's one about 10 minutes away.
This woman seems to be hurt. I'm sorry,
but could you please take her there?
Sure, I will.
Go, then. Take care of yourself.
Let's go. Are you badly hurt?
No, I'm alright. Sorry.
How did you get in here?
You're up. You had a lot to drink
yesterday, didn't you? Want some coffee?
What are you doing in
someone's room uninvited?
Your mother told me to
call her when you get up.
Mother, Ji Tae is up.
Just a second.
Yes.
Good morning! Have you had
a good night's sleep, son?
I eventually assigned the investor's team leader
position I had in mind for you to Jung Eun.
Haven't you heard?
I have.
I was thinking of a position for you, but
it's below Jung Eun's. What do you think?
Yes, I'll be happy to take it.
I'm also thinking of giving Jung Eun the position
you had as department leader. Is that okay?
Please do.
That means you need to vacate
the room you're staying in.
That room is not for
lower-level employees' use.
Sure. I'll clear everything up.
Alright. I heard you had a bit too much
to drink yesterday. Do you want some...
I don't care what you'll be doing
to me, but leave Eul alone.
If you touch as much as a hair of Eul,
of her brother's or of anyone's near her
I will not let it slide.
You know very well which card I'm
holding in my hands, Mother.
Choi Ji Tae!
If you have nothing more
to say, I'll hang up.
Congratulations, Department
Head Yoon Jung Eun.
I will be waiting for you to return.
-If you return, I'll...
-That won't happen any time soon. Not at all.
It will get gradually worse.
Excessive pain and headaches
as well as problems
with your motor nerves.
I look more like a panda after a night's sleep.
Is there a hospital nearby?
This woman seems to be hurt. I'm sorry, but
could you please take her to the hospital?
That cold-hearted jerk...
Hello, I'm the person who
asked for a raw egg earlier.
I'm sorry, but could I
please have another one?
Have you seen the $5 I
dropped around here?
I haven't.
This is the only place
I could've lost it...
Lift your shoes a bit.
Take them off.
Are you sure you haven't
hidden them in your sneakers?
That's weird. Where could it have gone?
This one too.
I don't believe it.
They say you're avoiding
me because you're afraid.
That you're afraid I might
soil your career or something
but I don't buy that.
How could I, when I
know what you're like?
You're not one to run away from me
for such a simple reason. I know it.
What do you know?
How do you know me so well?
I just do.
I know it all.
I even know what you're thinking of now.
I missed you, Eul.
I missed you so much.
It's okay to just say it.
You must live so comfortably.
You could misinterpret
everything and delude yourself.
If it's easier for you to believe that, then
fine, live while thinking you're right.
I missed you too, Sin Jun Young.
A lot. Totally. Extremely.
I missed you like crazy.
That's my answer to your thoughts.
See you later.
Tomorrow, the day after, and every day.
Let's see each other like crazy.
Did you pull out the radishes
and onions from the field?
Why are you here so late?
What? Is anything wrong?
The boss is really strange.
She brought boiled pork instead of yukgaejang
and booze to someone who asked for water.
A customer asked for a
spoon, she gave a ladle...
What's all this?
-What is it?
-You already bought these things.
Should I call Dr. Jo's office?
To make an appointment for two patients?
What is it, Ok?
What?
You never liked coffee with sugar.
No, I do now. My tastes have changed.
Have you been well?
Of course.
Oppa...
I mean, you did well too,
didn't you, Mr. Congressman?
Why were you at Sin Jun Young's house?
Have you gotten married?
Why did you call me? What is it?
Well, I wouldn't want you to sit around all alone
in the parking lot. Have some tea with us.
Have a seat.
This is his father.
Oh, right.
Hello!
Yes, hello.
I had no idea, so I haven't
greeted you properly.
Honey, what would you like to drink?
Water is fine.
Jun Young is my son.
His dad was really against
him becoming a celebrity
so he lived apart from us, but now we should
live together. We're family after all.
Oh, so that was it.
It must be so nice having such
a famous star as your son.
Well, yes...
But... what brought you to our Jun Young's house?
I owe him a lot.
He saved my life.
Wow, the world is so small.
Well, he takes a lot after his dad
because he can be so
nosy and meddlesome.
Honey, do you need some hot water?
-No, I...
-Honey...
And? Anything else you know about Jik?
Family, friends, personality,
hobbies, habits, blood type,
height, weight, clothes and shoes sizes, I even
told you what lotion he uses, but still more?
Doesn't he have a secret
past or something?
Why do you want to know
someone's secret past?
Is finding out about other people's
background your hobby, Noona?
It's not like that.
So your name is No Jik, not Oh Jik.
So that No PD is really...
Is PD No Eul your sister?
From now on, if you say one more thing
about me or my sister, you're dead meat.
How much do their meals cost?
Why are you paying for that? I
treated your friends after all.
That's right, this girl is interested in
you so she bribed us for some information.
-Ma'am, don't they suit each other?
-This Noona apparently has a ton of money!
Date, date, date!
I asked you how much does it cost!
Do you even have the money?
I told you I'm paying.
Let go. Why would you
pay for my friends?
Noona...
-Really?
-Yes!
You're saying she's out of it?
The doctors say she's fine, but
she can't remember anything.
She doesn't remember who she is or where her house
is and she won't come to the police station either.
Her phone?
I think she lost it, I tried to
find it but it wasn't there. What should we do?
Hi. Do you remember me?
What about him?
-No.
-What's your name?
-Elsa.
-Whats our country's capital?
-San Francisco.
-What year is it?
Sometime in the Silla period?
-What is this?
-A cow!
Follow me.
I don't think she has amnesia,
but she's definitely crazy.
-So what should we do?
-She's crazy about you.
She's crazy about you, she wants to spend more time
with you. She's a crazy girl pretending to be nuts.
She must have not studied at all
and read tons of comics instead.
That method comes out in
"Queen of Hitting on Men 13."
What does she take me for...
-What?
-Well,
what does she see in me that she feels
the need to pretend to be crazy?
I think she's so popular among guys.
She's cute.
That's why she's crazy!
Jik! What are you going to do?
"My Jik's favourite
girl group is GFRIEND."
"Favourite movie, A Murderous Memory ."
"Karaoke song: Number 18, Let's Ride a Horse.
Favorite chicken area, chicken breast."
This is all wrong.
Except for family and height, it's all
wrong. My favourite girl group is Fin.K.L.
Movie I like is Memories of Murder,
not A Murderous Memory.
Number 18 at karaoke is What's Wrong With My Age.
And my favourite chicken
area is drumsticks.
Stop asking my friends all this
stuff and just ask me directly.
I'll tell you everything.
Jik...
Hello.
Seo Yoon Woo is on standby already and waiting.
What are you doing, why aren't you coming out yet?
Oh, about that...
What are you trying to do right now?
Broadcasting must be easy?
It's easy making money working
in broadcasting, right?
Have you even got a brain?
Why does the VJ for the
Makings Of look like this?
About that...
I had some personal issues...
Why is a camerawoman
wearing those sunglasses anyway?
Do you think you're some actress?
I'm sorry.
You're such a mess.
Are you kidding? Did you come
here to work or to fight?
You're the one who hit the PD, punk!
Making her eye swell up like that!
Hyung.
I'm very sorry.
We'll make sure this
doesn't happen again.
What are you doing? Beg for forgiveness.
I apologize.
-I will take caution...
-Forget that.
-Go home.
-But sir...
Slippers and what's with your outfit?
When have you washed these clothes?
Geez, so dirty...
It stinks of kimchi all
the way up to here!
-Don't you understand? Go home!
-Mr. Seo...
A camerawoman is just supposed to film. Do
I have to present myself cleanly as well?
It's not like I'm even
going to sleep with you.
-What did you say?
-Hey, No Eul!
-Wow, this woman is crazy...
-I'm totally sane.
This is why everyone
calls you a pervert.
It's okay to not wash up or wear dirty
clothes. It's not like I'm stained with poop.
Hey, piss off. Piss off already!
You don't even know your place and...
Oh, I get it!
This is why Sin Jun Young
fired you, isn't it?
Hey! If you knew she was a hobo,
working as my camerawoman,
you should have let me know
of trash like this beforehand!
I didn't know, that PD No came
to you as your camerawoman.
If I did, I would've
told you, obviously.
No Eul?
Your business here is over. I'll make sure no
one will want to hire you, so be prepared.
-Mister.
-Yes.
You're the same. How dare you stick
me up with this tacky person?
-Do you want your business to go bankrupt?
-No, of course not, sir...
Hey, No Eul!
No Eul! How can you leave like that!
No Eul!
Why are you here? Aren't you
supposed to be filming?
I got fired.
I'm sorry, you tried
hard to get me hired.
Want some tea?
You were fired too, right?
I heard the team leader changed.
To the woman we saw yesterday.
It's the woman I almost got engaged to.
You almost got engaged to her?
On the day of the engagement
ceremony, I didn't go there
but went to see you instead.
Do you like Sin Jun Young that much?
-Please don't meddle in someone else's life.
-Even when you're hurting so much,
you keep wanting him, why is that?
Do you have no pride?
You're like that too.
When you could've gotten engaged
to such a woman, and got hurt,
why do you keep being interested in me?
Do you have no pride?
It's not pride. I'm clever.
If I wait for long enough.
I know that you will
come my way eventually.
That won't happen.
We could never be together.
You know it better than I do.
Nothing's set in stone. You never know.
Should we go to Seoul as a pair of
rejects? We could even have a date.
Where are you going?
I'm not going to be Sin Jun
Young's manager anymore. I'm done!
Are you crazy?
He just watched PD No Eul get unfairly treated and
he knew that she got hurt trying to protect you
but he was all "I didn't know,
if I knew she was going to be your camerawoman I
would have said something..." How can he say that?
Even if I have to clean plates
all my life with my dad
it's better than working under
such a low-life. I quit.
Stop right there. If
you move, I'll shoot.
I don't want to. I'm going to move.
Hey. Hey.
Shoot. Shoot. Hey.
You should get rid of trash
like me quickly. Shoot.
Hurry up and shoot! Hurry and shoot!
Lee Myung Taek! You killed innocent people
like it's a joke. Tell me who you killed!
Hurry up and tell me!
Hey, why are you hitting me?
This isn't the scene where
Jun Young hits him.
Hey! Wait a minute! Stop!
Hey, someone stop Jun Young!
Cut!
Excuse me. Can you give me a few
plastic bags? To put in wet clothes.
Just a moment.
Please give us our keys.
Did you finish filming already?
You said you're taping into the night.
There's been an accident. The
filming has been canceled.
I misunderstood the acting
sequence as me hitting Yoon Woo.
Yoon Woo is throwing a fit saying
he'll sue you, Sin Jun Young.
The director is trying
to talk him out of it.
Tell him to sue me.
I hit someone. I should pay the price.
Mr. Sin Jun Young!
Wait.
Before the reporters find out and things get
bigger, you should apologize, Mr. Sin Jun Young.
Mr. Sin Jun Young.
Yoon Woo hyung made a mistake
like this before with me.
He broke my nose back then.
He didn't apologize to me either.
He said, "While an actor is filming,
things like this happen all the time."
It was so difficult to get this movie
going. Should we cancel this movie then?
Cancel it. I have nothing to lose.
I'm frustrated.
This movie... it's my first
project as a team leader.
Which hospital did you say?
I'm sorry. Forgive me, Hyung.
-I don't want to.
-Yoon Woo.
I'm sorry. I was so out of it that
I misread the acting sequence.
I heard you've made mistakes like this before.
He's apologizing to you. Please accept it.
jerk did it on purpose to screw me over.
No way. Why would I beat you up
on purpose? I like you so much.
-Kneel then.
-Yoon Woo.
I'll forgive you if you
kneel in front of me.
Why? You can't do that?
Seo Yoon Woo. You're so bad.
What's wrong with you?
I'll just kneel.
I can just kneel in his place, right?
Forgive me, Hyung. Forgive me
generously and let's get along...
and let's make this movie.
You did that for me, right?
Seo Yoon Woo. You beat him up
for me, right? To revenge me?
Your Princess Syndrome is
more serious than I thought.
It's true. You did it because of me.
If you care for me so much,
why do you pretend not to?
Why do you continue to be mean to me?
I couldn't sleep since last night.
I'm going to sleep.
Will you leave?
If you're trying to tease me, continue.
No matter how mean you are
to me, I won't get hurt.
I won't be disappointed or misunderstand
you. Continue on all you want.
Do you want to sleep with me?
If you don't want to sleep
with me, tell me now.
I'll open the door for you.
Take this and return my
Ji Tae to his fiancé.
You and Choi Ji Tae both.
Aren't you both crazy?
How could you both fall
for substandard girl...
Are you crazy? Why won't
you go to college?
I'm sorry, but would
you drive me please?
I sold you out at 1
billion won, Ahjussi.
Who says you can sell me?
What is it you want to protect being
destroyed like this, Choi Ji Tae?
I know I'm no match for this fight.
Who cares if I receive some money?
The reason Eul and I can't be together. I can't
remember suddenly. I told you everything, Mom.
Do you know what the world is like?
I feel so sorry for my Jun Young.
What am I going to do, Oppa?
He can't even love someone he loves.
If I become even more cruel,
would you give up then?
Should I just forget about everything and
live the way I want to before I die?
If you're that sorry, just die.
Get out and die!