Duean Yi, please come back home more often so you can help me care for the plants.
Sure! I'll come back home more often.
- Okay! I'll go see Aunty now.
- All right.
Be careful, it's slippery.
You woke up early today.
I wanted to find something to do.
So I came down to help Ma take care of the plants.
And also...
About last night, I'm really sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
It's me who has to apologize to you.
No.
Actually, I think I was too harsh on Pa and Ma.
Do you really want to start a band?
About the band...
I don't think... I'll do it anymore.
Don't be like that.
If you really want to do it, I will help you.
When I had problems, you never left my side.
If you really want to be a singer, I'll be your first fan.
Thank you so much, Yi.
By the way, why did you come home suddenly?
Usually, it's not easy for you to come home.
I had a fight with that person who I told you that I liked.
And are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm trying to be understanding.
- Bro.
- Yes?
Can you promise me
from now on, if something is bothering you, please tell me.
Of course!
If there's anything, you'll be the first to know.
As for Pa and Ma, I think they'll understand you eventually.
Okay.
Don't give up. Let me give you a hug.
You too, Brother.
♫ It's just a love song, that you do not love ♫
♫ But instead I am heartbroken ♫
♫ With a song I heard about love without love ♫
Compared to last time, I think it's good!
- Thank you.
- Sure.
The lyrics you wrote were so deep. Are you in love?
But I think it can be better than this.
During the pre-chorus, I think you can play with words more creatively.
But I think it sounds pretty good.
I still think it can be improved.
You probably still don't understand it deeply enough.
Want to try being heartbroken?
I'm just kidding.
Oh, yeah. Winter is having their pre-debut show soon.
Can you please fix it on time?
Sure.
I'll go back and revise the pre-chorus for you again.
And for the next song, can it please be a sad song?
I can guarantee that the fans will be crying for sure.
I'll contact you again about that.
Got it.
Right, I totally forgot.
If this song is done, you can get ready to write the next song.
- Really?
- Really!
Why would I lie to you?
Jo, can I ask you something?
Sure, what is it?
I heard that you like to sing and you are interested in starting an indie band.
That's right, why?
Well, my brother is starting a band, in case you're interested.
I think someone as talented as you can make the band successful.
I think I better not.
Come on! Why don't you try it out first? Please?
Duean Yi, with the amount of work I do, I don't have enough time as it is.
Okay, that's fine then. I'm leaving now.
You are throwing away your opportunity to be a singer.
I'm leaving.
Fine! I'll give it a try.
- Thank you.
- Yeah…
- I'm going for real this time.
- Yup.
- I'm not going to turn around.
- Yeah…
- Just go!
- Okay.
- Bye now.
- Bye, see you later.
Sure.
Meji, your dad will get here soon.
Okay. I want to color my drawings at home.
Wow, you really like to draw and paint.
Next time I get off work early, I'll buy you coloring books.
Yay! Really? You are the best, Uncle Nawa.
You made a promise, okay?
I promise.
- Do you want some?
- Sure.
You're just saying that.
I'll take one.
Want more? Here.
Nawa, did you call me?
Come in first.
So... where have you been?
I took Duean Yi to see Jo, a moment ago.
I see.
Well, I have something to talk to you about.
Sure.
When you talk to the band members,
I'm afraid it'll look like you're close to them.
It won't look good on you.
But I think I act appropriately with them though.
I just mean that sometimes. You might have put your guard down.
Then... can you tell me what is considered inappropriate?
I just wanted to give you a reminder.
Well...
But it sounds unreasonable.
Janjao, when I'm giving you advice and warnings, I'd like for you to listen.
I didn't say that I won't listen to you.
You're doing it right now.
If this is all you have to say,
please excuse me.
Janjao...
I'm being jealous.
What... do you mean?
I like you.
What?
I think you also have the same feelings for me, right?
Nawa... I...
really respect you as my senior and boss.
But... I don't think this is right.
I think it'll be better to go back to how we were.
But... didn't you have feelings for me when we were in university?
That was then. It's not the same.
Please excuse me. I'm going back to work.
Hey, boy! Is my coffee ready yet?
Shit! Why is it taking so long?
Here it is! Nitro cold brew and sugar-free black coffee. Is that correct?
Oh... I know why it took so long.
I think the waiter was busy tucking.
(T/N: A technique to hide the crotch bulge)
He must have taken so long because he didn't want to shock the customers.
It's because nitro cold brew needs time to drip, but it is delicious for sure.
And if I taste you instead, will I have diarrhea?
If there's nothing else, please excuse me.
You better avoid him carefully before he walks behind you.
Excuse me! If you're so free, you should find something more useful to do.
Such as getting an education. Do you know what that is?
No one is tucking to impress others.
Hey! You're pretty fucking brave!
Don't start with me! I know I'm "pretty!"
Shit!
Bon appetite.
Come on! If you're brave enough!
From the looks of it, you're all talk!
You know what? What you just did was very cool.
Who wants to be cool about that?
Aren't you upset about it?
They were talking shit about you.
I am furious deep down inside.
But I don't see why I have to show it.
It's like I tried to get them to sympathize with me,
but it makes me look even more vulnerable.
Next time, if someone does this again,
just fight them as you did.
I'm already doing the best I can.
Ever since I've become who I am now,
I've been bullied and made fun of constantly.
Then...
If someone makes fun of you again,
you can tell me anytime.
Who will make fun of me except you?
Only I can do that.
Gene, you know what?
What you just did,
makes me feel that...
from now on, if something bad happens to me,
I'll fight back, just like you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Thitnuea.
Sure.
Hey! What are you doing Nuea!?
Oh my…
Let's go.
Seriously?
Hurry up.
Are you coming?
Slow down.
They're here, Plaengrak.
Hey, Gene.
You've got good support.
Are you feeling better now?
With him, I feel worse than before.
We shouldn't stop them, you know.
That's right. They're flirting. We shouldn't stop them.
Enough, both of you. Just stop.
Gene, if something like this happens again,
you can tell me right away.
- You can tell us, too.
- Yes.
Right! If there's anything, just tell us.
Thank you.
We should get back to work, right?
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
Let's go and clear that up over there.
Bring this cup to fill and...
This is the finalized budget
for the pre-debut until the debut day.
From the budget that Mr. Nawa set, there's nothing more to add.
And I think we'll even have a lot of it left.
The promotional art
from the content that Nara came up with is fine.
I've sent everything to Nara and Ms. Mermaid already.
Ms. Mermaid and I are the best at creating media hype.
But mostly, Ms. Mermaid is better.
We've already thought of the contents for promotion according to the plan.
As for the date and time, we'll update in the group chat later.
Next week, we'll have a cute little activity.
We'll let the band give it a try for the first time.
It'll be a pre-debut at the location Janjao selected
that was proposed at...
the Half Moon Café.
Very good.
So, is the song from Duean Yi finished yet?
I already followed up with him.
Duean Yi made an update with Jo the other day.
I'll check on it for you soon.
How can I be sure the band will have enough practice?
Until now, they haven't seen the song.
If we follow the timeline,
it's still within the plans we made.
Okay. That's good, then.
Mr. Nawa, you don't have to worry about it.
I guarantee the song will be done on time.
Please excuse me.
Hey, what are you doing here, Jebi?
I am waiting for Uncle Tanwa.
Where are the two of you going?
We are going to see the trainees practice their dance.
Woah, seems fun.
Is Uncle Tanwa in the practice room?
That's right.
Then, how about this?
You come with us to watch the trainees practice.
- Is that okay?
- Okay.
I will let Uncle Tanwa know, all right?
In case one day, when you get older,
you want to be like that. How's that sound?
Sounds good.
Then, shall we go?
Let's go. Are you happy? Let's go.
Lilly, where does it hurt?
My ankle hurts. It seems like it might be sprained.
Hey! Lilly fell down, we should check up on her.
Wait. Let her get up herself first.
Please help me move Lilly to that side.
I will help you.
If she chooses to walk on this path,
she has to be able to overcome this obstacle.
Oh my! Is this really you?
I never expected you'd have a good mindset.
I actually remembered it from Janjao,
seeing how she sounds so cool saying it.
[Half Moon | Slow Bar Coffee]
What's wrong?
You seemed like you've been in a war.
Please spare me for a day. I can't deal with it.
Fine. I'm yielding because it's you.
What happened to you? How did you end up in this condition?
I think...
I don't want to work there anymore.
Should I quit?
Seriously?
What happened? Tell me.
I think... I'm pretty professional.
But… every time I discuss work,
it's like I'm in a war zone.
Fine. I won't ask any further.
By the way,
Duean Yi doesn't come by much anymore.
Duean Yi?
He might be in a worse situation than me.
What do you think...
about us going to do merits at nine different temples?
(T/N: To dispel bad luck)
Or maybe eighteen temples is better?
In case going to more would help. We'll go immediately!
- That's not too much...
- Really?
I haven't talked to him yet.
Just leave him alone first.
That's good.
As for you, if you are lonely or bored,
you can always come here. Okay?
Aww, Gene! Thank you so much.
At least I know that I have you by my side.
And also order drinks here, too!
Gosh, Gene!
You'll have an iced cappuccino as always?
Yes. And add more sweetness,
because my life is bitter nowadays.
Will do!
Janjao?
Oh, Plaengrak.
Are you leaving already?
Yes, I was on my way out.
Is there something you needed?
No, not that.
I wanted to ask...
if you have talked to Duean Yi.
Oh… well…
I haven't talked with him yet.
By the way, may I ask you something?
What happened?
Why did Duean Yi suddenly act like that?
Well… It's my fault.
I… just feel that I'm not ready for a relationship.
I told him... to keep a distance.
I was afraid he would get hurt even more.
I made dessert for Duean Yi.
Can you give it to him?
Maybe not yet, if you're not ready.
Once you are ready, you can give it to him.
Plaengrak?
Plaengrak!
Oh, okay.
I'll excuse myself then.
- Yes.
- See you later.
Sun, can you listen to this tone?
I think you got the wrong key-chord.
Sun! Come here!
- What the heck is wrong with you?
- What do you mean?
If you didn't want to practice, then why are you here?
Aren't you being too much?
I can do whatever the heck I want.
What about practice?
The other day, you were telling the Winter band members that you idolized them.
But today, this is how you're acting?
Aren't you ashamed?
Our life is really uncertain.
A few days ago, someone was just cooking for you.
Oh, dude...
- What?
- I have something to tell you.
Today, Nawa said he likes me.
Oh! Why did he confess out of the blue?
He told me he didn't like that I was too close to the band members.
And he also told me that he was jealous.
How about you?
I told him that…
I don't want my love life to mix with my work.
We're better the way we are.
That's true.
Think about it…
What if we have a fight in the future?
Wouldn't the company be a mess?
You are so weird.
As soon as the person you've had a crush on for so long confesses,
you rejected him just like that.
Gosh, you...
Like today, we were putting pressure on everyone in the meeting.
Oh, hey...
I met your Plaengrak today.
So… did he say anything about me?
He seems remorseful.
There were a lot of customers today.
But I'd like to thank all of you.
Thank you.
It's because our barista is handsome. Everyone wants to come enjoy.
Do you mean they come for the coffee?
Yes, of course.
Well… I'm heading home now.
- See you tomorrow, Gene.
- Let's go.
- Get home safe.
- Thanks.
Let me help.
How was today? Are you tired?
Why were there so many people today?
Yes, it's true.
Gene.
You did really well today.
They messed with the wrong person.
Lucky for them, I am who I am now. If this was the past,
those two wouldn't have survived.
You're speaking bravely now.
But... you don't have to act so strong all the time.
Next time, if something like this happens,
you can tell me.
And everyone is ready to help you.
Especially, Thitnuea.
Gosh, what are you talking about?
What? What's wrong?
I was just shocked.
Shocked or shy?
Why every time Thitnuea is mentioned, you always act like this?
Plaengrak!
What?
Hey! I'm the owner of the café. You can't just throw stuff at me.
It's almost done, let's hurry so we can go home.
You're... going to see Thitnuea.
Are you rushing to go see him?
Are you going to stop?
Okay, quickly clean it.
Are you going home now?
- What is it?
- Do you want me to take you home?
No need, before Plaengrak sees.
Let's go together, okay?
No!
- Gene is going home with…
- Quite down and come here!
He's going to hear us!
So what?
Oh, hey...
There is one thing I haven't told you.
What is it?
The argument I had with Pleangrak
was really bad.
And so?
The Winter band members were also at the café that day.
Can you tell me in more detail, please?
Tell me exactly what happened.
I walked out crying and Tanwa saw it.
He also came to hug me.
Tanwa? The cute bassist of the band?
Maybe he likes me...
What are you thinking?
Actually, he is pretty cute.
Maybe if my boyfriend is a musician,
he might be understanding to a songwriter like me.
Dude...
Whoever you like or love, I will always support you.
But I don't want you to make decisions
at your happiest or saddest moments.
Because at that time, you won't be reasonable.
It's the moment our heart is the most vulnerable.
Thank you so much.
If I didn't have you, I'd probably be dating ten people.
Gosh, you...
Is this why you decided to speak to Nawa straightforwardly?
You're afraid it would affect your job.
Yes.
But it looks like he doesn't think that way.
Why so?
Because after I rejected him,
he didn't look pleased about it.
He was also nitpicking at me about work.
He would do that?
Yes. Just thinking about facing him,
already stresses me out!
Duean Yi,
is this the first song you're playing on the piano?
Yes. I still remember
I had to lie to Ma that I was sick at that time.
So I could practice this song.
Back then, you were such a nerd.
I never imagined that you'd grow up to be slutty.
(Bitch!)
Duean Yi...
When we were kids...
we were so happy.
That's true.
When you first started working as a secretary,
you came to see me while crying your eyes out every day.
And we ended up crying together in this room.
Do you remember?
When my Pa and Ma forced me to quit doing this job,
there was you,
who told them that you would take care of me.
It's true.
But at that time, I didn't know why I said it.
If I didn't have your help back then,
my first song probably wouldn't have been done by now.
Why are our lives so complicated when we grow up?
♫ Living with the emptiness ♫
♫ Embracing the loneliness ♫
♫ I have no one ♫
♫ Everything has already passed ♫
♫ The dream has ended without you ♫
♫ But love still remains ♫
♫ I still feel it, I still miss you so much ♫
♫ I'm still the same, right here ♫
♫ I want you to know that ♫
♫ My entire life has only you ♫
♫ The love that I gave you with all of my heart  ♫
♫ Will always be like that, I'll never forget ♫
♫ The image when we once had each other ♫
♫ I'll remember, to never change ♫
♫ How much we loved each other ♫
♫ I kept all the good things from the times when I had you ♫
♫ Because love still remains ♫
♫ I still feel it, I still miss you so much ♫
[Half Moon | Slow Bar Coffee]
Namnao, you think you can beat me?
Move ten spots.
Will you fight?
- Come on!
- Come here!
You're changing your opponent?
- Fourteen!
- Hey!
- All right!
- Oh!
- Got hit!
- How's it going, guys?
- Hi, Plaengrak.
- Hello.
You're all here.
Today is our day off, so we decided to take some time off.
Tanwa seemed stressed. We didn't want him to be alone.
Tell me if you need anything.
- Make yourself comfortable.
- Okay.
You guys continue playing. I'll be right back.
- Hurry up.
- Yes!
- Tanwa, hurry up!
- Tanwa!
- Let's continue!
- Yes!
Hurry up!
You and Duean Yi haven't made up yet?
Ever since that day... I still feel bad.
Why do you think he disappeared?
I always saw him try to approach you.
You didn't notice?
I think for someone who tries a lot,
while the other person doesn't see the importance,
it will be meaningless.
No matter how much they try, it's not worth it.
Can I give you some advice?
If you really like Duean Yi,
you have to put in the effort as well.
What if my relationship... turns out like before?
What should I do then?
Not everyone in this world is like your ex.
I understand the scar buried in your heart.
But it doesn't mean it has to keep you wallowing in misery forever.
Oh hey, Tanwa.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to chill with my friends; they are sitting inside.
By the way, what are you doing here?
I came to return some things to Plaengrak.
Since you're personally returning them yourself, it must be important.
It's just an apron.
He let me borrow one when I was learning to make coffee with him.
But now I probably won't be using it anymore.
I know what you're thinking with the matters involving Tanwa.
If you're jealous and protective, you should let Duean Yi know.
Do you think Duean Yi... still likes me?
I'll tell you one thing... The song that he wrote for us
with all the lyrics... I can feel that they're only about you.
I'll be back.
Duean Yi, can I please talk to you? Just a moment, okay?
What?
Come here.
I'd like to talk to you.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I just want to return the apron.
Duean Yi, you cannot return it ever again.
Why?
I just feel that it doesn't belong to me anymore.
And I shouldn't keep it.
Because no matter how hard I try,
I'm not suitable for this apron.
Normally, I don't give someone an apron that easily.
I don't need to be that person anymore.
I think I've had enough.
Since you already pushed me away.
Actually, I shouldn't have come here today.
Duean Yi, please calm down.
About that day... I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I understand everything that you tried doing for me.
But it's me who's so concerned about the past
that it made me neglect the person I'd spend my future with.
I want to ask you for another chance.
Let's start over again, Yi.
I'm not sure that everything will be the same as before.
But...
However, I still like you.
Can you promise me...
that you'll focus on the future from now on?
Even if the person standing here isn't me.
♫ These average words coming from an average person ♫
Don't let your past hurt you again.
Yes.
I promise.
♫ To penetrate your heart  ♫
May I ask you something?
♫ I sing this song from my heart ♫
What's between you and Tanwa?
We're just friends.
There is nothing between us.
♫ I'm singing to you from my heart ♫
♫ I want you to keep it ♫
♫ As our song ♫
♫ This is the first love song, no matter how many
times I sing it for you ♫
♫ I'll only do this for one person ♫
When you cry, you look cuter than usual.
♫ Time led us to meet, talk and, get to know each other ♫
♫ It's not a coincidence, out of thousands of people ♫
♫ But there's only you inside my heart ♫
♫ I sing this song ♫
Such a crybaby...
♫ I sing to express what's inside my heart ♫
Thank you, Duean Yi.
Thank you for giving me a chance.
♫ This is the first love song ♫
And this... is your apron.
Please don't return it, all right?
♫ As our song ♫
♫ This is the first love song, no matter how
many times I sing it for you ♫
♫ I'll only do this for one person, and that person is you ♫