So, what's up? Now that you can't nag me about work, you have nothing to say?
No, it's not that.
Fine, come in first.
You're so grouchy.
All right, so what's wrong?
You wouldn't even say anything in the chat.
Well...
The headquarters of the music company wants you to work with them.
Isn't it good news?
Why are you making a sad face, then?
Aren't you going to congratulate me?
Wait...
Headquarters of the music company...
In Shanghai.
It's dirty now.
- It's going to get my clothes dirty!
- How about again?
- So what?
- Plaengrak will scold me.
Well, that's his problem.
- Oh, no, it's getting messy.
- You think I'm scared of him?
I will definitely tell Plaengrak.
- Saying what, huh?
- It's messed up.
- You're such a snitch.
- You're so focused, I see.
If someone from the band, Winter, sees you,
he would be happy to death.
What are you talking about? I don't really want to do it,
but I did because you ordered me to. Right, Tasmin?
Tasmin!
What got into his eye?
Calm down.
You don't know anything.
Being so stubborn like this.
I'll wait and see if your heart is stubborn, too.
Who's stubborn? Is it you, Tasmin?
- No one.
- Oh, really?
- No one!
- No one?
Fine, if you say so.
Get back to work, Plaengrak.
Okay, Boss. I'll go back to work.
- Very good.
- Yes, sir... Wait.
Okay.
- What the heck, Gene?
- Look, I wrote it wrong now.
Damn it, Plaengrak...
Damn, what?
I didn't quite hear it.
So, what are you going to do next?
You know this is my dream, don't you?
I know, that's why I'm also stressed for you.
If it were you, what would you do?
You are asking the person who is also looking for their passion and is quitting from their old work place?
Come on, I want to know.
If it were me, I'd choose to go for sure.
At the end of the day, I'll still choose to follow my dream.
Dude!
Did you put sleeping pills in your coffee?
You are spacing out.
I can't decide.
But I didn't mean that you have to go.
Let's just say...
If I ask for more time to make a decision.
How many more months do I have?
Three.
Just three months?
Three weeks!
Put everything upstairs.
- Yes, Sir.
- Organize the books properly.
Okay. Where's the picture? Give it here.
[Half Moon | Slow Bar Coffee]
- Can you take this?
- Sure.
How do I prevent it from falling?
You guys seem busy.
Oh, you are here?
It looks like they enjoy doing it.
I think so too, but strangely...
they look more energetic reorganizing the café than making coffee.
No complaints at all.
I heard that.
- Or is it not true?
- It's true, Plaengrak!
- Oh! There is one other thing that Gene is energetic about.
- What is it?
- Fighting with Thitnuea!
- Do you want to fight?
Come on then, or is it not true?
Enough. Enough.
But I think that's true though...
Gosh! I'm not going to talk to you.
I'll just continue to work.
- Keep on working.
- Yes, yes. I'm doing it.
Here you are.
Janjao sent an invitation to the mini-concert.
She has an appointment to watch the band record today.
Okay, thank you so much.
I made you some coffee. I'll go get it for you.
It's okay.
Actually, I have to go now.
I'll see you later.
Okay, sure. Be safe on your way.
- Are you done yet?
- Got it.
That is still not straight. Make it straight.
Janjao.
Yes?
You're all here at once.
Please don't quit.
Please don't leave us.
If there is anything we can help with, you can tell us any time.
Or if I did something bad, please tell me.
I am ready to improve myself.
Relax, guys.
It's not because of you guys.
It's because of me.
Then please don't resign.
The reason we're able to get to where we are,
it's all because of you.
You cared about us when no one did.
We started from zero together.
I want you to be with us all the way.
You lead us further than we dreamed of going.
We've been through good and bad together.
Please stay here with us.
Thank you all so much.
Thank you, everyone, so very much.
But right now, I want you all to focus on your recording.
Do you understand?
Understood?
I'm so damn excited!
Hey! You can do this. Believe me.
Go for it guys.
- You can do this for sure.
- Thank you.
Do you still remember that day?
The day we signed up for a music club, and it turned out to be full.
And then suddenly you decided to open your own club.
I can still remember that feeling.
I know you can remember.
We came all this way... You can do this!
- Can I hug you guys?
- Come on.
Let's send some positive energy to Thitnuea.
Three... two...one... Winter! Winter! Winter!
- Are you ready?
- Lets do it.
Hey! What's wrong?
Well, I'm excited. Aren't you excited?
Of course I am.
♪ Every time I listen to a love song ♪
♪ I always think of you ♪
♪ And dream about you every day ♪
♪ There is someone the love song is written for ♪
♪ It seems their wish came true after listening to it ♪
♪ And hearing the words, "love" in the song ♪
♪ I will send this song to you ♪
♪ And I hope you feel the same way ♪
♪ But it turns out, I'm the one who's delusional ♪
♪ It's just a love song, that you do not love ♪
♪ That you do not accept ♪
♪ You won't feel affected, no matter how much you listen to it ♪
♪ It's just a love song, with sweet lyrics ♪
♪ But instead I am heartbroken ♪
♪ With a song I heard about love without love ♪
♪ What do you do when you listen to love songs,
but it's ineffective, unlike before ♪
♪ The melody that used to be sweet ♪
♪ But today it feels gray ♪
Hey, Duean Yi.
Why are you out here alone?
I see that it's quite busy inside and didn't want to be a bother.
So, what do you think?
Is it as good as you expected?
When I wrote the song, I could only hear myself singing it.
But when listening to you guys,
it's much better than I thought it would be.
Tanwa.
Congratulations to you.
When you become a full-blown artist, don't forget about me.
Come on. How could I ever forget you?
Actually, part of the reason I can come this far is because of you.
Duean Yi.
Well...
- I want to tell you that–
- Oh!
About that night, thank you so much.
If you weren't there at that time, I would have felt much worse.
It's fine.
I am willing to do what I can to help.
Well...
If you need any help, you can tell me.
We are like brothers.
If there's anything I can help with, I want to help you.
Tanwa, it's your turn. Please come in.
Please excuse me.
Go for it. You got this!
Oh my gosh!
What is wrong with you?
I'm happy and so overwhelmed!
All of a sudden,
my boys are already debuting!
Gosh! You shocked me. Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine. Go on.
Okay, then I'll send the plan to our chat group.
So everyone can check it once again.
You're the best, Janjao!
I'm so excited!
I can't wait to see the real event.
Aren't you exaggerating?
Well, it's the first project I got to work on.
Besides, you're more exaggerating than I am.
I am not exaggerating.
I must thank Janjao,
who saw the potential in the boys from the beginning.
And you tried so hard to push this project through until it passed.
That's right, Janjao.
We were able to get through everything because of your preparations
and the very well-planned organization.
Otherwise, we would be in a mess.
I would also like to thank you, Nawa.
You believed in me and trusted this project to me.
And thanks to everyone, too.
If it wasn't for you all, this project wouldn't have succeeded this much.
Enough, let's not be too dramatic.
Nara, I'm just speaking the truth.
I'm not being dramatic.
Then let's call it a day.
Let's update the rest later.
Okay.
All right, let's gather our things.
Well, well.
It's pretty late, why aren't you going home?
You're still making dessert. Who are you making them for?
Gene, you're really something. Aren't you getting tired?
Oh, come on, Plaengrak.
Seeing you happy makes me happy, too.
Did you know ever since you and Duean Yi got back together,
our café turned pink all of sudden.
Go home now!
Otherwise, I'll make you help me with the dessert.
- Oh, no!
- What's wrong?
My arm hurts all of a sudden.
- Oh, really? Your arm hurts so suddenly?
- I don't know what's wrong.
I think I should go home and rest.
- See you.
- Go on.
Gene! I see you're walking fine now!
Come back and help me first!
Bye.
These employees are something else.
Bro, did you wait long?
I've been here a while. How's it going?
It's good.
I've been thinking about going to Shanghai.
What about you? How was the recording?
It was good, actually better than I thought.
That's good news. I can't wait to hear it!
Sure.
So I heard from Jo that you're going to Shanghai soon,
and you have to give them an answer. Right?
Well... I'm still deciding.
Don't worry about matters at home.
I will take care of Pa and Ma.
Thank you, Brother.
Just focus on your job.
Do you realize that you're super capable?
You can really help me with everything.
I know that just a little bit.
Oh, right! Does Plaengrak know about it yet?
You're making this face, that means…
You haven't told him yet?
Brother...
can I ask you something?
I feel like everything is going so well between me and Plaeng.
But if there's this situation where I have to go abroad...
I think love is between two people.
The fact that you're going abroad,
doesn't mean you have to end your relationship.
It won't be ruined, will it?
I think love is about two people.
Especially when you're following your dreams.
The opportunity has come.
If he really loves you,
he should be the first person to understand you.
Don't overthink it.
By the way, how's the band going?
It's all right. There's nothing I can't handle.
Gene and the others are not here yet?
Oh, Duean Yi, you're here very early.
Well, last night they had some preparations to do till late,
so I let them come to work late.
By the way, is there anything, since you came so early?
I have to go abroad, so I came to tell you.
Oh, really?
How many days are you going? Is Janjao going with you?
Well, the music company wants me to go.
What did you say again?
I said Janjao is not going with me.
- Oh.
- Well...
The headquarters of the music company wants me to go.
That's good news, then.
Yes, but...
What country are you going to?
I'm going to Shanghai.
That's great!
But... Plaengrak...
Duean Yi, I'm really sorry,
but let me finish organizing and then we can talk. How's that sound?
I have to get this done soon.
Okay?
Hello.
Yes, hi.
All right, you can come in.
Yes, of course.
Please park out front, and I'll be there to greet you.
Yes, goodbye.
Duean Yi, I'm in a hurry to go.
Let's talk later.
Is everything prepared, Janjao?
Everything is good.
The band members have arrived and should be able to do a sound check soon.
Uncle Nawa.
The past few days that I've been with you at the music company,
I feel like I have more interest in music now.
Really Meji? I'm glad to hear that you know what you like or dislike.
No matter what, your parents and I will always support you with whatever you want to do.
I will work hard for the things that I like.
And I'll try my best to achieve it.
Very good!
Me too. If you like something, try your best to achieve it.
You don't have to worry,
you just have to focus on what you like to do.
Okay.
Why don't we head over there and check it out?
- Sure.
- Let's go.
Tanwa.
Did you come to watch as well?
Of course. Congratulations to you.
You are so cool!
And thank you so much.
Thank me for what?
Well, it's because of you that made me understand. That's why I focused on practicing again.
One day we will be like you guys for sure!
- I will wait for that day.
- Thank you!
Please do your best today!
- You got this!
- Of course.
Are you excited?
Very much! We haven't slept at all.
Yes, me too. I'm so damn excited.
Thank you so much.
For always being here for us.
Even though no one ever gave us a chance.
And you came along and became the perfect addition to our band, Winter.
Not only Sekram but also Janjao.
If you didn't give us the chance that day,
we wouldn't be able to debut.
There are so many people who are better than we are.
And there are plenty of people who make better music.
But they see our potential.
Thank you so much.
Thank you to everyone.
Thank you for fighting together all this time.
Thank you for not scolding me or getting angry with me.
Me too.
Thank you, everyone,
for giving me the opportunity to take care of you guys.
I never thought that we would come this far.
Do you guys remember when you guys had a fight?
I always thought to myself,
maybe it's because I didn't take care of you guys well enough.
Thank you, everyone, for working hard.
Hey, don't cry.
Please take care of us, bad youngsters, for a long time.
Let's cheer ourselves up. Let's go. One last time.
Let's go, three... two... one...
Winter! Winter! Winter!
We got this!
Here we go!
- Thitnuea!
- Hey!
- You guys came, too?
- We won't miss it for anything.
We'd like to congratulate you.
We've followed you since we saw your clip on the internet.
Now that you have come so far, we're so proud of you.
Whenever you're tired or feeling discouraged, we'll be by your side.
I have to thank you guys, too.
You all are the encouragement and support for me.
Which made me able to have this day.
Please do your best today.
We will be cheering for you at the front of the stage.
I guarantee you won't be disappointed.
Keep fighting! Keep fighting!
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thanks.
Keep fighting! Keep fighting!
Hey!
Aren't you performing soon?
Are you prepared yet?
Give me some…
What? Give you what?
What are you talking about?
Give me some encouragement.
Go on and prepare for the show.
Can't I ask for some encouragement?
Let me think…
Nope.
This is an important day for me.
Please just one time.
I'm nervous.
If you don't believe me, you can touch here.
All right, okay... Do your best!
I'll be cheering you.
Thank you.
Thitnuea!
Why not?
You can do it!
Do your best, okay?
Hello, everyone.
We are the band Winter.
Our band started when no one gave us any interest.
But we never gave up.
I believe that, if we try our best to do something,
if not done today then tomorrow will be successful.
Thank you, Duean Yi,
for writing this beautiful song for us.
Thank you to the music company for believing in us.
Thank you, Janjao,
for having faith in us
and making our dream come true.
And lastly,
thank you all of my friends...
for trusting in us.
♪ Every time I listen to a love song ♪
♪ I always think of you ♪
♪ And dream about you every day ♪
♪ There is someone the love song is written for ♪
♪ It seems their wish came true after listening to it ♪
♪ And hearing the words, "love" in the song ♪
♫ I will send this song to you ♫
♫ And I hope you feel the same way ♫
♫ But it turns out, I'm the one who's delusional ♫
♪ It's just a love song, that you do not love ♪
♪ That you do not accept ♪
♪ You won't feel affected, no matter how much you listen to it ♪
♪ It's just a love song, with sweet lyrics ♪
♪ But instead I am heartbroken ♪
♪ With a song I heard about love without love ♪
If one day... our band has our own concert,
you have to go watch us.
[I came to see you now.]
♪ What do you do ♪
♪ When you listen to love songs, but it's ineffective,
unlike before ♪
♪ The melody that used to be sweet ♪
♪ But today it feels gray ♪
♪ My heart used to be hopeful, but now it's broken ♪
♪ A love song with someone who doesn't love
me is different today ♪
♪ Because you don't want me ♪
♫ I will send this song to you ♫
♫ And I hope you feel the same way ♫
♫ But it turns out, I'm the one who's delusional ♫
♪ It's just a love song, that you do not love ♪
♪ That you do not accept ♪
♪ You won't feel affected, no matter how much you listen to it ♪
♪ It's just a love song, with sweet lyrics ♪
♪ But instead I am heartbroken, with a song I heard ♪
♪ It's just a love song, that you do not love ♪
♪ That you do not accept ♪
♪ You won't feel affected, no matter how much you listen to it ♪
♪ It's just a love song, with sweet lyrics ♪
♪ But instead I am heartbroken ♪
♪ With a song I heard about love without love ♪
♪ What do you do ♪
♪ when you listen to love songs, but it's ineffective,
unlike before ♪
♪ The melody that used to be sweet ♪
♪ But today it feels gray ♪
Congratulations!
You finally succeeded.
Thank you.
By the way, now that you finished writing your song,
you won't disappear from my café, will you?
I told you that I am not a person who changes my mind easily.
Are you sure?
Duean Yi.
Yes?
Are you ready?
What do you mean?
Will you be my boyfriend?
Did I say something wrong?
Do you remember what I've been trying to tell you?
About how I have to go abroad.
What I meant was...
Well...
I'm going to go and stay for work.
♪ Living with the emptiness ♪
♪ Embracing the loneliness ♪
♪ I have no one ♪
♪ Everything has already passed ♪
♪ The dream has ended without you ♪
♪ But love still remains ♪
Can you take this back to the café?
Hello.
Yes, what's up Janjao?
Janjao.
When I'm not here, you will be lonely for sure.
I know, just stay still.
Why did you raise your feet at me?
- Yi.
- Wash your feet now!
Hold on... Duean Yi.
Yi, I'm here now.
Why are you so drunk?
He was upset about you, so he kept drinking nonstop.
- Plaengrak, where have you been?
- Are you...
Are you okay?
Can I leave him to you to take him home?
I still have to go back to the office.
Okay, I'll take care of him.
Are you okay? Yi.
Are you okay?
Yi, stand up properly.
Okay, let's go. Sit here. We are at the sofa.
Get your legs up first.
Why did you let yourself get this drunk?
Are you all right?
Let me move you. One, two, three.
Are you okay?
Hug me.
All right, hug my hand then.
My Pleangrak is so adorable.
What is it with you?
- What's wrong?
- Pleangrak...
Yes?
I'm sorry, I have to move to Shanghai.
It's okay.
Please don't be mad at me.
You know how much I love you, don't you?
But I still want to write songs.
Yi.
I love you, too.
Now you start to smile.
Are you okay?
- Sure?
- Yes.
You're smiling now.
You are so drunk.