[Fall in You]
[Episode 8]
[Gu Jingyuan's biological father
reported his refusal to provide for him]
My name is He Wei.
I'm the father of Gu Jingyuan,
who's the President of Gu's Group.
Under my real name, I'm reporting that
he favors the rich and disdains the poor,
a-and he's an ungrateful man
as he refuses to provide for his father.
Do you have any evidence?
Yes.
All of this is the evidence.
At that time, Yuan...
Gu Jingyuan was called
He Yuan at that time.
After his mother died,
he thought his family was poor,
so he went to the welfare house himself
and claimed to be an orphan.
When I found him,
he had been adopted by Chairman Gu.
He refused to recognize me as his father.
All these years,
he has never cared about me.
But I never thought that
though he used to steal stuff,
now
for the so-called bidding,
he would even take advantage of the kids.
I... I... I...
I can't let him harm others.
Right?
[Gu Jingyuan's biological father
reported his refusal to provide for him]
After all...
After all, I'm his father.
[Gu Jingyuan]
Sorry.
The subscriber you dialed
is unavailable.
Please redial later.
Mr. Gu!
The kids on the Parent-Child Day...
Mr. Gu, answer my question.
Mr. Gu, please accept our interview.
Say something, Mr. Gu.
Yeah, Mr. Gu.
Mr. Gu, just say something.
Say something.
Mr. Gu, please give us a response.
Regarding this incident,
do you have anything to say to the public?
Please say something about
the incident on the Parent-Child Day.
Mr. Gu!
Did you steal my stuff?
I didn't steal it.
It wasn't me.
You're lying! It was you!
-Yes, it was you.
-It was you.
Take it out now.
Take it out!
Take it out at once!
It wasn't me.
Take it out!
It was you.
I didn't steal it.
Take it out.
Take it out now!
I saw it with my own eyes.
You stole it.
-Yes, it was him!
-It was him!
I didn't steal it.
It wasn't me.
It was you
who stole my mom's wallet!
I didn't steal it.
Because you're a bastard child.
A bastard child would steal wallets.
Little liar,
if you still refuse to give it to me,
I'll ask your dad to beat you up.
I didn't steal it.
You're still denying it?
I really didn't steal it.
Hey, He Wei.
Your bastard son stole something.
Will you discipline him or not?
He... He stole something?
Yes.
Little bastard!
H-How dare you steal stuff?
I didn't steal anything.
You're still lying?
I'll beat you to death!
He deserves to be beaten up.
How dare you steal stuff?
-Beat him up!
-He deserves it!
How dare you steal stuff?
How dare you...
I didn't steal it.
How dare you steal stuff?
Just let him beat you to death,
bastard child!
How dare you steal stuff?
Bastard child!
-He deserves it!
-Beat him to death!
How dare you steal stuff?
You wicked thief!
Bastard child!
Will you steal stuff again?
I didn't steal it!
Oh!
Isn't this my son, who's a president?
What's wrong?
You finally found your way home?
Huh?
Isn't this very familiar to you?
Are you quite touched?
Call me Dad.
Let me hear it.
You've never looked for me.
Why did you lie?
I want money.
I've raised you for so many years.
Isn't it quite normal
to ask for compensation?
If you had just wanted money,
you wouldn't have needed to
slander me from the start.
What on earth is your purpose?
Because I want to destroy you.
Because you didn't make me happy.
That annoying woman
gave birth to a bastard child like you.
I shouldn't have let you be born!
He Wei, you're such a villain!
What?
As the President of Gu's Group, you think
you're a member
of the upper class?
Huh?
You are just a bastard child.
A bastard child that no one wants!
You want me to keep living
in my childhood nightmare.
He Wei, let me tell you. Dream on!
I know
you have many ways to deal with me.
However,
don't you want to know
where your mom, Luo Qian, is?
Your mom is not dead.
I lied to you.
If you piss me off,
I can do anything.
Do you dare to risk
your mom's life?
Why should I trust you?
Lin Ze, have you got in touch with him?
I got it.
Qiao Yan!
Are you going to look for Yuan?
Wanqing.
Do you know about He Wei?
This is
what he hates to talk about the most.
He Wei
is not his biological father.
What?
He merely married his mother.
He Wei
is a scoundrel.
Every time he got drunk,
he liked to hit others.
What's more,
he was a habitual thief.
When people found out about it,
he would let Yuan be the scapegoat.
Because of that,
Yuan was beaten up many times.
No matter how hard he tried to refute it,
no one believed him.
So later,
whenever he's criticized,
he won't defend himself anymore.
I’ll go find him.
Qiao Yan.
Leave him alone.
When he's in a bad mood,
he doesn't want others to disturb him.
But I think
he probably hopes
that others can find him.
Then someone can listen to him
talk about his sadness
and grievances.
Uncle!
Uncle, are you there?
Are you here?
Uncle.
It's so dark here.
I'm so scared to be alone here.
Are you here or not?
If you still don't show up,
I will...
keep waiting for you here.
♪ I reach out to touch you ♪
♪ One inch away ♪
♪ Powerless, it slips from my fingertips ♪
I found you!
Don't worry about me.
♪ The secret I've been hiding ♪
I'm fine.
♪ Gathering in the depths of my eyes ♪
You're not fine.
♪ Reflecting you and me ♪
Come on.
I'll lend my shoulder to you today.
Cry as long as you want.
♪ Your arrival was like the night sky ♪
Who said I would cry?
♪ Lit by a passing shooting star ♪
You don't want to cry?
Then...
♪ All I want is to stay in this moment ♪
I'll work with you
to fight against He Wei.
This is none of your business.
You obviously need me very much.
I don't need you.
♪ If there were an 'if'... ♪
♪ I'd become the Milky Way for you ♪
♪ I'll shine with you ♪
♪ Until every wound has healed ♪
♪ Is it better to meet than to miss? ♪
You are
such a man of contradictions.
♪ If only you'd say the same ♪
You clearly wanted me to find you.
♪ Let your hands hold tight ♪
That was why you made a noise.
However,
♪ Replacing words with promises ♪
when I called you just now,
you just didn't respond.
You obviously hoped that
I could stand by your side.
You hoped to grab my hand.
But when I
stretched out my hand,
you pushed me away ruthlessly.
However,
I'm smarter than you think.
You heart is saying...
"Please."
"I beg you."
"Could you please help me?"
"I really need you, Qiao Yan."
Uncle.
I heard everything.
♪ If there were an 'if'... ♪
♪ I'd become the Milky Way for you ♪
♪ I'll shine with you ♪
♪ Until every wound has healed ♪
Thank you.
♪ Is it better to meet than to miss? ♪
Qiao Yan.
♪ Just let your heart choose ♪
What a fool.
♪ Embracing the pulse of this moment ♪
♪ Stronger than promises made with words ♪
He Wei went crazy
because he just wanted money.
We can just ignore him.
But I didn't expect that...
He ruined our event first.
Then he targetted you and slandered you.
Do you think
these two things are related?
It has something to do with the bidding?
Yeah.
I once suspected Qin Mian, too.
There must be traces
of what has been done.
He Wei is a good way
to make a breakthrough.
I know
you don't want to face him anymore.
Don't worry.
In terms of this thing,
you can count on me.
I'm the father of Gu Jingyuan,
[Xiaobai Interview Program]
who's the President of Gu's Group.
Under my real name, I'm reporting that
he favors the rich and disdains the poor,
a-and he's an ungrateful man
as he refuses to provide for his father.
This annoying He Wei...
How dare he do this?
He challenged our Gu family's bottom line
again and again.
How dare he openly say that
Jingyuan should
confront him in the live stream room?
Since he has approached us initiatively,
just let me fight this battle
for Uncle Jingyuan this time.
Okay.
Chairman Gu asked me to find
the solid evidence
to fight back against He Wei.
[Record of Child Growth
of Xijiang No.2 Welfare House]
[Basic Information of the Child]
[Case Reporting Information]
[Case Description]
Grandpa.
You're so amazing.
Yan.
Just do it.
If you can't refute that guy's argument,
I'll block his live stream room.
Yes!
[Case Description]
[Xiaobai Interview Program]
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to today's Xiaobai Interview.
Today,
Mr. Gu Jingyuan
didn't come to our live stream room.
We've been waiting for a very long time.
Mr. He.
Do you think Gu Jingyuan will come today?
I really hope that
Yuan can still have a bit of conscience.
He Wei.
You're the one who has no conscience, huh?
[Xiaobai Interview Program]
Hello, Ma'am.
I'm Qiao Yan.
I'm here
[Gu Jingyuan's biological father
reported his refusal to provide for him]
to tell the truth.
Mr. He
is just my uncle's foster father.
But he has never fulfilled his duty
as a father.
All he did
was abusing my uncle.
Even so,
my uncle
has never refused to provide for you.
You're slandering me!
Do you have any evidence
to prove that I abused Yuan?
I have two sets of evidence.
[Xiaobai Interview Program]
[Case Reporting Information]
This is the evidence
provided by the local police station
from back then.
[Case Reporting Information]
In October 2003,
Due to excessive drinking,
Mr. He Wei beat up his son, He Yuan,
and pushed him to a broken wine bottle.
[Case Reporting Information]
He Yuan was bleeding non-stop.
He had five stitches on his wrist.
[Case Reporting Information]
This is a document
provided by the welfare house.
[Record of Child Growth
of Xijiang No.2 Welfare House]
When He Yuan escaped to the gate
of the welfare house for the first time,
his body was full of wounds.
The wounds were identified
to have been caused by long-term beatings
and abuse.
[Record of Child Growth
of Xijiang No.2 Welfare House]
Later, He Wei went to the welfare house
and threatened them to ask for money.
Knowing that he couldn't get any benefits,
he abandoned He Yuan
in the welfare house.
[Record of Child Growth
of Xijiang No.2 Welfare House]
Since then, he has never cared about him.
I...
I did beat up Yuan.
However,
I just didn't want him
to steal stuff.
I can't make my child become someone
who harms the society.
Huh?
Look at this...
This apology letter.
[Xiaobai Interview Program]
This apology letter
was signed by Yuan back then
after he stole something
in the shopping mall.
You must have forced him
to write this apology letter.
If Yuan really has a clear conscience,
why didn't he come here today?
Let me tell you.
I...
I'm from that hospital.
See?
Those children who had been poisoned
were sent to our hospital.
I personally saw
Yuan negotiating with those kids' parents
on behalf of Gu's Group,
threatening them
and refusing to compensate them.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I'm not talking nonsense.
I'm Yuan's father.
I want him to come out
and apologize to me
and to those victims.
Guys, please calm down.
Just calm down.
Let's sit down and talk.
Alright.
Since the beginning
of the live-stream show,
both of them
have made relevant statements.
[Gu Jingyuan's biological father
reported his refusal to provide for him]
Now let's take a look at
what those highly-upvoted popular comments
[It's wrong to hit kids.
But stealing stuff is even worse.]
are discussing.
[If he had been a good person,
he wouldn't have used kids for marketing.]
[He should be punished by the law.]
Why do these people trust He Wei more?
He doesn't look like a good person.
Humph.
The comments
represent the public's opinion.
The public's opinion is the truth.
Gu Jingyuan
is in great trouble this time.
Humph.
In my opinion,
that's not necessarily the case.
It looks like there's no way
to clarify this incident.
Welcome back.
With the comments we just saw,
[Xiaobai Interview Program]
I believe
everyone has heard the public's opinion.
I wonder if Mr. Gu Jingyuan has heard it.
Gu Jingyuan just has a guilty conscience.
He Wei.
You've never treated Gu Jingyuan
as a child
or even a human.
In your eyes,
he's just a tool to vent your emotions.
To gain benefits,
you can even slander him
and let everyone cyberbully him.
Are you a human or not?
Nonsense!
She's just talking nonsense!
Sir!
Today, I...
Uncle.
Why are you here?
You've done so much for me.
How can I let you face it alone?
Alright.
Now Mr. Gu Jingyuan
has come to our live stream room.
It's okay.
There are more than 100,000 people
in our live stream room now.
It looks like
everyone is quite looking forward
to this historical moment of
Mr. Gu Jingyuan meeting his foster father.
Yuan.
How could you treat the victims like that?
What did I teach you?
H-Have you forgotten it?
Lin Ze.
Do you remember this tape recorder?
When I ran away,
I only took it with me.
When I was eight years old,
I couldn't stand He Wei's long-term abuse,
so I chose to run away when he went out.
I didn't steal anything.
This tape recorder
has recorded the evidence from back then.
Hey.
Bastard child,
why did you keep the door closed?
Huh?
What are you doing?
I picked it up because you didn't want it.
Come on.
Sign it.
[Apology Letter]
I didn't steal anything.
You brought all those things back here.
Hey, you bastard child.
So what if I brought them back here?
Just sign it when I tell you to.
It's not your first time.
Oh.
Can't you bear the responsibility for me?
Huh?
I didn't steal anything.
I won't sign it.
Hey.
How dare you talk back? I...
Where are you going?
Will you sign it or not?
Sign it!
-Will you sign it or not?
-No, I won't!
Come here!
-I won't sign it.
-You little brat.
You bastard child!
Hold the pen!
[Apology Letter]
[Apologizer]
I just won't sign it!
[Xiaobai Interview Program]
Enough!
He Wei.
Do you have anything else to say?
It's fake.
These...
These are all fake recordings
made by you guys!
They're all fake!
Regarding the authenticity
of the recordings,
I'll ask relevant departments
to verify it.
[Gu Jingyuan's biological father
reported his refusal to provide for him]
As for the food poisoning incident
on the Parent-Child Day,
I'll reveal all the investigation results
to the public.
And...
Everyone says
I'm a dog of the Gu family.
So what?
The Gu family gave me a home.
No matter what they think of me,
They'll always be my family
for the rest of my life.
From now on,
if anyone slanders my family
and Gu's Group online,
he'll just wait to
receive a lawyer's letter.
Come on.
Let's go home.
Okay.
Hey, Mr. Gu Jingyuan.
Miss Qiao Yan.
The live stream show is not over yet.
Gu Jingyuan
is indeed quite capable.
Dad.
I've found that you seem to
pay a lot of attention to Gu's Group.
Previously,
we did well
in the electronic technology field.
But we suddenly switched to
the real estate business.
After that,
you've been keeping an eye on Gu's Group.
In terms of doing business,
we should remember the rule,
"Business is business."
Why should we let the Gu family
monopolize the market in Xijiang?
Only by understanding our opponents
and hounding them relentlessly
will we have the chance to win.
But we originally...
Ziyu.
Everything I have now
will all be yours in the future.
Everything I'm doing now
is all for you.
Okay.
I haven't had hot pot for a long time.
Grandpa.
Why did you think of eating it today?
Having hotpot
is just for a lively atmosphere.
Hey, Xu Wen.
I'm here!
Go to the study room
and fetch my two bottles of old wine.
Okay.
Grandpa.
It looks like you're in a good mood today.
But don't forget that
the doctor told you
to avoid drinking if you can.
It's okay to drink occasionally.
Jingyuan.
Hey, Dad.
It's been a long time
since we drank together last time.
Don't you want to drink with me later?
Yes, I do.
Of course I'll drink with you.
But let's make a deal.
Just stop when you should.
Don't drink too much.
Yeah.
That's what my good son should be like.
Here's the wine.
Dad.
This wine is quite old, isn't it?
I remember it has existed
since I came here.
That's right.
I specially bought it and kept it
when you joined the Gu family.
We're drinking your wine today.
Alright.
Now
there are no outsiders here.
As a family,
let's drink a toast first.
Come on.
Dad, I wish you good health.
Grandpa, I wish you happiness every day.
Well,
thanks for my granddaughter's good wishes.
Cheers.
Hey, Dad.
Drink slowly. You're drinking too fast.
Jingyuan.
Yes?
Hai and I were apart,
wasting half of our lifetime.
You grew up with no one to rely on.
Since you joined the Gu family,
I've treated you as my own son.
Remember.
No matter what you do in the future,
the Gu family
will always be your strong backing.
Alright?
Come on.
Thank you, Dad.
Okay.
Hey, Grandpa.
We agreed
you would drink only one glass of it.
Why are you still drinking?
Just let me drink a little.
Let's have some meat.
I'm starving.
Oh. Okay.
Let's eat.
Hmm.
Thank you, Dad.
Hey.
Humph.
I'm not happy.
Grandpa,
all you know is giving meat to Uncle.
You're not even giving meat to me.
You're biased.
Oh, my goddess.
Everyone has it.
Oh, come on.
Here you are.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Hey, Dad.
Eat some, too.
Okay. Let's eat.
Here you are.
Dad.
Yes?
Regarding the Parent-Child Day incident,
don't worry. I'll handle it properly.
As for the land we're bidding for,
we'll certainly get it.
I believe
you will definitely handle it well.
Alright.
Let's not talk about this now.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Be careful.
Thank you, Uncle.
Oh.
This wine is quite strong.
Don't drink too much.
Okay.
Uncle, you're so stingy.
I haven't drunk too much.
I feel nothing at all.
This is strange.
Why is my heart beating so fast?
Am I really drunk?