[Fall in You]
[Episode 15]
Does it still hurt?
No.
I'm sorry.
Why?
Why are you apologizing to me?
I told you,
I would protect you,
never let you get hurt.
That's my promise to you.
And for that promise,
I'd give everything—
even my life.
But what happened today,
it's all because of me...
Are you stupid?
Well,
so I
get to be happy,
while you
take all the pain and blame.
Why?
We're a couple now.
We should
trust and rely
on each other.
Whatever
trouble or danger
comes,
we have to
bear and face it
together.
Yan.
Grandpa.
Dad.
why are you back?
Grandpa,
Mr. Gu
saw the news,
knew you two were in trouble,
and insisted on being discharged.
Yan,
don't be afraid.
Grandpa's here.
Dad,
I'll take care of Yan.
Your health matters more.
Please go back to the hospital.
Hospital? Forget it.
This is how you take care of her?
Grandpa,
you just got discharged.
Did you forget what the doctor said?
Alright.
Hey,
you two, stop standing here.
Figure out a solution soon.
Okay.
Well.
Yan.
Yes?
Now you see
why I opposed
you being with Jingyuan?
Public gossip can drown you.
But Grandpa,
new scandals pop up every day.
Give it time and everyone will forget.
Humph.
That's so optimistic of you.
Yan.
Yes?
Do you really
like Jingyuan that much?
Yes.
At first,
I treated him like family.
I think he's dependable
and reliable.
But gradually,
somehow,
I started having expectations of him
and caring for him.
And later,
I always felt sorry for him.
I'm thinking,
if my parents had stayed in Xijiang,
if I'd met him earlier,
I could've been by his side all along.
Given the current situation,
what are you going to do?
Dad,
I've made up my mind.
I'll hold a press conference
to tell everyone that
I've decided to give up
the Gu's adopted son status.
If my surname is not Gu,
I'm not Yan's uncle,
then our love is acceptable.
And the Gu family's reputation
will not be affected.
Most importantly,
no one can judge Yan anymore.
You've known Yan
only a few months.
How deep can your feelings be?
How far
can you go?
Have you
thought about that?
Yes.
I will marry Yan.
Whether I marry into your family
or keep the marriage secret,
I don't mind.
I won't leave the Gu family.
No matter who I am,
we'll always be the closest family.
And you'll always be my father.
You asked me here
to tell me something important?
No hurry.
I'll tell you slowly.
Have a seat.
Don't you want to know
why He Yue
had that video of you two?
I gave it to her.
I knew she'd
hand it to the reporters.
Why did you do that?
First tell me,
what's
Chairman Gu's attitude?
Grandpa's worried about us.
But no matter what happens,
no matter what others think or say,
Jingyuan and I will be together
and never back down.
Good.
Then
my efforts weren't wasted.
What do you mean?
As long as Yuan is happy,
I'm willing to do anything.
Since he likes you,
I'll make sure
you two stay together.
Yan.
Lu Wanqing, what are you up to?
I've found out
you sent that video to He Yue.
Yes,
I did.
But I did it for you.
Chairman Gu cares about his image,
but he's softhearted.
If you keep hiding it,
he'll never agree.
But if it blows up,
he'll feel for you
and take your side.
Who asked you to do that?
Yuan,
anything you want,
I'll help you get it.
Even if you rejected me,
we've been together since childhood,
and we're the closest to each other.
That
will never change.
Wan,
I don't need you to meddle
with what's between Yan and me.
Why did you bring me here?
This is the most
beautiful place in Xijiang.
Whenever I feel down,
I come here
and it always helps.
Hah.
Mmm.
Jingyuan,
do you have
something to say to me?
I'm sorry.
I apologize to you
for what Lu Wanqing did.
Actually, she's not a bad person.
She's relied on me
too much since we were kids,
so she's a bit extreme.
But don't worry,
I will handle it.
It's okay.
Actually,
I can understand Wanqing.
And
who knows—
this might work on Grandpa.
Also,
I'm warning you.
Stop saying "sorry" to me all the time.
Because in my heart,
our Mr. Gu shoud be proud.
I don't like seeing you bow your head.
You don't have to always worry about me.
Smile.
Qiao Yan,
marry me.
At first,
I cared about you like family—
thought you were lively
and adorable.
But after everything we've been through,
I cared for you a lot.
And then,
you could always stir my heart.
I want to protect you,
never let you get hurt again.
I'm thinking,
if I could spend every second
by your side in the future,
seeing you,
guarding you—
how wonderful that'd be.
Yan,
I know this isn't a perfect proposal.
No flowers,
no ceremony,
and no blessings.
But it's just us here—
and only us.
Qiao Yan,
will you marry me?
Yes.
I do.
♪ Let me hear it whisper in my ear ♪
♪ Today couldn't be trapped by the past ♪
♪ Roses bloom in silent loneliness ♪
♪ Your love draws me in so deep ♪
♪ In dreams, we embrace again and again ♪
♪ The warmth in my palm is
a longing carved into my soul ♪
♪ Life has held such precious memories ♪
♪ That will remain forever unchanged ♪
I love you.
I love you too.
♪ Let me hear it whisper in my ear ♪
♪ Come a little closer to me ♪
♪ Beneath the starry sky, your eyes ♪
♪ Pull me in once again ♪
♪ In dreams, love and hate
are crystal clear ♪
♪ Yet waking brings only
a boundless white haze ♪
♪ How many summers has life ever known ♪
♪ Only in winter nights do I realize ♪
Mr. Gu is here.
Come on.
Keep up.
Mr. Gu is here.
Hurry up.
Mr. Gu.
Mr. Gu, say something.
Tell us about you and Miss Qiao Yan.
Say something.
Are you and Miss Qiao Yan really together?
-Say something.
-Answer us.
We've been waiting for so long.
Just a few words, Mr. Gu.
Yeah, say something.
Mr. Gu.
Say something.
Miss Qiao Yan.
Were you two together last night?
What happened exactly?
Yeah.
Please tell us.
What's your relationship
[Gu Group]
exactly?
Tell us.
-Yeah. What's your relationship?
-Dad.
Chairman Gu.
Are you here to respond
about the relationship between
Mr. Gu and Ms. Qiao Yan?
You've been chasing us this hard,
waiting at the company every day.
It must be exhausting.
If I don't say something,
you
won't give up.
Everyone,
my adopted son
Gu Jingyuan
and my granddaughter Qiao Yan
are indeed in a relationship.
And they're
getting married soon.
Really?
Getting married soon?
Chairman Gu,
do you support their marriage?
What do you think
of their relationship?
They love each other—
there's nothing wrong with that.
Their marriage
should have
everyone's blessing.
Chairman Gu's right.
What about
the rumors that Gu Jingyuan's
doing this to fight for the inheritance?
What do you think?
Yeah. What's your take?
I'm handing Gu's Group to Jingyuan
not just because
he's my son,
but because of
his ability
and my trust in him.
All these years,
he's been dedicated
to both the company
and the Gu family.
But
Gu Jingyuan is your adopted son,
and Qiao Yan is your granddaughter.
If they get married,
wouldn't that—
Let me answer that.
Everyone,
I don't want any speculations
or misunderstandings
to make my dad worried
or my fiancee
wronged.
So,
I hereby announce
I'm giving up my status
as the Gu's adopted son.
Grandpa,
tell me.
Why did you suddenly agree?
What?
Don't you want me to?
Of course I do.
Maybe I should go back
and talk to them again?
I see.
Did you discuss it beforehand
without telling me?
Jingyuan told me not to tell you.
He didn't want you to worry.
Whether I'm Dad's son
or
your husband,
I'm still part of the Gu family, right?
That's great.
I wish you both the best.
From now on, you're in charge of
your own lives.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, Grandpa.
We'll be happy, for sure.
These old foxes
are so tough to handle.
No matter how cunning they are,
they still ended up
tamed by you, Mr. Qin.
Oh, by the way,
the violin has arrived.
The violin made by the master
is really different.
All credit goes to you.
Ordinary people
can't buy it even with money.
The one who receives it
must be very touched.
By the way,
any news from Xijiang lately?
Does this gossip about
the Gu family count?
[Livestream]
I hereby announce
I'm giving up my status
as the Gu's adopted son.
They're
getting married soon.
Book me a flight immediately.
I'm going back right now.
Yes.
♪ Let me hear it whisper in my ear ♪
♪ Come a little closer to me ♪
♪ Beneath the starry sky, your eyes ♪
♪ Pull me in once again ♪
♪ In dreams, love and hate
are crystal clear ♪
♪ Yet waking brings only
a boundless white haze ♪
♪ How many summers has life ever known ♪
♪ Only in winter nights do I realize ♪
♪ If I decide to fall,
then miss it afterward ♪
♪ Every time I tell myself
to try hard to break free ♪
♪ Hiding my feelings
so I won't fear there's no result ♪
♪ The rain pours hard ♪
♪ Yet I can hear you say you love me ♪
♪ Let me hear it whisper in my ear ♪
♪ Today couldn't be trapped by the past ♪
♪ Roses bloom in silent loneliness ♪
♪ Your love draws me in so deep ♪
♪ In dreams, we embrace again and again ♪
♪ The warmth in my palm is
a longing carved into my soul ♪
♪ Life has held such precious memories ♪
♪ That will remain forever unchanged ♪
♪ Let me hear it whisper in my ear ♪
♪ Today couldn't be trapped by the past ♪
♪ Roses bloom in silent loneliness ♪
♪ Your love draws me in so deep ♪
♪ In dreams, we embrace again and again ♪
♪ The warmth in my palm is
a longing carved into my soul ♪
♪ Life has held such precious memories ♪
♪ That will remain forever unchanged ♪
Jingyuan,
I'm entrusting Yan
to you on behalf of Hai and Yuling.
Don't worry, Dad.
I will love you
and protect you
with my life.
Looking forward to our future together,
Mr. Gu.
From now on, I'm all yours,
Mrs. Gu.
Yuan.
I wish you happiness.