(Chifuyu) Isn't this that weirdo?
(Koharu) Eh!
There are people who win big prizes for their novels➡
Are you going to propose to me?
(Kurosaki) I love it.
(cry)
Please don't cry anymore.
Yeah….
No... Kurosaki-san...
I can't see the screen because of my tears...
Koharu-san, what happened?
Ah~ I'm sorry...
I was so moved when I heard the continuation of "First Thunder Love"...
picture….
(cry)
``Today I'm here to ghostwrite Kurosaki-san's novel.''
``The other day, I injured Kurosaki-san's right hand...''
((Sorry!))
((That's right! Substitute writing?))
((Please let me help you with that typing!))
《I pushed myself to apologize to Mr. Kurosaki, who doesn't blame me➡
I decided to visit the store during its regular holidays.
I'm totally hooked...
Ugh…｡
The love between these two clumsy people was truly the best...
Ugh... I'm extremely happy...
Ah, please.
It was only planned for one book➡
There were so many requests for a sequel... Ah, that's amazing...
As a writer, I have never been so happy.
I will do my best to meet your expectations.
I'll do my best, even though it's a small effort!
thank you.
《What an amazing house...》
《I can't believe I can live in a house like this➡
Kurosaki-san is truly an amazing person.
《Stories are being created more and more》
``What's going on in your head? 》
《Now that I think about it... I wear glasses when I work》
《Perhaps because of that... Kurosaki-san today...》
Here and now...
《You look very adult...》
Ah... are you tired?
No, it's okay.
"fool! 》
``I'm Kurosaki-san's right hand now!'' 》
《I have to concentrate! 》 Here and now...
Can I hug you?
When I told her that...《That was a line...》
Her eyes flickered in confusion.
《That's right》
I'm sorry, I can't stop myself anymore.
《But I am conscious of it...》
I want everything about you so badly.
《So I become nothing~! 》
(Sound of keyboard hitting)
Kurosaki...
What? What happened?
Ah... I was worried about the development.
This is how I often come up with ideas.
Ah...｡
Or just clap your hands...
Hey...! Let's stop doing that now.
Because I’m injured…｡ Ah…｡
♬～
that….
If it's okay with me, I'll consult with you.
picture?
Sorry for interrupting an amateur.
Ah, no, that's it.
I'm grateful.
Oh...then could you please sit on the sofa?
Ah yes.
How can I say I love you and love you so much that I can’t stand it➡
Can you understand?
Tch... it's close! Ugh...!
Mr. Koharu? What are you doing?! Suddenly!
Ah... I wanted to recreate the scene from the novel...
I wonder if this will convey my feelings to the heroine...
Is that so?
it's okay! I think it gets across!
Thank you very much, that was helpful.
Shall we take a break now?
Well... let's do that!
♬～
Please eat a lot.
amazing…!
Ah...I'm sorry, I had to make lunch for you.
No, it's a menu to improve concentration and immunity.
Hehe...
Ah, me too.
Please. Oh, I don't have wine...
Ah, it's grape juice.
With glucose and polyphenols➡
I thought it would improve my concentration and immunity.
Ah, thank you very much.
Let's have it.
I'll enjoy having this.
♬～
It's delicious.
I also need to improve my concentration.
《Something is going wrong today...》
Koharu-san, how did you feel about the sequel so far?
Huh?
I would love to hear your thoughts.
Well, my heart is already pounding.
As expected, Mr. Kurosaki is amazing!
Ah, good...
From here➡
How will it develop?
Ah... the hero proposes to the heroine.
Wow, that's exciting!
Actually, I long for a warm family.
It's in the novel➡
I want the main character to build a family like that.
Do you admire it?
yes.
When I was young, I grew up in a home where my parents loved each other deeply.
Until my mother died and my father remarried.
My father and my new mother.
My younger brother was born during that time.
I was the only one who couldn't adjust well to the new family my father had created...
Oh, I'm sorry for talking like this.
home….
But I can't believe Kurosaki-san had such a past.
I don't have the same happiness as before➡
I had given up thinking I would never be able to get it again.
but….
When I met Koharu-san, I had a dream.
picture?
Warm, beautiful and very adorable➡
I dream of building a happy family with my beloved Koharu.
《That's right...》
I'm different from the main character➡
I proposed right away, but...
Hehe.
Ah... Ah, that's right!
I also brought dessert!
a….
(sound of hitting table)
Ah~ Excuse me! OK?
No problem at all.
Please take it off. Huh?
Okay, I need to wash that quickly! Mr. Koharu?
Please take it off! Mr. Koharu?
Yes, yes…! Koharu-san!
Where is the washroom? Wait...
I'll borrow the bathroom!
Good, it fell...
Koharu-san, I'm sorry.
I would like to ask for a little help.
yes.
♬～
I'm sorry for asking you to help me with this.
No, it's my fault.
Could you please bend down a little?
Ah yes.
♬～
《Kurosaki-san's back is… wide》
《Think something strange again! 》
Excuse me before.
Huh?
《That's strange》
《Even though I'm used to Nacchan changing clothes...》
I... I'm sorry, I'm so bad...
It's okay, it's okay to take it slow.
《Mr. Kurosaki is not my younger brother》
《He's an adult... he's a man》
Ah... what were you doing all the time?
Ah, if you choose clothes that are easy to wear, you'll be fine.
Although it takes time ➡
It's not something I would ask my brother to do.
younger brother? Did you say that earlier?
yes.
I decided to attend a university in Tokyo➡
We live together.
Huh... Is that so?
Well, we're good friends now.
Well... that's right.
Okay, one more thing.
I was thinking of just thinking about work today...
Koharu-san is working hard for me...➡
I love it so much that I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry, I got carried away even though I'm an acquaintance of mine.
I also look at Koharu like a novel➡
I want to be the kind of man who makes your heart flutter.
《My heart is already so excited by Mr. Kurosaki...》
``But if I say that, I'm sure he'll go berserk again...''
"but…"
Mr. Koharu?
Mr. Kurosaki…➡
We are no longer acquaintances.
Mr. Kurosaki➡
I've become someone you care about.
picture…?
♬～
In other words... one step closer to becoming a lover from an acquaintance➡
Can I interpret it?
Well… well…｡
Well then...!
⚟That's it! ⚞
Mr. Kiriya! I was surprised...
(Kiriya) Even when I rang the intercom, there was no response.
I got worried and came here.
Ah... that...
This time, I received my precious novelist's right hand...
I'm really sorry! Ah, no.
As for the book, Kurosaki is at fault.
I am very sorry.
More than that.
♬～
I agreed to have Mr. Shirase write for me, but➡
Should physical contact be prohibited?
Eh... I haven't touched Koharu-san at all...
You let me change your clothes...!
It's dangerous enough even if you don't actually touch it.
Kiriya-san, since when...?
Mr. Shirase is about to have a meeting➡
It's fine for you to go home today.
Thank you for writing on my behalf.
Ah, yes, please excuse me today.
Ah, if you'd like a lunch box, the two of you.
Please excuse me. Koharu-san...!
(Sound of door opening and closing)
《I said it was someone I was interested in》
``But does this mean I like it? 》
《Are you just excited because Kurosaki-san is being kind to you? 》
(Yui) Koharu-chan Hello!
Ah, Yui-chan, hello Fujita-san.
(Fujita) Hello, Koharu-chan, you seem happy today.
picture?
(Yui) Because I've been smiling ever since.
Did you see it? Well... that's not the case.
You look like something good happened, right?
I fell in love, I fell in love...! No... that's not it...!
It's cute. Being embarrassed like that feels like youth.
No, that's not right... Um... (Fujita) Enjoy it.
(Yui) Bye!
Ba... bye...
(sneeze)
♬～
《It’s love after all~⁉》
Are the words “I like someone” and “I like someone” the same thing?
You were thinking the whole time during the meeting, right?
Sorry, I can't concentrate.
Someone who cares, that is, someone who is aware.
There are times when your heart beats faster for me.
Ha! Is this okay to propose again?
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Do you realize that work is important right now?
This is not the time to be obsessed with love.
“CURO’s first romance novel will be made into a movie!
The director is master Mr. Yanagi!
The leading role is Rei Arisugawa, a talented young actress who is currently making waves! ”｡
There's a big project underway that will put our company's fortunes at stake, right?
I am aware of this.
But... I can't stop my feelings for Koharu-san.
I will be careful not to interfere with my work.
Could you please watch over me?
Sigh…｡
I hope my love will have a positive impact on my work➡
I was watching...
Relationships with minors cannot be overlooked any longer.
Kurosaki, I didn't say it because I thought you'd be depressed.
(sound of writing)
♬～
It's still too early to get excited.
That's so...
So... But Kiriya-san said it before➡
"Acquaintances have zero chance" was wrong, right?
I'm also learning about love.
I won't be confused this time.
Huh? Learning?
Haha... ah.
I'm sure I took it off at that time.
But if your love experience level is 5, then I...
1 billion.
Shall I tell you about my journey as a woman?
I know that Mr. Kiriya is highly sought after.
So let's make a suggestion.
If pushing doesn't work, try pulling.
It's a game of love.
I'm not telling you not to contact me.
It's an important time, so we should refrain from meeting together.
If you end up being chased by a weekly magazine like the other day➡
Shirase-san will be in trouble.
That may be true.
Smartphone) (ringtone)
yes.
picture? A special appearance in a movie?
Is it Kurosaki?
Ah... a request from Mr. Arisugawa...｡
Understood, I will look into it positively.
It might be better than being rumored to be underage.
I'm home.
(Akihira) Will it disappear? (Chifuyu: Natsuki) Eh!
(Akihira) Lie! Yeah! It'll be gone.
(Natsuki) Eh!
(Akihira) Welcome back Koharu.
(Natsuki) Hey, welcome back! (Chifuyu) Welcome back.
(Yao) Welcome back.
Huh? Dad, what about this?
(Akihira) The store has been busy lately, and Koharu seems to be in her youth➡
I decided to hire a part-time worker. Eh!
I wanted to introduce you to Koharu, so I asked her to wait for me.
This is Yuo-kun.
I've heard from the store manager.
Nice to meet you, Koharu-chan.
Ah yes.
thank you.
It's amazing that Yuio attended Kamikei University.
I also have a strong nervous breakdown! thank you.
I can't compete with Nacchan though.
(Natsuki) Hehe~｡
``Why is there such a sparkling person? 》
Um... why are you here?
I saw CURO being advertised on TV and it's close to my house.
Eh... Are you a fan of CURO by any chance?
picture? Well…｡
You love me so much... Um, but➡
Sometimes the person himself is at the store...
Of course, as long as I have a part-time job➡
I won't do anything that will cause any inconvenience.
That's right. I'm sorry for asking something strange.
We are a small shop, but please visit us.
No, thank you very much.
《He seems like a nice person and I wish he had a part-time job➡
I might be able to write for Kurosaki-san more.
Okay, I'll be serious!
Okay, let's do it then?
(Akihira) Isn't it Yuio-kun? Okay, okay.
(Akihira) Nacchan, it's okay. (Natsuki) I forgot, I forgot!
Ah...｡ Hehehe...｡
(Kiriya) Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry for barging into your place of work.
There will be schools and shops, so it's best not to be forced into it.
If you want to write for me, I can prepare it for you here.
it's okay.
I wanted to work with Kurosaki-san until his hand healed.
is that so.
Well, today I only have a meeting with the director➡
I hope you can work on the manuscript in your free time.
Understood.
Smartphone) (ringtone)
sorry.
Yes, what?
Ah, I understand, I'll go right away.
Sorry, I'll be back soon➡
Can I have you wait here?
Ah yes.
♬～
(Arisugawa) CURO!
I wanted to meet you for the first time in a while!
It's been a long time.
(Arisugawa) Thank you for playing the role of the heroine.
If it were to be made into a movie, the heroine would be➡
He remembered that I said I definitely wanted to do it.
Ah... no, I don't have anything...
I'm very happy to be able to perform together.
《What... what? 》
``You're a worker, right? 》
《But his arms are crossed...》
"picture? picture? Eh~⁉》