YoYo English Channel YouTube
Kissing myself thousands of times
The most reluctant moment is that moment
Live in the world
A thousand miles of crazy
Who never wanders
Who doesn't know the distance between the two worlds
The end of the world
Live in the world
Youthful and wild
The youthful and wild
The world is like a dream
Live in the world
A thousand miles of crazy
Who doesn't know the distance between the two worlds
Live in the world
A thousand miles of crazy
Who doesn't fall into sorrow
The world is like a dream
Live in the world
A Thousand Miles of Crazy
Episode 18
The child does not like to eat, do not cut it. Use dragon mother's drum shell. Dragon mother's drum shell invites you to watch Lotus Pavilion.
Oulin.
Who are you?
I...
Love is a little bit of a secret.
I'll cut you a few more times.
Who are you?
Sister Qiao.
The beauty in the martial arts world
must be compared with you and me.
Then tell me,
who is more beautiful?
But I'm not here to compete with you.
I'm here to tell you
that Li Xiangyi
is still alive.
Where is he?
I also want to know
where he is.
Through this Lotus Pavilion,
you are where the Heaven's created you.
The fragrance of the Lotus is so strong.
The fragrance of the Lotus Pavilion
is a question of the two worlds.
Unlock it.
The fragrance of the Lotus
is created by the eight-storied sky.
The shadow falls down.
The dead door is in front of the sky.
The deep door is in the earth.
The open door is in the mountains.
The door is in the mountains.
& &1
The
You can't stop me!
Of course you can't.
But today, all the martial arts groups are here.
You can't make trouble easily.
One more step!
One more step.
Why is the Black Immortal trapped in the Lihua Town?
The devil came to us to catch us.
What?
This is a destroyed town.
Be careful.
You look so old.
It's a pity that you're defeated.
It's been ten years.
Why did you come here today?
Your martial arts skills are still not good.
You're not qualified to ask me.
Although I'm not the best martial arts expert,
if you want to help me with the war and let me get married,
don't blame me for being rude.
Ziqi.
Your martial arts skills are much better.
I heard that you can repair internal injuries
with the help of the hammer.
It's hard to resist the power of the people.
Let's go together.
Don't be polite to him.
Go.
I'll come again.
Bad news.
Something happened in the west.
Miss Qiao went to the west.
Huanbin.
She's recovering.
The cicada in the ice,
cold and cold.
It's the antidote for its poison.
Yangzhou is slow.
It's Qiao Liqiao.
She poisoned Miss Qiao.
I'm sorry.
Eunuch Guan.
You use the golden needle to detoxify the poison.
You can certainly),
masa, take your lessons.
Earlier, I already checked on Miss Qiao.
The cicada Architecture and Cicada will be sterilized.
The poison only enters the mouth
And isõ championship title in half an hour.
The poison will have no hjn j.
Conclusion of this poison only uses the ends of the innards of Teeth and Collar.
This attack!!
So after the cicada alters the weapon
The patient playing safely.
If the coldness of the body is too strong,
it will hurt the patient
and make him die
in a very fragile condition.
The only person who can do this
is Yang Zhongman.
That's why I said
to detoxify him.
Otherwise, after three hours,
the ice will be hard to block.
Miss Qiao will die from the ice.
Yang Zhongman?
That's Prime Minister Li's special inner power.
If he can save An Mian,
he can ask me to kneel down and beg him.
But Prime Minister Li has died long ago.
What does the demoness want?
You don't have to use your inner power to save her.
Can you let me see Miss Qiao?
It's none of your business.
Don't touch Wan Mian.
Do you have any other way to save her?
Actually, Mr. Guan and I
have discussed the method of detoxifying poison.
We only found that the Bodhisattva's Five-Liang
But it takes three hours
for the Bodhisattva's Five-Liang to come here.
It's too late.
I know one or two
of the Bodhisattva's methods of detoxification.
If you believe me,
can you let me try it on Miss Qiao?
Can you really do it?
If you open your mouth,
do you know the consequences?
It's a matter of life and death.
I dare not to play a trick.
But the blood is cold and cold.
In the new spring,
the summer and autumn are more than 60 degrees.
With the fire burning,
the poison soup can be detoxified.
How can you
find the things you said?
Don't try to protect me.
There are many medicine shops,
fruit shops and tea shops in the town.
They can be gathered.
We can gather together.
I believe Brother Li.
I don't need you.
We are here.
I'll go find it.
You take care of Miss Qiao.
Leave the rest to us.
Please prepare three buckets of hot water.
Miss Qiao can detoxify at last.
Yes.
Miss Qiao.
You came looking for me.
And this 교.
It spilled.
Mr. Li, I've done with습니다
How's my miss going?
Can you open the door now?
Your Majesty, the situation in the Mumen Villa has changed.
Ming Zhu,
do you have the butcher's knife with you?
Corey.
What are you gonna do about it?
The teacher didn't even do it and it doesn't count.
About what?
I miss you.
Li's Mansion
You risked your life for her.
She's injured.
You even risked your life.
Is it worth it?
How is it?
What's going on?
Mr. Li has been keeping the door closed.
Li Lianhua.
We've prepared everything.
Mr. Guan and the others have been given the medicine.
How is it going?
Li Lianhua.
What's going on?
You should tell us.
I don't want them to know
that I can help you.
What are you doing?
Don't come over.
The sound of the enemy's flying...
To make her alive,
she's been locked in the prison for an hour.
Yan Meng will pay for it with his life.
Wan Ming.
She's injured.
Did the enemy's flying dust hurt her?
I'm fine.
It's just a sudden stroke.
Go after her.
How could it be sudden?
Come on, sit down.
How is it?
Where's your waist?
It's in the lotus house.
Go get it for me now.
Go.
Okay, hang in there.
I'll be right back.
The poison is like a worm.
The poison will eat the head of the stone.
It will start with a short life.
Then it will go in.
It will go crazy.
It will kill you.
Your Majesty.
She's been detoxified.
She just got a sleepwalk.
She's still unconscious.
I didn't expect
Your Majesty to cover for Li Xiangyi.
Li Xiangyi owes me a match.
I can't let her die so easily.
Besides, they're competing.
There's no need to do this.
Jiao Liqiao is behind your action.
He found Li Xiangyi alive.
He wants to lure her to show himself.
Why does Jiao Liqiao care so much
about Li Xiangyi's life?
She and I are not on the same page.
Go back and watch her every move.
Check how many people are still useful
in the Golden Thread Embroidery.
Yes.
Di Fisheng.
I've brought the person you want.
I just want Wan Ming to be safe.
Her poison has been reduced.
She's very well now.
I'm sorry.
Xia Yi.
Here.
This way, please.
He said he was in a state of panic.
I didn't know it would be so scary.
He hasn't woken up after taking the medicine.
The doctor didn't see anything wrong after he finished his examination.
He didn't give him any prescription.
Brother Guan.
Just look at him.
I thought you had a grudge against Su Yuan.
You always targeted him.
Why are you so anxious?
I was fighting with him.
It's more important to me.
Brother Guan.
Just look at Brother Li.
I thought you were having a good rest.
But I'm worried about Brother Li.
The pulse is hard to predict.
Why is it so strange?
The pulse is soft and weak.
The blood is running out.
There's no way to stop it.
The pulse is not enough.
Not enough for what?
Is it important, Brother Guan?
His heart is not full of qi and blood.
It's an emergency.
He has no life-threatening worries.
He should get rid of his worries and worries.
He can rest in peace.
It's good that he's fine.
I was hit by a heavy heavy dust.
Jiali Qiao said that only Yang Zhongman could save me.
Then...
The Golden Moon Alliance
is just trying to create a panic
and put pressure on us.
Di Feisheng wants to threaten me with your life.
He wants me to let King of the Silver go after me.
How can a King of the Silver go after you
who is more important than you?
Just give it to him.
Di Feisheng detoxified me.
Of course.
Li Lianhua
claimed to be able to detoxify you.
I believed him
and let him mess around.
I'm just glad that
the Golden Moon Alliance is asking for it.
Except for Di Feisheng,
no one else has the ability.
Zhishen,
today is our good day.
I failed to protect you.
I'm fine now.
We knew
the Golden Moon Alliance would come to provoke us.
But...
They designed it
just to kill King of the Silver?
Wan Mian,
just now...
I mean,
no matter who the Golden Moon Alliance is or anyone else,
I will never let them
have the chance to get you.
I have something to discuss with Ji Han and the others.
You still need to rest.
I'm here to tell you
that Li Xiangyi
is still alive.
Xiangyi?
Yang Zhongman?
I have Yang Zhongman's inner power in my body.
I saw Xiangyi.
Isn't it a dream?
How is that possible?
Your favorite osmanthus cake.
I've been waiting for it for a long time.
You made this rope knot yourself, right?
It's different from others.
You can't untie it.
How come it's
exactly the same?
It's you.
I'm so stupid.
You're alive.
You're still alive.
Brother Li.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just feel a little dizzy.
I feel much better.
Brother Guan prescribed a prescription.
The prescription is being taken.
Have some water to warm your throat.
I can't drink it for a while.
I'm not thirsty.
I'm really worried about you.
It's not a big deal.
Miss Si, your wound...
It's okay.
Brother Guan said he had a way.
He'll cure me.
Don't worry.
Brother Li.
I received a letter from my grandfather today.
He said the ice and the fingerprint were not found.
But the incense you took
is definitely the men's incense.
The men's incense
is the same as what Miss Zhi Yu said.
This is the second secret of men's incense.
It's the incense made by Wu Xinhua.
It can make people
fall into the illusion of the contract.
Losing the pain and the feeling of being cut by others
and being torn by the skin of people won't struggle.
If you use a large number of men's incense to deal with the martial artists,
you will lose all your martial arts.
Who on earth
put Wu Xinhua on my brother?
It's said that the third king of the Golden Moon Alliance killed my brother.
It doesn't have to be like this.
But the men's incense has been destroyed.
Wu Xinhua is getting less and less.
This incense is quite precious.
Not everyone
can get a large number of men's incense.
By the way, Brother Li.
Speaking of men's incense,
I saw it in the corner of the bridge today.
I found it was painted by men's incense.
I can't make it out.
But I'm sure it's the men's incense.
I heard my grandfather say that.
He must not know that I can hear it clearly.
Otherwise, he would kill me.
The corner of the bridge?
Actually,
my grandfather sent a letter
to ask me to go home.
But Brother Li,
I think...
Actually...
Actually, I think...
What do you think?
Such a big thing happened today.
In less than three days,
it will be passed on to Grandpa Su.
Do you still want him to worry about you?
Besides, the wound on your face
is very painful.
I'm afraid that
you can't get out of the wound.
Besides, the wound on your face
will be healed if you want to recover early.
You can't delay it.
Go back and pack up.
Leave tomorrow morning.
Okay, Brother Li.
I'll come to you
when I'm recovered.
Okay.
Brother Li,
this is the jade pendant of our Su family.
If you need anything,
you can blow this pendant
and send me a letter in exchange for my Su family's song.
Brother Guan,
is Miss Su's wound
very serious?
What's the matter with you?
I can't get out of the wound
no matter what poison you are poisoned with.
What's your background?
I'm just an ordinary person
who is unlucky.
I cut your pulse
and you can't survive for four months.
Do you know that you won't live long?
It's been less than four months.
Since you know your situation,
you need to annoy Miss Su again
and let her break your heart.
You
can catch his brain
if he gets old.
Everyone,
he consciousness
is about Black Snake.
SinceShe's decided to rectify this dance
and my strong body,
two fortresses that they won't spill out?
If we break they will also give more silver.
If we destroy them,
we will get thorough reward of seven battery.
So, I'are the one that holy.
I must be a bad guy.
Who will upload this to 伦 Talent Page?
You!
I must cut you into pieces.
I won't.
I don't really like those kinds of people.
Why don't you rest at this time?
I've been in the army for many years.
I've been waiting for you to save me.
But my poison is from Yangzhou.
What do you think?
Miss Qiao.
Your poison is not from my sister.
Di Feisheng gave you this.
Really?
You took the sachet I embroidered for Xiang Yi
and told me that Xiang Yi was dead.
You watched me make the sachet again
and told me to put it down
and move forward without any worries.
Did you do it on purpose?
No.
No matter
how I see it
you do this off.
You said he was dead
and let him show his dead séorama on purpose.
like the self-recommended
I of everyone
with him,
with one move,
with one dream,
no one is better than me
you could cheat others,
you could not me
why are you not turning around
I won't turn around.
Are you still blaming me?
You blame me
for the letter you wrote
before you went to the East Sea, right?
If you want to lie to me,
can you look at me?
Xiang Ying,
you still hate me, right?
You were
so stubborn.
How could I not recognize you?
I've waited for you for ten years.
Are you blaming me?
So you'd rather
run away for ten years
than come back
and give me a heartache, right?
A Min,
look at me.
I'm doing pretty well, right?
I see you now
have your own life.
I'm happy for you.
I'm happy for you, too.
Xiang Ying,
why...
Why have you changed so much?
I can't see
your face anymore.
It's only been ten years.
What happened?
When I fell into the sea,
I was just hanging in the ship's cage.
I didn't sink into the sea.
I went back to the Four Ancient Gates
and saw the letter you wrote to me.
Later,
I just wanted to change a magic.
No.
That's not what I meant.
You hate me for separating from you,
so you left?
You just won't forgive me for this.
Don't blame me.
Do you remember
your lover's untimely death,
so she died suddenly?
I remember it clearly,
There was never a moment
when she was not dying.
But I suddenly remembered
the expense you had spent
I can't chase after him forever.
But how could that be his fault?
Do you know how much I regret it?
These ten years,
I kept dreaming about you.
I dreamed about the moment when you were about to leave the house.
I tried my best to stop you.
But when I woke up,
I only knew that all of this was irreparable.
Now that you're back,
why didn't you tell us?
Why didn't you tell us?
The past has been so long.
I'm very tired.
I just want to be free.
Then why did you
appear at my wedding?
I promised you that I'd sleep.
I wanted to leave the sweetest candy
to you.
I was
too busy to make you happy.
At least,
I wanted to do that.
If you hadn't told me
that he was dead
at the Putu Temple,
I wouldn't have married Zi Jin.
You're not sad because you married Zi Jin.
You're not regretting marrying Zi Jin.
Xiang Yi,
you're still...
You're still like this.
You killed someone with a single word.
A-Ming,
you like Zi Jin.
It's not wrong to rely on Zi Jin.
Not loving someone alone
is not something you should blame yourself for.
Then you...
Don't you hate me?
I do.
I used to hate you.
In the past,
I hated everyone.
Later, I realized
that it was my own problem.
I was too selfish.
I was also selfish.
Why should I
try to avoid
and not forget Xiang Yi?
A-Ming,
we knew each other.
I was
ignorant at that time.
I didn't understand our feelings.
What was it?
What do you mean?
You mean
you never loved me?
We were young at that time.
We couldn't do anything.
A-Ming,
life is over.
We are not young anymore.
Forget about it.
I saved you
because of my friend's feelings.
Don't misunderstand.
You also know that
the thing I hate the most
is being involved in many things.
Now, the world is vast.
It's my life
that I want to live freely.
I also want to trouble you
not to let others know that I'm still alive.
I sincerely hope
you and Zi Jin
can grow old together
and live a long life.
Ten years is not enough.
Don't you have anything else to say to me?
So what?
Ten years is too long.
A-Ming,
today,
we should say goodbye
and live the life you want to live.
Okay.
Let me ask you again.
Will Li Xiang Yi
really not come back?
He won't come back.
Why did you come in such a pl feet like this?
P mittens stop the blood from evenlyicia
and turn into the body.
You like candy this much.
You really don't look like a hero.
Who said hero can't eat
candy?
By then,
I'll have some soy bean.
Is it good?
It's good.
Then have another one.
You're busy with such big things every day.
You always make me look at your back.
I'm really tired.
It seems that something really happened to Fei Ying Gang.
A Mian, I'll go out for a while.
Oh, right, A Mian.
What did you say just now?
Forget it.
Let's talk about it when I come back.
The sky is still clear.
I can't keep you.
A Mian is a shadow.
I'm tired.
But I can't walk with you.
I can't love you like before.
With this heart,
I'll say goodbye to you.
I wish you a long life,
though you have no friends,
and return what you wished for.
A Mian.
You're hiding from everyone.
I really don't understand
your indisputable stubbornness.
You scared me.
It's late at night.
Why don't you go to the main gate?
Since everyone chose their own way,
why bother?
I don't understand.
But I respect your persistence.
No need, Chief Di.
Just don't argue with me.
OK,ffein.
But you're always so bright and bright.
But you don't like to be honest.
I just want to confirm it.
Compared to before, you're much more cunning.
You're trying to cover up for me.
I owe you a favor.
Why did you bring him here?
Didn't you always blame me for killing your senior?
Master asked me to come
to explain to Sect Leader Li that
ten years ago,
Emperor Yan, Prince Bai, and the four Qing Zun
received the contract of the Shanku Sword.
We didn't believe it.
But when we arrived at the battle,
we found out that the Shanku Sword was dead.
Senior asked about the contract.