[English subtitles are available]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
[Episode 17]
[Lotus Tower Medical Center]
Sit down.
You must be hungry.
I knew you like lively places.
But you're here to keep me company.
That's enough.
Time is running out.
I have to find out
who killed Senior.
Looks like
I have to make a trip back to Sigu Sect.
Could it be that my Lord knew Li Xiangyi was alive?
Maybe he had met Li Xiangyi.
Why wasn't he surprised?
If it's true,
why did he hide all these from me?
He still doesn't believe me.
Did the people sent to investigate the Yuanbao Villa
manage to find anything suspicious?
There was a mysterious owner of the Lotus Tower
called Li Lianhua.
His identity is a mystery, we couldn't find anything about him.
But his appearance and age are similar to Li Xiangyi's.
But, back in the Yipin Tomb,
my Lord met him in person.
You mean,
my Lord didn't kill him then unexpectedly?
Is Li Lianhua
related to Li Xiangyi in some way?
I shall send someone to bring him here
so you may interrogate him, Saintess.
No need to rush.
Don't alert them.
Or it will be more troublesome in the future.
On the seventh day of next month,
Xiao Zijin and Qiao Wanmian will be
getting married at the former residence of the Sigu Sect.
Li Xiangyi loved Qiao Wanmian very much back then.
If he were alive,
he would definitely go.
I might as well give it a try.
Gongyang Wumen.
This new poison of his had better be
as good as he so readily claimed.
Hide.
Keep hiding.
Let your mother see
what you've learned out there.
[Tianji Hall Sect Master, He Xiaohui]
You're really something.
You even used the cruel and deadly
Million Blade Formation on your own son.
I think,
since I can't pass today,
I might as well stay here.
I will never marry the princess anyway.
You're really something!
Such a brutal attack.
Am I not your biological son?
You brat.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Why are you so anxious?
Am I really not your biological son?
You rascal really need to be punished.
You're out of your mind.
Just stay here and get some fresh air
to sober up.
Young Master.
Be careful.
She reacted so strongly.
Is there really something to it?
Xiaobao doubted his background?
That shouldn't be.
Few people knew about the matter
between Second Sister and Shan Gudao.
Could it be that Gongyang Wumen?
Such an ill fate.
Could it be Li...
Who is it?
Who else?
Why are you sneaking around in your house?
Show yourself.
Hurry up and come in.
Not bad.
You managed to break through the Million Blade Formation so quickly.
You've grown up. Not bad.
Tell me what you want.
I'll reward you.
I heard it.
Your aunt and I
were gossiping about other sects.
What's there to eavesdrop on?
Please tell me.
What's the relationship between
my deceased Second Aunt and Shan Gudao?
Your Second Aunt and Shan Gudao
were friends.
They had a child.
Gongyang Wumen told me everything.
He said
he treated you and my father.
You
are unable to conceive.
Look at you.
You've gone silly because of the Million Blade Formation.
What do you mean by unable to conceive?
Where did you come from then?
You are your parents' biological child.
No wall in this world is airtight.
It's not a big secret.
Why didn't you tell me?
Mother.
I just want to know the truth.
Shan Gudao was not my uncle, right?
Shan Gudao and Second Aunt.
Were they my biological parents?
Xiaobao.
Your mother didn't want you to know this.
Your mother was only 18 that year.
She only wanted to roam the martial world.
You and she are really alike in this aspect.
But the martial world is so lively
and dazzling.
It's also the easiest place to lose yourself.
[Tianji Mountain Manor, He Xiaolan]
You can't even protect yourself.
Don't save people on impulse.
What do you mean on impulse?
If it weren't for me, you would have died.
I can handle those weak thugs myself.
I didn't need your help.
You're so bad at martial arts.
Don't act tough in the future.
Or you might lose yourself too.
Explain yourself.
Don't underestimate me.
When she first met Shan Gudao,
your mother was prideful and confident.
She tailed after Shan Gudao.
They traveled the martial world
and went through a lot together.
Later,
her heart which once housed the martial world
had space only for Shan Gudao.
But Shan Gudao
only had a heart for the martial world.
He only wanted to be famous
and make a name for himself.
Your mother was heartbroken by him
and returned to Tianji Mountain Manor pregnant.
When she was pregnant with you,
she took a heavy hit.
You were born prematurely.
But your mother...
Your mother didn't make it.
Your mother wore this ever since she was young.
Your mother wanted to be with you forever.
It was your mother's idea to keep this from you.
She didn't tell Shan Gudao about you.
Before she died,
she simply entrusted you to Eldest Sister and her husband.
She hoped you could grow up safely,
live an ordinary life,
and stay out of the martial world.
That's why
you didn't let me roam the martial world.
Yes.
But later, Shan Gudao
found out about you.
He came to Tianji Mountain Manor
and wanted to take you with him.
But you were still young
and sickly.
How could you have roamed the martial world with him?
Of course, your father and I refused.
Xiaobao,
I brought you up
with my own hands.
You are my son.
How can I let others take you away as they please?
Shan Gudao ultimately
respected your mother's last wish.
He never tried to reconnect with you again.
He only told you he was my long-lost brother,
and let you take him as your uncle instead.
Besides,
Shan Gudao was devoted to his status and career.
He can't be a husband
or a father.
What's so good about the people from the martial world?
All of them are indifferent to family
and unpredictable in nature.
Fang Xiaobao,
don't be like them.
Do you hear me?
How could he possibly be like that?
Xiaobao is a good child who cares about his family.
Eldest Sister.
You raised him yourself.
Don't you know he's the most sensible and filial?
Mother.
These are all old matters to me.
I just wanted to understand the truth
to stop making mistakes.
In my heart,
you and my father are my closest kin.
This fact will never change.
It's good that you know it.
Your biological parents are gone.
You are my son.
If I don't care about you, who will I care about?
Alright.
Now that we've made it clear,
we'll never talk about it again.
Don't mention this again.
Do you hear me?
And you,
don't try to take advantage of this matter
and act pitifully or throw a tantrum.
Got it, Mother.
Are you still thinking about roaming the martial world?
Well...
Let me tell you.
I've activated all the major formation
outside the Tianji Mountain Manor.
You want to sneak out?
No way.
Just stay at home obediently
and marry the princess later.
That's the right thing to do.
Mother.
Please discipline your sister.
If you think you can, go ahead.
So beautiful.
I used to treat you
as a relative I had never met before.
I never thought of looking into your past.
What did you look like?
What did you like
and dislike?
I have no clue.
Fang Xiaobao.
I knew you would come here.
Did she draw all these?
She liked to draw things she liked
and things that looked interesting.
Have you seen this item before?
It's probably a rare item
your mother saw somewhere.
I don't know what it is, though.
I've seen this
ice shard before.
The Jinyuan Alliance seems to really want it.
But where did my mother see it?
It's definitely not from Tianji Hall.
But looking at these teeth marks,
I think they seem to correspond to a lock.
A lock?
You mean,
this ice shard is actually a key?
It's like a key to some kind of mechanism.
But it's not a technique from the Central Plains.
I understand now.
What do you understand?
I understand now, Aunt.
Aunt.
You don't need to understand.
Li Lianhua won't understand either.
I'll show him
what a detective of Baichuan Court is capable of.
Show some respect to Physician Li.
[Yuanbao Villa]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
[Lotus Tower Medical Center]
Back then, Qiao Wanmian refused to leave
after Li Xiangyi died.
Xiao Zijin didn't want to go against her will.
He hoped she could gradually get over her old love.
So he expanded and built the Mumian Villa
in the old residence of the Sigu Sect.
He stayed here with her ever since.
No matter what,
this is the hometown of the Sigu Sect.
Xiao Zijin wants to marry Qiao Wanmian
and hold their wedding here.
How is that appropriate?
Li Xiangyi has been dead for ten years.
The Sigu Sect was long gone.
Things have changed.
Be it a relative or a friend, we all need to move on.
Sigu Sect was not an ordinary sect in the martial world.
Li Xiangyi was also the embodiment of justice and chivalry.
I have no intention
of intervening in the wedding.
But if the old residence of Sigu Sect
allows the disbanding of Sigu Sect
and intends to erase traces of Li Xiangyi's legacy,
I will be the first one to refuse.
That's right.
Chaos has yet to descend upon the martial world,
but there are signs of trouble everywhere.
Sigu Sect was born out of the passion
to instill justice in the martial world.
It should not be forgotten at this moment.
Have you heard?
Di Feisheng, the villain head of the Jinyuan Alliance
has recovered from his old injuries.
He's establishing his prestige everywhere.
He even declared war on Baichuan Court.
Do you think
the Jinyuan Alliance
will come and mess up the wedding?
Your old injury
doesn't look too bad.
I've prescribed a prescription for removing blood stasis.
You need to let go of your past records.
Ten coins.
Ten coins for a stupid prescription?
Such a lucrative business.
What a coincidence.
This kind of nonsense
is worthless, my friend.
Let me remind you.
Don't be fooled again.
What are you waiting for?
Take the money and run.
Everyone,
come and have a look.
Come and have a look.
Come.
This man
calls himself a miracle physician.
But he has no benevolence or compassion.
He lies through his teeth
and deceives you with no remorse.
You'd be a fool to believe him.
Everyone,
take a good look at this person's face
and this signboard.
Tell your friends
not to be fooled
or lose money to this swindler again.
Understood?
Radish seed
and allium. A splendid match.
It's a good prescription.
My sworn brother Guan Hemeng learned from a famous teacher.
He's quite well-known in the martial world too.
[Miracle Healer with Needles, Guan Hemeng]
He's known as the Miracle Healer with Needles.
If he says it's a good prescription,
it can't be bad.
Everyone.
Physician Li of Lotus Tower
is worthy of his reputation.
He is Physician Li?
It's him.
Mister.
If you make up stories and spread rumors,
your tongue will rot.
Look.
Another liar.
Miss Su.
Last time, you used the
Miracle Healer with Needles' name to fool people.
Is he
the real deal this time?
Then, try my needles.
I was just kidding.
Don't take it seriously.
Miracle Healer with Needles.
Nice to meet you.
Look.
He ran away so soon.
What would you like to order?
Mr. Li.
Order whatever you want today.
My treat.
Manager.
Sir.
What did I tell you
when I booked the whole inn?
You said
you will pay for the expenses
of all the guests in the inn.
But there is one condition.
The man wearing plain clothes
with a blue bag on his waist,
called Li Lianhua,
is not allowed to enter the inn.
Not...
Are you...
I am
the guest who is not allowed to be here.
What are you waiting for?
Clear the table.
-Hurry.
-Wait, Fang Duobing.
What's the meaning of this?
Did Mr. Li offend you?
Besides,
you've made it so hard for us to get along.
Why are you doing this?
Wrong.
I'm not old and I don't want to die.
And it's not me
who didn't want to get along with Mr. Li.
It's Mr. Li's fault.
Fang Xiaobao!
How can you talk to Mr. Li like that?
Mr. Li.
Our kid is immature.
Please forgive him.
Aunt.
Why are you here?
Manager.
Prepare the best guest room and food for Mr. Li.
Okay, I'll go now.
Aunt, why are you still helping him?
He's a hypocrite
who goes against his words.
Stop talking!
Come with me.
Where are we going?
Go.
Li Lianhua, wait and see.
Go now.
Mr. Li,
I've figured out the Nanyin Script
you asked me to check last time.
But, there are many people here.
Let's go out for a walk.
Wait.
Senior Li.
I have a question for you.
I have a patient
who suffers from poison-induced madness.
He said he saw ghosts in the day
and was often in a panicked state.
He also couldn't sleep at night.
Later, he started killing people
and became extremely irritable.
I have prescribed medication for several days
and pierced his acupoints with silver needles.
But even now, there's no sign of improvement.
If the patient is from the martial world
and has decent inner power,
you can try to process fresh tiger palms
and let the patient eat it.
The tiger palm is extremely poisonous.
It should not be taken without proper preparation.
This is undoubtedly a risky gamble of strength
between the poison and the patient's inner power.
Such a gamble is as good as murder.
It's just fighting fire with fire.
If the patient wants to be sober,
they can take a risk.
If the patient lacks inner power,
I suggest consuming the
tiger palm after soaking it in medicinal soup.
Although the tiger palm is highly poisonous,
it can delay or shorten the time of frenzy.
When treating people and saving lives,
you can't suggest a treatment you're not certain of.
How can you be sure that
the patient won't die after taking the tiger palm?
I can't be sure of that.
You're disregarding human lives!
Guan,
as long as someone can detoxify the poison with pure inner power,
the patient won't be in danger.
How many people in the world have such power?
Pure inner power must be referring to Yangzhouman.
How can he bring Li Xiangyi back to life?
This method of using one's life to test the poison
is so cruel and vicious.
Why are you still defending him?
[Mumian Villa]
Your makeup is too plain, my lady.
Tomorrow, you should wear the golden phoenix and pearl
headpiece that Mr. Xiao chose.
After all, it's a wedding.
Mr. Xiao followed your instructions and kept everything simple.
In consideration of your habit and preference,
he made this old residence your new home,
and won't move out after marriage.
He thought of you in everything he did.
Am I too willful?
Zijin has
always fancied grand events.
I talked too much.
Mr. Xiao always goes along with your choices.
He said,
as long as you ask,
he's willing to die for you.
Why would I ask him to die for me?
I hate
people who abandoned everything
and readily choose death.
Mr. Li.
It's really you.
Why are you wearing a mask?
As a physician of the martial world,
it's natural that I have a lot of enemies.
With this mask,
I feel more at ease.
I see.
The people going in and out of Mumian Villa recently
are all from the martial world.
Better safe than sorry.
That's right.
I heard that the scenery of Mumian Villa
is really amazing.
I just want to see it myself.
I don't know if I can go in.
Why didn't you ask me?
I was about to visit Sister Qiao.
You know Miss Qiao?
Guan is close to Mr. Xiao.
I got to know Miss Qiao when they
brought me to Qingfeng Peak to sightsee.
Back then,
she waited for ten years
to confirm the death of Li Xiangyi.
She even built a cenotaph for him.
Ten years.
That's such a long time.
And yet, Mr. Xiao kept by her side
with such devotion.
It's not easy for them
to finally marry each other.
The person of the past has died.
The living
should cherish the present life.
By the way,
you mentioned you've figured out the Nanyin Script.
I was looking for a chance to give it to you.
I almost forgot.
Look.
This is the meaning of the Nanyin Script.
[Burn your body]
[Suiyan. A mark of a fiend from Nanyin. This mark represents revenge and devour.]
[Statue of the Suiyan fiend]
Burn your body.
It's like a sacrificial text.
Do you know its origin?
Grandpa said the same thing.
Unfortunately, there are too few historical records
about Nanyin.
He hasn't found anything about its background and origin.
However,
look at this.
He found the mark you drew.
This mark is called Suiyan.
It's said to be the mark of a fiend in Nanyin.
This mark represents revenge and devour.
Grandpa said
it's the same as a sacrificial poem.
He's investigating it in this direction.
Revenge and devour.
What does the Jinyuan Alliance want?
What is the connection between the Nanyin Script,
the Nanyin Incense, and the death of Senior?
Sister Qiao.
Xiaoyong.
Mr. Li.
Why are you here together?
It's Sister Qiao's wedding day.
Of course, I need to come and absorb some festive luck.
Mr. Li is also here.
I...
So Mr. Li
is the one in your heart?
Mr. Li
is a very good person.
Sister Qiao.
Tomorrow is the wedding.
Are you happy?
Of course I am.
It's rare to meet your other half.
Congratulations, Miss Qiao.
I brought some wedding candies as a gift.
It's nothing much.
Thank you, sir.
It's very considerate of you.
I've heard a lot about this villa's great scenery.
May I
stroll the villa on my own?
Sure, Mr. Li.
Just leave Xiaoyong here to chat with me.
Sister Qiao.
Mr. Li is not good at talking and socializing.
Sister Qiao, please don't be mad at him.
The candies
may not be very expensive,
but he must have prepared them sincerely.
I haven't said a thing,
but you're so eager to defend him.
Actually, the wedding candies he gave me
made me feel
very nostalgic.
♫I'm only getting into character after half of my life♫
♫The youth can't be friends♫
♫Let bygones be bygones♫
♫The customer dressed in white and asking for wine enters the banquet gracefully♫
♫Smiling foolishly without speaking♫
♫So much affection that it's endless♫
♫The long night accompanies the moon on the rooftop♫
♫Push aside the clouds to count the stars♫
♫Old worries are so far away yet so close♫
♫Since ancient times, how many heroes could♫
♫gamble their lives♫
♫to win against the odds of love♫
♫I long for a cup of blissful intoxication♫
♫I'll write a poem about old friends departing with me♫
♫It's just to choose♫
♫An ending that I like♫
♫Ask a question about the joys and sorrows of the lotus flower♫
♫Break a sword and throw it into the mud♫
♫Only when you're over your worries♫
Sect Leader.
Miss Qiao is outside now.
♫Can you live up to all beings♫
Tell us.
When are you going to marry her?
♫I long for a cup of blissful intoxication♫
Today is Sect Leader's eighteenth birthday.
Don't you think it's too early
♫I'll write a poem about old friends departing with me♫
to talk to him about marriage?
Not at all.
♫It's just to choose♫
Some people are already parents
at the age of 18.
♫An ending that I like♫
Sect Leader.
Don't think about finding someone
better than Miss. Qiao.
You'll get married sooner or later.
♫Ask a question about the joys and sorrows of the lotus flower♫
Why don't you get married soon?
We are all eager to have wedding candies, right?
♫Break a sword and throw it into the mud♫
Yes.
That's right.
♫Only when you're over your worries♫
Don't worry.
On Mian's wedding day,
♫Can you live up to all beings♫
you will all get wedding candies.
Of course.
The sweetest wedding candy
♫I long for a cup of blissful intoxication♫
is reserved for my dear Mian.
Did you hear that?
Sect Leader has already made plans.
♫I'll write a poem about old friends departing with me♫
Let's wish Sect Leader a happy marriage
and have a baby soon.
♫It's just to choose♫
Come on, let's drink.
♫An ending that I like♫
Come on.
♫Ask a question about the joys and sorrows of the lotus flower♫
♫Break a sword and throw it into the mud♫
♫Only when you're over your worries♫
♫Can you live up to all beings♫
[Profound Blue Sky]
It's still the same.
After Senior died,
I kept all his belongings here.
So...
What did you take this time?
Why are you here?
This is
my uncle's old residence.
Is it strange that I came here?
On the contrary,
why did you sneak into
my master's room?
Don't say you were lost again.
It's a rare opportunity.
I'm just here
to enjoy the view of the Sigu Sect.
After viewing the scenery,
it didn't feel that spectacular.
I'm leaving.
You've never been interested in matters of the martial world.
Why are you suddenly interested in the Sigu Sect?
It's a rare opportunity.
It's just a whim.
Can't I do that?
It's strange that you came to Qiao Wanmian's wedding.
You said you were looking for the remains of Shan Gudao.
But you knew
Di Feisheng who was missing for ten years.
Now you sneaked here.
This is your real destination.
Li Lianhua.
What do you really want?
Can you be honest?
Are you addicted to solving cases?
I'm not interested in
playing Guess with a kid.
The Jinyuan Alliance must be up to something.
It's related to the Yipin Tomb.
[Spirit and Pride]
It’s also related to the stolen ice shard.
The death of the Shan Gudao
is also involved.
Don’t think
you're the only one who figured these out.
What do you know?
I know you definitely don't know that
those symbols are not important.
The ice shard is the important one.
You don't know what that is, do you?
Let's make a bet
to see who will find out
the truth behind Jin Mantang first.
When did I say I wanted to investigate this?
Cut the crap.
You...
You're still a kid through and through.
Don't show others
your triumph card so easily.
Remember it.
Li Lianhua!
Come back!
You old fox!
Xiaoyong.
Can you ask your grandpa to confirm if
this incense is the same as the  Nanyin Incense
from Yuanbao Villa?
This incense remains...
Don't worry.
I can't tell you where the incense remains came from,
but I have no ill intentions.
I trust you, Mr. Li.
After we go down the mountain,
I'll pass it to my grandpa with a pigeon.
Thank you.
But I have something else
to ask you.
I heard that there are thumb-sized items
in Nanyin that looked like ice shards.
It is said that
it's related to
the fiend mark and sacrificial poem.
Have you heard of it?
I'll ask Grandpa about that too.
After the wedding tomorrow,
why don't you stay at Qingfeng Peak
for a few more days?
We can enjoy the beautiful scenery in the mountain
while we wait for Grandpa's news.
Okay.
Tomorrow is the wedding.
I hope everything goes well.
Congratulations.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Mr. Xiao.
You came after all.
Come in.
Brother Li.
Aunt.
Look over there.
Li Lianhua.
Mr. Li, how have you been?
Not bad.
He refused to be your wedding company yesterday.
But now he's standing
with Miss Su.
He completely disregarded you, the third most
beautiful woman in the Martial world.
-How dare he!
-That’s right.
He doesn't know what's good for him.
You have to teach him a lesson.
I won't give up
until I get Li Lianhua.
What do you mean get him?
Are you hot, Mr. Li?
Physician Li,
I invited you to enjoy the moon and drink with me last night.
But you were already asleep.
Why don't you sit next to me later
and make up for the owed wine?
Ms. He.
I'm not a good drinker.
If I got drunk at this banquet,
it would be rude of me.
Mr. Li already said that.
Why are you forcing him, Sister He?
Mr. Li, you'd better sit next to me.
It's not your turn to talk, Su.
But I want to talk.
Go ahead then.
I said, he must sit with me.
-He was going to sit with me.
-Here comes the bride.
She's here.
Mian.
You have to be good to yourself.
Come on.
[Peace and Bliss]
Thank you for coming all the way here.
Please forgive me if the reception
is not up to standard.
Drink, everyone.
Here.
Mr. Ji.
Happy wedding.
Thank you for coming.
I'll drink to show my respect.
Congratulations.
Brother Ji, have a seat.
Mr. Bai.
Brother Xiao.
Your long-cherished wish has finally come true.
Congratulations.
Brother Bai, you know that
Baichuan Court is like a home to Wanmian.
You are like her family.
I don't care what others say.
It's enough to receive
her family's blessings.
Brother Xiao,
you and Ms. Qiao are a perfect match.
So many people are envious of you two.
Look at all the people who came
to celebrate your wedding for you.
You get drunk easily.
Don't drink too much.
The wedding wine won't get you drunk. Come on.
That's right.
Have a seat, Mr. Bai.
Miss Shishui.
Look at her.
She has always been impatient.
She even drank the wedding wine first.
Miss Shishui has always admired Xiangyi.
She doesn't like me.
It doesn't matter.
But Wanmian and I
didn't do anything wrong
to Xiangyi.
I feel much better today.
Great!
You drink.
Here, please.
Have some appetizers.
Come on.
Alright, sit down.
Congratulations on your marriage with Ms. Qiao.
When Wanmian wrote the invitations,
she specifically asked me
to invite you, Physician Li.
She wanted to thank you
for bringing solid news about the death of Xiangyi.
I'm glad too.
-Well…
-Mr. Xiao.
Today is a day of celebration
for you and Ms. Qiao.
It has nothing to do with the dead.
You should enjoy yourself.
Congratulations.
Mr. Xiao,
you're not being very honest.
What do you mean by glad?
What would you have done
if Li Xiangyi came back alive?
Please forgive him, Mr. Xiao.
Xiaobao talks nonsense
when he gets drunk.
May you and Ms. Qiao have a long
and happy marriage.
It doesn't matter.
Enjoy yourselves.
Have a seat.
Come on.
Fang Xiaobao,
I know you like Li Xiangyi.
You hate to hear people criticize him.
But he's having a wedding.
What are you being so snarky?
To win a beauty's heart, you have to rely on your own ability.
I think you are
just full of mean energy.
Why don't you go outside
and fight in the sparring arena?
Don't make trouble here.
Fine, I don't fancy this wine anyway.
Watch your back.
Direct your Qi downward
and turn the tide.
Bravo! Bravo!
Good swordsmanship.
Good skills.
Di Feisheng is here.
Inform Xiao Zijin immediately.
Who is sending messages to help me?
Fang Duobing is fine.
Looks like you've taught him Yangzhouman.
If you had taught him ten years ago,
he could have used his inner power to detoxify you
and save your life.
But now, the Yangzhouman
can only keep him safe.
You're not here just to test Fang Duobing.
What are you doing here?
I just checked.
Prison 188.
The first Heaven Prison is here.
King Xunming of Yama is also here.
I'm here to take him away.
You can't find the Heaven Prison.
You will help me find it.
I don't care how much you love Qiao Wanmian.
I don't kill women.
But I have no problem
with killing Xiao Zijin.
I'll take you there.
Okay.
You may leave.
Yes.
Who are you?
You're in my way.
I'll draw more cuts on you.
Who are you?
Sister Qiao!