[English subtitles are available]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
[Episode 14]
Have fun training.
Li Lianhua,
why don't you tell me
more about my master?
You said too little last time.
I want to know more.
Don't you think your body feels hot
and your chest feels tight?
No.
The key to Suzhou Kuai is silence.
Most importantly, talk less and be quiet.
If you talk, your blood will be circulated,
and boom! You'll explode like a firecracker.
Do what you will with that information.
Seeking a famous physician?
Yes.
They don't even state what the illness is.
How will they find a physician like this?
I heard that the owner of Yuanbao Villa,
Jin Mantang, is rich.
He has a lot of money.
Even someone like this has an incurable sickness
that needs the attention of a miracle physician.
It must be an extremely tricky disease to cure.
[Medicine]
Did you forget?
Silence.
Don't talk.
You're asking me where I went, right?
It's time to depart.
You may have
the Suzhou Kuai now.
But it can only temporarily suppress the Gang Qi.
To eliminate all of Di Feisheng's internal power,
we need something extremely cold as a medium.
Currently, I can only think of
using the opal skull from Yuanbao Villa.
No need to reconsider.
Put on your clothes.
Let's go to Yuanbao Villa.
Are you afraid that the owner of the villa won't lend it to you?
Not a problem.
Jin Mantang is offering a lot of money to hire a physician.
I'm sure I can get in there
with my reputation as a miracle physician,
and borrow the opal skull from him.
Are you afraid my medical skills will be exposed?
Yes?
Look, Fang Xiaobao.
You still don't know me well after all this time.
I can even save Di Feisheng,
let alone a Jin Mantang.
What are you saying?
You're so annoying, Fang Xiaobao.
Where did your carefree
and agreeable personality go?
Why are you nagging so much?
The Tianji Mountain!
So you're afraid that Yuanbao Villa
is too close to Tianji Hall,
and they might take you back, right?
I thought about it.
But your life is more important.
As long as you are alive,
even if you were caught,
you could still escape.
Isn't this your usual style?
Let's go.
My Lord has started to suspect me.
He ordered Wuyan to investigate that past incident.
My Lord is a man of his word.
If he finds out about the thundering fire bombs...
Saintess,
you've done so much for the Jinyuan Alliance.
Even if my Lord knows about the past,
he won't blame you.
I did so much for the Jinyuan Alliance
just to make him happy.
If he doesn't care about the Jinyuan Alliance,
why should I care?
Even if you turn back time,
I won't regret
working with Wanshen Clan back then.
Back then, he set up 12 female guardians
as his right-hand man.
How can I tolerate having other women by his side?
When my Lord has nothing left,
he will realize that
I'm the only one who treats him best.
You are right, Saintess.
My Lord trusts you.
Trust?
I'm the only one beside him now.
But I don't have his heart.
But it doesn't matter.
I will give him the whole martial world.
By then,
he will give me his heart.
Granny Blood, isn't that right?
Yes, Saintess.
We have acquired the Rama Vessel.
We just need to find the four Rama Heavenly Ices
and open the vessel.
Then, we will get the searing karmic fire.
By then,
the martial arts world will bow down to you.
My Lord will never leave you again, Saintess.
OK.
Where is Snow Master?
Have you found the whereabouts of the four Heavenly Ices?
Yes.
OK.
Send a letter to Feng Qing.
I want to see his master.
Yes.
It's rare to see you
in such a rush, Saintess.
It's also rare to see Feng Qing's master
in person.
We've been working together for ten years,
but you've always hid your face
and kept your distance.
It's truly frustrating.
You are so eager.
Did something good happen?
The four Heavenly Ices required to open the Rama Vessel
were handed over to four Nanyin citizens
who lived in hiding in the Central Plains.
Now, they are in the hands of their descendants.
I can only tell you where one of them is.
My men will also go to get the Heavenly Ice.
We'll let skills decide who gets it.
At the end of it, we'll negotiate
based on what we have.
What do you think?
Okay.
Let me tell you where to find the first one.
He is the owner of Yuanbao Villa, Jin Mantang.
He is very timid and cautious.
Do you plan to steal it,
or snatch it from him?
No matter what it takes,
I will get the Heavenly Ice.
You said you wanted to hide my tower?
Tianji Hall wants to capture you,
not burn down my tower.
There's no need to hide so well.
What?
No.
[Yuanbao Villa]
What are you here for?
Don't panic.
We are not bad people.
I took the physician recruitment poster,
and I'm here to treat your master.
Since you are physicians,
why are you dressed like this?
Why are you sneaking around?
I was collecting herbs on my way here.
This can repel mosquitoes.
Please convey my message.
Tell him that Li Lianhua wants to see him.
How dare you!
Are you the miracle physician who can revive the dead,
[Housekeeper, Jin Changbao]
Li Lianhua?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
This is my assistant.
What a coincidence.
A few miracle physicians
happen to be in the villa right now.
You can have tea with them
and discuss medicine together.
Okay, thank you.
Please come in.
I often heard that Master Jin Mantang has many treasures.
He's always ranked top ten in the list of rich men.
Now that I'm here,
I can say that he lives up to his reputation.
You're too kind.
Stop!
Physician Guan.
His tongue is pale
and he suffers from vomiting and diarrhea.
It's clearly a case of spleen and stomach flu.
Let me give you some moxibustion.
You'll feel better in no time.
Physician Guan.
I'm really fine now.
You have been giving me moxibustion since yesterday.
I'm about to be cooked.
Usually, people beg me to treat them.
[The Elusive Physician - Gongyang Wumen]
But they have no chance.
I'm in a good mood today.
You look pale
and your breathing is weak.
I thought there must be air obstruction in your organs.
So I took the initiative to take your pulse from a distance.
I didn't expect your assistant to be so ignorant.
I see, you're the elusive physician,
senior Gongyang Wumen.
Excuse me for the unruly behaviour.
I'm Li Lianhua.
I was caught off guard just now.
Please forgive me.
Li Lianhua?
You are the legendary
physician who can revive the dead
and the owner of the Lotus Tower, Li Lianhua?
You look quite ordinary.
I just know a little about medicines.
This is Guan Hemeng, known as the
Swallow Needle in the martial world.
So you are Guan.
I've never seen a medical skill that could bring back the dead.
Li Lianhua.
Let's have a competition.
We'll see who's better at medicine.
We'll... treat him!
Where did the mute come from?
So rude.
Little mute.
Are you Physician Li's assistant?
He hasn't made a sound yet.
It's none of your business.
Why does a mute have so much to say?
I don't understand what you're gesturing.
Silence,
and grace.
Guan, don't be angry.
He is just my assistant.
He's new in the martial world and doesn't know the rules.
Don't take it to heart.
When I'm free,
I'll definitely come to consult you.
Physician Li is indeed gentle and polite.
But you little follower
needs some discipline.
You're right.
Don't mind him.
It doesn't matter.
This is the physician even the King of Hell fears,
Jian Lingxiao.
[The ghost-feared Physician, Jian Lingxiao]
There's nothing wrong with your throat.
It's just that there's a wave
of Gang Qi currently suppressed in his body.
Since it's not an illness, it can't be cured.
But you should talk more
to help you get rid of some Gang Qi.
You old fox!
Silence,
and grace.
So he's not a mute.
What a pity.
I'll get even with you later.
It's such an honor to have so many miracle physicians
[Master of the Villa, Jin Mantang]
gathered here in Yuanbao Villa.
Are you Jin Mantang?
Yes, I am.
I heard that you are seriously ill.
That's why you're recruiting famous physicians.
But looking at you now,
your voice is strong and clear,
and your face radiant and healthy.
It doesn't look like you're sick.
To be honest,
I invited you here
for another favor.
These are the letters I received
in the past month.
These letters all demand
that Master Jin surrender
all the assets of Yuanbao Villa.
Otherwise,
he will be killed.
Who sent these blackmail letters?
How outrageous.
Despite investigations, I have no clue.
Money is just a material possession.
To me,
it's not that important.
It's just that the family business was passed down by my ancestors.
How can I possibly surrender it
to those despicable people?
Now, my villa's security
has been reinforced.
It's not easy to break in.
But it's hard to guard against hidden arrows.
A servant died of poisoning recently.
As such, I can’t sleep or sleep well.
So you want us to come here
to keep watch of your daily life
and prevent any attempts at poisoning you.
And if something really happens,
there are so many great physicians here.
You can be at ease.
Right?
Exactly.
Who would have thought?
I'm a famous physician of the apricot forest.
But I was tricked here
to serve people to eat and sleep.
If you help me get through this,
I will reward you well.
You are really generous, Master Jin.
Looks like I didn't come here in vain.
Zongzheng Mingzhu?
Hello, you two.
How have you been?
Weren't you in prison?
I need to thank you.
If you hadn't meddled in Yu City
and framed me,
I'd still have been
an idle young master.
I would have never had the chance
to be the commander of the Supervision Bureau.
Everyone.
Don't panic.
Although I’m part of the martial world,
I once contributed to the court.
That's why I managed to get the help
of the Supervision Bureau and  Lord Zongzheng.
Arrest him!
Let's see who dares!
Who are you to arrest him?
Li Lianhua
is a con artist.
And murders happened everywhere he went.
He is very suspicious.
I think he's the one
blackmailing Master Jin.
Lord Zongzheng,
you're getting a little personal here.
I was always at the place of murder
because I was traveling with Detective Fang.
And I found the truth every time.
However,
the murderer took a turn
and cleared his name.
It's really interesting.
You...
The Supervision Bureau can only ask
about matters related to the court.
Li Lianhua is innocent.
He never gets involved with the court.
What does he have to do with the Supervision Bureau?
Don't you even care about the rule
set by the court and the martial world?
Okay.
I can't control Baichuan Court.
But this is Master Jin's villa.
Should we keep these
suspicious people here?
Master Jin.
Think carefully.
Forget it.
Stop arguing.
Fang Duobing.
The Supervision Bureau is deliberately against me.
Then I can only leave.
Although you, the young master of the Tianji Hall,
have some invincible mechanics,
it's all useless now.
Everyone.
See you.
Wait.
I think there must be some misunderstanding
between the two of you and Lord Zongzheng.
Since you are all my guests,
how can I neglect any of you?
Why don't you get along for now for my sake?
Harmony brings wealth, after all.
Actually, I've already prepared a banquet.
It's waiting for everyone to take a seat.
Lord Zongzheng,
what do you think?
[Yuanbao Villa]
Thank you for your hospitality.
You're welcome.
You said you wanted to talk to me.
Is it about setting up the mechanics?
Master Jin.
With my help,
I guarantee that not even a fly
can enter your room.
Outsiders can't harm you for sure.
Thank you, Young Master Fang.
It's my pleasure.
But I have a request.
Master Jin,
I want to borrow your opal skull.
What?
You want my opal skull?
This...
Master Jin.
Here's the thing.
We want to use the opal skull
for healing purposes.
It will be returned on the spot.
About borrowing...
Master Jin,
if it's not convenient,
we can leave now.
Goodbye.
Wait.
The opal skull is the treasure of my villa.
Since you want to borrow it,
you must show some sincerity.
If you can find the person
who intends to harm me,
borrowing the opal skull
will be no problem.
The mechanism is ready.
Master Jin.
This way.
This is the Thousand Bell Formation.
The only key to activating and deactivating
the formation is here in this room.
The formation has been activated.
As long as someone approaches this room,
they will be trapped by the sharp threads,
and the whole villa will be promptly informed.
This...
Someone broke into the formation so soon?
You are...
This is my goddaughter Zhiyu.
Godfather, I...
I was just passing by.
I didn't expect you to have guests here.
She is only 18
and rarely meets outsiders.
So, she's afraid of strangers.
Sorry for the confusion.
Go back now.
There is a formation here.
You can only enter with my permission from now on.
You may leave.
Let me untie you.
Your daughter is sick
and very weak.
She was born weak.
I've asked a physician to treat her.
I shan't bother you with it.
We'll talk about the opal skull after you have
captured the person who intends to harm me.
Master Jin.
He locked us out as soon as
I set up the formation for him.
It seems that I was too honest.
There are so many people guarding the Yuanbao Villa.
Now Zongzheng Mingzhu is here too.
If we want the opal skull,
we must help Jin Mantang with this matter.
Mr. Jian.
Gentlemen.
So you live in this room.
I didn't expect
you to love flowers too.
I just like to use flowers as medicine.
You are also an expert in medicine.
You should know the value of these flowers.
Of course.
For example,
I often use this to relieve pain and bruises.
You mean the gelsemium?
The gelsemium is also called heartbreak grass.
How can it be consumed?
I brought it by accident
when I was picking coltsfoot.
I was about to throw it away.
I see.
All things in this world mutually reinforce and neutralize each other.
If I remembered correctly,
there should be a grass called
the smiling Guanyin.
Yes, that's right.
It can adjust the poison of the gelsemium
and maintain its medicinal value.
It works well after taking it.
Do you remember it?
I just remembered
we have something to do.
Mr. Jian,
we won't bother you any longer.
Go ahead.
Look at you.
You are quite bold.
You were boasting in front of an expert.
Aren't you afraid of being exposed?
I'm pretty thickskinned.
I'm not afraid.
You're full of nonsense.
Also, you lied and said I shouldn't make a sound.
So I pretended to be mute on our way here.
I didn't get even with you on that yet.
Silence is gold.
None of that excuse!
Don't think I can forgive you
just by getting the opal skull for me.
Listen.
Today, I...
I...
What's going on?
What happened?
What did you do?
I told you to keep your voice down.
The Gang Qi in your body has blocked your mute acupoint.
Sit down and use the magic I taught you.
Hurry. Sit down.
Although it's temporarily suppressed,
if you accidentally
trigger the Gang Qi again,
you might be killed.
Stop being so arrogant.
It has reached the Bailuo acupoint.
We don't have much time left.
We have to complete Jin Mantang's request as soon as possible.
[Yuanbao Villa]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
Life is like a treacherous journey.
I'm just a traveler.
I'm cured.
It's better not to talk.
What do you mean?
I mean,
don't be so excited.
If you get excited,
the Gang Qi will rise again.
When it rises,
you'll become mute again.
Don't worry.
This damn Di Feisheng.
When I've treated this Gang Qi,
I'll take him back to Baichuan Court myself.
Master!
Let's go.
What happened?
Master hasn’t come out.
The Thousand Bell Formation is still activated.
Master Jin should be inside.
Master Jin,
please deactivate the Thousand Bell Formation.
What happened?
The doors and windows are closed.
We've been shouting for a long time,
but nothing happened.
Fang Duobing.
Break the formation.
Let's go inside and have a look.
Okay.
[Good virtue carries good fortune]
The mechanism is unlocked.
It's finally unlocked. That's great.
Yes.
Master Jin.
Where is Jin Mantang?
Master?
Master!
The doors and windows are locked from inside.
How did he get out?
Since the doors and windows are locked,
and the Thousand Bell Formation was activated,
it's impossible for Jin Mantang to leave the room.
Housekeeper Jin.
Where is the secret room?
Secret room?
I have never heard of that.
Master Jin
is a generous spender.
Why would he keep a comb with broken teeth?
I think...
This is the key.
Master!
Physicians.
Hurry! Save my master!
Save my master!
Master!
Master, what happened to you?
Master, wake up!
Look.
It's Dong Ling.
Dong Ling, the Jinling Sword?
That's right.
It's him.
Why is he here?
He was strangled to death.
He wasn't poisoned.
There are no other wounds.
The arrow is poisonous.
Let me test it.
It's the withered agave.
The poison of the withered agave
can cause nausea, suffocation,
and paralysis in the limbs.
But Dong Ling actually suffered a blunt injury to the back of his head
and died from excessive bleeding.
Could it be that Dong Ling was poisoned
and couldn't control his body,
so he hit the back of his head and died?
It seems so.
Was he the one who threatened Jin Mantang?
But...
Dong Ling the Jinling Sword had always been
a respectable figure in the martial world.
I've never heard of any conflict
between him and Jin Mantang either.
He doesn't look like a blackmailer.
Strange.
Did Dong Ling usually wrap himself up like this?
It's summer,
but he's wearing gloves?
Li Lianhua.
Look.
It's Tree Man Syndrome.
What's that?
It's a very rare disease.
The patient's skin
will gradually become like tree bark.
When the disease becomes severe,
the patient will be like a tree trunk
and develop root-like tumors.
The patient will look like a monster.
It's hard to cure.
The patient tends to die from pain.
The opal skull.
The opal skull is missing!
The opal skull is missing...
It seems that we found out why
Dong Ling came to the Villa.
Stop pretending.
Rumor has it that the opal skull can cure all diseases
and grant longevity.
It's hidden in this villa.
Everyone knows it.
I don't believe that the
famous physicians here
were never curious about the opal skull.
So Dong Ling came to borrow the opal skull
to cure his Tree Man Syndrome.
That's right.
Why don't you ask Housekeeper Jin?
Housekeeper Jin has never been in the martial world.
How did you recognize Dong Ling at first sight?
Yes.
I know him.
I could recognize him even if he turned into ashes.
Half a month ago,
Dong Ling came to see my master.
I listened to them from afar
and heard him asking for the opal skull.
What is an opal skull?
It's an extremely rare treasure.
I've only seen it a few times in my life.
How can he possibly have it?
Why don't we discuss it again?
-Cut the crap.
-No, no, no.
No.
Don't get me wrong.
What happened next?
A few days later,
Dong Ling took his Jinling Sword
and threatened us.
My poor master
had no choice.
So he hurt him with a sleeve arrow
and kicked him out.
Sleeve arrow?
That one just now?
Yes.
That's Master's self-defense weapon.
Then it's clear what happened.
Dong Ling failed to acquire the opal skull.
So he planned to steal it from the secret room.
But he was found out by Jin Mantang.
Dong Ling was highly skilled and strangled Jin Mantang to death.
While Jin Mantang was struggling,
he shot a poisoned sleeve arrow.
Both the witnesses and evidence are present.
The case is closed.
Guards.
Take the bodies out.
Yes.
Master.
From now on,
Yuanbao Villa will be handled by the Supervision Bureau.
Get rid of the rest of them.
This is not your home.
Why should I listen to you?
Master Jin asked for the court's help first.
It's only natural for the Supervision Bureau to handle this.
Take him away.
Wait.
No one here can leave.
Otherwise,
what will you do when the murderer escapes?
Dong Ling is dead.
Where else will we find the murderer?
Since it's a treasure robbery,
and both of them are dead,
let me ask you.
Where is the opal skull?
Don't forget.
The box was empty.
Did the content of the box
run away on its own?
Unless there is another explanation.
There was another person present.
The third person is the murderer.
The doors and windows are locked from the inside.
Young Master Fang's Thousand Bell Formation was active as well.
If there really were someone else,
how did he get out?
Commander Zongzheng is truly ahead of wisdom.
He won't understand that.
Let me translate it for you.
He's calling you stupid.
There are so many locked-room murders.
Don't forget.
The body of Yu Qiushuang that you innocently killed
was found in a place that didn't make sense too.
Don't be angry.
Besides,
don't you think something is strange?
What is it?
Shoes.
Shoes?
Jin Mantang's shoes.
He only wore one shoe.
He must have dropped a shoe
in the midst of their fight.
What's so strange about that?
Jin Mantang
wore riding boots, not low-cut boots.
As you all know,
riding boots are hard to put on.
How could it fall from a fight?
Besides,
if Jin Mantang was strangled by Dong Ling,
he shot the sleeve arrow with his last breath,
and Dong Ling died from dodging the arrow,
that proves that both of them died at the same time.
I really want to ask you.
Who took off
Jin Mantang's other shoe?
Well...
I know.
There must be someone else
searching for the key to the secret room.
That's why he searched Jin Mantang's body.
That's right.
Housekeeper Jin.
May I ask,
when did your master
return to his room last night?
I remember
it was at 7 p.m.
I sent Master back to his room to rest
and saw him activate the Thousand Bell Formation.
There was no one else in the room.
That’s strange.
I set the Thousand Bell Formation myself.
How did Dong Ling and this third person
go in and out of the room?
Look.
There are still many doubts to be addressed.
I'm afraid you need to find out more, Lord Zongzheng.
In this case,
we must find out the truth
to bring justice to the two victims.
[Yuanbao Villa]
Since there are still doubts,
let's talk about it.
I do have a question.
I heard that the owner of Lotus Tower
may have extraordinary medical skills,
but he never takes the initiative to treat patients.
As long as he has more than 50 taels of silver, he would never open business.
But why were you so eager to answer
the recruitment at the YuanBao Villa?
I happen to have less than 50 tales with me.
The Young Master Fang beside you
has erratic moments of muteness.
It's obviously caused by a fatal wave of Gang Qi.
I'm afraid you're also here
for the opal skull, just like Dong Ling.
Yes.
That's our intention.
But don't forget.
We refuted the silly theory
of the two killing each other.
Are we stupid enough to corner ourselves?
Who knows?
Maybe the two of you
hid the opal skull
somewhere in the villa after committing the crime.
Because I suddenly wanted to kick you out,
you found an excuse to stay
to retrieve the treasure later.
What you said
makes sense.
I
can't refute that.
Then, tell me
about your whereabouts last night.
Last night,
we were in our room
and never left.
We can testify for each other.
You two colluded with each other.
Your testimony doesn't count.
Besides, the bells outside Jin Mantang's room
were set by you.
If you wanted to go out,
the formation would naturally be silent.
You two are the most suspicious.
You...
Calm down.
Think about the Gang Qi.
I'm so angry.
Lord Zongzheng.
Speaking of suspicion,
what about yesterday?
Why did you avoid everyone
[Blessings and Prosperity]
and secretly met with Master Jin?
If I'm not mistaken,
you two
had a big conflict.
It's just some official matters.
What?
Do I have to explain to you?
No need.
However,
will you kill him
because of these official duties?
You...
Now that you mentioned it,
I remember something too.
Last night, I saw Physician Guan
sneaking out of his room with a bag in his hands.
I wonder what he was up to.
Me?
What's wrong with me going out?
If we're really talking about this,
I saw Mr. Gongyang
stalking Miss Zhiyu last night.
I just saw Miss Zhiyu leaving Housekeeper Jin's room
in the middle of the night.
I found it suspicious.
I just asked Zhiyu
to handle everyone's meals.
Mr. Jian.
You said you saw Guan going out in the middle of the night.
How did you know?
Were you just coincidentally
admiring the moon that night?
After listening for so long,
I finally understand.
Everyone here
has a little secret.
No use for pointless talking.
Since everyone is suspicious,
we'll just have to search the whole villa.
If the opal skull is found in one of your rooms,
the case will naturally be solved.
Yes.
Let's go somewhere else.
I think Zongzheng Mingzhu
is deliberately perfunctory
to close the case as soon as possible.
What is he trying to do?
Why does he have to get involved in the case of Yuanbao Villa?
He's certainly not here to investigate the case.
He is going to search the entire Yuanbao Villa.
Did he quarrel with Jin Mantang
because he wanted the opal skull as well?
Back in Yu City, I found that
the Jinyuan Alliance had something to do with him.
Could it be that the Jinyuan Alliance wants it?
But according to what you said,
would he be the murderer?
But with his intelligence,
he couldn't have entered my Thousand Bell Formation.
Give me the bag.
Otherwise, don't blame me for being rude.
Don't you dare!
I told you not to search!
What happened?
He won't let us search the bag.
Guan,
everyone in this villa has been searched.
Why can't you be searched?
If you are innocent,
just show it to others.
Guan,
can I have a look at this bag?
Everyone,
there's nothing hard in this bag.
You can rest assured now.
Let's go.
Li Lianhua.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
What's going on?
Why do you always side with him?
I'm helping you
so you won't be embarrassed.
Physician Li,
may I have a word with you?
Li Lianhua, may I have a word with you?
Let me show you something good.