[English subtitles are available]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
[Episode 25]
I've been out for so long this time.
Father must be worried about me.
The Supervision Bureau will escort me back to the palace.
Farewell, your Highness.
You're in such a hurry to bid me farewell.
Do you take me for a plague?
But you said you were leaving.
Is your brain only good for solving cases?
All right, I'm leaving now.
Don't worry about running away from the wedding.
I will go back and beg for leniency for you.
Your Highness, you're very understanding.
Thank you so much.
What are you thanking me for?
It doesn't matter how soon or how late we hold the wedding.
It's the same if we get married after you're done
roaming the martial world.
We're just delaying the wedding?
What else?
After all, it's a marriage bestowed by my father.
We can't rush it either.
You may be a little dumb,
but you are kind.
You'll make a good husband.
Well,
be careful.
Don't let others worry about you.
I'm leaving.
Farewell, your Highness.
[Huansha Pavilion]
Why do you look so troubled?
The princess is so righteous and brave.
Marrying her is a blessing no one else can get.
I'm in big trouble now.
I escaped all the way to Fragrant Mountain, but I got caught anyway.
I think
it's good for you to go home.
The martial world is filled with
bad blood and sinister schemes.
It's better to be a carefree consort.
Li Lianhua.
Can you stop saying that?
Thank you for your kindness.
The princess pardoned all of you.
We just handled the case.
We have no merit to claim.
We did consider keeping the gold bricks in secret.
If you hadn't reminded us,
we would have fallen into the hands of the villains.
We'll ask Baichuan Court and Supervision Bureau
to compensate everyone with the treasures
confiscated from Yu Louchun.
It's enough to live a comfortable life.
If the two of you visit Chehu in the future,
be sure to let us know.
We will meet you with our best hospitality.
It's not easy for you to reunite after so many years.
Go back and live a good life.
Make lots of money.
So that when we visit and eat to our heart's content,
you won't go bankrupt.
Deal.
When I heard that Physician Li can bring the dead back to life,
I thought it was a joke.
But after the events over the past two days,
I really admire you.
This is the medicinal wine I've been keeping for years.
Your body seems weak,
so I wanted to give it to you.
When we meet again,
let's drink till we're drunk.
Thank you, Lu.
I'm not leaving. Yes.
I won't leave. I can't leave.
I can't leave.
I won't leave.
The Girls' Mansion is a murder scene.
It will be sealed soon.
You must depart to Baichuan Court immediately.
My Lord.
We can't go.
We'll die if we leave.
We can't leave. Yes.
Lord Yang.
The guards refuse to leave
because they have been poisoned.
-Yes.
-Can you give me half a day
to find the antidote for them?
Okay.
Lock them here for now.
We'll seal the Girls' Mansion in the afternoon.
Yes.
Can he really cure us?
Then we can leave here.
Yes.
That's right.
Yes
The Nanyin people left their hometown.
But they must need a place to worship their ancestors.
We've found
Jin Mantang's ancestral hall.
But we've never seen Yu Louchun's ancestral hall.
I think the formula for the antidote
should be in the same place as the ancestral hall.
Mr. Fang,
can I have a word with you?
-Go ahead.
-I’m sorry.
I'll look into the ancestral hall.
Let's go there.
Mr. Fang,
are you the nephew of Shan Gudao?
Yes.
That's good.
Thank you for saving me from Li Yufu's
thundering fire bombs
just now.
But I have a favor to ask.
Please help me.
Go ahead.
Many years ago,
Shan Gudao once brought a piece of cloud iron
to the Weapon Valley.
He said he wanted to make himself an armor piece
and a sword for Li Xiangyi.
But he died in the battle against the Jinyuan Alliance.
It doesn't make sense.
Why?
Mr. Fang, you don’t know.
Cloud iron is both the toughest and softest material to exist.
The Weapon Valley had only ever seen
Shan Gudao with such a material once in a hundred years.
The armor forged from cloud iron
can only be penetrated by
Li Xiangyi's Wenjing Sword,
which was also made from cloud iron.
I saw my father forge it with my own two eyes.
There's no doubting it.
So I wanted to ask you
if Shan Gudao was wearing the armor
when he died.
This...
Only Li Xiangyi's Wenjing Sword
can penetrate Shan Gudao's armor.
Isn't it just like what they said at the Sigu Tea Party?
The death of Shan Gudao is very strange indeed.
My father held a grudge
over this matter for years.
That’s why I came to ask you.
He wasn't wearing
the armor.
I see.
Great!
Great.
I’ll take my leave.
If you do visit me in the Weapon Valley in the future,
I’ll compose ten poems for you.
Goodbye.
The armor was indeed on my father's body.
But a hole was pierced into it by a sword.
What the hell is going on here?
Fang Xiaobao.
Why are you spacing out?
Let's go. I found the ancestral hall.
I asked Xifei.
There should be a Yingyue Pavilion
near the Guanri Pavilion.
It's just a pavilion.
Why didn't Yu Louchun allow
anyone near it for the past few years?
All these years,
Xifei has only seen one guest,
Jin Mantang.
What's on your mind?
The fog here is so heavy,
it's exactly the same as the fog at the Yipin Tomb.
If my guess is right,
the key
should be this tree.
I did it.
Let's go.
Li Lianhua!
Fei!
At least you have a conscience.
The trick of this mechanism is the stone walls on both sides.
Think of a way to push them back.
Why don't you think of a way?
Yangzhouman?
I'm exhausted.
Your inner power is Yangzhouman?
I'm very familiar with inner powers.
Where did you learn it from?
Tell me,
what's the name of this technique?
Oh, it's an amazing one.
It's as powerful as Yangzhouman,
called Suzhoukuai.
This is not Yangzhouman.
It's called Suzhoukuai, understand?
I’ll teach you next time.
What are you waiting for?
Find Li Lianhua.
What happened to the two of you?
What took you so long?
Everything is here.
I found them.
Young master, here.
This is the formula for the antidote.
Take it.
Take a good look.
This is Yu Louchun's ledger from ten years ago.
I've checked all these ledgers.
Ten years ago,
Yu Louchun
rarely invited people to the Girls' Mansion.
Apart from Jin Mantang,
there were only two other people.
One of them was Four-faced Qingzun from the Jinyuan Alliance.
The other was the Lord of the Netherworld.
I think these two are descendants of Nanyin.
Four-faced Qingzun and Jinyuan Alliance?
Oh, right.
It's also a famous sect in the martial world.
It’s no surprise if you've heard of it before.
But the Four-faced Qingzun
had long died
in Prison 188,
which is your territory.
The only clue left
is this Lord of the Netherworld.
See?
I'm still the best.
Fang Xiaobao.
Why are you spacing out?
I'm not.
I just think
it's good to have a smart friend like you.
That's right.
Let's go.
You two nearly scared me to death.
Hurry up.
This is the prescription.
Please find a physician
to make an antidote for the guards.
Don’t worry, Mr. Fang.
Will you report back to Sigu Sect with us?
I have something important to do.
Please help me
report back instead, Sister Shi.
What are the Jinyuan Alliance and Nanyin up to?
If you've changed your mind,
it's not too late.
Maybe Baichuan Court
can reduce your punishment.
Fine.
You're on your own.
If it's really him,
how could he be hurt by Li Yifu?
He brought it on himself.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
He was right behind you just now.
You really didn't notice?
No.
Luckily you came in time.
That really scared me.
Check it out for me.
How is it?
Is it serious? Any marks?
Stop messing around.
Miss Shi,
shall we proceed to the
local government office
and count the confiscated goods?
Let's go.
It's time to move.
Let's find the Lord of the Netherworld.
Why are we avoiding the Baichuan Court?
That's because you've done a lot of evil in the martial world.
If someone finds out,
it'll be a big trouble.
Am I really wrong?
How could Li Lianhua be Li Xiangyi?
But...
What about the Yangzhouman?
Di Feisheng.
Li Xiangyi.
No.
I have to get to the bottom of this.
What are you doing?
Here.
Have a drink on me.
A celebration for
solving the big Girls' Mansion case.
You're treating me with my wine?
You're so eloquent.
I just want to drink and
chat with you, can't I?
What do you want to chat about?
How about why you know Yangzhouman?
What Yangzhouman? You're so full of strange words.
Stop pretending.
It's the inner skill mental factor you taught me.
Let me tell you.
I rarely offer to let bygones be bygones.
Think before you answer.
If you're really hiding something from me,
you'd better tell me everything today.
You mean the mental factor?
I remember it now.
What did I tell you back in that cave?
Can you stop talking nonsense?
There can't be so many coincidences at once.
Do you take this for writing a novel?
Let me ask you.
You know Yangzhouman,
and you appeared in Yuanbao Villa at the same time
as that mysterious swordsman in white.
You...
Are you Li Xiangyi?
Li Xiangyi? How's that possible?
Fang Xiaobao.
If I were Li Xiangyi,
how could Fo, Bi, Bai, and Shi not have recognized me?
Besides,
I asked you to practice every day,
but you only think about this nonsense.
What?
You don't trust me?
Do you know that
my father had impenetrable armor
forged from cloud iron?
Cloud Iron?
Junior.
It's your first time leaving the mountains for training.
The He family of Changma Blade Sect
was besieged by the Dongling Three Gang.
It'll be dangerous.
You should not take the risk.
My Shaoshi Sword is meant for
upholding fairness and justice.
The Changma Blade Sect has long retired.
The Dongling Three Gang claims to be eliminating bandits,
but they are actually coveting the He family's cloud iron.
I must interfere with this matter.
Father.
Father!
Wake up, Father.
Master He.
Here.
Gentlemen,
I beg of you.
Send my son to his grandfather's place in Luoyang.
Don't worry.
-We will...
-Junior.
I heard that the He family owns the
cloud iron, a material that is both tough and soft.
Heroes,
as long as my son arrives safely,
he will tell you the whereabouts of the cloud iron.
There is no need.
A hero does not
take advantage of others.
I'm just worried that it might fall into the wrong hands.
That's why I asked.
Master He, don't worry.
We will send your son
to your grandfather's home safely.
Senior.
You asked me to assist you outside the city that day.
You escorted the kid to Luoyang alone.
Did you personally send him to his grandfather's house?
Then why did he still die outside of Luoyang City?
Really?
Of course I sent him
to his grandfather's house.
The He family of Changma Blade Sect committed a lot of evil deeds.
It must be their enemies seeking revenge
and wanting to get rid of him.
How unfortunate.
Everything has its own cause and effect.
We've tried our best.
Did Senior still acquire the cloud iron in the end?
No.
He's definitely not that kind of person.
It's just a random guess.
How can I ruin his image
in Fang Duobing’s mind.
Why are you spacing out?
You haven't answered me.
There's nothing impenetrable in this world.
Someone must have made it up.
It's a lie.
Okay.
If you say there isn't,
then that must be the case.
I'm going to check on that Fox Spirit.
Fox Spirit.
Time to eat.
Li Lianhua.
You lied again.
If you had only stumbled upon the Yangzhouman,
you wouldn't have used it so well.
Listen here now.
Don't you think
your words are meaningless?
You don't even remember your own things.
What do you know about Yangzhouman?
I just don't get it.
You obviously lied to him.
But you don't seem to want to harm him.
Tell me something about myself
and I won't tell him that you lied to him.
Hurry up.
Okay.
I'll tell you something about you.
You died once ten years ago.
Died once? What do you mean?
That's the second question.
You'll have to pay if you keep asking.
Li Lianhua.
Li Lianhua!
[Shishou Village]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
[Tianyun Restaurant]
What do you think is the relationship between
the Jinyuan Alliance and Nanyin?
They tried several times to acquire the Rama Heavenly Ice.
The searing karmic fire
and those Suiyan marks of revenge.
I'm afraid the Nanyin people want to make a comeback.
If so,
we have to get the Rama Heavenly Ice
before Jiao Liqiao does.
Why isn't Su Xiaoyong here yet?
I wonder if she has found
the whereabouts of the Lord of the Netherworld.
There's nothing I can't find out in this world.
The Shishou Village.
My grandfather told me.
Lian Quan, Lord of the Netherworld,
was last seen in this place.
The Shishou Village.
It is said that Shishou Village was famous for
its Rouchang wine, which can enhance one's inner power.
Back then, many people in the martial world went there for the wine.
Rouchang wine.
I may have heard of this legend before.
Was the Lord of the Netherworld also seeking the Rouchang wine?
My grandpa looked into it.
Apparently, the Lord of the Netherworld
had a serious internal injury once.
If Rouchang wine can increase his inner power,
it's possible for him to go to Shishou Village.
But that happened more than ten years ago.
That village
was apparently flooded
by the rerouted river.
It should still be in the same spot on the map,
but I don't know if
you'll be able to find it.
Thank you, Miss Su.
We'll set off now.
See you.
-I’ll go with you.
-No need.
You!
Miss Su.
I'm afraid it's a dangerous trip.
Fei didn't want you to be in danger.
So he pressed your acupoints.
It will be unlocked in two hours.
I didn't think that.
It’s noisy enough having Young Master Fang around.
Shut up!
It's Fei's treat.
Eat more.
Fang Duobing!
Li Lianhua!
Come back!
They left me alone again.
[Traceless Wind and Cloud]
Saintess.
Li Yixi failed.
Yu Louchun's Rama Heavenly Ice
was intercepted by Li Lianhua and Fang Duobing.
Li Lianhua and Fang Duobing again.
Why are they always against me?
Where are they now?
According to the spy,
they seem to have gone to Mount Chrysanthemum.
Mount Chrysanthemum?
Snow Master. Granny Blood.
Saintess.
Go to Mount Chrysanthemum
and behead Li Lianhua and Fang Duobing.
Skin them while you're at it
and bring me the Rama Heavenly Ice.
Yes.
This Li Lianhua
is always getting in my way.
We can't keep such a nuisance alive.
Mount Chrysanthemum is Feng Qing's territory.
I'll wait for your good news there.
Go now.
We've been circling around Mount Chrysanthemum for so many times.
We haven't even seen a village.
No wonder
they said Shishou Village is a mysterious village.
Could it be that we're not destined to find it?
I don't know if it's destiny.
But we seem to be lost.
Lost?
Are you kidding me?
I've never been lost since I was six.
Even in the desert,
I could find my way.
We're already lost.
Stop bragging.
Let's go. Hurry up.
[Bahuang Hunyuan Lake]
Bahuang Hunyuan Lake.
Since there's a boundary stone here,
there should be someone nearby.
I'll wash my face by the lake.
Come and have a look.
I just wanted to wash my face.
But why are there skulls in the water?
It's the reflection of the strange stones.
Move!
Who are you?
Can't I wash my face in peace?
We're the ones who will kill you.
Windy Poplar?
My Lord.
Who are you? Why are you calling me your lord?
Don't you recognize me?
I'm your subordinate, Snow Master.
You are the director of the Jinyuan Alliance.
The Jinyuan Alliance. Director.
Let's go!
Are you okay?
I'm fine. How are you?
I'm fine.
What is this place?
Looks like
we've rounded to the back of the mountain.
Let's go.
Let's go over there.
Out of the woods, another village.
It's truly destined.
You were staring at that lake for a long time.
You must have long noticed that
something was under the lake, right?
Fei, what's wrong?
The Wuxin Huai poison is spreading throughout his body.
Use your power to suppress it for him.
I...
Why should I save this villain?
Hurry up.
Fine.
I can't let you die
before I take you to Baichuan Court.
Why is this small village so quiet?
Are you feeling better?
The Jinyuan Alliance. My Lord.
What do they mean?
You mentioned these words before.
You must know something.
Why do I have a headache whenever I think of it?
Well,
about the Jinyuan Alliance.
You really were
the evil leader of the Jinyuan Alliance.
You were their lord.
However,
you've turned over a new leaf.
You are no longer on their side.
That's why they poisoned you.
What's wrong?
Your words can never be fully trusted.
But I can't completely disregard them either.
Listen.
-I’m not lying.
-Let's enter the village.
Li Lianhua.
How long do you think we can
keep lying to him like this?
But if he regains his memory,
he might be able to figure out
what happened in the Jinyuan Alliance.
I have something
to ask him too.
Is it about your father?
If he regains his memory,
do you think he'll be a friend or foe?
[Shishou Village]
Shishou Village?
This is the legendary paradise?
Maybe it's not paradise season yet.
Right?
But this village is so hidden.
Did the Lord of the Netherworld really come here?
It's been so many years.
It's not easy to find someone.
It's not dark yet.
Why is there no one outside?
Kid.
Excuse me.
It's getting dark.
I told you not to run around.
The villagers are strange.
They seem to be avoiding something.
Wasn't this place known for its Rouchang wine,
and many martial artists came here for it?
Why is it in this state instead?
This place is indeed strange.
It's getting late.
Let's find an inn first.
Let's go.
[Yuquan Inn]
It seems
no one has lived here for a long time.
This village is so desolate.
But they built an inn here.
Who is it for?
Maybe it was quite lively a few years ago.
Don't forget.
Many martial artists
came here for the Rouchang wine.
Let's go in.
What is this?
Don't you think
there's a strange smell here?
What smell?
The smell of the dead.
It's all blood.
You're right.
The marks here are short and messy.
They weren't caused by swords or blades.
It's more like
someone tore into them with bare hands.
The blood splattered very fast.
I'm afraid the victim won't survive.
Look.
Be careful.
This way.
Someone hanged to death here.
Since they have retrieved the body,
why didn't they remove the cloth
and the bench on the ground?
At night, the ghost emerged from the fourth room.
It peeped into my window.
I am terrified.
I wish you were here.
It's a suicide note.
This is left by a woman.
Before her husband returned,
she encountered something terrible.
It forced her to hang herself.
She said a ghost entered through the window.
The main hall does have a lot of
bamboo tags with ghost characters on them.
Is this another haunted inn?
Don't you think it's strange?
There's the sound of wind outside,
but the wind can't get in.
It's as if someone is blocking the wind.
It's a ghost.
The ghost blocked the wind for you.
Are you done?
Fine.
Let's go our separate ways.
Did you find anything?
There are signs of a
serious battle in the room.
But the bodies are all gone.
It's like everyone disappeared
at the same time one day.
How did we get in here?
There's a door.
You're right.
What is it?
This severed hand was ripped off.
Judging from the decay,
it should be less than four to five days.
That means
this ghost is still killing.
Why are you looking at me?
Think about it.
We've been in the inn for so long.
Maybe we're already being targeted.
If we don't leave this inn now,
we'll be in danger.
Look. On the doorframe.
Looks like this hand
had an insane grip.
If not for the traces of martial arts,
I would have thought that the people here
were torn apart by a vicious tiger.
The pillar was broken like this.
I'm afraid this beast
was no match for the owner of this severed hand either.
They even managed to
split such a tough copper censer.
This was split open in one strike.
The person must have been quite skilled.
But they are still inferior to me.
Why are you looking at me?
The sword mark split the copper censer from the center.
But the sword tilted left by three points.
This seems to be a move from Zhaoyue Sect.
Also,
the fingerprints and the palm print on the doorframe
were also made by people.
The finger strength was strong enough to dent a hard surface.
There are also claw marks on each side.
This is the outer martial arts of the Kunlun Sect.
Identifying the moves and sects only through the marks...
Only those who are skilled in martial arts can do that.
Li Lianhua.
Who are you?
Zhaoyue here,
Kunlun there.
Looks like a bunch of skilled martial artists
really did fight here.
If it really was a fight between martial artists,
why are there so many
beast marks here?
Fang Xiaobao,
have you heard of
any sect in the martial world
that specializes in taming beasts?
What are you doing?
Why are you spacing out at night?
I've never heard of it.
You're right.
Where did these people go?
Whether they won or lost the fight,
they had to leave after fighting.
They might have left after the fight,
but this is an inn.
It has been deserted all these years.
Is there no one here to clean this up?
So many people died here,
and there are so many talismans downstairs.
Maybe no one dared to come in
because this place is haunted.