Good evening.
To those who just arrived, I am Timmy.
The most beautiful creature
in this school.
And next to me is, Miguel.
The most...
You guys decide!
Oh, really?
Anyway,
welcome to "Songs for Maria!"
- (See you tomorrow, 7pm. I won't be late.)
- (See you tomorrow.)
A concert for our beloved...
(Where are you na?)
Sis! You ready? It's almost 7pm!
We have to start on time
because Pim has to be
somewhere right after.
Can we wait? It's still early...
Sis. Ready or not, it's on.
Doesn't he have basketball practice?
No. Last night he promised he'd show up.
Promises! Promises! You flirts!
Two minutes but if he's
not here, then he's not here.
He's not worth it.
The shade...
Two minutes!
What are we waiting for?
Nothing, Brother Mike.
We're actually about to start, right?
Yes, yes! Right now.
And now, to start our program,
we'd like to call on our
resident singer-ist,
Dominic, to lead us in a song.
♪ Whatever you want ♪
♪ I will do ♪
♪ Whatever you desire ♪
♪ I will follow ♪
♪ All you have to do is
say when and where ♪
♪ Just call me
and I will be right there ♪
♪ Because I am yours ♪
♪ I am yours ♪
♪ I am yours forevermore ♪
♪ If things get rough
and seem out of reach ♪
♪ With all my heart,
I will face them with you ♪
♪ Because I am yours ♪
♪ I am yours ♪
♪ I am yours forevermore ♪
Go, Dominic!
Dominic! Dominic!
"Love Beneath the Stars"
(Episode 1)
I really thought
you weren't gonna make it.
Actually, me too.
Mr. Oyco's class took forever...
but I told you last night I'd be here.
So... here I am.
Well, I appreciate the effort.
Thank you.
Don't I get a reward?
Dork.
Hey, I think you need to go.
You'll be late to basketball practice.
Can't I stay a little longer?
Luke.
You're an athletic scholar.
You need to attend practice.
Even though I know you don't
want to see Philip and the guys.
Coach Mark will get upset.
Besides we'll see each other
this weekend.
Remember we scheduled with Baby R?
Do we really have to go?
Yes.
Okay, fine.
See you later, Dominic.
See you later, Luke.
So are you guys together?
I think?
Why does it seem like you're unsure?
I don't know. We haven't
really talked about it.
What about Grad Ball?
Is he your date?
I guess? I mean, most likely.
I don't know.
Talk to him! It's hard
to not know where you're at.
It's better to know what you are,
like me and Joseph!
You are so not together!
I know, but at least
we have a mutual understanding!
Don't be jealous, people die of that.
Your finger stinks!
You're just jealous.
You don't have a Joseph.
Whatever.
Fine, he's yours then.
You bet your ass he's mine.
What now, Armada?
Just because the tournament's over,
you're going to be late to training?
Coach, he's lost.
We don't even know if our
friend is straight or not.
Damn you!
Hey! That's enough.
I don't care what you do
outside of training.
Just don't ruin your future.
Remember, college teams haven't
finalized their recruitment.
I'm still lobbying you guys
to the top schools.
So if you want to get into
a team, do better.
Sorry, Coach.
It won't happen again.
I've reviewed the report of Mr. Oyco.
And what happened on Marian
Grounds is unacceptable.
For whatever reason,
violence is not tolerated.
You're parents sent you to a private
Catholic school to be decent gentlemen.
Not goons.
Because Christ was like that.
And you should be, too.
But what's done is done.
And now, here we are.
According to Mr. Oyco,
you'll be suspended for one day.
Mr. Oyco, give them the suspension letter.
You need to have your parents sign that.
You have until next week
to return those to me.
And don't even think about
forging your parent's signatures.
It won't end well for you.
D!
Gio?
Who else would it be?
D, wait!
Stop talking, we're in the library.
Just wait.
What is it that you want?
Why are you mad? Can't we just talk?
I don't know with you.
You were the one who left, remember?
Past is past.
You talk as if something happened
between us.
Hey. I'm kidding, D!
[Dominic]
What is it that you want?
I want to ask you to head the
decorations committee of our Grad Ball.
And be with you every day? Forget it.
Are you that grossed out by me, D?
Seriously.
I'm asking not as your childhood friend
but as your student body president.
I really need your skills
for the Grad Ball.
We all know you're the best
with decorations.
It's an extracurricular
and plus points
for your college applications!
I'm sure Aunt Faye would approve.
I'll think about it.
That's not a no.
Meeting is next week.
I'll text the details.
I didn't say yes.
What? You were suspended before?
Yeah, for cheating on my homework.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Mr. Tomas was being an ass.
We were behind so we copied off
someone's homework.
Me, Philip and Andoy.
The usual.
You guys are really close, huh?
Yeah,
like brothers.
Sorry.
Sorry for what?
You fought because of me.
You don't have to say sorry.
It's not your fault,
they're so close-minded.
I guess...
Still, I hope things work out in the end.
Maybe after Grad Ball.
Speaking of Grad Ball.
What's the plan?
Are we going together?
Of course!
Why would you think otherwise?
I don't know.
We never talked about it after...
you know... the field.
And you haven't done a promposal.
I need a promposal?
Of course!
You might think I'm an easy girl.
I mean, I made such an effort
for Karen's promposal.
Yeah. It's kind of weird now.
Have you spoken to her?
Not yet.
But I will. I promise.
Heads...
I'll talk to her.
Tails...
Maybe another time.
I think this is the right place.
It matches the message.
Are you sure it's the right place?
I think so...
Wait, you still haven't answered
my question.
What are we doing in a resort?
I don't know.
All she said was to come to this address.
Where is she?
Welcome! Welcome!
What are we doing in this place?
This is where I live now.
I'm the in-house fortune-teller
of the Good Fortune
Mountain Beach resort.
Good pay with free housing
and a pool! Bam!
Anyway, is he the guy from the cards?
Yes! Destiny favors you!
So, why are you here?
To show off...
What's your name?
Sorry. It's Luke.
Love it! Luke.
Like "Stop. Luke. Listen."
So, what can I help you with?
Guidance. Since, you know
the cards brought us together.
We just want to know how the cards
will help us stay together?
Is that so?
Perfect, I have a couple's promo!
Jopay, bring out the rope!
What's this?
My ritual. You ready?
Love.
Destiny. Love.
Help us.
Please sit.
Let me repeat myself, because
later on if you break up,
you might come for me.
The cards are merely for guidance.
They may change depending
on the decisions you make.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I will provide you with 3 signs.
These will help strengthen
your relationship.
Do you see this?
This is the card of the King and Fire.
You must be cautious.
Because this first sign
is a warning to you both.
There is a man, the King,
that you must avoid.
Because, like fire, get too close,
you may get burned.
A man that will come between us?
A third party?
Well, look at you?
Assuming a third party already.
May not be a third party.
This could also symbolize
a trait of a person.
It could be you
or Mr. Handsome over here.
Will the cards tell us
when it will happen?
It doesn't say. But it is inevitable.
Here is the second sign.
This is the card of the Sun.
It symbolizes knowledge
or something to be proud of.
Something you will not be ashamed of.
Beside it is the card of the Lovers.
This may mean that you
will be faced with a situation
where you will be proud of each other.
When will that...
The cards do not say when this will be.
Just treasure what you have right now.
Oh my gosh, exciting.
Maybe...
You'll tell your parents about me?
Then you'll invite me over for dinner.
LOL. Never gonna happen.
Why?
My mom would kill me.
No, I'm sure she'd love me.
No. I swear.
"No. I swear."
Stop being so dramatic.
We're not done yet.
Sorry.
Kids these days...
Here is the third sign.
This is the most important sign
for you both.
See this card?
This is "The Fool" card.
There is a man standing on a cliff
this means you both
have a decision to make.
Will you jump into the ravine
or stay where you are.
Next to this is the World card.
This means an important decision
will change both your worlds.
It doesn't say if...
it'll be a positive or negative impact.
Just remember, think long and
hard about your final choice.
Sounds so serious.
Yes. Destiny is no joke.
Actually, I have more questions now.
The promo is over!
I've already given you so much!
(mommy calling...)
Wait, I have to take this. Excuse me.
Fine. What is your question?
Well...
I'm looking for a sign.
If I should talk to her already.
Pull two more cards.
These are the Death and Star cards.
Two very different things
but deeply connected.
When you have closure, only then
can you change and grow.
Whatever it is you're waiting for,
don't wait any longer.
There will never be a "right time."
You just need to do it now.
Did I miss anything?
Nothing.
You did.
Payment.
Hi.
We should really stop meeting like this.
One where you know
someone is going to cry.
Yeah.
I know.
I'm sorry, Karen.
You're in love with someone else.
Who is she?
It's Dominic.
Are you serious?
How?
I don't know how it happened.
But it did.
I'm in love with Dominic.
I really am sorry, Karen.
No.
I still love you, Luke.
Gio, question.
Did you review the list of
people going to the Grad Ball?
Yes, Pim. What about it?
Timmy and Joseph are going together.
Is that acceptable?
Hey Pim, what are you trying to say?
Nothing, I'm just making sure
if it's allowed.
And why wouldn't it be?
We're both stag.
Yeah, but you're still both guys.
OMG. Homophobe.
I can't believe there's
a homophobe in this committee.
I'm not a homophobe, I just
want to clarify the issue.
Guys, relax. Timmy, calm down.
I have seen the list.
There's nothing wrong with
Timmy and Joseph going together.
Besides, there are no rules about that
in the student handbook.
Also, we welcome everyone,
including our friends
from the LGBTQ+ community.
Yes! Gio for best student president ever!
And Pim, don't worry about their dates.
Just worry about yours.
Oh, so you still don't have a date.
I'll hook you up with someone.
You, D? Do you have a date?
Oh wow, code names. Okay, "D."
Cut it out, sis.
Just answer the question.
Do you have a date?
Change topic.
My date is not the point of this meeting.
Well, that's true.
Anyways, that's all for today's meeting.
If you have any questions, just ask.
I'll be around.
- Thanks, guys.
- Thanks, Pres.
Thanks Gio.
D, hold on.
What now, Gio?
Nothing. Just...
wanted to thank you
for being the head
of the decorations committee.
Well, you said it would look
good on my college application.
Oh, I thought you did it for me.
C'mon. Stop it.
We're not kids anymore.
Anyways, I was thinking of signing up
for Journey's next batch.
Are you still active there?
I thought you were an atheist?
Well, I just want to see the hype.
Hype?
It's a religious retreat, not a concert.
I've been thinking about it.
You'll be with me right?
No.
Come on, D.
Can you stop calling me "D."
What the?
What's this?
Well.
You said
you weren't an easy girl.
So...
you deserve this.
♪ Whatever you want ♪
♪ I will do ♪
♪ Whatever you desire ♪
♪ I will follow ♪
♪ All you have to do is
say when and where ♪
♪ Just call me
and I will be right there ♪
♪ Because I am yours ♪
♪ I am yours ♪
♪ I am yours forevermore ♪
♪ Without a shadow of a doubt ♪
♪ I put my trust in you ♪
♪ Wherever you wish to go ♪
♪ I will go with you ♪
♪ And if things get rough
and seem out of reach ♪
♪ With all my heart,
I will face them with you ♪
♪ Because I am yours ♪
♪ I am yours ♪
♪ I am yours forevermore ♪
♪ There is no mountain high enough ♪
♪ Or ocean too deep ♪
♪ That can ever tear us apart ♪
♪ Because I am yours ♪
♪ I am yours ♪
♪ I am yours forevermore ♪
Dominic.
Destiny brought us together.
And I know it wasn't easy but...
It was all worth it.
And I know I may get lost sometimes, but
I just want you to know
that I will always,
always come back to you.
I love you, Dominic.
And I love you, too, Luke.
You know I don't like to assume, so...
Dominic.
Will you go to the Grad Ball with me?
Of course not.
Kidding! Of course!
So there, I said yes!
OMG! Sis! What is this,
an engagement?! "I said, yes!"
But in fairness, kudos to the guitar!
Plus points!
And we even sang together.
Our Queen Petite!
Hi Dominic.
(Next Episode)
I want you to know that I love Luke.
And I'm willing
to fight for him.
You're the only one who
doesn't take me seriously.
I didn't know you guys were close.
You're cute when you get like that.
What do you mean,
"when I get like that"?
When you get jealous.