Look at me.
You look pretty.
Oh, so pretty.
It's all done.
Hey! Stop frowning.
What's with the pout? Stop frowning.
Why do I have to go too?
When I am treating the director to a meal, who will babysit Yeon Soo then?
Your dad says he's too busy and he doesn't care about it. At least you should help if you don't have school.
I can only be in one place at a time.
I have previous engagement today.
With whom?
With a friend.
Push it back.
Does only Yeon Soo's schedule matter? How about my appointment with my friend? How can I reschedule all of a sudden?
You said it's a friend. It's not like you might never meet her again if you don't have time today.
Seriously.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Yeon Soo, don't sit back. Your curled hair will get messed up.
Hey, give me your cell phone.
- Why?
- Hurry.
Go over there.
- Mom, Unni (older sis) is meeting a boy.
- Hey, be quiet.
Don't say anything.
- Mom!
- Do you wish to die?
Hey!
You didn't leave anything behind, right?
If you can't find where to go, look this number. This is the number for the manager who helps Yeon Soo.
Don't get distracted, alright?
- You are going to buy me a cell phone for real, right?
- Just go. You always try to negotiate about everything.
Everyone else have it. It's always me who doesn't have it.
Says who? Should I check to see if everyone else really have a cell phone?
- Even Yeon Soo has it.
-I just give it to her briefly whenever she has a shoot.
Hurry and leave.
Unni, the weather is so nice. Look at the sky.
Multi-Cultural Space, Space Mall
Oh, so pretty. Just like a doll, like a doll.
She's so pretty. Look at her skin. It's like porcelain.
Unni.
Unni, I want to come too.
You can't.
I will just see his face and leave.
Don't follow me. You're going to die if you follow me.
Unni.
What?
It's a dream.
A dream with the same ending regardless of what I do.
Coral Public Bath
Hello.
Please enter.
Open for bathing
Episode 1
So you don't want to work.
I am not saying we won't work.
Please give us at least half of the overdue pay.
You must be full of yourself.
We are saying this since we are not full.
What?
Bastard.
Listen carefully.
You should consider yourselves lucky for being able to work.
It's not like I am not paying you when I have the money.
Look at those piled up containers.
We are not even able to pay the docking fee, so many of them get seized due to nonpayment.
It's difficult for everyone all around.
To share this difficulty, we—
Why do we need to do that?
Who are you to keep interrupting?
Isn't it true? We didn't get to enjoy any of the rewards.
Why are we, the ones who get mistreated, always the ones to share in the financial difficulty?
You, step forward. Please step forward.
This punk, is he out of his mind?
How dare you blabber?
Just do what you're told. Instead of smart mouthing.
Do you understand?
If you understand, get lost. You beggar.
Beggar?
Do you think I am begging for alms now?
This punk.
Aren't you going to let go? Let go. This bastard.
Pay up for my work. This bastard.
Call your mom. We have a customer.
Please pay the entry fee at the hair salon.
Coral Public Bath
Mom.
Mom, get up. We have a customer.
She wants to get a perm. Hurry.
Get up. Get up.
Oh, I am dead tired.
Why in the world
does someone want a perm?
Hyung!
Did you get into another fight? Did you lose?
If my face looks like this, what do you think happened to the other guy?
- He's pretty much dead.
- That's right.
Eat this, Hyung.
It's good.
Hello?
I got it.
Where are you going?
To work.
You don't get paid even if you work. Just play with me.
I can't.
Why not?
I don't have a good mom like you do.
Then let me come too.
Mom said I shouldn't come here. She said it's dangerous here.
Anything you could make money is dangerous. So stop following me.
Oppa, have some fun here. I will treat you well.
- Go home, I said.
I will give you lots of freebies. Come with me.
Answer.
I am leaving. I am.
Go.
Oppa, have some fun here.
Mary &amp; Club
At this size, instead of the building model
CEO.
we have to go with city planning.
Oh, I...
Weren't you supposed to be here next week? You've finished it already?
Did you even check the blueprint?
The blueprint?
Using piloti structure, columns are going to be spaced out every 13 meters?
You can't build it like that.
Are you the architect? Just make it.
Any revision, it's their responsibility.
Once it starts snowing, snow could pile up 30 cm in no time in this area.
Your estimate for roof weight is this low?
What if it snows? The building will collapse.
- Hey!
- What!
Just do it as instructed. Please.
This is only for presentation purpose, anyway.
Fixing mistakes during the inspection
is their responsibility. We just have to
make the models.
- CEO.
What?
- Why?
- Do you want to live in a place like this?
Can you live here with your kids?
Please ask them to change the blueprint.
I will make the models in time no matter what.
That kid, she's really good with her hands.
But she's needlessly picky.
How can I make them break up again?
I wonder why I have to agonize over
these two characters being lovey-dovey with each other.
Aren't you going to make them get back together anyway?
Exactly, that's what I am saying. They are going to get back together but why would they break up? Why?
In other cartoons, people say it's too chaotic since the main character acts as he pleases. But these two,
- they don't budge.
- Why do you need reasons?
Is there a specific reason why people would get together or break up?
Don't you know logical development?
Don't you know that the story has to make sense or it needs to be justifiable?
Forget about all that. You need to draw your main character more beautifully.
Your online cartoon is a romance, but you're being needlessly realistic.
Make the main character a drop-dead beauty.
Then even if it's not logical, everything makes sense.
So are they going to fix the blueprint?
What other work all of a sudden? What's so great about it?
Bio Town?
I don't want to. If they want me to just build a study (practice) model.
How great are the terms that they're offering?
Hey, why isn't she here? She asked me here.
Owner of the store is here.
Give me a glass of ice water.
They have loud and filthy mouths.
You're early.
- Are you alright?
- Of course, I am.
You don't seem to be doing okay though.
It's not anything new.
- Why did you ask me here?
- After putting the work in,
I was about to make good use of her. He beat her up like this.
You've heard that Bio Town will be built in Wooseok-dong, right?
- Where?
- The rumors have been
rampant about developing the area behind the store.
The director of that company brought him here.
He was showing off saying he's the on-site manager and he behaves this way.
Forget about him since we won't be able to get through to him.
Go straight to Director.
Pretend like she's your younger sister.
We have to get some monetary compensation for her to get herself together.
He is looking for you.
Okay.
He will be a handful. Be careful.
I will take 20%.
This is why I like you.
Cheong Yoo Construction
Jeong Yoo Taek
Moon Soo.
I am leaving.
Good bye, Auntie. Thank you for your hard work.
Your mom.
I am leaving.
Stop drinking.
- Why?
- I have a meeting tomorrow.
You have to manage the bath house by yourself tomorrow.
How can I manage it alone?
Do you know how hard it was today, because you weren't here?
That's why you should stop drinking.
And make sure to get the correct amount for the entry fee.
- Like the last time—
- You know what day tomorrow is, right?
People say your child only takes after you in looks but not in thoughts.
I can't read your mind.
Are you a bear (dense) or a fox (wily)?
Please eat some food with the alcohol.
I don't deserve to have food with the liquor.
I should eat it then.
You could criticize me instead.
Coral Public Bath
Cheong Yoo Construction
Jeong Yoo Taek
Gang Doo.
Let's go.
Mr. Technician.
If you just leave like this, who will do the rest of the work?
Then I will leave after welding some more steel sheets.
I will finish it fast. Wait for me over there while eating ice cream.
No! No! There is someone here.
There is a person here.
Who are you?
I am her older brother.
If you came to have fun, then you guys should just enjoy alcohol.
Your guest completely destroyed my younger sister's face.
How did you get in here?
Get out. Get out.
Are you doing your job as a security guard? How can a loser like this come all the way into my office?
I came here on my own, so don't blame an innocent person.
I want to leave quickly too. So shall we talk numbers?
Her face is really swollen.
What was he so displeased about?
No, that's not it.
Even if he was displeased, he can't do this to a person.
When your younger sister works at a bar, as an older brother you try to rip people off?
Work, if you need money.
Don't try to take other people's money. Shi*.
That's what I am saying.
My sister just turned 20 and worked hard to earn some money
because she saw that as work.
When she's someone who could be your daughter,
she tolerated people like you and smiled to your faces. But this is too much.
Let's not get emotional. Just pay up. Just pay up.
That's what you guys are good at.
Project
Urban Regeneration
Biotown
Cheong Yoo Construction
Seeing the world from a high spot like this,
don't people seem like people to you?
How do you know the CEO?
I guess we'll have to see about your skills.
Seeing that the CEO wants to work directly with you,
well, do you know him on a personal basis or something?
With whom?
Don't you know architect Seo Joo Won?
I don't think so.
This project is a large project. You'll have to make quite a few models.
Every time a new blueprint comes out, we'll need the study models for our presentations.
You'll have to come into office full-time for the duration of the project.
Work in the office?
I haven't heard anything about coming in to work.
Were you going to do this huge project at home as handcraft work?
All the famous companies are participating.
We're the only private company. Our CEO is so amazing.
It's not a project you can easily land with your experience...
The third floor here... Is it connected by the spatial structure?
With the open top, it does have an open view. I guess the sun will shine all day, right?
So that the movement is all the same wherever you enter the building from...
I guess you can do it like this, too.
What are you doing right now?
When do I begin?
This is storage, but
if we organize this, and when we get our laser cutting machine and work tables, it will be a useful space.
Seowon Architects &amp; Engineers
Yes, CEO.
Sorry?
Didn't you give the design sample to CEO?
That file hasn't come to us from the design team, so I gave him the original...
I gave it to him, but why is it sitting here?
Don't you know there's a meeting at 1 p.m.?
Who's going to take it to him?
I'm Seo Joo Won who has a meeting with him at 1 p.m.
He went up just a moment ago.
I'm sorry for being late, Director.
Did you have a previous appointment?
You came just in time.
I'm done, so get to work.
I'm Seo Joo Won.
I didn't ask.
Didn't you enter using my name?
Don't touch someone you don't know.
I brought the files.
Where do I need to go?
See me in front of the elevator on the 16th floor.
Sixteenth floor?
Ugh, I'm not even halfway there.
Look in front of you when you walk.
Are you...
going to stay like this?
CEO Seo Joo Won?
Why do you have that...
I'm Ha Moon Soo who was introduced to you by Builder Models.
Nice to meet you.
Oh.
Here.
All right then.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Take the elevator.
It's okay, this is more comfortable for me.
- Do you have any umbrellas?
- Hold on a sec.
It's 3000 won ($3).
Put it out in the front. It's going to rain.
Rain?  It's forecast to be sunny.
You know what day tomorrow is, right?
Hop in.
No, it's alright.
It's raining, get in.
I can take the bus.
I'm sorry for making you run an errand when you're not officially signed.
It's alright.
On top of that, you came here for nothing. My meeting got canceled.
I'm terribly sorry.
Please stop.
I'm really alright. If you keep apologizing, it only makes me feel uncomfortable.
Oh, I'm sorr...
I think it's become a habit for me to apologize.
It's better than not apologizing.
I looked at the blueprint.
The things you pointed out were very accurate.
In order to be able to bear the load, columns should be spaced out every 8 meters.
The weight of the roof will increase at least by 30%.
And if the snow piles on,
it will probably collapse as you mentioned, Ha Moon Soo.
That's why I urged the CEO to introduce you to me.
By the way, you walked all the way to the 16th floor?
Why did you skip the elevator?
Just because it's a bit stuffy not being able to see outside.
Here.
- You're going to get fired anyway. Just work with me.
- I don't want to.
Then have a drink before you go.
I don't want to.
Why not?
There are no windows here. It's stuffy.
- You know the building that Cheong Yoo is building?
- Yeah?
If it's a big construction, don't they need people on the construction site?
What? And you don't want to work with me?
I don't care what it is, just find me a job there.
Ow!
You got a boil the size of your fist on your butt and you had no idea?
Don't be dense. If you be that way, you'll end up spending more money than you earn.
Is it raining outside?
No, it stopped.
Aigoo, you must be hurting.
It's only called painkiller. They're all drugs.
Take it easy taking these. If not, you'll ruin your liver.
Why is there so much?
Please send it to Jae Yeong for me.
You can't even pay your interest on time, yet you want to act like an oppa?
She should live properly. She's different from me.
You were born from the same mother. How different could you be?
We're different.
I'll leave it to you.
Auntie.
Why are you here? What about Mom?
There aren't any customers at the bath house.
Your mom, she left earlier and...
Auntie, my bag.
Say it in front of me.
You think I don't know that you go around snickering?
Aigoo! She said she didn't! Stop accusing her!
I definitely heard her!
What? What did you hear?
Looking so terrible. You're drunk in broad daylight. Is letting your child die before you anything to brag about?
Living quietly wouldn't even be good enough.
You should be ashamed!
If you opened up your bath house with the money you sold out your child for,
you should put your head down and live a diligent life.
All you ever do is drink and go around all over the neighborhood. Aigoo, you're shameless.
Mom, your daughter's here. Let's go.
How many bottles did she drink?
Mom, let's go. Goodbye.
Mom, let's go.
Go and put her to sleep.
I will. Goodbye.
Do you also think I'm being unreasonable?
Did I seem that way?
Yeah.
Why did you do that?
- So that I won't forget her.
- Huh?
I should get yelled at so that I won't forget that I had to send off Yeon Soo first.
If I don't, I forget that sometimes.
If you can, forget it. I really can't remember it either.
You and I are different.
Mom needs to remember
because this is all my fault.
Why is it your fault?
It is.
It's the mother's fault when their child goes first.
If I live well, they'll say I live well.
If I destroy myself, they'll say I couldn't come to my senses even after letting my child die.
If I laugh or cry,
people will point fingers at me.
So, even if I drink and throw a tantrum,
don't hate me too much.
You don't age anyway.
Moon Soo!
I'm so relieved.
Moon Soo! Moon Soo!
Moon Soo, are you okay?
Moon Soo, can you hear me?
Mom.
Yes, it's Mom.
My baby, you're alright!
- How about Yeon Soo?
- Yeon Soo...
What are you talking about?
You were together.
Moon Soo, come to your senses.
Where's Yeon Soo? Where is she?
You were together, right?!
I don't know.
Why don't you know?! Why?!
Think about it! Yeon Soo! Yeon Soo! Where is Yeon Soo?
Why? Why are you the only one here?
Why are you here alone?
Yeon Soo!
Think carefully!
Is it her?
It's better if you don't see her.
No. Yeon Soo!
- Honey!
- Yeon Soo!
I told you to be together.
I told you to be together!
What about you?
Where were you, leaving your two kids behind?
I told you not to go around selling out Yeon Soo!
Am I the only one who did wrong?
This is my fault?
Who's the one who didn't even care for the kids because you were so busy outside the home?
Where were you when I was going all over the place looking for Yeon Soo?
Where were you?
Ha Yeon Soo's guardians.
You still don't remember?
What happened at the time of the accident?
Forget it. It's not something pretty to remember anyway.
It's a relief at least you made it alive.
Despite everything, it could've been worse.
There's no such a thing as being relieved because things could've been worse.
Being unfortunate is
just feeling miserable.
Kimbap, Noodles
Welcome.
I'll have noodles. Please make it spicy.
Aren't you going to ask if Mom is doing well?
Today's Yeon Soo's birthday. You should've stopped by home.
You came here to tell me that?
Yeah.
I thought you forgot.
Coming on strong in opposition.
In the end, the Gookmindang and Minjudang are negotiating the differences in their main points...
Milky Way
Five hundred won, 500 won! Seriously!
What's wrong?
- Come over here.
- What are you doing?
What's wrong? Come here.
Don't do that. What's wrong?
Stop, come here. I just think you're so pretty.
- I'm telling the truth.
- Why are you doing that?
Come here, stay still!
Aren't you going to sleep?! Let's keep it to a minimum!
It's not just today! Just keep your mouth shut and do it!
Is it good?
You feel like drinking when you fired me and ripped me off?
I get all the suffering and you get all the fun?
These days!
Bad guys live well comfortably!
What the crap is this?
Right? Ahjussi!
Why are you pointing at me?
Are you happy that you ripped me off, but you're eating pork?
If you're old enough, act your age, a**hole. Don't rip people off, man.
What's going on, Hyungnim?
Who the hell are you?
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
There weren't any hospitals that were open.
I can't just leave an injured person on the street.
Anybody in?
Yes.
Noodles, Kimbap
Are you awake?
I briefly cleaned your wounds, but you should go to the hospital. It seemed pretty bad.
It 's been ringing since a while back. I didn't want to intrude by picking it up.
Excuse...
You. Why did you come here? Shouldn't you be at the hospital?
- Did I say I wanted this from you?
- Hey.
What's wrong with a brother giving his younger sister spending money?
You yourself live in a crappy motel like this, and yet you want me to accept it?
Have you been well?
Why don't you answer your phone?
Are you studying hard?
What happened to your face?
Did you eat?
Don't be like this and come home.
This is my home.
Are you really going to live stupidly like this?
Stupidly? I'm living my life to the fullest for you.
Stop acting like you're fine. It's no use to me.
Go. You're not suited here.
Bro! Where were you?
Why are you here and not in your own room?
Mom told me to leave because she's cleaning.
Did you fight again?
No.
Does it hurt?
It hurts, it hurts.
See... if there's beer left in the can.
A really pretty girl came looking for you.
She left after crying here for a long time.
You shouldn't make girls cry. You'll get punished.
She's not my girl, she's my younger sister.
Is it okay to make your sister cry?
No, it's not.
I think I've seen her before.
- Huh?
- Uh?
Nothing.
I don't buy coffee outside. The espresso machine here is an expensive one.
It looks expensive.
The CEO remodeled this place himself.
He got all the materials himself.
Seriously... He looks like he just put on any outfit, but he has such a great style.
Doesn't he look rich at a first glance? I hear his family is very rich.
Not just with lots of money, but should I say from a good family.
I guess that's why he already has his own studio with his name on it at his age.
He must be talented.
- Pardon?
- He didn't open up his own studio because he comes from a good family, but he must be also talented.
How is Father?
He's not feeling well today. I think it will be difficult for you to see him today.
You made time to come here. What can we do?
I can come again next time.
Let's eat. It's been a long time since I had your food.
I can't tell whose home this is.
You should take care of Father's meal first.
Go ahead.
When is your sister coming back to Korea?
Next week.
She insists on coming back. Who can make her change her mind?
Wasn't it planned out to be used for a commercial purpose anyway?
What's with the public medical center and energy materials?
There was an accident on the District C lot, and there are a few questionable issues with using the lot for profit.
Who still remembers that?
That was all because of your father. And my father is the one who had to clean up after all that!
Stop it. Why do you bring up the man who passed away already?
That's what I mean.
So, think of your deceased father and do a good job without any mistakes.
Don't worry.
Joo Won!
Take this with you. You only have to warm it up.
Okay. Go inside.
Joo Won. I heard Yoo Jin is going to come back and take over your business.
Will that be okay?
It should be okay.
I don't like you doing that type of work.
Doing the construction there at the same place...
I feel like I'm looking at your father. Makes me nervous.
It can be problematic. I wonder if you're getting involved—
Father didn't do anything to cause problems.
I know. I know that, but I was stupid enough to come into this family...
I know it was because of me. So, I thank you.
No matter how hard I tried, how talented I am, I couldn't have come this far to this position without those people's help.
SOS
I wonder if people saw me do this, would they still say I became his second wife greedy over his fortune?
I'm just an unpaid maid.
Go inside. Don't get scolded again.
Okay.
I told them in advance, so go. They say it's a site maintenance team.
It might sound nice, but I don't know what kind of work it is.
Cheong Yoo Construction, Medical Innovative City
Where did she ever find a guy like you? Does she think we accept just anybody?
What have you been doing all this time? Nothing's written here.
Resume, Lee Kang Doo, Birthdate: May 3rd, 1990, current address: Gyeonggi Province Moksan City
Spit your gum out, jerk! How dare you chew gum during your interview?
We rotate every week taking the overnight shift. Today, you'll work full-time. 24 hours. You'll work the night shift tomorrow night.
So, come to work by 7 p.m. tomorrow. As for your official first day,
Sunday... Hey, are you listening to me?
Ah, yes.
Anyway, the most important task during the day is to manage the access point. And that's District C where the research building will be established.
And I hear there's going to be a park here.
It will be built at the end, so you don't have to worry about it.
And if you go over there...
Hey, what are you staring at? Huh?
Move diligently! This is the beginning!
Okay!
Please analyze at least last 10 years of weather and recalculate the number.
- Yes.
- This region is humid and the storms are frequent too.
Please analyze the users, equipment usage time, and transfer route to calculate the external forces.
Do you have the three-dimensional sketch of the lobby?
Yes, it will be ready today.
Today's meeting... I think the CEO is in a bad mood.
I heard from Cheong Yoo that a new director who is going to be on the project will come next week.
He's just looking over everything in detail before then.
They're still debating whether they'll hold an unveiling ceremony or not.
Oh, yeah. I feel uneasy about that, too. Must we hold the ceremony?
What about?
Don't you know about it, Unni?
Our construction site, there was a huge accident there.
Accident?
I hear they're going to commemorate by putting up some memorial before the groundbreaking.
It's worth commemorating. Only 48 people died in such a huge accident.
Only 48 people died?
Hundreds of people die these days when a disaster happens. Let alone 10 years ago—
Forty-eight people.
Not only 48 people, but as many as 48 people died.
Cradle of Life, Biotown
2005 S Mall Building Collapse Disaster Case Study and Measures
"Unbelievably disasterous collapse site"
Commemorate what?
♫  I open my eyes, I see you  ♫
♫  I wave my hand and erase you away  ♫
♫  No matter how much I try, even if I do that again  ♫
♫  You're still smiling in front of me  ♫
♫  I missed you, you were precious to me  ♫
♫  All the memories you left behind  ♫
♫  In all of those moments, in all of those times  ♫
♫  You always looked beautiful  ♫
♫  All the memories that pour into me, numerous words that pop into my head  ♫
♫  How can I hold you back?, I'll be here, I'll be here  ♫
Just Between Lovers
The person who brought me here. Who is she? That woman?
Did you see the man who just walked in? Who is it?
He seemed like someone from the construction site. You must like the type who is rough around the edges.
Do you work there? I think I've seen you before.
We were going to end up being a family. It would have been better if we did it first.
- That would have been harder for me.
- How about now?
I am sorry about earlier. I wasn't considerate of the fact that you don't take elevators.
No, not at all. You don't need to be mindful of that.
I am mindful of that.
Don't expect too much from him. You won't be able to marry him anyhow. Don't have lingering feelings.
Did you get married out of love?
The result of love doesn't always end up in a marriage.
You might seem fine on the outside, but you're not normal.
Just because you're young, don't abuse your body.
How can I live without going crazy in this crazy world?
Do you still see things?
♫  All the memories that pour into me  ♫
♫  Numerous words that pop into my head  ♫