Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Fated Lovers Team @ viki
Hyung!
Hyung! You're awake. Are you alright?
Oh, I understand. I hear you.
How did I get here?
I heard that you collapsed in front of Moon Soo's house.
Imagine how shocked she was.
Moon Soo is here?
She's been sitting outside since last night without even eating anything.
I asked her to eat, but she was just sitting there like a chunk of rock.
Wait, lie down. I will bring her here.
Your sister's chief doctor instructed you to stay in your bed.
Hyung.
Seeing you act like your life is over because of that type of thing
looks even worse.
What are you doing here blocking my way?
At the current state, transplant is your only solution.
There isn't much that can be done other than (transplant) surgery.
Since you don't have ascites (fluid accumulation) or sepsis yet,
you could receive treatments as an outpatient. If you could be hospitalized, that will be even better.
If there is a sudden onset of hepatic coma, it will be very difficult for you.
What did he say?
What
am I going to do?
Were you planning on not telling me this time too?
No,
I said I had something to tell you yesterday.
You were going to leave after saying what you had to say.
You said I shouldn't feel sorry.
But why do you keep making me sorry?
How can you do this?
I was just going to
leave in a dashing manner.
How can it be dashing when you're leaving?
What exactly have you done in your previous life
for your life to turn out so nasty like this.
That's not true.
Since I met you
I thought I had saved a country (done a great deed) in my previous life.
♫  It's an old longing to you, but  ♫
It hurts.
Stop hitting me.
Don't die.
♫  In such a sad story  ♫
If you die, I will kill you.
♫  You're beautiful comfort to me  ♫
I won't leave you to die.
I will be by your side till the end this time.
♫  Inside this cold story  ♫
♫  You are a warm place  ♫
♫  The day my heart melted,  ♫
Episode 16
Patient Lee Gang Doo's emergency level, is it still the same?
Organ Transplant Center
His rank is still the same?
Yes, he's still number two.
His condition worsened yesterday and was admitted as an emergency case. Shouldn't his number change?
I don't decide his number on the waiting list.
Some patients are waiting in ICU beds for their turn.
It's not something you can give just because you want to.
Why? Because we're not related?
Then, I can do it if I marry Gang Doo, right? I can marry him right away.
Even if you register your marriage, you could only do it after one year.
Also, you can't give it to him since you're smaller than him.
Because I am smaller than him?
Even if it's a match, the donor has to give 65% of her liver to the recipient.
With your build, it won't work.
Your intention is enough.
I will try to do everything I can.
He's so handsome without any cuts.
He is bigger.
Many customers who are traumatized after a car accident seek this out too.
Is this the best one here?
There isn't any more impressive a model?
If you want a more stylish vehicle, I will recommend a different model to you.
- Wait a moment.
- Okay.
You're going to decide on a car by how it looks?
You should compare maintenance cost, fuel efficiency, how it feels when you ride in it.
Hey! What's important for a car is not how it feels when you ride in it but how it feels when you exit it.
When you exit your car, everyone should be wowed by it.
You don't even ride it often.
My mom hates me driving.
She doesn't trust me. But I must drive from now on.
Why?
I don't want you giving me ride in your car.
Are you embarrassed? Are you showing off how rich you are?
Yeah. I am gong to show off how rich I am.
Money doesn't make you happy.
However, it is true that much unhappiness can be avoided.
You said your car used to belong to your uncle who used to beat you up.
Sell it. Let's drive a new car.
Here.
Wait.
Moon Soo. I bought a car. Do you want to go anywhere?
Hey! What's wrong?
I mean, you two just want to love each other. Why is it so hard for you two?
Unni. I don't understand.
Look at the life he lived.
He survived such hardship,
but he might die due to sickness.
Does that make sense?
So he could die like this, (God) spared his life?
Why is He doing this to Gang Doo?
He has it hard enough as it is.
Why does He make it harder for Gang Doo?
It feels unfair.
It's so unfair to us.
Don't cry.
Rather, cry your eyes out when you're with me.
Don't cry when you're with Gang Doo.
Gang Doo is so pitiful, what am I to do?
I am pitiful too, what am I to do?
You cry for him like this, why is Gang Doo pitiful?
Isn't a two-patient room too expensive?
I am a doctor.
Then, do you get an employee discount or something?
How is it that we don't even have relatives that we're close to?
Oppa.
When Mom was sick,
do you remember how I begged that I wanted to sleep next to Mom,
that I don't like the cot?
Yeah.
I decided to become a doctor back then.
If I became a doctor, I thought I would come to a hospital only to cure people.
I didn't know that it would turn out like this again.
I am sorry.
If you're sorry, then don't die.
Don't leave me behind, by myself.
I can't let Jae Yeong be alone.
I really can't die.
Gran told me to take my time to come see her.
I knew you'd be doing this.
- How did you?
- I left because I was in a condition to do so.
Did you stay up and put this together by yourself?
Mother Im Jin Hae who used to wait for her son, Choi Il Do every day by the front door.
We're waiting for you, Moon Byeong Ho.
Our Captain who stayed behind till the end to do repair work
Rebar Manager Mr. Lee Cheol Woo
In the work log you gave me,
there was contact information for workers who worked with your father. So I contacted them
and they only had praise for your father.
District A
You want this to be the memorial?
Yes.
Wouldn't it be uncomfortable to look at this?
I am not saying this on behalf of the company.
Some bereaved family members may think differently.
Because it's uncomfortable.
Because time has passed since we received the compensation fund,
we can't begin to forget like that.
That's why the same things keep on repeating.
The memorial park isn't being built for our comfort.
I vote for those words. Building it so it looks good isn't all there is to it.
Let's keep it this way. Cheongyu needs to do so.
I will try.
By the way, are you sick?
So this discussion is over. Please wrap it up well.
Those two get along well together.
Oh, wait.
Bio Town, many things are different from how they're specified in the business plan.
Use of laborers, materials and the processes too.
It was all approved by Director Jeong Yoo Taek.
Why are you giving this to me?
Even if I were to give it to the Cheongyu auditing department, they might cover it up.
I thought it would be better to trust you.
When they try to find the source, if it gets out that Seowon brought this issue up,
Seowon might not be able to get any work from Cheongyu in the future.
I won't get involved. If it's like this, I shouldn't get involved in the future.
Manager.
This.
What is this?
Mr. Lee Cheol Woo, Gang Doo's father.
I checked the blueprint of the shopping mall.
On August 5th, 2005, it says they cut the lower rebar of the elevator in District B.
- The marking person made a mistake so it was put aside.
- So what?
He might have privately dealt the rebar that was cut at that time.
But there is no evidence to be found anywhere that Gang Doo's father smuggled out any rebar.
I guess many people have high expectations of me.
You could set things right.
Please, I ask you.
Mr. Lee Gang Doo must feel secure since someone has his back.
I've heard that Mr. Lee Gang Doo quit his on-site job too. Is there something going on between you two?
No, nothing will happen.
I handed over the blueprint and the model to the design team. Also I've updated So Mi on any future work that needs to be done.
Thank you for your work.
Moon Soo.
Yes.
We will contact the family members of the bereaved.
The remains found at the site weren't a match to the DNA of the victim who was never found.
We have decided to compare it to other victims if the bereaved families want it.
- If you don't want that—
- No, that might be my younger sister.
Only my dad saw how Yeon Soo was at the end. But her body was so seriously disfigured that he wouldn't even allow my mom to see her.
My dad was really angry then.
When I look back on it, I think he coped by getting angry.
Oh, right. You saw my dad in front of the restaurant.
Yes.
The restaurant is closing down. Before that—
No, I don't think I'll be able to go that far yet.
However, I understand that he was angry.
Pardon?
I will be able to see you again at the memorial park with Lee Gang Doo.
Thank you. Thanks to you and Lee Gang Doo, I was able to keep myself in line.
Isn't the name of this bus stop ridiculous?
Look. It says "Front of S Mall." That's been gone for some time already.
Why do you remember that?
I don't forget anything now. Anything that's related to you.
I am proud of you.
I am really proud of ourselves.
Doctor. You haven't come by often lately. Are you really busy?
Yes.
- Then.
- This is good. I came to ask a question.
Let me at least get tested. I've heard that the liver grows back.
It's not something you could decide so easily like that—
Who said it's easy? It's not easy.
I looked away when my father died of liver cancer.
Pardon?
But I will give it to Gang Doo.
I could get tested, right?
Thank you.
- What does your older brother do?
- Pardon?
What kind of life did he live that so many people are willing to donate their livers?
What?
It would have been dangerous if it had been any later but it's good that a match has been found in preliminary testing.
What are you doing? Take it.
Result of the blood test, Ahn Sang Man. Blood type: O
Usually, unless you're a family member or a relative,
people might get suspicious that you're trying to sell your organ.
However, Hyung's address is here.
In order to prove that we lived together for more than 8 years,
I had to even go to city hall. It was very difficult, Mom.
I couldn't even eat for 6 hours.
Also, they poured something cold into my stomach. They drew many vials of blood too.
What are you saying now?
Were you listening when I explained everything?
If I share mine, Hyung could survive.
Stop saying useless things. You can't take even one step out from now on, do you understand?
Mom!
Listen to Mom's words.
Mom! I want to be useful too.
Oh, this thoughtless rascal. How can you stay that to your mother?
Mom.
Don't regard it as giving but instead gaining.
I am not giving a liver to Hyung. Instead, you're gaining another son. Isn't that lucky?
- Be quiet. Throw this out.
- Oh, Mom.
- No way.
- No, Mom.
- Mom.
- You can never go out. This fool.
You could give other things, but how can you give that? This fool.
Mom.
Oppa!
No matter how desperate you are, how can you do that to Sang Man? To Sang Man!
That was Sang Man's decision. Why can't you understand Sang Man?
Still, you should have stopped him!
Why should I stop him? Saving you comes first.
- You're fired.
- What?
I said you're fired. It's not only doctors who can be selective in taking patients.
Patients should be able to fire their doctors too.
Gang Doo.
You don't have anything, but why do you keep this pride? Just throw that stupid thing away, please!
If I throw that away too,
how can I live?
When I know that I will destroy it,
how can I live happily taking away what belongs to Sang Man?
Sang Man, come out. You'll really get in trouble with me if you don't.
Sang Man. Open the door. I said open the door.
- Mom.
- Open the door.
I can't live if I don't have you or Hyung.
So, you need to allow me to live with Hyung.
Aren't you coming home?
Please understand my acting like this. Too bad if I come across as being heartless.
What mother would agree to her kid's body being cut open to share his organ?
I know.
Aiyoo, I've known you for ten years, yet I am being like this.
People are petty like this.
I am sorry, Gang Doo.
Stop, Ahjumma.
Why would you feel sorry? I am the one who should be sorry.
Don't worry. I won't allow him to go through with it.
Even if Sang Man insists, I won't agree to it.
But what can you do? Sang Man needs to live first.
If I leave him like that, I am afraid he will be the first one to die.
When I already know that no one can change his mind once Sang Man's stubbornness kicks in,
I had to try to stop him at least once. I could be more at peace that way.
Why are you being like this too?
Since it turned out like this already, I guess you and Sang Man will become real brothers.
Since I've gained a troublesome son like you, it seems like I will have to tighten my belt even tighter.
Please live a long long time and carry out your filial duties. You must.
Gang Doo.
I understand how you feel and I understand how Sang Man feels too.
Then it was difficult to even think about who's correct.
So how hard it must be for you.
It's hardest for you now.
I won't do it.
You're being like this because you feel bad towards Sang Man, right?
Going through with the surgery, you think you're being greedy, right?
But you're wrong.
You're not the one being greedy, but it's we who are being greedy.
No matter how difficult it is for you, it's our greed that wants you alive next to us.
So you don't have a choice in this matter.
Even though it may be hard, you just need to live.
Seaweed Rolls. Noodles
I've heard that you're quitting the restaurant.
A position opened up in driving tour buses.
Your urge to wander around.
Geez, how did you endure it here for ten years?
Why did you choose here of all the places?
When it's so close by. Why?
Is that your way of coping?
In our relationship, we don't talk anymore.
Divorce... Let's do that.
So that we end up worse than strangers, we fought each other tooth and nail
for more than twenty years
to no end. Like a fool.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Fated Lovers Team @ viki
Starting with Bio Town, Cheongyu has decided
against any outsourcing and multiple levels of subcontracting out, practices widely accepted in the construction industry.
It's also a way to show Cheongyu's intention to not repeat the catastrophe of 13 years ago.
Since the memorial park will be built at the entrance of the town, we emphasize how it harmonizes with its surroundings as our priority.
Also, survivors of the catastrophe, Lee Gang Doo and Ha Moon Soo are personally involved in this project.
We paid special care in considering the victim's families as well.
What's going on? Move aside. Don't you know who I am?
Only the board of directors can attend this meeting.
I am a director.
Manager Jeong Yoo Jin told me you've been released from your board position.
What?
Please take good care of Cheongyu Environmental from now on. That's the place Cheongyu began.
Hey, Jeong Yoo Jin. You of all people, you stab me in the back?
Since it's me, I am doing this.
Since you're my older brother, I am not giving up.
What?
Believe me. More than anyone, I want you to turn out okay.
Please empty the office as soon as possible.
Hey! Jeong Yoo Jin!
Did you go to the hospital?
Shall we meet in the evening?
Is there anything you want to eat?
You're not sick?
What did your sister say?
- Hyung.
- Did you receive all the medicine?
You can leave. You have one more test left, but it should be alright, Sang Man.
You don't have pneumothorax or fatty liver. The size of your liver is good too.
Hyung. Don't look like that.
At times like this, you just need to say thank you.
I am so thankful, I can't bring myself to say those words.
Your paperwork is perfect too, so you'll get approved.
Once it's been approved, I will schedule the surgery right away.
So you must not drink any liquor from now on.
Let's go.
Leave. Make sure to answer when I call.
Work hard.
- Oh, why?
- Hyung. Smile.
Do you remember what Cho Woo said in Warrior Guard?
I don't.
"A person who needs to protect something (someone) doesn't die easily." Do you remember?
I remember. Right.
That's why you shouldn't worry. We won't die.
See you later, Hyung.
Cheongyu Jeong Yoo Jin.
I was going to buy you something yummy.
This tastes most yummy to me.
Why? Another dating consultation?
I was worried after hearing you're at the hospital. But it seems like you have enough energy to joke.
Ask when I have energy so you won't regret later.
Then... With my looks, qualifications, and a good family too,
why do you think I don't have a boyfriend?
You're too outstanding.
This stupid group of men have this useless disease in which they get exhausted by outstanding women.
So don't worry about those stupid jerks.
Then how about Moon Soo? Is Moon Soo popular since she's mediocre?
Look here. My Moon Soo is very outstanding and a good person.
It's just that a courageous man like me is hard to find.
She must be happy, Ha Moon Soo.
I'm embarrassed.
Talk about embarrassing and humiliating things too.
Don't just keep them to yourself. It's better for your health to talk about them.
Don't be sick.
You're my only friend with whom I can share embarrassing things.
This is the real reason for my visit.
The unpaid compensation to your father from the collapse.
Letter of Apology
If it wasn't for Ha Moon Soo, it would have been overlooked.
I am sorry for being late.
It was discovered that the rebar your father took was discarded rebar with no monetary value.
Even though Mr. Lee Chul Woo, who died in the collapse, cannot be held for liable for the cost, Cheongyu didn't pay the compensation fund.
I apologize again.
Jae Yeong.
Professor. Please. It might be different once you open him up.
Can you please reconsider?
Look. The donor has a deformity in his artery and even his biliary tract is a case that's difficult to operate.
I will convince him. You could at least try to open him up.
Once you open him up, it might be milder than it looks in the images.
If Mr. Ahn Sang Man agrees to it, we could go through with it.
But if we do so, what if he suffers biliary tract stricture and complications? What will you do then?
You're saying you could do it, right?
Hey!
The risk is too high. Let's keep doing maintenance treatment for now—
Hey. Hey!
Where are you going?
Why did you come back?
Are you going to Sang Man?
What are you going to do when you go see him?
What else? I'll tell him to prepare for the surgery.
Stop it.
Stop what?
You, Sang Man.
- You've done enough.
- Done what?
What did I do?
What did I do for you, Oppa?
You did a lot.
You did a lot, so stop it now.
Oh. Thanks for accepting my employees.
There will be a proposal for Moksan City Library design competition next month.
Moksan City Library Design Competition Proposal
Why are you giving this to me?
There's no reason Cheongyu and Seowon will work together in the future.
I haven't seen another architect who is as capable as you.
I told you before. Let's have a working relationship, not a personal relationship.
No. I don't think this is a project for me.
While I'm downsizing my office, I want to work on a project I really wanted to work on.
Still, this project is—
And our relationship is quite personal in nature.
My mother is also your mother.
You didn't leave yet?
I'm not leaving.
No matter how small an office is, you still need a marketing person.
I'm good at marketing.
Of course, I can design and I'm good at making models now.
- Thanks.
- Pardon?
I'm grateful for your heart, but you'll be great at Cheongyu, too.
Don't worry.
See you again.
He's so cool to the end.
Are you really going?
Yeah.
Really?
Are you doing this out of anger because you got a divorce?
- Think it over—
- Am I going somewhere strange?
I can't quit drinking by myself so I'm trying to get some help.
While this place is getting fixed up, let me get fixed up, too.
I have to be healthy in order for you to be comfortable.
You're not running away from me?
I'm trying to stay by your side for a very long time.
Don't you dare say you're sick of me.
They say there aren't any fingers that don't hurt if you bite them. But each of them hurt differently.
You and Yeon Soo are different. I'm not saying one of you is more valuable than the other.
Do you understand?
I can't drink once I go in there. Should I drink one more bottle before I go?
Mom.
Hey, just one bottle.
You can't.
Hey, let me just have one glass.
Geez, this girl!
She says I can play tomorrow. Jae Yeong gave me permission.
Did you wait long?
No.
Ah. I have lots of money.
Huh?
Thanks to you... I got money all of a sudden.
Everything you do is so pretty.
You were born to be loved by me, right?
What the heck.
Stay still.
Why?
I'm thankful.
Is there anywhere you want to go?
I don't know.
I told you I have lots of money.
I can spend all this money today.
Didn't you have things you wanted to do when you got some money?
I wanted to pay off my debt.
Shall we pay off debt then?
I did all that already.
How?
In any case... So, you can do whatever you want to do.
- Over there.
- Huh?
That's the place So Mi was talking about.
Where?
Motel
- Hey, hey, hey.
- You said do whatever I want to do.
Well, that's...
Let's go inside.
Hey, you... that place is—
I know what kind of place that is. So, let's go inside.
I think we walked too much. Let's just get some rest.
What? I said we'll just get some rest.
Did you have some weird thoughts?
I really won't do anything. I'll be still.
I'll just sleep.
Moon Soo. Moon Soo...
I want to stay with you, too.
Do you think it's easy for me hold myself back? I'm going crazy, too.
Why are you holding yourself back?
- Are you asking me that because you don't know?
- Forget it.
Had I known, I would've asked you to go to an island so that we could miss the last boat.
Don't laugh. Even if you beg me to go now, I won't go.
Let's go together.
Should we eat something? Octopus? You like octopus.
Forget it.
Why are you acting this way?
Why do you only think of yourself?
I'm greedy for the first time in my life. And that's you.
Who cares about a sense of responsibility?
I like you.
I want to have you.
I didn't mean that I wanted to come to such a nice place.
It's okay.
But still.
I said it's okay.
Take a look.
Gang Doo. Gang Doo, look in here. There's another room.
It's so big.
Gang Doo, the towel here is huge. It's bigger than me.
It covers everything, right?
Do you think I'm wearing my clothes behind this or not?
Hey, you're going to get in trouble.
The bed is huge.
Gang Doo, lie down. More than ten of me can lie down here.
It's big.
Right?
Come here.
We don't need a big bed like this, right?
♫  Somehow we are  ♫
♫  similar to each other, no  ♫
♫  Do only my eyes see that?  ♫
♫  Our footprints as we walked together  ♫
♫  Maybe that's why I kept liking you  ♫
♫  It's an old longing to you, but  ♫
♫  It makes me want to lean on you  ♫
♫  In such a sad story  ♫
♫  You're beautiful comfort to me  ♫
♫  that visited me one day  ♫
♫  Inside this cold story  ♫
♫  You are a warm place  ♫
♫  The day my heart melted,
You were by my side  ♫
Gang Doo!
Lee Gang Doo!
And how about Gang Doo? Where is Gang Doo right now?
If you were coming here, why did you leave me behind?
Sorry. I had some things to take care of.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Fated Lovers Team @ viki
Why?
What?
You snuck a peak at me a lot sitting here.
I did?
You were smiling by yourself looking at me.
That's when you started liking me, huh? Right?
It wasn't from then.
If you count that... When you drank, got drunk, and you first...
I kissed you first.
What the heck?
Do you remember everything?
Yeah.
If you remembered, did you pretend as if you didn't?
I did that because I was embarrassed.
It seemed like I was the only one who liked you.
Are you dumb? To a woman he didn't even like,
what man would lend his shoulder all night?
You're so pretty.
How could you be prettier as time goes by?
I'd become prettier if you kept looking at me.
Oh, yeah. I had something I wanted to ask you.
What is it?
Even if I couldn't remember you, you remembered me.
Why didn't you look for me?
Then, we wouldn't have had to come full circle and could've been together longer.
It was dark in there.
Huh?
I had no idea you'd be so pretty like this.
I love you.
There's not enough time left for me to live saying only the things I want to say.
I only realized that.
I love you... Moon Soo.
I made you struggle so much. You still like me?
Yeah.
Why?
Just because.
Geez.
Do you need a reason? For me to love you?
No.
Thanks.
Listen, Gang Doo.
I kept thinking about when I started liking you.
In the dark... when I heard your voice for the first time.
When you first sang that strange song.
♫  I don’t want to say anything  ♫
I think I started liking you from then.
♫  I don’t want to forget your face
Even for a single day  ♫
Are you listening to me?
♫  So I can remember
Even if we’re far apart  ♫
♫  Let me place you in my heart a little more  ♫
♫  My eyes that look at you I didn’t know it would be this deep  ♫
Did you hear that, Gang Doo?
Did you hear what I said?
♫  My hands that hold you I didn’t know they trembled this much  ♫
Can you hear my voice?
♫  This heart, to me  ♫
Gang Doo. What do I do? Gang Doo...
What do I do?
♫  Please let me be with this person more  ♫
It's been said that life is about getting used to parting.
♫  Please let me laugh with this person for one more day  ♫
No.
There is no one who gets used to...
parting.
♫  Stay with me for just one more day  ♫
The opening ceremony for the memorial park we've been building since last year...
will take place on December 11, 2018.
The memorial has been designed for the people to witness the timeline of the past accident.
It holds the meaning that history will repeat itself unless you remember it.
To remember the victims and to comfort the victims' families...
We hope that you will be able to attend the ceremony.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Kim Seon Woong's Old Home. I heard you're enlarging the house here.
Yes, why?
Architect Seo Joo Won
I'd like to work on it together.
- Manager!
- Yes?
How old is it?
It's about 70 years old, but it's been neglected for the last 10 years.
There probably aren't any materials we can restore. What type of wood are you thinking of?
I'm learning about that, too. What do you think is a good one?
The unit price would be high, but pine from Oaksan would be nice.
I worked with douglas fir before, but it twisted. Pine should be harder, right?
If that's the case, why not use metal and pour concrete? Why use wood?
- Excuse me?
- Since it's wood, of course, it cracks and changes.
It's our job to build it with all those things in mind.
Um...
Would we learn anything by chatting here like this? We have to see it for ourselves to know.
Aren't you going?
Executive Director?
I'm not a director anymore.
Hey, you! You said my wife worries about me. You said we'd grow old together.
What about it?
Does someone like that hand over the divorce papers as soon as I get demoted?
- I'm not interested in someone else's family affairs. Leave.
- Hey.
- Take responsibility.
- What?
Me.
- Give me a freaking break.
- Hey, hey.
I'm still my father's son. You think I'd end this way?
Enjoy.
It's so comfortable from just placing a ramp by the entrance.
Artist.
What?
Oh, my! Already top 10?
People are reading such an inconvenient story.
People recognize good work. Don't look down on readers.
Who's looking down on them? They're better than me.
But this girl. She's too much.
People would say she looks so different from me.
Right? I should've drawn her prettier.
If I drew her looking too much like you, I thought people wouldn't believe it. I'm sorry.
Thank you to our channel manager: kakashiandme.
Thank you to our English moderator: myriam_7c.
Thank you to our many other language moderators and subtitlers.
Thank you to our segmenters: pilar_velasquez, kitty100, sabrinafair, fizban, philar02, s14950, aanya_sawhney1_515, lil1508, and andres15_867.
Thank you to our Korean to English subtitlers: itgirlfornow, grrrcat, berryblast87, Jelly, jieun_rhee, and stars4u.
Thank you to our English editors: joysprite (chief), Jefftiger96, and singndance4life.
Thank you to our translation editor: itgirlfornow.
Thank you to our page designer: jean jean.
Dongtaetang (frozen pollack soup) at Shintanjin rest area is still delicious.
Let's go together next time.
Let's go.
There she is!
Mom!
Wait a minute. I'll come after I wrap this up.
My daughter is here, so I have to hurry.
- Mom, you're going to drink soy milk, right?
- Yeah.
- Auntie, you, too?
You're doing well, right? They're making a separate salon, right?
Yeah. On the second floor. Huge.
How about you, Auntie?
I told the spa that I'll work until next month.
You did well.
You never used to like sweet things.
- How about him?
- Huh?
What was his name? It sounded like a puppy's name. Gang Do?
Mom, what do you mean Gang Do? Gang Doo.
She was all smiles when she saw him. So, his name is Gang Doo?
Yeah. Lee Gang Doo.
Oppa. Oppa. Oppa!
Just as misfortune comes to you unexpectedly...
Miracles also come out of the blue just as we're about to give up hope.
It's a TA (traffic accident); there's no trauma to the liver. ACC (asystole and cross-clamp) at 22:35 (10:35).
Ischemic time is expected to be 3 hours. Yes.
Yes, we can arrive within 20 minutes.
But that miracle could come out of someone else's misfortune.
Miracles.
I don't believe them.
I don't believe them now. But it could at least happen once
for my oppa.
So, we should be thankful that we are alive.
We should become happier with more strength.
Remove the A shape ladder...
75 cm all around... Geez!
Why is it so hard?
Hey, Gang Doo! I went patrolling alone so you could study, but you're sleeping.
I'm tired these days.
Are you okay? Where do you hurt?
You're all healed, right? You punk! You say you're sick when you lack the advantage.
I hired you because I'm lacking workers. But you're being accepted here because of me. You need to know that.
Is this what you're studying these days?
- This is too hard. I have no idea what they're saying.
- Hey.
Did you think it was easy to become a design supervisor? Let's see. I'll help you.
You will, Team Leader?
You punk! I'm a manager now.
And it may be hard to believe, but I majored in civil engineering.
Let's see. Let me see. This is...
This has changed quite a bit.
I left it out so I could wear that.
Take it off. Hurry.
Aren't you going to take it off?
Hyung. I'm Ahn Sang Man. Who am I to you?
If it's for you, forget liver, even my heart—
Stop. I got it. Wear it then.
Hyung, I love you.
Read.
Sang Man! Gang Doo! Eat!
Aren't you coming down?
Hello, please sit there and wait.
Thank you. Thank you.
And this person. It's not a trauma. Please have him explain his symptoms.
Okay.
Is it doable?
One year. I'm doing this for exactly a year.
- Why are you looking at me like that?
- What?
Don't start off with, "This is the last fortress..." Don't even think about tempting me again.
The money Grandma left behind is quite a bit. A year?
I can run for the next ten years.
Doctor!
Yes.
His stomach feels uncomfortable and
he's dizzy.
- His head?
- Yeah.
And?
I can't recklessly get hurt.
Yes, second floor.
Please be careful so it won't touch the wall.
If I get hurt, there is someone who will be sad.
So at the most, in good health
without any incidents, I will live a long time.
That... is the thing that I can do for the person that I love.
I should decorate this place like in the Milky Way Inn.
It would be refreshing if you were to come up after a bath, right?
Yeah.
It's nice to come here together.
I love you.
I love you, Gang Doo.
Moon Soo loves me.
♫   Don't close your eyes anymore. I will hold you.   ♫
I love you.
♫  Don't cry I will be beside you.    ♫
♫  When I say the name that I've been hiding and covering up  ♫
Because we survived...
♫   My heart beats   ♫
♫  The two of us  ♫
It's a relief.
♫  What words are needed?  ♫
♫  Even hearing your name makes me tear up from missing you  ♫
♫  What kind of reason is needed?  ♫
♫  When we think of each other with all our hearts  ♫
Just Between Lovers
♫  When there's a hole in your heart
When you want to cry so badly  ♫
♫  Hold me and bury your face
You can cry for awhile  ♫
♫  I'll stand here from now on
Throughout all your hours  ♫
♫  Throughout your day  ♫
♫  What words are needed?  ♫
♫  Even hearing your name makes me tear up from missing you  ♫
♫  What kind of reason is needed?  ♫
♫  When we think of each other with all our hearts  ♫
♫  When there's a hole in your heart
When you want to cry so badly  ♫
♫  Hold me and bury your face
You can cry for awhile  ♫
♫  I'll stand here from now on
Throughout all your hours  ♫
♫  Throughout your day  ♫
♫  I think of you  ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Fated Lovers Team @ viki