Bulldog Mansion.
What?
Don't you know Bulldog Mansion?
I don't know.
Don't try to change the subject and answer my question.
You really don't know?
I don't know.
Fine then.
Hey, where are you? There is a traffic jam in the entry. There are piles of trucks waiting—
Yes, I will be there.
Episode 4
You're getting on my nerves. Aren't you going to work?
I will get lost to avoid getting on your nerves. So please answer the question.
About what? You have to ask a proper question for me to answer.
- Here.
- Was I here during the collapse? Is that your question?
No, happy now?
It's weird how you answer so easily like that.
- Don't be like that—
- Why do you ask when you won't even believe my answer?
Coming to see me unannounced and stirring a person until you hear the answer you want. That's a form of violence too.
Do you know that?
So let's say I was here like how you want it.
If that's the case, I must be feeling really shi**y then.
But why do you ask?
Just because you want to know?
Out of curiosity?
You treat other people's unhappiness as if it means nothing, but you can't hold in your curiosity.
You're a bad person.
- Ms. Moon Soo.
Didn't you say you could only come in by afternoon today?
Please move the car. Trucks go in and out of here.
Let's work. Work. Don't mind about other people's business.
Go back and move the car. Get in.
I said go. Move the car.
Get back in and quickly move the car.
You need to move your car too, Ahjussi.
Bulldog Mansion. Isn't it the band you like?
Band?
You listened to their music all the time you were hospitalized. So I thought you like them.
I did?
You don't remember that either?
Your memory loss isn't limited to the collapse?
Do you remember how we first met?
- We met at the hospital.
- Forget it. Let's not try to remember.
What's the point of remembering those dark times?
This is it.
What is this? What are you doing now?
It doesn't hurt to check again.
So you don't trust the result of my inspection?
I can't trust your father's construction inspection company, Project Manager.
Oh, enough is enough.
I am doing this so we can do enough.
Oh, you're driving me crazy.
What's this?
Isn't ground inspection already completed?
Oh, it is.
Before blasting the excavation site, another inspection—
I don't remember signing off on this.
What were you doing when we inspected it the first time? Why are you doing this only now?
Some areas were left out in the previous inspection.
Exactly. Why are you?
Why are you making the decision?
I am not doing this for my sake.
So I have to approve the cost and you want to show off about it.
You saw that. There are so many thieves like this; will there be any money left at the company?
Hey, you!
You! You!
Hurry up and come, dam*.
Who are you to keep showing up?
It's Lee Gang Doo.
At least remember my name.
Lee Gang Doo. I will remember. But you should remember too.
He's not the person who's paying you. It's me. Got it?
Now that you order a gangster around, does this place seem like it belongs to you?
You'll end up like your father if you continue. Be careful, Joo Won.
Oh, he's so good at belittling people. What would have happened if he wasn't made a director?
He's not a bad person.
The problem is his position is too much for him.
What was your business with Ms. Ha Moon Soo in the morning?
Something that has nothing to do with you, CEO.
What? Why? Do I have to report to you about my personal life?
- What is this?
- Your things left behind when you ran away with the CEO after ruining the company dinner.
- It's not mine.
- It's yours.
- That ahjussi left it behind, then.
- Who?
That site employee who always stands up for you.
I saw that he followed you and returned with this.
See? It's ointment for a burn injury.
He raised a fuss from the first time. There is something going on between you two, right?
There is nothing going on.
There is. There is.
- There isn't.
- Fine.
If that puts you at ease, let's say there is nothing going on.
Burn, Cut, Sunburn
Isn't he someone you knew?
No.
It seemed like he looked after you during the company dinner.
That's not it.
I don't know either. CEO personally hired him, like your case.
Then do you know his contact information?
There must be a copy of his employment contract there somewhere.
Employment Contract, Name: Lee Gang Doo, Address: Kyeonggi Provice, Moksan City, Mokdong Street, 41-2
You treat other people's unhappiness as if it means nothing, but you can't hold in your curiosity.
You're a bad person.
Kyeonggi Province, Moksan City
Welcome.
Please give me a bowl of noodles.
If you're here to eat noodles, just do that.
That strange song from earlier, who sang that song?
Don't you know Bulldog Mansion?
What?
You really don't know?
I don't know.
We will choose another company to do the ground inspection.
Choose the company you want. Then there shouldn't be any problem.
Since we know the problem, there shouldn't be any accidents.
I've heard there was trouble at the site. You look tired.
You can date a new woman.
However, don't let me see you with her.
- Yoo Jin.
- Don't sigh.
I must look laughable since I am clinging on to you.
So don't make yourself laughable anymore.
Are you going to be like this?
It's late. Drive carefully.
I didn't watch it on purpose.
Thanks to you, I couldn't meet the person I came to see. I came here in vain.
Look.
Pretend like you didn't see anything.
How can I pretend like I haven't seen anything when I already saw it?
Why? Are you embarrassed?
Mr. Lee Gang Doo.
Are you playing a game with the CEO?
I thought you were highly educated, but your'e dumber than I thought.
A man and a woman dating,
you lose if you like the person more and you win if you like the person less.
Even an ignorant person like me knows it's not like that.
Thank you for the drinks.
- Bye, Oppa.
- Bye.
By chance do you know Lee Gang Doo? His address is here.
No, I don't know him.
- Oppa, I—
- Excuse me.
Are you rich?
Pardon?
- I asked if you're rich.
- No.
Then follow me. It's expensive here.
Enjoy.
Do you live there?
No, I don't.
Your address was there.
- Then where do you live?
- Here you go with questions again.
If you're here to drink, just drink.
Aren't you drinking?
I don't drink soju. It's bitter.
I didn't come to drink either.
I came to apologize.
Apologize?
Belittling other people's unhappiness. Thinking that what matters are the things I am curious about.
Everything you said was correct, so I was uneasy all day.
I am sorry.
It was ridiculous.
You asked why I destroyed it.
Just to have their names engraved on that stone,
they croaked here. It seemed like they are asking people to remember such things, so I found it ridiculous.
That's why I destroyed it in a fit of anger.
Good job.
Ahjumma, beer please.
Let me ask you a question too then.
Then why are you curious about that?
Are you the only one who gets to ask questions?
You said it's violence forcing questions on people when they don't want answer
You're so good at using other people's words.
What was Bulldog Mansion?
You said you don't know.
I know now. They are singers.
They are not just any singers.
They are a great band. Yeah.
A funky band that was ahead of its time.
♫ Closer and even closer
♫ Love me
♫ Come closer to me
♫ Meeting you wasn't a coincidence.
♫ Closer, even closer
♫ Love me
♫ Come closer to me
♫ Meeting you wasn't for farewell.
Did you look into it?
He came to the site in person after seeing the advertisement from the hiring agency.
He signed a separate contact with Seo Won studio afterwards.
Fire him.
- But.
- I said fire him.
- You don't know?
About what?
Lee Gang Doo's father, Lee Chul Ho, is one of the workers who died at the site during the collapse.
Say it again.
He was an employee of the subcontractor who was charged with taking out the rebar, so he wasn't compensated for his death.
It was a decision made by the builder's section chief—
I remember it was a decision made by Director Jeong Yoo Taek.
I take back the instruction about firing him for now. Look into him a bit more.
Didn't you go home earlier?
What are you doing here?
- Noona.
- Yeah.
Are you close to Jeong Yoo Taek?
What?
Jeong Yoo Taek from Cheongyoo Builders. Do you know him well?
Why are you interested in a jerk like him?
I keep running into him. I need to know what kind of dirty bastard he is so I can decide whether or not to avoid him.
So why do you work there? You're quite something too.
So how is he?
There is a rumor that he's a family member of the Cheongyoo Builders owner.
What if he is? From the way  I see it, he's just a pitiful fellow.
Pitiful?
Can't you tell from how he insists on coming to my bar?
Compared to what he has, he has such a cheap taste.
Also whenever he sees me, he says lame things like how I look like his first love.
People like that, they are usually full of a sense of inferiority.
That means I shouldn't discriminate since I run a business.
It won't do you any good to get involved with him.
How can it be worse than how I am now?
What a naive thing to say.
Don't feel easy thinking you're at rock bottom.
You know that I like you, right?
Yeah. Everyone leaves after saying those things.
- Who was that woman earlier?
- Who?
Earlier. The woman you were appalled to find here and took out.
Who is she for you to care about her like that?
She's no one.
- You mean she's no one?
- No, she's no one.
Why are you smiling? What?
Seeing how you can't explain who she is. You must feel quite conflicted.
What are you talking about? You're overreacting.
We just need to wait and see if I am overreacting or I am good at sensing these things.
Oh, your nonsense. Seriously.
You want to rebuild the memorial.
I could demolish it myself. There is no need to hire anyone.
Since the contractor said it's not their fault and left, there is no one to take responsibility for it.
So, destroying it wasn't enough. You even want to rebuild it?
- If not, are you going to get rid of it?
- No, I won't do that.
That's what I am saying. The person who caused the problem even wants to solve it.
Please help me a bit.
I am not saying I will do it alone.
- Ha Moon Soo, if you pair her with me.
- Moon Soo?
You know better than me that I can't handle this alone.
It's not something I could decide on my own.
The budget needs to be approved by headquarters in order to proceed.
Headquarters.
Why Moon Soo of all people?
Just because.
Just because. She's the only person I know in this office.
Why are you looking at me with those eyes? It's the truth.
Please give me a call.
Are you looking for Unni?
You scared me!
Unni didn't come in yet.
What are you saying?
Thanks to you, I don't go to the site anymore, Ahjussi. Unni said she will handle it alone.
Ah-Ahjussi?
Why am I Ahjussi and she's Unni? I think we are about the same age.
Even though she may look older than her age, I don't think she's as old as you.
- How old are you, Ahjussi?
- Ahjussi?
- The steps aren't the only spot you do this.
- What?
Look ahead.
Why did you come here? Did you come to see me?
No.
We will see each other often from now.
It's freshly brewed.
Thank you.
It must be hard since the first deadline is kind of tight.
It's alright. I can get it done.
Haven't you forgotten anything? Don't you think you're missing something?
You didn't even know you left it behind in the car.
Oh.
Oh, right.
This.
It's your family's bath house, right?
Is the design for a remodel?
Lately, when we have time and money to spare. We are still quite short.
I liked it.
I want to see it. The building designed by you.
I washed your lunchbox.
Anyway, I was planning to submit the budget.
We are going to open the park first and we can't just leave it like that.
We can figure out later who should be held liable for it.
Who?
You know him too. Lee Gang Doo. My firm's site maintenance employee.
He's a security guard, just a mere security guard.
But there must be a reason, seeing at how you even called me.
Convince me why that job should be given to him.
What are you scheming?
What is this exactly?
- Don't you know how to read?
It's written he's the person in charge. Sign off on this.
This is at work. Speak properly.
Please approve it, Director (speaking formally).
- I don't want to.
- What's your reason?
Since I am in a position where I can reject such things.
Get out. Do your work.
- You should do your job properly, Oppa.
- Hey!
I've heard that 1/5 of the land for the commercial district building site is owned by someone else.
You didn't even properly sign the contract to own that land. Instead, you constructed a road and got the permit first.
That's my work. Don't meddle. Get out.
Don't think about saving pennies over small matters like this.
Please do a good job so I won't have to meddle, Director.
Hey! I said I won't approve it!
Why does it have to be him of all people?
Do you want to have dinner together?
Seaweed Rolls, Noodles.
I came to see you to buy something delicious.
This tastes better for me.
You're not asking why I came to see you?
You came to see me. I am sure you'll tell me.
I won't talk about work. It's past my work hours.
A mere security guard. There aren't too many people who'd speak to me like this staring straight into my eyes.
I like you.
I don't give counseling regarding dating life either.
Do I seem that low of a person to be talking to you about my dating life?
But I will listen to you. About 5,000 won ($5) worth.
I'd have to pay for my dinner.
Cheap.
But it ruins the mood. Nothing will change even if I talk about it.
Nothing will change.
But you might feel better.
If you had better qualifications, many women would have chased after you.
What the heck? Are you putting me down?
Do you think a man and woman can be friends?
It's something that could drive me crazy.
I'd have to hide my feelings.
If I want to see her close even if it means we remain friends. I can't help it.
If you don't like him that much, it's better to end it without a pretense.
It may not be a game, but it is true that the person who likes the other person more is at a disadvantage.
You are worth the price of the dinner.
But I didn't come here to kick back and talk about my love life.
Does Joo Won also know also
that your father was a construction worker who worked at the site. You have quite a story.
Are you two plotting something together?
Plotting what?
The CEO and me. The contracting company. You're a superior and I'm a subordinate. That's all.
Do I have to explain the fact that I'm trying to make a living?
Seeing your face, I guess Joo Won doesn't know it yet.
Let's grab a drink next time.
That means he likes you.
Why else would he bring you lunch?
On top of that, you said that great CEO shows his weak side to you.
That's the crucial evidence.
Why does our conversation take that direction?
Gosh! You're so frustrating. What's the use of him sending you signals? You can't decipher the meaning!
From what I heard from So Mi, the manager hasn't given up on the CEO.
Those two. They totally look great together. You're saying this because you haven't seen them together.
Of course, there's a woman by the side of a great guy.
But who cares? You can take him away from her.
Now, now. The CEO and I aren't meant to be—
Hey, you're always like that.
You pick someone to like who is impossible to begin with or you run away when the person starts to like you.
What do you think you're doing?
Drink it.
All right, fine. I'm tired, too.
How about my honey? Do you get to see him?
Who? Lee Gang Doo?
His name is Gang Doo?
That's nice. His name sounds tough. He's doing well, right?
Still the same. He speaks so rudely and does whatever he pleases.
But he's hardworking.
See? I'm good at judging people.
You get close to him first.
It's easy to get involved with a friend's friend.
He does seem a bit rough around the edges, but he seems like a good guy. Better than he looks.
But don't fall for him too deep.
If you fall for him after disliking him first, there's no cure for it.
Do all the way up to 100.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Oh, who's this?
I'm going to go in there first today. I can go, right?
Everyone, gather. I'll say one thing.
Twenty-six of all the collapse accidents that happen every year,
happen at construction sites.
Especially in the rain. There's rain in the forecast starting next week.
Before that, check if there are any sediment yield dangers.
Please check thoroughly and also check the drains.
Our lives. We have to take care of our lives ourselves.
Please keep that in mind. Fighting!
Fighting!
Aren't you going to eat lunch?
Aren't you eating?
I don't really like this kind of stuff.
Then, you should've said to go somewhere else.
You're the one who just walked in here without asking me.
How can you work at the construction site eating like that?
How about you? Why do you eat everything including even the pork slices when you're not doing anything physical?
You're always drawing something, measuring, and taking pictures.
What is it that you do exactly?
Building models.
What?
Building miniature models.
Ah, ones that look like toys.
Toys?
Look.
This is the 2D drawing of the building that the architect designed.
Can you tell?
This is 3D.
You still can't feel it, right?
No matter how you imagine in your head, you won't know until you build it.
There has to be a model like this.
You can find any risks while building or figure out any flaws in the structure.
Find out all the problems that can occur beforehand and decrease actual danger.
And you can find out the architect's intention behind the building—
- Is that why you're doing this?
- What?
Trying to prevent an accident? Is that why you're making it?
You could say that.
You're doing good work.
You're finished, right?
Since you're the only one who ate everything, I'm sure you'll pay on your own.
Instead...
This is too expensive. What's the difference between the price of a meal and this?
Just say thanks and eat it.
You should be able to taste something sweet like this in life.
Gosh, your taste. Not suitable for me.
I know I'm being rude if I asked you this, but—
If you know you're being rude, don't ask.
You can pass if you don't want to answer me.
There you go again with your questions.
How did you hurt your leg like that?
Last time, when I saw you in the alley when you got beat up, you had a huge surgery scar.
It'll melt. Hurry up and eat it.
- But why do you keep speaking casually to me?
- I heard we're the same age.
Who says? We are?
Who told you that?
- Which year were you born?
- You seriously ask too many questions.
Are you interested in me?
You always walk away first.
Speaking casually just because we're the same age. I don't think that's right.
Because someone's older, or your superior, or a sunbae...
Because the other person is a woman.
None of that matters.
The two people need to settle the matter. Are you listening to me?
Hey, Gang Doo. The new nightshift staff I hired can't be reached.
Let me ask you for a favor for one night.
If he can't be reached, you're asking me to work a day shift and night shift. A total full time.
Because of all the preparation to excavate.
Aigoo, I'm going crazy, man.
You said we're supposed to switch our shift every week.
It's only been three days since I became a day shift.
Fine, forget it!
Everyone cares about their own situation only. I'm the only one who worries.
Geez. What do I do?
You owe me one.
What?
Next time, take consideration for my situation.
Of course! Of course, of course! Thanks.
You picked on me last time saying people only care about their own selves, so why bother to help?
You helped my friend last time and came to my aid first when I was having a hard time.
Your words and actions don't match.
You talk way too much.
Aren't you going?
Over there?
You must feel good about life.
Why?
Shut up!
You're going to date her or something?
What?
I got the permit for the land, yet you couldn't find the landowner and couldn't sign a contract?
Mere several thousand pyeong (pyeong3 square meters)?
Well, we're looking for him—
To build residential homes, we changed the purpose of the property and even got rid of the altitude restriction.
Do you know how much money I poured into those jerks at the city planning committee and whatnot?
You think that's all? To make it look good, knowing we'd lose money, we built the road
and various infrastructure!
Who got the bid for all this business, huh?
- Your father, right?
- Yes.
My f***ing father-in-law!
I can't raise my head in front of my younger sister out of shame.
Hyungnim. It can get resolved.
We eliminated all the borrowed name account holders in line and the actual owner... We just have to confirm the person.
- There won't be any problems with the contract, right?
- Of course not.
The wasteland without any accessible road... We're willing to pay them way more than the market price. They can't turn it down.
Who's that lucky bastard?
Ten...
Scared me! You dork!
What brings you out here out of the blue? Are you exercising?
Good job. It doesn't suit you to be lying around sick, Granny.
Since you're out, you should be walking around somewhere pretty and bright. Of all places, here in this dark and gloomy spot?
You have no idea. When the snow comes down softly right here,
this is the most beautiful spot in the world.
I wonder if I'll get to see that again in my lifetime.
My knee hurts. My knee hurts. My knee...
What's the use of exercising? Quit smoking already.
Why do you think I'm exercising? So that I can smoke this for a long time.
I can't get a word in. Not a word, geez.
This kid. How rude.
You're trying to jump over a 50-year difference and be friends.
Are you allowed to treat someone who's going to take care of you until you go senile like that?
Is it my fault that I'm old? Why would you take care of me?
If you don't like that, exercise. I'll come by every day and check.
- Stop smoking!
- Oh, my gosh!
You jerk! Why did you throw that away?
What a waste.
I'm going to smoke it later.
- Granny.
- Huh?
You know how some say knowledge is power, but others say ignorance is bliss?
What kind of bulls*** is that?
I know.
What's right? When someone doesn't seem to know for real, should I let her know or leave her be?
Leave her be. Knowing that ignorance is bliss, there lies the power.
But still... Some people seem to live comfortably having forgotten everything. It's not fair.
Hey, how would you know if that person feels at ease?
It doesn't mean someone is in more pain just because he cries louder.
Stand up, stand up. Stop smoking and get up.
- Wait, wait.
- Aigoo...
Hurry up and stand up. You need to exercise.
I exercised too much. I can stop now.
Don't make me laugh. You're always sitting around.
Hurry up, move.
- C'mon, c'mon.
- Okay, okay, okay.
You don't like the girls?
If you keep rejecting them, it'll look bad for our girls.
I waited for you. It's no fun with other girls.
I'm expensive.
Expensive my a**.
Bring me a bottle of the drink I like.
Yeah.
Here you go.
What's your relationship with Lee Gang Doo?
Who?
How dare you try to trick me? You sent him to me to rip off money from me.
I didn't rip you off. I only received what I deserved.
Fine, forget about the past. Where has he been, that jerk?
- I don't know.
- Hey.
Don't hate him too much. Our Gang Doo. He did that because I told him to.
He does everything he can to make money.
He does whatever to make money. I like it.
He has a lot of debt. Money is something he's never had a chance to spend.
So, ignore him even if he upsets you.
When you mess with people who have nothing to lose, it doesn't end well. They want to fight you to the death.
Yeah, Noona.
Tomorrow?
Why?
You were going to demolish it. Why?
I don't know either.
Seeing how people are paying attention to you, it's making me pay attention, too.
To test you, I want to order you to do a job.
Go.
Is this the reason why you called me to come all the way here?
Then would I go to you?
You think time passes all the same for everyone, right?
Nothing in the world is fair, so don't be delusional.
Your time and my time carry a different value.
Aren't you leaving?
When will the display model be ready? We need it fast so that we can start selling—
It's more important to be accurate than to be fast.
Is excavation moving right along as planned?
To protect the incline, we do need some free land. If we're to meet the deadline for the construction—
Excuse me. The ground isn't strong enough in that area, the trench cut method—
She's an expert. Right?
She's quite an expert.
It's not like there are buildings in the area. The depth of field for excavation is shallow. It should be okay.
But still, we should stabilize the incline first—
Look. We didn't select the method just to shorten the time of construction.
The area condition, size, conditions of the ground. We did more research and evaluation than anyone else.
Each of us has our professional domain.
If problems arise, we'll take care of them. We're the ones who will take responsibility anyhow.
I understand that you're working hard, but don't cross the line for that reason.
A smattering of knowledge is the most dangerous thing.
Aren't you leaving?
We're all very busy people. Are you going to waste our meeting time?
I'm sorry.
Over what mistake?
It's my first time working on a project of this magnitude. I could be wrong.
It is a huge project, and Director Jeong's criticisms aren't wrong.
And you're not wrong either, Moon Soo.
The real mistake is just glossing over something when you have serious doubts.
Accidents. It rarely happens that bad people cause them intentionally.
Accidents happen when hard working people make mistakes.
So, you can't do this line of work if you're not confident about your judgment.
Ha Moon Soo, you belong to me. Don't be intimidated in front of other people.
What are you doing? We're meeting.
Go home first.
It was real.
What was? Me?
I thought I saw wrong.
What are you doing here blocking my way?
Just because... I'm going to rest a bit before going.
Go first.
You're down just because you were scolded.
You saw?
So you saw.
I keep on showing you a terrible side of myself.
Seeing you act like your life is over because of that type of thing looks even worse.
It's not that I look like a fool, I am a fool.
And everyone else is better than me.
It does seem like everyone lives well except for you, but if you go ahead, it's all the same.
Even the guys who seem to do well are stressed out behind the scenes.
Are you comforting me right now?
What? Are you going to feel touched by these ridiculous words?
Don't do that. It's every man for himself in life. Stay alert.
- We saw each other here before, right?
- I don't know.
- Why aren't you riding the elevator?
- That's nothing for you to know.
Oh right. But why did you come here?
Why are there so many things you're curious about? Do you really like me?
Wait a second!
Hey.
Why? What?
You live here?
Isn't your expression too obvious coming to someone else's house?
- I asked you to grab a drink and you said let's drink at home. Then, you bring me to a motel. Of course, it's weird.
- Oh, my goodness.
What did you expect? You're even weirder.
Let's set things straight. I didn't bring you here. You followed me.
Since we met each other coincidentally, while we're at it.
And my friend said we should try to get close to each other.
It's not cool. I think we have to put it in longer–
It's broken. If you get used to it, it's okay.
So you read these types of books. Are they fun?
I read them because they're fun.
Don't they always say the same thing?
That's why it's fun. Even if you get betrayed, there's one friend who trusts you.
Everything your teacher or mentor says is right so you only have to follow what he says.
If you work hard, results will follow. The bad guys will get punished.
That's nice.
- That's too obvious though.
- That's what's good.
The world sucks because you can't do what's obvious and simple.
♫  It's not longing, it's not regrets  ♫
♫  What could it be? This feeling that's coming on strong  ♫
♫  It grows when we’re far apart,  it comes back when we’re apart  ♫
♫  This excitement seems to be because of you for some reason  ♫
♫  I felt that, I flying on your eyes  ♫
♫  The time we were together, that day, I felt  ♫
♫  everything seems so great in this world  ♫
"Choo-goong-gwa-hyeol." What's that?
Through the blood passage, you're transferring energy.
If my energy runs out, I receive energy from nature.
When a pretty woman gets hurt, you take her clothes off for blood circulation and grope her to heal her and stuff.
It's that type of thing.
Hyung. You can't say that about the ultimate healing method.
This is something that's really dangerous for the person performing it too.
Because I'm giving you my energy, I have the possibility of receiving bad energy.
Not for the outward physical hurts,
but for the people hurt here on the inside, it's really effective.
There are 12 big different types.
Byeok-ta-go-jeung. Gui-geun-ahn-ma. Gwon-jong-ji-sa.
From a long ago, our hands were used very much as a healing tool.
What's right?
When someone doesn't seem to know for real, should I let her know or leave her be?
Leave her be. Knowing ignorance is bliss, there lies the power.
But still... Some people seem to live comfortably having forgotten everything.
It's not fair.
So you put your energy in your hand and heal other people with it.
I saw it all. Just drink it.
I drank too.
It's only evening, though.
Friend.
Wan Jin?
No. Just at the place of a friend I work with.
What about Aunt?
There aren't any customers, and I heard her husband caused trouble again.
She ran out as soon as she received a call.
That man is so consistent.
Seeing her hold it in when she calls him her enemy, they must really have a good relationship.
Would they live together just because it's good?
She's probably sticking with him because it's better to have him than not.
But I heard they're sweet on a general basis.
Geez...
There's nothing fun airing.
It'd be nice if we could switch channels like this in life whenever things got boring, right?
What would you do if you switched channels? You'd end up going to the first channel you were watching in the beginning.
Is that right?
You're right.
Was Dad sweet too?
Is that why you're not divorcing him?
That's just because I don't want to.
Why? Whenever you guys meet, you guys are eager to fight.
It feels like a waste.
If I didn't have him from the beginning, I don't know. It feels like he's being taken away from me.
Either way, I don't want to. Even if I told you, you wouldn't know.
They found her?
Is she okay? Is she seriously injured?
Honey. Honey, why aren't you saying anything? Honey. Honey!
You saw it wrong
Ma'am. Ma'am?
Ma'am, are you alright?
Wait, please help here.
Ma'am, are you okay? Ma'am, please try to get your head together.
Ma'am, can I eat all of this? Wow!
This is the best. It tastes so good.
Even if we're family, we can't feel the same emotions.
But I can only imagine that the sadness I felt losing my younger sister
would be less than the sadness a mother would have felt losing a child.
That's why the only thing I can do is...
Why are you like this?
Stay still. I'm giving you my energy.
He said it was choo something.
Well, either way, it's supposed to be a very good thing.
What are you doing? It's hot.
Stay still.
Why are you being gross like this? Go over there!
You really—
I'm crazy. I must be crazy.
I know it's not your business, but I'll ask you about it.
It's the bird's eye view of the memorial park.
I put a list of stone vendors that we deal with.
With this.
This is nice. There's nothing better than this flagstone for a tombstone.
The writing will be engraved clearly and it's strong.
We haven't decided on the design yet. How long would it take to produce it?
Are you going to make it different from the previous one?
That one is not that stylish and it looks too much like a tombstone.
Well, it is basically a tombstone.
Exactly. Who would like that?
If you want to change the design, it'll probably cost more.
Will something change just because you change the design?
Then what should we do? Give me your opinion then.
You're the one who volunteered for this, not me.
I am saying what's the point if you just make it pretty and engrave people's names?
Oh, you two don't know what you're talking about.
You don't erect this just to remember those who died.
The people who survived after sending their loved ones,
those who live on because they are unable to die. The memorial is for them to come and mourn as much as their heart allows them to.
We haven't forgotten them either. It's giving comfort to them through this piece of rock.
Well, what kind of hardship could you youngsters have suffered?
Please come to an agreement between the two of you first.
Supermarket
Making it so people can mourn as much as their heart allows them to.
I think he's right.
Did you see his hands?
His hands were like a piece of rock.
People who focused on one thing all their life, what they say is usually correct.
If you hadn't destroyed the memorial—
Don't do it.
What did I do?
Don't say "what if." There is no end.
What if I didn't go there? What if I hadn't done that? What if? If you start, there is no end.
♫ Closer and even closer
What are you doing?
What?
Why are you singing that song?
Can't I?
- You said you don't know it.
- I know now.
Don't sing it.
What? That's petty.
Are you trying to argue that you knew the song first?
I don't know. I am leaving.
What was that?
Now that you order a gangster around, does this place seem like it belongs to you?
You'll end up like your father if you continue. Be careful, Joo Won.
You're here? What have you decided?
Everything is pretty similar so I don't know. It's not like there is an alternative.
Don't try to make it different. It's a memorial.
What matters is the intention of those who make it.
At a place that won't stand out, classy enough to not draw criticism. That was my intention in the beginning.
It's actually better that we get to remake it. You two will be different from me.
You've worked hard. Please take some rest.
Yes.
CEO. You're a good person indeed.
We'll be different. Thank you for believing in us.
Dynamite
Mr. Technician. I almost fainted when I was digging the ground at Cheongjoo last year to build an apartment.
There were so many human remains.
There are rumors that here too, instead of dealing with it properly, they just covered it up instead.
- Really?
- Its unlucky. Let's go.
Are you done?
Yes, we're done.
Hey, since it's all set. Pull out up there.
Hurry and pull out. Let's get moving.
What are you doing? Hurry and move.
Are you scared?
That's what I am saying.
It would have been nice if you died back then too.
Seowon Architecture &amp; Engineers
Moon Soo. Moon Soo.
Get up. It's late.
Oh my gosh.
Let's go. It's raining so I will give you a ride.
Twenty-six percent of all the collapse accidents that happen every year happen at construction sites.
Especially in the rain, check if there are any sediment yield dangers.
He said he will cover the night shift.
I am leaving first.
It's not only 48 people died, but as many as 48 people died.
Ms. Ha Moon Soo, are you alright?
Didn't I tell you?
The crappy situation will come back anytime.
♫  Sunrise in your eyes  ♫
♫  Shines on your face  ♫
♫  We rise from the low  ♫
Just Between Lovers
I didn't even have time to drink water. Please get me one from the vending machine too.
I don't have any coins. I really don't have any. Hey.
I guess you had coins today.
♫  Dream in my eyes  ♫
Where are you now?
- I am in front now.
- Are you with Ms. Ha Moon Soo?
No.
How will you compensate for the lives of those who were miserable because they survived?
He's a thief who wants to take what's ours.
You need to take my side no matter what from now on.
Please do a proper job so it won't be embarrassing for me.
You go out more often lately.
I don't go out, I go out to work.
Be careful, Unni. It's perfect weather to fall in love.
Since a decent guy says he likes you, you're going to avoid him again?
It's not that.
Then what? You said he's a good person. What's the problem?
Because he's a good person.