Step back, step back.
Line up.
Everyone, line up properly.
Betting starts now.
I bet on number three.
I bet on number two.
I'm all in.
Bets are final.
First round of competition.
Begins now.
Shao Wanru versus Liu Fugui.
Start choosing shells.
When did you come back?
Just got back.
I went home, changed clothes, and took a bath.
Then hurried over.
You’re already competing.
Good thing I made it in time.
Thanks to Young Master.
Otherwise, Wanru would’ve lost this time.
She probably would’ve lost.
No need to worry.
I’ll win back whatever you lose.
Oh.
Young Master looks so relaxed.
I guess things in the capital went well.
Can you hurry up?
Picking a husband here.
Darn it.
Did I break any rules?
No.
Four.
Two.
Eight.
One.
Chosen.
Reveal.
Shao Wanru can not only guess if there are pearls,
but even the exact number.
She gets it exactly right.
She’s simply
amazing.
Nan County.
Lingyun Pearl House, Shao Wanru.
Wins.
Did you really come back?
So, how’s Hepu lately?
Hepu’s grain
is running out.
Even if people have pearls now,
they can’t exchange them for grain.
If this continues,
even winning the Pearl God Tournament
I’m afraid
it won’t help.
You sea merchants
can’t you bring grain from Jiaozhi?
Ship grain over?
You need to go to Jiaozhi.
No idea how things are with Rong’er now.
Hey, you rascal.
I’ve been looking for you.
Why are you here?
No.
Where are you going?
Don’t ask, there’s a surprise.
You could at least tell me first!
You’ve heard, right?
Shells from Linxia Village
all produce pearls.
Prices have skyrocketed.
Qingtian Village is in trouble.
No one wants their shells anymore.
Hey, what are you doing?
What?
You dragged me here just for this?
Patience is a virtue.
Just wait.
I...
If the Jiaozhi Pearl Envoy doesn’t arrive soon,
then Zhang Ji
will win by default.
She’s getting off easy.
Hey.
The Jiaozhi Pearl Envoy hasn’t arrived.
I announce
Nanguo Pearl House, Zhang Ji
The Jiaozhi Pearl Envoy is here.
Who said the Jiaozhi Pearl Envoy isn’t here?
Hey, here we go again.
Jiaozhi Pearl Envoy
Li Family Pearl Guild
Jia Rong'er
Have you forgotten
you're still wanted on the arrest warrant.
Guards,
arrest them.
Official Zhang
Long time no see.
And who might you be?
My voice...
Sir,
don't you remember?
Li Ling
Now everyone's here.
Official Zhang
Oh dear.
Official Meng has arrived.
What brings you here?
I heard
there's a wanted criminal at the Pearl God Tournament.
I was worried you might be short-handed,
so I came to help.
Do you need assistance?
Ah,
it's just one fugitive.
No need to trouble yourself, Official Meng.
What crimes have these two committed?
Nothing much,
just murder,
robbery,
and fleeing from justice.
Escaping arrest.
You're referring to
the Wang Cheng case of the Wang Family Pearl Guild, right?
Oh.
Official Meng,
do you
know this alleged murderer?
The Wang Cheng case was a major case in Hepu these past two years.
But after reviewing the files,
I found
there's no solid evidence.
Just because they were rivals,
and argued before Wang Cheng died,
Li Ling had a dispute with him,
doesn't make him guilty.
Isn't that a bit hasty?
If the biggest beneficiary
is the prime suspect,
then may I ask,
after Wang Cheng's death,
the Wang Family Pearl Guild was renamed the Nanguo Pearl Guild,
and all its assets went under the Prefecture's control.
So the biggest beneficiary
should be you, Official Zhang,
and your daughter, Zhang Ji.
So does that mean
the two of you
are the most likely culprits?
Then, Official Meng,
if Li Ling isn't the murderer,
why did he flee in fear?
When he returned to Hepu,
he kept himself hidden,
never showing his true face.
Replying to Official Meng,
I was in prison at the time,
subjected to torture,
and seriously injured.
They forced me, in that condition,
to marry Zhang Ji.
If I had consummated the marriage that day,
with my injuries,
I would have died for sure.
So I escaped.
I didn't expect that the next day,
Official Zhang
issued an arrest warrant.
I was inexperienced,
and afraid.
So I ran.
I didn't dare come back.
Even if I did,
I couldn't show my face.
That's
the whole story.
Official Meng,
so, Official Meng,
when you reviewed the files,
did you find
who really killed Wang Cheng?
Who is the true culprit?
The murderer who killed Wang Cheng
is still unknown.
But it is certainly not Li Ling.
I have reviewed the case files
and questioned the coroner who examined the body.
Wang Cheng was killed by having his neck forcefully twisted.
After that,
he was hung from the beam.
It was made to look like a suicide.
But Li Ling is just a simple traveling merchant.
He is not strong enough to harm anyone.
He absolutely lacks such strength.
As for Wang Cheng,
he died in his own room.
That day, Wang Cheng had an argument with Li Ling.
Everyone in the Wang family
already considered Li Ling an enemy.
How could Li Ling
enter Wang Cheng's room unnoticed?
Official Zhang,
do you not know
that the Han Dynasty Legal Code states
if there is any doubt,
one must not convict rashly?
Official Meng,
according to what you said,
I
will thoroughly reinvestigate this case.
The real murderer of Wang Cheng
must be pursued further.
They will be brought to justice.
Of course.
Husband,
it's been a long time.
Miss Zhang,
please behave yourself.
You lowly maid,
did you not announce the master's return?
This maid
spread rumors that day.
I kept her by my side as a warning.
What,
Miss Jia, do you have a problem with that?
You—
Ronger,
it's not the right time yet.
Official Zhang
I am the Jiaozhi Pearl Envoy.
Do I qualify to enter the Pearl God Tournament?
Of course, no problem.
Wait.
I withdraw.
I concede.
How dare you!
The Pearl God Tournament
is not child's play.
I thought the Pearl God Tournament
was just a simple bet.
I didn't expect it to be so complicated.
I concede.
Boss Zhu
You're really unfair.
I've lost everything.
That's right.
Are you all working together
to cheat us out of our silver?
Yes, losing money.
Losing money, losing money!
Quiet, all of you!
Anyone else wants to withdraw?
Step forward now.
Fengxian Pearl House
requests Official Zhang
to allow us to withdraw.
I concede as well.
Withdraw.
Longyang Pearl House also withdraws.
Approved.
Anyone else?
Official Zhang
The capital for Li Pearl House
comes from the Li family.
Lingyun Pearl House and Li Pearl House
are both owned by Li Ling.
So the two of us request
that Lingyun Pearl House and Li Pearl House
be merged for this Pearl God Tournament
into one.
Li Ling will act as the Pearl Envoy
to complete the competition.
Jiaozhi Li Pearl House
agrees.
Alright, approved.
Proceed with this change.
Let's continue.
Wait a moment.
Official Zhang
What is it now?
Since I've defended myself for so long
and am proven innocent,
shouldn't Li Pearl House
be unsealed now?
Approved.
Also,
I've been working hard outside for so long.
Shouldn't I go back
and recover a bit?
So I can compete in my best condition.
To show respect for the Pearl God Tournament
and for you, Official Zhang.
Li Ling, are you
trying to cause trouble for me?
Official Zhang,
my match with Zhang Ji
is the decisive battle for the Pearl God.
If it's rushed,
it won't convince anyone.
Don't you agree,
Official Meng?
Yes, Official Zhang.
The ownership of the Pearl God is important.
I think we should be cautious.
Alright.
Three days from now,
one battle will decide the Pearl God.
Hurry up and follow!