The first one is...
What's wrong with you?
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry
I'm f**king mad
I'm so sorry
I'm sorry
Today, you are joining the crew
Who is the first one to be caught?
Hello, brother Xia
Then, in the environment
is...
Yeah
Why don't you take a look at the film?
I'm a director of a TV show
And this is...
Come on, brother Xia
Come on
Oh, it's gone
Okay, you can have a look
It's okay
Let Wu Xin Yan introduce himself
to you
It's okay
You think this is the end?
No, we don't deserve to lose
We don't deserve to lose
I'm just waiting for their chance
and getting ready to be close
What's this?
I don't know what's this
It's a red flag
No, red flag
Today
It's already the first day
I'm going to warm up
I was out for a while
I was very cold
And you didn't see me
I didn't wear any clothes
I didn't wear any warm equipment
and equipment
I was really warm today
I was in the sun
We were all in the room
I didn't dare to come out
It was sunny and comfortable
And this side
I was resting
I didn't see this
I met this
I'm going to eat
I'm going to interview you
You let me
What are you talking about
You didn't eat the egg
I didn't eat the egg
I'm so bored
Then leave it
The bitter melon
What is that?
You don't like it
I'm going to film you
Teacher, we're going to film
I'm going to eat
What is this egg
I've never eaten it
It's so big
I want to eat it
I'm going to eat it
What?
I'm going to be a good cook
I can't give up
I want to fight for my life
You're so silly
You don't talk
Today
You guys saw the movie
Then the weather is nice
I won't be like you
Then
I'm going to be a good guest
The next episode
What is this?
I'm going to be a good cook
Are you done?
I'm done
Yes
I'm sorry
I'm finished
If you can't get the chance
Then let's chat
Actually we don't have
Those
Too
Very
That kind of drama
Because we are the kind of
Life is a little drama
Little drama
This kind of drama
So every day
Is
You are very disappointed
I haven't been to the movie
I went to see it when I was shooting
It's a good movie
I'm going to shoot the movie
The movie will be on the 5th
Everyone is there
It's a very difficult movie
There is a dance performance
So he's playing
He's running
I have been shooting for 5 years
Fortunately it's not that cold
It's cold
Basically what I do is
I didn't eat
I didn't eat much
I'm very tired
I'm very salty
I made it too salty
I ate two pots and I was soaked
It's a kind of
How about cooking
Noodles and hot pot
Then this
But there are still hot pot and barbecue
Is it coming?
I'm going to take a video
It's coming soon
Then you can take a video
You can