BASIC
OK, to see the second question
Let's see the clip first, OK?
That time
I say you that hope
maybe even
she would twist me
Private
Part external
Congresswoman
it is because
I don't want to be your concubine
I don't want to be living for you
I don't want to become a fear
Why?
Come back
Here you are
espacio
The story is too much.
Look, wait for her answer.
Stay with me.
This woman is interesting.
She's gone.
Why did she continue?
I really want to see it.
Don't stop.
Let me ask Jingyan.
Why did Yao Zijing
keep refusing Zhu Zanji?
Actually,
Yao Zijing
is a chef
in the city.
She wants to catch the market and love.
She can't catch the market
like Huang Taicun.
But I still have to
think about which side I want.
I want to let go of the love for a while.
I'll be there soon.
I'll be back sooner or later.
I'll do my job first.
I can't be promoted in the fashion room.
Qi just wants to trick me.
When I saw it,
when you were watching,
you kept saying,
don't.
Don't reject.
I was anxious.
If Zhu Zanji really gave up,
I wouldn't.
You've already gone on a diet.
You rejected me.
You must do it.
It's like this, Zhu Zanji.
You've successfully gained my attention.
You rejected me.
I want to get you.
That's how it feels, right?
Yes.
At this time,
there's a topic.
What is the role of career and love?
I'm a family member.
In career.
In my friends' mood,
what is the role of brotherhood?
Love is thicker.
Love is the first thing.
I think
family business is more important.
Work hard first.
Do your best.
But actually, this is not what I said.
For example, it's not good to be behind the stage.
Yes.
But what you're facing now
and the weight of your life
are currently with you.
Yes.
It's a stage.
If I take Love Playlist 3,
I won't say that I met someone.
I'll be together.
You're the fourth generation.
No such meaning.
It's just a serious problem.
Yes.
You see,
you're facing a situation now.
At present,
I just want to make the career better.
And I just want to stay with my family.
What's the point of a girl?
I think I've grown up.
Yes.
I'm the biggest.
You don't have to know yourself.
I suddenly feel that.
I really do.
I know myself.
Yes.
I know myself the biggest.
And then,
I suddenly grow up.
I feel like
I still want to stick to it.
I don't have a good relationship now.
At this moment,
I have something to do.
I just want to do what I can.
It's OK.
Last year, I didn't have a shoot.
I went home to take care of some family members.
I've been shooting.
I don't have time to take care of things.
I think I'm very satisfied.
You're another rich man.
Yes.
These are the things that people need.
I think it's great to be able to stick to it.
I think girls
might cherish it more.
Yes, cherish it.
OK.
Let's take a look at the third one.
OK?
It's also a question that the audience wants to know.
This question is asked by Wang Churan.
Does it hurt?
Look.
Tong Zhiran asked me to draw for you.
Come here.
Be gentle.
It hurts.
Don't draw.
I suddenly remembered something.
I have something to do.
I'm leaving.
It's so late.
What are you going to do?
I...
I'm going to get the food box.
Send the medicine in.
What is Su Yuehua and Yao Zijin's relationship?
Big confusion.
I'm so cute.
So, ask Chu Ran.
What do you think of Su Yuehua and Yao Zijin's relationship?
I think she's a domestic and a foreign person.
Because I'm actually more interested in Zijin.
A person who hurts himself.
Why do you want to keep him by your side?
So, I think
I'm not very familiar with Zijin's values.
So,
how do you think
the friendship between the three of you
should be maintained?
I think, first of all,
don't think so.
You should believe that you're the best.
And you won't
get cold because of others.
You should have this confidence.
And I think
try to balance
the relationship between the three of you.
Find some other people who are not suitable for you.
Take care of your feelings.
I think it's easy for girls
to be happy and buy things together.
And discuss
what to wear.
I think it's easy for three or four people to talk at night.
I don't know if the relationship between girls
and boys is easy.
I think it's straightforward.
I think boys are very straightforward.
Whether it's good or not,
or if there's a misunderstanding,
we can solve it very quickly.
I think boys have their own way of thinking.
If we play together,
we won't be forced.
If we can't play together,
then it's fine.
It's natural.
If we love each other, we play together.
And the character of the two of us
who are not suitable for each other
will be like this.
But we will never mention
the two sides.
Yes.
And the three or five group of boys
are quite normal and comfortable, right?
Yes, they are.
Girls are also dependent on the word.
Actually, if you have a girlfriend,
you can tell her who you like.
The word is also a word.
What is the magic of
being friendly between girls?
It's easy to talk to three or four people.
There won't be any pressure on good relationships.
Just say it.
Okay, let's see what Wang Yizhe's
question is.
What is his question?
See how you are rejected.
You are good at rejecting two people.
What do I mean?
No matter how you reject her,
she still can't tolerate you.
Now you are here.
Why is she so fierce?
You seduced me.
Really stubborn.
A stubborn girl.
Now you only have to be clean.
You rejected me.
Thank you, Mr. You.
How to thank?
What do you want?
Blood.
Don't be cold-hearted.
Really.
Can you ask why the You Yi Fan likes
Yao Zijin?
And why are you so stubborn?
Because they have a history.
The Internet world.
And then maybe I think
Yao Zijin is a very good person
in You Yi Fan.
So I want to protect her more.
I know.
Because I think You Yi Fan is very clear.
She is a person who loves and doesn't get.
She has no choice.
Her identity is not able to
really get Yao Zijin.
So she actually didn't say
that she has to force her to be with her.
Or what?
It's just a way to protect her.
I think.
She hasn't forced her.
That's all.
But you are very stubborn.
Have you ever had
You Yi Fan's vinegar?
I don't think so.
I have a good one.
You also trust her.
But I haven't seen
her two times.
She's always behind the kitchen.
She's always in the box
when she's peeing.
She doesn't know.
I don't know.
You only know.
You can see it, right?
It's nothing.
You can eat the whole day.
Okay.
Let's take a look at the next part.
It's about Rui Xian.
Let's take a look at Wei Xia.
It's called the assassin.
Ziping, the assassin Yao Zijin.
After the top, I'll tell you.
Is it that important?
The assassin.
It's important.
It's very important, right?
Very important.
He scared her.
Bye.
See you in his crew.
What happened?
These fruits.
cómo di las placed?
She's very cold.
This fruit.
If you want to kill me, why are you so nice to me?
If you want to blame me, blame yourself.
You're a killer.
You shouldn't be so kind.
I'm just a fool.
Kind.
You can't be without a bottom line.
You can't be a bad person.
You can't be a good person.
You're a killer.
Kind.
You can't be without a bottom line.
Let's ask Ruixian.
What was the mood of killing Yao Zijun?
Actually, this part
is a challenge for her.
She can't be sure about her ending.
After that,
her ending
is actually a very clear direction.
The most urgent point is here.
Maybe she can't understand
her growing environment.
She's been under pressure
and she's been working on her only mission,
which is survival.
Maybe she'll think about something else
for others.
It's a survival problem for her.
Maybe Zijun thought
I was trying to kill her
because I was on the top.
But she was so famous
that she was kicked into the palace.
She was found out
that if she were to die,
her family would probably die.
So, it's a very difficult decision for her.
It's a very important point.
Yes, a very important point.
Because Zijun and I
had some feelings at that time.
She knew Zijun was very good to her.
So, it was very difficult for her
to make this decision at that time.
I can see that
this part
is considered a heavy-headed drama for a woman.
The internal conflicts and various
things were revealed.
How did Yao Zijun
treat this friendship at that time?
At that time,
when she was shooting me,
I thought, Zijun, what's wrong with you?
Did you drink it?
I can't believe it.
You just have to move it.
What's wrong with me?
I'm drunk.
Then, when I was lying down,
I felt that it was true.
I just couldn't believe it.
You really want to kill yourself?
Because I don't know her.
I don't know what's wrong with her.
I just can't understand her behavior.
But at that time, I didn't tell you anything.
I didn't tell you to confess.
I didn't protect my life.
I want to live on.
Ask her about the other thing.
Yes.
Kindness must be at the bottom line.
This is very cool.
Is there really a friendship between the competitors?
I think so.
There is a friendship between competitors.
I think it's the same.
It can be saved together.
Yes.
OK.
Actually, we want to dig it.
We're afraid that we'll dig out the plot behind it.
OK.
In this part, I'll answer it next.
Everyone is
very interested in knowing some tricks.
Including the questions that
many people have asked just now.
Everyone wants to know some questions.
First of all, thank you for answering.
We are looking forward to
the characters of the plot.
We are also looking forward to
more wonderful plots.
I want to tell you here.
I want to know the members of the membership.
To use the public forum.
To meet the offline meeting.
To have more members' full-time activities.
Everyone must lock down
Mango TV's membership channel.
Mango TV's membership open day.
Live activities.
Come and follow us.
Next, we have a question.
We want to test
each other's understanding of each other.
Let's test our upper group.
Actually, we have already
asked the question and the person
to confirm a good answer in advance.
Next, please draw a thousand questions.
Let's answer them.
First, I want to tell you that
the green one is He Rui Xian.
The purple one is Wang Chu Ran.
The blue one is Wang Yizhe.
The yellow one is Xu Kai.
The red one is Wu Jinyan.
Next, if you want to draw,
just ask yourself.
You can draw two.
Two are different.
OK.
Let's draw two each.
I'll draw the blue one.
I'll draw myself.
Let's draw the green one.
So I'll draw...
The green one is He Rui Xian.
I'll draw a red one, too.
Yes.
Why do you draw three?
I don't know.
The yellow one is Wu Jinyan.
You can choose two.
Then the green one is He Rui Xian.
The blue one is Wang Yizhe.
I'll draw the green one.
You draw it.
The yellow one is Wang Chu Ran.
The yellow one is Xu Kai.
What color are you?
I'll try the blue one.
You can draw your own one.
You can't draw your own one.
Yes, you can't draw your own one.
You can leave it to others.
You can't draw your own one.
I get it.
OK.
Can I open it?
Yes, you can.
Let's draw one by one.
OK?
Let's see who is the first one.
Who is the first one we draw?
He Rui Xian.
Who do you think is the biggest difference
in the play?
You should answer this question.
I'll answer it.
You're so cute.
No.
I'll ask He Rui Xian.
Who will answer the question?
He should say Wang Chu Ran.
Because they have more time
in the upper class.
And I think they are very happy
every day.
I think they are very happy.
Yes.
Wang Chu Ran is different from
what he thought.
OK.
Let's see how much
the crew knows about the play.
Let's ask Rui Xian
to answer your own question.
Yes.
I'm the one.
Because I'm with Yin Ziping.
I'm the one who does the work.
Because my staff
is always scolding me.
They say if you have
half of Yin Ziping's career,
you'll be happy.
That's why I wrote this.
So your answer is
you, right?
OK. Let's see the second question.
Who do you think is the best?
Kai Kai.
Kai Kai thinks
which play is the sweetest in his drama?
The sweetest.
It's not the most impressive.
So you can say...
Let me guess the scene.
It should be in his study room.
I know which one.
Yes.
It should be in the play in the bathtub.
And the bathtub.
The bathtub.
The flower.
What happens in the bathtub
and the study room?
What happens?
It's very sweet.
Do you think so?
It must be
some very...
High-performance scenes.
Or the scene of sugar-coating.
You're so innocent.
Why don't you find the sweetest one?
Then I can't say it in the play.
Let's see.
Our Kai Kai
will tell us his answer.
I forgot.
I forgot his answer.
Oh no.
What's the slogan?
I think the sweetest one is
the one I brought you.
I like the slogan.
Okay, it's the slogan.
The slogan.
What's the question
that Kai Kai touched?
Fujian thinks
his signature move
in the play
is...
What's your signature move?
Cut vegetables?
That's too much.
He didn't mean it.
Because he's the kind of
muscle reaction.
He's the first reaction.
Yes.
You're the one who's the reaction, right?
I can guess it.
I didn't see the answer.
Yes, I know.
You can't even remember your answer.
I can guess
what your brain said
is so boring.
Really.
I can guess that he said that.
Cut vegetables.
I thought
my body
was the one who cut vegetables.
You can't think of anything.
His favorite move.
I can't think of anything.
Heart has a soul.
Yes, Kai Kai.
Kai Kai is good.
He's not satisfied with his performance.
I think so.
Let's see the second question.
Who is the most black-skinned
in the group of the top ten?
I think
we can know this.
Four people
suddenly got up.
I'm afraid that
I'll have a lot of black-skinned people.
The answer that Kai Kai gave
is...
It's not me.
Give me a certain answer.
Don't say it's not me.
I think it's me.
It's over.
Yi Zhe.
No, it's not you.
Really?
Who?
Jinyan.
It's me.
But I have to say that
it's not black-skinned.
I think it's a cute moment.
Because I have a lot of
competition with Jinyan.
So I often
shoot some of our work
or photos.
I remember that
I was in the photo shoot.
I went to see him.
When I was shooting my specials,
I went back to watch the video.
Jinyan was
staring at me
in the video.
I was very angry with that expression.
Then I sent it to him.
I think it's cute.
Yes.
I didn't expect it to be me.
There are more cute moments.
Okay, let's take a look at
Jinyan's questions.
Okay.
The first is Wang Chu Ran.
Who do you think
the crew of the show
is not doing?
It's me.
He Weixuan.
Because you eat
very seriously in the photo shoot.
I always arrange
to eat the name of the food I eat.
Will he eat the props?
He will eat it.
Will I eat it?
Every time it's delicious,
you tell me.
You taste it.
I say you taste it first.
Every time we have lunch, dinner, dinner,
the food in Yuexian is very rich.
Yes.
The whole tent is mine.
Let's announce the answer, okay?
Yes.
They are in Yuexian.
They can watch the show.
The second question.
If the crew of the show
opens a food shop,
Xu Kai will arrange
the old way
for the previous staff to promote the sales of the service.
Old way.
The boss will do it himself.
The previous staff
will do it himself.
The business is good.
Because there are five roles,
we have five here.
Okay.
We will arrange one for each.
The previous staff.
One.
The one who is handsome will come to the guest.
Yes.
I will be the guests.
I think
I have been
drinking tea and giving water to him in the old way.
I am a little nervous.
I have done everything.
I think I'm still okay.
The promotion.
The one who we can see
is very popular.
The promotion is like a book.
He talks so fast.
The promotion and sales are great.
Wang Chuan, the promotion and sales in Yuexian.
It's not related to the show
So the last answer
Xu Kai, do you need to announce it yourself?
I'm the boss
And the sales
We only have two men
The sales is for men to run everywhere
And the remaining three positions
You can choose the songs you like
You have arranged it, right?
Or you forgot the answer
I'm the boss
Let's see
If He Ruixian can bring something like modern
What will he bring to Yin Ziping?
Can help him
Always go forward
Always beat you
Bring something
Bring a wifi
Bring a handkerchief
I was just pulled up
I'm going to die
Bring a fish string
But it's related to the character
Yes
Can help me
I'm a professional
A good knife
So this answer is
You are very
It's like a random answer
Let's see
Let's see if Ruixian can announce it
Bring a Chinese vegetable dish
Don't use your own imagination, right?
Yes
Let's see the question
Wu Jinyan is trying to say something in the drama
What?
It's OK
Right?
You know me better than me
What do you eat?
What do you mean?
I'm confused
What?
Yes, I'm not good at it
I think it's more suitable for me
You wrote it with your own imagination
It's different
It's so convenient
You wrote it
You don't like to say it
You don't know how to say it
She can say it
Yes
It's delicious
It's so beautiful
It's fun
Let's see
We have Ruixian
If Suyuehua can experience it again
Which character will she choose?
Which character?
You won't choose me
Yao Zijin
Choose Yao Zijin
You can choose
You can choose Yao Zijin
Is the drama so small?
The drama
The drama is too small
Open it
Who wants to think?
Meng Shangshi
Why?
It's possible
It's open
Open it
The highest power
The most important thing
Sister Ming
I don't want to be a mother
The highest power
Let's announce it
The emperor
Zhou Gaochu
Yes
Because the crown prince is more light
And I usually have a heavy mouth
I think he eats
Every time he gives me food
Then it should be
A bite
Yes
It's a good thing
You can eat it
A bite
My dad
Let's see the second question
The second question is for Yizhe
If there is a bottle of bitter melon water
Who would Yizhe want to give it to?
What is this question?
Bitter melon water
Life is already hard
I think he wants to give it to Xu Kai
Who wants to give it to him?
He took your hand
I think it's reasonable
Right?
Yizhe, you should announce it
Who did I write?
Yes, Su Yuehua
Right?
It's already very bitter
Because many times Yuehua
Will be more bitter
Then it will be easy to get on fire
Then bitter melon water
Bitter melon water is to get on fire
Although you drink bitter melon water
You can get on fire
Good health
Don't be so angry
Women are very bitter
They are scared to live
Right
Thank you for sharing
I think we know each other
And we are happy
I know from your answers
In the drama
You feel that the relationship is very good
You got a lot of support from the last show
Mango TV members and fans
So today
We will prepare a lucky gift for the fans
This team is all thanks to you
Now we will play a small game
The winner
Can send the lucky gift to our members
The lucky gift
After watching the show
The tofu feast will be very impressive
So we prepared a delicious tofu
Each of you should play a game
There is a chess
So when you play
If the chess is in the game
Your challenge fails
Then you can win
Win the game
Are you ready?
Okay, the tofu is ready
Come on
Come on, each one
Let's start from Yizhe
Okay, start the challenge
Look at Yizhe's first spoon
It can't be broken
I tell you how much you eat
Oh, right
I eat it myself
You are cute
You are so cute
This is so dangerous
You dig it
You are very dangerous
You eat it and say
You dig it
You are so naughty
Come on, look at the table
I'm afraid that someone will fall first
Right?
Let's see who falls there
I should give the girl a little bit
Let's see
I tell you to dig it
Just dig it out
The circle of the eyes
Right
I'm standing in the right place
There is still a little bit left
It's not broken
Just say that I'm this side
Just a little bit
It's broken at night
How can you buy this
The quality of the beans is good
No, the boy eats a lot
The girl is so naughty
It's broken
I can't see you
He's still
He's still eating it all
It's stuck on the top
No, it's not
Isn't this under the wall?
No, it's under the wall
From this
Yes, Chu Ran
You have to continue eating
I have to continue eating
It's turned out right?
Yes, we can make it bigger
I think you should be able to make it
So sad
I'm so sad that I didn't eat it
So regretful
So you see
When Chu Ran played the fifth spoon
We just failed, right?
But the happy thing is our doctor
Our Xu Kai
Our Jing Yan
Chu Ran and our Rui Xian
Win for everyone
A lucky gift bag
Congratulations
I wrote it directly
I'm so sad
Obviously, we'd be fighting
Itadakimasu
Our aunt
I've lost to my sister
She's so good
I'll take дети
for now
So congratulations to our doctors, Xu Kai, Jing Yan, Chu Ran and Rui Xian
for sending us a lucky gift
So we will send out a lucky gift
to all our members
I hope you will take our lucky gift
and bring it to everyone
Here I want to remind you
Mango TV's director will be with you to pursue the show
Today we will be in the hotpot
Thank you for your love
We will be giving you a gift
Xu Kai and Jing Yan will give you a delicious special milk tea
Let's go to the milk tea shop
The milk tea shop
The milk tea shop is over
Let's cheer up
I'm so happy
I don't know what kind of milk tea Zhu Zan and Yao Zi Jin will make for you
I'll try first
OK, try it
OK
Who will you make the first cup of milk tea for?
This one
Is this for you?
This is for Zishu
So what's the combination?
Zishu and you
Brother
What's this?
Bo Bo, Golden Pearl
What about this?
This is red beans
Yan Dong, make a black tea, OK?
What's this?
glutinous rice
I'm also an old man
Snow glutinous rice
It can't be clouded
Don't put it down
OK
Wait
What's the key milk tea?
It's a small amount
I don't know how to drink it
It's OK
It looks very appetizing
Two cups of milk tea
No price
It's for you
It's called Zishu and you
Zishu and you
This is Zishu and you
It's for Yao Zi Jin
OK, it looks delicious
No price
Promise me you must finish it
You must finish it
I want to make one too
You can't attack the enemy
This one
You should make it more
Brother
You take this bowl of milk tea
No
Yutou and Yuyuan
I think it's enough
It's done
All the Yutou is made of Yutou
It's called Yuyi and Yuyi
Yuyi and Yuyi
Yutou and Yuyi
It's delicious
You can't make it next time
You really want to say this
Wait
It's ready for you
I'm making porridge
8 steamed buns
I don't know who can get this
Shurong
I think it's for girls
Girls can't eat so much
Wait, I can't open it
OK
Thank you
It's for the brother
I can't believe it
No
Don't be so honest
Oh my god
What kind of feeling
Sweet
Very sweet
I feel the sweetness of the brother
The friendship is here
I think what Jinyan made
It looks delicious
You have a round circle
It's round and full
Here you go
Thank you
Yuyi
I hope it's better
Thank you
OK
Our Zhu Zhanjie and Yao Zijun
All the milk tea for everyone
Right?
Actually, today
We have three people here
This is the three lucky members
who have been nominated for the Mongolia TV channel
They have prepared some questions
Let's invite three lucky fans
Welcome
Yes, a little nervous
Come on
Come in, OK?
OK
Welcome the three lucky members
and fans
Welcome
You seem to have prepared some questions
to ask, right?
Everyone knows
that you two have had a cooperation before
So in the cooperation
do you two have any small tacit understanding?
It's just
very
OK
Let's talk about it
Actually, our second cooperation
will feel very
It's not necessary to go to the Mongolia again
And we can directly
open the communication
You don't have to talk very much
or just keep talking
It will be a very fun
Actually, we are very familiar with each other
So the tacit understanding is also very high, right?
Yes
Actually, our Jingyan and Xu Kai
also prepared three milk tea for the three lucky fans
They also made their own adjustment
for the first cup of milk tea in spring
for the three lucky members
OK?
OK
It's a pity
There is one more
It's warm and very sweet
OK, we have sent our spring milk tea
I hope you can feel it
warmly
I hope you can continue to support the food, OK?
Thank you
Please support the food
OK
OK, the last one
is the first time
we have been together
as the first time of the last time
Let's take a family photo together
OK?
Come on, please give us your experience
Last time, the red and red were on fire
OK, today's meeting
is here
I hope everyone can remember to lock down
our Mango TV
and support our last time
As I said, the last time
will be the red and red were on fire
So, happy pursuit
and keep watching
and tell everyone
the last night's small photos
will be updated every Monday and Sunday
And the last time
will be busy
every Monday and Saturday
Of course, also help Zhen Ji and Yao Zi Jin
to surprise us
and we will wait for you to watch
So, you must lock down
our Mango TV
That's all for today's show
Then, we will see you next time
See you next time
Bye
This is the last time
Remember to watch it
Hello, everyone
I am Xu Yutong
Xu Yutong
Yum
Yummy
It is Guin novel
Didn't cook for me
It's cooked
Your auntie
You were pasta
or …
Mastic
It's really delicious
Nervous
Energetic
Birthday