The world is full of love and passion
The whole world is full of love and passion
The game is a little bit complicated
There are some short and short mistakes
Oh oh oh oh oh Oh oh yeah yes yeah yeah
The game is a little bit complicated
denome
It's also a matter of self-sufficiency.
If you really don't care about it,
why did you send the medicine?
Who sent the medicine?
I've never been here before.
I've never sent any medicine.
If you keep talking nonsense, I'll be your witness.
Episode 1
Your Highness, the perpetrator is a dead man who has been training hard.
He only left two alive.
The patient is badly injured. There is only one left.
The doctor is taking care of him.
As for the records of the attack on the day of the last day,
hundreds of classes, 500 million people,
Ministry of Public Affairs and the Ministry of Internal Affairs,
all of the soldiers,
totaled 643 people.
The staff are registered on the side.
The tea is still in the room for 10 days.
What do you think?
Your Highness, the real murderer is a dead man who has been trained hard.
If His Majesty and Crown Prince
I dare to say one thing.
I can't get rid of the two princes.
Enough.
Don't always bring these things up to make you sick.
Your Highness, the lunch is here.
Where is he?
He is still outside.
Your Highness, the hat.
Minister Mei, the last time that happened,
I was so anxious to find a chance to apologize to you.
Did you personally make the meal for me?
I see.
The meal was made by mistake.
I can't afford to save it.
I hope you can forgive me.
These are enough.
Your Highness, you are not going to put more food in the soup.
If you don't put too much food in it, it will be too much.
Minister Yao, how do you know that you are not sleeping well?
The lunch I sent over, you didn't finish it.
You only finished the soup of the He Zao Ren.
You are now doing it for the sake of peace and prosperity.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, you don't need to worry about the court affairs.
You should just rest and recuperate.
Your Highness, I dare not to reveal these things.
Minister Mei, please listen to me.
I just entered the door and I could smell a bloodstain.
Your Highness, you are so pale.
Your voice is also much better than before.
You should not be so loud.
Yes.
It seems that I can't go to visit my mother today.
So as not to be disappointed.
I feel good today.
Come.
Your Highness, do you have any dirty things on your face?
You are just like me. I will definitely misunderstand.
Either I am a very strict and arrogant person today.
Your Highness, you are finally smiling.
You always smile when you enter the door.
Since you entered the door, you have not said anything.
I thought that you were guilty.
Young Master, are you married?
Minister Mei.
Let's go.
Your Highness.
The imperial physician has already said that
he will not let you get up.
But you can't listen to him.
This is good.
The wound is open again.
In order not to make the Empress worry about the wound,
you even let others become the hero of the old family.
What's going on?
But where are those people who are so arrogant?
Go and bring my books over.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, the imperial physician has come to deliver the snacks.
He asked for your instructions and brought them in.
When did I tell you?
Let him in.
Yes.
Greetings to Your Highness, Your Highness.
Your Highness, the lunch is almost ready.
I have some snacks for you in the dream.
Your Highness.
The wait coming.
What is the news on this morning?
The things that are happening now.
I just want to inform you that
the army that sent me theダ både statusQu is very very special,
which is always involved in this situation.
So nice of you.
You will get scared otherwise.
I will protect you even if you leave before tomorrow.
OK.
Or maybe it's ok.
I told you not to be too polite.
You're injured.
Thank you, Your Highness.
No.
I want to thank you.
I'm a servant of the Imperial Court.
I dare not take the crown prince's life as a thank you.
You've protected His Majesty for me.
You've taken the responsibility as a son.
You should thank me.
But...
I'm just a servant of the Imperial Court.
I've been punished.
I hope you'll forgive me.
If you're so kind,
I'm not here to see you.
I'm here to kill you.
I'll reframe this role.
Chu.
His Lordship.
Did His Majesty agree
that Your Highness would usesta confirm
and punish the gap of struggle for
ausa gene
?
The whole house
I'm a father.
I can't bear to see you anymore.
But I came out to visit you
to see you.
Really?
Of course.
Lord Liu.
Your Highness.
Forget it.
I'll talk to you later.
I'll see you off.
Why is Eunuch Liu here?
Lord Liu,
answer the call.
Greetings to!
Your Majesty 어 throne Master you
are a mess.
Lord He,
I dare to make my announcement.
I'm afraid that you will be hurt.
I can't help you.
Fengzhe, you go first.
Congratulations to you, Lord You.
You got the blessing.
You won the gold medal.
I heard that even the crown prince is here to visit.
The emperor of the Crown Prince
has given a single iron fist to the palace court.
Even if you are so evil, you will be punished.
But the emperor's reputation is well-known today.
Lord You's blood will not be left.
Really?
I'm just kidding.
Why are you angry?
The gold medal is kept by the emperor.
I forgot your promise.
Don't worry.
It's not poison.
Go.
What's wrong?
Don't move.
Don't do anything.
You are young and ignorant.
I always hope that I can meet
someone who can hurt me.
But I didn't expect that.
Today,
I will take the blame for the accident.
I will be more lucky than you.
I will wait for you.
Young master.
Young master, wake up.
There is a criminal woman in the palace.
She is the one who killed the emperor.
Who is the criminal?
She is the criminal.
I've been dealing with a criminal.
As for what crime she committed,
why is she there?
How long will it take?
No one knows.
I'm curious
how someone would be involved in this.
And why she's so fond of it.
So I'm a little bit surprised.
I want to see
what kind of person she is.
I'm so happy to see you.
When I found out
there was such a fool in the world,
I thought
no matter what crime she committed,
I'd let her go.
What happened was losing
the murder of Zongz
I didn't believe you could believe me.
No.
It is beside the table.
Let's have lunch first.
Lord Mei.
Please.
Your Highness, I'm sorry to have made you wait.
I thought it was a joke.
I didn't expect you to be so considerate.
I'm the one who's prepared the food.
I'm not afraid of the food.
Your Highness.
Is the news of the Grand Preceptor?
Your Highness, then.
Your Highness.
You have dropping orders to send edict for Lord Mei.
He insidiously won't say a word.
Lord Mei.
I saw the news,
that one person was lovesick.
She wasn't coming back.
That person was!
I'm afraid.
It's really nothing.
not full.
Not when you pass them on secretly.
With fully mobilized content.
This dish is like nothing.
Lord Mei.
This is a squeezed lotus,
use jade salt,
flour,
and sealed.
Tilting up the Tina and~!
Ah.
Jesus?
에게 Alt turnerاء
I'm starving.
It's you.
What are you writing down?
What do you want to write about
intestine donation
sent by Eitherh Level?
The days ofaber
I should make 뚝兰
a large stream of blood.
During the whole days
Song Dynasty
has Jordanais
Let's go out.
Yes.
Why are you standing there?
Go outside.
Put some on.
Take it out.
Slow down.
What dish is this?
This one.
This is the braised pork.
The braised pork can smell the meat of crab meat.
You have to talk to me.
Your Highness.
Have some hot tea.
Have some.
Lord Mei.
You must not make His Highness drink.
What?
Are you angry?
It's all my fault.
I was too hasty when I made the same dish.
By the way,
I heard that you are good at cooking.
I have something to tell you.
Lord Mei, you are serious.
Just tell me.
I...
Your Highness.
His Highness has been ill recently.
How can he be in a daze?
Your Highness, let's hide in there.
Your Highness.
You are a good cook.
I think you are not well.
Lord Mei.
You are in a daze.
I remember there is something urgent.
Please tell His Highness that I am guilty.
I am leaving.
Lord Mei,
you are still not finished.
Come again tomorrow.
What are you doing?
Go inside.
Mount Fang.
Lord Mei, please wait.
Be careful.
Don't run.
Catch him.
What are you doing?
Give it to him.
I heard that you are in the palace.
I have been carrying the money bag with me.
This is the palace that the Ninth House should give you.
You are too young to do that.
I am afraid that you will be useless and have a bad luck.
I have been helping you.
I am sorry.
I have been standing for you.
Now, you are safe.
I am leaving.
Your Highness, please have a meal.
He is still ugly.
In this state,
Prince Philos balloon
still loves me very much.
Give me a break.
Goodbye.
I've never felt too much of it.
Yes, I forgot.
He's kind.
When you want to listen to the piano,
someone will play it for you.
Take him out.
Yes.
Deniu
S 만들is
Eunuch Chen.
What was His Highness going to help you with?
Lady Yao,
I don't want to esper a mom over you.
So I'd like to ask you
if you like the piano.
Xiaolian,
why are you still here?
That's brilliant.
How is it that your love for him keeps us under circulation?
So much love forott.
It belongs to me.
Your princess.
I氣 you.
Is she hurt?
Not at all.
How did she hurt?
Did I hurt your heart?
What did I do?
I've been on your side since childhood.
I'm sorry.
It's not my words.
You'd better change.
Your Highness, I've asked you
to send you back personally.
Please.
Eunuch Cheng,
what did I do?
Please.
From now,
I prefer to be respected
than be почsted by others.
As for me...
I won't stand for it.
Stop it.
Let me hug the standards.
Don't try to do it.
I feel lucky
because I won.
What is this?
Every day is an violate.
Imperial Physician Sheng will be in your care.
She will value the oppression.
I listened to my Queen Mother.
I'll go now.
I failed repair it as soon as time ago, but I've improved.
Give me back a hand!
Let's find a new buy...
So you're not先 cutting or cutting?
What are you talking about?
I will make a name for myself.
I will be the eldest son of the Ming dynasty.
You.
This word is used in the purple tree.
But it's not correct.
Please.
Give it to me.
I don't know how to draw.
But this painting is so detailed.
It can see the depth of the other person's love.
Who can be touched?
I'm not touched.
You are a good iron master.
If it's me,
I will leave some red and green gems.
The mother and the cat.
So I won't leave any old stones.
What is this?
Ying Ziping.
This wallet is for men.
Whose is this?
Zijin, give it back to me.
Tell me.
Give it back to me first.
Who is this man?
Tell me.
Give it back to you first.
Give it back to me first.
I will tell you.
Give it back to me.
Whose is this?
Zijin.
Give it back to me.
Okay, okay.
I will give it back to you.
Whose is this?
Give it back to me first.
Okay, okay.
Give it to you.
Be gentle.
Give me your hand.
You are dead.
Then go home.
When they arrived,
they had come all the way here quickly.
But that man's figure was ill-fated.
Do you still remember it?
Earlier, when I was eight,
my grandfather personally took the lead for the bleed
into battle against 505.
So he was one of the還 Bangs.
Yet His Majesty believed so stern.
The same people had work with someone else and
had no right to exert their efforts,
saying evils in the pain of death.
Yes.
No problem.
Thank you.
Very nice.
Please have a meal.
after the news returned,
I'm sure.
Run as Ifsu förow Consensus.
Around two finalement Dou dánkaları
sent the policemen from
Red've poison
who are heavily injured.
Let's start first.
He is also a good man.
Qin Daduo also
wants to neden
control the вопросы of
to send her out.
Mقتian and Xinyan
brought her to Yufeng.
She must have different Zhou pourquoi.
She poetically wants the world the same
as the country.
Especially to the family.
It will go in vain.
You won't get used to it.
By the way,
I forget that
you are so good.
Why would she say you?
Your Highness,
what do you mean?
Aren't you leaving the palace?
You want to let me go?
But, Your Highness...
I have my own way.
It has nothing to do with others.
You didn't frame me.
But why?
I haven't seen you smile so happily for a long time.
At least, she can make you smile.
In the future,
you'll be rich and rich.
You'll be happy.
I wonder if you'll remember
this book.
Or will you remember me?
Who is the person
you're talking about?
Let's go.
Or I'll regret it.
You want to marry me out of the palace.
Even if you're a good person,
you're not my sweetheart.
Who is your sweetheart?
It's not true.
Your Highness,
the stone-cutting knife
is made of
the skin of the sword
and the skin of the fat.
The person who died
after the blood was cut
was the best.
I'm not a good person.
I'm the best.
I know you've been
in a bad mood recently.
You can use it.
It's good for your wound.
You still say you don't care about me?
Your Highness, you misunderstood.
It's the imperial physician's prescription.
We're just
taking care of the wound.
Your Highness, the imperial physician knows
that your wound is not healed.
He's already taken the medicine.
The effect is the best.
He's the one who sent the medicine today.
This medicine
is so old-fashioned.
I told you to prepare the medicine.
But you asked me to give it to you again.
I'll take my leave.
Li.
You can leave.
Yes, Your Highness.
You don't want to say
I won't force you.
Anyway,
I can't resist you for a few days.
I'm going to go to Nanjing soon.
Your Highness.
Don't be too hard on me.
This is my father's name.
It's the crown prince's fault.
It's obviously my father's intention to do this.
Why is it my fault?
You're in a good mood.
You should let go of the past
and show your sincerity to His Majesty.
You think I've never tried it?
But every time,
my father has rejected me for money and gifts.
Maybe
you've used the wrong method.
You did a good job.
Fang Nian Shan.
Can I go to Song's today with you?
Yes.
You're so good at this.
A little bit of a good-looking man
would like to live in Qianqing Palace.
Why don't you leave?
Su Su Shan.
I'm in a bad mood today.
I can't go to Qianqing Palace to deliver food.
I just want to help Fang Nian Shan.
It's time for delivery.
Here you are.
Your Majesty.
The dessert is from Nansong Lin'an City.
It's made of ginseng and sugar.
People often call it abalone.
So the dessert is called abalone.
It's really good.
It's so good.
I'm a chef of the dried quail eggs
in Huoshan.
It's refreshing and appetizing.
Of course I know.
It's the flavor of the hometown.
The name of Nanjing Restaurant is
Ju Hua Nao.
It's used as a soup.
You've been
doing a lot of business lately.
You're so good.
Last time, I was reckless.
Please forgive me.
Father.
Your Majesty, be careful.
It's all my fault.
I won't blame you.
It's okay.
Please forgive me.
I'm grateful.
I heard the doctor say
that you were injured from the hospital.
His Majesty was shocked.
He was dizzy all the time.
That's why he thought
that the dried quail eggs
could cause dizzy and headache.
That's why he was afraid of the doctor.
Did he scare you?
I was really scared.
I was hiding in the corner
and was shaking.
Then I saw Noble Consort
was also by her side.
That's why I gave her a breath.
Hurry up and save her.
Save her.
Go.
Your Majesty.
Noble Consort Guo wants to see you.
I'm not seeing you.
Yes.
It's time to go to the court.
Send the dinner there.
Send it there.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
You're going to the south capital, aren't you?
Why haven't you got ready?
I've prepared the dinner.
Let's have dinner together.
No need.
Your Majesty.
Who is it?
Crying and laughing for a lifetime.
I'm lost.
I'm looking forward to
the beautiful things in the legend.
The light in the dark night is like the moon.
The light in the night is like the moon.
I hung out with you andヲ together.
Waiting for you.
Leaving now, leaving for이를.
code one meeting more often.
The What's My Baidu excited
Is there someone,
Just thinking about it.
I'm not afraid of you.