Previously, on The Season.
Welcome to The Season!
The season...?
Short for the boating season.
Where Hong Kong royalty
decides who of us ascends
and who is stuck here.
Sounds like a lot of work.
This is not work. This is war.
Christopher's family
practically invented colonialism.
And Fiona's old Hong Kong money
that bolstered the empire.
And I'm here
to get more of their business.
I'm a summer's associate,
but I'm hoping for a summer position.
- You must be new to Hong Kong.
- First time here.
Niki, my lovely wife.
Madeline. My niece.
She moved to Bali after...
Well, you heard the rumors.
Stop.
This summer is a chance for you
to show us all what you really are.
And he's single.
I'd like you to join the social committee
at the Harbor Club.
Your auntie's the chairwoman.
I hope Carrie brings you
to the races next week.
We've got surprises in store.
Someone here
has been looking into my past.
- We just need to find out who.
- I like your earrings.
They're just the nicest
thing my Dad ever gave me.
Vroom! Vroom!
You like the car?
I've got a very special
gift for you.
These belonged to your grandmother.
Wow!
You can wear them
when you're all grown up.
Yes, sir?
Right away, Mr. Hext.
I'm fine.
I want to know more about you.
You started a new job.
Uh, you're working
for a financial advisor.
Carrie Shen.
She has one of the most prestigious
summer associate programs.
Sounds like you can learn a lot.
Carrie advises some of the most
powerful families in Hong Kong.
This is about the Hexts.
Isn't it?
Carrie was my way
into their world and it worked, Ba.
I've been invited
to their private box at the races.
Cola.
I don't know what you're planning,
but you must stop.
You don't know these people.
I've been studying them for years.
We can still fix this.
There's nothing to fix.
All I want for you is to have a good life.
Christopher Hext tore our family apart.
- Cola--
- He framed you
and robbed me of a father.
I can't just let that go.
You must.
No.
I'm gonna get close to Christopher
and clear your name
and then take the Hext family down.
Soft with your hands, Alison.
Oh, look at her.
I knew this was a good idea.
My girls are happy, I'm happy.
Keep your shoulders up,
Alison.
You look great out there.
It helps to have such a great horse.
Beautiful.
This one's fine,
but you know what's finer?
Having your very own race horse.
Really?
We flew her in from Ireland.
Every Hext has had a horse.
Your mother thought it was time.
Thanks, Mom.
This is really cool.
And that's not all,
your horse is qualified
for this week's race at the Sha Tin.
We're having a party at the Jockey Club.
Isn't that exciting?
So the horse isn't really for me.
Of course it is.
The whole party's for you.
Fine.
Then I want to invite Madeline.
I doubt she'd be available
on such short notice.
I'll make sure she knows you want
more family time this summer.
That is what you said.
Right, Mom?
- Your daughter has a point.
- Hmm.
I've gotta go.
I'll see you later.
Madeline can come, but for the record,
she was the one who left us.
Now, what should we name your horse?
Whatever you want.
♪ Don't need no clap back ♪
♪ Just let them yap back ♪
♪ Yeah, oh, somebody's got the need
to critique about my everything ♪
♪ Best believe ♪
So, still wanna be a lawyer
like your Daddy?
I wanna be a doctor.
They help people.
We help people too.
But you don't save people's lives.
Fair enough.
You have a good day at school, okay?
And if your mom works late,
I'll come pick you up myself.
That's okay. Desmond is picking me up.
Who's Desmond?
She's fucking someone else already?
No, nobody said that.
I'm sure he's just a friend from church.
Oh, right, right. Yes. I'm sure she's
screaming, "Oh, my God" a lot.
Repeatedly.
Hey, hey, this is good, dude.
Now you don't have to be
such a sad boy all the time.
- Get your dick sucked, you know?
- You think I should start dating?
That is not what I said.
But I think it's time that we put
this eligible bachelor thing to use.
- Oh, "we"?
- Yeah--
- Can we please focus on the boxing?
- You need a wingman, dude.
Someone to heroically console
all the unhinged hot women
you leave in your wake.
I have to download an app, don't I?
- Okay, enough. Stop. Switch.
- No--
What?
Just leave it to me, okay?
I'll find you plenty of hot young babes.
Oh, Andrew. You're getting a call
from FWD Life Insurance.
Oh, yeah. Nice, nice, nice.
I need to take this. Thank you.
Hello?
Is this about my life insurance policy?
What's with the flowers?
Are you trying to get caught?
No, I'm trying to get laid. Is it working?
I can make myself available later tonight.
Or how about right now?
I've blocked out some time
for white collar knockout training,
so, uh, you know, I could get in
another little cardio session.
Oh, tempting.
But I have that social committee
meeting soon,
you know, the one your
very charming wife invited me to join.
Why would she invite you?
Hopefully, just to rile up Fiona.
Well, that is one
of her favorite past-times.
Still. Just call in sick?
Andrew, these are my people.
Or, you know, at least
they used to be.
I'm just gonna show up,
I'm gonna play nice,
and I'm gonna avoid giving them
any more reasons to talk about me.
Or we could spend the morning--
Sorry! Your policy's denied.
That was cold.
Hey, Bonnie,
any idea what Carrie's meeting
with Mr. Hext is about?
Um...
Business.
I'll see you
in a couple days.
Mr. Hext! It's great to see you.
Cola. We met on your yacht.
Right.
Well, I hope you enjoyed yourself.
I did, I was wondering--
Your ambition's admirable,
but that is not how things
work in Hong Kong.
Christopher's my client,
my relationship.
I didn't mean to overstep.
I'm sure.
Lunch?
This place is gorgeous.
The Harbor Club is the only place
to be seen during The Season.
Nikita's family pays a fortune
to upkeep it.
But with these views, it's worth it.
Uh, Caesar salad and grilled octopus.
Are you okay to share?
That meeting with Christopher
looked tense.
He's officially decided
to sell the Percy.
Why?
Hasn't it been in his family
for generations?
Who cares?
It's all a game to these tycoons.
All I know is I want the deal.
I'm sure you'll get it.
And I'd love to be part of the team.
We need to put together a pitch.
Before the races.
Which reminds me,
come by my place, I'll lend you
something appropriate to wear.
I never told you what I'm wearing.
You didn't have to.
What's her story?
Oh, Madeline, you came.
Somehow managed an invitation.
Let me give you the...
Tea?
Oh, yes, please. Thank you.
Madeline?
So good to see you.
Does it mean you're back in Hong Kong?
Just for a few days.
I love Bali.
Beaches, Botox, boys.
It's a perfect escape.
- Shall we begin?
- Yes.
Our top priority is to find
a celebrity emcee
for our charity
white collar knockout event.
Unfortunately, Eileen Chen
is no longer a viable option.
- Oh, why? What happened?
- Oh, honey, haven't you heard?
Scandal with a scarlet S.
She was caught cheating
on her husband with his brother.
- Ouch.
- Can you imagine?
The drama.
It's the worst thing she could
have done to her husband.
Well, not the worst.
Chablis. And bring the bottle.
When Madeline married Thomas
it was the talk of the town.
He was twice her age, newly divorced,
and Christopher's best friend.
- And Christopher was okay with that?
- Encouraged it.
He's always had a soft spot for Madeline.
Even more so after Thomas' disappearance.
What happened?
Boating accident.
Or not.
If you believe the rumors.
Moving on, we need to decide
who's gonna give the opening remarks.
Anyone?
I vote Fiona.
She's highly respected
and she always delivers.
Madeline, why don't you do it?
Me, give the opening remarks?
Hmm, you've always been a good speaker.
Madeline is a good speaker.
But perhaps someone who's name
inspires less speculation
would keep the focus on the cause.
Oh, my God. Just say it.
You don't want me speaking
because of the rumor. Fine.
You wanna know the truth?
I did it.
I killed Thomas.
I made him take out the boat,
I stocked the bar up,
and I polished the deck
so it'd be extra slippery.
Then I told him I miscarried. Again.
Just to be sure that he drank enough
so he'd fall overboard and never be found.
It was just a long con
to gain your sympathy,
so I could get invited
to this prestigious committee
and make the opening remarks
at your important fucking party.
Wow. Didn't know it was lunch and a show.
Running? Again?
That's not fair.
I don't deserve to be treated that way.
I told you before.
Leaving would only make things worse,
but you don't listen.
Now, if you really wanna salvage
your reputation,
come back to the table and behave.
It's good to be reminded
where your priorities lie.
I like it when it's quiet.
But it's not so quiet, is it, Jon?
Benny had a visitor in prison.
I'll have a name soon.
I can't have the past
muddying this family's future.
Timing could hardly be worse.
The police and court records are sealed.
Yet, still they're looking.
Meaning they're leaving a trail.
I'll find them.
Call Nigel.
Tell him we need to meet.
Hey, Carrie. I'm running late,
um, visa appointment.
Uh, I'm just at the embassy now.
It was awful.
The look on their faces like I
set fire to their Louboutins.
Are you gonna focus on this or not?
Sorry. Continue.
Hang on.
I think my leg's numb.
Look, by this time next week,
you're gonna be
on a beach in Bali doing yoga.
Like, who cares what the tai tais think?
More flowers?
Not unless they're from your dead husband.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Madeline!
Sorry to just drop by,
I was here for a meeting
and remembered you staying here.
Uh, how did you know
what room I was in?
The Percy's your uncle's hotel.
I figured you'd be in the penthouse.
Clever.
Doesn't explain what you want.
I saw you and Fiona at the Harbor Club
and you looked upset.
I know we don't know each other well,
but I'd like to.
We could grab a boba and talk?
Oh, I, uh...
Unless I'm interrupting.
I'll meet you in the lobby in five.
And we drink coffee in Hong Kong.
Were things always this tense
between you and Fiona?
Not always.
We were quite close when I was younger.
What changed?
I grew up.
Started making my own choices.
She never wanted me to marry my husband.
Optics, you know.
And what does Christopher
think of all this?
I'm curious as to why
you bring up Christopher at all.
Unless that's why you're really here.
I wanna get close to him.
He's an important client
and his endorsement could help
in Carrie extending me a full time offer.
And you think cozying up to
the grieving widow is the thing to do?
I think it's something people here do.
Well, you're not wrong about that.
Everything here is a play.
I appreciate your candor.
Only those excommunicado
can speak the truth.
Look.
You have to play Christopher.
Everyone wants something from him.
If you are going to stand out,
don't chase him.
Find a way to make him come to you.
How?
You're a clever girl.
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
♪ I'd like to show you the leaves fall ♪
Strategy...
♪ And pick you apples so red ♪
♪ I'd like to take you to my house ♪
♪ And have you sleep on my bed ♪
Are you spying on me?
Don't flatter yourself.
They make a great Cobb salad.
Oh, yeah, that looks very,
uh, Instagramable.
So is your date.
Yeah, uh...
Andrew set her up and, uh,
she's already asking me about Birkins.
What does she need a Birkin for?
Probably to store all the other bags
she want me to buy.
Try a Kelly then. Much smaller.
Is that personal or a professional
financial advice?
Both.
Well, from one friend to another, then.
Cheers.
David, I...
I'll see you at the races.
Yeah.
I completely and utterly froze.
He saw me sitting all alone
during The Season.
No.
Well, at least you know
he's ready to date.
- You can ask him out.
- Absolutely not.
Take the lead.
You have the power to control
your own happiness.
What a very American concept.
And let's not speak of it again.
We've got a winner.
Now to complete the look.
Oh, Carrie,
you've given me too much already.
Besides, I got in.
I got invited back.
Getting in is one thing.
Staying in,
that's the challenge.
They're beautiful. Thank you.
Just don't lose them.
They cost more than anything you own.
Darling, we don't have much time.
Right.
You seem distracted lately.
Only by your beauty.
And the mistakes I made last year
when you were sick.
A few bad investments.
Selling the hotel will cover our debts.
We've talked about this.
I know.
Has something else happened?
No, I think I'm just
getting in my own head.
What's important is that you're better.
And now you are,
you should tell Alison.
About the cancer.
When the time is right.
You're ravishing and radiant.
Ready to go?
Honestly, I don't know
if I have the stamina
for all the pomp and circumstance.
Welcome to the races!
Everyone, take a good look,
as we'll soon be placing our bets.
Though, the only winner is this beauty.
Bred from champion bloodlines,
I knew the moment I laid eyes on her
that she belonged in our family.
Spirited, intelligent, and headstrong.
So naturally, I named her Alison.
Oh.
Mrs. Hext.
The horse is still adjusting
to the humidity.
We should pull out.
Alison is racing and she's going to win.
Dad, did you know she was going to do--
And the bar is open upstairs
so have a drink,
but please, congratulate my daughter.
It's a good name.
No, he's not confident
on that one.
What do you mean? It looks fine.
Have you got any favorites?
I'm thinking number 10?
- 10?
- Worldwide Handsome?
Mmh.
Small, unimpressive pedigree.
So-called fighter, scrappy underdog
that everyone's rooting for.
Not you, I take it?
No, we don't bet on losers in Hong Kong.
My money's on King Hong.
The stallion with the biggest ass.
That was classy.
Uh, I was gonna put my money
on Blueberry Luck.
Small ass, but mighty.
Hi, Carrie.
Dear God, Christopher must've invited
every wealth manager in Hong Kong.
Yeah, I heard you're all
glad-handing for the Percy bid.
What else have you heard?
Just that if you get it,
your business will finally be cemented,
and that I wanna buy it.
So maybe there's a deal to be had.
What sort of deal are we talking about?
Well, you give me the inside scoop,
I swoop in and close quickly.
At a below market rate.
Bingo.
Madeline!
You came.
Only to see Alison. The horse.
I can't believe my mom did that.
Giving you a choice you didn't take
seems to be a family tradition.
I need a drink.
Thinking of placing a bet?
No, I left those to by husband.
He and Christopher, they used to take
these boys trips to Vegas every year,
until Fiona found out
how much they were losing
and put a stop to it.
Hey, why don't we go to Christopher
and get him to place a wager?
Reminisce?
It's not a good day.
See Alison's odds?
That means no one's backing their horse.
Fiona can't be happy
and if she is in a foul mood, well,
you can bet Christopher will be too.
They don't look upset to me.
Trust me. Fiona is fuming.
Yeah.
He's at the pub?
Don't let him leave.
Thank you.
- Hi, how are you.
- You know my name?
Yes, your friend told me your name.
Okay, um.
How would you like to go for a drink?
Okay.
Something on your mind?
Just the jewel of Hong Kong.
Oh, the Percy.
About that, I took a look at your bid.
$800,000,000 is a respectable
valuation, but, uh,
Goldman say they can
secure a billion, so...
Respectfully, it is not about a number,
it's about the partnership.
You wanna pitch me? Be quick.
Before Fiona realizes
you're breaking her rule.
One billion is a tempting valuation
if the goal is to watch what your family
worked so hard to build
become another heartless hotel chain.
You need the right buyer
to understand its value.
So your pitch is sentiment?
No. The future.
Christopher, the Percy is your legacy.
Let me represent its sale
and I'll make sure the hotel
is preserved as the landmark it truly is.
Okay.
I'll give you a shot.
But I still want a billion.
Mike. Good to see you.
10,000 on Alison.
You'll find me at the party.
My name is Madeline Wong.
Miss? Miss!
I was having a pint
when your friend dragged me here.
I felt this required a personal touch.
Benny's had a visitor in prison.
I need to know who.
I've been out of the game a long time.
That may take a little cash.
Maybe more than a little.
22 years ago, you helped me resolve
an unfortunate situation
and I rewarded you generously.
A home for your wife,
a flat for your mistress,
luxuries well beyond a cop's salary.
I'd tread carefully.
Unless you want a different type
of visit from Jon.
48 hours.
I need a name.
And if I can't?
Then you're of no use...
To anyone.
Where were you?
You almost missed Alison's first race.
Well, I'm here now.
Madeline Wong?
I'm looking for Madeline Wong.
Oh, I'm Madeline Wong.
Oh, no, but I didn't--
Who'd you bet on, Madeline?
Um... number one.
Alison.
Stop it, did you really?
Is this the first bet on number one?
And it's a big one.
Mom, did you hear that?
Madeline bet on our horse.
Well, it's an excellent pick.
Alison is a fine competitor.
I have no doubt she surprises all.
I figured I was due for a windfall.
I'll put a bet on Alison.
We're gonna bet on Alison right now.
Count us in too.
What?
No! What about King Hong?
I can't decide between
Baron Winmore or Blueberry Luck.
Both sound like champions.
Or losers.
Your date seemed nice.
I'm pretty sure
Andrew paid her to talk to me.
No judgement here.
So, how'd it go?
Maybe I'm just not ready
to get back on that horse.
Or maybe...
you just haven't picked
the winning horse yet.
Saw what you did for Madeline and my wife.
What I don't know is why.
Madeline wanted to make
things right with her auntie
and when I saw a way to help,
I took it.
Seems like quite a lot of effort
to go to for someone else's problem.
I grew up without my dad.
And my mom,
she resented having to raise me
on her own.
It was like she gave up on being a mother.
On me.
I've always envied families like yours.
Who love each other so fiercely.
Fiona and Madeline just needed a nudge
to see what they have.
So how
can I return the favor?
I'd like a one-on-one with you.
I wanna learn about you.
About how you grew this empire.
The network.
The people you keep close.
Well, as I'm sure you can imagine,
this season's quite busy,
but I'd be happy to sit
with you in the fall.
I'll have my assistant reach out.
How about a bet?
What are we betting?
If my horse wins,
I get that sit down
with you this week.
And if I win?
Your drink's on me.
Very well, young lady.
You got yourself a deal.
My pick is Baron Winmore.
What horse are you backing?
I always bet on the underdog.
Worldwide Handsome, huh?
We'd better get back soon.
To watch the horse
stumble out of the gate?
How desperate of Madeline,
placing the bet.
And at the club?
Tears in all the right places.
And the shaky voice.
Hmm, it was theatre.
Ladies, who are we talking about?
No one important.
I'm so sorry you had to hear that.
Tiffany was completely out of line.
Why are people so quick
to believe the worst of me?
Maybe...
it's because they trust the source.
You know who started the rumor?
No.
Tell me.
Who?
I'm a huge fan of yours, I'm so happy
to be able to see you.
- Me too.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for inviting me.
- Our pleasure.
All right,
ladies and gentlemen.
The tension is palpable here
at the Sha Tin racecourse.
The horses are making their way
up to the gate now.
Look at the focus.
The energy in each stride.
It's a strong field today.
Every horse is sharp and ready.
Now for our top competitors,
will it be our favorite, Baron Winmore,
claiming victory once again?
Or will the crowd's favorite underdog,
Worldwide Handsome,
pull off a stunning offset?
And they're racing!
Right out the gate Baron Winmore
takes the early lead.
But then a surprising turn for newcomer
Alison is right on his heels.
And look at Worldwide Handsome,
he's coming up fast from the outside.
Blueberry Luck right behind him.
It could be anyone's race.
We're halfway down the back stretch.
Alison, who started off strong
is losing steam
she's fallen far behind.
But Worldwide Handsome
is closing the gap.
Baron Winmore is ahead in front,
but Worldwide Handsome takes the lead.
And it's a neck-and-neck race
between these two stallions.
As we reach the last hundred yards,
it comes down to this.
Baron Winmore is starting to pull ahead.
Worldwide Handsome makes the push.
He's nudging forward.
It's anyone's race!
Baron Winmore pulls it out!
He wins! The champ is victorious!
Oh, what a race!
All right, that's it.
Well, at least she finished the race.
Too bad our horses didn't win.
They beat Alison, though.
I think I would've beaten
Alison on the back half.
So, now that you're running
the hotel sale,
I... guess we'll be working
together a lot more.
I always thought we made a good team.
I did too.
- Take me out.
- I'd like to take you out.
It's settled then.
Where would you like to go?
Surprise me.
I see how you did it.
Yes.
I'll give you that one-on-one.
Tomorrow. 11 AM.
I'll send a car.
Thanks for having me
at such a lovely event.
Even if you didn't win.
Horse me's just getting her stride.
Hey, do you mind if I
borrow your mom for a second?
Mm-hmm.
I appreciate the bet you placed.
We will of course reimburse your losses.
Did you start the rumor about me, Auntie?
How could you accuse me
of something like that?
You're right.
I apologize.
I shouldn't have told you that I knew.
But I've made a decision.
I'm not going to leave Hong Kong
until everyone sees the snake
that you really are.
Bye, I'll see you soon.
What was that about?
Committee meeting questions.
I won't bore you with the details.
Well, at least the two of you are talking.
And how about you?
Would you like to share where you
and Jon Kim disappeared to earlier?
A matter that is being resolved.
How enlightening it is
to be kept in the dark.
Can I stay here with the horse?
Just get in the car.
Carrie.
Cola, what's this I hear
about you meeting with Christopher?
I know Christopher's your relationship.
It was a spur of the moment thing.
I don't wanna cause any problems.
It's fine.
You got your in.
Carrie--
Just don't mess this up.
I won't.
This is the most important thing.
Do you have it?
Nigel got an address off the visitor log.
How do you want this managed?
No loose ends.
Understood.
Someone's toying with us.
Vroom, vroom.
Vroom! Vroom!
Little Dragon.
Police!
Benny Li, stay down.
You're under arrest for the murder
of Wong Chi Min.
Mr. Hext is expecting you.