[Truth or Dare - Episode 21]
[Third Young Master Rescues Wife]
Elder Brother Situ!
- Princess?
- Just now, I saw someone following you.
You should be careful.
Thank you, Princess.
Older Brother Situ?
What are you doing?
Let me go immediately!
So stupid. After everything, you still don't know who I am.
You and Wang Biao are colluding with each other.
You rat.
Do you want to live?
As long as you answer a few of my questions, I'll let you go immediately.
I am the princess.
You actually dare kidnap the princess. You're audacious and have no care for the royal laws!
Let me go immediately!
Since I dared to kidnap you, I obviously have some backing.
Who exactly is the Night-Spirited Hero?
Speak!
I will never tell you.
Tell me!
Who exactly is the Night-Spirited Hero?
Don't waste your energy. I won't tell you.
Why did you come? Leave quickly! Don't worry about me!
He can't touch me. I am the princess.
Night-Spirited Hero.
Let's see how capable you are in daylight.
The resentments between us have nothing to do with her.
First, let her go.
Let her go?
How could I? Only when she's here,
will things be more interesting!
You really are a shameful thing.
(T/N: He is literally saying "You really shouldn't be seen in light", usually used to describe rats or criminals)
Let me see your real image.
Let him go!
Some people are just greedy.
You clearly already live and own the general's manor...
Don't move!
Yet you still want to be the venerable hero that thousands look up to.
Is this the person you like?
From what I see, he's just a villain as cowardly as a mouse!
What about me isn't up to par with him?
You're not up to par with him anywhere!
At least, Third Young Master Mei would never take advantage of the misfortunes of others.
All I know is that the winner takes all and the loser gets nothing!
Here and now, whatever I say goes.
Kill me or torture me as you like,
as long as you let her go.
Third Young Master Mei is the romantic type!
Let him go!
However, you're currently on the brink of death.
In the future, the princess—
Don't move!
In the future, let me
- take care of the princess!
- You dare!
Situ Lin, if you dare to kill Third Young Master Mei,
your death won't be far away either!
What?
It was not easy for me to capture him. How could I kill him so easily?
I want to torture him.
That would be satisfying.
You psychopath! Madman!
You hypocrite!
If you have the capability, just kill me!
Neither of us will die.
I am the person who loves you the most.
I am also the person who understands you most.
I'll give you one last chance.
I can spare this rascal his life.
But in the future, you have to become my woman.
If you let him go...
Don't believe him.
Speak.
Speak! Speak!
Just kill us. Kill us
and we can be together for eternity.
You ungrateful brat.
I am going to kill you.
I am going to kill you both!
I will have you all killed!
Are you okay?
Wanzi! Wanzi!
Get better quickly.
As long as you get better, I'll never get mad at you again.
Really?
You're awake.
You're finally awake!
I'm not dreaming, right?
I'll go find Old Six right now.
It's fine.
I saw Yama just now.
(T/N: Yama is the god of the underworld in Buddhism. Seeing him means you have died.)
I told him there was someone I still couldn't let go of in this world.
He said "Fine."
"Since you are so handsome,
I'll let you live for a few more years."
Are you dumb?
Is this a time for jokes?
Wanzi, I've thought it through.
As long as you want to leave here, I'll send you off even if I must use my life to do it.
Xiao Bao, I really don't want to see you like this. It's all my fault.
If it weren't for me, how would you end up like this?
Don't speak nonsense.
Being... Being able to take the poison for you
makes me really glad.
Besides, Old Six will definitely find a way.
He's been thinking of ways.
We will definitely detoxify the poison. We definitely will.
It's all right.
Being able to see you so worried about me
makes my whole life worth it.
- That's enough, Wanzi.
- What's wrong?
Quickly help me get to Old Six's place.
No, you rest here.
I'll go help you find him.
It's fine.
I can go find him myself.
Who let you walk around?
This will speed up the spread of the poison. You—
Enough, Old Six.
Have you come up with the antidote?
I made a portion, but I don't know if it will work.
But let's just try it first.
Whether it works or not, I won't blame you.
- I'll go decoct it.
- Remember, combine three bowls of water to make one. You must simmer it slowly on low heat.
Got it.
Come.
Seriously! What were you thinking?
Old Six.
Do me a favor.
I want to take Xiao Wanzi down the mountain.
Don't do this. You may not want to live but I don't want to die yet.
If Big Boss finds out, what are we going to do?
Old Six, I don't have much time left.
I'm not scared of death.
But I'm scared... I'm scared that Xiao Wanzi will have no one to protect her.
So I want to send her down the mountain.
Tell me. How do I help you?
Make... Make me an especially effective medicine.
That way, I can definitely hold on until we're down the mountain.
If you push your body and go down the mountain,
not only will she be unable to make it, but you'll also definitely die.
I'm willing to use all of my vitality
in exchange for Xiao Wanzi's safety.
How did she bewitch you to the point where you don't even want your own life anymore?
I'm begging you, fulfill my wish.
Fine, fine, fine. It's your life. What you say goes.
Thank you, Brother.
Am I pretty?
Pretty. No matter how I look, it's not enough.
Then just wait
until Brother Six finds the cure.
Once your body heals, you can look all you want.
Wanzi,
if you could get off the mountain, what do you have planned?
I want to go somewhere with the ocean.
I heard that the sunlight during sunset by the ocean is golden.
- Wanzi.
- Yes?
No matter where you go, I hope you can be happy.
Find a good man.
A man who is willing to sacrifice his life to protect you.
♫ I'll exchange the rest of my life for heartfelt words
This is my only consideration ♫
Take the medicine.
♫ Although our love threads are two lines,
moon shadows in pairs  ♫
♫ Once we gaze into each other's eyes,
life and death don't matter ♫
♫ I only fear that I can't wander with you ♫
♫ If I miss out on that, I’ll go crazy ♫
♫ I ask that my diligence becomes the floral scent ♫
♫ that is reluctant to leave your body ♫
♫ Go through thick and thin together,
experience the hardships together ♫
♫ The lonely geese whose heart are ignited
will protect each other, ignite them once again ♫
♫ Never forget each lit lamp ♫
You may not want to live but I don't want to die yet.
If Big Boss finds out, what are we going to do?
I'm not scared of death.
But I'm scared... I'm scared that Xiao Wanzi will have no one to protect her.
So I want to send her down the mountain.
If you push your body and go down the mountain,
not only will she be unable to make it, but you'll also definitely die.
I'm willing to use all of my vitality
in exchange for Xiao Wanzi's safety.
How did she bewitch you to the point where you don't even want your own life anymore?
Old Six, I'm begging you, fulfill my wish.
Fine, fine, fine. It's your life. What you say goes.
Thank you, Brother.
Master Bao, here, drink some water.
Old Six.
Why am I still so weak?
Did you give me that strengthening medicine or not?
I did, I did.
Old Six, are you not going to listen to me?
Listen. Of course, I'll listen to you.
Tell me. What's going on?
I've had enough of you two.
Let me tell you.
Brother Six.
Is there something wrong?
I heard what Xiao Bao said earlier.
Can you not do what he said?
You two. One says he wants to go down the mountain and one says she wants to save the other.
Can you two come to an agreement before seeing me?
Brother Six, if he takes me down the mountain, only one of us can make it alive.
But if I stay here and we try different medicines to cure him, then perhaps we'll both be fine.
Okay. I'll listen to you.
Let's stay and look for a cure.
That's what happened. Say, between you two,
one wants to save the other and one wants to go down the mountain.
But I think she's right. Saving you is the most important.
So we didn't give you that strengthening medicine.
Why is she so dumb?
Before, she wanted to leave so much.
Now she doesn't want to leave.
To her, saving you
is more important than anything else.
I don't know how much longer I can last.
Just give me the strengthening medicine first. I want to take her away.
Don't rush. Everything must proceed step-by-step.
Besides, the effect you're looking for needs to be developed slowly.
Moreover, precious medicines are hard to find.
There aren't that many lingzhi and ginseng on the mountain.
Xiao Bao!
I heard you got poisoned and do not have much time left.
I came specially to see you.
Old Wu, are you looking forward to me dying?
I especially ordered my brothers to get you some ginseng.
Thank you, you've outdone yourself. This is a first, right?
Come, come. Have a seat.
Don't be polite. Make yourself at home.
I'm guessing it won't be of much use.
This poison doesn't have an antidote.
Who said there isn't an antidote?
There's an old saying, treating an illness is like making silk.
We aren't in a rush. We'll take care of it slowly.
Then I'll trouble you, Miss Boulder Shattering Chest, to take care of my brother.
Naturally so there's no need for you, Master Wu, to worry.
Farewell.
Go on. I won't see you off then.
How is Xiao Bao?
Even if he doesn't die, he would only have half a life.
Old Six and that boulder-shattering girl are treating a dead horse as if it's alive.
He can't forget her even when he's dying.
If he wants to die that much,
then just let him go die. Why did you gift him ginseng?
Men.
I have to let our brothers know that I'm a good friend.
Master Wu.
Do you think I made a mistake?
I clearly know that Xiao Bao doesn't like me
yet I want to wholeheartedly treat him well.
I clearly know he thinks I'm annoying
yet I keep forcing him to marry me. Am I silly?
Silly, you really are so silly.
So silly you have forgotten how cute you are,
how pretty, how likable you are.
Look at all the brothers of this fort.
Who doesn't cherish and treat you like a princess?
Why are you hanging yourself on Xiao Bao, that one tree?
Who says I'm trying to hang myself on one tree?
The one who is dying is him, not me.
All right, I won't say more.
I'm leaving.
I wonder if I can completely defeat that damn Xiao Bao.
Has the princess woken up yet?
Young Master, you've already asked that ten times today.
Once the princess wakes up, I will tell you immediately.
Young Master, rest assured.
The princess, a blessed person, has Heaven on her side.
The only thing that eases a few my worries right now
is confirming that Situ Lin is the chief of the Salt Gang.
He exposed his identity so he will not do anything for now.
Next, we should find all of the Salt Gang's shops in the city.
Young Master, you are right.
Please rest assured. I have ordered people to investigate all the shops in the city.
All right.
After that, arrange our scouts to infiltrate
each of their shops.
Yes.
When can our princess wake up?
The princess is not in any serious condition.
She injured her head and that is why she has been unconscious.
She will be fine after resting for a few days.
- Thank you.
Isn't Xiao Wanzi someone who was trained to shatter boulders on her chest?
Why was she so easily defeated?
She trained for a boulder-shattering chest, not a steel head.
Heavens, bless us. Please do not let her continue to be unconscious.
What if.... What if His Highness finds out?
I hope Xiao Wanzi wakes up soon. Nothing can happen to her.
Princess! Princess!
Thank the heavens and the earth, you are finally awake.
Are you thirsty?
Are you hungry? I can pour you some water.
Princess!
♫ Scene after scene flashes by ♫
♫ Lifting my head, I gaze at the galaxy ♫
♫ I diligently become more persistent little by little ♫
- Princess.
- Princess, be careful.
Wear your shoes first. Don't catch a cold.
♫ Even if this doesn't belong to me, ♫
♫ I won't regret having wholeheartedly loved before ♫
Shiqing. Shiqing!
I'm here.
♫ "Whom does your heart cling to?" ♫
♫ The moon stains the night with spots of light ♫
♫ My heart is like fire, burning for you ♫
♫ Even my tears are hot ♫
♫ No regrets as my heart loves ♫
♫ Fingertips brushing, you ask me,
"Whom does your heart cling to?" ♫
♫ The moon stains the night with spots of light ♫
♫ My heart is like fire, burning for you. Even my tears are hot ♫
♫ No regrets as my heart loves ♫
When I woke up, I didn't see you. I thought you were dead.
Don't worry, I'm very blessed.
Just like in the stories,
only the bad people die. Heroes won't die.
It's so great that you are all right.
I'm not dreaming right?
Of course not.
Good thing you are all right.
I'm fine.
The saying, "two of a kind," is about them, right?
Nonsense! If you don't know how to talk, then don't speak at all.
Miss Qiao Yun, are you unhappy?
Nonsense. I am more than happy that the princess has recovered.
It doesn't look like that to me.
Young Master, that is about enough. It is time to change the dressing on your wound.
All right.
I'll help you.
Princess, you just recovered.
The doctor said that you need rest and take care of yourself.
I know. I'll be careful.
Let's go.
Miss Qiao Yun, since we have nothing to do now,
how about we go take a walk in the garden together?
Go with Qiu Hua.
But—
My Lord, your calligraphy improved again.
Look at those strokes, full of vitality.
Whether the calligraphy is nice is something to be debated.
However, you seem to be in a good mood today.
If you know the news, you would be in a good mood as well.
What good news?
The servants just reported that the princess has woken up.
The princess is awake?
That is indeed good news!
Then tell the kitchen
to prepare some delicious food for our daughter-in-law who loves to eat
and can eat a lot.
My Lord is so nice.
Look at how meticulously considerate you are of the children.
It is a pity that these children do not understand us, parents.
Princess has already woken up but she hasn't come to greet you.
It is a waste of your concerns for the past few days.
Madam, those are trivial matters.
Yes, yes! Just trivial matters.
It is just that Shiqing and Princess...
How do you think they sustained such serious injuries?
They did not even come to explain it to you.
They really do not respect us, parents.
Madam, I want to quietly practice my calligraphy right now.
You can go now. Go on.
When I was unconscious these days,
did anything happen? Have you found Situ Lin?
He is a sly fox. Would he be found so easily?
But him knowing that you are the Night Spirited Hero,
would he wait for a chance to secretly get back at you?
Rest assured. I have already strengthened the manor's defense. Don't be afraid.
I feel like you have changed lately.
How so?
You've become adorable.
When have I not been adorable?
You should answer me seriously now.
You also like me, right?
Look at my eyes.
If you like me, then you like me.
Third Young Master.
Third Young Master. Princess. The general has invited you to his study.
All right. I got it. We will go after we change.
All right. Sorry to trouble you, Third Young Master and Princess.
That...
General Mei must have asked to see you because of Situ Lin.
Then, how should we tell him later?
It will be all right. Just follow my lead later.
My Lord, Third Young Master and Princess have arrived.
- Let them in.
- Yes.
- Father.
I wonder what you have asked me here for.
How are you two recovering?
Thank you, Father, for your concern. We are almost fully recovered.
A few days ago, you both got injured and I did not ask.
What exactly happened?
Father, it is just a trivial matter.
A few days ago, there was a drunk who was harassing the princess. I-I had a dispute with him because of that.
So then we got some light injuries.
Mei Shiqing,
in Qingzhou, there are only a handful of people who can injure you.
Father is right. There are indeed very few who can injure me.
However, I was careless that day.
I forget there will always be someone better than me.
That person is an expert at martial arts who was just passing by.
I ate a small loss.
Is that so?
If Father does not believe me, that day we were at
Ruyi Restaurant. You can go ask.
I heard that you don't get along with the chief of Qingzhou Merchants Guild.
It is not because of him, is it?
Those are just rumors.
Pleas do not believe in them easily, Father.
Mei Shiqing, you are a dignified junior general after all.
Do not be out of practice with your martial arts after getting married.
Yes, I should follow your teachings, Father.
I will take my leave now.
Let's go.
This brat. You want to fool me.
That scared me. Should you let A'Rou know?
Rest assured. I am already prepared.
Why didn't you tell the truth?
Let General Mei send men to capture Situ Lin.
First, I am worried that word will get out.
The fewer people who know, the better.
Second, many people are involved in this.
I'm afraid Situ Lin has people backing him.
Father should not be involved in this mess.
Just asy what you want to say.
You actually took the time to explain it to me.
If you would like, all my time from now on is yours.
I brought your cloak.
You must take care of your body after just recovering.
Qiao Yun, take the princess back to rest.
Yes.
Xiao Wanzi, didn't you promise to return the prince consort to the princess
and will have no improper thoughts towards him? Did you or did you not?
I know. I know I broke my promise from back then.
But I really cannot control myself.
I do feel guilty. However, the more I deny my feelings, the more I cannot control them.
I am also conflicted.
She is a dignified princess and she was kidnapped to a mountain fort.
If the prince finds out, what should we do? If the emperor finds out, what should we do?
If the princess is blamed for tarnishing the imperial family's reputation, what should we do?
If you and Third Young Master Mei really fall in love,
then where should the princess go when she returns?
I know I am pretending to be the princess.
Rest assured. I will surely give the princess a proper explanation.
♫ Light is casted in my eye by chance ♫
♫ Just like how I came into your world by chance ♫
♫ If the painting is beautiful, it's because of you ♫
♫ If time turned back, would we meet again? ♫
♫ The most beautiful scenery of this life ♫
♫ is the clouds passing through the moonlight ♫
♫ Twisting and turning, I've fallen into your palm ♫
♫ The moon is covered; the moon is spotted ♫
♫ My treasured memories ♫
♫ and my simple feelings are difficult to write down ♫
♫ The moon rises as a lonely body; the moon sets as tears fall ♫
♫ It's me missing you ♫
♫ Facing the moonlight, I say, "I'll wait for you" ♫
♫ The night awakens us with the silver moonlight ♫
♫ Whoever catches the firefly shall walk together with me ♫
♫ Fated chance destined it to be you ♫
♫ What a pity to not meet in all this time ♫
♫ The moon is covered; the moon is spotted ♫
♫ My treasured memories ♫
♫ and my simple feelings are difficult to write down ♫
♫ The moon rises as a lonely body; the moon sets as tears fall ♫
♫ It's me missing you ♫
♫ Facing the moonlight, I say, "I'll wait for you" ♫