To call that...
the beginning of love,
it was far too uncomfortable to be that.
I knew I shouldn't take that hand.
I had a bad feeling.
If I did,
there would be
no turning back.
"Call Me by No Name"
(Episode 1: Prove that we are lovers)
- Something on your mind?
- Whoa!
No, um, well...
It's nothing.
Can I borrow a hairdryer?
Oh, yeah.
Here.
Thanks.
Um, what's your name?
My name?
I mean, I can't let someone
stay at my place when
I don't even know their name.
Most people wouldn't let a stranger
into their home in the first place.
Well... That's true.
What's your name?
Yotsugi Megumi.
Oh,
how's it written in kanji?
The 'Se' from 'world,'
the 'ji' from 'next generation,'
and the 'Megumi' with
the kanji for 'love'.
That's a beautiful name.
It's a beloved name.
I like it, Meguchi's name.
Meguchi? You have no naming sense.
It's cute, isn't it?
So, what's your name?
Hmm?
I said what's your name?
Huh?
Ah.
I said, what's your name?
Scheherazade.
Scheherazade?
Do you not know
A Thousand and One Nights?
I do, but…
What about it?
That's my name.
No way that's true.
Can you prove it's not?
That is...
If you can't believe me, that's fine.
Call me whatever you like.
Can I dry my hair now?
Then...
I'll call you Chiyako
meaning a thousand nights.
Meguchi's naming sense
is just as terrible.
Noisy.
( Six Main Categories of Legal Principles)
(Examples of six main types of law)
Are you a college student, Meguchi?
So many law books.
Mmm.
I'm a second-year law student
at Eichi University.
Wow, you're smart.
Umm...
I don't have an extra futon for guests.
We can just sleep close to each other.
If that's okay with Chiyako.
Are you nervous, Meguchi?
I'm not!
Hmm?
Oh, you're awake?
Ahhh! What?
You're too loud.
You'll bother the neighbors.
Let me go!
It's fine. Just leave it to me.
Think of it as my thanks for
letting me stay the night.
What does that even mean?
You don't have to understand.
Meguchi just needs to feel good.
I will...
I'll call the police!
Do you think they'll take us seriously
if we say it's between women?
It doesn't matter!
Even if it's between women,
if the other person doesn't agree,
it's a crime!
Wow,
Meguchi seems to know a lot.
Huh?
Are you angry?
If you want to kick me out, go ahead.
I won't kick you out.
I'm playing Sekiro now.
Huh?
You can use the futon, Chiako.
So you're going to play games all night?
Yes.
I'm not kicking you out,
but I'm not doing that, either.
I see.
The light's too bright to sleep.
Ouch.
I'll mute the sound.
Mmm.
Goodnight.
Now then, A Thousand and One Nights
refers to the collection of
stories told by Scheherazade.
According to the tale, a king would
- Of all topics...
- take a virgin maiden every night,
spend the evening with her,
and then have her executed by dawn.
To stop his atrocities,
Scheherazade herself married the king.
Each night,
- after fulfilling her conjugal duties,
- What is this class?
- World Classical Literature 101.
- she would regale him with tales
- Not what I meant.
- throughout the night.
When the king was captivated,
she would say, "I'll tell you
- You seem upset.
- the rest of the tale tomorrow."
Even though I helped someone
- to find a way to get easy credits.
- The same thing would be repeated.
- That is...
- It's called
“One Thousand and One Nights” because
it was repeated for
a thousand and one nights.
- This is a collection of folk tales
- You've been very helpful.
from Persia, India, and Greece,
and translated by Antoine Galland
a scholar of the Orient who supported
- Let's graduate together, Megumi-chan!
- Louis XIV in the 18th century.
Which was translated from
the Arabic version of
The Thousand and One Nights.
However,
only 282 episodes of this tale of
one thousand and one nights
have been confirmed to exist.
Are you going to the job hunting
guidance on Friday?
Already talking about job hunting?
It's too early.
I think I'll pass this time.
I'm going to think about what
I'm going to do from now on.
I see.
Oh.
What's wrong, Megumi-chan?
Sorry, you two go ahead first.
Enough, stop pestering me like this.
Kotoha, I'm really sorry.
At that time, I couldn't
control my emotions.
I couldn't stand the fact that
Kotoha was going in and out
of various men's places.
What does that have to
do with Murata-kun?
Because I...
- My feelings for you...
- Wait!
Huh?
Sorry,
can I borrow this person?
Why are you suddenly interfering?
So I'm saying I have
a business with her.
I have something important to tell too.
Ouch!
By the way,
for shoving me the other night,
I haven't forgiven you.
Consider this payback.
Alright. Let's go.
Huh? Wait!
It wasn't fate.
It was something far more forceful
that was about to begin.
Wait!
Huh?
Still asking a question?
Explain it to me.
How come you're at the same university?
I can explain, but…
are we keeping our hands like this?
Tell me your real name.
Furuhashi Kotoha.
Furuhashi as in ‘old bridge,'
Kotonoha as in ‘koto' the instrument,
and ‘ha' for leaf.
What department?
Second-year,
Science and Engineering
at Eichi University.
Why didn't you tell me that night?
Well...
It's not like I introduce myself
to every one-night stand.
Right?
If you were going to leave,
you could've at least woken me up.
You were having so much fun
playing your game all night.
Even so, I was worried and lonely.
Huh?
You were lonely, Meguchi?
Anyway, why did you do that?
Why?
It was the only way I could
repay you for letting me stay over.
So you mean you did that every time
someone lets you stay over?
Pretty much.
Though I didn't expect you
to hate it that much.
Everyone else I've done it with,
guys and girls,
ended up liking it.
Liking it...
Anyway!
You should stop doing things like that!
Things like that?
Whether it's to repay or whatever,
but going into a stranger's house
and doing things like that!
You keep saying ‘things like that.'
I'm being serious.
Stop it.
Then Meguchi,
will you go out with me?
Huh?
Well, I don't see why
a complete stranger like you
gets to meddle in my private life.
No.
Why does that mean
becoming your lover?
If we were lovers,
Even if you interfere in my affairs,
it can't be helped.
Can't we do that as friends?
I want to be your friend.
But I don't.
Worrying about me
but wants to be my friend?
It's not like I'm worried...
Then...
If you win a game,
I'll be your friend.
A match?
Yes.
A match.
(One Thousand and One Nights)
The rules are simple.
It's a name-guessing game.
While we're ‘dating,'
if you can guess my real name,
you win.
Your real name?
What about Furuhashi Kotoha?
That is...
Not my real name either.
You said earlier
that you want to know my real name.
Try guessing.
- It's a lie.
- It's not a lie.
It's the truth.
My destiny is tangled,
entwined like a curse.
Of course, if you're not up for it,
we can drop the game.
But in that case, you'll have to
stop meddling in my business.
I understand
I'll go out with Kotoha.
Then from now on,
Meguchi and I will be lovers?
I guess so.
I've never dated anyone before,
so I don't really know too.
Really?
Then I get to be
Megumi's first-ever girlfriend.
Well,
if you don't have anywhere
to go in the future,
you can come to my place again.
I'll let you stay over!
That's all.
Wait,
Meguchi.
What?
Give me a kiss.
Huh?
Kiss me.
Since we're dating,
I guess we can do it, right?
No.
We just started dating!
But you have to prove
that we're really dating.
Prove that we're really dating?
Because I'm
your first girlfriend, right?
If you treat me like a friend,
it would be really bad.
You really want me to do it?
Alright, hurry up.
How long are you going to kiss?
Well, I didn't know when to stop.
You should've told me how
many seconds or something!
Seconds?
That will ruin the mood.
Anyway,
this proves it!
Proof that we're dating.
You've got something on your lips.
Uh,
just to make sure...
You're not actually in love
with me or anything, right?
You being like this,
I don't hate it.
What do you mean?
I'm counting on you, Meguchi.
(Next episode)
How can you suddenly ask me out?
Do you like me?
Why are you so aggressive?
Don't act cute.
Why do you think people
have to change their names?
Probably because they want others to
know the reason for changing names.