With this,
now, we're friends.
I had known from the start
that this would happen.
At that time, I...
might have expected
love to begin.
"Call Me by No Name"
(The End: Proof of Megumi)
The ‘Se' from world,
the ‘Ji' from next generation,
And Megumi comes from
the word 'Ai' that means love.
That's a nice name.
It's filled with love.
I like it, Meguchi's name.
At first it was just a light feeling.
I just wanted to tear
this girl's love apart.
That was all.
Do you think they'll take us seriously
if we say it's between women?
It doesn't matter!
Even if it's between women,
if the other person doesn't agree,
it's a crime!
Wow,
Meguchi seems to know a lot.
Are you angry?
If you want to kick me out, go ahead.
I won't kick you out.
I'm playing Sekiro now.
I see.
I think you're a strange person.
What are you doing?
Figured if I stayed here,
you'd come and pick me up.
But...
Somehow, being next to
Meguchi felt comfortable.
- Just a bit, please.
- Please go back.
- I'm sorry.
- Please!
But...
The end came quickly.
(Happy birthday)
Is it delicious?
Mm.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
At that moment...
Ah.
I realized I'm just like that woman.
To me,
Kotoha is Kotoha.
Nothing is strange at all.
I...
I love Kotoha.
Today, Meguchi's taking the lead, right?
That night,
you found me, Kotoha.
Let's get married.
Shall we stay together forever?
I never thought in my life I would
have the chance to be so happy.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry,
Meguchi.
I'm sorry...
Let's end this.
(I found the name.
Meet me at the aquarium)
With this,
now, we're friends.
We've been competing for that
since the beginning.
At this point, are you still going
to say that and run away?
Kotoha!
I'll wait for you!
You've finished it?
- It's done.
- That was fast.
I have to do it this evening.
I'm not fast, Megumi-chan is slow.
- Am I slow?
- Of course.
If you have something to say,
just say it.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
You were watching Megumi.
That's none of your business.
You always dodge like that,
but deep down, you're just scared,
aren't you?
Scared of confronting her directly.
What are you saying?
Megumi has always been
serious about you.
If you're just going to keep
running away, then go ahead.
Hey,
can you stop already?
What, are you a stalker now?
It's not like that!
Don't follow me.
- Wanna walk together, at least partway?
- No.
- Then at least to the station.
- You're annoying!
I was asked to do this.
She said...
it might be dangerous.
Huh?
There might be some weird guy
near campus.
She told me to walk you home
if you stayed late.
Who?
Some weird girl from the law department
who claims she's dating you.
I...
said some really awful things to her.
Like how if two women date,
they can't get married,
and that I could stay by
your side forever instead.
But you know what?
She actually bowed her head
to someone like me.
When I saw that...
I realized, maybe that's
what true love really is.
Kotoha.
Meguchi.
Why are you here?
I thought maybe you'd come
if I waited here.
Hm.
Hm!
Why
are you always like this, Meguchi?
do you still like me?
There's no reason for liking.
I...
am scared,
Meguchi.
Of what?
One day,
I'll end up hurting you.
That won't happen.
Yes, it will!
Because that's
the only kind of love I know.
My happiness is mine to decide.
Fate, curses, none of that matters.
Even if I hurt Kotoha from now on,
or if the two of us have to
face something terrible,
I want to be happy with you!
Besides, Kotoha,
you like me.
But...
Women can't even get married.
There's nothing to
prove our relationship.
Then let's prove it.
We'll prove it by
staying together forever.
By loving each other a lot.
It's prove it together forever.
Just like you once proved yourself.
Kotoha.
Let's compete.
Compete?
Yes.
Compete.
It's simple.
If, while we're together,
we can make the world
recognize our love,
I win.
And...
if you lose?
Who knows?
But...
I'll keep challenging it,
until the day I die.
Meguchi,
I like you!
I know.
I'm sorry...
Don't cry.
I love you.
Kotoha!
You know, it really
didn't come true in the end.
Hmm?
That thing you said
if you say your wish out loud,
it won't come true.
Our date that day
ended up a mess anyway.
Oh, that.
But my wish did come true.
Huh?
What did you wish for?
That I'd come back here with you.
Meguchi, what's wrong?
Sorry,
just now, my heart skipped a beat.
Geez, hurry up and come here.
Meguchi,
what did you wish for?
Not telling!
Huh?
But I think…
it was probably the same as yours.
Yeah, I think so too.
Here.