Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Spring 2000
Letter number 53!
You’re finally discharged from the army.
Congratulations friend!
Hey friend!
- Sang Hoon.
- Long time no see.
It’s been a while.
About 2 years I think.
Where’s Nan Hee?
Behind you.
I was here for awhile,
you finally notice me.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
What’s with her?
She got dumped by her boyfriend
and showed up like this.
I don’t know if we should
acknowledge her as a friend or not.
We’re still thinking.
Hyung Tae.
You smoke now?
I think I'm going crazy.
You’re a mess right now.
I’m gone for 3 years in the
damn army while you're like this.
Nan Hee.
When you visited me last time, I want to
thank you for not keeping your promise.
Hyung Tae.
Seung Won.
The first impression was like Scarlet O’Hara.
You’re back.
Who’s that?
Isn’t she Yoon Sung Ah?
You know her?
She’s visiting Korea.
She’s our special guest.
I thought she would refuse but
she said okay without a problem.
2000 spring.
She came into our lives like the wind.
Seung Won, is it hard to learn guitar?
Hey! Hey, you know, right?
Answer for me.
Hey! Hey! How can I take roll for you. Hey!
Byun Hyung Tae.
He’s not here.
Nan Hee.
What about roll?
I did it.
What about mine?
Of course.
Can you guys separate a little?
I can see you guys sweating.
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
We couldn’t imagine ourselves without her anymore.
Who’s this?
I’m a little nervous because
we haven’t talked for so long.
You were the same way when
you were dating. Don’t complain.
That’s scary.
You’re trying to get away with it by using my first
dating experience as an excuse, aren't you?
Sung Ah's leaving soon.
What are you going to do?
She’s not going.
What?
She said she'll stay.
Didn’t she have to make a record?
Aren’t her parents in Spain?
She wants to be with me.
How come everything happens
on a whim for her?
That’s why I’m worried.
I bet you are.
You’re only 23 and it's not
like you can take care of her.
Wait a minute. Are you even capable to do so?
Think carefully.
Nan Hee, what if one day Sung Ah leaves me
just like she decided to leave her career?
You’re both crazy.
Yeah , we're both crazy.
It should be okay.
It’s raining a lot though.
It’s too much for a hike.
It’s not much. I heard it'll stop later.
Still that course is pretty rough.
Let’s forget it.
Yeah, let’s go after the rain.
We can go tomorrow too.
It will be okay.
Let’s just go. It’s Sung Ah’s birthday.
We came to hike and Hyung Tae won’t give in.
You’re right.
Let's go.
Seung Won.
It’s okay, just go.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
Seung Won!
What happened?
What do we do?!
Seung Won.
Through that accident we lost a friend and
while we were all mourning, she left us.
She didn’t leave anything for Hyung Tae,
and without any reason, she just left us.
And now, the sadness is barely healing.
Why aren’t you coming?
What time are the tickets?
[Love Letter]
[Sung Ah]
Try some kiwi, it's good.
Eat a lot okay?
It's me.
Say something.
Hyung Tae.
Yeah.
What should I say?
Did I come too late?
Since this phone was off, that means
I’m past the expiration date, right?
Yes.
You're right.
I’m sorry.
You shouldn’t be.
Yeah.
Why should I be?
Byun Hyung Tae!
Byun Hyung Tae! You really look like a
member who works for the society.
Why isn’t he coming?
He's coming now.
Right here.
Can I get some attention too?
What's going on?
Are you two together again?
No. Jun Mo had to meet her
for work, so he brought her.
I missed you guys.
Hey! You're the one that
left us and now you miss us?
You're right.
They seem quite intense with each other.
Well... I guess they are a bit.
Do you have any idea what
Hyung Tae went through?
Hey, are you guys watching out for me?
You guys are really great.
But I’m okay, so take let's stop the tension.
What about us?
We were all best friends, then suddenly...
Stop it already.
None of you are kids anymore.
I’m glad you're here.
- Nan Hee should ride with me.
- Huh?
Let’s go, they should get some privacy.
Does he actually still like her after all that?
Does he?
Nan Hee, let's go.
We decided to ride with Jun Mo.
Why? We go the same way.
It's okay. You two should talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
Let’s meet again.
We didn’t get to talk much.
Nan Hee, Let’s have a girls' night out.
Okay.
What are you thinking about?
Huh?
That I’m going home.
That's not much to think about.
It's pretty important to me.
Well then...
It doesn’t mean anything whether
Sung Ah is back or not. So don’t think...
You don’t have to say it.
I know what you're going to say.
You want to be alone, right?
No.
Don’t you think we don’t get
enough personal time these days?
Here.
You're going to sleep?
Yes.
Alright.
Ah! The movie.
Nan Hee.
I’m sorry.
This time, I kept my promise.
Yeah.
Look at that.
That's her letting go of the man
she kept in her heart.
It's really moving.
Are you doing well?
I’m doing fine.
You should yell at me.
I said I’m sorry.
You want to hit me?
I’m really a bad person.
It was supposed to be our first date.
I'll forgive you since you're sorry.
Really?
It's understandable since it was
a shocking incident today.
Is there another girl as great as you?
You're my best friend and my girlfriend.
I’m really a lucky guy.
But let’s end it.
It wasn’t as if we were officially a couple,
but still let's forget about
this confusing relationship.
Hey!
Sung Ah came back to get with you.
Are you really going to ignore her?
Why does it matter?
I don’t care.
Can’t you trust me?
There's that line all men use.
Nan Hee.
I don’t like this.
It's uncomfortable to hear things come out of
your mouth that hasn’t for last 30 years.
I think Byun Hyung Tae,
the boyfriend, is whatever.
I can’t even say what I want.
Same for you too.
It was so much easier before.
When one of us was feeling trashy,
the other would be the trash can.
Sometimes we would cheer for
each other no matter what.
We were able to stop and go for each other
and that's the kind of friendship we had.
Whenever I wanted to cry,
you were the first on my mind.
You probably were the same.
Look at us now.
It wasn’t long ago when you spent
my money to go to Spain.
I doubt you forgot about her already.
She meant a lot to you.
I bet it was killing you inside to act
like nothing happened today.
You're hurting more than anyone right now.
And you're trying so hard to hide that from me.
Don’t you think I know how you feel?
Because I know how you feel,
I can’t really do anything.
Damn it, seriously.
Hey, are you crying?
Be quiet. Can’t you pretend you don’t know?
It was too obvious to pretend.
I’m so angry.
Do you want a hug?
Oh my.
She asked if canceling the phone
meant that I’m over her.
She definitely came back for you.
How did you know?
I never thought she would be
back but she came back.
I feel better now that I told you.
You like me better as a friend, right?
Half and half. I wish there were two of you.
I really do like you.
If you didn’t reject me,
I wanted to keep dating you.
I don’t think I ever had
that much courage before.
I knew if I told you how I feel,
there was a lot we could lose.
I thought about it and thought about it.
But after, it was so much fun.
I can finally date someone with ease and joy.
Just the fact I can date like
this at age 30 was great.
The hand that I held thousands of times
before became something more.
The small jokes I spit out
suddenly had meaning.
I enjoyed it a lot.
It amazed me that it was happening.
I can’t do this with any other woman,
these are things that I can only do with you.
As sweet as that sounds, I like it hot.
You're talking about that brat.
I hope you and Sung Ah
feel something hot as well.
Don’t push me.
I’m a little confused.
The ball is on your side now.
Just hit it.
It will either complete your love,
or if it doesn’t work out,
just walk out and leave.
Make sure your heart can have a resolve.
At your state now, no matter whom you meet.
Sung Ah will always be in your mind.
You think you're so great, don’t you.
I’m going to work on my book.
The deadline's coming up,
and I don’t have time to get
in your triangle of love.
I’m doing this for my mom,
I have to make it.
Okay, stop. I got it.
Us...
How long do you think we can be friends?
When we were in our 20's,
we drifted due to dating.
But now we have to get married.
We would still see each other.
But it's going to be different.
I don’t know where we would be,
but one day we would say something like,
Was there ever a time when
we were actually friends?
Stop thinking that.
Just go on as much as we can.
Okay?
Okay.
Let’s go.
You go in first.
I’m staying for a bit.
12th Inning > It seems like our friendship is coming
to an end at the bottom of the 9th 2nd inning.
The hand that I held thousands of
times before became something more.
The small jokes I spit out suddenly had meaning.
I enjoyed it a lot.
It amazed me that it was happening.
I can’t do this with any other woman,
these are things that I can only do with you.
She should have come back
earlier or a little later.
Worst timing.
I liked it too.
My heart was so excited.
Friend!
Do you want to go running?
Alright.
Did you write more?
See it later.
Why?
I’m just testing printing.
Let’s go.
One step closer, one step further
I'm sick of going backward, forward like this
If you like me just say so
Let's not waste our effort
My love, I love you.
What?
Give me the $230.
You're breaking up so soon.
This is not damaged, right?
I'm selling this on the internet.
What kind of relationship is this?
It's not a 3-minute fast food, you know.
Yet it's over so quickly!
And what are all these books?
Joo Young's novel is almost ready.
I have to look for other writers now.
You were dumped?
$230!
Yes?
Nan Hee! I've done it!
What?
He said he'll forgive me and
he'll take it as it didn't happen.
That's really great.
I've been worried sick,
now I can finally relax a little.
This is really good news indeed.
Why were you worried sick?
Oh, nothing much. It's over now.
That's great.
- Anyhow, I'm so grateful to him.
- Yes.
- Or maybe I should buy him a gift?
- Yes, go ahead.
What should I buy?
A man who's in his forties...
What's good for him?
Forties?
Where is it?
How about shoes?
Would that be too expensive?
Who says so?
Even if I had to spend all my salary,
I should still buy it for him.
But I don't know his size.
Just buy the closest size and
he'll change it if it doesn't fit.
Wait a minute...
Director Im,
What size shoes do you wear?
275. Why?
Nothing.
Hello?
Just buy size 275.
Sung Ah
So you are here.
Oh!
Are you guilty about something?
Why the scare?
So those who are guilty get scared easily?
Shall I let you have this spot?
I'll tell you three shocking things,
Shall I start from the biggest item,
Or shall I start from the smallest?
The middle one.
You and I will be working on
the same project again.
And what will it be this time?
I'm fine with it,
You're... Alright with it too?
If we win it, it'll be a 3-months long project.
A campaign?
The biggest item will have a huge impact on you
so I shall start with the smallest item.
What is it?
I'm being included by my peers.
You happy?
There's value from splitting up with you.
It won everybody's pity hence removing
the distance between me and them.
Also, occasionally we gossip about you,
behind your back, pulling us closer together.
If I got dumped again, I might even
be the leader amongst my peers.
And the most shocking piece of news,
This will be our next project.
Hey!
You must have a huge headache, right?
Stop laughing.
It's true. I myself find it hilarious too.
What do you call this?
Hey! Are you Boss Shima Kousaku*?
(*a manhwa character)
The territory of girls you've hugged before is really big.
This time, even a world class guitarist
will join the crowd?
I say, how about try me out too?
I won't hurt you.
You just have to follow me slowly.
Crushing in a broken can, are you?
Really!
Your friend's right.
Your first sight of her and your heart's dropped.
Why are you fighting it?
Is this still...
Love?
Meet her up then check it out.
On the other hand,
I'm sick of my current situation.
I like Nan Hee.
But if I asked her to be with me
as I am right now, it'll only hurt her.
If she gets hurt, my heart will ache.
See! You're joined together already.
Didn't you say you wouldn't hurt me?
Fine. Then let's sort this out one by one.
When you first heard her voice
on the phone again,
What is the word that came to your mind?
Sung Ah...
She was calling my name.
Game over.
What was that?
You know and yet you ask.
Whether that's love or the remnant
of your missing her,
You're not done with her yet.
Hey! Boss Shima, you'd better solve
this before the project starts.
Who knows? Maybe you'll have
to meet her often in future,
You better not let it affect your work.
Even though living is hard
Even if I fall in love
But someday a good day will come to me too
This is the beginning
The star of life is me
Don't forget who you are
It's okay, don't worry
It's suppose to be hard for everyone
After one night's sleep
Everything will be fine again
I don't know how to give up
I'm fine and strong
Always cheerful and happy
[Nan Hee, tonight I'll...]
I will patiently endure it
I believe
Even though living is hard
Even if I fall in love
I will never cry or complain
This is the beginning
The star of life is me
I never don't cry
Sad tears goodbye
I want to buy this.
Hard worries goodbye
It's $10.
The beautiful day that I have
imagined last night, here I come
What are you doing here?
This is a book we published,
why pay money for it?
Hey! This book is finally out in the market,
I want to be the first reader.
What great loyalty!
Why are you here?
Ah really! I'm being tortured
to death by author Lee Kyung Ha.
What now?
Recently, she's hooked on bowling,
she's in a semi-retired state.
Guy problems again?
What should I do with her?
Hey!
There's still a little hope in bowling.
I was once mesmerized by a financial agent.
Our conversations centred around
adult manhwa and stock market,
The chief threw away all the office appliances.
Let's not talk about it.
[I'll be late.]
Shall we have a drink together?
Ah! Drinks?
Fine. I know a great place.
Shall I show you?
Oh my gosh! Stop fidgeting with it?
It's shedding a layer of skin already.
This book...
Is the accompaniment into
the next phase of my life.
This book...
And all that surrounds it,
I'm so grateful for all of it.
Manager Hong,
Every time you remember that kid,
your expression changes. Did you know that?
Jung Joo?
Yes.
If I describe it in manhwa terms,
There should be an “Ah”
speech bubble next to you now.
My Jung Joo...
I wonder if he's doing well?
Is he sick at all?
Ah!
Today you seem a little different.
You seem a little mixed up.
This, this!
This is the expression when you were
stacked up with that $230 guy.
Oh! Don't tell me this is occupational disease?
You gave me a shock!
Are you doing well*?
(*from the Japanese movie "Love Letter")
How are you?
How are you? I said!
- Crossing over one step at a time...
- I'm fine.
One bright, sunny day
Into the world of author Lee Kyung Ha.
I'll still hurt a lot
Goodbye, Manager Hong.
Even if I closed my eyes
Jung Joo!
Even if time passed
The memories are still in my heart
How are you?
Flowers facing the sky
Are you doing well?
I look at you
Jung Joo!
My heart keeps growing
We're always together yet we're blind to it
Like the hands of a clock
Do you see my tears?
Do you hear my voice?
Don't be too late
Come over and hold the crying me
You're the only one
You're the only one in this world
Who can make me laugh
Now I finally realized it
I want to say thank you
I want to say sorry
But why don't I have the courage?
Why do I say hurtful words?
I only realized it now
It's you who I love
Do you see my tears?
Do you hear my voice?
Don't be too late
Come over and hold the crying me
You're the only one
Hey! You spent the night away,
how lonely is your room mate!
Furthermore, it's sauna day.
You're feeling embarrassed, right?
Yes, a little.
Thanks to you, last night I could focus fully
and cleared a milestone smoothly.
What milestone?
Someone with writer's block,
finally finished 3 pages.
Well done!
And you?
Have you crossed the milestone with Sung Ah?
What are you saying?
Oh! Good job!
Who says good job?
We just chatted, that's all.
What did I say?
We decided to start over again.
But,
How did you know I was with her?
Your message was too short.
I'll... be late.
Just three words.
You must have tussled over what to say,
Then finally you chose
the shortest sentence, I'll be late.
Don't bother about me.
And don't feel embarrassed about it.
Have a happy, passionate relationship for once.
Fighting!
Can't you be just a little jealous?
Hey! You ignoring me?
Hey!
[I'll be back after seeing Sung Ah, is this better?]
Give me a moment.
What are you looking at?
How does it feel?
Your book is published and
the response is good too.
I feel great now.
Finally, I found out how to
contact Jung Joo oppa.
What were you expecting from me?
There must be water in my brain.
We didn't even talk about that.
Well, it's true, that day...
You cried so terribly,
I don't know how the time just passed.
After you left, I was like
a zombie for a long period.
Finally, I was fired by the office.
I had wanted to go back to live at Jeju island,
But I just couldn't focus and my father
had to give me a good beating.
After a course of twists and turns,
Nan Hee finally dragged me back to Seoul.
Now I eat well and sleep well,
And I'm happy in my job too.
I gave you such deep hurts,
Yet you're willing to take me back.
I had wanted to push you away,
But I just couldn't do it.
Why don't you ask me about it?
I knew I'd come running back to you crying,
So why did I choose to leave?
Aren't you curious?
Whether I saw your albums or
in news report, it just didn't seem real.
But the moment I walked in here,
I understood all about it.
Sung Ah is very successful person.
A person who was so successful,
Was tied down by me for 4 years.
She did the right thing to leave me.
Sorry.
I'm very sorry.
You don't have to say that anymore.
I'll work hard to make up for it.
Your sad period of hurts,
I'll make it all up to you.
There's not even a little echo in this place.
That's how I can hear the most accurate sound.
How long do you practice per day?
12 hours.
Wow!
It's not the same for you, right?
[2007 Collection of New Writers' Works]
Ms. Hong, Be careful or your butt
will be stuck to the floor!
How could they do that?
Why? What happened?
How could they write it so well?
Crazy!
You're mad over a book you wrote yourself?
I'm really...
Not sure what's all this I've been writing.
What are you saying?
Hey! What happened to you?
It's too embarrassing, too ridiculous!
Hyung Tae!
You write well too.
It's hardly half a month to the deadline
for the submission of articles. What should I do?
I read mine again but my work
is too far off, it's not even close.
What if I fail again, Hyung Tae?
What?
It's your first reading of
this author and you like it?
Yes.
You hardly have enough time yourself so why
do you bother to read other people's work?
Let me read it again.
I really like your works.
What do you like about it?
Which section?
Don't you think it's too plain and boring?
Wait...
Have you eaten?
Yes. How about you?
I've eaten, of course.
Hey, take off that tissue stuck to your face.
You want to become a writer that badly?
You think there's no hope too, right?
It's because the deadline's coming and you're anxious,
that's why you're acting like this.
In my job, I have such moments too.
Oh my, really!
Calm down.
You want some water?
No.
Luckily, you came.
At least I feel a little more settled.
Oh my goodness!
Don't cry anymore.
It's interesting.
- Is it really?
- Yes.
But as you get closer to the end,
it loses the plot.
It's alright. Good!
Your novel's the best.
Don't you worry!
Getting that author named "So Woon" under
the flagship of your company is not a bad idea too.
Thanks!
And congrats for getting back
together with Sung Ah again.
If I have any regrets,
It's that from now on,
your life is a finished product.
I'm afraid in future the things I can do for you
will become pitifully few so I regret that a little.
What do you think?
Not bad, right?
Such an impressive writer,
will he work with us?
I'll go ahead and try.
It's a new writer anyway.
You're not the only one reading this book,
This must have spread out already.
You think it's a good idea, right?
I'll just work on it then.
You'll be embarrassed,
This is not a writer we can house.
It's alright if I get embarrassed.
Boss, you want to publish
this kind of books too, right?
If it works, it's a heap of money.
No.
I'll tell her if she gives us
the opportunity to publish,
it doesn't matter if we have
to wait for some years.
Yes.
She's new, maybe she'll be touched by that.
Why are you so indecisive?
Before the reviewers publish
their thoughts, we have to move fast.
Fine. Let's try!
Do you know the way to contact her?
Of course I do.
But is this a guy or a girl?
I think she's a girl.
It'll be better if he's a male.
- So Woon...
- Hello?
I'm away for now...
I want to become an island.
Why?
Firstly,
I'm shocked because he's a guy,
Then the recording on the auto-answering
machine is too low-class,
I forgot what I wanted to say.
Why? What did he say?
Firstly,
We should believe in the product, right?
Yes, of course.
Then I'll leave a message.
I'm back.
- You're back.
You seem to be in good mood today.
Oh! You bought new shoes!
This? Oh! It's a gift from someone.
So who is it from?
What's the occasion today?
It's just from a friend.
Seeing you have clean shoes, I feel fresh too.
You should have done that long ago.
It seems the response is good for our books,
It's such a treat to be rewarded with a meal.
Yes, hello.
[Sung Ah]
Yes, hello, Mr. Writer.
I'm Hong Nan Hee from Jang Comics.
I hope you'll return my call
when you get this message.
I'm sorry to take you out
from your busy schedule.
No.
We'll keep meeting up from now on.
When you see me, are you uptight?
What needs to be spoken, should be spoken.
Why the sudden silence?
Oh! It's past midnight.
- Sung Ah, happy birthday!
- Hey, why are you saying it first?
Oh, I just can't stand you.
So what if someone else said it first?
- Yes so what?
- I should be the first to say.
- Sung Ah, happy birthday!
- Me too!
Thanks, everyone!
Let's sing the birthday song.
Happy birthday to you,
Happy birthday dear Sung Ah,
Happy birthday to you!
It's raining.
It's quite heavy. Can we climb tomorrow?
Why won't they go to sleep?
Oh! I'm sorry.
At that time, I was dating Seung Won.
After he died, Hyung Tae was
blaming himself for it,
He said it was he who kept pulling Seung Won
along then the accident happened,
I couldn't bear seeing him like that,
I felt that it was my fault instead.
So I just pretended that nothing
happened and decided to leave.
But from the moment I left, I missed Hyung Tae,
And finally I just had to come back.
Don't explain any of this to me.
I'm...
Starting over again with Hyung Tae.
I won't tell him anything, don't worry.
Please...
From this moment on, I will forget it all.
You please forget it too.
I'm really thick-skinned, right?
Don't mention about that ever again.
Seung Won is not coming back,
Thinking it through, it's no one's fault actually.
Let's not make Hyung Tae upset again.
Nan Hee.
Hyung Tae wouldn't even get angry at me.
I made him hurt so much,
Yet he doesn't ask me about it,
Nor does he get upset.
He just held me real tight.
That's why I feel even more sorry,
So I want to hang onto him even more.
Now it begins to feel a little more real...
He doesn't ask and he's not upset,
His expression when he came home
after accepting her all over again,
The process of Sung Ah's perfume
transferring onto Hyung Tae's body,
All this surfaced in my brain just as if
it appeared right before my very eyes.
- I'm back.
- Oh, you're back.
Who on earth is it?
This is number what?
Nan Hee.
Sit over here.
No.
You two go ahead, I'll just leave.
Why?
Sit here.
One more cup here, please.
Here, cheers!
It's been quite a while since
the three of us last drank like this.
What's this?
Nan Hee, you still draw attention, you know?
I know.
I can't do anything about the 8-year age
difference, but I still look quite good.
You get one every Monday,
Who could it be?
Since it's been 5 weeks, it should be in the realm
of a one-sided crush or a stalker.
I thought he would show up after a month,
And I was full of anticipation too.
You have no guesses at all, who it could be?
Yes.
At least it won't be some youth,
This is not something a hot-blooded youth would do.
That's lucky for me.
If it was a youth, he could be very poor.
I don't care if he's poor,
it just better not be someone I know.
Why?
To know someone too well,
is a very tiring thing.
When I see him next time,
I'll ask him, "Who are you?
Do you know me?"
You're insinuating!
Hey! Are you alright?
You drank a lot.
Yes. I'm fine.
Let's go.
Yes.
You go ahead.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: the.elephant, ai*
Spot Translator: purpletiger86
Timers: julier, Victory
Editor/QC: Suz07
It's only now that I feel... all this is real.
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ d-addicts.com