Subbers: Archanfel, Toki
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Life After Life
Subbers: Archanfel, Toki
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Life After Life
Episode 8
Meng Yo moved into Li Bugui's home
Tried every means to make him shed tears
Why can I touch you?
You're not a Spiritual Officer?
I...
I'm sorry, Lady Shen.
I have a task to do,
so I can't tell you the truth.
Of course, I'm not a Spiritual Officer.
I am
just an ordinary person.
But since my cousin was entitled the Town God
after he died,
so I piggybacked on his status
and saw Spiritual Officers a few times.
But
they all seemed so mysterious
and didn't talk to me too much.
Then did you get close
to us by their order?
Why do you ask so?
Do you have issues with them?
No.
It's Li Bugui.
He doesn't like the people of Lingyuan.
Does he have any secrets?
There are no secrets.
As long as you're not a Spiritual Officer.
You alright?
I'm fine.
You,
come with me.
Huh?
Don't try to help others
since you can't fight.
Who were they?
Why did they hunt me?
It's Ji Bofeng.
You are his target.
Why did I get in such trouble?
You can no longer stay in Guangping.
Leave now.
I can't. I have things to do here.
Does it matter more than your life?
It does.
Well,
my petty life matters a bit also.
Do you have any relatives here?
Yes,
my brother is in the town.
Go seek refuge with him.
All right.
Brother, I'm here to seek refuge.
Could I live here?
I...
Are you going back on your word?
We just swore to be siblings.
You...
Fine.
Change your mind if you like,
I can keep staying in this deserted temple.
Look,
I can choose a corner to lie down
and sleep.
Stand up.
How can you sleep here?
I think you are right.
I need a quilt.
There is a rag by the gate.
Though it has many holes,
I can make do with it.
Besides,
it's not a bad thing to sleep here
though it's a bit cold and damp
and there are also some insects.
Anyway, don't worry, brother.
I'm used to them.
What's more,
even if Ji Bofeng comes to kill me,
what's the big deal?
People
die anyway.
But I'm glad
to die for my brother.
Get up.
Since you saved my granny's sister,
you may move to Lingxiao Sect.
Thanks, brother.
It will be easier
to get his tears at that place.
Let me warn you first,
if you do something absurd,
I can still drive you out.
What
is the thing absurd?
I will tell you
when you do it.
All right.
Thank you, brother.
You're so kind, brother.
Goodbye, brother.
See you tomorrow.
Heroine.
I'm impressed by you.
Once you move into his home,
we will have more chances
to do it.
I've prepared this useful item to make him cry.
There are onions, artemisia argyi and pepper in it.
I'm sure they can protect you
and help you to make it.
With them,
I can get the tears
and make Lethe Water soon.
Yes.
Heroine.
Why are you sighing?
Li Bugui kept me safe
all day,
yet I've been lying to him.
Don't blame yourself
because you didn't have a choice.
You need to save the whole Lingyuan.
Besides,
you are not going to kill him, right?
Li Bugui carries the grudges
of two lifetimes,
so if you let him drink Lethe Water,
you may help him to relieve.
Then
he may have a happy life.
That being said,
will he be happy
when he forgets everything?
Well...
I was wondering
why you let that suspicious lass move in.
So you want to use her to lure Ji Bofeng out.
Since she has learned Ji Bofeng's secret,
he will come after her.
Fortunately,
she has eaten my Bettle Pearls of Blood,
I can know her whereabouts anytime.
Therefore, I can wait
till Ji Bofeng is drawn out.
But I still don't know
the reason that woman
gets close to me.
Is it possible
that she gets close to you for no reason special
or
she just loves you?
Love?
I'm not sure if I guessed it right.
Look,
she tried to approach you.
She swore to be your sister even when she knew
you killed many people.
She sucked out the poisonous blood for you
and insisted on living near you.
I'd do the same if I loved someone.
There is no reason else
which can make her treat you in that way.
She saved you today,
did she also buy your tongue over?
Fine.
Whatever you say.
Let me help her to clean up.
Love?
This is your room.
Feel free to use the gold,
the silver and other things here.
If it's not enough,
take more from the treasury.
What's more,
you may also order the servants here.
I didn't know you were such a thoughtful person.
It's so well-prepared.
They are
prepared by Li Bugui.
Huh?
That bru...
My
brother?
Just settle down here.
Li Bugui is in the next door.
Call him when you're in danger
and he'll show up at once.
Wow?
At once?
Yes.
Thank you, brother.
You're so nice.
This is the main hall of Lingxiao Sect,
a place where we handle the businesses
and other things.
Okay.
That is...
the drawings of Ten Spiritual Officers.
So he has been guarding against the Spiritual Officers.
I'm not on it luckily.
I wonder if he saw me
when he refused to drink Lethe Water.
Those devices are used to guard against the Spiritual Officers.
Once any Spiritual Officer steps into this house
they can't get away.
Okay.
The Spiritual Officer?
Why are you on guard against them?
Did you see one?
You don't need to know it.
Okay.
Ji Bofeng
is your largest threat.
You're safe now.
I'm relieved to be with you.
Anyway, I have made up my mind.
I won't be a freeloader here.
Feel free to tell me what you need.
I can be happy with you when you're glad
and I can shed tears with you when you're upset.
Just take me as a brick of yours
and place me anywhere you like.
What do you think?
I don't need any brick.
He does,
he just doesn't realize it.
All right.
What is it?
Why is it so irritating?
It is my special
spicy tear hot pot.
It's said to be great
for fighters.
Indeed?
It tastes good.
Isn't it?
Shuanzi,
why don't you take a bite?
Yes, brother,
have some meat.
I'm good.
I hate that taste.
I've prepared it carefully.
Forget him.
Let's eat.
So I can't use the hot pot
to make him shed tears.
Hey,
why did you call him Shuanzi?
It's his infant name.
His mother was afraid that he would die,
so she named him Shuanzi
which means holding his life.
I see.
Shuanzi.
Brother Shuanzi.
Want an onion bath?
How did you get inside?
Out.
If you don't like onions,
I also have other herbs
for you to have a herbal bath.
I'm so healthy
that I don't need it.
I'm sure you do.
You do.