Subbers: Archanfel, Toki
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Life After Life
Subbers: Archanfel, Toki
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Life After Life
Episode 11
The affections in the previous life
Meet again in this life
It's the chicken soup for you.
Try it.
Here.
I don't want it.
You can't get well
if you don't eat.
Besides,
you got ill because of me,
so I'll blame myself
if you can't recover.
Here.
So,
does it taste better
when you are fed by someone else?
Listen to me.
I'm not like you
who has been accompanied by Lady Shen.
I've been alone for so long,
so nobody takes care of me.
When I was ill,
I had to decoct for myself.
When the decoction was too bitter
to drink,
I came up with an idea.
I pretended to be my mom
to feed myself.
Like this,
Yo, I know it's bitter,
but you'll get well after having it,
so I don't have to be worried.
Just have it for me, okay?
Then I would
drink up the whole decoction.
Do you think
something is wrong with me?
Brother Shuanzi, have more.
In fact,
when you are alone,
you may deceive yourself
to go through.
Look,
don't you want to know
how I found you?
Yes.
Let me show you something.
It's called Bettle Pearls of Blood
which is the concentration of the cluster bettle blood.
What's in me is the maternal blood
and what you had is the filial one.
So when you are in danger,
I could sense your position.
Bettle Pearls of Blood?
When did you let me eat it?
That's not your concern.
Just remember
I'll go to rescue you
when you're in danger, that's enough.
You will show up
whenever I'm in danger?
What are you chatting about?
What brings you here?
Zhang Shen, the young master of Yuling Villa, awaits you.
Yuling Villa?
Let me meet the man.
No. He wants to see her.
Huh?
Me?
I am Zhang Shen of Yuling Villa.
It's an honor, Master Li, Lady Meng.
So it's him.
For what
do we owe this honor?
Honestly,
I do have a business
and I need your favor.
The elder brother is said to be like a father.
I fell in love with Lady Meng
at first sight,
so I made bold
to ask you to let me marry her.
Marry her?
Precisely.
Little Gourd,
do you know him?
All right. Walk the guest out.
Hold on.
Lady Meng.
Could you look at this painting
before driving me away?
This is...
How did you get it?
Did you
have the same dream repeatedly?
For 23 years,
I always dreamed
of a weeping girl.
So when I saw you yesterday,
I felt like being struck by a bolt.
Lady Meng,
do you
believe in the love in the previous life?
She doesn't.
You may leave.
Master Li.
She hasn't answered yet.
Little Gourd,
what's wrong?
I have no idea,
but he seems like an old friend.
She doesn't feel well today.
If you'll excuse us.
Master Li,
our Yuling Villa
is a celebrated sect after all.
So if you're not satisfied with me,
just tell me frankly.
Why must you just reject me?
I have made it so clear.
You are free to go.
Walk him out.
In that case,
I'm taking my leave.
Lady Meng, if you change your mind,
feel free to see me at Yichun Teahouse.
I will always
be waiting for you.
Is he really Tao Ran?
How could it be so coincidental?
No.
Since I've managed to come to Qingchuan,
I need to find the truth.
But what shall I say to him?
He said it was a dream,
so he should have forgotten me.
Besides, I can't tell him
that I'm a Spiritual Officer.
However,
what if he still remembers me?
What am I thinking about?
He drank Lethe Water already,
so he must have forgotten me.
But how did he find me?
Forget it. I need to see him tomorrow.
Where to?
Brother,
I want to see Mister Zhang.
Go.
Thank you, brother.
Ji Bofeng is waiting to kill you outside.
As long as you show up,
thousands of blades will come to you.
Don't we have
Bettle Pearls of Blood?
Won't you come
to save me when I'm in danger?
It depends on my mood.
Then I'll tell Mister Zhang
to save me.
He seems to be strong enough.
Do you know him?
If you go out
and encounter any danger,
I won't save you.
I don't care.
Excuse me.
Why did you come here?
I'm afraid your Mister Zhang is too weak
to protect you.
Why are you laughing?
Because you said you wouldn't protect me,
yet you still worry about me, right?
I'm so lucky to have a good brother
like you.
Humph.
Good brother?
Brother Shuanzi, I'm going upstairs.
Let me go with you.
No.
There are things
I need to figure out myself.
Okay.
I'll be waiting here.
That's not necessary.
It is cloudy now,
so it's going to rain.
Just go back.
Lady Meng.
I knew you'd come.
Please sit.
Okay.
Mister Zhang,
about the love in the previous life you mentioned,
what did that mean?
I didn't believe my previous life in the first place.
But I was
disturbed by the dreams
about you,
so I got this Nine-dimensions Mirror
from a guru.
One may find the whereabouts
of the person he cared about the most
in the mirror.
Then I saw you
in it.
Since we happened to meet on the street,
I made bold to propose to you.
Is he really Tao Ran?
We can be together again
after I have been waiting for so long?
But now I am...
Lady Meng?
I understand
if you don't believe it.
The past
is the past,
so who can be sure about it?
What I want
is our relationship in this life.
The relationship in this life
is kind of thorny.
Huh?
Mister Zhang, are you happy
in this life?
My happiness
relies on you.
Thank you for your flattering,
but I'm not bonded to you this life.
Should there be the next life...
The pouring rain ended up with a colorful rainbow.
The fresh torrent rushed onto the broken shore.
There is no need
to go on with this heartbreaking topic.
Tao Ran said the same words to me.
It's Moon Sacrifice the day after tomorrow.
I have prepared this for you especially.
It's said that two people will be together forever
they eat the affectionate fruit together.
Would you like to put on the sacrifice gown
and join me to eat the fruit?
I...
No.
Why is it raining heavily?
Is Li Bugui still waiting for me downstairs?
It's raining heavily.
Master Li should have left already.
Lady Meng,
why don't you go back till it stops?
No.
He should be waiting.
Lady Meng.
It seems
he did go back.
Lady Meng.
Though it stopped raining,
it is still humid.
If you want to leave,
let me walk with you.
That's not necessary.