♪Amidst the urban chase♪
♪We hustle♪
♪In the weaving crowds♪
♪Time repeats its course♪
♪From dusk till night♪
♪I give it my all♪
♪There's no turning back for me♪
♪In unwavering belief♪
♪I'm endowed with exceptional talent♪
♪Racing to the starting line♪
♪Sunlight pierces through clouds,
dazzling and bright♪
♪You're a ray of morning light♪
♪Filling every inch of the darkest seams♪
♪I yearn to resonate♪
♪In harmony with you♪
♪Side by side♪
♪Creating a miracle together♪
♪My drive knows no bounds♪
=I May Love You=
(Adapted from Mo Yanchuan's novel
"I May Love You")
=Episode 4=
(Now That I've Tasted It,
I Won't Think About It Anymore)
(Rich Lady's Diary)
(Yu.)
(You ask how long have I liked you.)
(I won't answer it.)
(Next question.)
Miss Chen.
Miss Tang.
Are you looking for Mr. Tang?
He went out but will be back later.
Okay.
I'll wait for him here.
Why don't I
call him for you?
It's fine.
I'll wait for him here.
Alright.
Mr. Gao.
Remember to bring the documents
that need signing to me.
Alright.
Waiting for me?
Come in then.
Miss Chen.
You may go home now.
Okay.
Mr. Gao.
Why are you wearing glasses today?
I've been wearing contacts too much,
and my eyes are a bit inflamed.
Mr. Tang.
I've not eaten. Have you?
I'll order food for you both.
And add a cup of juice.
Thank you.
Why are you looking for me?
Mr. Tang.
Why did you suddenly
want to renew the contract for
"A Dream for You"?
Weren't you not planning on filming it?
The development schedule
hasn't been confirmed yet.
You can choose not to sign.
Did you renew it
because of the novel,
or was it because of me?
It's the same to me.
Tang Yu.
Do you know
that Ming Zhu and Captain Lu
got married?
You have no chance anymore.
Tang Xin, are you just
looking for something to say,
or trying to provoke me?
You don't understand.
This is called
desensitization therapy.
I just need to say it multiple times,
and you might get over it.
Am I right?
Tang Yu.
Do you like me?
Take a guess.
Since you already know,
why did you still ask me?
When?
Are you asking when
I started liking you?
It hasn't been that long.
Probably the past few months.
Don't ask me why I like you.
You're handsome,
rich,
and not fickle.
So it's normal for me to like you.
Just because of this?
Tang Yu.
Do you think I'm pretty?
Can I be your girlfriend then,
since you think I'm pretty,
and I think you're handsome?
Who told you
I only want a pretty girlfriend?
Isn't that it?
Men all like pretty girls.
If I only wanted pretty girls,
I would have
a whole truck of girlfriends.
Then answer me.
I want to be your girlfriend.
Do you want me or not?
We
aren't suitable.
Tang Yu.
You should've just said
that you don't like me.
Why did you say "not suitable"?
That's so formal.
Tang Xin.
I understand.
I won't disturb you anymore.
(Tang Yu.)
(I've liked you for nearly 1400 days.)
(The one glance that felt like eternity
four years ago,)
(I thought it was destiny.)
(Since then,)
(you've been)
(the person I want to stand beside by.)
(I like that you always)
(keep to your principles.)
(I like your confidence)
(that can turn any dangerous situation
around.)
(I like that you seemed disgusted)
(but would still
carefully feed the kitten.)
(I also like the gentle heart)
(hidden under that cold face.)
(But all these)
(have nothing to do with me anymore.)
I can't stand it
if I don't say this.
A man asking a woman
to help him pursue someone,
and that person being her best friend,
haven't you ever thought
how foolish this behavior is?
Since you don't like me,
why give me hope?
Why renew the contract
for a novel you clearly don't like?
Also,
if you get bitten by a cat, dog,
or person in the future,
don't come looking for me.
Why me out of so many staff
in the company?
I must have been out of my mind
to play along with you for so long.
You led me to misunderstand this.
You also made me hopeful.
And now you're saying
that we're not suitable.
Tang Yu.
You're really quite awful.
What are you looking at?
You haven't seen your boss
being scolded before,
or you haven't seen him reject a woman?
♪In the mystery of countless nights♪
♪Thoughts of you grow and sprawl♪
♪This heart suddenly ablaze♪
♪Yet, realization comes only later♪
Tang Xin.
You...
♪Seeking an answer♪
♪To conclude things gracefully♪
♪But you keep walking farther away♪
♪Until you're no longer in sight♪
♪I hesitated, I struggled, I tried♪
♪No matter what happens, I won't let go♪
♪It's me who missed out,
time slipping away♪
♪Why, when I love you,
can't I hold your hand?♪
♪Impulsive moments, courage tested,
wounds endured♪
♪No matter what I do, it seems futile♪
This way, you also gain something
and won't think about it anymore.
♪But in the end, what can I blame?...♪
Mr. Gao.
You look quite good in glasses.
Keep it up.
♪Thoughts of you grow and sprawl♪
♪This heart suddenly ablaze♪
♪Yet, realization comes only later♪
♪Seeking an answer♪
♪To conclude things gracefully♪
♪But you keep walking farther away♪
♪Until you're no longer in sight...♪
Mr. Tang.
Why don't I...
come back later?
Come in.
♪No matter what happens, I won't let go♪
♪It's me who missed out,
time slipping away♪
♪Why, when I love you,
can't I hold your hand?♪
The documents you need to sign.
♪Impulsive moments, courage tested,
wounds endured♪
♪No matter what I do, it seems futile♪
♪I loved wrong, passion worn away♪
♪But in the end, what can I blame?♪
♪Impulsive moments, courage tested,
disappointed...♪
Mr. Tang.
Actually, these documents
aren't that urgent.
♪What happened to the story,
at this moment♪
Call Tang Xin.
(Hello?)
(Miss Tang?)
Why are you calling me?
Afraid I'll do something drastic?
You tell Mr. Tang.
I've already
tasted an exquisite man like him
and felt nothing special.
He's not worth dying for.
Hello?
What did she say?
Miss Tang said
she's gone home
and won't do anything drastic.
Also...
Spit it out.
She said
she already tasted
an exquisite man like you
and felt nothing special.
You're not worth dying for.
Miss Tang is so mean.
She's clearly playing you.
If it were me,
I...
If you dare leak
one word about today's incident,
I'll deduct...
I understand.
Loud and clear.
(Rich Lady.)
(You left after taking the red dress)
(and forgot the two newly
arrived coats.)
(Come get them when you're free.)
(By the way,)
(When do you plan to wear the red dress)
(and dazzle Tang Yu?)
(I won't be returning.)
(The red dress might not suit me.)
♪When the dream flies through time...♪
(It's Tang Yu's loss to reject me.)
♪Drifting at the boundary♪
♪Circling around the halo of dreams...♪
(I don't feel sad at all.)
♪You cast your gaze♪
♪Illuminating the entire night♪
♪Brushing past me♪
♪Falling at the starting point
of a single line♪
♪I want your love, want you♪
♪I want to land by your side...♪
(Then why don't I be your girlfriend?)
We
aren't suitable.
♪Wait you♪
♪Writing the fable of our heartbeat♪
♪With plots that involve you♪
♪How should I write that page♪
♪Oh, how I wish to traverse it♪
♪Flying within the realm of dreams♪
♪Even if the distance is vast♪
♪I'll fly to be by your side♪
Don't ask me why I like you.
It's because
you're rich,
handsome,
and not fickle.
So it's normal for me to like you.
♪Cause I miss you, miss you♪
♪Every reason I chase after♪
♪Yearning for a glance,
a hug to possess♪
♪To end the lonely wait♪
♪Oh♪
♪Wait you♪
(Official Announcement:
I'm about to do something big!)
(What is it?)
(A secret!)
(Have you done it?)
(Did you succeed?)
(Tell us if you need help.)
♪Hastily encountering fate's design♪
♪A glance turned, frozen in time♪
♪A universe of tenderness
in that fleeting view♪
♪At the crossroads of the night♪
♪Flowing streams of passing cars♪
♪Waiting in stillness
at our meeting place♪
♪The evening breeze
extinguishing the alley's glow♪
♪Embracing you♪
♪A forehead kiss so divine♪
♪Fearing the wait might be too long♪
♪By your side, I patiently abide♪
♪Yet, to love enough in every way♪
♪All of it♪
♪You are my everything♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
Hua Juan, I'm sorry.
Did I scare you?
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth...♪
Hua Juan.
♪No longer a secret...♪
Would you hate me
if I gave you to someone else?
Forget it.
You wouldn't know which woman it was
that gave you
to that pig Tang Yu, anyway.
Unknown origin.
You're not cute at all.
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪I accompany you
through the endless rainy season♪
♪Shielding you with an umbrella♪
♪If love creates miracles♪
♪Then that is my honor♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
♪Deeply in love with you♪
♪Lucky to have met you♪
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you♪
♪How much I love you♪
Tang Xin.
What's up, Mom?
I sent you three photos.
Have you looked at them?
Which do you think looks best?
Tell you what.
I think the first one is not bad.
This kid
just became a civil servant last year.
He's also
a distant relative of Ms. Chen.
Mom...
I...
I'm not in the mood
to talk about this right now.
What's wrong?
Why does your voice sound hoarse?
Your eyes are also swollen.
Did you cry?
No.
You cried.
Look at her. Come over.
She cried.
- Come over, quick.
- Let me see.
Look.
Look at her eyes.
Aren't I right?
Did she cry?
Xin.
Who bullied you?
I...
I stayed up late
to write my script.
When I got to a depressing part,
I couldn't help but cry.
What do you mean by depressing?
Depressing means very sad and sorrowful,
like being depressed.
Think about it yourself.
So stupid.
Xin.
Tell me,
who made you depressed?
I was writing a sad story
about the character.
Don't over think it, Dad.
Are you sure it's your script
and not someone mistreating you?
Tell me the truth.
Nothing of that sort.
That's not right.
Look at her.
She's clearly in a bad mood.
Right? Isn't she?
You're just like your mom.
Your emotions are
written all over your face.
Xin, why don't you
come home for a few days?
Forget it.
Your mom and I
will visit you.
No.
I confess, okay?
I just had a heartbreak.
A heartbreak?
So. Dad,
please stop my mom
from finding me blind dates.
Xin.
Which jerk rejected my daughter?
Is he blind?
My daughter is so beautiful.
How could he not like you?
That's right.
Please stop nagging.
I just had a heartbreak,
and you guys
are rubbing salt in my wounds.
Also,
stop finding me blind dates.
I'm so good-looking,
but you make it
as though no one wants me.
It's precisely
because you're heartbroken
that you should go on a blind date.
Hear me out.
The guy in the second photo
looks good, too.
He's Ms. Lin's son,
self-employed, and runs his own company.
He's quite good.
Look. See?
Come on.
Just one glance.
I can't hear you. I can't hear you.
Hey.
Forget it.
She refuses to listen,
so let's end this topic.
Dad, Mom.
I still have work to do,
I'll talk to you guys next time.
Rest early.
Bye.
(Mr. Tang.)
(The agenda)
(for the next half a month)
(in Malaysia has been sent to your email.)
(Please take a look.)
(Your flight is 9.00 a.m. tomorrow.)
(I'll be downstairs at 6.30 a.m.)
(Got it.)
Now let's invite Mr. Tang
to cut the ribbon
for the grand opening
of Time Cinema.
Mr. Tang, please
cut the ribbon
for Time Cinema's grand opening.
(This must be the handsomest
president there is.)
(How I wish I were Mrs. Tang.)
(I wonder what kind of a woman)
(could tame such a guy.)
(I'm drooling.)
(If he plays a role in a movie)
(It will certainly be a hit.)
I've kissed him before.
He's just an ordinary person.
Smile.
Why are you smiling?
Are you that happy?
Hello, Mr. Lu.
Tang Xin.
Have you made a decision
about your copyright?
I'm still thinking.
No worries.
I'll be in Shanghai for a few days.
Let's meet up
and talk about this after I return.
Sure. Bye.
Mr. Tang, are you alright?
We have hangover medicine at the hotel.
I'm fine. See?
I've arrived at the hotel.
The higher...
It's getting late,
so you should head home, too.
No need to escort me.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Mr. Tang, do you need some warm water?
It's fine.
I'm alright.
A pig. A fist.
A smile. A goodbye.
What does Sugar Heart mean by that?
Let me ask you.
I heard
that she went
to your office again the other day.
What did you talk about?
I didn't say anything.
So, something did happen.
Why didn't you tell me? You...
You're so inconsiderate.
There's nothing to say.
Since you won't say
I'll make a guess myself.
Tang Xin
confessed to you.
I noticed it a long time ago.
Tang Xin is interested in you.
I'd say,
isn't it good that Sugar Heart
can express her feelings so directly?
How interested could she be?
It's probably just a momentary impulse.
If you say it that way,
it means you rejected her.
How did you know?
It's obvious.
Why else would you look so dejected
if you didn't reject her?
We're fundamentally different
and not suitable for each other.
That couldn't be right.
Two days ago, he said it himself
that Tang Xin
is proactive, hardworking,
thoughtful, and enlightened.
So your impression of her
made a three sixty turn
after she confessed to you.
Take it easy.
Mr. Huo.
Actually, Miss Tang...
She...
She said she only liked me
for my wealth and looks.
Did you believe her
because she said that?
You're kidding, right?
You've known Tang Xin
for quite some time.
That young lady is stubborn
with a soft heart and sharp mouth,
Right?
It's brave enough of her
that she told you
she liked you.
What more do you want?
Do you want her
to express her feelings with tears
and say a hundred reasons
why she likes you?
You're so...
You clearly like her
but are too stubborn to admit it.
You'll regret it sooner or later.
♪Hastily encountering fate's design♪
♪A glance turned, frozen in time♪
♪A universe of tenderness in that fleeting view♪
♪At the crossroads of the night♪
♪Flowing streams of passing cars♪
♪Waiting in stillness at our meeting place♪
♪The evening breeze...♪
(Gao Heng: Mr. Tang.)
(There are no work plans for tomorrow.)
(Would you like to hang around here?)
♪A forehead kiss so divine...♪
(No need.)
(Go back to the company directly.)
♪By your side, I patiently abide♪
♪Yet, to love enough in every way♪
♪All of it♪
♪You are my everything♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
♪Deeply in love with you...♪
(What's wrong?)
♪Lucky to have met you...♪
(Nothing.)
(It's just a sudden realization.)
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you...♪
You can't even draw
your boyfriend's face.
Are you sure others can understand
what you draw?
♪I accompany you
through the endless rainy season...♪
It's okay.
If having a face is necessary,
I can use a pig's head as a substitute.
♪If love creates miracles♪
♪Then that is my honor...♪
What's wrong?
Is that not okay?
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth...♪
(Is he trying to threaten me?)
(He rejected me first.)
(Why am I threatened when I post
on my moments?)
(I'm not afraid of you.)
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪Never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you♪
♪How much I love you♪
Mr. Tang.
The various data of Time Cinema
for this month
are steadily increasing.
The film occupancy rate
and average attendance per screening
have both exceeded market expectations.
Revenue has increased
by 21 percent compared to last quarter.
Mr. Tang.
Go on.
The internal original film projects
of the company
are in progress as well.
The Screenwriting Department has already
submitted proposals for topics.
They're waiting for your review.
Several initial projects already have
intentional screenwriting teams.
The adaptation proposals
have been submitted.
There will be a "Light of Tomorrow"
promotional meeting this week,
and we look forward to your attendance.
How is the progress
of "White Dew to Frost"?
The filming is going very smoothly.
That's it?
Miss Tang Xin.
Make an arrangement.
Visit the set of "White Dew" tomorrow.
Understood.
After Tong Xin encounters danger,
her reaction seems a bit off-character.
It's mainly in the emotional scenes.
The pacing feels a bit dragging as well.
Please make adjustments
as soon as possible.
Okay.
Director.
Mr. Tang has arrived.
Mr. Tang, welcome to inspect the work.
Mr. Jiang, you've worked hard.
Please have a seat.
How's everything going?
How's the progress of the shoot?
The coordination is getting better,
and we've caught up with the schedule.
We were discussing the upcoming scenes.
Is that so?
(Don't be afraid.)
(You're holding nothing.)
(What's there to be afraid of him?)
Mr. Tang.
I've felt a sudden surge of inspiration
since your arrival.
Director.
Why don't I share it with you?
You two go ahead.
I'll just listen casually.
Sure.
Go ahead.
This scene depicts Tong Xin's
emotional scene
after being hurt by Mu Zisheng.
I took a look just now.
I think the female lead
seems too vulnerable.
How about we make Tong Xin
more unrestrained?
Let her focus on the case
after her heartbreak.
And then,
we'll make Mu Zisheng's encounter
more miserable.
For example,
getting hit by a car
when leaving the house,
or being injured by falling objects
from a height,
or getting bitten by a dog.
Director.
These plot points
might be a bit cliché.
But look at here,
the danger in ancient mansion later,
with the lungs being pierced.
I think it's very reasonable.
After all, Mu Zisheng
is a supporting male character.
Even if Tong Xin used to like him,
but now,
he's no longer an important person
in Tong Xin's life.
For the upcoming emotional scenes,
I think we can delete them
and have Mu Zisheng exit directly.
Director.
In my opinion,
for the mid-part, we can intersperse
some events of Tong Xin returning
to the crime scene.
In this way, we can better
reflect the character's personality.
Just a little interruption.
Sorry about that.
In my impression,
Mu Zisheng shouldn't be a bad person.
Yes.
I didn't say he's a bad person.
But
good people can also make mistakes.
Hurting someone as good as Tong Xin
is the biggest mistake he has made.
Tang Xin, you...
Yeah.
This is actually quite interesting.
About the actor playing Mu Zisheng,
his handling of emotional scenes
always lacks something.
If we follow your idea,
we can
highlight the character's
shining moments
when he faces danger and gets injured.
That way, we can avoid dragging
and meaningless emotional scenes.
I actually think this change
would make it more intriguing.
Mr. Tang, what do you think?
In my opinion...
Mr. Tang.
Aren't you just listening casually?
I don't have any objections.
You're in charge
of the creative process.
You make the decisions.
Okay.
So, Director,
I'll work on the changes,
and then show them to you.
Alright.
You go ahead and make the changes
according to your idea.
What's happening there on the scene?
I'll go take a look.
Tang Xin.
Mr. Tang.
Do you have anything else?
If not, I'll go and get busy.
You can just wander around casually.
You have no idea how terrible
Tang Yu's face looked.
Aren't you being too harsh?
He just rejected you,
and now he doesn't even have the right
to have intact lungs.
I was just venting my frustration.
Can I really hire someone
to assassinate him?
Your behavior
of seeking pleasure
through verbal revenge
could only mean
you can't let go of him yet.
Exactly.
If I could move on so easily,
I would become the female lead
in an idol drama.
But honestly,
your post-breakup state
is much better than I imagined.
You look like there's nothing wrong
at all.
After all, we're adults.
It's just a breakup.
I don't want to cry and look ugly.
I still need to maintain some dignity.
Hanging out at your place.
Life goes on, day by day.
Ming Zhu is the happiest.
Traveling around the world
for honeymoon.
Right now,
she must be sunbathing on some island.
Oh, you.
We've got customers.
These are the two girls
I told you about last time.
How are you?
How's your combat power today?
Don't underestimate a woman
who just went through a breakup.
I'll leave it to you, bestie.
I'm out.
Welcome!
Hello, miss.
It's been a while.
Do you remember me?
Of course I remember.
We got a lot of new arrivals this week.
How about I show you around?
Sure!
Do you remember the camisole
you bought last time?
This is a scarf woven
with special-grade silk from Jiangnan.
It matches well with the camisole
you got last time.
It feels pretty good.
I'll take this one.
Alright.
Let's look at this piece of clothing.
This is a handcrafted limited edition
from our designer.
Only one piece available.
How about giving it a try?
No need.
I'll just take it.
Okay.
Let's look at this dress.
It is a knitted dress.
Isn't it nice?
It's really nice.
Although this is not a limited edition,
several D-list celebrities have already
taken a liking to it,
saying they'll come to try it
in a couple of days.
Then sell it to me.
I think it suits me better.
Sure.
I think the same as well.
I'll reserve it for you then.
This knitted sweater.
Don't be fooled by its plain appearance,
it looks fantastic when worn.
Sure, I'll take it.
Great.
Now, let's look at the clothes here.
These colors really complement you.
They're perfect.
Miss.
I think this is enough for today.
Let's just get these for today.
Sure.
Please have a seat first.
I'll prepare your bill.
Sure.
Would you like some drinks?
Anything is fine.
Great. Please have a seat.
You're so efficient.
Of course.
Hurry up.
Prepare the bill.
Sorry for the wait.
Please have some water.
Thank you.
This is the bill.
Why is it more expensive than last time?
Really?
It's okay.
Here, buying and selling are free.
If you don't like it,
you don't have to buy it.
It's not that.
I just feel like,
are you doing this on purpose?
Why would I do that?
I mentioned last time.
Our store
sells handmade high-end designs,
and the pricing is very reasonable.
(It's just that I recommended
the most expensive ones to you.)
Wait a moment.
I'll make a call.
Please have a seat for a moment.
- Sure.
- Enjoy some juice.
I'm begging you, take it easy.
Don't ruin my brand reputation, okay?
Didn't you ask me
to improve my combat power?
I asked you to...
You should keep your combat power
to explode Tang Yu's lungs.
Hello, Dingding.
What's wrong?
Hello, Yu.
Let me tell you.
You definitely mistook the person.
Ming Zhu
is not as good as you imagine.
Just now, she...
Get to the point.
I was buying clothes
at her friend's studio.
The clothes she recommended to me
are getting more expensive one by one.
Way more than the last time.
She really tried hard to bleed me dry.
No, bleed you dry.
Is Ming Zhu in Nangang now?
No, she's not.
Earlier on,
I heard from her bestie, the editor,
she went on her honeymoon.
Let her.
She has found her true love,
yet she still bullies your sister.
And you actually let her do that?
Even if our family is wealthy,
you can't be so extravagant.
Does she have a mole
on the right side of her cheek?
Yes, what's wrong?
Her name is Tang Xin, not Ming Zhu.
Tang Xin?
Isn't Tang Xin Ming Zhu's best friend?
She even helped you pursue Ming Zhu.
Tang Dingding, didn't I tell you
not to mention this again?
Why would I let her do that
if she's not Ming Zhu?
I owe her.
I understand now.
I guess I'll
help you coax her then.
Later.
Mr. Tang, rest assured.
I guarantee not to disclose
a single word
about Miss Tang Xin.
How did the copyright renewal discussion
go with her?
Miss Tang Xin has been working
with the film crew lately
and rarely comes to the company.
But don't worry.
I'll go remind her immediately.
I'll pay with the card.
Card, please. What's wrong?
Nothing.
Please sign here.
All set.
Good.
Here's your card.
Do you know who I am?
Should I ask who is your dad?
My dad?
Tang Haiming.
Tang Haiming?
Isn't that Mr. Tang Sr.?
Then, Tang Yu is...
Tang Yu is my brother.
I'm Tang Dingding.
Tang Yu's sister.
(Six months ago)
(I just want to be a fallen rich lady.)
Come in.
Mr. Tang. It's time for dinner.
Thank you.
Your ambitions are quite big, huh?
Not only you want to be a rich lady,
but also you want to indulge
in male charm.
Can't indulge in male charm
mean being indulged with just one man?
(Of course,)
(that man has to be impressive.)
By the way, during this few days,
did you forget the important matters?
After your fabricated plan,
it won't just come to an abrupt end,
will it?
It was a completely unexpected situation.
I couldn't arrange a meeting
with Ming Zhu last time.
Don't worry.
I've already planned the next steps
for you.
If you want to capture someone's heart,
you must first capture their stomach.
The meals you cook yourself
are full of heartfelt intentions.
So...
This is not a bad idea.
If I remember correctly,
both you and Ming Zhu are from Suzhou.
How about you teach me to cook a dish
from your hometown?
What's wrong?
Can't you cook?
How is that possible?
I've been cooking
since I was a kid.
I can be considered a culinary expert
in Suzhou.
If you're looking for a teacher,
you've found the right person.
You're quite confident.
What dish are you planning to teach me?
How about Yangzhou Fried Rice?
That's too common.
How about Sweet and Sour Mandarin Fish?
Of course.
But for Sweet and Sour Mandarin Fish,
you'll need a lot of ingredients.
It's quite a grand dish.
It's not a problem with the ingredients.
Tell me more about it.
First, we need a mandarin fish.
The mandarin fish can't be alive.
It's not good for frying if it's alive.
However,
it can't be dead for too long as well.
The time of death
should be between 45 minutes
and an hour.
We also need
aged vinegar, fruit vinegar,
balsamic vinegar,
cooking wine, ginger wine,
rice wine.
The aged vinegar
should be over ten years old.
The fruit vinegar
needs to be three months old.
The balsamic vinegar should be fragrant.
13 percent cooking wine,
28 percent ginger wine,
3 percent rice wine,
and...
A mandarin fish that died within an hour.
It shouldn't be alive for frying,
but it also can't be dead for too long.
The aged vinegar over ten years.
Three-month-old fruit vinegar.
The fragrant balsamic vinegar.
13 percent cooking wine.
28 percent ginger wine.
3 percent rice wine.
There are pepper, peppercorn, chili,
dried ginger, star anise,
cinnamon, tangerine peel,
mint, cardamom, basil,
clove, fennel, bay leaves, rosemary,
lavender, jujube, and tamarindus indica.
Do I lack any ingredients?
She probably doesn't remember
what she said before.
Do you?
I...
Of course, I remember.
I'll give you credit
for having some cooking talent.
Let's get started.
♪Hastily encountering fate's design♪
♪A glance turned, frozen in time♪
♪A universe of tenderness
in that fleeting view♪
♪At the crossroads of the night♪
♪Flowing streams of passing cars♪
♪Waiting in stillness
at our meeting place♪
♪The evening breeze
extinguishing the alley's glow♪
♪Embracing you♪
♪A forehead kiss so divine♪
♪Fearing the wait might be too long♪
♪By your side, I patiently abide♪
♪Yet, to love enough in every way♪
♪All of it♪
♪You are my everything♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
♪Deeply in love with you♪
♪Lucky to have met you♪
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪I accompany you
through the endless rainy season♪
♪Shielding you with an umbrella♪
♪If love creates miracles♪
♪Then that is my honor♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
♪Deeply in love with you♪
♪Lucky to have met you♪
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪Never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you♪
♪How much I love you♪