♪Amidst the urban chase♪
♪We hustle♪
♪In the weaving crowds♪
♪Time repeats its course♪
♪From dusk till night♪
♪I give it my all♪
♪There's no turning back for me♪
♪In unwavering belief♪
♪I'm endowed with exceptional talent♪
♪Racing to the starting line♪
♪Sunlight pierces through clouds,
dazzling and bright♪
♪You're a ray of morning light♪
♪Filling every inch of the darkest seams♪
♪I yearn to resonate♪
♪In harmony with you♪
♪Side by side♪
♪Creating a miracle together♪
♪My drive knows no bounds♪
=I May Love You=
(Adapted from Mo Yanchuan's novel
"I May Love You")
=Episode 21=
(Can Tang Yu's Eight Points Be...)
(Sugar Heart's Diary)
(Tang Yu.)
(I think I'm not worried
about the ten-point law anymore.)
(Even if you don't like me 100%)
(like how much I like you,)
(it's still alright.)
(You make me happy easily,
and I like you.)
I believe
you will become
the shining,
brilliant,
actress
you want to be.
Do your best.
Tang.
Let's eat.
Thanks.
It's nice.
Getting candies for Mr. Lu again?
Yep.
He saved my life.
I'd be dead otherwise.
I have to get him something as thanks.
I was ad-libbing at the hotel,
but I never thought
that accident would happen.
I'm telling you,
after your brother heard of it,
he destroyed
the person in charge.
I think
after he comes back
from his business trip,
he'll talk to Mr. Lu.
Oh no.
Please don't let him do that.
It's normal for actors
to run into accidents during shootings.
Besides,
Mr. Lu's the one who got hurt.
("A Dream For You" Group Chat)
(Incoming perk.)
(Mr. Huo of Time Pictures)
(is inviting everyone for dinner tonight.)
Mr. Huo's coming tonight.
I know.
My assistant told me.
This is a new flavor.
I'll get it for Mr. Lu.
(Huo Chendong came to the set.)
(Don't worry.)
(I'll keep an eye on Dingding for you.)
(Tang Yu: I miss you too.)
(Instant reply.)
(What are you doing?)
(Did you even think about the reply
before you typed it, Mr. Tang?)
Dingding.
Come here.
Look.
Doesn't this figure look familiar?
That's my brother.
Look at his grouchy face.
Hey, it looks like him.
Look at the eyes.
Doesn't look like him. Look at me.
Oh, you make a mean impression.
(Tang Yu: No.)
- (But I felt it in my soul.)
- It's cute.
Let me see.
Hi.
I want this one.
Mr. Lu, I'm here.
Are we going to check scene 29
or should we
start a shoot first?
It's alright. We're in no hurry.
Have you eaten anything?
- Mr. Lu, eat something.
- Food's ready.
Thanks.
Dingding.
I got you pizza.
I come and see you guys,
knowing night shift's going to be hard.
Fill yourselves up.
I'll grab something to eat.
Go.
This is durian pizza.
Here, Dingding.
Thanks.
You're taking a liking
to all things durian lately, aren't you?
This is nice.
Dingding.
I heard an episode happened
a few days ago.
How did it go?
Everything alright?
If you're tired, you can take a day off.
I'm fine.
I'm fine, aren't I?
Besides,
I can't let the whole crew
wait for me a whole day.
You're growing up.
You're more mature now.
Of course.
I am a brilliant actress
who grows stronger with every obstacle.
Aren't I?
This is for you.
Oh, I get something too?
This is the local product.
I think it's nice.
If you don't like them,
give them to your girlfriend.
I don't have a girlfriend.
With how fast you're moving,
you will have one soon.
Going back to your room?
I'm giving the candies to Mr. Lu.
The candy he ate at the shooting site
was from you?
Yep.
I'm a newbie.
I don't have experience.
I caused him tons of trouble
during the shoot.
If I don't cheer him up,
he'd lecture me.
He dares lecture you?
I'll talk to him.
No, wait.
It's nothing.
I was kidding.
Besides, nothing bad
with having some candies.
I realize
Mr. Lu's mood has taken a turn
for the better lately.
I'll be going now.
You get back to work.
Bye.
Who's there?
Mr. Lu.
I'm here to bribe you.
I thought you'd only
come with that tomorrow.
Once every ten days.
It's only
the ninth day today.
You count the days?
However,
I have cookies this time.
I tried it out, and it's nice.
You...
You should taste it a bit later.
Do you know what is the first thing
I want to do after I get to Nangang?
What is it?
Forget it.
Why aren't you telling?
Why don't you finish your sentences?
Come on, spill.
I'm not leaving until you do.
The first thing I want to do
after going back to Nangang
is to get my teeth checked.
Lately,
I ate too many candies.
Maybe I'll get cavities.
Sorry. I'm not going
to tease you anymore.
Then I keep them for myself.
Come on.
You bought them already.
It's a waste not to give them away.
I'll give you something else then.
Example?
For example...
Bitter tea.
Bitter gourd.
Black coffee.
The bitter stuff
can cancel out the sugar.
I'd rather take the sugar.
Filmmaking is a hard enough job.
Don't make it any more bitter than it is.
Um...
Mr. Lu.
It's getting late.
I should sleep.
You get some rest too.
Sure.
Hi.
- Hi.
Hey.
It's late. What do you want?
Dingding came to give you candies again?
I saw them. Give me some.
No. It's not enough for even me.
Sleep tight.
She's not replying.
Coming.
What's wrong?
You stepped on my foot.
Sorry.
Why do you look like
you did something wrong?
I did do something wrong.
I steal your hearts.
I thought you were going to give me
some presents.
You're a shy person.
When I pounced on you
and gave you a kiss,
you didn't even respond.
Where's the present?
So, does it look like you?
It's hideous.
Doesn't look like me at all.
It looks exactly like you.
Look.
Those droopy eyes.
It looks just like you
when you lecture your employees.
That sneer goes to the chin.
Looks just like you when you're mad.
It doesn't look like me at all.
- Can't believe you'd say that.
- It looks just like you.
Just like you.
Give it back.
Not a bad position.
Stay here for a while.
It's late.
I'm going back to sleep.
You were so brave earlier, though.
Why are you getting shy now?
I am not shy.
I just don't want You Huan
and the others
to find me missing
when they get to my room.
They know where you are anyway.
Nothing to be scared of.
Why don't you stay here
for the night?
I'll get showered.
(Don't tell me
Tang Yu's eight points is...)
Are you ready?
What are you thinking?
Dry my hair for me.
Who's there?
Me.
Got you some good wine
from a nice vineyard.
I want to chat with you.
I don't have time.
Hey, don't be like that.
Don't you care about your friend?
Have a drink with me.
You have too much time.
Why don't I get you a plane ticket
to Africa to survey the new project?
Alright, see you around.
I must be stupid.
Why'd I want to talk to him
about Dingding's stuff?
Good thing I didn't go in.
Or he'd kill me.
He's gone.
So...
I'll be going back.
Let me see the front.
Nice.
You're pretty.
I'm nervous.
I'm still nervous. What should I do?
I can't believe the biggest test
for my acting came so fast.
It's alright.
Calm down.
Let's hug.
Your hands are shaking.
Come on, hugs.
- Calm down.
- Is my brother really not coming?
He said
he doesn't want to see
your kissing scenes.
My brother's not coming,
but he is.
He's probably here to see
your kiss scene.
I have to practice.
Tang Xin.
Dingding.
I'll talk to her.
You go first.
Sure.
I'll get to work.
You guys talk.
I'll be going.
Go.
So what's up?
You...
Have you thought this through?
If you can't do it,
tell Sugar Heart to change the script.
You can't change the script
just like that.
Why don't you...
Do you know how to fake a kiss?
This is your first kiss, after all.
That has nothing to do with you.
I know.
It's none of my business.
I just want to remind you.
I'm an actress now.
I am prepared for this.
I think giving my first kiss
to the big screen
is cool.
Cool?
Miss Dingding.
The set is ready.
You may start now.
Okay.
You're sure about this?
Yes.
Alright, get into positions.
Tang Xin.
This scene cannot be changed?
The plot requires it.
I can't change it.
It doesn't look too good.
The lighting's not optimal.
Give us a moment.
We'll need to check things out.
Tuck that umbrella away, thanks.
Come.
- Thank you.
Here's the thing.
I'd like you to spin around.
- Okay.
- Like this?
You'll have to exert your right hand.
Put it around her waist.
Good. And don't overlap your hands.
Is the spin easy?
Mr. Lu, this is a slope.
My right hand's hurt
from the last shooting.
I can't exert it.
What about your left hand? Try it out.
I think my left hand's alright. Try it out.
What do you think, Dingding?
What's more comfortable for you?
Left hand feels really bumpy.
But this...
This position is a little...
A little awkward.
Something feels off.
I'll get up there. Give me a second.
No suitable...
It's fine.
Mr. Lu's showing the moves himself.
- Ji.
- I'll have to get some salve, Mr. Lu.
Go.
Okay.
Ji.
Where do you think we should move to?
Do you think
you can move backward?
A bit more inside, right?
Yes.
Are you alright?
Mr. Huo.
Alright, it's fine.
It's fine now. Get down, Mr. Huo.
It's fine, it's fine.
- Mr. Huo.
- Don't drag me.
I know this set more than you do.
Thanks for pulling me up, Mr. Lu.
I'd have fallen down otherwise.
It's alright.
What do you mean?
You think I didn't see that?
Leave. If you're not leaving,
I'll tell Tang Yu to send you to Africa.
So you were in the room that night?
Stop talking and leave.
Leave.
Go.
Ji.
Was that position alright?
Yes, Mr. Lu.
That's alright.
Alright, then get shooting.
Alright, get ready for the shoot.
It's starting.
Peng Zhou, hold her waist
with your left hand.
Okay, Mr. Lu.
Need an umbrella, Zhou?
No, thank you.
Alright, okay.
Mr. Lu.
I just need to act
where you stood, right?
Right?
Okay, sure.
I'll check the surveillance cams.
Okay.
Talk to me.
How's your first kiss on the screen?
I think she doesn't remember
any first kiss on the screen.
All she thinks is her first kiss
with Mr. Lu.
- I'm not listening, lalala.
- What is going on?
Um...
What's the meaning of this?
Don't say anything stupid.
It was just an accident.
If you say anything stupid,
Mr. Lu will get mad if he finds out.
You're worried about him getting mad
instead of you getting kissed?
Something's off with you.
Hold up.
You and Lu Zhixing kissed?
That was just an accident.
Good thing I have no scenes tomorrow.
Or I'd be awkward.
Here.
Tell me the truth.
Do you think
you were taken advantage of or not?
You were going to do the scene
with Peng Zhou,
but Mr. Lu took it away.
Why don't
I talk to your brother?
No.
Please don't tell him.
Don't tell him, please.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you laughing so happily?
I just remembered.
I saw Huo Chendong just now,
and he had this weird look.
He was pulling a long face.
So this is why.
I'm telling you,
if I hadn't stopped him,
he would've punched Mr. Lu.
Is that right?
Now that you say that,
it's a good feeling.
♪Hastily encountering fate's design♪
♪A glance turned, frozen in time♪
♪A universe of tenderness
in that fleeting view♪
♪At the crossroads of the night♪
♪Flowing streams of passing cars♪
♪Waiting in stillness
at our meeting place♪
♪The evening breeze
extinguishing the alley's glow♪
♪Embracing you♪
♪A forehead kiss so divine♪
♪Fearing the wait might be too long♪
♪By your side, I patiently abide♪
♪Yet, to love enough in every way♪
♪All of it♪
How long to the next venue?
About twenty minutes.
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
Stop the car, driver.
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
♪Deeply in love with you♪
Mr. Lu, where are you going?
Getting some stuff.
Don't follow me.
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
I thought he had a cabinet of candies.
Why is getting more?
♪How much I love you♪
(Mr. Lu: You asleep?)
(Dingding: Not yet.)
(What do you need, Mr. Lu?)
(Mr. Lu: No candy for today?)
(Dingding: I don't want you to overeat
and see the dentist.)
(So I don't want to give more.)
(Dingding: I don't want you to overeat
and see the dentist.)
(So I don't want to give more.)
(Mr. Lu: Open the door.)
(I have something for you.)
Give me a second.
Anything?
Nothing.
Just giving a return gift.
It's alright. You don't have to.
Just take it as an apology gift.
You really don't have to.
It might be an accident,
but I'd like to apologize to you.
You don't have to hide from me.
After all,
we still have to meet
for the remaining shoots and marketing.
Of course,
if you think this isn't enough gift...
It's enough.
I didn't mean to blame you.
You don't have to be bothered.
I'll take the present.
This is water under the bridge.
Okay.
That's great.
Get some rest.
Good night.
Night.
I was so nervous.
(Celebrationg for a Wrap)
It's a wrap!
You guys worked hard.
Change the spot.
Not a good idea, Yu.
The producer has to stand in the center.
- Change your spots, people.
- You got cheeky.
♪From dusk till night♪
♪I give it my all♪
♪There's no turning back for me♪
What is it?
There are people around here.
So what?
That's enough.
It's alright.
If it weren't
for Mr. Tang and our screenwriter,
this shooting might've not gone
so smoothly.
So what am I? Chopped liver?
You're not chopped liver.
The director is our lynchpin.
Coming.
Hold up your red packets.
One, two...
It's a wrap!
♪Filling every inch
of the darkest seams♪
♪I yearn to resonate♪
♪In harmony with you♪
♪Side by side♪
♪Creating a miracle♪
♪My drive knows no bounds♪
Hua Juan.
I'm picking you up.
Here.
Why's he looking tired?
I think you got fat.
Bloating in the belly, maybe?
I'll have to check.
Don't move.
Hm, it's a little bloated.
How much food did you feed him
in the morning and afternoon?
Um...
Let me check.
I think
we didn't record it.
You didn't record it?
How's the cat's socialization?
Does it get along well
with other kittens?
He gets along with them fine.
He's the kitten with the best
personality here.
If he sees new friends,
he'll groom them after a few days.
Groom?
Do you use hairball paste, then?
Yes.
We'd give it hairball paste
on the regular.
We bathe it every week.
Every week?
Don't you know
cats cannot be bathed regularly?
You'll ruin the sebum it excretes
and expose it to diseases.
Yes.
Alright, that's enough, Daddy.
Relax.
I told her to give Hua Juan
a total checkup.
He's healthy.
Thanks.
We'll be going now.
See you.
Let's go home.
I thought you hated cats.
You sounded like an expert back there.
Anything you like,
I like too.
If you like cats,
can we get another one?
When I was a kid,
my mom took me to a fortune teller.
He said I would have two kids.
I need one more to fulfill the prophecy.
No.
If you take one more cat,
what about our own kid?
If I marry you,
I won't be tasked
with continuing the bloodline
and keep making babies
until we have five kids, will I?
I'm telling you,
no matter the gender,
I'll only give you two more kids at most.
Just kidding.
If you don't want kids,
it's fine too.
Really?
Of course.
I'm not kidding.
If you'd like to,
give me a mini Sugar Heart.
A girl
as mischievous as you.
No.
If that girl steals your love from me,
I'll be upset.
She won't.
(Tang Dingding's follower: keep growing)
(Felicia's brand ambassador:
Tang Dingding)
(So, megastar, have you picked
the fan reward for three million followers?)
(Which set of photos
do you want to post?)
What's wrong?
Can't get used to the rising popularity?
I am not.
But it's rising a bit too fast.
I thought
it would only happen
after the movie aired.
Now I can't even go out feeling free.
It's like I'm being watched
from all angles.
Which means your brother
did a good job promoting you.
What's there to be upset about?
Nothing.
My brother and agent
told me about this.
Besides,
who wouldn't want to be famous?
I just get a bit
nervous.
I'm worried after the movie airs,
everyone feels disappointed in me.
So you don't have confidence in me?
That's not what I meant.
I didn't mean that.
Just kidding.
Mr. Lu.
Why'd you ask me out for dinner this time?
Well,
it's an apology.
Another apology?
I'm not that petty.
This apology
is for the weight loss
I told you to do before
the shooting began.
I lost so many weight before shooting.
I'll have to put them all on back.
It'll take about
70 to 80 meals.
Sure thing.
Mr. Lu.
Have you seen a dentist?
Yes.
No cavities, I hope?
No.
Next time,
if you want to bribe me,
you can give me more candies.
Sure thing.
If you can be bribed with candy,
it's worth all the money.
♪Liking you like this
is love at first sight♪
♪Concealing the reason
for my sudden heartbeat♪
♪A solo journey through riddles♪
♪Every detail about you♪
♪Is my eternal one and only♪
♪Willing to become a better self for you♪
Mr. Lu.
Why don't you take a photo for me?
You take photos better.
Sure thing.
♪In the tender gaze♪
♪Traversing a great distance♪
♪Just wanting to dream for you♪
♪I love you, who said you♪
♪The secret in my heart♪
♪Together with you,
chasing the expectations of the future♪
♪Eyes meet, making a silent agreement♪
♪Holding hands,
embarking on a long journey♪
♪My decision is you♪
♪I need you, following you♪
♪Entrusting you with my heart♪
♪Awaiting your response
as we flip through time♪
♪The sound by my ear♪
♪Unraveling this mystery for you♪
Did you take it?
♪Saying the answer, love♪
♪It's you♪
Done.
♪Liking you
goes beyond the initial sensation♪
I expected no less from a director.
Done?
Then we should leave.
My agent arranged
a one-hour thank-you livestream
for the fans.
Let's go.
Dingding.
Nothing, I just...
I have something for you.
What is this?
Don't open it.
Check it out after you get home.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm tired.
Sis.
Your schedule's packed
from morning to night.
You have to change outfits
about seven times a day.
Working out and facial care
are work requirements now.
This is too hard.
You had it hard too.
Go home and get some rest.
I'll be going now.
Bye.
(This thing)
(is the token of love
given by the male lead)
(to the female lead
in Mr. Lu's last film.)
The original is in a local film museum.
I can't get it.
I went through hoops
just to get the original maker
to make a one-to-one ratio replica.
How is it?
I'm happy with it.
I checked it out.
The craftsmanship is marvelous.
And it's retro enough.
What are you doing this for?
Feng.
How goes the selection for the topic?
Understood.
I'm not going
to look into your private life.
(Tang Dingding:
Three-million-follower perk is here.)
(I can't believe you didn't tell us
you were dating.)
No, Mom.
I wasn't going to hide this
from you guys.
I only found out
about my daughter's relationship
through the wefie of her movie crew.
(I guess my girl's all grown up now.)
No, Mom.
I...
I didn't get to explain in time.
Don't take this the wrong way.
(Whatever you say.)
We can't rein you in anymore.
You're going to marry someone else
and be their family instead.
Mom.
(You forgot)
(about your own parents.)
No, Mom.
(That's it.)
Bye.
What should I do?
I'm telling you,
after my parents found out
about us dating,
they're furious.
I'll have to go back
for Spring Festival earlier.
Dad.
Mr. Tang.
I think he has his earphones on.
Maybe listening to his playlist.
Hold on.
I'll straighten you out.
So, how do I look?
Fine. Good.
Okay.
Go.
Your hand.
Dad.
Who's there?
Hello, Mr. Tang.
(I want to tell you a little secret.)
(Tang Yu.)
(When I first saw you,)
(I thought you looked like my husband.)
(Before this,)
(I thought Tang Yu
was like a moon in the sky.)
(I had to look up to him.)
(But now,)
(he's finally mine.)
♪Hastily encountering fate's design♪
♪A glance turned, frozen in time♪
♪A universe of tenderness
in that fleeting view♪
♪At the crossroads of the night♪
♪Flowing streams of passing cars♪
♪Waiting in stillness
at our meeting place♪
♪The evening breeze
extinguishing the alley's glow♪
♪Embracing you♪
♪A forehead kiss so divine♪
♪Fearing the wait might be too long♪
♪By your side, I patiently abide♪
♪Yet, to love enough in every way♪
♪All of it♪
♪You are my everything♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
♪Deeply in love with you♪
♪Lucky to have met you♪
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪I accompany you
through the endless rainy season♪
♪Shielding you with an umbrella♪
♪If love creates miracles♪
♪Then that is my honor♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
♪Deeply in love with you♪
♪Lucky to have met you♪
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪Never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you♪
♪How much I love you♪