♪Amidst the urban chase♪
♪We hustle♪
♪In the weaving crowds♪
♪Time repeats its course♪
♪From dusk till night♪
♪I give it my all♪
♪There's no turning back for me♪
♪In unwavering belief♪
♪I'm endowed with exceptional talent♪
♪Racing to the starting line♪
♪Sunlight pierces through clouds,
dazzling and bright♪
♪You're a ray of morning light♪
♪Filling every inch of the darkest seams♪
♪I yearn to resonate♪
♪In harmony with you♪
♪Side by side♪
♪Creating a miracle together♪
♪My drive knows no bounds♪
=I May Love You=
(Adapted from Mo Yanchuan's novel
"I May Love You")
=Episode 23=
(Not Just Full Marks)
(Sugar Heart's Diary)
(Hey, look, Tang Yu.)
(You must love me too much now.)
(I won.)
Thank you for taking my undesirable son.
Tang Xin.
When are you two getting married?
Don't worry.
We're not urging you.
But you know how it is.
Once you get to that point,
you get hitched.
Whether you want a Chinese wedding
or a Western one, it's fine.
As long as you like it,
we're fine with it.
I...
It's not like we
don't want to get married.
We just haven't thought that far.
So you do want to get married.
Okay, okay. I'm not urging.
We're in no hurry.
Yeah.
You two call the shots.
But you should decide
on the date soon.
Right.
So we can prepare.
Tang Xin.
Food's almost ready.
Why are you still here?
Where's my brother?
He went and made a call.
Tang Xin.
Tell me.
Since you two
have met each other's parents,
and my brother wants to marry you,
his love for you is at nine points.
No, wait.
Not just that.
He loves you so much.
That's full ten points.
Really? Really?
What are you talking about?
That was so hard.
What do you mean ten points?
Nothing.
Nothing?
I saw you two.
Are you hiding something from me? Tell me.
Tang Yu.
Take the food.
Tell them lunch is almost served.
Okay.
Go.
Tell me later.
Let's go.
Have lunch.
Tang Xin.
Do you know that?
What?
Mom.
I'm telling Dad.
Tang Xin is here.
Your dad won't even lecture me.
Come.
Drink with me.
Usually,
it's the son-in-law and father-in-law
drinking a ton,
but it's the other way around for us.
Doesn't feel good, does it?
Get some sleep.
I'll wake you when we get there.
Tang Yu.
I'm here.
I like you so much.
Me too.
It's not the same.
The feelings I have for you
can't be described with words.
We're home.
Careful.
You drank so much.
Turn on the lights.
What's wrong?
It's too bright.
Don't turn on the lights.
I want water.
Careful.
♪Hastily encountering fate's design♪
♪A glance turned, frozen in time♪
♪A universe of tenderness
in that fleeting view♪
♪At the crossroads of the night♪
♪Flowing streams of passing cars♪
♪Waiting in stillness
at our meeting place♪
♪The evening breeze
extinguishing the alley's glow♪
♪Embracing you♪
♪A forehead kiss so divine♪
♪Fearing the wait might be too long♪
♪By your side, I patiently abide♪
♪Yet, to love enough in every way♪
♪All of it♪
♪You are my everything♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
♪Deeply in love with you♪
♪Lucky to have met you♪
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪The evening breeze
extinguishing the alley's glow♪
♪Embracing you♪
♪A forehead kiss so divine♪
♪Fearing the wait might be too long♪
♪By your side, I patiently abide♪
♪Yet, to love enough in every way♪
♪All of it♪
♪You are my everything♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
Tang Xin.
Do you want it?
Answer me.
What's the deal
with the nine and ten points?
It means you want to marry me.
It's not that simple, is it?
Ask Tang Dingding.
She told me that.
You drank today.
Can't be too impulsive.
Be good.
Get some sleep.
Will you stay with me?
Of course.
I'll stay with you
until you fall asleep.
Good night.
You're awake.
I made some noodles for you.
You must be starving.
Done.
Here.
Here's supper.
Okay.
I'll give it a try.
How is it?
Just like my dad's cooking.
He gave me the recipe.
Years of experience made this.
It's your favorite flavor.
My dad is really something.
I made that bowl of noodles.
And you're not bad too.
Right.
So what kind of proposal do you prefer?
I'm asking for your preference
so I can prepare.
Is that a question you ask me?
At moments
and places like this,
shouldn't proposals be a surprise?
You are so dense.
You're right.
I'll come up with a plan.
Why don't we
look into it more
and narrow down the scope?
Some proposals
are really mortifying.
I don't trust you on this.
Me neither.
So I made some preparations.
Check it out.
This is too retro.
You don't like retro?
Look at this one then.
This is the one.
This is the mortifying one
I told you about.
Hey.
Don't tell me
you used to have this idea.
No? Good.
- Next.
- Next one, please.
This looks too fake.
Not good enough.
But it has some merits.
If that's the case,
I'll go through
all the most popular proposal ideas
from the last six months with you.
Just kidding.
If it's you,
I'm fine with anything.
I don't need flowers.
I don't need a lot of people.
As long as there's you
and me,
that's enough.
Okay.
I think there's nothing for you to worry
about in relationships now.
Is that work?
"A Dream for You"
has its airing date set.
The promotional material's out.
A few companies' producers
added me on WeChat
and asked me to write them a new script.
They added you on WeChat?
Which companies' producers?
Why do you want to know?
I have to ask them myself.
How dare they
try to steal you from me.
Don't they know you're the wife
of Time Pictures' boss?
I still am not your wife.
Don't get in the way of my career.
Sure.
Since you're not giving me any leeway,
I'll extend a formal invitation.
On behalf of Time Pictures, I now
invite you to join our development team.
Will you take it, Ms. Tang?
I'll think about it.
Sure.
I see I'll have to give you
a copy of the company's intro
so you can know more.
That's good.
Knowing more is always nice.
Mr. Tang.
Do you need my resume
so you can know me more?
I'm amenable to that.
(Lu Studio)
Mr. Lu.
Dingding.
Why's there no one here?
Because it's the weekend.
Everyone's taking a break.
Oh, right.
Present.
Thanks.
Have a seat.
Feng can't make it. Sudden business.
Tang Xin and your brother
are on their way.
You came early.
By just about ten minutes.
They're a couple.
So maybe they'll be slow.
Sit.
It'll be a while before they come.
You can look around.
You haven't gone to the second floor,
have you?
Check out the second floor.
Sure.
I'll call you when it's done here.
(Dingding:
Tang Xin, please get here soon.)
(Feng's not coming.)
(I can't stay in a room
with Mr. Lu alone.)
(I can't control myself.)
Hey.
It's a good chance.
What are you saying?
It's about Mr. Lu.
He just texted me.
The hard disk has gone wonky.
It can't be used.
He tells us to skip the meeting.
(Your brother and I have sudden business
to settle. Can't make it.)
- (Seize the chance.)
- What about Dingding?
I'm texting her right now.
There are a few hours
until your meeting.
Why don't we go for the Japanese eatery
at the food district last time?
Anything you want.
What do you think?
It's good. I like it.
You have a lot of stuff here.
Looks expensive.
Aside from these,
I have a collection of old movies.
All the old movies you can think of,
I have their disks.
Really? That's good.
Anything you want to see?
If I don't have it, tell me.
I'll try to get a copy.
You can come over and watch it.
Come over here?
My editing room is a theater too.
Want to check it out?
Can I?
I asked you guys here
to see the edited version of the movie.
Of course you can check it out.
Let's go.
I made this video back in university.
It must've been ten years.
Ten years.
I was barely older than ten back then.
Yeah.
I remember a line in this video.
How should I describe
this scene I see?
It's a beautiful scene
I've never seen before.
This file
and the folder here
contain all my released
and unreleased works and BTS
over recent years.
Check them out.
Hello?
(How's it going, boy?)
Good news.
Tang Xin texted me.
She and Tang Yu won't go to the studio.
They're making a chance for you.
Seize it.
What? You guys can't
just make a chance like this.
If you aren't coming, why'd you call?
To check on the progress?
(No. I've been thinking about it,)
(and I'm worried about you.
You might fumble the ball.)
(Right, Lu.)
(Honestly,)
age isn't a problem.
It's the modern era.
What girls need is romance.
We'll talk later.
I...
The device crashed?
Reboot it.
♪Liking you like this
is love at first sight♪
♪Concealing the reason
for my sudden heartbeat♪
♪A solo journey through riddles♪
♪Every detail about you♪
Feng Cheng said
Tang Xin and your brother aren't coming.
Do you know what that means?
I did not delete
this BTS.
I couldn't do it.
♪Traversing a great distance♪
That's why I've been keeping it.
♪Just wanting to dream for you♪
Now I hand you the choice.
You can delete this.
I have no backups for this BTS.
This is a unique copy.
No one else has it.
♪Eyes meet, making a silent agreement♪
♪Holding hands,
embarking on a long journey♪
Or, you can give me your answer.
Is that alright?
Delete it,
or keep it around,
you decide.
♪The sound by my ear♪
♪Unraveling this mystery for you♪
♪Saying the answer, love♪
♪It's you♪
♪Liking you
goes beyond the initial sensation♪
♪Perhaps, our hearts
had already resonated long ago♪
♪Unknowingly, memories linger♪
The computer's coming back.
♪I believe, this dream belongs to you♪
♪I love you, who said you♪
♪The secret in my heart♪
Give me a quick answer.
I won't delete this.
I don't want to.
♪My decision is you♪
I'll keep it as a memento.
Can I?
♪Awaiting your response
as we flip through time♪
♪The sound by my ear♪
♪Unraveling this mystery for you♪
♪Saying the answer, love♪
♪It's you♪
You scared me.
I thought you'd delete it.
So...
So are we a couple now?
Of course.
Even if you want to break up,
I won't let you.
♪Suddenly we coincidentally meet♪
♪Suddenly love at first sight,
suddenly longing♪
♪Suddenly, it's you♪
♪Appearing by my side♪
♪Suddenly the sky is blue,
suddenly there's lightning♪
♪Suddenly my vision blurs for you♪
♪Suddenly, I feel♪
♪A bit tipsy♪
I'll be going then.
You sure you don't want me
to send you off?
Yeah. Just go back.
Yu is getting off work now.
If he finds out,
we'd be selling out Tang Xin.
Fine.
Dingding, this one's for you.
I'll get cavities, Mr. Lu.
You won't.
Just brush your teeth.
Alright, go back now.
Bye. Be careful.
(Tang Yu)
Hello?
I'm here.
You're picking me up, alright?
Okay, I'll be waiting.
What?
You want to film a proposal video?
And a secret filming too?
That is correct.
Even though Tang Xin
wants it to be simple
and private,
I think
we should at least record it.
My request is simple.
Edit it so it looks pretty.
But not too exaggerated.
Or just make it look lively.
That suits her better.
However,
don't make it flippant. Make it serious.
Alright, I'm stopping you there.
I think you should hire someone else.
I'm busy.
I can't trust anyone else.
I...
I can pay.
I take your silence as agreement.
Hey, that's just forced transaction.
NDA. Sign it.
Fine.
We've known each other for so long.
I'm not checking the contract.
I'll get you the gear.
I'll place the cameras
somewhere hidden.
Try not to have Tang Xin notice it.
And also,
I'll set a few things up
in some hidden spots.
Remember.
Find the mark during the proposal.
Alright.
You agreed fast.
I thought
I'd have to hash things out more.
Tang Xin's my friend too.
Just skip the formalities.
Lu, something feels off with you today.
Something's wrong.
You actually
smiled at me.
You were imagining things.
Move.
Just as well.
Look at this.
I picked this ring for Tang Xin.
What kind do you think is better?
You want me to pick a ring for Tang Xin?
You think she'll like what I pick?
You have a point.
I think I need to brush up
my requirements.
You mentioned hiding the cameras?
That's a good idea.
Can you up the number of cameras?
How does eight cameras sound?
How many do you want?
Eight.
Eight?
Is that too little?
No, it's enough.
Honestly, you...
Fine.
I'll come up with a plan.
We'll talk after that.
Okay?
If nothing else, you can leave now.
Or I'll leave.
Put your back into it.
I want the plan next week the latest.
(Tang Dingding: Mr. Lu.
What are you doing?)
(I think...)
(I think I miss you a little bit.)
I miss you too.
Who's missing you?
None of your business.
Not missing you, that's the point.
Cheeky.
You...
Just buying it?
Buying things out is insincere.
Listen to me, buddy.
If you have no money,
and you buy a gift for the lady,
then it's a rare treasure.
Problem is, you're filthy rich.
And you're still going to just buy stuff?
That's just flippant.
Especially when it's a wedding ring.
So you're saying
I have to make one myself?
Yep. You have tons of talented guys
working for you.
Why not use them?
A toast
to a successful proposal.
Should we engrave something here?
That's so cliché.
I think we should have a film here.
They started dating
during the movie's production.
- Right?
- Is this your proposal
or Tang Yu's proposal?
We'll go with this one.
Beautiful.
I'm prettier.
You're prettier.
One more problem.
Do you know the size of her finger?
Size?
What are you looking at?
Variety show.
You're a movie screenwriter.
Why are you watching variety shows?
It's called getting inspiration.
Maybe one of my future characters
is a variety show producer.
Oh, right.
You don't like the new project
and the topic selection the company
gave you two days ago?
I kind of don't want
to write romance for now.
I want to try something new.
Like thriller,
martial arts, or even sci-fi.
Fresh stuff.
You want to transform
Time Pictures again?
Never said I'd write for you guys.
Alley oop.
I can't get your new stuff
even when I'm your boyfriend?
Why don't we do this?
I'll tell Gao Heng to make you
a new screenwriter contract tomorrow.
All the original stories you write,
must be given to me first.
Unless I don't like them,
then you cannot give it to anyone else.
Even if you
want to take adaptation jobs,
you have to leave some slots for me.
Unless you don't want any projects
in our reserves,
then you can give your slot
to someone else.
But don't worry.
Anything you write,
I'll love it.
This isn't a contract signing.
You're being a bandit.
I just don't want you to be duped.
I want you to be a protected girl.
I applaud the thought.
But...
I want to be an independent woman.
I can't rely on you forever.
In case my son
doesn't want to inherit the family,
at least his mother has enough money
for him to chase his dreams.
But then,
his father isn't a stubborn guy.
If he wants to,
he can inherit my wealth.
If he doesn't want to,
he can do what he wants
and date who he wants.
What's that?
Nothing.
It's this wide.
So you didn't get to measure it?
What was I supposed to do?
Tang Xin's smart.
If she finds out,
the surprise is ruined.
It's alright.
This is fine.
Mr. Tang.
The ringmaker I hired is a pro.
He only makes three custom rings
like this every year.
If we don't hand in our design,
someone will take up our slot.
How long will it take?
Before "A Dream for You" airs.
I see. Thanks.
I hope we can get the stuff on time.
Okay.
We have work to do,
so we'll be leaving.
You do your work.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I will not
botch my best friend's happiness.
I'm counting on you.
Aren't you leaving?
Nope.
You...
I've gone through the contracts
of the two new artists signing on with us.
I've also given the promotional gifts
for "A Dream for You".
I've also given Mr. Gao the feedback.
Also,
the marketing plan you wanted me to do
is in progress now.
I have no work. Just let me
have the day off.
Fine.
Good weather today.
Let's have some coffee.
Coffee.
Thanks.
I think the first set's nice.
The lines are clear.
The style's new.
The patterns
have a retro air too.
If this is paired with jewelry,
it'll be great.
If we go with the first set,
I can recommend it to some magazines
and get you a cover photo.
It'll be great for marketing.
Thanks, Mr. Huo, but no thanks.
My talents haven't fallen to the point
of needing your recommendation
to survive.
But you do have an eye for aesthetics.
I prefer the first set as well.
I put too much thought
into the two sets after that,
so they feel redundant.
Then the first set it is.
I guess I'm not totally useless.
I've never denied
that everyone has flaws and strengths.
But some people
have more of flaws than strengths.
You have a point.
But I think
you haven't seen all my strengths yet.
Why don't we try it out?
Try what out?
You're single.
I'm single.
I'll stop you right there. No.
If it's fun you want, stay away from me.
All you get from me is a beating.
Why are you staring at me?
You talk a lot.
It feels weird when you stop talking.
The best part about me
is I know when to shut up.
You refused me clearly,
and I don't hound people.
However,
I have another strength.
I am patient.
Then I'd like to see
if that is really a strength.
(A Dream for You
ETA: 10 days)
I think
it's normal for us to lose out
to Indie Jones 5.
It's a Hollywood production,
and our airing slot is the same as theirs.
I've seen that movie.
I don't think
it's better than "A Dream for You".
Yeah.
Local movies are on the rise.
We can't give up so easily.
Well said.
That's why I summoned you guys here
to this meeting.
So you have a plan?
I cobbled a roadshow this morning.
Tell Gao Heng
about your schedule
and which roadshow you can go to.
I hope everyone
can attend every road show.
We'll do our best
to close the gap.
- Okay.
♪I yearn to resonate♪
♪In harmony with you♪
♪Side by side♪
(The Premiere of A Dream for You)
It's almost sold out.
I'm trying to get the tickets here.
Is that okay?
Yep. I got it.
(The Premiere of A Dream for You)
Told you to get the tickets sooner.
The seats are full.
Look.
Look at this five-star review on Douban.
Mr. Tang's roadshow is a success.
I heard this movie's airing overseas.
(Directed by Lu Zhixing)
(Screenply by Feng Cheng and Tang Xin)
(The Premiere of A Dream for You)
And finally,
I would like to especially thank
my female lead, Tang Dingding.
Her journey is still long.
I hope you'll give them a chance.
Encourage them.
Thank you.
♪The proud cheers♪
♪The inner struggles♪
(Box Office: Increasing)
♪I want to embrace the light,
refusing to admit defeat♪
You're now an actress
with a big hit under her belt.
Aren't you worried about paparazzis?
No.
I've checked the coast.
It's safe here.
And the movie sold for a billion.
We made this miracle together.
I can be allowed to kiss my boyfriend
and celebrate, can't I?
Sweetie.
I thought you said
you wanted to get some fruits
from the supermarket tonight.
Go.
It's late.
But I'm watching the show.
Can I buy it tomorrow?
Of course.
It's so painful all of a sudden.
What's wrong?
Where does it hurt?
My teeth.
Your teeth hurt? Here.
Open up. Let me see.
Open up and let me see.
Do we have anything
to treat hurting teeth at home?
I don't think we have.
I can go down and get some for you.
Sure.
A hurting tooth
can kill.
Yeah.
There's ice in the fridge.
- Just put them on your cheek.
- Okay.
It hurts here too.
I'll go right now.
Wait for me.
Be careful.
I'll be back as soon as possible.
I'm not in a hurry.
Twenty minutes.
Done.
Bubble gun.
Good.
Where's the ring?
Tang Yu.
I'm back with the meds.
Does your tooth still hurt?
Here.
Check it out.
This can work.
Why are you sweating so much?
Does it hurt a lot?
Um...
I was exercising.
It helps with the pain.
Right.
Now it doesn't hurt anymore.
It's alright.
Sit down.
Thanks for the help.
But...
I'll get you some tissue
- to wipe your sweat.
- It's alright.
I'll exercise some more.
Go.
It doesn't hurt now.
♪Hastily encountering fate's design♪
♪A glance turned, frozen in time♪
♪A universe of tenderness
in that fleeting view♪
♪At the crossroads of the night♪
♪Flowing streams of passing cars♪
♪Waiting in stillness
at our meeting place♪
♪The evening breeze
extinguishing the alley's glow♪
♪Embracing you♪
♪A forehead kiss so divine♪
♪Fearing the wait might be too long♪
♪By your side, I patiently abide♪
♪Yet, to love enough in every way♪
♪All of it♪
♪You are my everything♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
♪Deeply in love with you♪
♪Lucky to have met you♪
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪I accompany you
through the endless rainy season♪
♪Shielding you with an umbrella♪
♪If love creates miracles♪
♪Then that is my honor♪
♪How fortunate to have encountered you♪
♪Promising to never part for eternity♪
♪Our silent understanding♪
♪From this day forth♪
♪No longer a secret♪
♪Deeply in love with you♪
♪Lucky to have met you♪
♪We pledged never to part♪
♪Never to part♪
♪In the quiet night♪
♪Guarding a devoted passion♪
♪Afraid to be without you♪
♪How much I love you♪