THE FIRST RESPONDERS
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, INCIDENTS, GROUPS,
AND BACKGROUNDS DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
As a police officer,
I exerted my authority...
I exerted my authority and trampled
on the suspect's human rights.
I deeply regret my misconduct,
and I will take this as a lesson
to reform myself--
That darn Jindo Dog.
-With all my might.
-His dad will cover it up.
How envious. You're even slipping
through punishment.
Now you're criticizing me openly.
Knock it off.
See you.
REGIONAL INVESTIGATION UNIT
LIEUTENANT JIN HOGAE'S DIRECT ASSAULT
DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE
COMMITTEE MEMBER, CHAIRMAN
RESPONDENT
CHAIRMAN
AS A POLICE OFFICER, I EXERTED
MY AUTHORITY AND TRAMPLED ON...
You disregarded the prosecution's request
to hand over the suspect.
What's your deal?
Why are you taking my suspect?
Your suspect?
I guess you haven't grasped
the situation yet.
You got the wrong person.
Stop spewing crap.
Along with your unseemly language,
you punched the suspect's face.
Then you continued
with your indiscriminative violence.
In the end...
-Oh, no.
-He's crazy.
Jindo... I mean, Lieutenant Jin Hogae.
Do you have anything to say
before the voting?
Yes.
Hmm...
I trampled
on the suspect's human rights, and I...
Sir.
Honestly, that bastard is a real scum.
-What?
-Unbelievable.
He deserves more than just a beating.
When I see him again, he'll be dead meat.
-What?
-What did you say?
-That hopeless punk.
-Goodness.
Hey! You people are police officers.
Your job is to realize justice.
-What is he saying?
-He's unbelievable.
THE FIRST RESPONDERS
CODE ZERO: EMERGENCY CODE
ISSUED FOR A DANGEROUS FELONY
Good work today. Bye.
-Good work.
-Yeah.
You worked so hard today.
Thanks for coming.
I should have come sooner.
-Are you going this way?
-No, that way.
I see, I'm going this way.
Take care, and text me.
-See you around. Bye.
-Bye.
-Why won't she pick up?
-The number
-cannot be reached...
-She asked for instant noodles.
Are you awake?
Oh. I thought you were dead.
Who are you?
Don't you remember?
You were in an accident yesterday.
An accident?
So why would you roam around
in a remote place by yourself?
It really sucks for you.
Can I...
go now?
How will you go alone? You're hurt.
Call your family to come get you.
You're not going anywhere.
Please let go.
Why are you doing this to me?
Stay away from me!
Put that down.
Please... I want to go home.
Please let me go!
No, don't! I'm sorry!
Please don't!
This is where your heart is.
If stabbed properly,
you'll die in ten minutes.
Exsanguination. Have you heard of it?
This is where your liver is.
It has a big artery
called the hepatic artery.
The younger you are, the softer
your liver is, so it can tear easily.
No.
If you pull that out, you'll bleed a lot.
That's not good.
If you keep doing that,
that knife will cut the muscles,
veins, and nerves on your thigh.
Jeez.
Do you have to spill your blood like this
before you die?
Sohee.
Damn it.
Please call me. Anyone, hurry.
Reflect on yourself.
MOMMY
Where are you?
You shouldn't sleep out
without telling me.
Mom, call the police right now. Hurry.
INITIAL REPORT AT 8:38 A.M.
AROUND 8 HOURS AFTER ABDUCTION
Not yet. Wait.
Wait.
There! Let's eat!
-Get the noodles first.
-What about plates?
-Bring them here.
-The plates.
Here are plates that don't need a wash.
Take three each.
Hey. Won't it be too hot?
It cools down faster
once you fish them out.
What if the alarm rings?
Don't worry. It never rings
when I'm in my red underwear.
-Hey!
-Damn.
-What's this?
-What?
-Let's eat.
-What is that?
Whoo!
What a silly coincidence.
Be careful.
Where are you? We got a report!
Yes, Mr. Baek.
What is this so early in the morning?
It's Code Zero, an abduction case.
Run over here now!
Abduction?
Okay.
Darn it. I'm off.
If it's an abduction,
they might call for a joint response.
Eat quickly.
Dispatch for medical and rescue teams.
Abduction and detention victim
injured and requesting rescue.
Dispatch for medical and rescue teams.
Abduction and detention victim
injured and requesting rescue.
EMERGENCY MEDICAL SERVICE
That punk, Jindo Dog.
He's late to a case on his first day.
A Jindo dog?
Lieutenant Jin Hogae who's in a rut...
I mean, who's assigned today.
People called him the bastard Jindo Dog
in the Regional Investigation Unit.
He's one spiteful bastard
with no sense of seniority.
I guess you know him well.
I'd rather choose not to know him at all.
We'll be going first!
Is that all they train for every day?
Let's take off.
POLICE AND FIREFIGHTERS AT 8:40 A.M.
JOINT RESPONSE AND CODE ZERO ISSUED
The victim evacuated into a room,
locked the door, and made a report.
Then share the communications
with the fire crew
through the open wireless system.
Yes, sir.
Can't you hurry over here?
I'm so scared.
Where are you right now?
Well...
I'm not sure.
We got the location of her phone.
ONJO APARTMENTS
It's the Onjo Apartments.
But the base stations
in this area are 1.2 km apart.
I can't get any narrower.
This is Taewon Ambulance One,
received location.
This is ridiculous.
What?
This is an emergency response.
Motorcycle, move aside.
Motorcycle.
-What?
-What the...
What? He's making a way for us.
You're right.
Motorcycle, thank you.
What the heck was that?
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
Please move! We're in emergency response.
Turn off the siren.
You want to broadcast this everywhere?
Put the ambulance and pump here,
and follow me.
If they see fire trucks all lined up,
they'll know she made a report.
What's with that guy?
Excuse me!
Who are you to know about the case?
-Well...
-Move your cars right now!
I'm sorry. We're currently
in emergency response.
Please wait a moment.
Hey! I'm in an emergency, too.
Don't talk back to me.
Your paycheck comes from my taxes.
What do you think you're doing right now?
Let's not do this and just move the cars.
So what if you glare at me?
You want to bring it on?
-What are you doing?
-What?
-Mister.
-Damn...
Can't you see this yellow line?
Should I get you a ticket
for illegal parking?
Hey. Who are you to say this crap?
Fine, get me one.
Go ahead and get me a ticket.
Go on.
-What's your problem?
-What? Did you just hit me?
-Are you a thug?
-What?
-You little...
-Hey, Jindo Dog!
You can't get into a fight
on your first day!
Hello, sir.
You stay right here.
I'm not sure
about which building and unit I'm in.
We're close by, so calm down.
Tell me what you see outside the windows.
The windows won't open.
I can't see anything.
Listen...
I have a knife stuck in my thigh.
Hold on.
The victim must not move right now.
The knife could damage
her nerves or veins.
If it cuts her artery and leads
to a hemorrhagic shock,
we won't be able to talk to her again.
There are more than 1,000 houses here.
How do we find her without an address?
-Clean things up here.
-Yes.
-And come up to the rooftop.
-Yes, sir.
Let's move up our gear first.
Hurry up.
Is this it?
-They're all the same.
-They are?
Do you have CCTV cameras
at the entrances?
There are five car entrances.
But there's only one CCTV camera
at the center.
The rest is a blind spot.
It can't be that easy
to drag an adult woman to his house
in an apartment complex.
Did any resident
see anything strange last night?
No one.
Anyway, the culprit lives here.
Maengpil, hurry and identify
any ex-convicts
-among the residents.
-Yes, sir.
Especially if there are any sex offenders.
-Yes, sir. Let's go.
-Yes.
-Are we connected?
-Yes, just now.
Check the victim's condition.
Can you hear me? I'm a paramedic.
What is your name?
Kim Sohee.
I see, Ms. Kim. Let me ask you one thing.
Does blood gush out from your wound
every time you breathe?
Or is it coming out little by little?
It's gushing out every time I breathe.
I see. Then lie down and press your wound.
It might hurt,
but press it as hard as you can. Okay?
Okay.
A thigh injury isn't a serious one, is it?
A pulsatile bleeding
that follows the heartbeat
is a hard sign of a severed artery.
There's a femoral artery in our thighs.
The situation is very serious.
How much time do we have?
Until she collapses or dies
due to excessive bleeding,
we have an hour at most.
Only an hour?
This is driving me crazy.
So, did you reflect on yourself?
Please...
Please don't kill me.
I'm so scared.
So why did you have to crawl in there?
Good job. It'll be easy to clean up.
Let me boil some water.
He's boiling water.
That lunatic.
-Boiling water?
-Please help me.
What is he trying to do?
Ms. Kim, it's okay. Calm down.
Tell us everything you heard, saw,
and felt about the culprit.
Even a small clue can help the profiling.
Well, he used medical terms
like where a heart is,
and exsanguination or something.
Listen. Is there anything
we can spot from outside?
Like if he hung something out
on the veranda.
No, nothing.
It's all covered with plastic
and the curtains are closed.
There's a wheelchair in the living room.
The bathroom is very clean.
Sanitary pads.
There are a lot of sanitary pads.
This bastard is a perverted lunatic.
He's not a lunatic.
He's a perfectionist and most likely
works in the medical field.
He knows how to get rid of evidence.
So, he's not a first offender.
It's good, then.
We just need to check
the list of ex-convicts.
It wouldn't be this simple
to catch a guy like him.
Mr. Baek!
-You got the list?
-Yes.
There are no ex-convicts living here.
Not even one?
What's going on?
Hey, you there.
Let me ask you something.
Where do you keep sanitary pads?
Excuse me?
Where do you keep
your sanitary pads at home?
In the bathroom.
So why does he have sanitary pads
in his bathroom?
A lot, at that.
Maybe he got those from the victims
as trophies.
No, guys like him don't keep trophies.
It could work as crucial evidence later.
Then what's with the pads?
They were there from the start.
It's not his house.
Search through KICS
for any missing female residents.
Even the unsolved cases.
This bastard already killed one
and settled down there.
Yes, an unsolved case. Please hurry.
KICS, KOREA INFORMATION SYSTEM
OF CRIMINAL-JUSTICE SERVICES
Ms. Kim, are you okay?
I'm so cold.
Try pressing your nail.
Does it turn back pink?
No, it stays white.
She's having cyanosis,
a symptom of hemorrhagic shock
accompanied by hypothermia.
If her body temperature
falls lower than 32 degrees Celsius,
or she loses more than two liters
of blood, she'll be unconscious.
In the worst case,
she could lose her life.
Dojin, get ready.
Okay. Message me.
I'm so sleepy.
Mom.
Ms. Kim, you shouldn't fall asleep.
Keep talking to me. Okay?
Ms. Kim, can you hear me?
Why isn't she answering?
She shouldn't pass out.
You said we had an hour.
Sohee, pull yourself together.
You need to see your mom.
Sohee.
Kim Sohee!
Mom...
Yes, right. You must stay awake
to see your mom.
Mom.
Kim Sohee, do not pass out.
Do you hear me?
No one went missing
in Onjo Apartments, Woosung-dong.
There weren't any missing reports.
Gosh.
You said there would be.
What do we do?
You know the victim's condition
is getting worse.
The fire crew will begin searching.
-Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
Wait. Not yet.
Got any other way then?
There were no missing reports?
Then let's try one more.
Kim Yeji, aged 27.
Her last phone call was four months ago.
There's no history since then.
The bill and installments are all overdue.
And her credit cards?
They're the same as her phone.
They haven't been used
since four months ago.
All her bills are overdue,
so her account is reported as delinquent.
-What's her address?
-Building 103, unit 1305.
It's a high floor. Let's move.
Let's go.
Let's get a move on, fire crew.
All right.
Mmm.
Won't you open the door?
Come out and eat with me.
It won't be good if it goes cold.
I think he's back.
He's talking nonsense
about eating with him.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry and unlock the door.
It's a digital lock
with a mechanical spare key.
The hardest one to unlock.
We'll have to open it by force.
Then he'll notice.
What if he loses it?
What do we do?
I doubt there is a master key.
We'll try to figure out a way.
Darn it. Jindo Dog, are you nuts?
Is it the detectives?
Please wait a moment.
Who is it?
Hi, I'm from downstairs.
There's a leak in my ceiling.
I'm wondering
if it's coming from your house.
I didn't turn on any water.
It's practically flooded downstairs.
I can't just take your word for it.
I'm with someone from maintenance.
Let us go in and check.
I'm from the maintenance office.
We'll have to check
if there's any leakage.
What is...
You bastard.
Ms. Kim!
Freeze.
You're under arrest on charges
of abduction, confinement, and rape.
What?
Ms. Kim!
-She's not here.
-What's going on?
-No?
-What?
-She's not in the bathroom either.
She's not here.
Hey, where did you hide
the woman you abducted?
Hide? What are you talking about?
You shouldn't smoke in the bathroom.
My house is filled
with smoke from here.
I'm sorry.
I've been stressed out lately. That's why.
I won't do it again.
I'm sorry.
Be extra careful
from now on. Okay?
Sure.
Let's please keep things peaceful, okay?
I'll be careful.
I'm sorry.
Where's the woman who lived here?
She's in hospice care.
I hear she's completely paralyzed
at the late stage of osteosarcoma.
What about that woman?
Goodness.
-BAEKL I'm sorry about this.
-Darn it.
We've confirmed Ms. Kim Yeji
to be under hospice care.
Her condition worsened drastically
and she had to leave everything behind.
Her support worker visits her house
to get things for her from time to time.
All right, understood.
Hey, Jindo Dog.
We wasted our effort all together,
because of your wrong guess.
And we're running out of time, darn it.
ARREST FAILURE AT 9:12 A.M.
34 MINUTES SINCE THE REPORT
Mom...
I guess you still have energy.
Dojin, shouldn't we do something?
We can't be wasting time like this.
Let's do something!
This is driving me crazy.
Let's search in a joint group of two.
There seems to be no other way.
-There is a way.
-Can't you just...
Honestly speaking,
we wasted so much time because of you.
What other way? What's left?
Fire crew.
Let's do something you hate the most.
Set fire?
The smoke will allow us
to locate her right away.
What about the victim?
If we waste our time, she'll die, anyway.
Either the abductor
or excessive bleeding will kill her.
Fire cycles accelerate in confined spaces,
so it spreads immediately.
Are you aware of that?
Good, it'll make smoke quickly.
She just needs to be away
from the fire for a moment.
Fire isn't the only thing
that causes people to die.
Suffocation, oxygen deficiency,
-and--
-How talkative.
Mr. Baek, let's just take action!
-It's annoying.
-It's too dangerous!
This is driving me crazy.
It takes more than an hour
to search every building here.
What if the abductor sees us
and goes wild?
My earphones are out of battery.
Why aren't you here yet?
Sohee, we'll be there soon.
Wait just a little longer. Okay?
Can't you make it?
It's...
all over now.
No, we'll be there soon. Don't give up.
Sohee.
I also...
want to go home.
Ms. Kim. If you want to go home,
pull yourself together and listen to me.
Check if there's a lighter
near the toilet.
What?
Yes, there's one.
Ms. Kim, start a fire right now.
You little... I said no!
What are you doing?
We need to send her home.
Put out the fire and rescue her!
That's what firefighters do.
That's a battery warning.
It'll be disconnected soon.
Mr. Baek!
Sohee, trust us and start a fire.
We'll find you no matter what.
It has no gas.
The lighter doesn't work!
She'll arrive soon.
Isn't there any other way? Fire crew.
Goodness, it's driving me crazy.
Is it a normal gas lighter?
Yes, it is.
Then do as I say from now on.
Take the iron plate off it first.
Wrap it with toilet paper
and scratch the spark wheel on the floor.
Then sparks will be made.
Oh, no. I don't think I can do it.
My hand feels so weak.
Ms. Kim, it's not difficult.
Just keep trying.
-What happened?
-I'll tell you on the way.
This way.
We're taking her.
Ms. Kim, you can do it.
Ms. Kim, don't fall asleep!
-Ms. Kim. Ms. Kim.
-Her mother's here.
Just a moment.
Sit here, ma'am.
What happened to my Sohee?
You can start talking.
Sohee, it's your mom.
I'm here. Can you hear me?
Mom...
Yes, the people here will rescue you.
So try one more time.
Just one more time. Okay?
It worked.
Ms. Kim, put the toilet paper
near the windows!
It worked. We have no time!
Wet a towel in the bathroom,
cover your nose with it, and bend down.
We'll be right there.
Ma'am, it's okay. Come this way.
Sending out the heat detector.
It's responding.
Arrest Team, come to the rooftop HQ.
-I called them in.
-Okay.
Stand by. I'll let you know
as soon as we locate her.
High heat detected!
-Ten o'clock direction!
-Do you see it?
It's Building 1202!
Building 1202 on the 12th floor. Let's go.
Not through the front door.
What is it this time?
What about the front door?
It's a two-bay house
with a deep entrance hallway.
The fire from the room
will cause a rollover.
And the door won't open.
Then what should we do?
Follow me.
Yes, sir.
Send a high-ladder truck
to Onjo Apartments. It's a high-rise fire.
What do you mean?
There hasn't been a report.
I'll explain later. How long will it take?
It'll take at least ten minutes from now.
Ten minutes?
Ten minutes... It'll be too late then.
Hold on.
You can operate a ladder truck, right?
Yes. Should I get it ready?
We'll take care of it.
Go on.
Guys, are we ready?
Yes, we've loaded the hose nozzle,
oxygen tank, respirator, and lifter.
Listen carefully.
Us two will enter through the veranda.
Then we'll put out the fire first.
What do you mean, us? Me too?
Aren't you going to arrest him?
-Darn it.
-Get him geared up.
Yes. Let's go this way.
Dojin, I'm going with you.
It'll be too late
if I don't treat the victim right away.
And I promised I'd be there.
Okay, get ready.
The lower smoke is flowing backward.
The smoke being sucked in
means no more oxygen inside.
The moment we open up the room,
the oxygen inflow will cause an explosion.
A back draft, I mean.
Isn't it a good thing?
That bastard is dying to open the room.
You're crazy.
Hey. If the fire exhausts the oxygen,
the victim will suffocate.
What are you saying?
You're taking oxygen tanks.
Don't you care about the victim at all?
Whatever. You guys, rescue her.
I'll get the culprit.
Do I get on that thing?
Closing the gate.
Hey, Detective Team. Go around there.
-Lift us.
-Lifting.
Here it is.
All right. I'll open the door now.
That's not it.
Let's see...
Sorry I kept you waiting.
They're open. Open them.
We've entered the house.
Start pumping it up.
I'll turn off the radio now.
Get the hose nozzle.
We'll put out the fire,
and I'll go inside to rescue the victim.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
Don't move.
Or this bastard dies.
Tell the ladder truck guy
that you're going down.
Now.
-What do we do?
-I don't know.
The smoke being sucked in
means no more oxygen inside.
The moment we open up the room,
the oxygen inflow will cause an explosion.
A back draft, I mean.
Hey. You didn't know we were
on the phone with the girl, did you?
That little...
I almost hurled listening to your rants.
You crazy bastard.
Stab me. Are you scared?
Let me get promoted thanks to this.
I personally need it, too.
If he cuts my carotid, treat me.
You bastard.
If you wanted to take a hostage,
you should have gotten the girl, not me.
A back draft is about to occur.
-What about you?
-We'll have to go along with it.
If you're going to kill someone,
see the end of it.
Only a loser gives up in the middle.
Dodge!
Start spraying!
Spraying!
Locate the fire's center point
and spray it wide!
I'm going inside.
WIDE SPRAY
SPRAYING THE WATER IN A WIDESPREAD MANNER
Ms. Kim!
Go take care of her!
Ms. Kim.
That little brat...
Hey! You said you'd get the culprit.
Wake up, you darn bastard!
Hey!
Mom...
Ms. Kim. Are you awake?
Let go!
You crazy bastard!
You darn bastard!
There's no getting out
once a Jindo dog bites you.
Gosh, I almost lost all my teeth.
Darn it.
RESCUE AND ARREST COMPLETE AT 9:35 A.M.
57 MINUTES AFTER THE REPORT, CASE CLOSED
Sohee!
Sohee.
It's Mom. Are you okay?
It's me. Your mom's here.
Mom.
She did a great job hanging in there.
She's safe now.
Thank you.
Get going.
Let's go.
-Good work.
-Thanks.
I'm exhausted. Aren't you?
I am.
Hey, your hair got burned.
It's okay. I was going to get
a haircut, anyway.
Right, you can always grow
your hair again.
We've identified
his fingerprint, and his--
Goodness.
His name is Cho Doochil, aged 37.
He ran an animal hospital
until it was suspended
due to overprescribing
and illegal euthanasia.
Overprescribing and illegal euthanasia.
I knew it.
Wait.
He's burned badly.
I'll take him to the hospital first.
Wait.
One plus one.
Stop glaring at me.
You beat me up to a pulp.
That plastic in the bedroom
was impressive.
You wouldn't get one trace of DNA.
I've never seen such an honest cop.
You knew, and you bit me like a dog.
Hey.
Let's have a serious conversation.
Conversation, my foot.
Why would I ever tell on myself?
Come on. It's not like that.
I know you're itching to brag.
Consider the expertise
of forensic investigations these days.
And you committed hidden crimes
that weren't even reported.
HIDDEN CRIME
A CRIME NOT REPORTED HENCE NOT REGISTERED
Yes, I'm sure you want to brag about it.
But unfortunately,
the witnesses are all dead.
We can figure out everything
just by checking the pipes and blender.
Just come clean. How many did you kill?
Six and a half.
A half?
I didn't finish that girl from earlier.
Get up, you bastard.
What happened to the woman
who lived there?
Her family lives abroad.
I sent them a text from time to time.
You paid her phone bills, too?
Yes, I considered it a monthly rent.
So you probably used the same method.
You disguise it as an accident,
render them unconscious
with animal anesthetics,
and transport them in a wheelchair.
Others might have thought
you were a devoted husband.
A kind man...
is never suspected.
Why did you kill them?
There was only one thing that satisfied me
in my whole life.
So I did just that.
Do I need a reason?
Did you realize it
through illegal euthanasia?
Humans are no different.
Humans and dogs are the same.
When they know they're about to die,
they urinate and even foam at the mouth.
They desperately beg me to spare them.
You don't know
how pathetic people can get before death.
But I...
become noble instead.
And...
Crazy bastard.
You know you shouldn't use violence.
Gosh, he pisses me off.
Hey, what you said just now
will work against you in court.
What's so funny?
So what?
Close your eyes and shut up.
I'll cool down the area.
Your inner skin is exposed.
It could be infected.
THE SAFEST TAEWON,
RESPECTED AND BELOVED TAEWON POLICE
-Pork belly.
-Pork belly?
-Kimchi?
-Kimchi.
-Kimchi stir-fried pork.
-Let's go before it gets cold.
-You're not going anywhere.
You guys visit next door to slack off
whenever you get a chance.
Are you the police or firefighters?
I'll stay with you until I die.
Jeez.
This Taewon Police Station
is not a recyclable bin.
I don't get why
they assign only the idiots here.
I'm going to get constipated
because of you guys.
Should I get you some diapers then?
Is this my desk?
-Yes.
-Good to see you.
Hello.
From smoke into smother.
You didn't get to say hi, did you?
He's Jindo Dog.
I mean, Detective Jin Hogae.
I'm Kongmyeong Pil
from the Detective Team.
My surname is Kongmyeong,
and my given name is Pil.
Just call him Maengpil.
That's how everyone does.
My name isn't Maengpil.
My surname is Kongmyeog,
and my given name is Pil.
You're a funny guy.
My name isn't Jindo Dog. It's Jin Hogae.
They just call me Jindo Dog.
I'm Bong Anna from the Forensic Team.
I did some real work in a long time.
A criminal caught in the act
sure is worth searching through the AFIS.
Yes, and putting handcuffs on.
Also, whom should I tell this to?
You can tell me.
This vehicle was parked illegally
near Onjo Apartments.
I took a picture.
Send him a parking ticket right away.
What is it?
You're so spiteful.
Do you know each other?
When he went to police academy,
I was his mentor.
As if. All you did was make me drink.
Look at you.
That's what mentors are for.
Buying drinks during your hard times.
By the way, did you call your father
to tell him you were assigned to Taewon?
A busy chief prosecutor has no time
to answer a police officer's call.
My goodness.
Your father's a chief prosecutor?
Don't freak out. We cut ties long ago.
But, Detective, I heard you were doing
well at the Regional Investigation Unit.
Why were you assigned here in the suburbs?
Do you want to know?
Last fall when the leaves were falling,
I went on a trip to Busan.
I went on a subway and dozed off.
When I woke up...
Then what?
The train was at some subway station
with a dual-side platform.
It was between Busanjin Station
and Beomil Station.
This stop is Jwacheon,
Jwacheon Station.
It cost me 180,000 won
to come back by taxi.
That's a lot of money.
What? That's all?
You need to finish up the story.
Why that punk... 180,000 won?
Those little...
Hey, Pil.
Is Lieutenant Jin Hogae part of your team?
Apparently, he was really big
in the Regional Investigation Unit.
-But--
-Feign ignorance, guys.
His nickname there was Jindo Dog.
He went wild barking
and ended up getting demoted.
It was not Mad Dog?
No wonder he made the scene into a mess.
Dogs often make a mess out of things.
Who wants rice?
-Me.
-Me. I'll have some.
Are you sure this is the cheapest studio?
I'm telling you.
It's the same size,
but the monthly rent is 40% cheaper.
Stamp your seal on it.
The number cannot be reached...
Why wouldn't she pick up?
I think it's way too cheap.
Are you sure it has no problems?
Gosh, it's not like that.
That place is close to both
the police and fire stations.
It's safe and nice.
I see.
GEUMHWANG REAL ESTATE AGENCY
JIN HOGAE
-Thank you.
-Sure.
CHIEF PROSECUTOR JIN CHULJOONG
The number cannot be reached...
You seem to be on great terms
with your son, Chief Prosecutor.
Jindo dogs are known
to be very wild, you see.
The wilder it is,
you need to keep it on a tighter leash.
Now that he's come to Taewon,
he'll be under our control
no matter how wild he gets.
What an exhausting day, isn't it?
No, wait. Stop!
-What?
Let's see... The eighth floor.
Is there a fire on the eighth floor?
No way. Two firefighters
live on that floor.
Right.
We're neighbors now.
I'll be seeing you often.
Let's not see each other often.
It's not good to have a case big enough
for a joint response.
Still, a detective needs a case
to warm up a little.
What did you tell the abductor
earlier today?
I irritated him a bit.
You responded quickly there.
As if.
What is this?
Did you sign the lease
because of the cheap rent?
I guess you need to warm up some more.
What then?
Am I not allowed
to sign a cheap lease as I want?
That place...
is haunted.
It's true.
Damn it.
There's a call!
Assumed suicide. An unlock request.
Level one response.
Those off duty included.
What are you doing? Come.
Me?
Assumed suicide
is a joint response for sure.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
This is better than a ghost.
THE FIRST RESPONDERS
WE WOULD LIKE TO THANK JEONG JAE-EUN &
KIM JUNG-HO FOR THEIR SPECIAL APPEARANCES
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs