Lord Song.
(Song Ancestral Hall)
The Duke requests your presence.
The elders from both families are here.
I'm not going.
I don't see the need to be there.
Since everything is already arranged,
why put on airs and graces now?
Lord Song.
His Majesty has decreed.
If word of this gets out,
people would chastise both of you
for being ill-mannered
and disregarding your family duties.
Even the officials
may call you disrespectful and rude.
My reputation has never been pristine.
I don't care.
You should go.
It's good for you
to see what's going on.
Ms. Longevity.
Even in a war, civility comes first.
Besides, we'll be staying
here for a long time.
We can't avoid them forever.
You have never been one
to back down so easily.
What's wrong with you now?
Are you scared?
Why would I be scared of them?
But I promised you
that you wouldn't have
to deal with such trouble.
This is only our first day of marriage.
It's fine.
Come on.
=Blossom=
(Adapted from the novel "Blossom" by Zhi Zhi)
=Episode 20=
(Duke of Ying's Residence)
You offered tea to Huisun first?
You offered tea
to a dead person before us.
You have no regard for rules.
We didn't know that all of you
have been waiting for us here.
It's just that
the dead must always
be remembered and honored.
That's what His Majesty said
during one of his hunting trips.
What a glib tongue.
(Wife of the Eldest Uncle)
Even the tea has turned cold.
Is this how you act
right after you married into our family?
Yes, the tea has gone cold.
You should brew
(Wife of the Third Uncle)
a new pot of tea for us.
Come on.
Eldest Uncle, Third Uncle,
have you forgotten
what happened here?
Yizhi Hall detached itself
from this residence
soon after my mother passed away.
As the saying goes, "when
everyone has left, the tea turns cold."
That's why the tea is already cold.
Do not forget
that you are the future Duke of Ying!
You are right, Father-in-law.
Now that I am married to Lord Song,
that makes me the future duke's wife.
Father-in-law, drink some tea.
(General)
This is for you, Sister-in-law.
My brother used to play chess with me
whenever he returned.
We may not play regularly anymore,
but you're here to keep him company.
Thank you, Han.
It's not like I'd have
your brother all to myself.
Now that you have
a sister-in-law to dote on you,
you should visit us more often.
See?
Han is such a sensible child.
Actually, we have prepared gifts
for our new niece-in-law.
All that talking
made us forget about it.
Bring the gifts.
Thank you for the gifts.
I guess there's a lot I need
to learn from you as a newly wed.
Since I am now part of this family,
I shall humbly learn from you.
It's not that much.
Now that Yantang is married,
our family has decided to do our part
and renovate Yizhi Hall
as a token of our affection.
That's a wonderful idea.
Once Zhao deposits her dowry
into the residence's treasury,
you may proceed with the renovations.
This farcical ceremony
and your sweet promises
are just a ruse
to confiscate Zhao's dowry.
By tradition, the eldest daughter-in-law
is the mistress of the household.
Eldest Aunt, instead of handing over
the tokens and keys to the treasury,
you keep eyeing on my wife's money.
Yantang.
That's not true.
Even though we've separated
from the main residence
after your mother died,
your eldest aunt is still responsible
for managing the finances
and daily operations of the household.
Your wife has just
married into our family.
Someone has to guide and teach her.
That's not necessary.
My wife has already calculated
and declared all her assets
in front of His Majesty.
Even the Ministry of Revenue
has adopted her calculation formulas.
I wasn't so calculative in the past,
but since you are so particular
about money,
we should separate
the treasury accounts too.
What are you saying?
The Emperor has always advised us
to maintain harmony in the family.
It's improper for you to defy.
Besides, running the household
is no easy task.
There are dozens of issues that
need to be settled every day.
It's normal to stay up late.
- Third Aunt...
- Third Aunt,
those are exactly our biggest concerns.
Money is simply superficial.
Family harmony matters the most.
Since all of you care about me,
I shall let Eldest Aunt
manage my dowry.
Su Lan.
Call Mr. Chen here.
Yes.
I knew my daughter-in-law
would be sensible.
Your elder is willing
to go all out to help you.
You must be grateful.
You are right, Father-in-law.
This...
I thought you lost
all your money in Futing?
Yes.
However, that was not my only asset.
My other ventures
have been successful.
The Miaos' potato
business has taken off.
I funded 80% of their starting capital.
Young Lady.
I did a rough calculation.
There's about 70,000 taels here.
- Zhao has a keen eye for business.
- This...
This is the dividend
she earned this year.
You mean, 70,000 taels
is just the dividend?
Just two chests of these
is worth ten years' of food
expenses in the residence.
Don't act like an ignorant fool.
She might laugh at you.
I was planning to deposit my dowry
and the dividend here
into the residence's treasury
to share the elders' burden
by managing the residence's accounts.
By then, our wealth is expected
to grow by 20% every year.
Our real estate, trading,
and agricultural ventures
can generate at least
70,000 to 80,000 taels in profit.
Now that Eldest Aunt
will manage everything,
I'm sure you will earn more than I do.
70,000 to 80,000 taels a year?
How could I?
Yes, yes.
My dowry also includes
some farming lands and shops
that I have co-invested with other
aristocratic ladies.
If our profits were to fall,
I'm afraid they'd stop working with us.
After all, it's important
to maintain business credibility.
Once you lose it,
it's hard to maintain
business connections,
and you might even
offend other stakeholders.
Everyone in the capital knows
(Eldest Daughter-In-Law)
that you're a skilled businesswoman.
My mother-in-law spends all her time
managing the household.
It's not even worth mentioning
compared to your business ventures.
I guess it's better
that we keep our accounts separate
so that we don't end up arguing
over money matters.
As a man,
it is pathetic to eye
on his wife's dowry.
Miss Miao,
take the money back
so that we don't
attract unwanted gossip.
Sure, I'll continue managing
Zhao's business on her behalf.
Take them back.
- No...
- This is...
Zhao.
Mind telling me
how you earned so much money?
I didn't expect
that we have such
a capable niece-in-law.
Yichun, why don't we let her
manage the residence's
private assets as well?
She's family, after all.
We can trust her, right?
Yes, that's a great idea.
If that's what you wish,
I wouldn't say no,
but if my father-in-law doesn't agree,
I wouldn't defy him.
Yichun.
You...
I'm keeping my hands off this.
Wait.
- Yichun.
- Yichun, you can't just leave.
Zhao.
Can you also
reserve a spot for us
- in your business ventures too?
- Yes, Zhao.
We have some savings.
- We can pass them to you...
- I thought she
was good at observing palace politics,
but I didn't know she's also good
at managing household affairs.
I know you want to protect her,
but the deaths of
the Duke of Ding and Mrs Jiang
are connected.
In this large residence,
we can only start investigating
through money allocations
and what the servants say and do.
Young Lady is trying to gain power here
so that she could help you
win the favor of the household.
By then, we will get to access
the matching tokens.
That's right.
(Meritorious Service)
Yichun.
You can't just stay out of this.
We're talking about
70,000 to 80,000 taels.
As they say, money is king.
Exactly.
We don't have to be scared
since the matching tokens
are still in our hands.
That's right.
Have I not treated you well?
She's only been here for a day,
and yet she's already got you
all under her thumb?
No...
You're a disgrace to our ancestors!
What a stubborn man.
Come on.
Yichun.
This is about money.
Stop wasting your
breath on him, Brother.
Come out!
Your Grace.
Don't worry.
Everyone in the residence
is loyal to you.
She's just a newcomer.
The servants wouldn't listen to her.
She'd soon realize
how difficult it is to survive here.
I underestimated Dou Zhao.
To think a young lass like her
could be so sly.
Perhaps I made a mistake
and infuriated that defiant son of mine?
Everyone in the capital knows
that my father and I
have separated our households.
As for my uncles, aunts
and their daughter-in-law,
you don't have to
worry about their assets.
Better yet, you don't have
to interact with them,
or else you might fall sick from anger.
I approached them
not to let them infuriate me.
Your father doesn't want me
to manage the residence's treasury
and tries to convince
his brothers to stop me.
However, they've never been of one mind.
Your uncles are money-hungry.
Your eldest aunt
isn't as strong as she looks.
Your third aunt is an easy read.
They may seem to follow
your father's arrangements,
but they all have their own minds.
Only your eldest uncle's
daughter-in-law is clever enough
to know that if she gets caught between you
and your father,
the deal would be off.
She may be our breakthrough point.
What's wrong?
You know them well
though you've only met them once.
How could my wife be so clever?
Back when I saved Wu Shan in the manor,
you also immediately recognized
the hidden dynamics in my family.
In fact, you're better at identifying
the subtle expressions
on people's faces.
If the Duke of Ying's Residence
tries to do anything funny,
get Mr. Chen to find me
at the Imperial Guards.
Don't carry the burden alone.
You just called me
a strategist last night,
and now you don't trust me?
It's not that.
I'm just worried.
By the way,
let me give you something as protection.
This is my first time.
It's fine.
Stay calm.
Look at your target.
Aim.
This is even louder than the fireworks.
- Careful, it's hot.
- You didn't even blink.
It's normal to be scared
on your first try.
The more scared you are,
the calmer you need to be.
Stay calm.
Relax.
I'm beside you.
I missed.
You're already doing a good job.
If you can hit the wind chimes today,
you'd pass your first entrance test.
Try it.
I'm going to freshen up.
I hit it!
My dear.
You have talent.
What happened to your hand?
Show me.
Why is it bleeding again?
It's fine.
It's nothing.
Yantang.
I said I can bathe by myself.
Your hand is still injured.
Before it heals, you need
to keep it away from water.
Allow me.
It's fine.
I can manage myself.
Allow me.
If I can't take care of you
when you're injured,
how could I call myself your wife?
I didn't expect that
the mighty General Song
can feel shy sometimes.
♪Riding across the desolate battlefield in the wind♪
♪The turbulence unfolding one after another♪
♪The lingering uncertainty has yet been resolved♪
♪I gaze at you, and all is calm♪
♪The world is vast and turbulent♪
When I said I could manage,
I wasn't being shy.
I didn't want to scare you.
♪When the time comes,
all pride will be laid down♪
Back at Zhaowen Bookstore,
after Mr. Chen bandaged
your wounds, he said
that your back is covered in scars.
I see them now.
♪Ferrying me to the other side♪
♪You're my light of redemption
amid the darkness♪
♪You're my saving grace♪
♪Warming my heart♪
Ms. Longevity, I'm sorry.
You got these scars from defending
our nation and people.
In fact, you injured your shoulder
to protect me.
There's nothing to apologize for.
Yantang.
When two people live together,
the most important thing
is to make each other feel
more comfortable
and free.
In the future,
no matter what happens,
we need to be honest with each other
and face everything together,
won't we?
Sure, I promise you.
(Reinvigorating Spring)
Your Lordship.
You're here, Ming.
You're hiding something from me?
I'll see it anyway.
Let me look.
Ming.
You'll get to see it
when I finish drawing.
No, I want to see it now.
Ming.
This is a secret.
Fine.
Have some fruits, Your Lordship.
Let me see!
Why are you keeping it from me?
- I'm not showing you.
- Let me see!
Your Lordship, come on.
Ming, I'll show you when it's done.
Ming, you look so pretty today.
Your Lordship, Your Ladyship.
The Eight Treasure soup
for Madam Wei is ready.
Time to greet her.
Greet her?
All we do is greeting those people.
How annoying.
Fine, you may leave now.
Yes, Your Lordship.
I'm going, then.
Thank you, Ming.
Go.
How dare you talk back?
What happened?
Did Nanny Zhou do anything wrong?
She was trying to order you around,
and all I did was to rebuke her.
You're serving the young duke's wife,
and I'm serving the senior duke's wife.
Rebuking me is an act of disrespect
towards your mistress's sister-in-law.
Make sure you remember that
on behalf of your mistress.
Your Ladyship.
- Nanny.
- Your Ladyship.
Ming.
Serve the soup now.
Hurry up.
Your Ladyship.
You have to kneel and lift the bowl
over your head to show your respect.
I prepared the rehmannia root
in the soup all by myself.
I heard this soup is beneficial
for your constitution.
Since this is the Duke's residence,
we're very particular
about rules and decorum.
From helping your mother-in-law
get dressed in the morning,
to preparing your
mother-in-law's bed at night,
these are your duties
as a daughter-in-law.
Make sure you learn
and follow all these rules
in the days to come.
Your sister is already contributing
her wealth and power
towards the Duke of Ying's Residence.
And you?
Do you even know
how much money we have,
and how long it'll last?
The current deficit
is caused by the grand funeral
held years ago
when the previous duke and duchess died.
You must have heard
how much Dou Zhao's dowry
and personal assets are.
We took you in,
yet you're not showing any gratitude.
All you're doing now is keeping
my silly brother happy.
Have you thought about
the residence's future?
What happened to the benefits
your mother promised us?
What are you doing?
Ming, come on.
Get up.
Are you fine?
What happened to your hands?
As your sister, it's normal for me
to teach your wife about decorum.
This has nothing to do with you.
This is my residence,
not yours.
Of course this is my business.
If it's about money,
I can sell my paintings
and calligraphy works.
I know you're jealous
of Dou Zhao's dowry,
but you can't vent out
on Ming.
What did you say?
I've paid so much for you
over the years,
and you've been taking it for granted.
Now, all I'm asking
is that she contribute some money
to help the residence,
and you're chastising me?
The heavens must be blind.
They should have sent
a bolt of lightning to strike you!
Sister-in-law.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have started this argument
between you and my husband.
As for your request,
I will ask my mother when I return home.
Slow and steady does it.
Be careful.
Put them here.
So many gifts.
This must be a first in the Capital.
I hope you'll enjoy
the gifts I prepared.
Let's talk inside.
This way.
You're trying to embarrass my daughter.
Still, if you weren't
as rich as you are now,
I'm sure Song Mo
wouldn't treat you so well.
My daughter Ming and the Duke of Jining
are happily in love.
They don't need
these material possessions.
You are
just a pitiful girl.
Hearing these words from your mouth
is actually surprising.
Money is hard-earned,
but love fades easily.
This is what
I learned from you years ago.
Seventh Madam.
The Duchess of Jining is back.
Your looks haven't changed
over the years, Mother.
We don't look like
mother and daughter now.
Instead, we look like sisters.
Exactly.
I feel so relieved
now that you're no longer here,
so I look younger naturally.
On the contrary,
it's only been a while
since you got married,
and you've lost so much weight.
Has Wei Tingzhen been abusing you?
Is this how the Duchess of Jing
behaves as a sister-in-law?
Someday,
I'll settle these scores with her.
Mother.
The Duke is protective of me.
He treats me very well.
As if.
What gifts did he bring
the last time he came?
Just look at your sister today.
The Duke and I don't care about that.
But your residence needs to maintain
a certain standard of living.
Even if he doesn't care,
his sister won't just sit by and watch.
Mother.
You don't have to worry about me.
She's nice to me, too.
That's enough.
Don't try to fool me.
You think I don't know
what kind of person Wei Tingzhen is?
If she knows
how much Dou Zhao's dowry is worth,
she'd make your life hellish
in the Duke's residence.
You insisted on marrying him,
and now you can't even tell me
how much you're suffering there.
You useless girl.
I know everyone is comparing
my sister's dowry and mine,
but why are you also
doing this to me, Mother?
What else can I say?
Ever since I was born,
everything I do is a mistake
in your eyes.
If that's the case,
I shall not linger around and annoy you.
Your Ladyship...
Look at her.
She's unhappy about her in-laws,
and she's bickering with me?
Look at her behavior.
She's just like her father.
Madam.
You don't know
how much Ming is suffering
over there.
Ming.
What happened?
Why are you crying?
Ming must be missing home
since she just got married.
Why don't we let them chat
while we enjoy a drink?
After getting married, I realized
that your advice was true.
The Duke's residence
is not as wonderful as outsiders think.
They insist on putting up appearances
even when they're broke inside.
I don't have the capabilities
to cover their deficits
or maintain their facade.
Let's not talk about the past.
You should focus on the future.
The higher a family's status,
the bigger their deficits.
Don't blame yourself.
My dowry is nothing
compared to the debts
they have accrued.
How can I, a domestic lady,
get the money to pay their debts?
While domestic life can seem trivial,
there are many things
to pay attention to.
For example, the rice
from Liaodong may be softer,
but it costs 900 wen per dan.
Meanwhile, rice from Jiangnan is firmer,
and it only costs 700 wen.
So, when you're cooking rice or congee,
for every two parts of Liaodong rice,
mix in one part of Jiangnan rice,
and it'll taste just as good.
You can save
up to 500 to 600 taels a year.
You can deposit half of it in the bank
and invest the rest in the tea trade
to earn thousands of taels a year.
That's an amazing idea.
Sister, you must be the goddess
of wealth in your past life.
Besides,
you need to manage
your residence's assets.
If you have any taverns or shops
that haven't been making profits,
you should sell them off
and reinvest the money in booming trades
like fragrances and apparel.
No need.
Ming.
My father and I will support Ming,
so she doesn't have to
learn your miserly ways.
I will make sure
that Ming doesn't live in poverty.
I'll get my father
to assign a position for her husband.
Once the Duke's career takes off,
they won't have to worry over
such material concerns.
Come on.
Mother.
Did you really mean that?
But, Grandfather has always been fair,
and he despises nepotism.
Why would he...
You know,
when you have children,
you can't live for yourself.
Back when my father was demoted,
I had to cast my pride aside
and sell porridge to earn a living.
Now, I'll do this again
for your sake.
I'll beg my father to make an exception.
(One hundred taels)
Take these.
Mother.
I can't take these.
I know that you're
facing a difficult time too.
How did you get so much money?
I may be useless,
but I cannot be a bad daughter.
Illegal moneylending is a major crime.
The palace takes it seriously.
Mother.
Let's think of other solutions,
shall we?
As a woman in the house,
other than being a noble lady,
what advantage do we have?
We can't possibly be like Dou Zhao
to affiliate ourselves
with random hooligans
and their lowly trades.
Ming.
Remember this.
You are a duchess.
Never get involved
in such despicable business.
Keep the money.
Don't be a pushover
in the Duke's residence.
I'll always support you, understood?
Once the Duke has a stable career,
your sister-in-law won't
order you around anymore.
Really?
By then, my worries
will come to an end.
Mother.
Silly girl.
Mind the step.
Go.
Even though you scold her often, Madam,
you love her deeply.
I need to secure a position for the Duke
and arrange everything for her.
Pawn off a few more items
from my personal treasury.
Yes, Madam.
(Yizhi Hall)
(Ledger)
The purchases seem exaggerated.
Check every entry and tell me how much
money has been embezzled.
Madam.
We don't have the matching tokens,
so we can't order the servants around.
They've been rejecting
all our requests.
At this rate,
they're forcing us to pay
from our own pockets.
And that's only one
of our many problems.
What's more,
someone has been spying and listening in
everything you're doing here.
They'd sneak to the Duke's
main residence at night.
I recorded every single one of them.
These servants
are loyal to the Duke of Ying.
In fact, we seem to be
unwelcome in the residence.
What do you think, Lord Song?
Should I replace all our servants
with a new batch?
We cannot control the Duke's servants,
but we can control ours, can't we?
It's not that simple.
All the servants in the Duke's residence
must have had ties to the previous dukes
since generations ago.
Some of them even watched me grow up.
It's not just hard to replace them.
It'll makes me feel bad.
But, we can't let those
servants get their way
and torture our mistress.
Su Lan.
I am married to Lord Song.
Don't see him as an outsider.
I was wrong.
I am sorry, Your Lordship.
Even if we replace our servants now,
it'll take time to gain their loyalty,
and we might attract spies instead.
The Crown Prince and Lord Qing
are trying to win your favor.
If they plant their spies here,
our situation would turn worse.
Your Ladyship, Your Lordship.
We don't have to replace
everyone from the main residence.
They're loyal to the Duke's residence,
not Song Yichun himself.
Your Lordship,
you used to be quite violent,
so they saw you as the enemy
of the Duke's residence.
That's why they're on
Song Yichun's side.
You're right.
If His Lordship
can take control
of the entire residence,
and Her Ladyship obtains
the treasury's matching tokens,
the servants will be on our side.
Now, the key issue
is that Lord Song was beaten up,
and there are signs of foul play
in his mother's death.
Even though we've already replaced
many of our servants,
perhaps some of them
may know the truth behind all these.
That's why we need to keep them here.
Did I say anything wrong, Your Lordship?
You just told Su Lan
not to see me as an outsider,
but what did you just call me?
Yantang.
Say that again.
They're all here.
What are you doing?
- Not anymore.
Why are you staring at me like this?
I've always said that
I have a bad reputation.
Now that I think of it,
you used to have an ugly reputation too.
I didn't want to get married back then,
so I didn't care what they
have to say about me.
But, now that we're a married couple,
if you want to advance further,
we can't let Wang Yingxue
and Song Yichun
spread malicious gossip
and damage your reputation.
I need to put an end to this.
I wanted to give you a carefree life,
but now, I'm involving you
in our family affairs.
It's my fault.
My family is no better than yours.
It's no one's fault.
Besides, you said I'm your strategist,
so I have to share your burden.
Strategist, is it?
What's wrong with that?
In fact, you...
What are you doing?
We're discussing serious issues here.
Everything you've been
discussing in this room
isn't serious at all.
Then, what sounds serious to you?
Call me Hubby.
Song Mo.
♪I want to hide like the moon♪
♪Like a butterfly drawn to flowers♪
♪Like ink drops fading into my heart
that turns to longing♪
♪Like the sun waiting
for the flying wild geese♪
♪The sound of weapons
chasing the long whip♪
I was wondering why
His Lordship looked miffed,
and it's because Young Lady
hasn't called him Hubby yet.
I never thought
we would work together
in the same residence.
Just months ago,
we were still enemies.
The future is hard to predict.
I was wondering
what would happen now
if that arrow didn't
miss your vital organs
during the siege.
My friend.
Look, the scar is still here.
Mr. Chen.
We have the best Ganlubai wine here.
Let me offer some to you
to show my apology.
- Sure.
- This way.
This way.
Your Grace, bad news!
Why are you yelling?
Mind your manners.
I think something's wrong.
Everyone in Yizhi Hall
is moving things around.
All those camphor wood chests
are filled with money
to the brim.
There were six or seven people
calculating everything,
so busy until they have
no time to drink water.
Even when we did our year-end
accounts every year,
we'd finish in a day or two.
How much dowry did she bring exactly?
I know the Dous are famous merchants,
but they're not that rich, are they?
Exactly.
Keep an eye on them.
Investigate what's going on.
Yes, Your Grace.
(Duke of Jining's Residence)
If it looks like it's going to rain,
keep the Duke's paintings
so that they don't get wet.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Well?
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
I'm glad to see
that you like it.
You were drawing this that day,
weren't you?
That's right.
I wanted to give you a surprise.
It's beautiful.
Your Ladyship.
Madam wants to see you now.
Understood.
Can you come with me?
Ming,
I haven't finished painting today.
- Once I'm done...
- But...
Ming.
Ming, don't worry.
My sister is already married off,
while you're married into this family.
You need to show your prowess
as the mistress of the residence.
Don't let them push you around.
Sister-in-law.
Look at this!
How are you the mistress
of the household?
The residence is heavily in debt now!
What have you been doing?
How unfortunate for us.
If my brother
married your sister instead,
our residence wouldn't be in this state!
Are you mute?
You're right, Sister-in-law.
My mother just gave me
some money last month.
It's only been a while,
and I'm thinking if we could
reduce our spending instead.
Reduce our spending?
This is the Duke's residence!
That's all you can do to keep us afloat?
As the mistress of the residence,
aren't you afraid that people
might laugh at you?
If the residence keeps spending
without any source of income,
we'd eventually go broke
no matter how rich we are.
That's why my mother
begged my grandfather
to appoint the Duke as
the Deputy Commander
of the North Warden's Office.
(Letter of Appointment)
This is his letter of appointment.
I wanted to share this piece of news
together with the Duke and you.
That's more like it.
You're the one
who made Ming lose her child.
If you can't give me
an explanation today,
we'll take this case to court.
Sister, you warned me
that the Duke wouldn't
make a good husband.
Do you regret it?
I'm a beast!
(Request for Divorce)
I was wrong, Ming!
♪If dreams are shattered,
can they be whole again?♪
♪If today brings hope, will it stay?♪
♪Will the pain just
weave itself deeper?♪
♪Where can this
restless heart find peace?♪
♪Left alone in an empty hall♪
♪A lifetime chasing fate's lonely call♪
♪Watching seasons fade and storms rise♪
♪It hurts but it's not all for nothing♪
♪My heart is as empty as a quiet street♪
♪Who cares about the path I walk alone?♪
♪Would you take away
the weight of the past?♪
♪Life is fleeting, like morning frost♪
♪Even a moment feels endless with you♪
♪Like a stream flowing
steady through time♪
♪A lone flower falls from the eaves
Moonlight graces steps beneath♪
♪Can anyone ease the pain of goodbye?♪
♪If dreams are shattered,
can they be whole again?♪
♪If today brings hope, will it stay?♪
♪Will the pain just
weave itself deeper?♪
♪In this chaotic world♪
♪Only love lasts♪
♪We'll get through
every challenge together♪
♪No matter how cold
or uncertain the road♪
♪There's nothing to fear
when I'm with you♪
♪My heart feels empty♪
♪But I can hear your voice♪
♪In this life, under moonlight
and across the oceans♪
♪We'll find our way back to each other♪
(No animals were harmed
in the making of this drama.)
(Every medical behaviour involved
and medicine used in the drama)
(is required by the story.
Please don't try this at home.)
♪Together, we'll make
every moment count♪