It's a good idea
but it's not your usual approach.
Which teacher taught you?
Tell me.
It was
a female teacher.
A female teacher?
Who?
So, who?
Why aren't you answering?
So secretive.
Could it be your crush?
No more wild guesses.
Tell me which family she is from.
I, Earl Yunyang, will go all out
to be the matchmaker.
Stop messing around.
My mother is still ill.
No nonsense in front of her.
But if you ask me,
don't you think
you're overthinking this case?
Your mother fell ill.
My aunt, the empress,
and my uncle, the emperor,
sent imperial physicians
to check on her.
They're just as concerned as always.
We have Official Wu
who is working to mediate things.
Honestly, I think His Majesty
might scold him a bit at most.
Duke of Ding won't be
in any serious trouble.
I hope so.
=Blossom=
(Adapted from the novel "Blossom" by Zhi Zhi)
=Episode 6=
Official Wu, please wait.
I wasn't targeting you
in front of the emperor earlier.
It's just that the emperor asked,
I can only speak honestly.
Honestly, huh?
If it's for the court's stability,
then it's all good.
But this concerns major matters
in the southeast.
It seem not to be related
to the Ministry of Rites now, does it?
With the Dragon Boat Festival
approaching,
why don't you go home
and rest for a few days?
Since you've instructed me to do so,
I can only comply.
Mr. Wu,
is this Official Dou
from the Western Dou Family?
Yes.
His Majesty read officials'
memorials against the Duke,
then he asked
about Meisun's health instead.
That shows he's worried, doesn't it?
But Dou Shishu went on to say
that bringing the Duke of Ding back
under arrest
could destabilize the southeast.
Isn't that like accusing Meisun
of building up an army
to start a rebellion?
Does Dou Shishu have a grudge
against Uncle?
Dou Shishu has always been cautious
and low-profile,
especially before he was promoted
to the Ministry of Rites.
He has never crossed the line.
It turns out,
he's just been hiding his ambition
and coveting the vacant seats
of the Grand Secretariat.
If Uncle is painted
as a treacherous minister,
then Dou Shishu
who calls for his removal
will naturally get the credit.
Take good care of your mother.
When Meisun arrives in the capital,
the Grand Secretariat will have ways
to deal with this.
Thank you, Mr. Wu.
Have you tried
the Dou Family's rice dumpling?
Rice dumplings?
You must try it.
If that's the case,
then it must be Fourth Young Lady Dou
who tipped off her uncle.
That wicked woman.
Earlier, you praised her
for being sharp,
loyal, and kind.
I... I'm terrible at judging people.
If she's really targeting
the Duke of Ding,
the Shadow Guard
would have wiped out Tan's Manor.
But everything's fine over there,
and the child is well taken care of.
Also, General Yan is keeping
an eye on things.
That just makes it even stranger.
Fourth Young Lady Dou
has been living in seclusion.
How would she know
all these court affairs?
There's also another possibility.
It's not just Dou Shishu.
The entire Dou Family may be her pawns.
She could be plotting
and manipulating people from afar.
Then Young Lord has become her leverage
to control us.
If that's true,
it's hard to believe
someone as beautiful
as Fourth Young Lady Dou
could be so ruthless.
Uncle hasn't even arrived here yet,
and we've already crossed paths
with the Dou Family twice.
There's bound to be more conflict ahead.
We have to figure out
what they're really after.
Xingyi suffered a lot in the past
and ended up with rheumatism.
That's why I sent over
some mugwort medicinal oil.
It wasn't anything valuable.
But he returned it to me.
We're in-laws
and serve the same court.
Yet, the way he avoids any association,
you'd think we were complete strangers.
Father only didn't want
to give anyone an excuse to find fault
and drag us into trouble.
The Ministry of Rites keeps you busy.
You rarely come home.
Yet you still worry
about Father's health.
I'm truly grateful, Fifth Brother.
No need to thank me.
We're family.
I came back during my leave
because there's something
I need to discuss with you and Shiying.
Sit.
Ms. Longevity is 23 this year
and Ming has turned 16 this year, right?
Yes.
If it were a boy,
he'd be preparing
for the imperial exams.
Not being able to leave an heir
for the Dou Family
and making you worry about its future,
it's my failure as a sister-in-law.
This entire household runs
because of you.
How could it be your fault?
If anyone's at fault, it's Shiying.
He may be an official.
But he's driven by a set of principles.
He's completely clueless
about the court's situation.
If the Dou Family wants
to set a strong foothold,
we can't do it alone.
If Ming and Mr. Wu Shan's marriage
works out,
the two families will be united
and support each other.
Honestly, they get along well.
They're just a bit shy.
In that case,
invite Dezhen here
for the Dragon Boat Festival banquet.
As elders,
we should do our part to help.
All right, I'll send out
the invitation right away.
Also, the Marquis of Jining
was in a mourning period.
The three-year mourning period is over.
It's time
to address his and Ms. Longevity's
verbal engagement now.
You should send out the invitation
for that too.
I'll talk to Shiying about this.
All right.
The arrangement for Fifth Young Lady
and Mr. Wu Shan is a good thing.
But Dou Zhao's childhood engagement
had been long overdue.
Why does Fifth Master seem
to be interested in it again?
He is not on leave.
Father already sent word.
Fifth Brother made a mistake in court
and went against Official Wu.
He was forced to take leave.
Now,
he's depending
on his two nieces' marriages.
One is to aim for a powerful family.
The other one is for a noble official.
Isn't our Wang Family's connection
not enough?
My father is straightforward
and upright.
He always does what's right,
not just favoring family.
Now he wants a position
in the Grand Secretariat.
Father won't want
to get involved in this mess.
But if Dou Zhao
becomes Marchioness of Jining,
won't she overshadow you?
Wei Tingyu is famous for his extravagant
and careless lifestyle.
Even though his family
has held the title for generations,
they've spent all their wealth
on funeral expenses in recent years.
His sister, Wei Tingzhen,
married the Duke of Jing
as his second wife.
This whole family is driven by greed.
They might be useful allies.
Be careful, Madam.
This butterfly loves
those silk tree flowers.
Once their scale powder touched
the skin,
the itch would be unbearable.
I'll have the servant take care
of all those butterflies right away.
But they're so beautiful.
Won't it be a pity to catch them all?
Have a drink, Your Lordship.
That's a wonderful painting.
It's nicely painted.
You're flattering me.
You paint very well, Your Lordship.
Your Ladyship,
it's truly an honor to have you here.
Where's the Marquis?
He...
Madam, wait.
Excuse me, ladies.
Madam, slowly.
Watch your steps.
Why don't you
let me inform the Marquis first?
Madam, please have mercy.
If you barged in like this,
the Marquis would beat me to death.
Then I'll beat you foolish woman
to death now!
Madam!
Wonderful.
Well painted.
Peijin.
Tingzhen?
Fourth Young Lady Dou?
Why her again?
I've heard something reliable.
(Wei Tingzhen, Duchess of Jing)
She's making
at least this much in Futing now.
But it's all just material stuff.
Didn't Seventh Master Dou send
a letter earlier
saying matters of marriage
should be left to fate?
Doesn't that mean it's all over?
Of course, not.
Now the Dou Family
is taking the initiative,
inviting us to join them
for the Festival outing.
These past few years,
there have been disasters everywhere,
and the harvest has been halved.
But the expenses
at the household haven't dropped at all.
Without anyone to help,
do you know how much it costs
to run the household?
I...
Just do as I say.
Once Father's mourning period is over,
we need to finalize
the marriage right away.
But Tingzhen...
The Dou Family's household
is in turmoil.
She also grew up in the countryside.
A young master who attended
their family's banquets said
she doesn't care about the differences
between men and women,
speaks disrespectfully,
and even argues with elders.
She's completely uncouth.
I was going to say
that Dou Zhao is famous for her beauty.
She's truly a stunning woman.
Perhaps she could catch your eye?
But since you seem
to dislike her so much,
I won't worry
about your marriage anymore.
Three.
Two...
Tingzhen,
I'm a Marquis after all.
So I should be more open-minded.
Since we've already accepted
the invitation,
it would be rude if we don't go.
How about this?
You can take charge of this.
What a pity, really.
One wrong stroke.
Such a shame
for this winter plum blossom painting.
Not at all.
It's a beautiful painting
of the winter plum blossom.
No, it's not a pity at all.
Everyone, please take a look.
"Who could have known
the winter's snow would come late,
and a single winter plum blossom
would bloom out of the wall?"
That's brilliant!
Indeed.
The tiger talisman
is something you can buy.
Wang Yingxue only wants you
and Dou Ming to embroider it
to torture your poor little fingers.
Exactly.
That's why
I made sure to stitch it
all crooked and uneven.
In any case,
I should appear worse than Dou Ming.
Are you downplaying yourself?
Not entirely.
The real trouble is asking you
to handle the banquet.
Old Madam
and Seventh Master Dou finally managed
to ease things up a bit.
Now she's dragging a whole group
of people to join the festivities.
I'm worried
it'll cause some misunderstandings.
I don't think Wang Yingxue cares
about the festival at all.
She just wants to set up
a marriage for you and Dou Ming.
Young Lady,
we got news from Zhaowen Bookstore.
Wu Shan has been posted
as Assistant Director
of Court of Imperial Sacrifices.
I am fine with Wu Shan coming.
But after six years,
doesn't Wei Tingyu get the message?
Why is he still coming?
How shameless.
Precisely.
The physician said
her days are numbered.
Once she's gone,
I will marry you.
Song Mo is arrogant
due to his achievements and favor.
He kidnapped and eloped
with Marchioness of Jining, Dou Zhao.
Execute them
to uphold the family law.
This needs to be settled.
I'll give him a proper welcome
if he dares to show up.
This way, please.
The scenery here is beautiful,
and the repairs are done well.
As expected from the Cui Clan of Ji'an.
Even a countryside manor
can have such elegance.
My mother-in-law doesn't like
the bustling city.
So she stays here to rest.
Over the years,
all thanks to Zhao's company
and her helping around the manor.
I bet she's busy attending
to my mother-in-law's afternoon nap now.
I hope you won't mind
she couldn't welcome you personally.
Zhao is gentle, and virtuous,
and manages our household perfectly.
Everyone who meets her
has nothing but praise.
Even her sisters
are all kind and graceful,
smart and composed.
Oh, hello Uncle.
Ru,
what are you doing?
I'll catch some more
to add an extra dish
for tonight's banquet.
Come on.
I...
Sorry about that.
Ru takes
after her father.
She's a bit too lively.
Come this way, please.
Please come this way.
Mr. Wu, this way.
Aside from Ru,
who's a bit energetic,
the rest of the ladies
are all very quiet and graceful.
I win!
You lose again.
Hurry up and pay up!
Accept your defeat.
Which tenant's daughter that?
She's acting so rough.
Chase her out now.
Fifth Uncle!
Let's play another round.
It's me, Ansu.
Ansu?
Zhao taught me this game.
It's so much fun!
Do you want to play together?
Miss Su is really good
at mental calculation.
So it's no surprise she likes this game.
Let's check out the backyard.
Come with me.
Come on, it's your turn now.
Quickly.
This courtyard
is my mother-in-law's
favorite courtyard.
Look at these flowers and plants.
They're carefully tended to every day.
The courtyard is always green,
with birds chirping
and flowers blooming.
It's really lovely.
There are more over there.
Let's go and take a look.
All right.
Ming.
As for Zhao, she's very quiet.
Most of the time,
she writes and reads books.
She's refined and graceful,
truly a woman of culture and virtue.
Come.
Ms. Longevity?
That is very rude of you.
I wanted to greet the guests
with this willow-shooting equipment.
But my skills aren't great,
and I ended up startling
our honored guests.
It's perfect
that Fifth Master and Seventh Master
are discussing official matters
in the study.
With the two old scholars not around,
the children would feel more at ease.
I've heard the Dou Family's Madam Wang
and Fourth Young Lady Dou
are both quite skilled at making money.
Madam Wang,
you've helped many officials
become rich.
Seventh Master Dou marrying so well
means his official career
will surely go smoothly.
I don't deserve such compliments.
I only make a small profit
to support the household.
It's Zhao who is truly extraordinary.
She comes from wealth
and is remarkably talented
at managing manors.
She's already one of the richest
in the region.
It's a pity that she doesn't trust me
as the matron of the household.
If she would invest with me,
I could guarantee her a 30% profit
in just half a year.
If you make this marriage happen,
I'd be happy to contribute 40%...
No, I mean 50% of her dowry
for you to manage.
You're too kind.
If we happen to become in-laws,
there's no need
to mention helping or not.
We're not outsiders here.
Have some tea.
Sure.
What's the fun of shooting willow?
(I knew your archery skills
are terrible)
(and care so much about your face.)
(If I made you think
we don't have the same interests)
(and angry out of embarrassment,)
(maybe you'd call off the engagement.
Now, that's the fun part!)
What are those?
A small gift from my elder sister.
It's a kite soaring in the sky,
symbolizing good fortune.
"Look far to see a thousand li ahead,
rising to new heights."
Madam Wei is so thoughtful.
Are these for Fifth Master Dou
and Seventh Master Dou?
Madam Wang, take a look.
"A fresh start leads
to soaring heights."
What a fine verse.
Even the sentiment is wonderful.
I had Peijin inscribe it personally.
I wish him a bright future,
a harmonious and happy life,
and soaring high together
with Fourth Young Lady Dou.
How did this archery turn
into shooting in the sky?
Fourth Young Lady,
are you shooting willows
or kites?
My archery isn't great,
and the wind is strong today.
That's why I missed my target.
(I don't want to soar high with you.)
(I prefer shooting you with this arrow.)
Madam,
Zhao usually doesn't practice archery.
I'm not sure
what's gotten into her today.
Ming!
It's some men having some fun.
Why are you trying
to draw attention to yourself?
Women shouldn't even
be learning archery in the first place.
Madam,
why don't we head back to the house
to enjoy some fruit and rest for a bit?
Good idea.
You...
The wind really is strong.
Fourth Young Lady,
am I in trouble?
It's only a kite.
The Marquis won't mind it,
right?
Zhao,
can you teach me
how to release the arrow?
I heard the Marquis of Jining
is famous in the capital
for his archery skills.
I...
Your Lordship.
I wouldn't call myself an expert.
But this little willow-shooting trick
is no challenge for me.
Fifth Young Lady, you see.
To shoot accurately and steadily,
the arrow needs to be exactly
three times the length of its head
and perfectly symmetrical
along all four sides of the shaft.
Only then do you have a steady aim,
achieving what is mentioned
in the Rites of Zhou,
"Even in strong winds,
it will not falter."
You're very knowledgeable,
Your Lordship.
Knowledgeable indeed.
But if you don't shoot soon,
the flowers in the gourd will wither.
Fifth Young Lady, watch this carefully.
Your arm must be steady,
and your mind must be calm.
Aim for the roundest part of the gourd.
Then release the arrow.
This...
It is indeed very windy.
Yes, it sure is.
Do you want to try one more time?
The wind
was indeed strong just now.
I'll try one more time.
Aim for the roundest part of the gourd.
Then release the arrow.
The arrow's fletching is definitely
not made from eagle feathers.
It can't shoot accurately.
The arm must be steady,
and the mind must be calm.
Aim for the roundest part of the gourd.
She hit it!
You truly have remarkable skills.
I learned in one try
and hit the target on my first try
just by following your instructions.
You're a quick learner.
But who picks up archery this fast?
You're already skilled in archery,
right?
(This woman is decent in appearance.)
(But she's brash and sharp-tongued.)
(Why is she so infatuated with me?)
(This won't do.)
(How do I call off this engagement?)
(How do I explain it to Sister?)
(What a headache.)
Madam Wang's words
are too narrow-minded.
Women like Fu Hao
expanded territories in the past
and Mulan
took her father's place in the army.
Today, there's Madam Wa Shi
who suppressed a rebellion
and took over administrative duties.
There's no such thing
as something only men can do
and women cannot in this era.
She says plenty of things
that aren't right.
I won't take any of it to heart.
Mother is going to blame me
for being useless again.
I often hear the ladies
in the capital praise
Fifth Young Lady for being skilled
in the four arts
and needlework.
Seeing you today,
you're even more gentle and dignified.
Women have always been admired
for their gentleness and obedience.
Fifth Young Lady, why belittle yourself?
To Mother,
if my sister can do something
that I can't,
that means I'm useless.
That's too narrow-minded.
It's like this branch and this arrow.
Which is useful,
and which is not?
The arrow can be used in battle.
But what's the use of the branch?
If the branch is on a tree,
it can shield people
from the wind and rain.
The bark can be used to make paper.
Both serve different purposes.
Neither is more or less important.
It's the same with people.
There's a leaf.
Wearing tiger talismans
on Dragon Boat Festival
can ward off evil
and bring good fortune.
These two young ladies
personally embroidered tiger talismans
for you two gentlemen,
hoping to bring a good omen.
The embroidery and inlay work
are both exquisite.
Ming embroidered this one.
Her stitches are delicate.
This one was embroidered by Zhao.
Zhao's embroidery...
Well,
it's still a tiger talisman.
It's quite good as well.
Please accept it, gentlemen.
Thank you, Madam.
Thank you.
(Fourth Young Lady Dou's embroidery
is rather rough.)
(But she still put in a lot of effort)
(to make a tiger talisman for me.)
(It shows how deeply she cares for me.)
(It's a pity
our personalities don't match.)
(I'll have to let her down.)
(But Fifth Young Lady's work...)
(Fourth Young Lady)
(has a unique mind,)
(She's genuine and sincere.)
(Truly rare qualities in this world.)
Our tea plantation in the back hills
has beautiful scenery.
Since this is your first time visiting
our manor,
I've arranged for a servant
to take you both on a stroll there.
Thank you, Madam.
Since we both dislike heat
and prefer quiet,
we'll just head to the pavilion.
Once Zhao and Ming
have prepared the banquet,
we can go straight
to the feast and have drinks.
Please come with me.
All right.
This way, please.
Everything is arranged.
But those things
don't understand human speech.
How can we make them
only go for the Marquis?
What if it goes for Mr. Wu Shan?
They won't make a mistake.
They will definitely go for Wei Tingyu.
I've cleared everyone out.
We can't afford any slip-ups
with Dou Zhao.
After an hour,
I'll bring Madam Wei over.
Yes, Madam.
It's indeed a beautiful scenery.
It's all right, I guess.
Wait, Mr. Wei.
Thank you.
Truly exquisite.
Fifth Young Lady truly has a refined
and thoughtful nature.
Every bead in this design
is clearly crafted with great care.
Well, Fourth Young Lady also put
a lot of thought into it.
But her thinking
is unique.
"The crane calls in the marshes,
the fish lurks in the depths."
If these were reversed,
the crane wouldn't be a crane,
and the fish wouldn't be a fish.
If we could switch them,
wouldn't that be perfect?
This... this is something made
by a young lady
and given by elders.
Exchanging it privately
would be too impolite.
Mr. Wu, I must disagree.
Festive gifts are no big deal.
Besides, can something forced upon us
by elders truly bring joy?
How shallow.
Mr. Wei,
this... this might not be appropriate.
Mr. Wei!
The variety of light and hearty dishes
is still fairly acceptable.
But the cold dishes
shouldn't be served in bowls.
Switch to platters instead.
Yes, Young Lady.
Before serving the duck and barley soup,
make sure to shred the duck meat.
Yes, Young Lady.
Prepare more snowflake pastries.
If anyone doesn't eat cold dishes,
serve them room-temperature
mung bean soup instead.
Entertaining distinguished guests
at a banquet
requires the utmost care.
Zhao, you truly consider every detail.
What do you think
of the fruit-serving dishes I chose?
Are they appropriate?
Fourth Young Lady,
I'm truly sorry.
Why are you so careless?
Luckily, it wasn't anything hot.
Come with me.
Let me attend to Fourth Young Lady
to the side room
to get changed.
It's all right.
Let me just get everything ready
for the banquet first.
We have a lot of guests today,
and your dress is quite sheer.
If someone sees you like this,
it could damage your reputation.
It's better if you change first.
Zhao.
Keep preparing.
I'll go and see what's going on.
Your dress is sheer.
What if you catch a cold?
It'll be quick.
It's just ahead. Come on now.
(Dai Jian, Governor of Shengtian)
It's just a small gift.
I hope you'll accept it.
This is quite a generous gift.
Yuanji, you're too generous.
Then I shall accept them.
Send this to the Governor's carriage.
Yes, Master.
Please have a seat.
You, too.
We're almost there.
Why are you in a rush, Nanny Zhou?
The banquet is going to start soon.
We can't delay it.
I'll accompany Zhao.
I can cover a little for her.
No need.
I mean
I can help her get changed.
You don't have to twist my arm
when I want to help her to get changed.
We can attend
to Fourth Young Lady's need.
What are you trying to pull here,
Nanny Zhou?
I'm not.
Just helping her to get changed.
You don't allow Dou Ming to follow me.
I want to see
what's waiting for me in this room.
Mr. Wu?
Why is Mr. Wu here?
When Mr. Wu was taking a stroll
in the back hills,
a group of swallowtail butterflies
suddenly appeared
and chased after him.
After that, he fell unconscious.
Swallowtail butterfly?
Get the physician here quickly
and notify the elders at home.
He is covered in scale powder
and only breaks out in rashes.
No need to let both Masters know.
(The Miluo River is full
of lingering resentment.)
(Wrongfully Killed Man)
(The Miluo River is full
of lingering resentment.)
(Wrongfully Killed Man)
(The child was buried
in the southern mountains.)
(Qu Yuan's life ended
in the Miluo River,)
(Wu Shan)
(and today is the Dragon Boat Festival.)
(The poem speaks of early death.)
Still hiding the truth?
You were setting up a situation
where a couple isolated together
to meet while getting changed,
forcing me to marry.
But you didn't expect
Wei Tingyu to swap
the tiger talismans with Wu Shan.
For others, the scale powder
only causes redness and itching.
But Wu Shan has a lung condition.
This could cost him his life!
Mr. Wu came to the manor as a guest.
If anything bad happened to him,
how do we explain it to the Wu Family?
Just do as Zhao says.
Yes, Young Lady.
His breathing is getting worse.
There are too many curtains in the room.
The air isn't circulating properly.
Suxin,
go and get someone
to carry him to the yard.
Make sure they are gentle
and move him carefully.
Then bring me my acupuncture box.
Yes, Young Lady.
Master is hosting guests at the manor.
No one is allowed to disturb.
I, Song Mo, the heir of Duke of Ying,
have come to pay a visit
with gifts for the Dragon Boat Festival!
Now, Grand Secretary Wu
has the final say in the court.
No one can argue with him.
I am of low status
and have little influence.
I truly have no power
to relieve His Majesty's concerns.
The southeast has been hit by a storm,
causing miles of devastation.
While others are avoiding it,
the Dou family wishes
to step into the eye of the storm,
using the wind to their advantage.
Such courage.
Fifth Master,
I couldn't stop His Lordship
from entering.
The Dou Family has no connections
with the Duke of Ying.
Since you are here uninvited,
what brings you here?
You sent rice dumplings
to high officials in the capital.
I am curious
about the peculiar filling inside.
So I asked Official Wu for a few to try.
It turns out they're filled with gold.
It seems like Official Wu
has quite a strong prejudice against me.
It's just a regular festival gift.
He can refuse it.
But he actually let you return
it to me in person.
You should put down your weapon,
Lord Song.
From my position
as the Governor of Shengtian,
it looks like
you're publicly threatening
an official of the court.
I dare not.
Your Lordship, you
I have come to inform you respectfully,
Official Dou.
If you still plan
to accuse the Duke of Ding
of any crimes,
then I shall offer these rice dumplings
to His Majesty for a taste.
By then, even the Shengtian Prefecture
may not be able to protect you.
You...
Master,
Mr. Wu Shan is unconscious.
Fourth Young Lady has ordered someone
to carry him to the backyard.
Quiet!
Do not speak recklessly!
Great.
You dare to harm Official Wu's
only grandson!
Preposterous.
Absolutely preposterous!
This is your territory.
If I let him walk around like this,
what would be left of my dignity!
Someone!
You cannot.
Official Dai, don't do it.
You're worried that this marriage
won't be settled anytime soon.
In my opinion,
once fate comes its way,
nothing can stop it.
You're right about that.
Tingzhen!
Why are you here?
Tingzhen,
Mr. Wu is...
Song Mo?
Suxin. Sulan.
Fourth Young Lady,
what are you doing?
What are you trying to do to Dezhen?
He has tuberculosis and lung abscesses.
His breathing is getting weaker.
His lungs must be filled with pus now.
Now, he's on the verge of death,
fighting for his life.
I need to perform acupuncture
on his Dazhui and Xuanji acupoints
to save him.
Dou Zhao!
How dare you!
In broad daylight,
you and Mr. Wu are tugging at each other
with your clothes in disarray.
What are you trying to do? Get up now!
Mr. Wu Shan's illness flared up
strangely.
Zhao is about
to perform acupuncture on him.
If acupuncture is needed,
it should be done by a physician.
There are rules between men and women.
You have acted in such disgraceful
and improper behavior.
If this gets out,
what will happen
to the Dou Family's reputation?
Someone,
quickly help Mr. Wu Shan up.
You're right.
Mother,
saving him is more important now.
Quiet.
Since it's a respiratory condition,
he should be quickly sent
to the physician.
Someone, take him away.
We've already sent someone
to bring the physician here.
But the nearest medical hall
is ten li away.
By the time the physician arrived,
Mr. Wu Shan would be dead.
You've grown up on the battlefield.
So you must know
some injuries and illnesses
cannot be delayed.
Please look into my eyes.
Since you're skilled
in reading facial expressions,
you will know I'm not lying.
I can save him.
You can let go of me.
Hold onto Dezhen.
Lu Zheng,
Bring out all the folding screens
and set them up around tightly.
Yes, Your Lordship.
Everyone, turn around!
If anyone dares to look,
you'll lose your eyes.
Fourth Young Lady,
proceed with the acupuncture now.
Your Lordship,
you openly pointed your blade
at an official of the court.
Do you intend to rebel?
Anyone who stands in my way today
will die.
You've repeatedly tried
to stop me from saving him.
What are your true intentions?
Why do you believe
that this girl can save him?
I trust my judgment.
You...
Lord Song,
you're causing trouble at my place.
Are you forcing me
to bring this matter to the emperor?
I'm sure you know
exactly how Dezhen's illness acted up.
If you want to bring this
before the emperor,
are you prepared
to discard your family's reputation
and the women's honor?
Mother.
Dou Zhao,
are you trying
to get the entire family killed?
What a clever plan, Lord Song.
If something happened to Mr. Wu,
the emperor would think the Dou Family
is ambitious and power-hungry,
and that we would harm others
because of political differences.
Don't worry, Yuanji.
As the Governor of Shengtian,
I'll testify to this.
Song Mo broke into private property,
threatened a court official
with a blade,
and obstructed efforts to save a life.
Even if this matter reaches the emperor,
the truth will be the same!
This embroidery is quite exquisite.
Fortunately, Song Mo comes
from a military background
and doesn't know
the underhanded tricks of a household.
Otherwise, today would
be a great disaster for the family!
I suggest you to be careful
with your words.
She is genuinely trying to save you
despite the criticisms.
Are you saying
Fourth Young Lady
also has feelings for me?
I lean in and gaze at you
as calm as serene waves
I'm aware of the vast
and turbulent world
Moving forward alone,
the expectations of many are hard to bear
When the time comes,
I will cast aside a lifetime of pride
To wear a flower stick for you
Or perhaps my heart yearns
for the other side
Yet there's no place
for me to go in the end
Your presence by my side
is irreplaceable
Like a ship crossing
the desolate river
That brings me
through a chapter of my life
You are the light
that saves me in the darkness
Having you is a blessing
My heart filled with warmth
By your side,
I spend the rest of my life
Your presence by my side
is irreplaceable
Where my heart yearns
is where I will go
Breaking waves over the desolate river
The wind rises as my heart finds peace
You are the light
that saves me in the darkness
Having you is a blessing
Only by being by your side
I can spend the rest of my life
Until the waves are all spread out
And the past sinks into the river
Always together, looking back
Only sighing at the commotion
(No animals were harmed
in the making of this drama)
(Every medical behavior involved
and medicine used in the drama)
(is required by the story.
Please don't try this at home)