I shall pour this water
to prove that
these pandan leaves are consecrated.
If these pandan leaves turn black,
you must leave Lady Chavala.
Dear.
Is it possible that we are truly
under a love charm?
The wheels of karma will turn for you!
Noi has come!
Noi is here?!
A ghost cannot report a crime, My Lord?
Yes, it cannot.
Muen Vorachai! You killed me!
A ghost of Noi?!
Jerm, you are the only one who knows
if it is truly her.
The real Noi was not from Ban Noen Sung.
She was from Khoktum.
She was an orphan since childhood.
I wish to report an offense.
An offense of defamation.
I hereby judge Lady Pimpilai to be guilty
according to the law of Ayothaya.
Seek out those whom Saenkam has wronged.
I must make everyone realize
that the wicked man was to blame,
not my daughter!
Khun Saengplarn shall help us, sir.
Muen Vorachai trembles
every time he is on trial for this matter.
Va herself also suspects
that those pandan leaves
were truly meant to arouse her.
Are you saying
that Muen Vorachai truly
did use a love charm but failed?
He killed Noi to sacrifice
her blood for a love charm.
Darn it!
O sacred beings of heaven and earth,
and all the spirits of my forebears,
grant this humble soul
the strength to avenge itself!
May karma be their judge,
if the law could not!
May the cruel
be damned to burn in a living hell!
Your relishes, sir.
Noi!
Is that you?!
A ghost of Noi, sir?!
You bitch!
Die!
I do not fear you! I will kill you again!
Noi, you must help us find your body!
Let the wicked be punished
and suffer the same fate as you did!
Noi, forgive me!
I will kill you, ghost!
Please! Do not harm me!
Let them suffer
beyond the pain you and I knew!
Dear.
Lady Pim arranged
for someone to return this to you.
How did you remember this?
Our bond was not
this strong during that time.
But somehow, every time I see you cry,
my heart grows tender.
Let me put it on for you.
Yes.
Dear, I very much appreciate this.
Is this your family's sigil?
It is not.
I only know that it is truly important.
Father asked Chai
to keep it around his neck.
It may have some relevance
to being a customs officer.
Relevance to being a customs officer?
Yes.
Yet Chai never wore it
and even sold it.
Do you believe that…
Muen Chai
truly cast a love charm on us?
I do.
And do you believe that he killed Noi?
For this matter,
I can only wish
that it was not him.
Thong!
Do you need my help?
I brought this cloth for you.
Thank you, Thong. It is truly nice.
I am looking for new clothes
to wear to the temple as well.
You have my thanks.
- Is he Laor's friend?
- Yes.
He comes to court Laor.
That sharp-faced bastard
still visits Laor, sir?
Do you know him?
Yes, sir. I have seen him before.
But Laor did not mention him,
so I thought he stopped seeing her.
I thought you had
a special affection for Laor.
You two are always close.
Uh, no, sir.
We consider ourselves siblings.
I teach her how to fight,
while she does the house chores for me.
That is our agreement.
It seems that this Thong is serious.
He visits her day and night.
I do think that even
an unwavering girl such as Laor
shall be wed to him in less than a year.
Think it through.
Rueang.
Oh? Ming?
Why did you return so soon?
I am not done cleaning.
You can wait for me then.
Does Thong see you at the house often?
Yes, he brought me gifts.
Then…
Are you two seeing each other?
Oh, not at all.
I still do not want a husband now.
If you do not want him,
you should tell him to stay away.
Why would I?
Thong always brings me nice gifts.
Do you know
that no one has brought me
such nice and valuable gifts?
Nice and valuable gifts?
If he puts in this much effort,
his eventual proposal
will leave you no choice.
Oh, we have talked about this.
You have talked to him?
With all these gifts you have brought me,
are you looking to wed me?
Yes.
I do not think about marriage as of now,
but my thought may change
in one or two years.
What? You have been thinking
about getting married as well?
I have been thinking of everything.
Unlike you, who has
no regard for your future.
Saiyud told me
that a girl my age still has
a few years to find the right person.
So, I plan to wait for a while
to consider well
and look for someone wealthy.
Are you looking for a wealthy man?!
Laor,
are you obsessed with wealth that much?
Well, I am a servant.
My future husband must be
wealthy enough to free me.
Do you think my child
should inherit my servanthood?
Oh, I do not think so.
You think of having a child as well?
I have been thinking of everything.
Every life must have a goal.
I need to plan mine as well.
And how did Thong respond?
Next year,
I will be appointed a squad leader,
and there will be an annuity.
A prosperous future is indeed assured.
Then we shall see
which division you are to be assigned to.
We shall see
how your commanding officer is.
If your commanding officer is good,
I may accept your proposal.
Would you truly accept?
Wait. Hold on.
Why was it as easy
as shopping in the market?
Why must it be difficult?
I am merely a child of servants.
Ming.
How much is the annuity
for a squad leader?
For a squad leader, it is not much at all.
I shall become a major by next year.
What? How does this concern you?
Well, I…
I…
Whatever!
Listen. I am truly disappointed in you.
Did you not tell me you would be
like my little sister for a long time?
Once you are wedded,
I will not have anyone to keep me company.
How would we practice Muay?
And who would take care of my house?
Oh, I will talk to my husband
regarding that. No problem at all.
- Talk to your husband?
- Well,
I am done with cleaning. I am leaving.
I must retrieve the shrimps from my trap.
Wait, what? Uh…
Laor.
I am here to see Khun Saengplarn.
This way.
Khun Saengplarn. Sir.
What is it, Chuang?
I have found my wife's body, sir.
Luang Athikorn has one nephew
who is a drunkard.
He only causes trouble and does no work.
And he constantly
asks his uncle for money.
A while ago, when Phin,
my wife, disappeared,
this man has been seeing
Luang Athikorn more and more.
Go away! Leave at once!
You have been threatening me too much!
I do not fear you!
I only asked for some money.
Did you not hear me?! Leave!
Do not ever show your face again!
Go, you bastard!
I saw them arguing,
but I did not hear what it was about.
I only heard the loud yelling.
Then, I followed Terd.
He stays in the abandoned
monk's house of Wat Tabaek.
I had recalled something,
so I went to the cemetery
behind the temple.
Why did you think
of looking in the cemetery?
Do you believe that
Terd was hired by Luang Athikorn
to kill your wife?
Yes, sir. To extract a large amount
of blood out of the victim,
the killer would need some time.
That was why he killed her
in the cemetery, to bury her right away.
Why did I not think of this?
So, I asked the undertaker
if he saw something strange
during the last few months.
And he led me to dig up a corpse.
I found my wife's body.
There is a knife mark on the neck bone.
Her throat must have been slit,
killing her instantly.
Phin.
She passed without suffering,
did she not, sir?
She did not. She may not even be aware.
It was the best way to extract
the most blood from the body.
And how can you be sure
this is your wife's body?
The remaining garments.
She had woven them herself.
I could not bring myself
to tell anyone but you.
Good.
Good judgment.
Luang Athikorn
was once in the military force.
He is cunning.
We shall need a thorough plan
to ensure the prosecution
of Luang and Saenkam.
Shall we not report this crime now?
Not yet.
Use some hay to conceal this body.
Do not let anybody see it.
Ask for the undertaker's help
to keep this a secret.
Yes, sir.
Dear.
What are you doing?
Does it feel good?
It truly does feel good.
Massaging here
shall ease your back pain.
Doing it here
shall ease your neck's stiffness.
What about this?
This shall arouse physical desire.
Dear.
What is it you are saying?
If I am
successful in capturing Saenkam,
please let me stay in this house with you.
Saenkam is no ordinary shaman.
He was once a mere lackey of Taen Seenil.
He took the lives of my parents
and my sister.
Is that true?
I remember him.
His habit of raping women
has stuck with him since he was a thief.
If he is such a vile soul,
execution is what he deserves.
Dear.
Will you truly be able to capture him?
We have found the body of Phin,
Chuang's wife.
It shall not be difficult now.
Really?
I was at the temple this morning
and saw Luang Athikorn as well.
How is he doing?
Well,
he went as far
as killing one of his servants
to offer the blood
to that disgusting plant.
And look what he got in return.
His son was doing better for a few weeks
and has now become frail again.
A vile soul such as Saenkam does not
possess the merits to cure anyone.
Should all go as planned, in ten days,
we shall lie together.
- Dear.
- Huh?
What is it you are talking about?
You can count the days. Only ten days.
I shall bid farewell
to the cold raft house.
Why is it
that you are so certain?
Terd. Terd.
I have palm wine.
Come with me. There are snacks as well.
Good?
Wait, dear. Is that not Chuang?
Why is he with Terd?
What are they talking about?
No, dear. We must not be too hasty.
There are people here.
Let us go.
Very well.
These are all fine treats.
Why are you sharing this with me?
I told you I only want company.
Terd. Terd.
Are you acquainted with Luang Athikorn?
I saw you argue with him the other day.
What was it about?
My uncle is incredibly stingy!
He refused to pay me
for what I did for him.
What task did you do for him?
I cannot tell you. It is a secret.
Terd.
Hey, Terd. What is that secret?
- Go away.
- Terd!
Let me sleep.
Terd did not slip up?
Does that mean your plan failed?
You seem enthusiastic
about bringing Saenkam to justice now.
Come here.
- Dear…
- Come. Come here.
Come here. Come.
The raft house
does not smell as nice as this house.
The perfume you gave me
is merely an imitation.
It is not as fragrant
and warm as you.
No, dear.
We shall speak of this no more.
I shall leave now.
I shall continue with the plan then.
What is next, dear?
But you must come here first.
Come.
You can tell me the plan if you wish.
If not, you can keep it to yourself.
Are you selling well?
I shall return to you.
Saiyud. Yesterday, Khun Saengplarn's men
found a buried body
of a woman at Wat Tabaek.
A woman's body? Who is she?
Her throat has been slit as well.
It is most horrible.
Khun Saengplarn said that there was a case
where a man reported to the authorities
that his wife had been missing.
He must have taken that man
to identify his wife's body by now.
What did she do
to deserve such a brutal death?
Khun Saengplarn also said
that the truth shall be unveiled
in only a few days.
The body is full of evidence,
and the place of murder is clear.
The murderer will surely be captured then.
Terd, die!
Wait. I surrender.
I surrender! I surrender!
- Remove his mask.
- Yes, sir.
Uncle? Did you intend to kill me?
Phin's body has been found.
So, he intended to silence you, Terd.
- Phin's body?!
- Terd!
- Do not say anything! Silence!
- Hey!
Laor.
What are you doing?
Khun Saengplarn told me
to start moving his clothes here.
He said he will spend
the night here tomorrow.
You should stop being shocked
and prepare yourself, Va.
Please excuse me.
Laor.
You should indeed prepare yourself.
Tomorrow
will mark ten days,
exactly as I have told you.
Have you successfully
captured Luang Athikorn?
I shall go to the court of the Ministry
of the Royal Household tomorrow.
If Luang Athikorn admits his crime,
Saenkam shall be found guilty as well.
Let us conclude
that I have managed to defeat Saenkam
as I promised.
Then, what if…
What if Luang Athikorn does not confess
and Saenkam denies your accusation?
I have studied governance for my mother
and martial arts for my father.
But I most favor the art of strategy.
I have planned everything.
No one
shall escape my grasp.
Dear.
Dear, you have always been
a master schemer since I met you.
You planned this nonsense as well.
And what if I do not agree
to lie with you?
What will you do?
If the lady rejects me…
then I must…
Dear! Dear.
You must leave at once.
But this is my bedroom.
- Va.
- Dear!
My Lord. Have you heard the news?
Luang Athikorn
will be on trial today, My Lord.
Saenkam is most greedy.
Was he not so obsessed with money
and fame, this would not happen.
Will it be connected to me, My Lord?
I have sent my men to observe.
And you,
do not show yourself around the trial.
Stay put.
I have been working for you.
- And I killed someone for you--
- You!
If I am to be captured,
please help me, My Lord.
Fine.
You gave me your word.
Please do not let them imprison me.
Yes! You have my word.
Luang Athikorn.
Why did you make
an attempt upon Terd's life?
He has been threatening me
for money at my own house, My Lord.
Everyone knows about this.
Is it the truth, Terd?
I…
Luang Athikorn
hired Terd to slit
the throat of my wife, Phin,
to offer her blood to the plant given
to him by Master Saenkam, My Lord.
Is it true, Terd?
No, My Lord.
I did not kill Phin.
I do not know anything.
I am Terd's uncle.
We have had minor disputes.
Henceforth, I shall cease
all acquaintance with him.
I regret what I have done.
Please judge me
for only a petty offense, My Lord.
Should this case be closed,
Luang Athikorn shall go unpunished.
What about your life, Terd?
Khun Saengplarn.
This does not concern you.
How long do you wish to flee from him?
Where do you wish to flee to?
Are you content with drinking
and sleeping anywhere as you did
now that you realize
he would try to silence you any day?
Terd.
I am your uncle. Why would I kill you?
Think it through!
You were trying to kill me
last night. It is obvious.
I request to present
the next witness, My Lord.
He is the undertaker of Wat Tabaek,
who pointed me to the spot
where Phin was buried.
My Lord, my name is Singh.
What did you witness?
He has come to support my statement.
Singh, describe all you witnessed.
Two months ago, I saw Terd
doing something suspicious
in the cemetery.
Then, after a careful recollection,
I found that the time matches
the age of Phin's corpse.
Given this witness's statement,
will you confess
to the deed of Phin's demise?
I…
Hey. Look at me. You are my nephew.
The murderer shall be
imprisoned for 20 years.
But your confession
shall halve your sentence.
And if you were not the mastermind,
you shall face five years of punishment.
And Luang Athikorn shall be
sentenced to 20 years in prison.
The royal prison is a terrible place.
No one has ever survived
more than 20 years inside.
If you wish to feel safe,
the one to spend 20 years in prison
must be Luang Athikorn.
Then I wish to confess, My Lord.
I was the one who killed Phin
by Luang Athikorn's order.
No! It is not true!
I did no such thing! He is framing me!
You ungrateful nephew!
Why would I kill Phin
when I did not even know her?!
Luang Athikorn commanded me to.
He told me to extract
fresh blood from Phin
to water the plant from Master Saenkam.
Why must it be the blood?
He wished for his son
to recover from illness.
His son has been frail
for many years, My Lord.
That plant is still
at Luang Athikorn's house.
You may observe it, My Lord.
There are still bloodstains
around that plant.
Luang Athikorn. Will you confess?
It was not my doing. It was not my doing.
I will confess, My Lord.
I will confess.
My son!
- What are you saying?! Stop at once!
- No, my son.
It was my fault.
I have been unwell.
Please forgive my father, My Lord.
Phin has died.
And I have not recovered.
Phin died because of me.
That vile shaman has fooled us all.
Chuang.
Forgive me.
Please forgive me.
The witness and evidence are clear.
I hereby judge Luang Athikorn
to be guilty of masterminding murder.
You shall serve 20 years in prison.
And you, Terd.
You have confessed
and provided helpful testimony.
Yet you were despicable enough
to take a stranger's life for profit.
Hence, I hereby sentence you
to ten years in prison.
Ten years?! Did you not say five years?!
Khun Saengplarn!
You tricked me and Terd!
Is this your plan all along?!
Phin, my dear.
I did it.
You shall rest peacefully now.
Oh, dear.
This case still has
one more accomplice, My Lord.
He was the one who manipulated
Luang Athikorn into killing a person.
My Lord, I request
to open a new case
to bring Master Saenkam to justice.
Very well. I am to open a new case.
We shall prosecute Saenkam.
Bring him in for a trial tomorrow.
The soldiers are coming
to capture you! You must flee!
I am not fleeing! I did no wrong!
Luang Athikorn was the murderer!
What he said was right, My Lord.
He merely suggested it to Luang Athikorn.
No one was reckless enough
to do what Luang Athikorn did.
Do not forget the failed amoria bloom!
Muen Vorachai has been on two trials now.
Lady Pimpilai and Pansaeng
are both looking for evidence to prosecute
us! You must flee while you can!
I am sick and tired
of being a forest bandit!
Then you shall be imprisoned!
I will not! I have helped you!
I have helped our master!
You shall not ditch me so easily!
Do not ever dare blame me!
You have been drinking and raping
enough to lose your magic!
You have brought this upon yourself!
You!
Cease your temper towards him!
Your magic is now nothing
compared to his. Remember!
We shall wait and see what our lackeys do.
They shall buy us time.
What lackeys?
Do you all want these leaves?
- I do!
- I want them!
- I want the leaves!
- Please give me!
Take them!
Take them all!
- I have it now!
- Take more!
I have it!
Here!
- That is mine!
- No, it is mine!
- I have one!
- What?
- Huh?
- Why are they here?
State your business.
We are ordered to bring Saenkam on trial!
- What?!
- On trial?
Have you all heard that?!
These people are disrespectful enough
to call our master only by name.
You all must protect our master
by pushing them away!
Leave at once! Our master
has done nothing wrong!
You must not capture him!
- What did you say?!
- Go away!
Do not harm our master!
He was falsely accused! Go!
- Let us drive them out!
- Go away!
- Get out! Go away!
- Go! Go away!
- Get out! Get out!
- Leave at once!
- Go away! Go!
- Get out! Go away!
- Get out! Get out!
- Get out!
- Go! Get out!
- Go away! Out!
- Get out! Get out!
- Out! Get out!
- Get out! Go!
- Leave Master alone!
- Get out! Get out! Get out!
We soldiers are forbidden
by law to harm civilians.
That is why we must
retreat for now, My Lord.
Then you are to go after dark,
when everyone disperses.
We have already tried, My Lord.
But they were camping there
and refused to move.
They are blocking the way in and out.
These followers of the shaman
are truly ignorant.
Then, we shall wait.
- Yes, My Lord.
Chuang has won the case, my lady.
I am now truly more hopeful.
As of late, I have been asking
the undertakers in many temples.
Some day, we shall hear about Noi.
Saenkam still refuses to be captured now.
But if more cases emerge,
we shall have more hope, my lady.
I heard Khun Saengplarn let you gather
those who were wronged by Saenkam.
Does it fare well, Aon?
It goes fairly well,
but most are intimidated
by Luang Bovorntat, who is supporting him.
We must encourage them. We have
hope now, and they should speak up.
I light incense and tell Noi every day
that Muen Chai shall get what he deserves.
Forgive me, my lady.
I understand, Jerm.
Whether Chai truly killed Noi or not,
I shall make peace with it.
The truth shall always be the truth.
What is this area called?
Wat Heeplat cemetery, sir.
How could I have forgotten this
until now? What a fool I am.
I think I know
where Noi's body is.
What?
Muen Vorachai again?
This is the third time!
This time, Khun Saengplarn has requested
the soldiers to witness the exhumation.
We have found Noi's body, My Lord.
It is not her ghost,
but her corpse this time.
Noi… Noi, my dear wife.
Jerm.
Compose yourself…
and look for anything unusual.
Yes, sir…
Noi.
This is me.
Loosen your grip for me.
This does not belong to Noi, sir.
This watch bears the engraved initial
of Praya Ratanathipok, your father.
No.
I did not know of such a thing.
These servants are the witnesses
who confirmed that this watch is one
of a kind and belonged to Jaokhun Rat!
It was stolen.
I do not know when I lost it.
It was not my doing, My Lord.
Enough with the lies!
Noi, who has been killed,
was holding this watch in her hand!
I have been framed, My Lord.
These servants are framing me!
Answer me. Did any of you
see me killing Noi?
Anyone? Did you?!
I request to present Ngiam,
the witness, My Lord.
Forgive me,
Khun Saengplarn. Greetings, sir.
I practice white magic.
I had never conjured any spirits before
until my first time
with the ghost of Noi.
On a boat ride through the river,
I saw the ghost of Noi.
I do not wish to listen
to such a scary tale, sir.
I saw her with my own two eyes.
If the ghost of Noi could not haunt
Muen Vorachai into confessing his crime,
she will surely come for his accomplice,
such as you.
What did you witness?
Muen Vorachai… Uh, Muen…
Speak up!
Yes, My Lord! Muen Vorachai
ordered me to lure Noi
onto a boat, My Lord.
Why did she have to be on a boat?
Uh, to… to…
To be killed
and have her blood used
for the plant, My Lord.
Ngiam! You are framing me!
Are you now confessing
that you lured Noi to Muen Vorachai?
Yes, but I did not kill her, My Lord!
I only brought her to him.
I do not know anything else.
I have told all, My Lord.
Please let me go! I beg you! Please!
The witness and evidence are clear.
I hereby judge Muen Vorachai to be guilty
of the murder of Noi.
The sentence is execution!
However, with his
past duties for our nation,
his sentence shall be lessened
to 20 years imprisonment!
Va.
Dear.
Tell me it is not true.
Soldiers!
Put him in prison!
Uh… Luang Bovorntat.
You promised you would help me.
If you ditch me, I will expose you.
Luang Bovorntat was the mastermind.
He commanded me to kill Noi
because he is planning
an insurrection.
Insolent!
What insurrection?
That is a baseless accusation!
Pansaeng has thwarted
your plan to smuggle weapons.
That was the reason
Luang Bovorntat commanded me
and Saenkam
to cast a love charm on my own sister.
He knew Pansaeng could not take a wife.
If he did,
his magic would fade away.
My Lord.
This mad dog is desperate.
He is now distracting us with lies.
It has been common knowledge
that Pansaeng and he
have held a grudge for a long time.
He only wishes to make
the court and all of us
confused!
It is merely trickery.
No, My Lord. The person
who wishes to kill Pansaeng
is Luang Bovorntat! It is you, not me!
Stop at once, Muen Vorachai!
You are disrespecting
a high-ranking noble with your accusation!
Flog him ten times
before his imprisonment!
No, no. I shall not be imprisoned!
Luang Bovorntat
has used me for his bidding!
Let go of me!
He will start an insurrection!
- Chai!
- Let go of me!
- Va.
- Va. Va, help me!
- Chai!
- Va! Let me go! Let me go!
- Chai! Chai!
- Chai!
- Va.
You achieved nothing for me,
yet you dare expose me.
May your end come
in prison in a mere week.
Dear. Dear…
Is it true,
as people say, that no one would survive
more than eight years in prison?
Even the citizens of Ayothaya
are now struggling to get by.
You cannot imagine
what it is like in prison, Va.
Grandfather and Father
were praised by all.
The honesty of our house
was held in high esteem.
- But at last, our names are flawed.
- No, no.
Listen.
You have done your best.
You warned him. You tried to stop him.
Dear.
What can we do?
Can we bring food, drink, or medicine,
- or even a blanket to him?
- Yes, we can.
We shall do our best.
Muen Chai shall probably survive
longer than others.
But now, you must not lose your strength.
You must rest well tonight.
I shall go to the prayer hall.
You go to sleep.
Yes.
Chai.
I brought some food for you.
I do not wish to see your face, Chavala.
But I shall visit you every day.
You must eat and sleep.
You must survive, brother.
My life is in ruin because of you.
Is this what your heart desires?
You now have my house
and all my servants.
Is this what you wished for?
I have had no one but you,
and now you have no one but me.
Because you are the only one I have,
I grew furious when you took
the side of the man who stole my position!
Put your mind at ease,
so you do not lose your strength.
Eat something.
Had you helped me
get rid of Pansaeng that day,
I would not suffer this fate.
But you
decided to love him
and joined him in prosecuting me!
Look into my eyes.
If I were to die the next day or two,
it will all be because of you.
You are killing me. You betrayed me!
You are killing me!
Chai.
Eat something.
- Eat it all.
- Go away.
Leave at once.
Leave at once! Go!
Leave me alone!
You traitor! You wicked sister!
I said leave me alone!
Saenkam!
- Capture him!
If any of you wish to be
rammed in the guts,
then try me.
This Saenkam shall only bring
destruction to anyone who supports him!
And if our Master
comes to help us tomorrow,
the three of us shall kill him!
The same goes
for all these people behind me.
They are overflowing
with hatred and anger,
enough to destroy you many times over!
You shall face me today.
A life of power
or death surrounded by love.
Subtitle translation by: Anan Pratchayakul