Pansaeng is surely facing illness
from amoria bloom.
He shall die without our effort.
How long shall it be?
Master! Please come out and help me!
Perhaps we should visit Noi's grandmother.
Does the house spirit follow you, My Lady?
Saiyud! Do not scare me.
Aon. What was that?
I do not know, My Lady.
- Hey!
- Sir, why are you here?
Did you secretly board the boat with us?
I would never betray you, Khun Saengplarn.
I shall take a walk.
Do not follow me.
Sir.
Your breakfast, sir.
Do you wish to have it now?
Yes. Thank you.
Sir.
About me and Saiyud…
If you do not believe me,
- I--
- Oh, no, no.
- I believe you.
- You do, sir?
I do, completely.
You have found one, have you not?
The gentle soul who cares
for both your body and mind.
Yes, My Lady.
I have witnessed the pain
you went through while serving Chai.
Now, I am relieved.
Someone as kind as you
shall have Aon to depend on.
I am most rejoiced.
We are still in trouble, My Lady.
I beg you and Khun Saengplarn
to keep this a secret.
If Muen Vorachai knows,
he will surely kill Aon.
Does that mean the two of you
must be together in secret?
We shall love each other
for the sake of love. That is enough.
Our lives together
are in the hands of destiny.
Did Aon give it to you?
Yes.
Can I see?
Is it pretty, My Lady?
You could not stop touching it.
I shall report this to Khun Saengplarn.
Yes.
Shall we go?
The family went around
asking in all the villages
from Ayothaya to Ban Khoktum,
and nobody had gotten sick or died lately.
So, we have not found Noi?
Khun Saengplarn, sir.
With your magic, could you please help us?
What do you wish for me to help with?
It has been ten days. Noi
must have been dead.
We have accepted it,
but we wish to find her body
and make merit for her
to send her to the peaceful realm.
Did Muen Vorachai not send soldiers
from Ayothaya to look for her?
We are not asking for soldiers, sir.
We’re asking for your help
to call Noi’s spirit and ask
how she died and where her body is.
Call Noi's spirit? That is it.
The power of your magic is immense.
Please help us.
Dear. Could you actually do it?
The spell for calling spirits does exist,
yet my school strictly forbids it.
It's considered a sin.
The dead are travelling to the next realm.
Calling them to us may confuse them
and cause them to be stuck
in this realm, unable to move on.
Noi.
- Noi.
- Dear.
Fine.
We shall try once.
Let’s simply focus
all our thoughts and love on Noi.
If her spirit is still roaming
and has enough strength to come to us,
we shall know the truth.
You have my thanks, sir.
We are deeply grateful.
Repeat my words.
May Buddha aid us.
- May Buddha aid us.
- May Dharma aid us.
- May Sangha aid us.
If the spirit of Noi remains unbound,
we ask that you appear before us
to guide us. Let the unseen
be seen.
Let the unknown be known.
Let the concealed be brought to light.
- Is she truly here?
- It is fine.
Noi. Noi. Where are you?
Do not leave me by myself.
Where are you going, Noi?!
Noi.
Do not leave me.
I did not see or hear anything.
Noi.
Are you wandering around here, Noi?
Noi. Who did this to you?
Come out and tell us.
It is possible
that her spirit has found rest.
The fact that she did not hold on
might also be a blessing.
During this time,
keep praying and making merit.
Let the good deeds ease your sorrow.
That way, Noi shall have no worries.
My apologies, sir. Victory is mine!
- Darn it.
- Let us start again.
Let the unseen be seen.
Let the unknown be known.
Let the concealed be brought to light!
What is it, sir?
As you served me in life,
so shall you serve me in death!
I am not afraid of you!
Noi! Noi!
Noi!
Get off me… Noi!
This young lady was born
with tremendous potential.
When she was born, did you dream anything
unusual or experience anything strange?
We did. Her father was promoted then.
I have met with many fortune tellers.
Every single one of them stated
that this child would bring
prosperity to her parents.
Might you be interested
in an empowerment ritual with me?
Spend a few nights here
to pray and receive blessings.
Certainly, Master. She will.
What shall happen after the ritual?
She shall bring even more wealth
and honor to your family.
Look, My Lady. This place is crowded.
As of late, people inside and outside
the palace are speaking of nothing
but the magical power of Master Saenkam.
How could an ordinary tree
turn into a magical tree?
But many have confirmed
its potency, My Lady.
All of them had their wishes granted.
Please give it a try.
It shall help with Khun Saengplarn.
The two of you, how may I be of service?
My Lady,
you were born
with strong spiritual power and merit.
Do you wish to commence
an empowerment ritual with me?
You only need to pray
with me for two nights.
Perhaps not. I only wish for a love charm.
You have someone you desire.
What is the name of that nobleman
or wealthy merchant?
- Can I keep it to myself?
- For someone such as you,
might I suggest the magical plant?
Normally, Master would give only
the leaves. But for a special lady,
he shall give the entire plant
for you to worship.
But it requires a sacrifice.
- Is that blood?
- Chicken's blood.
Boil these leaves and give that tea
to your intended to drink for a few days.
He shall think of nothing
but you and could not even eat or sleep.
It is best to sacrifice
with the blood of a pregnant woman.
The magic shall be most effective,
and he shall madly
beg to be with you.
This is madness.
Who would kill a person for this?
Even if a servant's life were sacrificed,
none would dare hold the daughter
of a noble such as yourself accountable.
Many have their wish granted.
You can ask around
if you do not believe me.
Is that not Muen Vorachai? Why is he here?
The spirit of Noi haunted you?
Did she appear before you?!
No, Master. But I have been
dreaming about being suffocated
by her for many nights now!
Then it is all in your head.
No need to be afraid!
But I have not slept for four nights.
Look at my face!
I can no longer take this, Master!
You think too much about a mere servant.
She is dead and should not concern you!
But she became a ghost!
Whatever. I must have amulets
to shield myself from her.
I cannot tolerate
this anymore, Master! Please!
Fine. I shall give you one.
You need not fear.
What is this area called?
Wat Heeplat cemetery, sir.
Are you truly not planning
to use this plant, My Lady?
Look at this, My Lord.
He does not even respect us.
My sister’s honor has been tarnished.
What are you talking about, brother?
How do you wish to hold him responsible?
He must hold a wedding ceremony
to restore my sister's honor, My Lord.
- Wedding?
- We cannot let that wedding happen.
That was a reasonable request.
Do not say that, my dear.
I have disrespected your honor,
all out of love for you.
Khun Saengplarn and Lady Chavala
were not said to be in love.
Only Muen Vorachai alone was trying
to force the marriage upon them.
What is it
you are thinking about, My Lady?
Pao. Send someone
to look in Muen Vorachai's house.
What is it we are looking for?
Find out if someone
has died in that house.
Noi must truly be dead, My Lady.
My life comes to an end.
Jerm. Do not do this.
You must have some food
and take your medicine. Please.
My Lady.
For seven years of marriage,
we have remained childless.
Then, we were able to have one.
I have stopped drinking since that day.
I intended to be a good father.
I could do it. For eight months,
I have not touched any liquor.
Where love takes root,
miracles blossom.
Yes, My Lady.
I did not believe I could do it.
But then Noi had to die.
Both the mother and the child are gone.
After this meal,
I shall return to the camp right away.
Very well.
What is it?
Hey!
Are you teasing me?
What? You said that you never
saw me laugh when I am around you.
So, I showed you.
What is wrong with you?
You were sad about Noi only a while ago.
Well,
I saw Aon splash a pot of tea towards you,
and I truly wanted to try as well.
Fine.
- It is my turn now.
- Dear.
Come here.
What is it you are doing?
What happened to Noi and Jerm showed me
how little time we truly have.
Hm.
Jerm could not eat or sleep.
He suffers because of love.
And that of Aon and Saiyud.
These two fare no better.
Love that has no hope of a future
shall be a lifelong agony for them.
They have made me realize
that fate is indeed cruel.
It can confine us
as servants of all kinds.
It confines you
as a good disciple who would
never betray your master's teachings.
Our bodies may be confined for any reason,
yet our hearts shall always be free.
We can hold anyone in our hearts.
Hold anyone in our hearts?
What are you trying to say?
We shall love
for the sake of love.
That is enough.
Our lives together
are in the hands of destiny.
I should return to the camp.
Dear.
Could you wait for me?
Let us take some time
to enjoy these flowers together.
This is the only season of the year
when these trees are in full bloom.
It is like my dream.
If you only walk past them,
you will have missed your chance
when they have all fallen.
If you keep stopping for the flowers,
what of the goals in your life?
My goal is to avenge
my parents and my sister
and save those who are wronged.
I appreciate them for only a few minutes.
I do not wish to own them.
It does not take long to appreciate.
You did not study any magic.
Yet the fragrance of flowers
on the house and on yourself
is even more powerful than magic.
If flowers serve no purpose,
why would they exist in our world?
I have thought it through.
I shall hold you in my heart.
I love you,
not as a sibling.
And it is not merely an admiration.
No. You will be the one to suffer.
Do not do this.
You need not worry.
I shall help you
uphold the vow you took with your master.
I only wanted to tell you
and celebrate the freedom of my heart.
I wish to appreciate the flowers.
And I wish to appreciate
our lives together.
That is enough for me.
I should not have done it, Master.
I have brought an enemy into my life.
The worst enemy there is.
I shall not survive this time.
Please help me, Master.
Please help me.
I have a crime to report! My wife was
killed and her blood was used for a plant!
My wife was killed!
I am here to report a crime!
My wife was killed,
and her blood was used to water a plant!
- Go!
- Advance!
- Yours is doomed.
- That shall not be!
Go! Go!
It must look for the right time to strike.
- Go!
- Well done.
- That is it.
- Attack!
- Go. Go.
- Daeng, attack.
My Lords. My Lords.
- My Lords.
- Hey!
My Lords. I am here to report a crime.
Please do not dismiss me.
Who are you?! How did you get in here?!
Guards! Get him out!
I did not harm anyone.
I am only troubled. Please listen to me.
Go report your trouble to your governor!
The governor did not listen to me,
so was the capital court.
No one was able to help me, My Lords.
Please.
A citizen comes to report a crime,
and must he be hurt for it?
But it was against the law
to trespass the palace vicinity!
Did you not hear
that nobody listened to him?
We have a duty to help citizens
resolve their problems.
And this is a time for duty,
not entertainment.
You insolent bastard!
In the palace vicinity, we are unarmed.
Letting outsiders in is dangerous!
How shall we live without rules?!
My Lords. I beg you.
You can execute me,
but my wife deserves justice.
Well. State your problem.
My name is Chuang, a servant
at Luang Athikorn's house, My Lords.
My wife's name is Pin. I suspect that
Luang Athikorn killed my wife, My Lords.
You are accusing a nobleman of high rank.
No wonder everyone denies your report.
Luang Athikorn's only son
is gravely ill. Two weeks ago,
he received a magical plant
from Master Saenkam.
This plant requires a sacrifice of freshly
spilled blood from a pregnant woman.
Then, my three-month
pregnant wife disappeared.
She has been missing
for seven days now, My Lords.
Are you assuming
that your master killed your wife
to offer her blood to the plant?
Yes, My Lord.
Are there any eyewitnesses
or any evidence?
No, My Lord.
Luang Athikorn refused
to help me find my wife
and offered me 20 hun of gold.
If he was not responsible,
why must he give me the gold?
Did Luang Athikorn tell you
the reason he gave you the gold?
He said that
I did my duties well, My Lord.
A mere assumption cannot be
considered a criminal case.
Also, you have no witness or proof at all.
Are you not going to help me, My Lords?
At least you must have the body
for us to investigate further.
But the culprit is a Luang! He would not
leave the body for us to find, My Lord!
We are sorry
we could not take this accusation.
But you shall be punished
for trespassing the palace ground.
Put him in prison!
Guards! Take him away!
Come here.
I spoke the truth!
Luang Athikorn killed my wife!
- He killed my wife and child!
- Take him away!
- Let go! Let me go!
- Get him out of here!
The problem is solved, My Lords.
An artifact that requires blood offerings.
A savage cult such as this one
must be watched closely.
Yes, My Lord.
A simple archery shot
should not be this hard for a renowned
soldier such as Khun Saengplarn.
Dear.
Shall we go somewhere quiet
and talk about Master Saengkam?
A few days ago, someone reported
that a sacrifice
for Master Saenkam's magical plant
is blood from pregnant women.
But there is no evidence
of someone actually offering it.
But there is one pregnant servant missing.
No. Two of them.
One is from Luang Athikorn's house,
and another is from Muen Vorachai's.
It was Noi.
I see you have heard something.
Hm.
I am here to tell you
that I saw Muen Vorachai
at Master Saenkam's house as well.
May I ask what you were doing there?
I went to observe that place
on Father's behalf. Am I not allowed to?
You are.
Dear, please see if you are
experiencing anything strange.
Is your strength
or are your skills beginning to diminish?
How are they relevant?
Well, from the beginning, Muen Vorachai
forced you to marry his sister
to try to weaken your magical abilities.
If he truly asked Master Saenkam
to curse you with a love charm
using that servant's blood,
you shall become sick,
unfocused, and insane.
You shall lose all your skills.
Are you feeling any changes?
Traitor!
After all I have done for you!
Was it that pleasant
to spend the night together?!
Sir.
Well, not that much.
But you feel something?
That is it. I always knew
Lady Chavala's intentions were not pure.
Well, I suggest you return
and look through your house carefully.
You shall find the magical plant.
If you find one, you must
drive Lady Chavala out of the house.
I do not wish for you to end up like Prai.
Ah.
What business has led you
all the way to this camp, Lady Pim?
This is a bedroom.
Perhaps I was sleeping here.
I am here to bring you your meal.
I happened to miss you.
How could a lady say such words?
I do not know.
I truly missed you.
I wanted to see your face.
Let me pour some tea for you.
I sense no enchantment.
What are you doing, dear?
I was only swatting flies.
Here.
Have plenty, dear.
I have missed your cooking so much.
Your chili paste is so…
Actually,
you did not have to walk me home.
I can return by myself.
I must fetch something anyway.
Very well.
Can I have a tiffin back?
Thank you, dear.
You found nothing?!
How could that be?
Or perhaps Khun Saengplarn's
weaker magic compared
to Master Saenkam's
prevents him from detecting it?
Hey.
My apologies, sir.
But Pao's words also make sense.
He may be using illusion magic.
You said yourself
that you feel somewhat unusual.
Unease from sickness is completely normal.
Let us say that
I have taken a look and found nothing.
I shall go train
the soldiers now, My Lady.
We must go see with our own eyes, Pao.
Yes, My Lady.
Pao, Aum.
- Yes, My Lady?
Look through every plant. See if there are
leaves like this one. Search everywhere.
- Yes, My Lady.
What is this?
What is it you are doing here, My Lady?
Lady Chavala, your brother
cast a love charm
on Khun Saengplarn with the magical plant.
And I am here to find proof.
Cast a love charm using a plant?
Yes. The magical plant
from Master Saenkam.
Well, there is no such thing here.
A love charm must be cast on two.
You may not realize yet.
Any strange feelings?
Agitated? Irritable?
Hm?
I did not find any, My Lady.
I found nothing as well.
Lady Pim. Lady Pim! Wait!
Nothing.
Lady Pim, stop at once!
Lady Pim! Listen to me.
Why must I cast a love charm on him
when I am already
his royal-bestowed wife, his only wife?
A wife he loathes
to the point of moving away to the camp?
Are you still calling yourself his wife?
It is nothing to be concerned about.
Regardless, you are not to come between us
for Khun Saengplarn is mine
and mine alone.
Only for now. I shall unveil
the conspiracy you hatched
with your brother to destroy him.
It is all because of you
that I couldn't eat or sleep for months.
You shall die today!
Lady Pim!
You are wrong to pick a fight
with a merchant like me!
- Stop!
- It hurts!
How could you destroy
other people's belongings?!
- Stop!
- It hurts!
What a mess! This is an all-out war, sir!
Stop! Stop at once!
Va, stop! All of you, stop!
Dear!
Why would you hug Lady Pim?!
Let go of her! Come here!
What is this, Lady Pim?
What is it you are doing here?!
I am here to save you.
To find a plant you could not find.
And have you found it?
With the three of you,
one plant should be easy enough to find!
Must you all fight?!
What?
And have you three found it?!
No, sir.
Hm.
A slander. Lady Pim accused me
because she wants my husband for herself!
She could not be any more straightforward.
Lady Pim. If you search
my house in this manner,
I could report you to the judge.
Are you under a spell?
Could you bring yourself to report me?
I am not under any spell, Lady Pim.
But if you do not leave
my house now, I shall really do it
The daughter of the Minister
of the Royal Household
was reported
by Khun Saengplarn for trespassing!
It shall be a scandalous case!
You are truly under a spell.
It is obvious.
What good does a woman like her have
that makes you so fond of her?
One day, I shall find a way to save you.
It is your time to go.
- You!
- Go away!
- Enough!
- Hey!
Go away. Take your things too.
Aum, enough!
- What a pain.
- What?
You too! Why did you not stop your lady?!
Well…
You were much calmer and did not
turn to violence like this before!
I was not protective
of you then, but I am now!
And how would it end
if you two kept fighting?
She accused me of using a love charm.
It was only her excuse to see you!
So, Lady Pim can go see you at the camp,
but I am not allowed
to work with Aon at the market.
Lady Pim and I have nothing going on.
Aon and I have nothing going on either!
If she can freely visit you, how can I be
sure she does not spend nights with you?
- What? Are you out of your mind?!
- Well?!
- There are soldiers at the camp!
- There are people at the market as well!
If you do not wish for me
to work or to see Aon,
you should spend nights at your house!
At least I’ll feel reassured
that you’re not with anyone at night.
Checkmate!
What was that, Ming?
I played chess
with Yong this morning, sir.
The Bishop checked the King,
and he had nowhere to go.
Shut up!
It does not matter.
Whether I sleep here or at the camp,
we shall not lie together anyway.
Dear!
I do not wish to lie with you, but my
honor was hurt. Lady Pim disrespected me!
Whatever, dear!
If you stay within my sight
and Lady Pim
sneaks in to see you at night,
at least the dogs will bark
and I will wake up to watch over you!
- No! I shall spend nights at the camp!
- What?!
Women are such a pain!
Both women and men
can be consumed by jealousy!
Well… Who was it that was
destroying things at the market?
- Hm?
- You!
I shall not talk to you anymore!
The King can still run away, Ming.
This game is far from over.
We must keep watching.
You constantly dictate others' actions,
yet you don't behave yourself.
- Tian.
- Yes, sir.
Laor is not here yet? I requested
a scented candle. Did she deliver it?
- She will not come.
- What?
Laor said that
from now,
I shall be the one cooking for you.
Why?!
Lady Va is angry with you.
That is all Laor told me.
Angry with me?
- Yes.
- Angry with me?
Why does the sound feel so close tonight?
All this time,
is it you who has been playing the fiddle?
You are worried
if I meet with someone at night,
so I am here to tell you
I have been coming
for someone at the dock nearby
to play the fiddle for her.
It is truly you.
Well, Tian has told me before,
but I did not believe him.
The house is on one side, yet you played
the fiddle on the other side of the river.
How strange.
The music from this fiddle
has made my nights not feel lonely at all.
Has this music helped
to calm your anger towards me?
Did it calm my anger?
Hey. Wait.
I did not wish for you to do this.
You are out of line now.
Always surprises me with strange acts.
Everything I did is only to assure you
as siblings only.
Siblings. It is all we shall be.
Very well, siblings.
Father, Mother, this is Pansaeng,
the one I am wedded to.
Help! Please help me!
It is our human nature to believe
that achievements come from
the sacred power, rather than ourselves.
Are you here to challenge me?
You have robbed my family!
Who are you?
My name is Khun Saengplarn!
Your obsession with a woman weakened you.
Your magic has faded now.
I wish to be reborn
to meet you in every life
and for us to always remember each other.
Subtitle translation by: Anan Pratchayakul