CONDOLENCES
MAY THE DECEASED REST IN PEACE
SONG WONKYUNG: UNTITLED
Luna.
SAA ARCHIVES
1,783 FILES CONTAINING "LUNA"
UNIDENTIFIED CONFIDENTIAL FILE
CHECK SECURITY CLEARANCE LEVEL
SECRET STORAGE
What could this be for?
We'll find out once we get down there.
E1 and I will climb down first to check.
Stay here.
Contact us if something happens.
Yes, sir.
What is this?
How can there be so many plants here?
There's a storage room here.
Why are there so many plants here?
Are you sure it's okay for us
to just walk in like this?
This storage wasn't on the map.
Look at these stems.
How does this make any sense?
Tell me about it.
You don't see anything
this large back on Earth.
How did they grow all this?
Man, this place is amazing.
It looks like there are multiple storages.
Wow, isn't the mission a success
if we retrieved just one?
Look at how many there are.
They're all green.
That means they're all
in good condition, right?
They hid them all down here?
It seems like the system
for this facility
is separate from where we were.
What is this?
A lunar water capsule broke.
How can all these plants grow
with this little water? It makes no sense.
You're right. If we use this,
we'll never have to worry
about water again.
Only if we can keep it under control.
-Begin the retrieval.
-Yes, Captain.
-Chief Gong, search the premises.
-Yes, sir.
E1, Sun.
Yes, sir.
How many capsules is this?
Hurry. It's been neglected,
so we don't know what state it's in.
Yes, Captain.
Chief Gong, how does
the other storage look?
The situation is similar.
Most of the samples are fine.
These samples are full too.
We'll have to use a rover to carry these.
Let's go home already, please.
-What's that?
-What?
Hold on.
What is this?
What's wrong? What's going on?
Get it!
Look out, E1!
Wait here.
Are you all right?
I'm fine, sir.
E1.
Get back inside!
Watch out!
It's headed your way, E2!
Captain.
We have to get out of here. Now!
Evacuate, now!
Samples. I'll grab the samples.
I will. I'll grab them.
You should go first.
What about E1?
-We have to get out now.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
-No, wait.
Let's go!
Warning. Thermoregulator anomaly detected.
Warning.
-Thermoregulator anomaly detected.
-Get over here!
I need help!
E2.
-E2!
-We have a man down here!
-We need to get him to the infirmary.
-What?
Give me a hand. Lift him.
There's blood in his lungs and pleurae.
His heart rate is at 146,
and his BP is 75 over 43.
I need to open him up. Sterilized gauze.
Scalpel.
His BP is way too low.
Can you grab all type B blood bags
in the medical kit?
We have two.
That's not enough. Can you ask the others?
We need more type B blood.
I'm type O. You can draw my blood.
Do you feel dizzy?
No, I'm fine.
Let me know right away
if you feel dizzy or unusual.
Okay.
She ripped off his arm.
Then she crawled all over the ceiling.
What is this…
First, some water killed people,
and then a monster shows up too.
Could she be the one who killed Lee Gisu?
Yes.
I think so.
Why is she following us around?
-To kill us all?
-I think it's because of the lunar water.
What?
I think that's why she killed Gisu,
and attacked us.
She keeps showing up
where the lunar water is.
She's after the same thing as us.
Is it really possible
that she's a survivor?
A survivor?
How can she be a survivor?
A kid can't live here for five years.
She was a kid, right? Wasn't she?
She was. She seemed like a child
who wanted to keep what's hers,
who didn't want us to take it away.
It may sound odd…
but that was the behavior of a child.
Are you saying we're the intruders?
Like with Gisu,
she may be using only
ventilation shafts to get around.
You can get anywhere you like
by using shaft INP-07. You're right.
We're connected to the SAA.
RECEIVING SIGNAL
Did you find the intruder?
The intruder's whereabouts
are still unknown.
What about the samples?
We may lose more lives at this rate.
Do we have to continue?
As I mentioned before,
this operation will be a failure
if anybody else gets the lunar water.
I don't care if you kill the intruder.
You must catch them.
Also, make sure you retrieve
the lunar water that was taken.
It was a kid.
What?
The intruder seemed like a little kid.
The kid was wearing a lab coat too.
So what?
Is there a possibility
that this kid's a survivor?
Stop trying to make things
more complicated than they should be.
That's not what's important.
Why does the kid's identity matter?
That won't change your mission.
I…
sometimes
dream of standing in the rain.
When I wake up from that wonderful dream,
it's painful beyond words to wake up
to this horrendous and sad reality.
We must
make sure it rains,
once again,
over this land, so that water
may flow abundantly on Earth.
We must recreate that world again.
I'll send you backup very soon.
Hold out just a little longer.
PHOTOS
Is it because of Director Choi?
Why can't I go back into the data storage?
It's too dangerous to go back.
We don't know what happened
to the lunar water after it leaked.
I finally found it.
I can't give up like this.
It's dangerous, and that's it.
I can't condone more deaths.
There were 117 crew members
here at Balhae Station.
None of them survived.
If we take the lunar water back now,
we may end up sacrificing more.
It doesn't matter what you find out.
The lunar water will be taken back
with that kid.
Then that's all the more reason
to get to the data in the data storage.
Now that we know the danger
that lies in the lunar water,
we need to investigate as much as we can.
I don't care if you don't trust me.
I'm not doing this
for personal reasons only.
Captain, we're ready to make a search.
Okay. I'll be there.
I know you'll go even if I say no.
Go with Doc Hong. You can't go alone.
If you find anything on the lunar water
or that child, report back right away.
Okay.
I'm at Storage Three.
We're still on our way
to the facility hallway.
-Get into the shaft there and take a look.
-Yes, sir.
I'll start searching here and move there.
Yes, sir.
It'll take a while.
If it ends before we get back,
call for me. I'll come for you.
Okay, Doc.
Are you sure
you two will be okay?
What's the worst that could happen?
Why? Anything to say?
Do you think
the lunar water research data is in there?
I hope so.
I really do.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Damn, that thing is here again.
Those eyes keep popping up.
She must like to draw.
Captain, we've arrived
at the shaft of the facility hallway.
The cover is still intact.
I don't think she escaped through here.
Chief.
Damn it!
It looks fine, right?
Yes.
Let's go.
DATA BRICK SEARCH
SEARCHING DATA BRICK
What was Dr. Song Wonkyung like?
I had no idea she had been working here.
I only found out after the accident
at Balhae Station was made known.
I thought you two were
by yourselves without parents.
How could she keep you in the dark?
Back then, something else
was more important to her than me.
There was this one time
when she contacted me first.
It was right before the accident.
SONG WONKYUNG
If I had
picked up her call…
would it have changed anything?
Captain, we're inside
the facility hallway.
This area is not on the map,
but it looks like…
this leads to the dorms.
We'll expand our search
and check the dorms too.
Okay. Be careful.
I'm sick of this.
It worked. It's open.
SEARCHING DATA BRICK
DATA BRICK SEARCH COMPLETE
What?
This is impossible.
There's nothing in here.
Wait, did someone erase everything?
DATA BRICK SEARCH COMPLETE
It looks like
the data was erased on purpose.
Damn it.
Captain.
Why are you two here?
What about searching the dorms?
I see why people can die
when they're too shocked.
This doesn't seem right.
It looked like this hallway
would lead us into the dorms.
It feels like we've been
circling the same area.
Exactly.
It's like playing tag.
She knows exactly where we are
and always manages to avoid us.
She knows her way around here
much better than we do.
Who could have deleted this?
Why? For what reason?
I told you to call me.
No, I'm fine.
What happened to the research data?
Why did you take them out?
Aren't you supposed to join the search?
Oh, you haven't heard.
We decided to stop the search
and meet at the command center.
There could be a safety issue
if we leave these here.
So I'll move the samples
back to the command center.
Why?
Was it Captain Han's order?
You said
that monster seems to be
after the lunar water like we are.
Don't worry.
We're only being careful,
just in case anything happens.
No.
I make the decisions
when it comes to the samples.
We'll keep the lunar water
and the kit here.
All right, then.
Let me know right away
if anything happens.
Did we miss a passage
on the holographic map?
I'm sorry. I'll check once again
when we get to the command center.
But that girl…
That monster?
What do we call her? Whatever.
But why is she so important?
We should head home
now that we found the sample.
Captain.
Captain, she's here.
What do you mean?
Doc Hong, respond.
Captain.
Wait!
Dr. Song, step back.
One second.
Don't get near me. Give me a second.
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, NAMES, AND INCIDENTS
ARE PRODUCTS OF THE IMAGINATION
OR USED FICTITIOUSLY.
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO REALITY
IS ENTIRELY COINCIDENTAL.