How does it feel to be a part
of the mission on Balhae Station?
I don't know. I'm not sure.
It's great.
What was the training like?
Good.
Isn't it tough?
No.
Do you stay in touch with your family?
I feel more comfortable alone.
5TH PSYCHOTHERAPY SESSION
How do you feel today?
Good.
Don't you think you might regret
taking part in this mission?
No.
What kind of thoughts help you
bear through a tough situation?
I don't think about anything.
What about your family?
My parents passed away when I was young,
and my older sister died
in an accident five years ago.
What does your older sister mean to you?
I'm not sure.
I think I relied on her a lot
when I was a kid.
10TH PSYCHOTHERAPY SESSION
Why did your older sister leave?
I don't know.
But I'm sure she had a reason.
What does your older sister mean to you?
KEY TO SALVATION
How are the capsules?
The internal temperature is unstable,
so I'll have to see.
Let's try not to move these around
until we transfer them outside.
What were you thinking?
What?
Did you think she wouldn't attack us
if you gave her the lunar water?
I only
wanted to show her
that I won't hurt her.
That I'm not trying
to take the capsule from her.
I thought she'd feel that too.
If you expose yourself to danger,
you burden the whole team.
You saw her.
You saw how
the lunar water reacts with her.
We all saw it.
Yes, her cheek opened and closed.
And her wounds were healed in an instant.
How is that possible?
Dr. Song, do you have any idea
what kind of being she may be?
I don't know.
But what I do know is
the lunar water won't kill her.
He'll be fine.
His cut isn't too deep.
Anyway, what was that girl?
Did the lunar water bring
some kind of change to her body?
It seemed like her body
adapted to the lunar water.
Adapted?
She didn't simply adapt to it.
Her physical ability… and the speed
of recovery showed it's more than that.
She may have been born
with antibodies for it,
or it may be
a special case of genetic mutation
caused by different environmental factors.
What we do know is she's a danger to us.
We should resume the search
and catch her even if we must kill--
No, we can't kill her.
We need to kill her or whatever
to put an end to this and go home.
We can't kill her.
She may be the only key
to the secret of the lunar water.
She might just be everyone's hope.
This is just…
You're a bit feverish.
It might be the wrong antibiotics.
There's nothing we can use here,
so I'll check another lab.
I'll find something.
Are you all right?
I'm okay, sir.
I'm sorry to make you worried.
Don't mind the mission.
Look after yourself.
Hello, Captain Han.
I heard the situation isn't looking great.
Are you all right?
I'd like to ask you a question.
Are you there alone?
Yes, this is a secure channel.
Please go ahead.
How much do you know
about this series of events?
It was Director Choi's decision
to shut down Balhae Station.
There are some who question that decision.
What about you?
Is there anything else
I should know regarding Balhae Station?
You're the one…
who's there at the station now.
What do you mean?
Please have a talk with Dr. Song.
The truth lies there,
not here.
Current outdoor temperature, 23 degrees.
Humidity, 36 percent.
-Air quality is at Level D.
-Doctor.
Did you say Hajin is gone?
We just found her.
What happened?
I'm not sure.
She must've had a bad dream.
She kept looking for her dad
and barely managed to fall asleep.
Stop!
I said stop!
I'm warning you!
Stand back.
This is a warning.
Return to your original places.
We will fire if you do not stand back.
Stand back.
Mom…
I suddenly remember
the time I went to a swimming pool.
I got on a slide
and fell right into the water.
It was so damn fun.
Right?
You've done that, haven't you?
If this mission is a success,
we could see a pool once again.
We'll lure her out and capture her alive.
Map of the ventilation shafts.
Show INP-07.
The shaft INP-07 leads
to many key facilities in the station.
If we lure her
with this lunar water capsule
and block off this intersection of INP-07…
right here,
she'll have to come out through the vent
in the hallway of the machine room.
Then we'll shut both ends of the hallway.
Like hare coursing.
So we want to chase her down
and trap her. But there's a problem.
That hare can
easily rip a person to pieces.
He's right.
Even if we get lucky
and trap her in the hallway,
it's still too dangerous
to subdue her and catch her alive.
That's why we need Dr. Song.
Captain.
We can't use guns.
Please don't provoke her
as long as we must
until I calm her down.
That's my decision to make on the scene.
Even within the SAA,
some people were against
moving the lunar water to Earth.
If we carry something back
without confirming its safety,
it could pose a danger for everyone.
But Director Choi or other higher-ups
probably thought it's more important
not to let anyone else
get their hands on the lunar water.
Knowing everyone in this station
was killed by that very lunar water?
There are enough reasons
to take this risk.
I think…
my sister deleted all the research data.
Perhaps she hoped no one
would find out about the lunar water.
Then why do you think
she left you that message?
In the end,
she probably thought
someone had to do this.
Wouldn't that be why she called you here?
I'm not sure.
Once I find out the entire truth,
what am I really supposed to do?
I have no idea.
My device.
Drop your gun.
Why are you doing this?
Drop your gun!
Dr. Song, are you ready?
Yes.
To your position.
Yes, sir.
Let's get ready.
Lieutenant Ryu, can you hear me?
Lieutenant Ryu, where are you?
Lieutenant Ryu.
Doc Hong, what's going on?
Lieutenant Ryu and E2 are both missing.
I'm not sure where they are.
What do you mean, they're both missing?
Did E2 regain consciousness?
No, he hasn't come back.
Even if he did,
he can't move in that condition.
I understand. Please be on standby.
-We'll be there as soon as--
-Captain.
She's here.
Now.
Dr. Song, come on out.
No.
Don't move.
You'll get more hurt.
Luna?
Luna 073?
This is the best we can do for her.
Dr. Song…
Are you okay?
We got her, Doc Hong.
We finally got that monster.
What? You got her?
Okay.
Are E2 and Lieutenant Ryu with you?
What a relief.
We can go home now.
Yes, okay.
So are E2 and Lieutenant Ryu with you?
No, that's why I'm heading over there now.
No, don't come back here.
Go to the command center
and find their locations.
I'll stay here.
They might come back.
All right, then.
Captain.
Is everyone all right?
I'll get her ready to be transported.
Let's get her treated first.
Do we hand her over to the backup
as soon as they get here?
They will take her to Earth, won't they?
Do you know what will happen to her
and where she'll go?
GATE CLOSURE
Activating gate closure.
Activating machine room gate closure.
Dr. Song, no!
Darn it, what's going on?
What is this?
What the heck is going on?
Damn it.
Dr. Song!
Dr. Song…
Activating gate closure. All members,
evacuate from the machine room.
Captain, we have to move now.
-This way.
-Evacuate from the machine room.
Activating main lab closure.
All members, evacuate from the main lab.
Captain.
Captain!
We're now…
The main lab is shut down.
The fire door just shut off the area.
What's going on? Is everyone okay?
We're trying to get
a grasp of the situation.
Kim Sun, where are you?
I barely escaped.
I'm on my way to the command center.
Check the system when you get there,
and locate the crew.
Yes, sir.
Captain.
Captain, can you hear me?
Shutdown complete.
It won't open.
Captain, I don't think
the entire station was shut down.
Just a few areas.
Doc, have you found E2 and Taesuk?
No, I can't reach them.
For now,
I'll pick up the lunar water samples
and find a way out of here.
They're probably still in the shaft.
This is AP-4,
connected to the outside of the station.
We can come across where Dr. Song is
at the second intersection.
Ryu Taesuk…
He volunteered for this mission, right?
Yes, that's what I confirmed.
GATE CLOSURE
Where did you go?
Were you
waiting for me?
Are you okay?
Does your leg hurt?
Have you been
living here all along?
Do you
want to try this?
Here.
No, no.
Not like that.
Right.
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, NAMES, AND INCIDENTS
ARE PRODUCTS OF THE IMAGINATION
OR USED FICTITIOUSLY.
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO REALITY
IS ENTIRELY COINCIDENTAL.