♪Counting the many romantic scenes we share with you♪
♪I keep everything you love and adore in my mind♪
♪Love feels like magic, its endless warmth wraps around you♪
♪And all my devotion. When the stars light up the sky♪
♪That is my answer to you♪
♪Even if we're thousands of miles apart, my love will not waver♪
♪Your smile creates ripples in my heart, as if you're saying "I do"♪
♪My thoughts stretch on without end, deep beyond measure♪
♪My love makes no sound, hidden quietly within your gaze♪
♪If we ever meet again, I'll hold you tight with all my strength♪
♪I'll run straight toward you, landing softly in your dreams♪
♪And take you to witness the splendor of love♪
[This Is the Feeling of Love]
[Adapted from "This Is the Feeling of Love" commissioned by Migu Reading]
[Author: Lucky Apple Wealthy Pineapple]
[Episode 6]
Thank you.
No matter what happens,
I'll always be by your side.
Make a wish.
Legend says it will only light up with true love.
Have I really fallen in love with him?
Drink more water.
What do you mean?
Spring is here.
Every creature awakens.
The animals are beginning to breed and multiply.
We still have work to do. Stop talking nonsense.
I'm getting something.
Boss, Zhen Beixing is ruthless.
She fired me.
I've been serving you for so long.
I deserve some credit for my hard work.
You must save me.
She's not showing me any respect.
I can't survive like this.
You are an important subordinate of mine.
I won't give up on you so easily.
But you saw it yourself.
Zhen Beixing is too smart.
Don't worry. I know what to do.
However, you should keep a low profile
and stop causing any trouble recently.
Also, stop harassing any women.
Ma Tianming has information
that Zhen Quan doesn't want exposed.
If he can threaten Zhen Quan,
that means he does have something important in his hands.
Someone like him is the most dangerous.
He might take drastic measures when he's desperate.
So, we must act instead of waiting.
We must find a way
to dig out all of Ma Tianming and Zhen Quan's
inside dealings.
I'll try to readjust the listening device.
Let's see if we can capture more useful conversations.
When there's a chance,
we will expose Ma Tianming's conduct to the public.
Sure.
Uncle Zhen Quan.
Why are you here in person?
I came here for Ma Tianming.
I can just deal with it myself.
You don't need to come here.
Ma Tianming has served the Zhen family for a long time.
He contributed a lot to the company.
You just took over.
If you are too harsh on him,
it might hurt the veteran employees' feelings.
Uncle Zhen Quan, you are right.
I understand.
However, it might be hard to appease the other employees
if Ma Tianming isn't punished for his act.
In that case, let's call for a board meeting
and get every shareholder to discuss a solution
that protects the company's interests
and also takes care of the veteran employees.
Ma Tianming
might have made a mistake
but he has been in the company for decades.
His loyalty to the company is unquestionable.
We should give him a chance to reflect on his mistakes.
Uncle Zhen Quan,
I understand your concern
but Ma Tianming's action this time
has seriously tarnished the company's reputation
and breached our employees' rights.
I can't sit by and do nothing.
Ma Tianming is an old employee.
Sometimes, he gets carried away.
We should focus on correcting him instead.
You are right.
We should
consider the company's internal harmony and stability.
I can see how Ma has been doing in recent years.
He has been doing his best for the company all his life.
Even though he made a small mistake,
his merit overshadows his blunder.
A small mistake?
Harmony and stability might be important
but we can't sacrifice the company's image
and the employees' rights to achieve that.
He completely broke the company's rules with his behavior.
He must be dealt with according to the law and rules.
Beixing, you just came here.
You don't know the company's internal structure well.
We can completely
resolve Ma Tianming's problem internally.
There's no need
to make an issue out of it.
It can only be resolved internally under the condition
that Ma Tianming has truly regretted his actions
and is willing to accept the punishments.
Otherwise, I must protect the company's image
and the employees' rights
as the company's leader.
If we look past his mistake,
where's the justice for all our employees?
I must maintain my principles firmly.
A new leader has to show authority.
I understand that.
But you can't sacrifice a veteran employee.
Zhang, you will be retired in two years, right?
If she can fire someone who has worked for the company for decades today,
she can also slowly get rid of the people
who worked with Zhen Cheng.
[Gu Chen]
Hello, Lin Mo.
Post the video
I sent you just now all over the internet within ten minutes.
Don't worry. I'll make sure it goes viral.
It's terrible.
The video of Ma Tianming harassing Qin has been exposed.
The online criticism is completely out of control.
People are calling for Ma Tianming to be terminated.
Every media outlet has started reporting this.
They want to get an interview here. Please look at the screen.
Recently, a scandal involving a manager of the Zhen Group
harassing a female employee
has drawn widespread public attention.
An independent investigator who cares about social responsibility
and wishes to expose unfair practices
has decided to expose the footage to the public
after a thorough investigation
- in hopes to of bringing justice - The culprit must be punished.
- and workplace equality. - Justice for the victim.
- We must boycott the company. - Zero-tolerance for workplace harassment.
A manager of the Zhen Group
- Punish the jerk! - is accused of harassing female employees.
How can women's workplace safety be ensured?
This is bad.
Our company's brand image has taken a huge hit.
Our share price has triggered a limit down.
Inform the PR department immediately
to initiate crisis management
and stop it from going viral.
Yes.
Since Ma Tianming's behavior has affected the company negatively,
I've decided to relieve you of your duties immediately.
Beixing,
this is too reckless of you.
You will bring more trouble to the company.
Ma Tianming, we hope you can regret your actions in time
because of your past contributions.
But now,
your behavior
completely went against the company's rules.
We can't just sit idly and do nothing.
For the sake of the company's long-term development,
we must make the correct decision.
That's right.
You are right.
That's it.
Ma Tianming, you've betrayed our trust
and harmed the company and its employees.
I also agree to relieve you of all your duties
and hand you over to the authorities for further investigation.
Zhen Beixing,
this is personal, isn't it?
I contributed so much to the company
and you cut me off easily.
You completely went against the company's rules
and moral standards.
We must have zero tolerance for acts like these.
This is the decision of the board.
It also shows our firm stance to the public and all our employees.
Yes! Fire him!
- Fire him! - He must be fired!
Gu Chen.
Thank you for today.
It's what I should do.
Sorry. I can't accompany you tonight.
This is a hidden tracker.
Here.
This hidden tracker
has two-way communication.
If you are in danger,
press the button twice.
Your position will be sent to my device.
You should be careful, too.
Sure.
Do you think you can just do anything to me as you wish?
Let me tell you.
It's not that easy.
Ma Tianming,
why are you here?
I've contributed so much to the company.
How can you just fire me as you wish?
If you won't give me a way out,
you will die with me!
Stop!
Are you all right?
Zhen Beixing, your father was...
It isn't what you think...
I will investigate it clearly.
♪The hazy streets rewind, bidding farewell to every heartbroken visitor♪
♪Parting flowers wither and fall, their lingering fragrance fades away♪
♪Your figure is swallowed by the crowd, as if you never stood by my side♪
♪The once moving vows vanish with the passing of time, who remembers them?♪
♪It's hard to define what I've truly possessed until now♪
♪Was it you or just memories? Snow melts, winter passes♪
♪Everything is like our fleeting encounter, how can one let it go?♪
♪It's hard to define what I've truly possessed until now♪
♪Was it love or regret? Amid the river of time and sea of people♪
♪You and I embrace only for a moment before we part unwillingly♪