♪Counting the many romantic scenes we share with you♪
♪I keep everything you love and adore in my mind♪
♪Love feels like magic, its endless warmth wraps around you♪
♪And all my devotion. When the stars light up the sky♪
♪That is my answer to you♪
♪Even if we're thousands of miles apart, my love will not waver♪
♪Your smile creates ripples in my heart, as if you're saying "I do"♪
♪My thoughts stretch on without end, deep beyond measure♪
♪My love makes no sound, hidden quietly within your gaze♪
♪If we ever meet again, I'll hold you tight with all my strength♪
♪I'll run straight toward you, landing softly in your dreams♪
♪And take you to witness the splendor of love♪
[This Is the Feeling of Love]
[Adapted from "This Is the Feeling of Love" commissioned by Migu Reading]
[Author: Lucky Apple Wealthy Pineapple]
[Episode 24]
Beixing.
When will you wake up?
Oh, no.
Beixing is dreaming again.
What can I do to wake you up?
Where am I?
How come my mind is a blank?
I can't recall anything.
Who are you?
Why does that face look so familiar?
As if it appears often in my dreams.
He must be someone important to me.
But I lost him.
Gu Chen, I finally found you.
You're finally awake.
Beixing,
you finally woke up.
Do you know?
After you fainted,
I sent you one paper crane every day,
praying that you'd wake up soon.
Look around you.
There are more than 1,000 paper cranes in this ward.
Exactly.
My hands are all calloused from folding the paper.
Qian, thank you.
I'm moved.
Beixing.
Do you know?
Gu Chen woke up three days ago.
We've all been waiting for you.
I'm okay, Qian.
I appreciate your concern.
You're okay?
- Qian. - Both of you almost...
Beixing just woke up.
She needs to rest.
Let's head back first
so that they can get their rest.
Okay.
Beixing, rest well.
Mo and I will visit you tomorrow.
Okay.
Bye.
Let's go.
Gu Chen.
Were you not afraid?
I heard that if you couldn't wake me up,
you would fall into an endless slumber as well,
turning into a coma patient in bed.
I wasn't afraid.
Only when you live
that I can live.
Gu Chen.
How come you were so sure
that you could find me
in those dreams?
Because I believe
that no matter how many times we meet,
we will fall in love with each other.
Be it reality or a dream,
you're a constant like the North Star.
Wherever you are,
you are the eternal light
in my life
that guides me to you
through the mist.
Beixing.
I love you.
I love you too.
Are you ready?
We can't let Beixing find out.
You can count on us.
Are you sure?
Just the two of you?
Qian.
Yes?
The three of you
have been hanging out a lot lately.
We... No.
We ran into each other by chance.
Is Gu Chen cheating on me?
Mmm.
No.
Impossible.
Beixing, you're reading too much into it.
Mo?
I'm here.
Coming.
Don't rush me.
I'm here.
What is going on?
Are you hiding something from me?
No way.
Hahaha.
Lin Mo is looking for me.
Look.
I have to go now.
Hey!
Tch.
Qian, Lin Mo, and I
studied the images
in your brain for a long time
before we made this Flutterheart Ring.
♪I thought I hid it well, but my longing overflows♪
♪You're always filled with joy♪
Zhen Beixing.
Do you
want to marry me?
I do.
Yay!
Great!
So sweet.
- Woah! - Ah!
Haha.
♪That is my answer to you♪
♪Even if we're thousands of miles apart, my love will not waver♪
♪Your smile creates ripples in my heart, as if you're saying "I do"♪
To all my esteemed guests,
ladies, and gentlemen,
welcome.
Today
is the wedding between Mr. Gu Chen and Ms. Zhen Beixing.
We shall bear witness
to the romantic wedding between them.
They shall promise their lives
to each other.
Let's give the bride and the groom
our sincerest blessings.
- Yes! - Yay!
Congratulations.
They look good together.
Mr. Gu Chen,
in all the days of your life,
will you love Ms. Zhen Beixing
and care for her till the end of time,
in sickness and in health,
in good times
and in bad?
I will.
Ms. Zhen Beixing,
in all the days of your life,
will you love Mr. Gu Chen
and care for him till the end of time,
in sickness and in health,
in good times
and in bad?
I will.
- Wow. - Wow!
Please exchange rings.
♪Counting the many romantic scenes we share with you♪
♪I keep everything you love and adore in my mind♪
♪Love feels like magic, its endless warmth wraps around you♪
May you spend the rest
of your lives together!
The single ladies may now come to the stage.
Let's see
who the next bride will be!
- Me! Me! - Me! Me!
- I'll grab it. - One, two, three.
Ah!
Mo, I caught it!
Well done, Qian.
Do you want another gift?
Huh?
- Wow! - Woah.
Oh my god!
Qian.
Marry me.
- Marry him. - Marry him.
Yes.
Gu Chen, where are you?
♪The hazy streets rewind, bidding farewell to every heartbroken visitor♪
♪Parting flowers wither and fall, their lingering fragrance fades away♪
♪Your figure is swallowed by the crowd, as if you never stood by my side♪
♪The once moving vows vanish with the passing of time, who remembers them?♪
♪It's hard to define what I've truly possessed until now♪
♪Was it you or just memories? Snow melts, winter passes♪
♪Everything is like our fleeting encounter, how can one let it go?♪
♪It's hard to define what I've truly possessed until now♪
♪Was it love or regret? Amid the river of time and sea of people♪
♪You and I embrace only for a moment before we part unwillingly♪