♪Counting the many romantic scenes we share with you♪
♪I keep everything you love and adore in my mind♪
♪Love feels like magic, its endless warmth wraps around you♪
♪And all my devotion. When the stars light up the sky♪
♪That is my answer to you♪
♪Even if we're thousands of miles apart, my love will not waver♪
♪Your smile creates ripples in my heart, as if you're saying "I do"♪
♪My thoughts stretch on without end, deep beyond measure♪
♪My love makes no sound, hidden quietly within your gaze♪
♪If we ever meet again, I'll hold you tight with all my strength♪
♪I'll run straight toward you, landing softly in your dreams♪
♪And take you to witness the splendor of love♪
[This Is the Feeling of Love]
[Adapted from "This Is the Feeling of Love" commissioned by Migu Reading]
[Author: Lucky Apple Wealthy Pineapple]
[Episode 7]
Zhen Cheng, according to the rules,
we are supposed to take turns keeping the Flutterheart Ring.
I know Dad has given the ring to you.
Why not give me back what I deserve right now?
Also, about my removal from the office.
I don't get it.
You are my older brother.
Why are you always siding with the others?
Zhen Quan.
You have embezzled a lot of money from the company.
I can cover the tracks for you,
but I cannot allow you to use inferior materials
that might put someone's life in danger.
You should resign now
before things get out of control.
Seriously, Zhen Cheng?
I merely took some money.
You have lost your mind to old age.
Stop me again
and I might stop treating you as my brother
and kill you.
- Hmph. - You...
Come in.
And these
are ledgers indicating Zhen Quan's embezzlement in recent years.
Does this mean
Uncle Zhen Quan killed my father?
And why does he want the Flutterheart Ring?
To fill the monetary shortfall
or is it for another nefarious plan?
This key evidence
shows that Zhen Quan has an ulterior motive.
But it isn't enough
to prove his intention to kill.
We need something more direct.
What should we do now?
We can't just let him do what he wants.
We can use the video
and the ledgers
as our bargaining chip
to pressure him into slipping up.
I'll make the necessary arrangements
to make sure that nothing goes wrong.
Beixing, rest up now
for the upcoming storm.
I trust you.
No matter what,
I won't let my dad die for nothing.
I've examined all ledgers.
Zhen Quan has transferred all his money to an offshore account.
The evidence is irrefutable.
These ledgers and footage should be enough
to make Zhen Quan slip up.
But we need him to do that
in public.
So you plan to...
I plan to
meet him
with the evidence.
He will panic,
and then, he will make mistakes.
Why don't we call the police?
Police can't do much without
incriminating evidence.
The board members will back him up too.
You're taking
a huge risk for Zhen Beixing.
She's my only lead
to my past memories.
- I have to... - Don't get carried away.
Love is a double-edged sword.
What if she isn't the person you seek?
I don't know.
But I won't forgive myself
if she gets hurt.
The conversation between Zhen Cheng and that person was interrupted.
Why is that?
It says here that there was a power cut.
I'm seeing Zhen Quan tomorrow.
Let's make sure everything is in order.
Every piece of remote equipment is already in place,
and they are ready for activation during crucial moments.
Tomorrow is the day.
Beixing cannot be in danger anymore.
Oh.
Keep an eye out for Beixing.
Zhen Quan might harm her again.
Ma Tianming's car crash is not an accident.
If Zhen Quan did kill Zhen Cheng,
he wouldn't spare Beixing either.
Okay.
I will keep an eye on them at all times.
Lin Mo invented this.
It contains a global communication and positioning chip.
I made a few tweaks
so that it's connected to my watch.
You can call me
whenever
and wherever.
It's no problem at all.
Okay.
I'm seeing Zhen Quan tomorrow.
Let's make sure everything is in order.
Tomorrow is the day.
Beixing cannot be in danger anymore.
Dad,
I cannot wait for someone else take the risk for me.
It is what I must do.
I will face Zhen Quan in person.
Uncle Zhen Quan,
let's talk.
Beixing.
What brought you here so early in the morning?
Seriously, Zhen Cheng?
I merely took some money.
You have lost your mind to old age.
Stop me again
and I might stop treating you as my brother
and kill you.
What is the meaning of this?
I hope you can surrender yourself to the police.
Otherwise, I'll take immediate action.
You really are very naive.
You think this is enough to blackmail me?
I was arguing with your dad.
And people say all sorts of things in the heat of the moment.
This doesn't prove anything.
Uncle Zhen Quan,
come clean as to whether you asked someone
to call my dad and cause that fatal accident.
These ledgers prove that you committed embezzlement.
If you don't turn yourself in,
I will hand them to the police.
Beixing.
I know who was behind it.
But why must I tell you?
You should work with me
and hand over the Flutterheart Ring
and the shares.
And maybe, I'll tell you the truth before you die.
Do you know how much trouble you're in?
You might not be able to leave this building alive.
If I'm ready to be here, I'm ready for anything.
I want everyone to know the truth.
I can't let my dad die for nothing.
You have one day to turn yourself in, Uncle Zhen Quan.
And don't go thinking that I don't have extra copies.
If I don't leave this place alive,
the evidence will be given to the police immediately.
Follow Zhen Beixing.
Kidnap her after half an hour.
Destroy any evidence you find.
Oh, no, Gu Chen.
Zhen Beixing went to meet Zhen Quan.
Zhen Quan just ordered to have her kidnapped.
What? Where are they?
I'm trying to locate Zhen Beixing
through her watch signal.
I don't see anything here.
Stop talking and start searching.
- Found anything? - No.
It's all useless stuff.
Boss.
We found nothing.
Keep on searching.
Leave no stone unturned.
Yes. Let's continue.
She's in a remote area near the beach.
Zhen Beixing, where are you?
Zhen Beixing? This is bad.
She is in danger. I must go to her.
Update me about her location at any time.
Okay.
This is your final warning.
Hand over the documents in the USB drive.
No.
You won't have those documents.
Beixing, hand over the ledgers
and you will still be my beloved niece.
I won't let you have them.
I see. In that case,
you shall be reunited with Zhen Cheng.
So you did kill my father!
So what?
You will see him soon.
You're digging your own grave.
Hang in there, Zhen Beixing.
I'm almost there.
Goodbye, Gu Chen.
Please, doctor. Save her.
Sorry. We've done everything we could.
♪The hazy streets rewind, bidding farewell to every heartbroken visitor♪
♪Parting flowers wither and fall, their lingering fragrance fades away♪
♪Your figure is swallowed by the crowd, as if you never stood by my side♪
♪The once moving vows vanish with the passing of time, who remembers them?♪
♪It's hard to define what I've truly possessed until now♪
♪Was it you or just memories? Snow melts, winter passes♪
♪Everything is like our fleeting encounter, how can one let it go?♪
♪It's hard to define what I've truly possessed until now♪
♪Was it love or regret? Amid the river of time and sea of people♪
♪You and I embrace only for a moment before we part unwillingly♪