♪Counting the many romantic scenes we share with you♪
♪I keep everything you love and adore in my mind♪
♪Love feels like magic, its endless warmth wraps around you♪
♪And all my devotion. When the stars light up the sky♪
♪That is my answer to you♪
♪Even if we're thousands of miles apart, my love will not waver♪
♪Your smile creates ripples in my heart, as if you're saying "I do"♪
♪My thoughts stretch on without end, deep beyond measure♪
♪My love makes no sound, hidden quietly within your gaze♪
♪If we ever meet again, I'll hold you tight with all my strength♪
♪I'll run straight toward you, landing softly in your dreams♪
♪And take you to witness the splendor of love♪
[This Is the Feeling of Love]
[Adapted from "This Is the Feeling of Love" commissioned by Migu Reading]
[Author: Lucky Apple Wealthy Pineapple]
[Episode 13]
Beixing.
Allow me to present someone.
Come here.
This is the buddy I mention often
to you.
Genius IT specialist.
Lin Mo.
Hi, Lin Mo.
Hi, Beixing.
Thank you so much.
Thanks to you,
the negative articles all disappeared.
It's just a piece of cake.
While the scandal is over,
there is something odd about it still.
Tian Yu and I have been photographed together before.
But it has never snowballed
like it did this time.
It's as if someone
is trying to blow it out of proportion.
Am I reading too much into it?
I have implemented online surveillance.
We will track IP addresses that post inflammatory articles.
That way, they won't
be able to hurt you again.
Beixing, whoever the perpetrator is,
we won't let them win.
Hmm?
So many people out of the sudden.
What now?
There she is.
She's the evil woman.
Shameless!
Evil woman! Cheater!
- Home wrecker. - Home wrecker.
Liar!
Shameless!
- You seduced Tian Yu! - Liar!
How could you do this?
- Shameless woman! - Evil woman!
- There she is. - She's here.
Beat that shameless woman to death!
- Home wrecker. - Beat her up!
Shameless!
- Evil woman. - Leave Tian Yu alone!
Evil woman! How dare you take Tian Yu away from us!
Ms. Zhen, your coffee is here.
Thank you.
Wait.
Who ordered the coffee?
I don't know.
I'm just in charge of the delivery.
Don't drink this coffee.
Let me get you a glass of water.
Gu Chen is always by her side
when we act.
We can't find any opening.
- Right. - Exactly.
Only when she's away
from Gu Chen
that we can succeed.
How to lure him away then?
Gu Chen is with her 24/7 now.
I have an idea.
What is it?
Listen.
Right?
Zhen Quan isn't the murderer.
If you want the truth,
come to the rooftop alone within 10 minutes.
This could be the key
that unlocks the mystery surrounding my father's death.
They are members of the fan club?
Yes.
Most of them are students,
mobilized via online communication.
Their plan
is systematic and organized.
Keep an eye on them at all times.
If anyone approaches Beixing,
let me know.
There is one suspicious IP address.
Which one?
It always appears within the Zhen Group office building.
She could be one of the employees.
Who could she be?
She's still inside the office building.
Hello, the person you call...
Lin Mo.
Locate Beixing for me.
Zhen Beixing and the owner of the IP address
are on the rooftop.
Rooftop?
Be careful!
Stay still.
One wrong move
and you might fall.
You're the one who texted me.
Yes.
But also no.
All you need to know
is that many people want you hurt.
Even if I didn't do this today,
someone else would have done it.
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want you gone forever.
You are engaged to your fiance.
You're not worthy of Tian Yu's company.
You're not worthy of what Tian Yu has done for you.
You are
Vivian.
You figured it out very quickly.
In this case,
I don't need to hide myself anymore.
Vivian.
I've been nothing but kind to you.
You...
You like Tian Yu?
Tian Yu is perfect.
If not, just a bit too kind sometimes.
He failed to see
your true face.
I won't let anyone hurt him.
But
what you see
isn't necessarily the truth.
If what I see isn't the truth,
what is the truth then?
An infidel woman like you
must have lied to Tian Yu.
Ah!
Stop!
See?
Mr. Gu sure loves you a lot.
He rushed to rescue you.
Don't come any closer.
Take one step further
and I'll push her.
Okay, I'll stay here.
Calm down.
Do you think Tian Yu will fall in love with you
once I'm gone?
You broke his heart.
So you shall die.
But you can't even break his heart.
You're just a stranger to him.
A creepy stalker.
I'm sure you have your friends and family.
I'm sure you parents put in a lot of effort
to raise you.
I'm sure they want you
to have a happy life,
don't they?
If you hurt me today,
Tian Yu will regard you as a criminal.
Do you want to sacrifice the rest of your life
for a celebrity who won't even bat you an eye?
What about those who love you?
- Stop talking! - Ah!
Beixing!
Ah!
Consider yourself lucky that Beixing is safe.
Wait.
I wish to speak to her.
Tian Yu.
I'm doing this for you.
You are not me.
You are not responsible for my life.
And I don't need anyone to save me.
No one can make a decision for me.
Love cannot be an excuse to hurt someone else.
Even less so to commit a crime.
No matter what you do,
I will never choose you.
Let go of your obsession.
Tian Yu.
If possible,
I want Beixing to be mine solely.
But will she accept me
once she sees the real me?
It's not that serious.
The wound I get from scaling
my high school dormitory wall
was worse than this.
Gu Chen.
What's the matter?
I'm fine.
Zhen Beixing.
Why did you meet Vivian alone?
Don't you know that was dangerous?
You never listen to me.
I didn't know she would do something crazy.
I just wanted to handle it myself.
I didn't know it'd turn out like this.
Why must you face danger alone?
Zhen Beixing, I want to protect you.
Can you stop getting hurt,
please?
Gu Chen.
Why do you care so much about me?
Because I'm in love with you.
Beixing, seeing you injured
pains me.
Not only do I want to protect you,
I want to be someone you can rely on.
No matter what happens,
I'll be there for you.
I like you a lot.
Let's date.
For real.
Zhen Beixing.
Would you date me?
Yes.
♪The hazy streets rewind, bidding farewell to every heartbroken visitor♪
♪Parting flowers wither and fall, their lingering fragrance fades away♪
♪Your figure is swallowed by the crowd, as if you never stood by my side♪
♪The once moving vows vanish with the passing of time, who remembers them?♪
♪It's hard to define what I've truly possessed until now♪
♪Was it you or just memories? Snow melts, winter passes♪
♪Everything is like our fleeting encounter, how can one let it go?♪
♪It's hard to define what I've truly possessed until now♪
♪Was it love or regret? Amid the river of time and sea of people♪
♪You and I embrace only for a moment before we part unwillingly♪