[Phoenix's Gambit: Love or Crown]
[Episode 7]
Let me go.
Don't go and get yourself killed.
Brother!
Are you lying to me?
What proof do you have?
Back then, someone who still remembers this matter
is Steward Gui, who returned home.
I can bring him back to confront you.
In my past life,
I was willful and arrogant, and made a grave mistake,
yet remained completely unaware.
In this life, Bai Xiyue clearly knows the truth
but still wants to frame Bai Xiyao.
Lianxin,
you clearly could've killed me just now,
but you saved me instead.
Lianxin,
you're not evil by nature.
Don't let yourself be used.
Come back with me.
I'll give you an explanation.
My Lady.
If you don't dare to kill her,
then I'll do it.
My Lady!
Lianxin!
No time to worry about that!
What's going on?
You have inner strength?
Are you alright?
My Lord.
He committed suicide by poison.
Quick, save her!
Bai Xiyao!
Master Yuan,
how is she?
Miss Bai was too exhausted
and fell asleep.
I, the celestial maiden,
am boundless in celestial power.
Don't even think of harming me.
It's fine.
As long as Miss Bai wakes up.
Are you alright?
Are you badly hurt?
My Lady.
I should've died
to atone for my sins.
Don't say such nonsense.
What sin have you committed?
You were just being used,
and today's assassination was her doing as well.
She never intended for either of us to return alive.
I have a carriage
and can escort Miss Bai safely back to the city.
Tao Yu.
Why did Yun Yichen suddenly appear?
It's best to keep your distance from him.
Thank you for your kindness, Prince Yi,
but we also brought a carriage from our residence.
There's no need for you to trouble himself.
Tao Yu,
why are you dazing off?
May I ask, Miss Lianxin,
where are you from?
What's your childhood name?
Do you have any older brothers?
I'm from Huangqijia Village in the outskirts of the capital.
I'm the second child in the family.
My parents called me Qiao'er.
Qiao'er...
Do you still remember how we fled into the mountains
and caught pheasants to stave off hunger?
In the end,
we only caught this one tail feather.
He's the mute boy from back then!
Brother,
is it really you?
You're still alive?
I've been alive all along.
I've been searching for you all these years.
It's been ten years.
B-Brother,
you… you can speak now?
It was the Duke.
My Lord.
He was a little beggar.
What happened to him?
Is he still alive?
Seems he still has a breath.
We found a feather
and pottery shard on him.
I'll carry him.
Don't let him slow down our journey.
Put him on the cart.
I want to save him.
This...
Okay.
You're finally awake.
You've been unconscious for seven or eight days.
Quick, get up.
Your throat problem is an old condition from childhood.
It will take time to fully recover.
What's your name?
When we found you,
you only had a pottery shard and a feather.
So we called you Tao Yu.
Tao Yu…
His Lordship cured my throat.
He was the one who saved me when I was abandoned in the wild.
My Lady.
He's my brother.
Thank you, My Lord, for saving my brother's life.
No need for formalities, Miss Lianxin.
Tao Yu,
hurry and take your sister into the city for treatment.
You'll have time to catch up later.
Yes, My Lord.
Let's return to the city quickly.
This is too exhausting.
Who would've thought the person Tao Yu saved today
was the sister he had been searching for.
Indeed.
A heartfelt reunion.
It's wonderful.
I too
have someone I wish to find.
But we've yet to meet.
Who asked you?
Don't just talk to fill the silence, okay?
Then I wish you early success in his search.
That depends on whether little Bai is willing.
Me?
I don't understand what you mean.
You lied
about the sachet.
Darling…
Xiyue, why are you here?
Xiyao.
I came to seek guidance in music from Brother Yichen,
so I can perform at the new emperor's coronation.
Why are you here?
I noticed your sachet was worn,
so I brought you a new one.
I already have a suitable sachet.
Who told you to do such a useless thing?
Xiyao,
that sachet
was one I gave to Brother Yichen when we were children.
I'm his wife now.
Aren't you
being a bit too close with Xiyue?
Xiyue and I have been close since childhood.
Besides, she's your sister.
I didn't think you'd be so jealous.
I'm truly disappointed.
Xiyue,
let's go.
Trying to prove
you're the rightful owner of the sachet with your embroidery?
Brother Yichen's favor
isn't something you can exchange with just a new sachet.
In my past life, I did lie about my identity.
But now, isn't Bai Xiyao's identity
a lie as well?
This sachet
was hand-stitched for me by little Bai.
It's exactly the same as yours.
Where did yours come from?
So there really was only one sachet given to Yun Yichen.
Who forged the second sachet
to lure Bai Xiyao to Wangxin Lake?
She just made two identical ones, that's all.
What's so strange about that?
Besides, who remembers things from childhood so clearly?
It wasn't you, so of course you don't care.
Why were you at the charity hall?
Where I go
has nothing to do with you, does it?
Thank you, thank you, My Lord.
Even if you're thanking me,
there's no need to bow so deeply.
I thank you
for saving my life, Prince Yi.
The person who tried to assassinate you today
was highly trained from planning to execution.
After failing, he committed suicide immediately
to prevent revealing his employer.
It appears
to be the work of Luozhi Hall.
Luozhi Hall?
You know of Luozhi Hall?
I heard storytellers at teahouses mention it.
Didn't expect you, a noble daughter,
to be so well-informed.
Luozhi Hall isn't just an assassination organization.
They also excel at setting traps.
In my past life,
I was the one who framed Bai Xiyao with their help.
[Yanxia Pavilion]
Welcome, miss.
Feel free to look around.
All my rouge and powder are of the finest quality.
Whatever you choose,
put it on my tab.
Thank you, My Lady.
My Lady,
I have an urgent matter to report.
Speak.
Third Prince visited Bai Xiyao last night.
How did Yun Yichen react?
Third Prince snuck into the mansion at night.
His Lordship was unaware.
A secret meeting?
What did they say?
Third Prince wanted to take the lady away,
but she refused.
Third Prince is deeply devoted to her,
saying he will never give up no matter what,
and is determined to take her away from the Duke's Mansion.
If Pei Yan had half the affection for me that he has for Bai Xiyao,
I would've already had the Empress Dowager arrange our marriage.
In the end,
as long as Bai Xiyao remains,
Pei Yan won't give his heart to me.
When do you plan to kill Bai Xiyao, My Lady?
Killing her is never the goal.
I need Bai Xiyao to be my stepping stone.
Once I step over her to reach the top,
I'll crush her completely.
Yes.
What should I do?
I've already had people from Luozhi Hall set the plan.
When the time comes,
you'll lure her to Yanxia Pavilion.
I've prepared a good show for her.
Yes.
Ever since Bai Xiyao was disfigured,
Yun Yichen has despised her.
-Madam, the food has gone cold again.
-She became a resentful woman trapped in the inner chambers.
Reheat it.
But if we reheat it again, it won't be edible.
Then make another table of dishes.
It's almost the hour of Hai now.
His Lordship has likely dined outside already.
Reporting, Madam.
His Lordship will stay at Qingzhi Pavilion tonight.
He won't be returning.
Madam,
His Lordship doesn't usually send word
when he's not returning to the mansion.
That Qingzhi Pavilion
is the courtyard the Empress Dowager granted Bai Xiyue.
Isn't that an open provocation?
Such blatant bullying.
Clear the dishes.
I'm tired.
I'll go back to rest.
But you haven't taken a bite.
I can't eat.
I've lost my appetite.
Madam,
why not visit Yanxia Pavilion tomorrow,
pick out some rouge and powder?
Go by yourself.
I'll grant you half a day off.
Madam,
I heard they've just received a new batch of pearl cream.
Apply it to your face,
it smooths out wrinkles remarkably well.
Why don't you give it a try?
Maybe then His Lordship won't go out anymore.
Why would that work?
It's just a marketing gimmick.
Madam,
you're idle all day anyway,
why not come with me,
just to pass the time?
[Yanxia Pavilion]
Madam's beauty is remarkable,
yet flawed like jade with a blemish.
The heavens must be jealous of such a face.
Rest assured,
with my pearl cream,
you'll surely be reborn.
Truly?
Our Si family's craft spans a hundred years.
You'll know with one try.
Lianxin,
go pick what you like.
Yes, My Lady.
Madam, look at this.
The scars are indeed less visible.
Only…
If we had treated it properly back then,
Madam's face
wouldn't have ended up like this.
I've added centella asiatica to this pearl cream.
As long as you keep using it,
the scars will surely fade.
Then wrap all of these up.
Very well.
Please continue browsing.
Lianxin,
have you picked?
Madam,
I still need to fetch a lip balm.
Miss,
I'm terribly sorry.
I was in a rush.
I'll pay for whatever was damaged.
You seem like
a scholarly gentleman.
Why would you come to
a makeup shop full of women?
Lianxin, don't be rude.
You were the one who rushed
and bumped into the gentleman.
I sell calligraphy and paintings,
saving up some silver
to buy a birthday gift for my mother.
Truly a filial son.
Miss, may I ask,
which family are you from?
That dress hem won't be easy to clean.
I, sunamed Zhao, will surely send silver
to your residence.
I'm no noble lady.
I'm a maidservant of the Duke of Zhen's Mansion.
My name is Lianxin.
Greetings, Madam.