SIX SINGLES UNDER ONE ROOF
This feels like a birthday party.
Yeah, I get what you mean.
- Back in school...
- A class rep's party?
- Yeah.
- A rich kid's party.
So what are we doing tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
- I'm just not sure.
- What should we do?
- It's tricky.
- Totally.
I have one suggestion, though.
Let's stay at home if possible.
To make the most of our time here?
- Yes, exactly.
- Goodness.
- Seriously...
- Let's try to stay home.
- Something along that line?
- Yeah.
THEY DECIDED TO STAY HOME TOMORROW
THINKS IT OVER
If we're not leaving the house
- everything has to happen here.
- Exactly.
That's what I want. It's just...
WHAT IS HE PLANNING THIS TIME?
WHAT SHOULD I COOK TOMORROW?
MASTER PARTY PLANNER'S EXPLOITS
1. GIANT OCTOPUS
2. CONVEYOR BELT SUSHI AT HOME
AP'S OUT-OF-THE-BOX IDEAS
ARE ON ANOTHER LEVEL
ALWAYS CONSIDERING
OPTIONS FOR A BIG FEAST
WHAT IS HE PLANNING NOW?
I think you can rest up now.
The sushi train was enough.
THANKS
She's right.
WE'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOUR EVENTS
DEEP IN THOUGHT
How's this?
Why don't we each invite
a best friend home?
We're inviting a friend here?
When I told my friends
about this show
so many of them wanted to know
about the people I'd be staying with
and what we'd be doing together.
- It is a place worth showing off.
- You're right.
I want to take them around the place.
If you guys are up for it
- I'd like to invite people over.
- I'm in.
It's a chance for us to get to know
each other's close friends.
That's a nice bonus.
I'm in, too.
LET'S EXPAND OUR SOCIAL CIRCLE
Can you think of anyone to invite?
AT THIS HOUR
AND AT OUR AGE?
- Let's see.
- I'll need to check.
Let's do that.
WHO WOULD BE AVAILABLE?
- No one comes to mind this instant.
- Everyone is welcome.
If we were still in our 20s
we would have no trouble
inviting friends over.
I could call anyone at this hour
and still get a yes back in the day.
Yes, but we've aged over the years.
Many have families of their own
- So true.
- and work to manage as well.
It feels like my social circle
is shrinking little by little.
Totally.
Your social circle may shrink,
but the friendship deepens.
- It sure does.
- Totally.
Every friend means so much to you.
THAT'S TRUE
Friends...
But...
WHO SHOULD I CALL?
DAZED
WE'D GET A FEW GUESTS, RIGHT?
- We'll need to contact our friends.
- Yeah.
- Not everyone might be available.
- Exactly.
You think so?
Should I try contacting them?
Who should I invite?
Let me check who I can call.
RUSHING TO CONTACT THEIR BESTIES
HIS FINGERS ARE BUSY
GOING THROUGH HIS CONTACT LIST
- You've got so many friends.
- Well, yeah.
- That's easily over 400.
- How many friends does he have?
I'm not sure who might be available.
EVERYONE IS SERIOUS
ABOUT LAST-MINUTE INVITES
The friend I have in mind
is a woman.
INTEREST PIQUED
Really?
She looks like a cat.
Seriously?
He suddenly went, "Seriously?"
Their looks changed
with anticipation.
- Really?
- You like girls who look like cats?
- I do.
- She looks like a cat.
My friend loves Keun-suk.
SLIGHT SMILE
You're just messing with me again
with false hope.
No, it's not like that at all.
What's going on?
SECOND-HAND DOPAMINE RUSH
She wanted to get to know him better.
It's rare to find someone like that.
- Who can it be?
- She did say that.
WHO IS THIS CAT-LIKE GIRL
WHO LIKES KEUN-SUK?
DEEP IN THOUGHT
- I have two candidates.
- Tell us about them.
- Two people?
- Yes, I have two candidates.
One is a non-celebrity
and the other is an actor.
- An actor?
- Yeah.
THE GIRLS ARE INTRIGUED THIS TIME
- My friend's a superstar.
- Who can it be?
What's more
he's handsome.
UNABLE TO SUPPRESS A SMILE
Is he like an A-lister?
- He's an absolute A-lister.
- Really?
A FELLOW SAME-AGE TOP STAR
Is he available?
It won't hurt to ask.
- Yes, ask him.
- I'll do that.
I'll ask if he's available.
Who can it be?
There's someone who comes to mind.
- Who is it?
Well...
He's practically my mini-me.
- You?
- Your mini-me?
He's my favorite mini-me.
ANOTHER PRINCE IS MENTIONED
- I have someone who comes to mind.
- Who can it be?
It's someone in the elite class.
- Highly intelligent.
- Really?
This should be fun.
It's really last-minute.
I'd appreciate anyone who can come.
Yeah, and if we could all be friends
- it'd be so nice.
- Totally.
IT WOULD BE NICE
IF WE ALL BECAME FRIENDS
What if we throw a party
but no one shows up,
and it's just the six of us again?
- Just cricket sounds.
- Yeah.
Cricket sounds like in animations.
A small party can be nice,
rather than a wild one.
- Tomorrow should be fun, right?
- You bet.
Let's have a meaningful day.
EXCITED
WHO WILL END UP COMING?
What if no one shows up tomorrow?
That'd make it funny.
- What?
- That's fun in its own way.
NO ONE GETS ANY SLEEP
OUT OF ANXIETY AND EXCITEMENT
EVERYONE IS BUSY
SENDING OUT INVITATIONS
DESPERATELY HOPING
AT LEAST SOME WILL BE AVAILABLE
THE NIGHT OF ANTICIPATION ENDS
WHO WILL VISIT THE HOUSEMATES TODAY?
THE 2ND-FLOOR HOUSEMATES
ARE STILL IN DREAMLAND
CURLED UP
THEY NOW SLEEP IN THE SAME POSITION
THE 1ST-FLOOR HOUSEMATES
ARE ALSO STILL IN DREAMLAND
SHIFTS
DO-YEON RISES EARLY
DESPITE NOT HAVING WORK TODAY
AS PER HER MORNING ROUTINE
SHE'S PICKING UP HER PHONE?
SHE USUALLY READS IN THE MORNING
WHY IS SHE CHECKING HER PHONE TODAY?
AS SOON AS SHE'S DONE
SHE GETS OUT OF THE BED
THIS INTROVERT USUALLY STAYS IN BED
FOR 2 HOURS TO AVOID HER HOUSEMATES
SNEAKS OUT
WHY IS SHE LEAVING HER BEDROOM
RIGHT AFTER WAKING UP?
SHE'S HEADING STRAIGHT TO THE KITCHEN
BUT DO-YEON IS HARDLY A GOOD COOK
WHAT BRINGS HER HERE?
OPENS THE FRIDGE
SHE STARTS TAKING OUT INGREDIENTS
WHAT HAS GOTTEN INTO
GUGI-DONG'S NEWBIE COOK?
Since it is our last day together
I wanted to cook for my housemates
as a little present.
She's clueless about cooking.
DAY 1
- I got a cut, too.
- Where?
NEWBIE COOK IS BANNED
FROM THE KITCHEN AFTER THE INCIDENT
DO-YEON HAS FELT BAD
FOR NOT HELPING OUT
My housemates put so much effort
into preparing delicious meals.
I wanted to do something in return.
I was worried they might come
while I was still cooking.
They could finish
everything in a flash.
That would defeat the whole purpose.
That's why I was worried.
It was a breakfast buffet theme
inspired by a hotel or B&amp;B.
SO NERVOUS
THIS 14-YEAR DELIVERY FAN
RARELY PREPARES BREAKFAST FOR HERSELF
CAN THIS NEWBIE COOK
PREPARE BREAKFAST FOR 6 PEOPLE?
CURRENT TIME
HOW LONG WILL IT TAKE?
FIRST DISH
ORANGES, A STAPLE IN BREAKFAST BUFFET
IT IS ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE TO RUIN THIS
ALL YOU NEED TO DO IS CUT THEM UP
STARTS WASHING THE ORANGES
ONE AT A TIME
SLOWLY
AND LEISURELY
SHE TAKES TIME AND EFFORT
TO WASH THE ORANGES
SHE IS IN NO WAY IN A RUSH
WAIT, AM I DOING THIS RIGHT?
I don't think this is how it looked.
Do I keep the top part?
WHEN WILL SHE EVER GET IT DONE?
Darn it.
I should've kept the top.
What do I do?
WHY ARE THE STICKERS STILL ON?
Darn it.
HOW IS SHE NOT NOTICING THEM?
I have to hide these.
All done.
THINGS DON'T LOOK GOOD
FOR NEWBIE COOK'S BREAKFAST BUFFET
Can you believe it?
LOUD CLATTER
SHIFTS
WILL SHE BE ABLE TO GET READY
BEFORE EVERYONE GETS UP?
Do I cut this part?
ANOTHER BUFFET STAPLE, BANANAS
I hope so.
SOMEWHAT BOLDER
I think they cut them like this.
PILED UP
A MOUND OF BANANAS
WHY DOES IT LOOK FAMILIAR?
I wasn't going for a zoo vibe.
I started preparing raw food first.
THIS ISN'T FOOD FOR ORANGUTANS
DECIDING WHAT HUMAN FOOD TO MAKE NEXT
Caprese...
HER NEXT PROJECT IS CAPRESE,
A CLASSY BREAKFAST DISH
30 MINUTES HAVE PASSED ALREADY
Is it this way or like this?
FIRST TIME MAKING CAPRESE
IN FORTY YEARS
ONE CUT
ONE PHOTO CHECK
The key is getting thin slices.
A QUICK CHECK AFTER EVERY SLICE
SPEND 10 MINUTES CUTTING THE TOMATOES
TIME TO ARRANGE
CHEESE AND TOMATO SLICES
Cheese should be at the end.
THIS PROCESS
ALSO TAKES AGES
CAN SHE REALLY MAKE A BUFFET FOR 6?
Why does it look so off?
SOMETHING IS MISSING
WHAT'S THE MISSING ELEMENT?
RIGHT INTO SEARCH MODE
I got everything... Wait.
BASIL LEAVES
BUT
Basil.
SHE FORGOT TO ORDER BASIL
CAN I USE ANY OTHER VEGETABLE?
DO-YEON'S SUBSTITUTE CHOICE
A BAG OF SPINACH?
ONLY A NEWBIE COOK
WOULD MAKE SUCH A CHOICE
CAN I EAT RAW SPINACH, THOUGH?
IS IT SAFE TO EAT RAW SPINACH?
A LARGE QUANTITY OF SPINACH
MAY INCREASE KIDNEY STONE RISKS
GUESS THE ANSWER IS NO
SPINACH IS OUT
OTHER VEGETABLE TO THE RESCUE
CONCERNED ABOUT PRESENTATION
DESPITE THE TIGHT SCHEDULE
A SOMEWHAT GREEN CAPRESE
Maybe I shouldn't cut these.
ALL IT NEEDS NOW
IS THE BALSAMIC GLAZE
It's surprisingly easy to make.
BIG SPLASH
A SEA OF BALSAMIC GLAZE
That's too much.
I added too much, didn't I?
WHO KNEW YOU COULD RUIN CAPRESE?
I can pour some out.
That should do it.
QUICK DAMAGE CONTROL
BARELY MADE IT
Is this right?
50 MINUTES HAVE PASSED ALREADY
THE COMPLETED DISHES SO FAR
It's giving Midnight Diner vibe.
THIS DISH WILL FINALLY INVOLVE FIRE
OCTOPUS-SHAPED SAUSAGES
THIS HOTEL'S BUFFET PRIORITIZES
PRESENTABILITY OVER SPEED
ALMOST MISSES
IT TAKES 15 MINUTES TO CUT THEM
It's so cute.
IT TAKES 15 MINUTES TO GRILL THEM
FINALLY READY AFTER 30 MINUTES
IT'S NOT DONE YET
CAUTIOUS
Shoot.
I meant to draw eyes with ketchup.
TWO EYES ON EACH OCTOPUS?
WITH A LOT OF CARE AND EFFORT
SHE IS PLANTING THEM EYES
Oh, no.
THIS MIGHT BECOME A LUNCH BUFFET
1 HOUR AND 30 MINUTES HAVE PASSED
HER GOAL WAS OCTOPUS
BUT THEY LOOK LIKE GHOSTS
SHEDDING BLOODY TEARS
Let's try making a rolled omelet.
If I fail, I'll make scrambled eggs.
FIRST ROLLED OMELET IN 40 YEARS
Is it 9:30 a.m. already?
THE HOUSEMATES WILL BE UP SOON
COOK A ROLLED OMELET
BEFORE EVERYONE GETS UP
SCRAMBLING
WHERE IS THE SPATULA?
A RICE PADDLE
TO MAKE A ROLLED OMELET?
This won't work.
THINGS ALWAYS GO MISSING
WHEN YOU NEED THEM THE MOST
NEW TOOL OBTAINED
ACTUALLY, THAT'S ALSO A RICE PADDLE
Can't I salvage this somehow?
THE TASTE IS THE KEY, NOT THE LOOKS
QUICKLY ADDS MORE BEATEN EGG
AND PREPARES TO ROLL IT
DETERMINEDLY HOLDS
A SPATULA IN EACH HAND
It worked.
MADE IT TO THE HALF-WAY MARK
I think I did it.
I just need to flip it one more time.
A BIT TOO WIDE, BUT IT'S FINE
SUCCESS
CONGRATS ON YOUR FIRST ROLLED OMELET
I should be on C***nary Class Wars.
GUGI-DONG'S WHITE SPOON CHEF
I'm jazzed.
SO THIS IS THE JOY IN COOKING
This is wild. I did an amazing job.
My goodness.
MAKING IT PRESENTABLE
FOR THE HOUSEMATES' SAKE
My gosh.
What should I write?
A heart feels too corny.
A MESSAGE DECORATION
DESPITE THE TIGHT SCHEDULE
HYPER-FOCUSED MS. LONG-LEGS
FRIENDSHIP
I live for corny stuff.
LITTLE HEART DECORATION
Gosh, it's so corny.
A LOT OF HEART AND TIME WENT INTO IT
This is great.
PROUD
How exciting.
RUSHES OVER TO SET THE TABLE
BEFORE ANYONE WAKES UP
WHY IS DO-YEON IN THE KITCHEN?
KEUN-SUK WOKE UP ALREADY?
SWALLOWS HARD
Can you go back upstairs for a bit?
OBEDIENT
DO-YEON IS COOKING?
IS THIS A DREAM OR REAL LIFE?
SOMEHOW ANXIOUS
This too will pass.
PLEASE...
AFTER RUNNING INTO ONE HOUSEMATE
DO-YEON FEELS THE HEAT!
2 HOURS HAVE PASSED ALREADY
I need to hurry.
They'll all be up soon.
FOR A SUCCESSFUL SURPRISE EVENT,
SPEED IS A MUST!
AM I DREAMING?
WHY IS DO-YEON IN THE KITCHEN?
Do-yeon.
FREEZES
THERE GOES THE SURPRISE EVENT
DO YOU WANT ME TO LEAVE?
YES, PLEASE
CONCERNED, BUT RETREATS AS REQUESTED
THE OTHER THREE ARE STILL ASLEEP
SHE MUST WRAP THIS UP
BEFORE THEY GET UP
Thank goodness.
IN A RUSH
What are you up to?
THIRD PERSON TO WAKE UP
- No!
- What?
- What? I didn't see anything.
- Get back.
Can I get some water?
Pass me your cup.
- What's going on?
- Keep your eyes closed.
- Don't look.
- I didn't see anything.
Go upstairs with your eyes covered.
- Join me when I ask you to.
- Okay.
I didn't see anything.
Cover your eyes and your nostrils.
By the table, in the second drawer...
- On the right side
- Yes.
- there are some eye drops.
- Eye drops?
Eye drops and stick packs.
I didn't see anything.
RUNNING ERRANDS TO KEEP THE SECRET
- Thanks, Do-yeon.
- Go upstairs. I'll call you later.
Okay.
She was cooking something.
EVERYONE IS WORRIED
What do I do?
CHEF IS GETTING ANXIOUS
RUSHES TO COOK HASH BROWNS
BACON
AND SAUSAGES
DO-YEON'S HOTEL BUFFET
IS SOMEHOW COMING ALONG NICELY
My gosh.
RUSHES TO FINISH EVERYTHING
BEFORE EVERYONE WAKES UP
THE BREAKFAST BUFFET
IS FINALLY READY AFTER 2.5 HOURS
I should go wake them up.
IT'S TIME TO BRING EVERYONE OVER
SCURRIES
Da-hee.
Come have breakfast.
IT'S HER FIRST TIME WAKING SOMEONE UP
AFTER PREPARING BREAKFAST FOR THEM
EXCITED ENOUGH
TO CLIMB 2 STAIRS AT ONCE
OUT IN THE TERRACE
COME ALONG
What was that?
- Come and eat.
- Eat?
- I'm hungry.
- That's insane.
- Eat?
NICE ENOUGH TO FEIGN SURPRISE
For real?
Well, it's just breakfast.
SLIGHTLY EMBARRASSED
BY THEIR REACTION
- Come have breakfast, Daniel.
- Okay.
- See you downstairs.
- All right.
DID DO-YEON PREPARE BREAKFAST?
AM I STILL DREAMING?
ANXIETY DRIVES HER TO HURRY OVER
DESPITE DA-HEE'S CONCERN
QUITE A FEAST AWAITS HER
ROUGH AROUND THE EDGES
BUT FILLED WITH GENUINE AFFECTION
Isn't this the best dish
Do-yeon can make on her own?
THE FIRST BREAKFAST DO-YEON MADE
FOR SOMEONE ELSE
I can't believe this.
TOUCHED
GIGGLES
NEWBIE COOK IS EMBARRASSED
Join us for breakfast, Soo-jin.
It's so hot.
Hold on.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
Do-yeon.
This is embarrassing.
AM I STILL SLEEPING?
EVERYONE GATHERS ONE BY ONE
There are also flowers.
What on earth?
I PREPARED EVERYTHING
- Daniel.
- What's going on?
YOU PREPARED ALL THIS?
This is incredible.
MOVED BY DO-YEON'S COOKING ON HER OWN
- Daniel.
- Just incredible.
- My gosh.
- It feels like I'm abroad.
It's giving hotel buffet vibes.
Just a reminder.
My inspo was a breakfast buffet
so I'm wrapping up at 10:30 a.m.
- I'd better eat quickly.
- We have ten minutes.
Just ten minutes.
That's when it ends.
I've been at this since 7:30 a.m.
MIGHT BE HARD TO UNDERSTAND,
BUT IT TOOK FOREVER
You've started preparing at 7:30 a.m.
When did things come along?
- Just now at 10 a.m.?
- At 10 a.m.
I see.
The owner gets the final call, right?
Sorry.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU WENT THROUGH A LOT
- That's good.
- Are you sure?
Since you prefer it mild...
- That's right.
- You know what?
Goodness.
Look at what she's doing
to avoid cutting the ketchup letters.
IT'S TOO PRECIOUS TO CUT
Do-yeon.
WAS I TOO OBVIOUS?
You guys are free to cut them up.
Thanks, Do-yeon.
- No problem.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you, Do-yeon.
- No worries. Please enjoy.
- Thanks.
- You're the best.
I HOPE THEY ENJOY EVERYTHING
I should start with this.
I WANT THE CAPRESE FIRST
CURIOUS ABOUT HER REACTION
It's nice having a mini buffet.
This is so good.
Delicious.
HER FIRST COMPLIMENT ON HER COOKING
It's delicious. This is so nice.
A BIG BITE
- It's ketchup.
- I drew eyes on them.
They have ketchup eyes?
Their eyes are drawn with ketchup.
- Does this one have it?
- My gosh.
- It's so cute.
- It probably took time cutting them.
DO-YEON'S FIRST-EVER BUFFET
WON EVERYONE OVER
It's delicious.
I mean it.
It was nothing.
It's store-bought at best.
You've made my day.
- Are our friends coming later?
- How did it go?
My friend is in.
- Really?
- My friend is in.
Want to ask our friends
to do that physical age test?
I gave it some thought
on what we can do last night.
Why don't we hold a sports day?
The weather is perfect for it.
OUT OF THE BLUE?
What would we do?
To be honest
I don't have any memory
of attending one back in school.
I've always wanted to try, though.
AS A CHILD ACTOR,
KEUN-SUK HAD TO MISS SPORTS DAYS
We could split into two teams
and have a competition.
Sounds good.
We'd have a mini sports day
- with our friends.
- All right.
- Let's do it.
- Sounds good to me.
- Sure, sounds like fun.
- What comes to mind...
What comes to your mind
when you think about sports day?
- How about flags of all nations?
- Flags of all nations?
- Like a proper sports day.
- Are you feeling it?
Can't we do a treasure hunt?
Jegi, skipping rope...
- Charade.
- Sounds great.
Why don't we add a really nice prize
like a Korean beef set?
- A prize will keep people motivated.
- Yes.
How about 1kg of octopus?
- Not a bad idea.
- About 1kg of octopus.
- What about 1kg of octopus?
- Just about 1kg.
Premium octopus leg.
- Good idea.
- Yeah.
That's a good one.
SHOULD I ORDER IT AGAIN?
- Let's shower and get ready.
- Good.
- Yeah.
- Good point.
We'll all get sweaty anyway.
Let's wait until it ends.
DON'T EMBARRASS US BEFORE OUR GUESTS
Don't you think we'll sweat buckets?
AT LEAST HE'S CONSISTENT
I knew I'd have to shower today
so I didn't last night.
Skip today, too.
You can wash tomorrow.
I'm actually considering it.
Sports day? Should I wash up after?
You're unbelievable.
Why eat at all
when it will turn into stool?
PERFECT EXPLANATION FOR DANIEL
Do you get it?
It's nice having a mini buffet.
- This is so good.
- Thanks, guys.
- How do we pay for the buffet?
- For the buffet?
You've given me so much love.
Let's call it even.
RUNS AWAY
THE WORLD'S MOST PRECIOUS BREAKFAST
UPSIDE OF LIVING TOGETHER
EXPERIENCING THE JOY
OF COOKING FOR OTHERS
Should we get ready?
Okay.
Shouldn't we prepare
light refreshments for our guests?
Yeah, let's get some snacks.
Good idea.
THE HOUSE CLEANING
IS DONE BY JAE-HYEON AND DANIEL
You might hurt yourself. Use this.
GUGI-DONG'S FINEST CHEFS
ARE PREPARING REFRESHMENTS
I'm good.
WE NEED TO MAKE AN EFFORT
FOR OUR GUESTS' SNACKS
Something like that.
What's going on?
Dash.
YOU NEED GOOD WORK MUSIC
WHEN YOU'RE WORKING
Something like that.
TEAM FORTIES PLAYLIST
DASH BY BAEK Z-YOUNG
That used to get me pumped up.
- It got me pumped.
- That was a good one.
TEAM FORTIES PLAYLIST
OH! HAPPY BY COUNTRY KKOKKO
SLEEK FOOTWORK
MR. CHOI IS HYPED UP AS HE CAN BE
PERFECT PARTNERSHIP
Next...
There you go.
HYPED-UP AUDIENCE MEMBER CUTS IN
You need music for work.
So clean
CONNECTING THROUGH OLD MUSIC
We used to play CDs
and cassette tapes.
Of course.
Our main music spot back in the day
was C**orld.
I remember. You were an icon there.
I was a powerhouse there.
- No one came close.
- I had a hand in its success.
WHEN YOU LISTEN
TO ANDRÉ GAGNON'S MUSIC...
KEUN-SUK TURNED FLEXING
INTO A TREND AS AN OG INFLUENCER
I used that song a lot back then.
- What?
- That song by Bobby Kim.
Another night
With drinks and cherry tomatoes
- This one?
- That's it.
That was the key song in my playlist.
- There's that iconic song.
- Which one?
TEAM FORTIES PLAYLIST
Y BY FREESTYLE
Y by Freestyle.
SINGING ANOTHER OLD CLASSIC
IT BRINGS ME BACK
Do you know that song by Brown Eyes?
ONE PROMPT IS ENOUGH
TO GET MR. JUKEBOX SINGING
TEAM FORTIES PLAYLIST
GRADUALLY BY BROWN EYES
IN THE ZONE
COMING IN NATURALLY
HERE'S CHOI NAUL
GRINS
NOSTALGIA OVERLOAD
FOLLOWED BY SIDE EFFECT
HOWLING
My goodness.
- What's going on over there?
- What?
What's going on?
Did someone get possessed?
I guess Brown Eyes are here.
- Naul.
- You think so?
That's cool.
TRIP DOWN THE MEMORY LANE
GOES ON FOREVER
HERE TO WATCH THE GROUP SING
What's going on?
We've been going over
our favorite old songs.
- I heard.
- I bet you're a great singer.
I've been listening to you guys sing.
Stars from the 2000s
paid a visit today.
All right.
Please welcome Ms. Jung Kyoung-hwa.
- Jung Kyoung-hwa joined us today.
- She's here.
MS. JANG KYOUNG-HWA
HOLDING A BANANA AS A MIC
VEINS ON HER NECK POPS OUT
SHE'S SURPRISINGLY GOOD
APPROACHING THE SING-ALONG SECTION
DESPERATELY HITTING THE HIGH NOTES
RUNS AWAY BEFORE SHE BLEEDS AGAIN
FIRST-ROW EXPERIENCE
TO THE LEGENDARY PERFORMANCE
I feel like throwing up.
LEAVES WITHOUT HESITATION
AFTER THE CHORUS
- So clean.
- It's spotless.
It's totally clean.
ASSORTED LIGHT SNACK IS ALMOST READY
Just roughly cut it
to go on top of the fruit.
It's all about presentability.
It's so pretty.
- My gosh.
- You guys did a great job.
Kudos to Daniel
for preparing all this.
- Get the large one on top.
- Just like this.
Our guests will love them, right?
Let's go in and wait for them.
- It's time now.
- Okay.
I can't wait to find out
who will join us.
I was just as curious
when I first got here.
WHO WILL SHOW UP
ON THIS EXCITING DAY?
Hey, Da-hee.
- Hi there.
- What's going on?
- Did you have lunch?
- No, not yet.
Not yet?
Want to try this?
It's a great meal replacement.
Isn't it green tea?
No, it's a green smoothie.
You should try it.
Let's shake a bottle each.
- All right.
- You have to shake it.
SHAKING
What do you think? Super easy, right?
Try it.
GREEN SMOOTHIE READY FOR DRINKING
- It's legit.
- Right?
- It totally tastes like salad.
- It does, doesn't it?
Most importantly
I love how easy it is to prepare.
It's good.
Let's dance.
BRINGING UP THE ENERGY LEVEL
BEFORE FRIENDS ARRIVE
REVISITING TEAM FORTIES PLAYLIST
A FRIEND OF MY OWN BY SOLID
GOT A LITTLE BIT OF BREAK?
IT'S PRINCE'S SHOWTIME
LADY SOO-JIN JOINS THEM
GROOVING
LET'S HAVE SOME FUN
EXCLAIMS
This is what I'm talking about.
THIS IS THE JOY
OF LIVING TOGETHER IN GUGI-DONG
NEVER-ENDING TEAM FORTIES PLAYLIST
YOU IN VAGUE MEMORY BY HYUN JIN-YOUNG
BRING UP THE TEMPO
GO GUGI-DONG
Like this, right?
BYE-BYE, GLASSES
Like so.
PICKS THEM UP IN A FLASH
HAVING TOO MUCH FUN
- You sped it up too much.
- What do you think?
- Bring it down.
- It's going so fast.
THEIR BODY CAN'T KEEP UP
OLD CLASSIC SPECIALIST IS BACK
THESE TWO MEN ARE DETERMINED
TO ENJOY TODAY TO THE FULLEST
HYPING UP WITH THE OLDIES
TO PREPARE FOR TEAM FORTIES PARTY
Are you ready?
THEIR VOICES FILL UP THE ENTIRE HOUSE
How nice.
- They're young.
- Oh, dear.
JUST 2 YEARS YOUNGER
THEY ARE STILL IN THEIR YOUTH
POURING EVERY LAST DROP OF PASSION
He's good.
DEEPLY SATISFIED
It's hot.
That was fun.
WARM UP BEFORE THE FRIENDS ARRIVE
We went all the way.
- Pretty neat, right?
- We had a proper party just now.
Pretty neat.
We're only getting started, right?
Let's go.
- It's time to greet our guests.
- Shall we?
Let's go. It's hot in here.
10 MINUTES BEFORE THE PROMISED TIME
ONE MAN IS VERY EXCITED
What's up?
EXCITED TO MAKE NEW FRIENDS
He looks delighted.
How's my jacket?
It got it from a vintage shop
for 100,000 won. How is it?
That cost 100,000 won?
It's quite a lot.
You think so?
To be honest,
I paid 150,000 won for it.
OH, DEAR
That kind of changes it.
Jumping from 100,000 won
to 150,000 won...
FASHION POLICE ARRIVES TIMELY
It's a good experience.
Yeah.
STUDIES HIS LOOK
Do I look okay?
DA-HEE'S GAZE TENSES HIM UP
Is that your jacket?
LET ME SEE
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
He got it for 150,000 won
at a vintage shop.
You mean the jacket?
It's nice.
You think it's good?
Let me try it.
- This is from a vintage shop?
- Yes.
- It's XXL.
- Yeah.
It's from an American brand.
IT'S NICE
- It looks nice.
- She's done it again.
It looks better on you.
- Cool.
- It looks nice.
- That's sick.
- It looks better on you.
It's so stylish.
You look really good in it.
If you were to ask me
100,000 won for this
I'd take you up on the offer.
- Really?
- Sure.
- But I can't go for 100,000 won.
- Why not?
- What happened to our friendship?
- I paid 150,000 won for it.
- Take it for 200,000 won.
- For 200,000 won?
How's 130,000 won?
- No can do.
- No?
Here's an idea.
Settle for 50,000 won
and a slow dance.
A slow dance with 50,000 won?
ANOTHER GO AT MY HOUSE SQUAD GOAL?
GIVES UP RIGHT AWAY
Here you go.
It's cute. It's a nice find.
Very cute.
- Sorry.
- You know what?
You're pretty cold.
Just so you know
my birthday is coming up.
That's true!
She gave you dress shoes, remember?
WHOSE JACKET IS IT NOW?
So this is how...
Hey, our friends are here.
Darn it.
- That was killer timing.
- Is someone here?
Let's see who it is.
We forgot about our guests.
Come on. Whose friend is this?
WHO IS AT THE DOOR?
WHO HAS HELPED DANIEL
KEEP HIS JACKET?
What a fancy mansion.
Whose friend is this?
ALL RUSH OVER
Who is it?
- Isn't that So-min?
- Who?
Who invited So-min?
Who is it?
JEON SO-MIN, BORN IN 1986
SOLO DWELLER OF 9 YEARS
WHOSE FRIEND IS SHE?
- Tell me, who invited her?
- Hi, guys.
Hey, So-min.
So-min.
- Is that you, Daniel?
- Yes.
This really is an impressive place.
Buzz me in.
Actually
you have to climb up the wall.
- See the wall?
- Just buzz me in already.
Okay, just one second.
CERTIFIED BESTIES
Gosh, this is just...
SHE CAME OVER
DESPITE THE SHORT NOTICE
What an amazing mansion this is.
DANIEL'S FRIEND
ONCE CO-STARS, NOW BESTIES
- Goodness.
- What's going on?
This is so fancy.
- Hello.
- My goodness.
- Nice to see you.
- Welcome.
- Can I come in?
- Of course.
UNFILTERED DUO
Just who do you live with...
- Come on in.
- Hello.
Gosh, Do-yeon.
Welcome.
JUST LIKE ON THEIR FIRST DAY
- Welcome.
- Guys.
- I didn't expect to see you.
- Here's my friend.
- So-min!
- Hey, Da-hee.
FRIENDLY FACES REUNITED
THANKS TO DANIEL
You didn't have to get us anything.
I'm worried I got too little. Hello.
- Hello.
THESE 87ERS KEEP THEIR DISTANCE
AS THEY MEET HER FOR THE FIRST TIME
- Can I use your bathroom?
- It's right here.
- Upon arrival...
- We've got one here.
There's one inside, too.
WERE THESE 87ERS ALWAYS THIS QUIET?
MIRTHLESS LAUGH
The 87ers are all at a loss.
- A bit.
- Even your pose looks awkward.
Because I am feeling that way.
Look at him rubbing his arm.
- I can't help it.
- Without realizing it...
It feels awkward.
Take a seat.
Someone's here!
Hey, someone else is here.
- Who can it be?
- Is someone else here?
ALL RUSH OVER
- What's the matter?
- Let me see.
- My friend's here!
- Who is it?
SOLO DWELLER OF 5 YEARS
KEUN-SUK'S FRIEND
He's got a fancy place.
He's practically my mini-me.
WHO IS THIS LITTLE PRINCE
AND A MINI-ME OF AP?
YOU CAN TELL HE IS KEUN-SUK'S FRIEND
FROM HIS EYE-CATCHING CLOTHES
Who is it? I can't see.
I can't see.
Who is it?
- It's Lee Hong-gi.
- Who is it?
- Right?
- Hey, Hong Star.
- Buzz me in.
LEE HONG-GI, BORN IN 1990
- Lee Hong-gi?
- Isn't that Hong-gi?
- You two share that vibe.
- Right?
- Mini-me.
- That's why he's little Keun-suk.
- You're right.
- Yes.
- This is pretty cool.
- Is he our age?
- No, he was born in 1989.
- Really?
LEFT UNATTENDED
THEY ALL FORGOT ABOUT DANIEL'S FRIEND
Please have a seat.
Gosh, So-min.
Welcome.
- Welcome.
- Here are Keun-suk and Jae-hyeon.
- Hello, it's nice to meet you.
- And Soo-jin.
I believe we met
when you were on my show.
- Oh, you're right.
- Yes.
It's nice to meet you again.
Turns out we've met before.
KEUN-SUK GOES TO GREET HIS FRIEND
Hong Star!
FRIENDS SINCE THEIR DAYS
ON YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL
- Keun-suk.
- Thanks a lot.
- No problem.
- It was on such short notice.
- Keun-suk.
- Yeah?
Come on in.
You live in this fancy place?
Hang on. I'll get you slippers.
- Are you two acquainted?
- I've never met him before.
- Ever seen him?
- What about you?
I worked with him on a show before.
He sure stands out.
Gosh, he really does.
- We've got a real celebrity here.
- He's got this bold look.
- Hello.
- These are my housemates.
My gosh.
CLAPS
This is Hong Star.
- Please welcome Lee Hong-gi.
- It's a celebrity.
Hey, Keun-suk.
He does look like you.
- Dude, I'm the good-looking one.
- You look like brothers.
The other earring is likely with you.
Did I get it right?
Did I get it wrong?
- Is it not a matching item?
- You two look alike.
- Come on in.
- This way.
It feels like I've become
one of your housemates.
Lead the way, So-min.
You got here first
- so you count as a resident.
- Totally.
Feel free to look around.
The kitchen's that way.
This is our family portrait.
What on earth?
- Is it AI-generated?
- No, it's an actual photo.
Everyone keeps asking
if this is an edited photo.
- As in an AI-generated photo?
- It's real stuff.
So it's real.
It's so nice to meet you, Hong-gi.
Hey, someone new is here.
Who is it?
- That's my friend!
- Who is it?
Give me a minute.
- Hey.
- What?
Is that the lady
who wants to get to know me?
It's so cold.
HERE IS DO-YEON'S FRIEND
WHO LOVES KEUN-SUK
WHO IS THIS WOMAN
WHO LOOKS LIKE A CAT?
DOESN'T SHE LOOK FAMILIAR?
Gi-ru!
ANOTHER HIT OF DÉJÀ VU
Do-yeon.
SHIN GI-RU, BORN IN 1981
DO-YEON'S FRIEND
NOTE: THIS IS HER 2ND VISIT HERE
Do-yeon.
You really came.
- You really came.
- Hey.
- It's relaxing to be here.
- My abs.
It almost feels like I'm home
in my own neighborhood.
- My abs hurt from laughing.
- Has no one found out I was here?
- First things first.
- Yeah?
- We haven't revealed who we invited.
- Really?
- I was lucky to catch you in Korea.
- Me?
I had a show yesterday...
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THE OTHER 87ERS
STILL IN THEIR WALLFLOWER ERA
Why does it feel so...
- It's just...
- It's awkward, right?
MAKING FRIENDS AT THIS AGE ISN'T EASY
Don't just stand there.
- Look around.
- Take a look around.
- Wow, this place is so nice.
That's my room.
THE 87ERS GIVE THEIR GUEST A TOUR
TO BREAK THE AWKWARD SILENCE
THESE TWO ARE STILL ON THE STAIRS
I don't want to embarrass you
so I can't be huffing and puffing.
Let me take a breather.
I just told them you look like a cat
and that you'd like
to befriend Keun-suk.
Really? His heart must be fluttering.
WILL HIS HEART FLUTTER TO SEE HER?
- It will probably drop.
- Should I just go home?
Why don't I go catch a cat somewhere?
I saw enough roaming around.
No, everyone's really sweet.
Give me a second.
I shouldn't let it show how fat I am.
- You're the funniest.
- Right?
- You're great.
- I said you're the funniest.
NERVOUS TO MEET HER HOUSEMATES
- How should I act?
- What?
Are they around that dining table?
Yeah, but don't tell them
you visited just yet.
IT'S STILL A SECRET
Hey, Do-yeon.
- I didn't want to make you look bad
- Wear these.
- so I wore branded shoes.
- Great job.
But you need to take them off.
- Want to carry them inside?
- Like this?
- Hang on.
- I'll go tell them.
Are you ready to meet my friend?
- Yes.
- Of course.
SO NERVOUS
COME ON IN
Hello.
- Hello.
- Feels like I'm watching TV.
EXPLOSIVE REACTIONS
PRETENDING TO BE NEW HERE
- Hello.
- The hottest comedian right now.
- Introducing Shin Gi-ru.
- Hello.
Gi-ru.
Are you perhaps a fan of mine?
Yes, I love you so much.
- I've never met them before.
- Really?
Doesn't she look like a cat?
Meow.
Someone is in the hallway.
- Sorry.
- Meet my friend.
WHILE GI-RU IS INTRODUCED PROPERLY
- Hello, Gi-ru.
- Hello.
THE LAST GUEST IS HERE
Is this the place?
KIM DAE-HO, BORN IN 1984
SOLO DWELLER OF 22 YEARS
JAE-HYEON'S ELITE FRIEND
Hey, we've got another guest.
THAT'S MY FRIEND!
- Isn't that Dae-ho?
- Who is it? Let me see.
Just a second.
So he invited Dae-ho.
I'm pretty close with him.
RUSHING OVER TO WELCOME HIS FRIEND
SOMEHOW LEAVING THE GUESTS
WHO ARE TOTAL STRANGERS ALONE
How many iced Americanos?
WHILE THE HOSTS PREPARE DRINKS
This has tomato in it.
- Really? I should try it.
- This has eggplant.
- How fascinating.
- Potato, sweet potato...
Please enjoy.
THEY'VE RUN OUT OF TOPICS
REMINDS YOU OF THE HOUSEMATES
ON THEIR FIRST DAY
THIS NEW GROUP
IS PRETTY MUCH THE SAME
CAN'T SOMEONE PLEASE JOIN US?
I'm not good at breaking the ice.
LONG AWAITED FRIENDS
- Sorry.
- This isn't my place
- so I'm not sure what to do.
- Gosh, thank you.
- How about a toast, So-min?
- I'd love to.
What a heartwarming sight.
This is how you make new friends.
TEAM FORTIES' BEST ICEBREAKER IS BEER
THE ONLY '90S KID
OPTS FOR BREAD INSTEAD
DESPITE THE COLD SWIG OF BEER
SO-MIN STILL FEELS AWKWARD
This is super awkward.
What a heartwarming sight.
This is how you make new friends.
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO BECOME FRIENDS?
This is super awkward.
What took you so long?
- Hey, this place is so...
- What do you think?
You guys use this entire place?
It has the vibe you dig, right?
- Yes.
- It's your dream house.
- It's fabulous.
- What do you think?
I'll show you around later.
THEY BECAME FRIENDS OUTSIDE OF WORK
- Everyone, my friend is here.
- Guys.
- Who can it be?
- Here he comes.
- Hello.
- Hi, Dae-ho.
- Hey, Gi-ru.
- Hello.
It's great to see a friendly face.
Have you worked together before?
No.
We met in a frozen pork belly place.
Dae-ho!
- Dae-ho.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- It's a pleasure.
Did you greet So-min, Dae-ho?
We're good friends.
Did you invite her?
- Yeah.
- I knew it.
Dae-ho knows most of the people here.
Do we have everyone?
Yes, I think we do.
THEIR BESTIES ARE ALL HERE
At times like this...
Would you like some bread?
I have one here.
Hey, Dae-ho.
Don't you guys know each other?
- It's my first time meeting her.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- Absolutely.
I assumed you guys were acquainted.
- We've never met.
- Seriously?
Hong-gi and I've never met either.
- Same goes for Keun-suk.
- Really?
- Want me to swap seats with you?
- It's okay.
- Are you sure?
- You look so uncomfortable.
No way.
You're acting all strange.
I'm just fine.
You guys have a lie detector.
It's out of power.
It's just a prop.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
I'm an introvert myself,
so I'm not sure what to do.
THEY ARE ALL CELEBRITIES
WITH A STRONG CAREER
Things feel awkward
- with guests at our place.
- Hey, Dae-ho.
TURNS OUT THEY'RE ALL INTROVERTS
AWKWARD, ANXIOUS
It's so awkward.
What party were you thinking?
EMBARRASSED
Oh, no.
What kind of party is this?
I'm trying to remember the last time
I was at such an awkward event.
I haven't been to one lately.
MAKING FRIENDS AS ADULTS ISN'T EASY
I don't even know
what this gathering is about.
- You just took a leap of faith.
- Yeah.
- The tissue hasn't done anything.
- I know.
It's getting shredded.
- I'm sorry.
- No worries.
STRESS RELIEF
- Check out Hong-gi.
- He's doing the same thing.
CHECK OUT MY TISSUE
Would you like a tissue, too?
I already have one.
I'VE BEEN DOING THE SAME THING
TURNS OUT EVERYONE WAS COPING
WITH A LITTLE STRESS RELIEF PROJECT
We have five guys and five girls.
Hey, you're right.
SERENDIPITOUS GOLDEN RATIO
I didn't realize
we matched the numbers.
What? You're twisting things.
I mean...
Looks like you orchestrated this.
- This isn't a dating show.
- I wasn't trying to imply that.
Doesn't it feel like
we're on a celebrity retreat?
- Rather than a retreat...
- Not at all.
CRITICIZED EVERY WHICH WAY
I see.
I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE
GIVING HIM AN EARFUL
SILENCE FALLS AGAIN
JUST A FEW MOMENTS LATER!
SHY AROUND STRANGERS? NOT US!
TEAM FORTIES GROWS SO CLOSE
AND THEIR ENERGY LEVEL SPIKES
MY FRIENDS, I'M ON MY WAY
Hold on.
WAIT AND SEE
THIS IS HOW TEAM FORTIES
BECOMES CLOSE
WELL, THEY MIGHT GET TOO CLOSE
FORTIES SPORTS DAY, COMING SOON
- Okay, let's go outside.
- Let's go
Let's go.
OUT ON TO THE YARD WITH NEW FRIENDS
Goodness.
You guys did a thorough job.
This place is pretty spacious.
What's that?
Are we taking a nap here?
CHUCKLES
- Look at all this.
- How exciting.
It is exciting.
Even my heart's racing.
I'm psyched.
HOUSEMATES LAID OUT
BLANKETS UNDER THE SUN
The weather's wonderful.
ONE BACHELOR IS BLISSFULLY HAPPY
CHUCKLES
I'm actually enjoying this.
CHUCKLES AGAIN
- Dae-ho's hyped. He's loving this.
- Really?
I've never gone
on a group retreat before.
I know it can be awkward,
but there's a certain charm to it.
- I'm having so much fun.
- It has this charm.
I can even stay late.
CHUCKLES
- Hello, let me introduce myself.
- Please do.
- Hello.
- Yes.
Oh, about Jang Do-yeon.
Holiday, for which we all yearn.
Web comic scene has Lee Mal-nyeon.
Old K-pop had Noh Sa-yeon.
And I'm comedian Jang Do-yeon.
JANG DO-YEON
GUGI-DONG MC
WAY TO GO, FRIEND
- We prepared a variety of games.
- Okay.
They're nothing major
but I hope they will help us
get to know each other better.
GAMES SOUND LOVELY
It's difficult to make new friends,
especially at our age.
This group's average age is over 40.
BURSTS INTO LAUGHTER
Age 40 is...
- Why are you laughing?
- I'm sorry, Do-yeon.
Let's do the Cushion Quiz.
- That's not on our agenda.
- Okay.
Back in the day,
we used to solve quizzes together.
TEAM FORTIES IS
JUST AS UNRULY AS TEENAGERS
Enough with chatter!
It's bad manners to chat
when your MC is talking!
RIGHT UP HIS ALLEY
I'm tired as is.
DO-YEON'S OUTBURST BIT
MELTS ALL THE AWKWARDNESS
I know I still need to do my best.
Sorry about that.
Without further ado
let's begin Keun-suk's
House Squad Goal.
It was Keun-suk's House Squad Goal?
This is "Sports Day for the Forties."
SPORTS DAY OUT IN THE YARD
SPORTS DAY FOR THE FORTIES
I never got to participate
in school sports day events
growing up.
I wanted to have fun with friends
if you guys were available.
That was one of my House Squad Goals.
IN HOPES OF MAKING MEMORIES
HE NEVER GOT TO MAKE AS A BOY
Is there a prize involved?
Of course.
- Please look here.
- Great.
- What?
- You actually prepared stuff.
- I'm glad I came.
- They're underneath this cover.
CARE PACKAGES FOR SOLO DWELLERS
Honestly
- we prepared them ourselves.
- He's right.
We pooled money for them.
- For real.
- Out of our shared fund.
I can confirm it as the treasurer.
- You're the treasurer?
- Yeah.
Really?
WE'RE WORRIED ABOUT THIS HOUSEHOLD
I can see "dried seaweed."
- Dried seaweed?
REACTING NIMBLY
Dried seaweed?
- Are you sure?
- It says so.
Dried seaweed...
OLDER GUESTS CAN'T SEE SO CLEARLY
CHUCKLES
- It says so.
- Dried seaweed...
Your eyesight is great.
Hey, good catch.
GOOD EYESIGHT
IS SOMETHING TO BRAG ABOUT HERE
We have a few newcomers.
In some cases, you might have gotten
to know each other through work.
Who would you like
to get to know better, Gi-ru?
- Tell me.
- Of course
I'd like to be friends
with everyone here.
But I'd love
to be good friends with Keun-suk
the most.
Can I ask why?
How should I put this?
- You're not sure?
- Well...
- I'm hoping
we can enjoy good food together.
I know he's quite the foodie.
You said it was for a reservation
at some Japanese bar.
Before you got here
Do-yeon kept saying
she invited an actual cat.
- She got all of us pretty hyped up.
- Oh, right.
Meow.
- For real... Meow.
- Meow.
She's a shy cat.
AP IS DELIGHTED
Looks like you're shy, too.
She's a shy cat.
EMBARRASSED
- I hope you'll get closer.
- Thanks.
- I hope this takes up the full day.
- I love your attitude.
EVERYONE CRACKS UP
You live close by, don't you?
- Yes.
- Don't you have work tomorrow?
- No.
- No?
- What a coincidence.
- Just a plan for the evening.
I'll ask on behalf of people here
who want to know you better.
What kind of qualities
would they need?
They just need to...
To be honest,
I'd love to be friends with everyone.
My social circle's pretty small.
OH, NO
Really?
YOU POOR THING
Now that I've reached an age
where you rarely get
to meet new people.
So I find myself
doing whatever it takes
to seize all opportunities
to socialize.
I really want to, too.
It's really hard to make new friends.
I get it. As age goes by
we click better
with a different crowd, too.
- You're right.
- "As age goes by"?
As days go by... Hey!
SPOOKED
I'm the only one standing up here!
That can wear you out.
I'LL ZIP IT
THE MORE DO-YEON SHOUTS,
THE LESS AWKWARD IT GETS
Hong-gi and I are
the same on this end.
If you want to be close to Hong-gi
you've got to go a bit crazy.
IT'S NOT EASY TO MAKE NEW FRIENDS
Being rather atypical
there were times
when I felt rather alone.
But I'd like to remind you
that even I got to find
a kindred soul in Hong-gi.
You guys really look alike.
- Totally.
- Most definitely.
You do look alike.
THEY EVEN SIT THE SAME WAY
I wanted to prove
that I'm not all that odd.
We're not odd at all.
That's why I invited
someone who's exactly like me.
TWO PEAS IN A POD
- "We're not odd at all."
- Hong-gi.
- What's your MBTI?
- Well...
I get ENTP and ENFP 50-50.
So you're an ENTP.
I'm an ENTP, too.
I knew there was a reason
I felt close to you.
- I'm glad we've met.
- So cool.
Out of the blue...
- You rock.
- I really don't like that about him.
How absurd, right?
They actually have nothing in common.
None at all.
ALL HIS FRIENDS NAG AT HIM
Do you know my MBTI?
OOPS
You're an E...
He's guessing.
THAT MEANS HE DOESN'T KNOW
FAIL, AND OUR FRIENDSHIP IS OVER
E...
N...
F...
P?
He did get it right, but...
SAME REACTION
- He got it.
- True friends.
HE MANAGED TO SAVE THEIR FRIENDSHIP
GOOD JOB
I'm an introvert in the evening
and an extrovert by day.
- That's how I see it.
- Are you an extrovert now?
- Yes, I am.
- Okay.
Now, let's get closer
while we play the games.
- How are we going to get two teams?
- About that.
Most of us have our besties here
- but a few don't.
- Right.
- Soo-jin and Da-hee
- Yes.
can each take turns
to choose your teammates.
- We can choose people?
- Yes.
- To form a team?
I'll go with Daniel and So-min.
- Daniel and So-min.
- Thank you.
I'd like to have Gi-ru on my team.
- She then gets both of us.
- We'll be a team.
- Take me in as well.
- Okay.
- Is it because of me?
- Sure.
- Really?
- Is that why?
I WANT TO TEAM UP WITH MS. CAT-LIKE
- So the five of us are a team.
- Exactly.
We're all sitting close by.
That's neat.
We're on the same team.
- All right.
- Okay.
TEAM DA-HEE
Team Soo-jin gets the blue vest.
TEAM DA-HEE GETS THE RED VEST
Who got these vests? I'm curious.
- Daniel did.
- Your bestie did.
My bestie?
You have terrible taste.
Hey, bestie.
BITE ME
The first game is called
"Step On Me."
LET'S GET PHYSICAL TO BOND!
STEP ON ME
What a throwback. It's been a while.
- It's been ages since I tried this.
- It's been forever.
Each team's player
will start hopping to the other side.
Upon contact,
they play rock-paper-scissors.
The winner can continue.
EXPECT TO SEE A LOT OF CONTACT
The first to reach
the other team's territory
takes the match.
We can just shove people, right?
- Of course.
- With brute force?
Yes, we can do that.
- On contact, that is.
- I see.
I get the feeling shoving
is the way to victory.
SO COMFORTING AS AN ALLY
SO FRIGHTENING AS AN OPPONENT
It all comes down
to rock-paper-scissors.
Even if you start slow
- you can win if you're good at it.
- That's right.
MR. ELITE'S STRATEGY IS QUITE SIMPLE
What's the prize for this game?
All right, everyone.
The prize for this game
is assorted premium Korean pork.
Oh, that one?
THE MOST EXPENSIVE PRIZE,
ASSORTED PREMIUM KOREAN PORK
- Oh, that one?
- We've got to win.
- Let's go for it.
- Pork.
- Let's get everything.
- I'm in.
- Meat.
- Just say the word.
I'LL GET EVERYTHING
SWEET DA-HEE'S CHILLING AMBITION
PRIZE BRINGS EVERYONE TOGETHER
That's the real deal.
Is it our turn to step in?
Let's do our best, Gi-ru.
There it is.
PREOCCUPIED WITH PORK
- This is fresh premium pork.
- There are some ribs.
- We have an assorted variety here.
- Look at that cut.
It tastes heavenly with some salt.
- We're not going to grill it now.
- I know.
We've got skin-on and regular pork
- plus pork ribs.
- That's right.
- The skin is visible here.
- All right.
This fine Korean pork set
will go to the winning team.
MOOD LIGHTENED UP
THANKS TO THE PORK SET
All right.
- Why don't I go first?
- Go right ahead.
- It's a one-time match.
- We need a nimble player.
THE COMPETITION HAS TAKEN OVER,
LEAVING NO ROOM FOR AWKWARDNESS
Let's do this. It's time to go wild.
Ready.
Let's make that pork set ours.
HE NEEDS TO WIN TO WIN GI-RU OVER
This is for you, Gi-ru.
I LOVE KOREAN PORK
- I'll go first, Dae-ho.
- Okay.
I'll do it.
Let's do this.
- I'm on it.
- You've got this.
Jump right in.
I HAVE TO WIN
OR I'LL GET AN EARFUL FROM DA-HEE
Ready.
- Set. Go.
- Move fast.
- Looking good.
- No.
SUDDEN HUG
A BROMANCE PAIR NO ONE WAS EXPECTING
So you're an ENTP.
I'm an ENTP, too.
KID, WOULD YOU MIND IF I GOT CLOSER?
I'VE NEVER RUN INTO A GUY'S ARMS
ON OUR FIRST MEETING BEFORE
- Why the sudden shift to romance?
- What's going on?
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Why the sudden shift to romance?
Rock-paper-scissors.
- I won!
- Darn it.
Quick, get out there.
HEARTTHROB HONG-GI WON
- Hang in there.
- Oh, no.
THANK GOODNESS
- Rock-paper-scissors.
DAE-HO AVOIDS CRISIS
Go, Dae-ho.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
DAE-HO WON AGAIN!
- Go!
- You're doing great.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
THAT'S 3 WINS IN A ROW!
HE ONLY NEEDS
TO DEFEAT DO-YEON TO WIN!
HAVE THEY GOTTEN THIS CLOSE ALREADY?
What happened?
UNEXPECTED COLLISION
SHOCKS EVERYONE
STARTLED BY THE BOLD ACTION
FROM THIS PAIR IN THEIR 40S
What just happened?
BEWILDERED BY THE SPICY ACTION
What was that?
Nothing happened.
EMBARRASSED
What's going on between you two?
Sorry, Do-yeon.
I'll apologize on his behalf.
Don't worry. It wasn't so bad.
- Really?
- My goodness.
Did they actually collide?
- Their cheeks touched slightly.
- Really?
- Move ahead, Do-yeon.
We gave them a penalty.
One, two, three.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Come on. Move in.
ADVANCING AFTER A VICTORY
Oh, my.
ANOTHER UNEXPECTED COLLISION
CRACKING UP
I WAS JUST STANDING THERE
DO-YEON CAUSES ANOTHER CONTROVERSY
I mean...
She's a repeat offender.
- It was just...
- She keeps doing that.
I knew it.
HOW SPICY
You're way too enthusiastic.
Did you come here to get a kiss?
REASONABLE DOUBT
NO ONE KNOWS HER TRUE INTENT
- You're angling for a kiss, right?
- Do-yeon.
Are you a kissing gourami?
Kissing gourami?
- Rock-paper-scissors.
KISSING DO-RAMI LOST!
- Move ahead.
- Go!
HERE COMES KISSING DO-RAMI'S FRIEND
THUMP
AHN-GEL ADVANCES FEARLESSLY
THUMP, THUMP
Gi-ru!
POW!
Great job!
- Way to go, bestie!
- Get back here!
GIGGLING
Great job!
- I did it.
- All right!
Get back here!
SCARED HE MIGHT GET SHOVED AGAIN
Come on, Gi-ru. That's not fair.
I moved.
I'M LOSING MY MIND
- Rock-paper-scissors.
I won!
JAE-HYEON WINS!
MY TEAM RULES!
- Move forward.
NEXT OPPONENT IS SOO-JIN
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Nice! Keep going.
- Rock-paper-scissors is a pain.
IT'S ANOTHER GUY THIS TIME
HABITUAL HUGGER
Rock-paper-scissors!
- I won!
- All right. Go for it.
Great.
YELP
EVEN WHEN IN A HURRY
AUTOMATICALLY TURNS AWAY
HE DOES HIS BEST
He pulled his hands back.
THAT'S MY FRIEND
WOW, GOOD JOB THERE
He's got great reflexes.
HE KEEPS HIS RESPECTFUL DISTANCE
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Get moving quickly.
- Go, So-min.
ONLY ONE CELL AWAY FROM VICTORY
Hong-gi is incredible.
PLEASE GET ME THAT KOREAN PORK SET
Rock-paper-scissors!
I WANT TO WIN THE KOREAN PORK SET
TO BE CLOSE TO GI-RU!
Rock-paper-scissors!
WILL HE BE ABLE
TO WIN PORK AND FRIENDSHIP?
ROCK, PAPER
I won!
You did it!
Bring it in!
Team Soo-jin won!
TEAM SOO-JIN WON THE FIRST GAME
- Don't worry about it.
- It's okay.
- Everyone has to jump in right away.
- I see it now.
COMPETITIVENESS IGNITED
OVER A LITTLE FRIENDLY GAME
This is their forte.
Let's play another round.
- Not bad.
- You did great.
- Good work.
- Well done.
- Okay, let's move on now.
- I did it.
Great job.
Are you all enjoying the game?
- Yes.
ALL AWKWARDNESS IS GONE
I'm having so much fun.
The next game is "Flip the Panels."
THE NEXT GAME INVOLVES
PHYSICAL CONTACT, TOO
You have one minute to flip
the colored panels on the floor
so that more panels
show your team's color.
3 PLAYERS FROM EACH TEAM WILL COMPETE
I'll now introduce
the prize for this game.
- It's canned ham.
- All right.
- It has a long shelf life.
- Also
- you can win the tuna cans!
- Tuna cans!
- I love it!
CANNED HAM AND TUNA COMBO
- I love tuna cans.
- Me too.
MUST-HAVE FOR SOLO DWELLERS
- We've got to win.
- If you want the tuna cans
- work harder.
- Okay.
Tuna cans are great.
- I love tuna cans.
- Let's win that for Dae-ho.
- For this guy.
- Do you like tuna cans?
- I love it.
- I'll do my best
to get it for you.
BURNING DRIVE
I'm actually extremely competitive.
No, I can find balance again.
COMPETITIVE GODDESS
CANNOT ACCEPT DEFEAT
SHE EVEN SEES HERSELF
AS A BITTER RIVAL
FISTS CLENCHED
TODAY IS THE DAY
DA-HEE GOES ON A RAMPAGE
Should we send the younger trio?
Doesn't this game require
a lot of action, too?
You have to move fast
or block them effectively.
- Blocking is an option?
- Yes.
If I can sit or lie on the panels,
they simply can't push me away.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GOING TO WIN AGAIN!
- Do you have any strategies?
- Got any ideas?
Do you have anything?
Please keep it down.
Da-hee's pretty competitive.
- She's really intense.
- She goes all in to win.
MR. ELITE'S STRATEGY
One of us can collect the panels
and run away.
The other team
will chase them, right?
The remaining players
can flip everything.
I'll handle the running part.
Please take care of things here.
We can flip everything here.
DA-HEE'S ROLE IS TO RUN AWAY
Players, please stand on each end.
You have one minute.
Ready.
TEAM DA-HEE HAS A FIERCE ACE PLAYER
One minute ends in a flash.
TEAM SOO-JIN HAS A STRONG ACE PLAYER
RELAXED AND CONFIDENT
Show us what you've got.
You have one minute.
Ready.
- Set. Go.
- You've got this!
Good luck!
THE GAME HAS BEGUN!
- Set. Go.
- You've got this!
Good luck!
DASHES FORWARD
AS PLANNED,
DA-HEE COLLECTS PANELS QUICKLY
LIGHTNING FAST
- You've got this!
- Good luck!
YOU'RE DOING GREAT, DA-HEE
- Hang on.
- No fighting, Gi-ru.
- Dae-ho.
- This isn't a boxing match.
ACTIONS BEFORE WORDS?
No fighting, Gi-ru.
This isn't a boxing match.
GREAT! GI-RU IS THE BEST!
- She tried to flip him.
- Everyone is working fast.
SHE STARTS FLIPPING PANELS
INSTEAD OF PLAYERS
- So quick.
- They're collecting panels.
TEAM DA-HEE IS FAST
- Both teams had similar strategies.
- Yes.
All the panels are gone.
Where did all the panels go?
Sit here, Gi-ru!
- Here, Gi-ru.
- Just a second.
TEAM SOO-JIN RELIES
ON GI-RU'S PHYSIQUE
SLIDING PANELS UNDER GI-RU'S BUTT
- Here.
- Hang on.
- Just a second.
- She's not budging.
INVINCIBLE
Goodness, look at them go.
They're hugging already.
Hang on, I can't really...
All right, fine.
- Pass it to me.
- Hong-gi.
Steal those panels!
- Hang in there.
- Hold on.
PUSHES ASIDE LIKE HE WEIGHS NOTHING
ONE PUSH
CAN SEND ANYONE FLYING
Watch out.
WAY TO GO, MS. CAT!
Gi-ru.
- Hong-gi.
- How is this fair?
CANNED HAM IS MINE, MEOW
WHILE ALL OTHERS
ARE WRESTLING WITH GI-RU
ONE WOMAN RUNS OFF WITH PANELS!
TEAM LEADER DA-HEE
IS CARRYING OUT THEIR ORIGINAL PLAN
STEP ASIDE
Hang on.
FEEBLE MEN!
THE COMPETITIVE GODDESS
IS ON HER WAY!
Over there, Hong-gi.
DA-HEE'S FIRST PREY,
THE YOUNGEST HONG-GI
Take it from him.
Wait!
HANGS ON TO HIS ANKLE
DETERMINED NOT TO LET HIM GO
Hang in there.
Hong-gi, there are more panels.
Hold on.
THEY ONLY MET TODAY
CLAIMS HER ORIGINAL TARGET
THEIR BLOSSOMING FRIENDSHIP
IS MAKING OTHERS LAUGH HARD
- Da-hee is no joke.
- No, she isn't.
Her competitiveness
is on another level.
Be careful.
LET ME KEEP HONG-GI'S PANEL
You're amazing, Da-hee.
Don't go!
IN THE MEANTIME,
HONG-GI HAS LOST EVERYTHING
Am I the only player or what?
FIGHTS ALONE
I'm...
I'm all alone!
No, Gi-ru. Don't move!
- You can't go.
- Are there panels here?
Your time is almost up.
Please remember the panels
should touch the ground to count.
Lay them out to score.
- Lie on them, Gi-ru!
- No overlaps.
FLINGS HIM AWAY
Everyone.
OH, DEAR
Nine.
- Eight.
- Gi-ru!
Gi-ru!
A RAIDING PARTY ARRIVES
WHILE GI-RU IS AWAY
Seven.
IN THE MEANTIME,
DA-HEE ROLLS OUT HER COLLECTION
Four. Three.
- Gi-ru!
- Two. One.
Your time is up!
- Stop it!
- It's over now.
- Time is up! Stop it!
- Stop!
- Stop it, Da-hee!
Come on, Da-hee.
Stay right where you are!
Stop moving, all of you!
CHORTLES
STOPS MOVING FOR NOW
Stay still.
I'm going to start counting.
I'll count the blue panels first.
IF ONLY SHE CAN WIN
EVEN CHEATING IS NOT BENEATH HER
- She just flipped one.
- I didn't!
- Which hand did she use?
- Chop off her right hand.
- But I didn't.
- Hold out your hand.
Which hand shall I cut off?
- Take her right hand.
- I only flipped this one.
Get your act together.
Let me count the blue panels first.
One, two, three, four, five...
My gosh, Da-hee is so competitive.
SIMPLY AWE-INSPIRING
Even at a glance,
there are more red panels.
- What a shame.
- So, Team Da-hee
takes the game!
VICTORY BUILT
AROUND COMPETITIVE GODDESS
Let's do this.
They're just not good enough.
FRIENDSHIP GROWS WITH VICTORY
Try to make it
more entertaining, will you?
Let's have some fun,
for goodness' sake.
It should be neck-and-neck.
I'm having a blast.
STRONGER FRIENDSHIP
BRINGS ON LOUDER VOICES
- We're giving it our all.
- It was fun, too.
Come on, admit it.
The way I see it,
the ham gave you tunnel vision.
You gave up on fairness
and sportsmanship.
I hope you're happy
you've won through cheating.
- Congrats.
- Thanks.
I'll give you the canned ham set.
Excuse me, MC.
That was really...
You went too far.
Seriously, that was low.
Here's the truth.
As you get older
making new friends becomes
closer to something of a miracle.
The opportunities are rare
making it an extreme challenge.
YOU FEEL MORE HESITANT
TO PUT YOURSELF OUT THERE
It felt like we were
all innocent children again.
I had so much fun
and was truly happy.
BONDING EASILY JUST AS THEY DID
IN THE PLAYGROUND AS CHILDREN
Let's do this!
SPECIAL TREAT
FROM THE YOUNGEST MEMBER
CLASSIC OLDIE, LOVESICK
EVERYONE SINGS ALONG
THE HIT SONG OF THEIR 20S
WHILE THE TIME HAS PASSED,
THE SONG STILL RESONATES WITH THEM
BECOMING ONE
THANKS TO THE CLASSIC SONG
HONG-GI'S SPECIAL GIFT SHINES
EVEN WITH A SIMPLE BLUETOOTH MIC
HE KILLED IT!
MY FRIEND ROCKS
- That was the best.
- So incredible.
OUR NEW FRIEND IS SO COOL
Thank you.
- It's an honor to be here.
- So cool.
- That's my pal, okay?
- He's so cool.
- Totally.
- So sick.
LET'S BE GOOD FRIENDS!
- Bye.
- Don't forget your presents.
Take them with you.
- Can I get your number?
- Oh, you want it?
- I hope this is not a fake number.
- No way.
PRIM
- Can we exchange numbers?
- For real? What's with you guys?
Hey, Do-yeon.
These guys are asking for my number.
- I just...
- I got the text.
- You did? Let me double-check.
- Sure.
CHUCKLES
- Not your second number, is it?
- Oh, no.
- "Second number"?
- No way.
People keep giving me
their second number.
Don't worry. I only keep one phone.
It's all in your head.
Do-yeon, if you're interested,
I'll give you the guys' number later.
Okay, thanks.
- You'll bring me closer to them.
- Really?
Could we exchange numbers, too?
Just a second, please.
Let me save this first.
Her phone's out of storage.
GENTLEMEN FIRST
- I'll text you, Jae-hyeon.
- Would you like canned ham, Gi-ru?
Why are you flirting with me?
- It's gotten so cold.
- Great work, Dae-ho.
- You too, guys.
- Good job, Dae-ho.
You guys must've had a lot of fun.
- Of course.
- Us? We sure did.
I had a blast.
It's always fun with a crowd.
- We're only two years apart.
- Exactly.
Good work, Hong-gi.
- You too.
- Thank you for the good time.
- Great work.
- You too.
You seemed to enjoy it the most.
Oh, well...
Around my age
it's hard to find people
to hang out with.
- Reach out to her first, Jae-hyeon.
- Of course.
MAY TODAY'S FRIENDSHIP GROW FURTHER
I'll call Gi-ru.
- "Where are you?"
- "This is Jae-hyeon."
- Thank you.
- Let's grab rice wine later, Dae-ho.
PROMISING TO MEET AGAIN
- Take care.
- See you.
LET'S FOCUS ON OUR GROUP NOW
That was fun.
A SMALL GATHERING
AFTER THE GUESTS LEFT
SIGHS
I feel hollow for some reason.
- Tell me about it.
- You keep sighing, right?
- Yeah.
- You can't help it for some reason.
THIS IS THEIR LAST DAY TOGETHER
AND THEY HAVE BEEN TRYING
TO IGNORE THAT ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM
3 HOURS UNTIL THEIR LEASE EXPIRES
AND THEY RETURN TO SOLITUDE
Aren't you guys hungry?
- Shall we get some snacks?
- Let's do
one more thing together
before we leave.
Let's eat together.
- One last time.
- One last time?
We didn't finish
the seasoned vegetables we bought.
- We can empty the fridge.
- We should.
- The fridge?
We can make bibimbap.
- Hey.
- With everything in a bowl.
- Mix it all in one giant bowl.
- Yes.
- Bibimbap sounds nice.
Let's get aggressive, shall we?
- With fried eggs.
- Let's do this.
Are you adding the octopus, too?
- We're saying goodbye to it.
- That's a no, then.
It went to meet its maker.
ENTERS WITH NEW DETERMINATIONS
Let me check the side dishes.
CHEFS SOO-JIN AND KEUN-SUK
Bean sprouts.
- What else?
- Radish salad.
- Bracken.
- That's perfect.
We've got to have that bibimbap.
- Let's get to work.
- All right.
It's as good as decided.
- Let's mix them up.
- The heavens want us to do that.
Let's do this.
- Let's go!
- All right!
TA-DA
I'll cook six eggs for six of us.
Go ahead.
- It has significance.
- Of course.
Are we using all the side dishes?
Yes.
- We've got to add sesame oil.
- Of course.
INGREDIENTS BECOME ONE
JUST LIKE THE HOUSEMATES
- Should I add eggs now?
- Yeah.
Here we go.
WITH 6 FRIED EGGS ON TOP
6-PEOPLE-6-INGREDIENTS BIBIMBAP
IS READY NOW
- Let's do the mixing over there.
- Shall we?
- Can we do that?
- Let's mix it together.
- Let's do it together.
- Okay.
- Just one.
- Okay, then.
2 HOURS UNTIL THEY RETURN TO SOLITUDE
We're all set.
ONE LAST MEAL IN GUGI-DONG
- Pretty impressive.
- This looks nice.
- Shall we?
- Let's mix it up.
- Can we?
- Let's get to work!
BRINGING THE ENERGY UP
TO HIDE THEIR SADNESS
It's a gourmet meal
for a leftover cleanup.
- Totally.
- Absolutely.
Just like us, right?
- They're becoming one.
- Blending in.
Yes, everything came together.
Who's the rice?
It's a great dish
but you rarely make it
when you're alone.
- You get too many portions.
- Exactly.
- You want to add many side dishes.
- You're right.
It even tastes different
when you eat off a large bowl
- rather than a small bowl.
- Totally.
So true.
We've got no clumps.
SOMEHOW GETS EMOTIONAL
WHILE TALKING ABOUT BIBIMBAP
You're doing great, Soo-jin.
- She's so thorough.
- Good job.
Not a single white clump in sight.
- That's how it should be, right?
- It's amazing.
The vest makes you look
like a restaurant employee.
NOT MISSING THE CHANCE
TO MAKE A SILLY JOKE
- No doubt the food will be amazing.
- For sure.
It just has to be.
You did such a fine job.
- All right.
- It's more than ready to serve.
- Bon appétit.
Turns out we didn't need fried eggs.
The egg soup is really nice.
- Your egg soup is amazing, Keun-suk.
- Is it good?
CHUCKLES
Dude, it's to die for.
- Is it the best?
- It's a killer. Try it.
All right.
- Take your favorite ingredients.
- Yes, we can do that.
THAT HITS THE SPOT
It's the full package.
I haven't heard that in a while.
SINGLE HARMONIOUS DISH
MADE UP WITH 6 SEASONED VEGETABLES
It's so good.
All the ingredients
come together nicely.
- Everything we had here was amazing.
- What?
All the dishes tasted amazing.
It's seasoned to perfection.
It's so good.
SILENCE FALLS
THEY HAVE NEVER BEEN THIS QUIET
DURING MEALTIME
DA-HEE KEEPS GLANCING OVER
AT THE LIVING ROOM
So this is our last meal together.
It makes you emotional, right?
It's just not sinking in.
Did you guys complete your card?
- Yeah.
- I did.
EARLIER, AFTER SEEING THE GUESTS OFF
What's this?
SOMETHING IS ON HIS BED
What is this?
"Your lease is up.
Please pack up your belongings
and vacate the room by midnight."
MOMENTS WHEN I WAS HAPPY
TO HAVE HOUSEMATES
MOMENTS WHEN I WAS DISTRESSED
"Lastly, please write a comment
for each housemate."
THEY CAREFULLY WROTE DOWN
ALL THE THINGS THEY DIDN'T GET TO SAY
SOME WERE OVERCOME WITH EMOTIONS
AND HAD TO COMPOSE THEMSELVES
THEY MADE PREPARATIONS
TO RETURN TO THEIR SOLITARY LIVES
It feels like our first day, right?
- My thought exactly.
- We're chatting, sure.
- But we're just being vague.
- Yeah.
Knowing this is the end
makes you look back
on our time together.
SILENCE CONTINUES
SNORTS OUT A LAUGH
GRINS
WHAT'S WITH THIS STRANGE AIR?
- Let's come up with something.
- Okay.
No one's talking.
Why do our conversations
keep fizzling out?
Am I the only person who finds this
worse than our first day?
- No, I'm with you there.
- Right?
We all get it.
But if we really dig into it
I will get emotional...
That's why I don't want to.
- I see.
- When one person gets touchy-feely
- it will spread to the whole group.
- Okay.
I'm sure we're all faking a smile
to avoid that.
TEAM FORTIES WANTS TO REMAIN CALM
So we're all on the same page.
What will it feel like
when we get home?
I'm wondering that, too.
The moment I lie on my couch
the silence around me
will feel so strange.
I've gotten used to hearing,
"Let's eat. What are you doing?"
HOUSEMATES FILLED THE LIVING ROOM
WITH LIVELINESS
I'd be surrounded by silence.
THE SILENCE AT THEIR OWN HOMES
WILL FEEL MORE DEAFENING
I might not feel at home
in my own home. You feel me, right?
Totally. It will feel unfamiliar.
Even in my own home.
When I was packing my stuff
I could just do it
without getting emotional.
When I looked up
I saw Da-hee taking her suitcase out.
Man, that really shook me up.
DO-YEON WAS RESTING
AFTER PACKING HER BELONGINGS
THEN, SHE SAW DA-HEE
CARRYING HER SUITCASE
THEY UNDERSTOOD EACH OTHER
THROUGH THAT ONE LOOK
She had her suitcase in her arms,
and our eyes met.
That's when it hit me.
"She's leaving.
I'm leaving, too.
We won't be roommates anymore."
It felt so strange.
"We won't be roommates anymore"?
What are you implying?
How else do I put it?
Just eat your bibimbap.
Let's get it out of our system
before we leave.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
Sure, we might as well cut ties.
- Good idea.
We won't miss each other then.
It's worse to leave things unclear.
When you phrase it that way,
we might have to go at it.
IF GUGI-DONG'S AHN-GEL
FEELS THAT WAY...
- Did you prepare a speech?
- Are you holding a grudge?
If Jae-hyeon demands it,
we have to do it.
- Of course.
- Oh, no.
- He meant it.
- I felt it, too.
Want to read the cards together?
Okay, let's go get them.
1 HOUR UNTIL THEY RETURN TO SOLITUDE
CLEARS THROAT
REACHES OUT
IRONCLAD DEFENSE
GRINS
This is hilarious.
We're keeping the cards covered
- to keep them secret.
- Yeah.
Everyone's feeling shy.
So shy.
EMBARRASSED TO GO OVER
THE CARDS TOGETHER
Let's make necessary changes
as we go along.
- Let's hear it.
- Da-hee can go first.
She wrote so much.
EVEN AT A GLANCE, THAT IS OBVIOUS
You did write a lot, Da-hee.
I SHOULD GET IT OVER WITH
BEFORE I TEAR UP
- I'll get right on it without fuss.
- Okay.
"Moments when I was happy
to have housemates.
Shared meals
all the little moments
that turned my daily life special
and the time shared together
on sleepless nights.
Moments when I was distressed
to have housemates.
Bathroom breaks, but I got over it."
- It's so simple.
- Yes.
- Totally.
- It's almost dry.
- You like it?
- I do.
I sure do.
Don't try anything funny
to make everyone tear up, okay?
- Yeah, don't do it.
- Okay, let's not do that.
No one's getting exiled.
- Right.
- Exactly.
- We can keep in touch, right?
- Of course.
"Lastly, please write a comment
for each housemate.
Do-yeon.
It was uncomfortable
and awkward at first
but you were my rock
throughout our journey."
THE VERY FIRST COMMENT
IS ABOUT TO SET HER OFF
IS HE TEARING UP?
SCRATCH, SCRATCH
My eyebrows feel itchy.
- What's going on?
- Sorry.
- What's with you?
- They're so itchy.
I CAN'T GO ON
DID SHE JUST RUN AWAY?
- What's with you?
- They're so itchy.
- Can I not show my face?
- Of course.
- Sure.
- Just your voice...
You can all read yours
at some other place.
- Just let us hear you.
- It can be embarrassing.
"Do-yeon.
It was uncomfortable
and awkward at first
but you were my rock
throughout our journey.
I was happy to have you
as my roommate...
and grateful..."
Oh, dear.
My brows are killing me.
THEY DO THEIR BEST NOT TO TEAR UP
"I will always remember
our time together.
Daniel.
Just when I was getting used
to your unfiltered chat
we have to part ways.
I now have a better grasp
on your unfiltered thoughts
and the person you are
and I'm grateful for that.
Your considerate and caring heart
made my stay in Gugi-dong
so comfortable
you wannabe comedian.
Keun-suk.
You made every moment special
living up to your nickname, AP.
It couldn't have always been easy
but you never let it show.
You were so dependable.
Open up a restaurant someday
with Soo-jin."
- We can call it "Sookeun Sookeun."
- Goodness.
"With Soo-jin."
THAT DRIED UP HER TEARS
- We can call it "Sookeun Sookeun."
- Goodness.
"Sookeun Sookeun."
WIPING THE TEARS
LOOK, HE'S CRYING AGAIN
PUFFY EYES
That's it for me.
BACK TO HER ORIGINAL SEAT
I would also like
to avoid making it emotional
just because it's our last day.
- Instead...
- Like you needed to ask.
- That's tacky!
- Don't do it.
Let's not be tacky.
We all live in Seoul.
Yeah, we all live in the city.
- Yeah.
- Right.
WHY ARE YOU CRYING, THEN?
Seriously.
- You know my style, right?
- Stay true to yourself.
- All right.
- Seriously.
"Do-yeon.
It looked like you usually skip meals
when you're out working.
I hope you'll try to eat healthy
when you return home today.
Daniel.
I get the feeling
you might talk to the wall
when you return home.
Don't do that. Hit me up instead."
Keun-suk's messages
are about the future.
- Right.
- Yeah.
AP LOOKS TOWARD THEIR FUTURE
"Da-hee. You are
the most meticulous of us all.
If I get the chance
I'd love to help you
with your House Squad Goal"
TOUCHED
Soo-jin is next.
"Soo-jin.
We won't be getting married."
Just like that?
DID HE JUST REJECT HER PROPOSAL?
"But if you need a drinking buddy,
I'll be there."
- That's the best.
- A rejection
- followed by an olive branch.
- Exactly.
I'LL GIVE HIM THAT
Last but not least, Jae-hyeon.
"My man, Jae-hyeon.
I just knew you'd be
such a great friend to me.
Thank you."
BESTIES JUST GET EACH OTHER
- Nice and neat.
- It is nice and neat.
"To me,
Six Singles Under One Roof was
not a single photo
but a roll of film."
Wow, so sleek.
THIS IS IT, AP STYLE
I predicted this, okay?
MAYBE HE IS SMITTEN?
- Thanks, guys.
- That was nice.
It was lovely. It was heartwarming.
That was nice.
You had our future in mind.
Let me wrap up this session.
LAST IS BRAVE DO-YEON
- I tried to keep it dry, too.
- Okay.
"Moments when I was happy
to have housemates.
Even when I was alone..."
- What's with you?
- What's up with her?
Don't be so dramatic.
Come on, Do-yeon.
I want to look away, too.
We got choked up, too.
We sucked it up and pulled through.
I'll stand over here
and read the rest out.
"Even when I was alone
I could feel a sense of connection
between us. I loved it."
Is no one home?
AS AN INTROVERT
DO-YEON STRUGGLED WITH BEING
AROUND THE HOUSEMATES THE MOST
BUT BEING ALONE ONCE AGAIN,
THE TEARS BEGIN TO FALL
What do I do?
- I'm sorry.
- What's wrong with you?
THEY HAVE LONG THOUGHT
THAT SOLITUDE GAVE THEM COMFORT
BUT PERHAPS THEY WERE
SIMPLY ACCUSTOMED TO IT
I'm going to read the rest
under the table, too.
- Under the table?
- Hey.
Let me start over.
Sorry, guys.
- No worries.
- What's going on?
It's okay.
I was so sure I wouldn't cry.
- I thought you wouldn't cry, too.
- Let me try again.
THE TIME TOGETHER HAS LEFT A MARK
DEEPER THAN ANY OF THEM HAD THOUGHT
"Moments when I was distressed
to have housemates.
I loved hanging out with them so much
that it threw off my daily routine."
That's cute.
It's pretty adorable.
When I try to read the newspaper,
I just can't focus
because I know
you guys are out the door.
"Jae-hyeon,
you have the kindest soul.
Your warm words
made me love our time here more.
Thank you.
Keun-suk.
You introduce yourself as a freak
but behind your wild gaze
is a young boy's innocence
and a generous heart
that finds joy in giving to others.
I learned so much from you.
Thank you, Keun-suk.
Soo-jin, you said
you've always wanted an older sister.
Your smiles are so lovely and warm.
I will cherish them in my memory.
Thank you.
Daniel, you said you thought
we might not get along that well.
But the moment you told me
I had crooked lips
I had crooked lips...
I sensed that we'd be
the best of friends.
Thank you for being my friend.
Just so you know,
my lips aren't crooked.
The problem is my jaw.
Last but not least
sweet Da-hee.
We practically had to share
our rooms and a bathroom.
I was sure we'd have
a bumpy ride ahead of us.
I can't pinpoint when,
but I found myself loving
your warm presence around me.
Thank you so much.
All the happiness I felt here
is all on you. I mean it.
Thank you so much.
All the happiness I felt here
is all on you. I mean it."
DA-HEE HAS TAUGHT DO-YEON
THE WARM COMPANIONSHIP
THAT ECLIPSES ANY DIFFICULTIES
OF SHARING LIVING QUARTERS
"To me,
Six Singles Under One Roof was
like Wi-Fi...
because we stayed connected."
That's it.
THE MOMENT THEY DECIDED
TO LIVE TOGETHER
- Why are you crying?
- I'm sorry.
THEY BECAME A FAMILY
UP NEXT IS SOO-JIN, THE YOUNGEST
"Moments when I was happy
to have housemates.
Shared meals
being taken care of while I was ill
and messing around together."
And next.
"Moments when I was distressed
to have housemates."
People call it the lonely crowd.
In all my years of living alone
I've never felt alone.
WHILE LIVING ALONE
THEY NEVER HAD TO FEEL LONELY
- Strangely enough
- I feel you.
when we were together
I felt more lonesome at times.
THEY HAVE FINALLY COME TO FEEL LONELY
"Jae-hyeon.
You're so tender..."
Sorry.
I got choked up for some reason.
This is hard for me.
"But you're a manly man
deep down inside."
I see you figured it out.
"Keun-suk.
Here's to our future."
- For real?
- Did you really write that down?
IT'S REAL
KEUN-SUK, HERE'S TO OUR FUTURE
MISCHIEVOUS SOO-JIN
HASN'T GIVEN UP YET
Moving on.
SOLEMN SILENCE FALLS AGAIN
Let's get going.
- Let's go.
- Shall we?
- We'd better.
- We should go.
- Okay.
- Let's leave without hesitation.
Are all your things packed up?
- Sure.
- Of course.
REMAINING TIME
UNTIL THEIR LEASE EXPIRES
30 MINUTES
We're all in our 40s
and we've been living together
for a while.
And before leaving,
we just read some letters.
But boy, did I cry a lot.
I figured it was just business.
Turns out we were all sincere.
When I'm at home
I'm rather like stainless steel.
I rarely have mood swings
or an occasion to put myself
in other people's shoes.
I never have to do something
for others either
because I'm alone.
But during my time here
I had so many moments
when my heart melted
and grew tender.
It was almost like
I became a living being
like a plant or an animal.
I think you turn
into a coward after 40.
You're hesitant
to open your heart to someone
or close it up again.
You're too afraid
to make those choices.
I was slowly losing the confidence
to open up my heart.
My housemates
gave me so much courage
and strength
to help me put myself out there.
KEUN-SUK FOUND THE COURAGE
TO OPEN UP AGAIN
Do you guys remember
that dance game we played
after trying Pu*p It Up?
- J*** Dance?
- Was that it?
Want to go out dancing
to leave things on a high note?
- How did the dance go?
- Something like this?
- Like so?
- Did we have this move?
- Let's go out with a bang.
- Let's do that!
That's the spirit.
LET'S LEAVE WITH A BIG SMILE
Let's not cry.
Seriously, guys.
A GROUP OF NEW FRIENDS
BY THE NAME OF GUGI-DONG FAMILY
HAS ENTERED THEIR SOLITARY DAYS
- Should I turn this off?
- Yeah.
BETWEEN SOLITUDE AND WILD NOISE
BETWEEN DISCOMFORT AND WARMTH
WILL WE EVER GET
TO LIVE TOGETHER AGAIN?
WE CAN DO THAT WHENEVER YOU'RE LONELY
STAY TUNED FOR AN EPILOGUE
I unknowingly cleared
another House Squad Goal.
- What?
- What is it?
- An album?
A FAMILY ALBUM FILLED WITH MEMORIES
PREPARED AS A PARTING GIFT
- That's crazy.
- It's literally a family album.
"First dinner for Gugi-dong fam."
That's cute. "Team Octopus for life."
How clever.
MEMORIES PLAY IN THEIR MINDS
LIKE FRAMES ON A FILM REEL
There's our highlight.
SLAPSTICK BROUGHT US TOGETHER
"This is what I'm talking about."
MEMORIES COMING BACK
Dude, I look so silly here.
PHOTOS OF DANIEL'S BIRTHDAY
Check out the photo with the cake.
When you look closely
- you can see tears in his eyes.
- Totally.
He got teary.
PHOTOS BECOME MEMORIES
Our time together was warm.
AND MEMORIES MADE THEM ONE
- "Odd eyes."
- Our time together brought me
unexpected joy,
touching moments, warmth
and dependable friends.
I'm glad I joined this show.
I've learned that small comforts
could be turning points
that change your life forever.
"Even if I could turn back time,
I wouldn't trade these memories.
Goodbye, my dear Gugi-dong fam."
That's the sign-off.
GOODBYE!
Subtitles by Jeongwoo Kim