♪Loving you is like being thrown
into a role without any preparation♪
♪I got immersed in the act
but I lost myself♪
♪It seems you've also sensed something♪
♪Playing along quietly♪
♪Loving you is like a distant wind
sweeping every corner♪
♪Simple yet unique♪
♪Even if I'm just a passerby, so what♪
♪Who cares if it's worth it♪
♪Giving you happiness
was enough, wasn't it♪
=Taking Love as a Contract=
=Episode 22=
(Don't think you'll have it easy)
Hi.
Can I help you?
I came specifically to tell you
some good news.
(Engagement Banquet,
Ji Chengxuan and Shen Yueran)
Engagement.
Why don't you two just get married?
Xia Tian,
looks like you are just jealous.
So are you coming or not?
Shen Yueran, are we familiar?
You're here to invite me
because you want
my gift money that badly?
Are you scared?
Yeah.
You're a mere bumpkin.
How could you possibly have the nerve
to come to my engagement party?
Yes, I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that I'll steal your thunder.
I'll be waiting for you.
Whether you bless or curse us,
you can't change anything.
I've had enough.
Shen Yue...
Hello, your delivery.
You're Xia Tian, right?
Chengxuan.
What took you so long?
I
went to invite the important guest
to our engagement party.
Okay, I know you have your reasons.
The engagement is set for tomorrow.
It might be a bit rushed time-wise,
but I did my best.
Chengxuan,
it's so good to have you around.
Order something.
You didn't order?
Nope, I've been waiting for you.
Waiter.
I'm just too pretty.
Xia Tian,
you're just a little bug.
Miss Shen,
Mr. Ji Chengxuan
was engaged with Miss He Shanyue
who's your cousin.
May I ask what happened
between you?
That was our grandpa making a mismatch.
Chengxuan and I are meant to be.
And only if I marry Chengxuan,
can the group...
Why is she here?
Yeah.
What is she doing here?
Ji Chengxuan.
What's it?
Ji Chengxuan,
you hired me to pretend to be He Shanyue
to help you seize
the He family's fortune.
Now you've realized
that marrying Shen Yueran
can help you get the fortune faster.
You're really marrying for money!
Xia Tian, what are you doing here?
I don't know. I just heard about it.
I forgot to introduce myself.
My name is Xia Tian.
I'm an unknown actor.
This one is my former employer.
And the other is my former sworn cousin.
So you know,
how could I not come
on their big day?
So that's how it is.
Xia Tian,
stop it.
Ji Chengxuan,
you said you would marry me,
but you abandoned me
and even pushed me
to the ground in my dream.
You're just a heartless man!
Miss He,
may I ask
if everything you just said is true?
Has Mr. Ji Chengxuan really done that?
Yes.
He had me impersonate He Shanyue
and toyed with me.
He is a hypocrite clothed
as a gentleman.
This bumpkin really pissed me off!
She ruined my plans.
That was the guest
you invited.
I asked her to come over and see
how perfect we are together.
What's wrong with that?
Now our scandal
is all over the Internet.
Are you happy now?
It's all because of you
being obsessed with that bumpkin.
That's why I did it.
Shen Yueran,
are you using me as your punching bag?
Chengxuan.
Chengxuan, I was wrong.
I was wrong.
I heard that the stock price fell,
so I was too anxious.
Who cares about the scandals?
When I sell the company,
we can take the money and go abroad
to live a carefree and comfortable life.
How about that?
The stock price has been halved
and you still want to sell it?
Tomorrow is the acquisition meeting.
I'm going to sell it no matter what.
What does it matter
if we lose some money?
That money
is enough for us
to live a carefree life together.
Hold me.
♪Unconsciously, I look at you♪
♪Your eyes are filled with stars♪
♪With only my reflection♪
♪The warm sea breeze kisses you♪
♪My longing makes me hold my breath♪
♪My mind is so certain♪
♪This love silently♪
♪Orbits the trajectory of stars♪
♪Hidden in the breath,
leaked through the eyes♪
♪Listen, the silent heart
awakens for you♪
♪I nearly missed the chance
to embrace you♪
♪Lies can't hide true feelings♪
♪Listen♪