♪Loving you is like being thrown
into a role without any preparation♪
♪I got immersed in the act
but I lost myself♪
♪It seems you've also sensed something♪
♪Playing along quietly♪
♪Loving you is like a distant wind
sweeping every corner♪
♪Simple yet unique♪
♪Even if I'm just a passerby, so what♪
♪Who cares if it's worth it♪
♪Giving you happiness
was enough, wasn't it♪
=Taking Love as a Contract=
=Episode 18=
(Would you let me be that 5% of you?)
Look over there.
Ji Chengxuan,
you're making me so embarrassed.
What are you doing?
Why? It's not embarrassing.
Come on.
What an ohnosecond.
So embarrassing.
Okay.
Calm down.
I can't calm down.
Calm down for a moment.
Don't do it.
Don't tell me you're going
to say you love me.
Go ahead.
Miss Xia Tian.
Broadcasting tone.
Don't laugh.
OK.
Again.
Miss Xia Tian,
maybe
our encounter
wasn't perfect.
It started with interests
and
was interspersed with countless lies.
Your acting is superb,
and I am
dominant.
Would someone speak about
himself like that?
Okay, be serious.
Continue.
I am dominant.
The two of us
are the most insincere
in the world,
but we are also
the most in-sync pair.
♪Unconsciously, I look at you♪
I have told you before.
Love only accounts for
ten percent of my life.
♪The warm sea breeze kisses you♪
But after you terminated the contract
and left the He family,
I realized that ten percent
is the most important in my life.
Without that ten percent,
the remaining 90 percent
becomes meaningless.
So, Xia Tian,
I want to use the rest of my life
to tell you one thing.
♪Listen♪
I love you.
Would you let me be
that five percent of you?
♪To keep gathering up
the courage to love♪
♪Don't worry. I have bet everything♪
♪To rush towards you♪
♪This love silently♪
♪Orbits the trajectory of stars♪
♪Hidden in the breath,
leaked through the eyes♪
♪Listen, the silent heart
awakens for you♪
♪I nearly missed the chance
to embrace you♪
♪Lies can't hide true feelings♪
♪Listen♪
♪From now on, I'll spend nights
by your side and have sweet dreams♪
♪My beloved, please allow me♪
♪To keep gathering up
the courage to love♪
♪Sky wakes, and stars are asleep♪
♪Memories of meeting you
replay in my head♪
♪The script unfolds♪
Is that okay?
♪I get it♪
♪In your world, will I be your love♪
♪I send my longings to the clouds♪
♪Wherever we end up doesn't matter♪
♪Your smile is home♪
♪Loving you is like being thrown
into a role without any preparation♪
♪I got immersed in the act
but I lost myself♪
♪It seems you've also sensed something♪
♪Playing along quietly♪
♪Loving you is like a distant wind
sweeping every corner♪
♪Simple yet unique♪
♪Even if I'm just a passerby, so what♪
♪Who cares if it's worth it♪
♪Giving you happiness
was enough, wasn't it♪
♪Loving you is like a distant wind
sweeping every corner♪
♪Simple yet unique♪
♪Even if I'm just a passerby, so what♪
♪Who cares if it's worth it♪
♪Giving you happiness
was enough, wasn't it♪
Mr. Ji.
Mr. Ji,
please have mercy
and let me sleep a bit longer.
Ji Chengxuan, Xia Tian,
how long do you plan to hide?
Grandpa,
all of this is my fault.
I hired Xia Tian to put on this act.
She disagreed with
deceiving you from the start.
It's not like that.
I wanted to make money.
I was the one who deceived you.
It has nothing to do with Chengxuan.
Now you know you were wrong.
What took you so long?
With these little tricks of yours,
do you think you can fool me?
I knew it all along.
Actually,
I'd been looking for Shan.
I'd searched nearly everywhere
at home and abroad,
and yet, I found no news of her.
Until a few years ago,
I received news
that she had died
in a car accident long ago.
So, over these years,
I've been very sad
and guilty.
I failed to protect her.
Later on,
you had her put on an act.
On one hand,
I wanted to make up for some regrets.
On the other hand,
considering
the company's situation back then,
I just played along
with you.
At first, I saw you as just an actor,
but I didn't expect
that you would be
so clever,
kind and filial.
After spending some time with you,
I didn't want to let you go,
so
I tampered with the DNA report
for you.
Shan,
no,
Xia Tian.
Since you've come,
stay.
This is your home.
We are all your family.
Let me ask you.
Do you want
to be my granddaughter?
♪Listen, the voice in my heart♪
♪Is so strong♪
Yes, I do.
♪It makes me want
to hold you even tighter♪
♪This time, let me
look at you more closely♪
♪It's you who came into my world♪
♪Telling me happiness
is actually easy to come by♪
♪The dreams where you exist
are irreplaceable♪
♪Seeing you until I wake up♪
♪Wait for the next shooting star♪
♪To fulfill the promise we made♪
♪We'll never part again♪
♪We'll no longer consider
maintaining any distance♪
♪I'm lying in your arms♪
♪You give me much courage♪
♪Wait for the next shooting star♪
♪I see the passage of time in your eyes♪
♪Travel with me♪
♪Forget about those deep
and elusive philosophies♪
♪Right now, it's just you and me♪