♪Loving you is like being thrown
into a role without any preparation♪
♪I got immersed in the act
but I lost myself♪
♪It seems you've also sensed something♪
♪Playing along quietly♪
♪Loving you is like a distant wind
sweeping every corner♪
♪Simple yet unique♪
♪Even if I'm just a passerby, so what♪
♪Who cares if it's worth it♪
♪Giving you happiness
was enough, wasn't it♪
=Taking Love as a Contract=
=Episode 8=
(Nothing happened last night)
♪Unconsciously, I look at you♪
♪Your eyes are filled with stars♪
♪With only my reflection♪
♪The warm sea breeze kisses you♪
♪My longing makes me hold my breath♪
♪My mind is so certain♪
♪This love silently♪
♪Orbits the trajectory of stars♪
♪Hidden in the breath,
leaked through the eyes♪
♪Listen, the silent heart
awakens for you♪
♪I nearly missed the chance
to embrace you♪
♪Lies can't hide true feelings♪
♪Listen♪
♪From now on, I'll spend nights
by your side and have sweet dreams♪
♪My beloved♪
♪Please allow me♪
♪To keep gathering up♪
♪The courage to love♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪I have bet everything♪
♪To rush towards you♪
♪This love silently♪
♪Listen, the silent heart
awakens for you♪
♪I nearly missed the chance
to embrace you♪
♪Lies can't hide true feelings♪
♪Listen♪
♪From now on, I'll spend nights
by your side and have sweet dreams♪
♪My beloved♪
♪Please allow me♪
♪To keep gathering up♪
♪The courage to love♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪I have bet everything♪
♪To rush towards you♪
What are you doing here?
This is my room.
Then how did I end up here?
Maybe you have a thing for me,
and sneaked in?
You wish.
Let me give you more details.
Last night, you…
Prepping for
Laba Festival dishes, Mrs. Yang?
Yeah.
Take a break.
I'll do the washing for you.
Perfect. I need that.
Nice to have some help.
So much of it.
It will be more than enough.
May I join?
Don't you want to know if you…
If I what?
Snored last night?
No, thanks.
What are you doing?
It's rainbow.
Like it?
It's alright.
Don't worry.
Nothing happened last night.
However,
I've recorded funny videos of someone
sleeping weirdly.
Ji Chengxuan.
What's wrong with you?
Give me the phone now.
No.
Come on.
Never.
You better delete it.
No way.
It's not fair.
I'm not in the mood.
I'll soak you.
Just delete it, okay?
That's the story.
There's this old lady,
all alone,
looking after the house
her late husband built,
only with memories left.
She just can't let it go.
And then there's you,
the cold-hearted business person,
trying to take away people's lives
with a tough demolition plan,
stripping away someone else's memories
for 20% above market price.
Either change her situation
or change your mind.
You don't have to do that.
I can change the proposal.
Do you mean…?
Did you know all along
that Mrs. Yang didn't want to move
because she wanted to
keep the memories with Mr. Yang?
I've done my research.
I'm wondering,
does anyone
still have a lifelong love
like Mrs. Yang's these days?
When I was a kid,
I dreamt of being a captain,
steering my own ship
on an adventure.
Now, I just want to
inherit the family business
and take charge of He's Group.
Making fighting for family inheritance
your life goal?
Seriously?
He's Group's situation
is way more complicated than you think.
I get it.
Anyway,
love isn't
part of your life plan, right?
Maybe 10%, tops.
Aren't you the same?
True.
I've got to take care of my grandma,
and buy back our ancestral house.
No time for love.
It's like 5%
for me.
We really are the same kind of people.
♪Sky wakes, and stars are asleep♪
♪Memories of meeting you
replay in my head♪
♪The script unfolds♪
♪I play the imperfect role♪
♪I get it♪
♪In your world, will I be your love♪
♪I send my longings to the clouds♪
♪Wherever we end up doesn't matter♪
♪Your smile is home♪
♪Loving you is like being thrown
into a role without any preparation♪
♪I got immersed in the act
but I lost myself♪
♪It seems you've also sensed something♪
♪Playing along quietly♪
♪Loving you is like a distant wind
sweeping every corner♪
♪Simple yet unique♪
♪Even if I'm just a passerby, so what♪
♪Who cares if it's worth it♪
♪Giving you happiness
was enough, wasn't it♪