♪Loving you is like being thrown
into a role without any preparation♪
♪I got immersed in the act
but I lost myself♪
♪It seems you've also sensed something♪
♪Playing along quietly♪
♪Loving you is like a distant wind
sweeping every corner♪
♪Simple yet unique♪
♪Even if I'm just a passerby, so what♪
♪Who cares if it's worth it♪
♪Giving you happiness
was enough, wasn't it♪
=Taking Love as a Contract=
=Episode 16=
(I'm a liar, and I don't deserve it)
Hello.
It's me.
My grandma's gone?
Where did she go?
(7 days later)
(Mourn)
(Xia Tian,)
(you aren't coming around)
(to see me as much lately.)
(Now you aren't gonna call me)
(unless I call you first?)
(Grandma, I've got something
to do right now.)
(I'll get back to it
and call you back later.)
I know.
I know it's a huge shock to you
that your grandma suddenly passed away.
I also know
that whatever anyone says now
won't help.
But Xia Tian,
you need to get through
this on your own.
Your grandma must also hope
that you can continue to live well.
You thought I wanted to commit suicide?
I just found myself
really good at acting.
I lied to my grandma,
saying I took on a big project,
and that the house was still there.
And in the end,
I was still lying to her.
Shen Yueran was right.
I kept on acting.
Now even heaven couldn't stand watching.
This is my retribution.
You should believe
your grandma would not blame you.
But I can't forgive myself.
Ji Chengxuan,
I don't want to act anymore.
Let's end
our contract.
I'm going to say farewell to Grandpa.
Shan,
come here and see
what I prepared for you.
Shan,
I heard about
your grandmother's death.
I'm grieved too.
She raised you with much hardship,
and look how smart, kind,
gorgeous
and graceful
you've become.
I am happy about it.
It's just a pity
that I didn't get to thank her
in person.
I know
you must be feeling terrible.
I don't know how to comfort you.
I can only give you these mundane things
to make you feel better.
I'm not sure if you like them.
Shan,
don't cry.
Don't worry.
I will take extra good care of you
and cherish you twice
as much as your grandma would.
Grandpa, I am not He Shanyue.
My name is Xia Tian.
I've deceived you all.
I am just a liar.
I don't deserve your love.
♪The greeting gaze of a stranger♪
♪It accompanies you
in your loneliness instead of me♪
♪The starry sky reflected in your eyes♪
♪It's the wish in your heart♪
♪A past filled with tears and sorrow♪
♪With a relieved heart as a bonus gift♪
Mr. Qin.
I've already told Mr. He
the truth.
I've already left
the He family.
That's pretty good.
It's not too late.
It's already too late.
The cost is too great.
Can I buy you a cup of hot chocolate?
I thought
you never wanted to see me again.
Do you
still remember
last time, at this same place perhaps,
I told you
to keep things real?
Actually, my words
were quite harsh that day.
I'm sorry.
But my intention was really
for the company's good.
I know.
Since you've left the He family,
why don't you go home?
Now,
I don't have a home.
What about him?
We have already ended our collaboration.
It's good that music can take you in.
I'll go get you chocolate.
♪Sky wakes, and stars are asleep♪
♪Memories of meeting you
replay in my head♪
♪The script unfolds♪
♪I play the imperfect role♪
♪I get it♪
♪In your world, will I be your love♪
♪I send my longings to the clouds♪
♪Wherever we end up doesn't matter♪
♪Your smile is home♪
♪Loving you is like being thrown
into a role without any preparation♪
♪I got immersed in the act
but I lost myself♪
♪It seems you've also sensed something♪
♪Playing along quietly♪
♪Loving you is like a distant wind
sweeping every corner♪
♪Simple yet unique♪
♪Even if I'm just a passerby, so what♪
♪Who cares if it's worth it♪
♪Giving you happiness
was enough, wasn't it♪