=Hot Blooded=
=Episode 22=
Kang.
Where are we going?
We're almost there.
Nianci.
These three are the elders
of Beggars' Gang.
They are Elder Jian,
Elder Peng, and Elder Liang.
Greetings, Elders.
No need to be so formal, Miss Mu.
I heard Chief Hong
guided you.
So you should be
a member of our gang.
Given our relationship
with Mr. Yang,
there's no need for such formality.
You...
I've decided to join the Beggars' Gang.
Really?
Does Miss Mu object?
Mr. Yang is a young hero.
If he joins us,
that would be fortunate
for our gang.
Miss Mu, please agree.
Why would I disagree?
The Beggars' Gang is
the largest gang in the world.
Qigong mentored me and showed me kindness.
If you can accept Kang,
I'd be most grateful.
Of course I'll agree.
From now on,
I'll fulfill my dreams
and ambitions in the Beggars' Gang.
I won't let you down
or worry again.
It's wonderful to hear that.
Elders,
please guide Kang
in the future.
Of course.
Today,
in front of the elders
and the Beggars' Gang brothers,
I want to do something I've longed for.
Nianci.
I know you've suffered a lot
along the way with me.
No matter what happened,
you've always been
by my side.
From today on,
let me protect you.
I've owed you too much.
Let me
stay by your side to repay my debt, okay?
Okay.
Elders,
tonight is the Beggars' Gang Assembly.
There no time like the present.
I wish to marry Nianci today.
Will that be good?
Good! Good ! Good!
(Double Happiness)
(Qinxin Pavilion)
- Father.
- Kang.
How is it?
The location of the Book of Wumu
records in this painting.
This...
I got this painting
from Guo Jing and Huang Rong.
These words
must record the location
of the Book of Wumu.
(Book of Wu)
Middle Peak of Iron Palm Mountain?
It's in Master Qiu's
Iron Palm Mountain.
That would be easier.
Kang.
You've made another great contribution.
For Father's career,
I will do anything.
Good boy.
Now,
there's another important task
for you.
What's that?
The Beggars' Gang has always been
our enemy in the North of Yangtze River.
When our army advances south,
the Beggars' Gang
will attack our leaders
and burn our supplies.
I have been constantly troubled,
with no solution in sight.
If we can make the Beggars' Gang
move to the south,
it would save us
a lot of trouble.
No one knows a father better than his son.
After tonight,
I'll be the chief of the Beggars' Gang.
Then, I'll arrange for them
to migrate south.
But I just took over and my foundation
is unstable.
I'm afraid they won't obey me.
Don't worry.
I'll send people to support you.
Thank you, Father.
Where is my Ke?
Mr. Ouyang?
Greetings, Mr. Ouyang.
May I ask what are you doing here?
Prince,
where is my Ke?
Mr. Ouyang Ke?
I went to get the Book of Wumu.
You were supposed to look after Ke.
How could you not know where he is?
Mr. Ouyang, you never returned
when you left that day.
I thought you went to search for
Mr. Ouyang Ke.
When I reached Niujia Village,
Ke was gone.
Maybe Mr. Ouyang Ke
left first?
Impossible.
I can't even
see our secret signals
we use.
He might have been killed.
I left Niujia Village
and went to the Iron Palm Gang.
I don't know where Mr. Ouyang Ke is.
You can't even protect Ke.
You are of no use to me anymore.
It was Guo Jing!
I saw that at Qu Tavern
that day.
Guo Jing killed Mr. Ouyang Ke.
Kang...
Mr. Ouyang Ke harassed Huang Rong.
Guo Jing held a grudge
and killed him
when he didn't notice.
If you lie to me, you'll wish you were dead.
If I lie,
may I die from
Mr. Ouyang's poison.
It's my fault.
I couldn't defeat Guo Jing
and watched
Mr. Ouyang Ke
being...
Being...
Wait, Mr. Ouyang.
Guo Jing and Huang Rong are in my hands.
I got this Beggars' Gang
token from Huang Rong.
I planned to kill them
at midnight at Xuanyuan Terrace,
Junshan Island
to avenge Ke.
But I have one more request.
Please agree.
After Mr. Ouyang Ke passed away,
I realized that without skills,
one can be easily harmed
in the martial world.
I am about to become
the chief of the gang.
It's like walking on thin ice.
I've long admired you
and wish to be your apprentice,
learning martial arts
to unite the Beggars' Gang.
If you take Kang as your apprentice,
the Beggars' Gang
and the Mount White Camel will be close.
My son and I
will try our best
and help your manor
become the most powerful in the martial world.
Master, please accept my kowtow.
I will
avenge your nephew!
You two sleep soundly.
Elder Peng,
Jing and I are both
Qigong's apprentices.
So,
we are peers.
Aren't you afraid of Qigong's wrath
for tying us up with no reason.
You rebellious apprentices
dare to mention
Chief Hong?
We'll end your lives
at tonight's Beggars' Gang Assembly
to comfort Chief Hong
in heaven.
No one believes you,
old man...
Enough.
(Double Happiness)
It's not the time yet.
Why are you here now?
On the wedding night,
only when the groom
lifts the bride's veil
are they truly married.
Nianci.
I can't wait.
You should go to the assembly.
Don't delay.
I'll wait for you.
Okay.
I'll come for you
after the assembly.
You should go.
(Beggars' Gang Central Altra)
Brothers!
Tragedy has struck the Beggars' Gang.
Chief Hong
was attacked in Lin'an City!
What's wrong with Chief Hong?
Chief Hong
has passed away.
- Who killed Chief Hong?
- Yes.
We'll avenge Chief Hong!
Elder Peng,
who witnessed
Chief Hong's death?
If Chief Hong is still alive,
who has the nerve
to curse him?
The witness who saw Chief Hong's death
is right here.
Who is it?
Mr. Yang, please come here.
Brothers!
I am Yang Kang.
I witnessed Huang Yaoshi,
Master of Peach Blossom Island,
Eastern Heretic,
his daughter Huang Rong,
and son-in-law Guo Jing
killing Chief Hong!
Miss Huang and Brother Guo
are Chief Hong's apprentices.
Why would they kill him?
Huang Rong and Guo Jing eloped.
But Huang Yaoshi got angry
at Qigong
and attacked him.
They fought for a long time.
But to please Old Heretic Huang,
Guo Jing ambushed
and killed Chief Hong.
Nonsense!
Chief Hong and Master Huang
were friends.
Why would they kill each other
over such a trivial matter?
If Huang Yaoshi wanted to
gain an advantage
in Duel atop Mount Hua,
wouldn't he eliminate his rival first?
Elder Lu,
even if you don't believe him,
you can't deny
this token.
If the chief hadn't given it willingly,
who could have taken it
from him?
Since Chief Hong gave the token to Mr. Yang,
it's clear that
he intended for Mr. Yang
to succeed
as the chief.
Brothers!
We have two major tasks now.
First,
follow the Chief Hong's last wish
and appoint a new chief.
Second,
let's discuss
how to avenge
Chief Hong.
Appoint a new chief!
Avenge Chief Hong!
- Brothers!
- Appoint a new chief!
Listen to me!
When Chief Hong
was alive,
he intended for Elder Lu
to be the new chief.
Today,
an outsider wants to take over?
I say
Elder Lu should be the chief!
Elder Lu! Elder Lu!
Elder Lu!
Tell your
Dirty Clothes Faction to stop!
Is the Beggars' Gang Assembly
not open for discussion?
You...
Brothers of the Dirty Clothes Faction.
In terms of virtue,
martial arts,
and popularity,
Elder Lu
is most suitable as the new chief.
But with Chief's token here
and his last wish,
we must follow it.
If any brothers
have doubts,
please come up and have a look.
Recently, Mr. Yang has been wielding this staff
in Yuezhou, rallying support.
I thought it was just talk
and ignored it.
But now,
Mr. Yang dared to come here.
I must take a good look.
Since
it's Chief Hong's last wish,
how can we disobey?
I, Lu Youjiao,
pledge to support Mr. Yang
as the 19th chief of the Beggars' Gang!
Since Elder Lu has no objections,
neither do
the three of us.
Four Elders,
I'm not that talented
and virtuous,
unworthy of this responsibility.
Since it's Chief Hong's last wish,
you don't have to underestimate yourself.
We'll help you
handle the gang's affairs.
Mr. Yang, don't worry.
Mr. Yang!
Mr. Yang can be the chief!
It's settled then.
Mr. Yang.
Don't let Chief Hong
and the brothers down.
I can't refuse such kindness.
Since that's the case,
I will accept.
Brothers.
Please welcome Mr. Yang
to the initiation ceremony.
To Xuanyuan Terrace, please!
(Xuanyuan Terrace)
Chief Yang, please don't be mad.
This is a tradition of our gang.
When a new chief is appointed,
he must endure spitting from the members.
As beggars, we face
humiliation from all.
So, as the chief of beggars,
one must endure humiliation from members.
I see.
Chief Yang,
please don't mind us.
That's okay.
Now I'm a member of the gang,
so I should follow the rules.
This is Chief Yang,
19th chief of the Beggars' Gang!
Chief Yang!
Although the main culprits
of killing Chief Hong
have not been caught,
two accomplices
have been captured.
Bring them up.
Kill them! Kill them!
They betrayed Chief.
That's a grave sin.
Tonight,
I'll kill these two rebellious apprentices
for the soul of Chief Hong!
There must be
some misunderstanding.
Yes. Chief Yang.
I met them
in Baoying.
They are righteous
young heroes.
I can bet
my soul on it
that they had nothing to do
with Chief Hong's death.
Only Elders can speak here.
You can't interrupt!
Chief,
this involved the serious matter of the gang.
Please investigate thoroughly.
Investigate thoroughly!
Lu Youjiao!
You pledged to support the new chief.
Now why do you
defy his orders?
Investigate thoroughly!
Since the Dirty Clothes Faction
has doubts,
I'll ask them directly
to clear things up.
I'll ask your questions
but you don't need to speak it out.
Nod if
I am right.
Shake your head if I am wrong.
If you lie,
don't blame my sword.
This woman is Huang Yaoshi's daughter,
right?
Hey!
Answer Chief Yang!
This woman is Huang Yaoshi's daughter,
right?
You want to marry her,
but Huang Yaoshi doesn't want to
marry his daughter to you,
right?
Chief Huang was ambushed
and gravely injured
with you two present,
right?
Kill him! Kill him!
They admit their guilt directly.
We should give them
a swift end.
Kill them! Kill them!
Decapitate!
Look!
What's that?
Elders.
What's this?
An important guest is here.
Who?
Iron Palm Gang.
Chief,
The Iron Palm Gang is a major faction
in Sichuan and Hunan.
Their master is here to pay tribute.
We must welcome him properly.
Chief,
we can deal with
these two later.
Alright.
Master Qiu, welcome. Your presence honors us.
I heard
Chief Hong passed away?
Yes.
The world lost a hero.
I have never dueled with him.
What a pity.
Master Qiu.
let me introduce him to you.
He is our new chief
appointed today.
A young hero.
Congratulations to you.
I've long heard of Master Qiu.
Seeing you today,
I understand why people call you
Iron Palm Water Skimmer.
Master Qiu, may I ask
what brings you here today?
Our gangs have long
fought over territory.
I heard Chief Yang
is taking over tonight,
so I bring you a great gift
on someone else's behalf
to apologize.
I also want to
ask you an important question.
Master Qiu,
I'm afraid we can't accept
such a great gift from you.
I mean I was acting for someone else.
Didn't you hear?
The Sixth Prince of Jin asked me
to give these to you.
What did he mean?
I don't know.
We can't accept that.
Don't worry.
I'll send people
to support you.
Is the important question you mentioned
also from the Sixth Prince?
The Sixth Prince told me,
the north
is poor and barren,
not suitable for expansion.
He hopes...
He hopes our gang
move to the south of the Yangtze River.
Exactly.
The north is harsh
compared to the warm and rich south.
Your gang could rest in the south.
Everyone will be envied.
Master Qiu and the Prince's suggestion
is exactly what I want to do.
Our gang leads a modest life
and suffers in the cold weather.
Moving to the south
would ease our hardships.
So,
Chief Yang agrees to
move the gang to the south,
never to return to the north?
Chief.
Think it over!
Chief Hong was known as the Northern Beggar.
People know our gang's stronghold in the north.
How can we abandon everything?
Besides, our gang has been loyal and brave.
The Jins are our enemies.
We can't accept their gifts,
let alone move to the south
of the Yangtze River!
Elder Lu,
we should listen to the chief,
not you, right?
Elders,
what do you think?
We will follow Chief's lead
and won't disobey.
Alright.
We'll move to the south
on August, 1st!
How can we move?
Move to the south?
But our home is here.
Even if you are determined,
I won't go!
Lu Youjiao!
Are you trying
to defy the chief?
Even if I am dismembered,
I will not betray the chief.
But I can't disregard
the teachings of our ancestors!
Our gang has hundreds of thousands of members,
spreading across the world.
How can we be confined by the Jins?
You defy Chief's orders.
You must intend to
split our gang
after failing to become the chief.
Lu Youjiao, if you want to rebel,
you must first ask the members
behind me if they agree.
No!
The new chief
is collaborating with the Jins
to destroy our foundation.
Brothers, don't be fooled!
Our gang
has always
fought for justice
and protected the people.
Who are you really working for?
Brothers!
Master Qiu is here
for the sake of our gang's future.
I know it's hard for you
to accept moving to the south.
But don't worry.
As long as I'm here...
Yang!
How can we let our great land
be taken by enemies?
I don't accept you
- as the chief!
- You...
We, the Beggars' Gang,
would rather die than be traitors!
We can't be traitors!
(The Seven Stars transformation)
(is similar to the grand formation)
(of Quanzhen School.)
Rong. I got it.
Jing.
You got what?
I considered Tiangang Big Dipper Formation
of Seven Immortals of Quanzhen
and found it's connected to
the Nine Yin Manual.
So, I combined the seven's strength into one
according to the manual.
I didn't expect it to be so powerful.
That's great, Jing.
Do you
accpet that or not?
Just kill me.
Okay.
Brother Guo, don't underestimate him.
Master Qiu.
Since you are here,
how can we let him mess around?
(He is quite skilled.)
(Duel atop Mount Hua is approaching.)
(I don't have to waste energy on him.)
- Rong.
- Jing.
Master Qiu.
Please kill these thieves.
I'll reward you generously.
After we ambush the Mongol envoys,
I hope Master Qiu
can go to Yuezhou
and assist my son, Kang.
No problem.
Thank you, Master Qiu.
I'll take my leave.
Brother!
How was my performance?
Wasn't it impressive?
A bit over-the-top and exaggerated.
Impossible.
I must have looked imposing.
It's fine.
Duel atop Mount Hua is approaching.
I need to focus on training
and don't want to be bothered.
I'll leave the assassination
of the Mongol envoys to you.
Really?
Great!
Fighting may occur with the Beggars' Gang.
I'll go in person.
That's not necessary.
I think you can
(Qiu Qianzhang/ Qiu Qianren)
leave it to me.
I'll take good care of it.
You will ruin my plans.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because a loser
can always be a loser.
Yes.
I know
what to do
and what not to do.
It's not for you to tell me.
Chief Yang is appointed tonight.
You should assert your authority.
I can't steal your thunder.
Elders.
We have many heroes here.
We can't let him look down on us.
Chief, don't worry.
We won't let an outsider look down on us.
All members!
Fortified Wall Formation!
He has indeed learned
Chief Hong's whole set palm technique.
We must put an end
to both of their lives.
Kill them
and avenge Chief Hong!
Jing, give me a hand.
Let me show you the real
Beggars' Gang martial arts.
That's Untroubled Ease Palm.
The authentic Untroubled Ease Palm!
Wanyan Kang,
you want to be the chief of the Beggars' Gang?
Brothers!
Chief Hong isn't dead.
He is a Jin Prince, spreading rumors
and plotting to seize power.
Nonsense!
Brothers!
Don't be swayed by our enemy!
You said one month ago,
Qigong was ambushed during a duel.
But one month ago,
I was with Qigong.
He was perfectly fine,
eating at least three Beggar's Chickens a day.
He had a great appetite
and was in good health.
Qigong is alive!
Chief asked you to catch them.
What are you waiting for?
How could
the mighty Beggars' Gang
be fooled by a little girl?
Brothers! Look!
Qigong's Dog Beating Staff
is in my hand.
I'm the chief personally appointed
by Qigong.
You snatched the staff
of our gang from me.
Everyone saw that clearly.
Wanyan Kang,
you claim the Dog Beating Staff is yours.
Do you know how to use it?
You keep calling it Dog Beating Staff.
How dare you belittle this staff?
You deserve to be punished.
As the chief of the Beggars' Gang,
you just call it "staff".
What?
Are you looking down on our Dog Beating Staff?
Or don't you know
it's the Dog Beating Staff?
Because you stole it
from me?
Simply holding the Dog Beating Staff
doesn't make someone the chief.
If it were kept in a cupboard,
would the cupboard become the chief?
We've already appointed Chief Yang.
How can we let an outsider insult him?
Brothers!
Our gang travels the world,
but today we've been humiliated.
Who caused Li Sheng and Yu Zhaoxing
to be killed?
Who injured Elder Lu?
Who is forcing us to move to the south?
Shut up!
How can we let a little girl
boss us around here?
Brothers!
He intends to destroy our Song Dynasty.
His surname isn't Yang.
He is Wanyan,
the son of Prince Zhao of Jin Empire!
♪I wander in the martial world♪
♪I drink a thousand cups of wine
and sing to the sky♪
♪Life and death intertwined♪
♪Leaning against the railing and shouting♪
♪Stars and moon over the wild expanse♪
♪Longbows shooting toward the distant sun♪
♪We meet in mountains and rivers♪
♪Rushing through narrow paths♪
♪I wander through the martial world♪
♪All glitz mere illusions♪
♪Cutting off all debts♪
♪Only the shadows of swords
and gleaming blades can be seen♪
♪Fearless, undaunted♪
♪The marial world is a lifetime of daring♪
♪Who knows my dreams and ambitions♪
♪Wakening to find them as distant dreams♪
♪The road ahead is long♪
♪The path is vast and grand♪
♪Thousands of dreams span ages♪
♪Whirling and swirling♪
♪Ask the youth what it means♪
♪Heroes face all challenges♪
♪True to their hearts♪
♪Or lost in the dust♪
♪The road ahead is long♪
♪The path is vast and grand♪
♪People in the world varied and numerous♪
♪Whirling and swirling♪
♪Who truly understands♪
♪Heroes face all challenges♪
♪Searching to truly grasp♪
♪Only then do they discern♪
♪Achievements and mistakes are transient♪
♪To the end, yet steps persist♪
♪We can feel pain and also joy♪
♪We can charge forward or retreat♪
♪No need to look back♪
♪Rush through wind and clouds,
shake the universe♪
♪No matter the journey's length♪
♪Entering the martial world♪
♪I fear not the endless journey♪