=Hot Blooded=
=Episode 19=
Give it to me.
Easy.
(I've always scorned tradition and rituals.)
(But when it comes to Rong,)
(I've become more worldly.)
(How pathetic.)
Grandmaster,
this place is deserted.
We got some food from the nearby village.
Please have a bite.
Grandmaster,
don't you like these dishes?
Senior, I'll go make some other dishes.
Miss Cheng,
do you want to marry him?
- Grandmaster...
- Time passes quickly.
If you want to marry him, just do it.
If you want to marry him,
marry him now.
Tie the knot and head to the bridal chamber!
In times of crisis,
you both are willing to risk your lives
for each other.
In this world,
where can you find
such a good match?
My marriage
should be decided by my father.
That's not necessary.
If you two are in love,
today,
I'll agree to your marriage.
Guanying,
what do you think?
Grandmaster,
I'm not worthy of Miss Cheng.
You are an apprentice of Peach Blossom Island.
Not worthy?
I'm not skilled in martial arts,
and I'm not talented.
- And I...
- And?
Grandmaster, I know it's my great luck
to meet her here.
If I can marry her...
You're talking too much.
Do you want to marry me?
I...
I do.
Silly girl.
They'll bow to Heaven and Earth.
Bow to Heaven and Earth!
Shagu loves seeing
people bow to Heaven and Earth!
Bow to Heaven and Earth!
Miss... Miss Cheng.
You can consider today's
wedding ceremony a joke,
just to make
my grandmaster happy.
He always does things like this.
Let's put on
a good show.
Once he's done,
I'll send you back.
Mr. Lu,
do you really think this is just a joke
to make your grandmaster happy?
Don't take me wrong, Miss Cheng.
But...
At this moment,
I hope it's true.
Me... Me too.
Your grandmaster's flute
sounds nice.
Miss Cheng, don't listen to it.
This tune is odd.
Mr. Lu...
I can't believe my father.
He says he doesn't care about rituals.
But when it comes to my marriage,
he sets three challenges.
Jing!
Your breathing is erratic.
Calm down and stay focused.
Rong.
I don't know why.
My heart is racing.
Jing.
Don't move.
Or you'll lose control of your inner power.
I feel so hot.
I can't control myself.
Hang in there, Jing.
I'm sorry, Rong.
I don't know why this is happening.
This tune makes me...
It's not your fault, Jing.
Stay calm.
Or you won't withstand
Emerging Waves from the Dark Blue Sea.
I'm hungry.
I'm starving.
Who are you?
Did you stay here all night last night?
I... I...
I arrived here
before you.
I didn't mean to.
Have you been seeing us all night?
I didn't see anything.
And... And you two
didn't do anything last night.
Why did you stay silent and watch us
all night?
Sir,
Ma'am,
I'm not a local.
I'm handicapped.
I just wanted to find a tavern
but stumbled upon bandits.
They knocked me out,
and I was unconscious for a few days.
Why were you silent all of last night?
You came in all of a sudden.
I thought you were
with the bandits.
So I didn't dare to speak.
Sir,
Ma'am,
I've been hungry for days.
I'm dizzy and faint.
Please, give me
something to eat.
Guanying...
The young venomous creature
was in the side room.
They were careless.
They didn't find him
all night.
Will the
young venomous creature harm Mr. Lu
and Miss Cheng?
Hard to say.
Don't rush. Take your time.
We have more.
How long have you been not eaten?
What he's doing...
I didn't realize
you were in such dire straits,
yet you are a neat man.
To be honest,
I value cleanliness
and fragrant things
the most.
I've been tortured
in these past few days.
Since you've had
a good meal,
we'll leave.
Wait.
Why the rush?
You saved my life.
So
I must repay you.
This flower is my treasure.
It's beautiful in color.
(This flower looks familiar.)
But it withers shortly
after being picked
like a beauty.
Isn't that right,
Miss Cheng?
How do you know my wife's surname?
Guanying,
he is Ouyang Ke,
the lecher.
Let go of my husband!
Miss Cheng,
put down your sword.
Or
I don't know
what I might do.
Let him go!
Drop the sword.
It smells so good.
Shameless.
I am shameless.
On my worst night,
you let me see
a bridal chamber scene.
Since you gave me
a good show,
I'll return the favor
for Mr. Lu tonight.
Courtesy demands reciprocity.
Please let my husband go.
Miss Cheng, why are you sweating?
Why don't you
take off some clothes
to cool down?
What did you say?
Make me happy,
and I'll let you go immediately.
But if I'm unhappy,
I don't know what I might do.
Take them off.
Take them off!
That lecher!
Let's go out and kill him.
We can't move now.
Aren't we doing nothing?
If we rush out,
we'll waste our efforts
and get injured.
We won't save Miss Cheng,
and we'll lose our lives.
Then what should we do?
I want watermelon!
Shagu wants to wash clothes
for the pretty girl.
Shagu loves washing clothes
and water.
Your clothes are dirtier. Take them off too.
Get away, lunatic.
You're the lunatic.
I won't wash it then.
Men are so mean.
The girl eating watermelon...
The girl eating watermelon!
The girl eating watermelon?
The girl eating watermelon,
do you want to wash clothes?
The weather is sunny today,
a good day for washing clothes.
Let's change to using one palm now.
The girl eating watermelon!
Take off your clothes.
I'll wash them.
The girl eating watermelon!
Say something.
The girl eating watermelon?
Could there be
a girl hiding in here?
Is there another way
to access this secret room?
No.
No?
I won't tell you.
The girl eating watermelon and the big brother
are secretly eating watermelon inside.
Shagu,
listen.
There's no sound inside.
They must have suffocated
in this room.
We need to open it and save them.
Shagu can't say.
Sister Watermelon told me not to say.
Shagu, we should save them.
There are many ways to die,
but suffocating is the worst.
Think about it. We'll open the door
and find that the people inside stink.
Bugs will start to grow.
Wouldn't that be scary?
Right?
They can't be suffocated.
They'll suffocate inside.
Yes, save them.
- Save them. Save them.
- Save them.
Isn't that my Sister Rong?
The girl eating watermelon
is you.
We really have a deep connection.
What?
Are you healing Guo Jing?
Rong,
even if he survives, he'll be crippled.
But you're young.
Why do you have to
marry a cripple?
What do you think?
Rong, you're usually so sharp-tongued.
Why aren't you speaking today?
Can't speak while channeling internal energy?
Then can you move?
Do you need my help?
Come on.
Let's continue.
I don't believe
you can heal
while I'm staying here.
I'll force you
lose control of your inner power.
Bullying a cripple?
That's all you got?
My uncle will be back soon.
I'll wait for you outside.
Jing!
Let's switch back to using both palms.
A hedgehog.
A hedgehog!
You become a hedgehog.
Stop that!
A hedgehog!
Still smells good.
Haste makes waste.
I'd better
not waste this.
Is anyone there?
Miss,
you...
Good things come in pairs.
Good things come in pairs!
Miss Mu.
Last time I went back to find you,
you were taken by someone else.
Now we meet again.
This is destined by heaven.
Brother Ke.
You're quite busy.
Young prince?
Brother Ke, why are you alone?
It's a long story.
I've had bad luck
and ended up alone.
But I didn't expect...
Young prince.
Sorry, I didn't see it.
Is this Miss Mu
your lover?
If she's yours,
I'll give her back to you.
We are friends.
Let's not fight
over a woman.
She was my lover.
But now,
I no longer care
about romance.
You don't
care about romance.
Really?
I was troubled by love recently,
feeling uneasy.
But seeing you
treat women as playthings,
it suddenly enlightened me.
That's great.
Young prince, are you mocking me?
No.
Working together,
we can achieve greatness.
If you want
this woman,
she's yours.
Consider it a small gift for the Ouyang family
of Mount White Camel.
Their conversation
makes me sick.
I thought
Yang Kang was just greedy for power.
I didn't realize
he was so despicable.
Ke,
your uncle rules the martial world
and my father commands troops.
If we join forces,
not only can we can enjoy ourselves,
but also stir the world
and control the land.
The young prince's enlightenment
puts me to shame.
Though we are not sworn brothers,
we are closer than full brothers.
Full brothers?
Since you
have put it this way,
how about we
use these two women
to seal our brotherhood?
What do you think?
What do you mean?
I'll give you Miss Cheng.
And Miss Mu
is mine.
Let's do something
out of those emotional
and moral constraints.
How about that?
Well said.
Then I'll follow your lead.
Brother Ke,
after you.
You smells so good.
Why do you want to kill me?
I don't care if you ravage others.
But Nianci is my betrothed.
You've repeatedly harassed her.
Today I must kill you
to ease my anger!
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing at us.
Isn't it ridiculous
that people like us
saying such things?
Nianci is my last dignity.
You...
You don't even acknowledge your own father,
and you talk about dignity?
We are just
two orphans
heading to
the underworld together.
Ke,
come home with mother.
Kang!
It's okay.
I'm here.
We need to clean this up.
If Ouyang Feng returns,
he'll definitely kill us.
You are Lu Guanying of Guiyun Manor?
I'm sorry.
Last time you spared me
out of kindness.
But this time, I can't let you go.
Kang.
Don't kill the innocent.
They saw me kill Ouyang Ke.
I need to silence them.
They were victims of Ouyang Ke.
They won't sell us out.
I doubt that.
If Ouyang Feng captures them,
they'll spill everything
to save themselves.
If we want to be peaceful in the future,
we must silence them.
Kang,
I don't want you to kill anymore.
But if I don't kill them,
others will kill us.
No.
Not everyone in the world
is bad.
I hope you won't let me down.
Are you okay?
Please don't worry.
We won't speak of anything today.
Thank you for saving our lives.
You'd better go before I
change my mind.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
This staff looks familiar.
I think I've seen it somewhere.
Seems to belong to the Beggars' Gang.
Beggars' Gang?
Then why did Ouyang Ke have it?
(This staff must be related to)
(Guo Jing and Huang Rong.)
(If Ouyang Feng)
(comes looking for his nephew,)
(I can use this staff)
(to defend myself.)
We'd better keep it.
Is your injury
healed now?
I'm fine.
Actually,
it was my fault.
You're a grown-up man.
but I've kept you
hidden in the wilderness.
I was too selfish.
Are you
trying to send me away?
No.
I can't live without you now.
It's just
that we can
live in a better way.
You always admired Brother Guo
for having a master like Qigong.
When I was young,
I had connections with Qigong
and the Beggars' Gang.
If you return this staff
to Qigong,
maybe I can ask him
to take you as his apprentice.
Really?
Instead of staying with Ouyang Feng
and the Jins,
I'd rather you
make friends with true heroes
and take the right path.
I want to learn real skills
and make something of myself,
so I can protect you better.
Are you hungry?
I'll cook you some noodles.
Nianci.
♪You are deeply rooted in my heart♪
♪An endless bond♪
♪You are the thread in the wind♪
♪Holding me tight for a lifetime♪
♪Since love in this world is sinful♪
♪Forgive my foolishness♪
♪No room for regrets♪
♪I won't give myself time to regret♪
♪You are the one I willingly suffer for♪
♪You are my obsession♪
♪You are the mountain peak♪
♪An unscalable summit♪
♪Even if the world is against me♪
♪And my deep love passion remain unsolved♪
♪I won't compromise♪
♪I'm obsessed with this♪
I didn't know Sixth Prince was here.
Sorry for not greeting you properly.
Master Qiu.
If it wasn't an emergency,
I wouldn't have come
here to visit you
without a notice.
You are so anxious.
If I'm not mistaken,
the Mongol-Song alliance
must have been formed.
Exactly.
Moreover,
I haven't found
the Book of Wumu.
Both of them
are very unfavorable to our Jin.
Your Royal Highness, isn't this going too far?
You have Ouyang Feng, Western Venom,
by your side.
I can't find
Mr. Ouyang now.
It's...
It's hard to explain.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
I...
I made a mistake.
I should have invited...
Whom should you have invited?
Ouyang Feng is renowned among Five Greats
for some diabolic tricks.
But I
have mastered Iron Palm.
But...
Forget it.
Exactly.
I've never doubted
your abilities.
Now I want to
reverse the situation.
Please help me.
Do I have to make the decision?
Fine.
What's your plan?
The urgent priority
is to intercept
the Mongol envoy
on their way back.
Blame the Song,
and nip their alliance plan
in the bud?
Exactly.
Old Venomous Creature,
you've chased me from Lin'an to Jiaxing,
and then back to Lin'an.
Several days and nights,
you haven't caught me.
The contest is over.
What do you want now?
But you haven't gotten rid of me.
If you don't tell me about the manual,
I will chase you
wherever you go.
Fine.
Let's skip eating and sleeping,
and see who can run faster
and longer. Dare?
Why not?
I want to see who tires out first.
I'm not tired at all.
Brother Ouyang!
Yaoshi?
Old Heretic Huang?
Didn't you say
he drowned?
Last night,
I heard Old Imp calling out in Niujia Village,
so I chased him here.
Yaoshi, you're mistaken.
Those words weren't from me,
but from those Jins.
Old Heretic Huang.
You want Old Imp
to die?
A leaky boat
couldn't kill me,
so you
come after me now?
You're fine,
but my daughter Rong was...
Where is Guo Jing?
Where is he?
Tell me.
I'll kill him!
Old Heretic Huang
heard a wild story!
Don't laugh.
Explain to him.
What's there to explain?
Let him stew a bit longer.
It's fun. It's fun.
Stop that.
You went too far.
Jing and Rong
will be mad.
No, they won't!
Old Heretic Huang locked us up for 15 years,
and we didn't get mad.
Can't we play a joke on him
and have fun?
You have a point.
Since that's the case,
we can play with him.
What do you want to play?
Tell me!
You startled me, Old Heretic Huang.
You want to kill Brother Guo.
Are you trying to trick me now?
That's not fair.
Right?
You gave me no chice.
Wait.
Old Heretic Huang,
let's play a game.
If you can catch me, I'll tell you.
Zhou Botong!
Wait. Wait. Wait.
No. No. No.
I wanted to go out
for a stroll.
I forgot...
I...
I left Old Beggar
in the palace.
I forgot about him.
No. No. I need to find him.
Listen.
You go to the Niujia Village first.
I'll find Old Beggar
and then meet you there.
We can play later.
See you!
Old Imp!
Yaoshi.
We can catch him.
You can ask your questions, and I'll ask mine.
I locked him up for 15 years,
but he didn't say a word.
Forget it.
Let's go to the Niujia Village now.
Alright.
♪I wander in the martial world♪
♪I drink a thousand cups of wine
and sing to the sky♪
♪Life and death intertwined♪
♪Leaning against the railing and shouting♪
♪Stars and moon over the wild expanse♪
♪Longbows shooting toward the distant sun♪
♪We meet in mountains and rivers♪
♪Rushing through narrow paths♪
♪I wander through the martial world♪
♪All glitz mere illusions♪
♪Cutting off all debts♪
♪Only the shadows of swords
and gleaming blades can be seen♪
♪Fearless, undaunted♪
♪The marial world is a lifetime of daring♪
♪Who knows my dreams and ambitions♪
♪Wakening to find them as distant dreams♪
♪The road ahead is long♪
♪The path is vast and grand♪
♪Thousands of dreams span ages♪
♪Whirling and swirling♪
♪Ask the youth what it means♪
♪Heroes face all challenges♪
♪True to their hearts♪
♪Or lost in the dust♪
♪The road ahead is long♪
♪The path is vast and grand♪
♪People in the world varied and numerous♪
♪Whirling and swirling♪
♪Who truly understands♪
♪Heroes face all challenges♪
♪Searching to truly grasp♪
♪Only then do they discern♪
♪Achievements and mistakes are transient♪
♪To the end, yet steps persist♪
♪We can feel pain and also joy♪
♪We can charge forward or retreat♪
♪No need to look back♪
♪Rush through wind and clouds,
shake the universe♪
♪No matter the journey's length♪
♪Entering the martial world♪
♪I fear not the endless journey♪