=Hot Blooded=
=Episode 13=
If the house is left
uninhabited for too long,
it'll become dismal.
But we're living here.
In a few days,
it will be spruced up.
Kang.
If you don't like this old house,
we can find another place.
How can that be?
I just feel moved.
The abducted child
has just returned home.
How can I not be emotional
about how fickle the world can be?
Dad.
Have a seat.
It's been so many years.
So many years.
Shouldn I celebrate
your birthday today?
Dad.
It's really hard to forget someone.
Mother has been gone for so many years,
how did you work through that?
Can that jar of Drunken Haze
really make people forget everything?
Forgetting is not hard.
What's terrifying is
not being able to forget.
(After I go to see Jing,)
(I'll let him go back to Mongolia.)
(Dad,)
(you can drink half the jar)
(of Drunken Haze.)
(Leave the rest to me.)
The fifteen years I spent
on Peach Blossom Island
are not wasted.
I created the 72 Vacant Fists
which value nihility and gentleness.
Like the Eight-Diagram tactics
on the stone wall,
it's the most powerful
to combine Yin and Yang.
It's a counter-move against
your Eighteen Subduing Dragon Palms.
Senior.
This fist position you created
is very much like
the Proud Dragon Repents
Qigong told me.
The beggar has good eye
for choosing disciples.
Come.
Let me teach you.
Dad.
I want to see him for the last time.
Then I'll ask him
to return to the grassland.
Impressive, you little brat.
You've learned
most of my Vacant Fist techniques
overnight.
I learnedf from the best.
Remarkable, remarkable.
You have some talent.
If I don't use
internal power
and rely only on the moves,
I can't beat you at all.
So now we are
two Guo Jings
and two Old Imps.
Even if we encounter Old Heretic Huang,
we don't need to fear him.
With your current strength,
you don't need to fear Mr. Huang.
Rest assured.
I won't make things difficult for you.
I won't make you fight with
your father-in-law.
Sir, I didn't mean that.
Don't I understand what you mean?
Boring.
Let's play something interesting.
Today,
let's escape from
the Peach Blossom Forest.
The formation
of the Peach Blossom Forest
reversed Yin and Yang.
The secret of this formation is
the four doors of Yin
and the four doors of Yang
can change positions constantly.
I can choose the final two doors.
But in the end,
I always can't figure out
which one is the Growth Door
and which one is the Death Door.
Let's split up.
One of us
will reach the Growth Door.
What should we do?
It seems that
since you arrived on the island,
Old Heretic Huang
has changed the formation again.
But it can't baffle me.
(River Map)
Go that way, and take it with you.
Okay.
Finally found it!
The last door
is right around here.
Sir, where should we go next?
There are only two ways, left and right.
They're the Growth Door
and the Death Door.
You go that way.
- Go.
- Okay.
Growth Door! Growth Door!
This Old Imp is really fearless.
He actually found this place.
My father's formation
is not this easy to break.
Both the left and right doors
are Death Doors.
This is a dead end.
It seems like
I can only rely on Mr. Zhou.
Jing.
Where are you?
Rong.
Jing.
It's so good to find you.
Let me down first.
Put me down.
We can't go on like this anymore.
During these days without you,
I figured it out.
I really like you, that's for sure.
But I won't allow anyone
to share your love.
Rong.
I've told you before
I just treat Huazheng as a sister.
I don't want to be her husband.
I just want to be with you.
Now is your last chance
to leave Peach Blossom Island.
I got my father drunk.
I will take you to leave here.
Don't come back.
I didn't lie to you.
I came here
with no intention of leaving.
If my father wakes up,
you will be trapped here forever.
Then I'll stay here
for the rest of my life.
Stop talking nonsense.
My father will really kill you.
Then let him kill me.
I will be
wherever you are.
Let go of your hand.
You scoundrel.
Dad.
My daughter
went through all this trouble
to let you go.
Since you want to die,
I will grant your wish.
- Dad.
- Stop!
As a grandmaster,
how can you bully the weak?
Shameless, shameless!
What does this have to do with you?
I'm just trying to help this kid.
It is my business.
If you're unconvinced,
let's have a duel.
Have you forgotten why you've been
on my Peach Blossom Island
for fifteen years?
I forgot!
My martial arts skills
have greatly improved now.
Do you dare to have a match with me?
Snake!
Sir.
You can't beat me,
so you used this evil trick.
Are you okay?
Rong.
Silver-bellied snake.
Snake.
Dad.
Why are there
so many snakes on our island?
I'm most afraid of snakes.
Hurry up, kid.
- Rong.
- Back to the cave.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Sir, let me carry you.
- Hurry and go.
Run fast.
I didn't expect
this time,
I'm going to die
because of the snake.
Don't suck it.
This snake venom is special.
It will kill you.
Jing.
This medicine is specifically
for detoxifying snake venom.
Apply it for three days, and he'll heal.
Comfortable.
Comfortable!
Sir, you're awake.
- How do you feel?
- You little rascal.
You sucked the snake blood.
How come you're fine?
I once sucked the blood
of a Seven-Step Viper,
so I became immune to all poisons.
So powerful.
Thank you for saving me.
Yes, yes, I cannot die.
I haven't defeated
Old Heretic Huang yet.
I can't die.
Mr. Huang is so powerful.
You should first...
First break his formation.
I can win, kid.
Do you look down on me?
Old Heretic Huang.
I have come up with a brilliant plan.
I have come up with a brilliant plan
to break Old Heretic Huang's formation.
What are you doing?
No, no, please get up.
Since you think I'm not bad,
how about we become
sworn brothers?
I can't do that.
You are Master Ma Yu's martial uncle.
That doesn't matter.
You call him Master,
call me Big Brother.
Kneel down.
Today,
I must make you
my sworn brother.
Why do you have to
pick me?
First,
this is how I deal with
Old Heretic Huang.
Don't ask
about the specifics.
You will know when the time comes.
In any case,
it's beneficial for you with no harm.
Second,
it's also the most important.
I think highly of you.
You are simple, honest.
And you saved me.
It's okay, sir.
If you don't mind,
let's become sworn brothers.
Since you think so highly of me,
well,
it's better to obey respectfully.
To the white condor above
and the cockroach down,
all living beings are the witnesses.
Today, Guo Jing and I
become sworn brothers.
We'll share wealth and happiness,
eat happily together,
practice together,
and be happy together.
Happy, happy, extremely happy!
Whoever regrets it
will be struck by thunder.
Okay, be happy!
Call me Big Brother.
Big Brother.
Kowtow.
Ceremony completed.
Big Brother.
My good brother.
I have a little brother now.
I have a big brother now.
Little rascal.
My brother.
Go drink water.
Brother.
This is what you used to save me.
No, this is what I use
to wrap my dagger.
Brother.
Where did you get this thing?
My second master gave it to me.
He probably got it from Mei Chaofeng.
Do you know
what is written on it?
What?
I haven't opened it before.
I can't understand it either.
(You little brat.)
(Fortune really favours fools.)
(He actually doesn't know)
(this is the Nine Yin Manual.)
Big Brother, what's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Brother.
I like this thing.
How about giving it to me?
If you like it, then take it.
I'll find another one.
Thanks.
I like it.
Snake!
I fear nothing in the world,
except for snakes and insects.
I have been on
Peach Blossom Island for fifteen years,
and I have never seen a snake before.
Why are there so many snakes today?
Hit it, hit it!
That's not right.
Rong said her dad does not keep snakes.
Could it be...
Uncle.
Ke.
Your snake formation can't break
the one on the Island.
Remove it quickly.
Don't lose your manners.
Yes.
Ouyang.
Yaoshi.
How have you been?
This is my nephew.
Just now he was messing around.
Please forgive him.
Ke, pay your respects.
Ke.
You are the junior.
It is only natural
to make a big salute to Mr. Huang.
One more.
Uncle.
I'm here to pay my respects.
I am not unfamiliar with you.
Before,
you bullied my disciple.
Then you set up a snake formation
to attack my daughter.
Truly a young hero.
They are just playing around.
It didn't count.
I also didn't discipline him
very well.
I will punish him properly
when we get back.
Don't blame him.
Sorry for not welcoming you earlier.
Please.
If Ouyang Ke really came,
I wonder how Rong is doing now.
Not to mention Ouyang Ke,
even Ouyang Feng is here,
Old Heretic Huang won't suffer.
Besides,
where we are now?
The Peach Blossom Island.
Isn't that right?
You're right.
Don't think about finding Rong.
Isn't it asking for trouble for yourself?
Moreover,
can you get out?
You're picking on me again.
If I could go out,
I would have left long ago.
Okay, okay.
Let's try to figure it out.
We will definitely
break through this formation.
Right?
If you feel bored,
I will teach you some moves.
I've learned
your Vacant Fist
and Technique of Ambidexterity.
What other things can I learn from you?
I didn't teach you
my most powerful moves.
You are just bragging.
No way, no way.
Are you really going
to give the Nine Yin Manual
to this kid?
The second volume
was brought by him in the first place.
It proves that he
has a connection to the manual.
You are going against Senior's promise.
You want to read the manual yourself.
You want to learn the moves on it, right?
Senior just doesn't want me to practice
the martial arts in this manual.
He doesn't forbid others from practicing.
I asked this brat to practice.
It doesn't count as breaking the promise.
And I
just steal a peek
of the manual.
What does it matter?
Big Brother.
What are you thinking about?
Brother.
I've been keeping this in reserve.
We are sworn brothers now.
I think I can teach it to you.
Do you want to learn?
I'll learn whatever you teach me.
This is something
I created by myself.
It's called the Imp's Manual.
The Imp's Manual
combines the wisdom
I gathered for a lifetime.
If you can integrate it
with my Technique of Ambidexterity,
72 Vacant Fists,
and the old beggar's
Eighteen Subduing Dragon Palms,
you will be invincible
at the next duel atop Mount Hua.
I have never thought about
becoming invincible.
Little rascal.
My brother.
If you can become invincible,
Rong will be yours.
Rong?
Sit down quickly.
Okay.
Swing the sword admist peach blossoms,
playing the song on a jade flute.
This statement is true.
The environment here is much better
than Mount White Camel.
The Western Regions are vast.
If there's a chance,
you must show me around
at your Mount White Camel Manor.
Sure, Yaoshi.
I wondered why there are so many snakes
on this Peach Blossom Island.
So you are here.
Rong, don't be rude.
Hurry up.
Pay your respects to Uncle Ouyang.
Greetings, Mr. Ouyang.
Okay.
Dad.
This Ouyang Ke
bullied me many times
on the Central Plains.
Is that so?
I came specifically
to apologize to Rong.
Who knows what are your intentions?
Rong.
No wonder Ke
is so deeply in love with her.
Luckily Rong takes after her mom,
not you.
Rong.
This is a rhinoceros horn pill
obtained from a divine beast
on our Western Regions.
It was carefully cultivated by my uncle.
Carrying it with you,
you are immune to all poisons.
There is only one in the world.
What exactly do you want?
I...
I want to propose a marriage
and ask Rong to be my wife.
With it,
you can marry into the Western Regions
and no longer fear those
venomous snakes and insects.
Uncle Ouyang.
Our Peach Blossom Island
has neither insects nor poisons.
No need for this treasure.
It'll definitely be useful.
Yaoshi.
Everyone in the world
knows I am skilled in using poison.
I will give this antidote
to Rong.
This is enough to prove
our sincerity.
Yaoshi, you can rest assured.
Rong.
Take it first.
Thank you, Uncle.
You're welcome.
Having accepted this gift,
does it mean you want
to make friends with me?
Are you crazy?
Dad.
I'd rather you beat me to death.
I would rather die
than be with a wicked person like you.
You...
I'm going to tell my mother
you don't treat me nicely.
Rong.
This girl
was spoiled by me.
My apologies.
It's okay, Rong
just want to test Ke's martial arts.
The feelings between them
can be gradually developed.
Once they start to fight,
they will get closer to each other.
Well...
Ke is very
devoted to Rong.
If you agree to this marriage,
we will be family
and be doubly related.
If you need my help in the future,
I will go through fire and water for you.
I will take
this anti-poison treasure.
The marriage
is not in a hurry.
It's not easy for you
to come by.
We haven't seen each other
for so many years.
You must stay a few more days.
The two of us
can have a drink.
Sure.
It is the Way of Heaven
to diminish superabundance,
and to supplement deficiency.
It is the Way of Heaven
to diminish superabundance,
and to supplement deficiency.
A man takes away from those
who have not enough
to add to his own superabundance.
A man takes away from those
who have not enough
to add to his own superabundance.
(I finally saw)
(what is the Nine Yin Manual.)
(It's really awesome.)
You fell from the clouds into the mud.
I understand that you feel bitter.
Let's get used to it
when we're in the new place.
I will always be with you.
I know.
My heart is loftier than the sky,
but my life is thinner than paper.
Don't say that.
Let's go buy some seeds,
flower seeds and vegetable seeds.
We'll dress up our house and garden
so beautifully.
Stop!
Where are you running?
The Four Devils of the Yellow River
are chasing the Beggars' Gang.
- Even if we return to Niujia Village,
- Come back!
it'll be the same.
There is no pure land in this world.
Beggar, keep running!
I'm indebted to the Beggars' Gang.
Qigong once taught me martial arts.
- Don't run.
- I must help them.
- Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Get lost.
Don't let me see you again.
Go, go, go.
Thank
the both of you.
Qigong once taught me
some martial arts.
Although he does not take disciples,
in my heart,
he's always been a mentor.
I have always been grateful
to the Beggars' Gang.
You know Qigong?
That's great.
I was afraid of ruining everything.
What is it?
Why do the Four Devils of the Yellow River
want to kill you?
The Book of Wumu.
Do you recognize
the mark of the Beggars' Gang?
Yes, Qigong told me.
On the fifteenth day of next month,
at the gathering in Yuezhou,
pass the message to the gang.
The Book
is in
Cuihan Hall.
Kang.
I need to go deliver the message
to the Beggars' Gang.
Please take care of him.
I should go instead.
I'm almost part of the gang.
If I go, things will be easier.
I'm leaving first.
Be careful on your way.
Okay.
Do you know what you want?
Do you want to stay here
all your life?
The Book of Wumu.
The Book of Wumu. The Book of Wumu.
What are you waiting for?
Take action!
Go ahead!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Big Brother.
Your Imp's Manual is really good.
These days,
my skills have improved a lot.
What do you think?
But you are still too young.
This Nine...
Your foundation is not stable enough,
and your internal energy not deep,
so you cannot fully
exert your strength yet.
I suggest you practice
the Imp's Manual daily.
Okay, understood.
I will practice diligently.
Jing.
Rong.
Can't watch it.
Can't watch it. Can't watch it.
Rong, you're finally here.
I've missed you so much these days.
Jing.
My father has become confused.
Ouyang Feng came to propose a marriage.
He wants me to marry Ouyang Ke.
Ouyang Feng came to propose marriage?
Old Venomous Creature really came.
I wondered why there are so many snakes.
This is going to be interesting.
Let's leave Peach Blossom Island.
Big Brother.
Do you want to come with us?
I'm not going.
Why do you call Old Imp big brother?
I have become sworn brothers
with Guo Jing.
From now on, you are my sister-in-law.
Old Imp.
You're playing quite big this time.
I'll play even bigger.
Bigger surprises are prepared
for your dad.
What surprise?
Can't say now.
Big Brother.
You really aren't coming with us?
No, take her to leave first.
I still have an unfulfilled appointment
with Old Heretic Huang.
My words have always been trustworthy.
Well,
I will come to find you
when I settle the score with him.
Okay then.
Take care of yourself, Big Brother.
- Go.
- Let's go.
Brat.
You left so quickly.
I asked the mute servant
to arrange a boat for me,
why is there no boat?
Rong.
Want a boat?
Ask me.
I can take you away.
Ouyang Ke.
What are you doing here?
I am here to propose marriage.
You're eloping with
my not-yet-married wife.
Isn't that a bit too much?
Who is your wife?
All you do is
talk nonsense all day long.
Jing, help me knock out one of his teeth.
Looking for death.
Rong, don't come over.
Master.
- Master.
Qigong.
You've aged quite a lot
after we last saw each other
at Mount Hua.
Old Venomous Creature.
Do you think you haven't aged?
Is this your disciple?
Impressive skills.
He
is not good at martial arts.
Doesn't control the force.
Several times,
he beated your nephew so hard
that he coughed blood.
After so many times,
I think your body
should be used to it, right?
Rong, what did you call him
just now?
Dad.
I didn't tell you before.
Jing and I
have already taken Qigong
as our master.
You often say Qigong
is skillful and righteous.
I heard it many times.
I'm sure you must agree to this.
Yaoshi.
Qigong.
It's been years.
Actually, I always tell her
to learn whatever
she wants to learn from you.
Why bother looking for me?
I took her as my disciple
because there's fate between us.
Second, I want to eat
the food she makes.
I didn't tell you beforehand.
I am here to apologize to you this time.
Not at all.
Qigong.
My daughter is mischievous.
Being able to be your disciple
is her luck.
Ouyang.
It's windy by the seaside.
Let's go to the Island.
Let's go.
(Sword Trial Pavilion)
Yaoshi.
This time I come
is because I want to ask for a favor.
I don't know if you can agree to it.
We have been friends for decades.
Qigong.
Please tell me.
I haven't even mentioned what it is yet.
What if it's something
difficult to handle?
You were willing
to come all the way
across the sea in person
to my little island,
this matter is surely not easy.
I haven't seen Qigong personally
ask for help.
Even I'm curious to hear.
What's it to you?
What do you want to meddle?
Be ready to attend the wedding banquet.
Wedding banquet?
How old are you?
Yaoshi.
Rong and Jing are both my disciples.
Everyone can see
that these two young people
have long been a couple.
Today I am here
to help them
propose a marriage to you.
I hope you can agree.
It's just a pity.
Qigong.
I have already helped Ke
give a proposal gift
to Yaoshi.
You're late.
My dad hasn't agreed yet.
But that doesn't mean he disagrees.
You can't say it like that.
Marriage is not something
that first-come, first-served.
Dad.
You are marrying off your daughter,
not selling me.
Rong.
Yes, Rong.
You can't talk to your dad like that.
But Yaoshi,
Rong is right.
This really can't
be taken as business.
When I propose, it's business.
When you do, it's not?
You...
Yaoshi is a man of character.
He disregards etiquette
throughout his life,
and does things his own way.
I suppose he doesn't care much
about these rules.
Rules are meant
to be broken.
That's it.
We are all sincere and genuine people.
These two young people
are a perfect match.
No one can separate them.
Furthermore...
Furthermore, this Ouyang Ke
has an extremely bad character.
He has insulted me several times.
If it weren't for Qigong
who helped me
for your sake,
you would've lost me.
Our Ke
is erudite and versatile.
Feeling needs to be cultivated.
The two people
need to spend years
together,
not just a few hours and days.
If she's with
a dunderhead
every day,
can she be happy?
Mr. Ouyang.
Jing.
Ouyang.
Rong is not highly cultured
and steeped in propriety,
but she's very lucky
to gain the favor
of the nephew
of yours
and the disciple
of Qigong's
at the same time.
this matter
It does put me in a dilemma.
I don't think it's a dilemma at all.
Just fulfill their wishes
and let them follow their hearts.
That's where you are wrong,
Beggar.
Yaoshi has to decide
on something as important as this.
How can we allow them to act recklessly
as they please?
You are the one who can make decisions.
Your nephew has hurt many girls
as he pleased.
Don't act like you don't know.
Talk nicely.
We're martial arts practitioners.
We can't talk nicely.
- Let's have a fight.
- Alright, bring it on.
Ouyang.
Let's settle this with our fists. Go.
You got on my nerves. Go.
I wander in the martial world
I drink a thousand cups of wine
and sing to the sky
Life and death intertwined
Leaning against the railing and shouting
Stars and moon over the wild expanse
Longbows shooting toward the distant sun
We meet in mountains and rivers
Rushing through narrow paths
I wander through the martial world
All glitz mere illusions
Cutting off all debts
Only the shadows of swords
and gleaming blades can be seen
Fearless, undaunted
The marial world is a lifetime of daring
Who knows my dreams and ambitions
Wakening to find them as distant dreams
The road ahead is long
The path is vast and grand
Thousands of dreams span ages
Whirling and swirling
Ask the youth what it means
Heroes face all challenges
True to their hearts
Or lost in the dust
The road ahead is long
The path is vast and grand
People in the world varied and numerous
Whirling and swirling
Who truly understands
Heroes face all challenges
Searching to truly grasp
Only then do they discern
Achievements and mistakes are transient
To the end, yet steps persist
We can feel pain and also joy
We can charge forward or retreat
No need to look back
Rush through wind and clouds,
shake the universe
No matter the journey's length
Entering the martial world
I fear not the endless journey