CATCH THE GHOST
THIS DRAMA IS FICTION
THE CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
INSTITUTIONS, AND EVENTS AREN'T REAL
Don't move, or I'll shoot.
Arrest them.
Run.
Damn it.
Locust. Grab them!
Catch him!
I just rented out the ship to them.
They told me that they were going fishing.
Where's the last one?
Son.
I'm exhausted now.
EPISODE 12
Why are you here when you're suspended?
You don't mind if you get fired?
You said you couldn't join the RIU
because of your mom.
That's why you broke up with me, too.
But what is this now?
Explain why you gave up everything...
and ran here.
Well...
Ma-ri.
Ever since Rookie joined our team,
she kept stirring me up.
At first, it was uncomfortable
and annoying,
and I wanted to ignore it.
But then I realized
I couldn't avoid it anymore.
The person that I was before.
The reason why
I became a police officer...
and where I want to run toward.
Rookie reminded me of them again.
You are your old self again.
The Ko Ji-seok I fell in love with.
But...
You can't come back to me, right?
I'm sorry.
Hey, get off.
We'll go return this car
and take the subway.
Okay. Good work, Detective Lee.
Bye, Su-ho.
Bye. Good work today.
You should go, too.
Okay.
Wait.
I don't want you to be
in a bind anymore because of me.
If you show up like this
when you're suspended...
I'm okay.
I'm not.
You were suspended because of me.
-I can't cause you more trouble.
-I'm really fine.
But I'm not okay with it.
I will call you
after I catch him.
After you catch him?
Then I guess
I won't be able to see you for a while.
All right.
That's your top priority, after all.
See you later.
Also...
Don't forget to eat...
and make sure you get enough sleep. And...
Okay. I'll get going now.
Rookie.
REGIONAL INVESTIGATION UNIT
Go inside.
Aren't they the Locust Swarm?
Yes, they are.
But why did the RIU
catch the Locust Swarm?
Hello, Director Choi.
I have something to ask you.
-Yes, Detective Park.
-Yes.
We should be investigated
by the Subway Police.
Send us there.
Neither of them is the Subway Ghost.
The DNA from the hideout...
doesn't match either of theirs.
What?
Let's go to the Subway Police.
Sit back down!
So the one that ran away
is the Subway Ghost?
His name, age, and family.
Tell me everything you know.
His name is Boss. He's older than I am.
That's all we know.
Is that what you call an act of loyalty?
He's a serial killer.
A serial killer? Come on.
Chief Ha.
This is the police, right? I'm dying here.
Two murderers are after me.
They are the Locust Swarm.
One of them could be the Subway Ghost.
Han Tae-ung, you bastard.
Han Tae-ung? Is that his name?
Han Tae-ung. He is 31 years old.
He's 31 years old, and...
They really don't know anything else?
Han Tae-ung. Thirty-one years old.
What about his family?
-We don't know.
-Where does he live?
We don't know.
We just lived together.
Where?
NO ENTRY
INVESTIGATION IN PROGRESS
"Podori at the Subway Police's
30th-anniversary event
is the Subway Ghost. Shocking news."
"Podori, the police mascot,
is the Subway Ghost."
How did this article get published?
Well, I tried to stop it, but...
We're not even sure
Locust Swarm is the Subway Ghost.
How can you let
this article get published?
-I'm sorry.
-Take care of this right now.
Hey. Stop the reporters.
Ko Ji-seok.
I need you out in order for me to survive.
When the body was found
at the 30th-anniversary event,
it was Boss who insisted
that we get on that train
and steal from the cops.
So he hid the body there
and acted like he was sad
because we weren't trending
on the Internet
because of the Subway Ghost?
Shit. I've got goosebumps.
Han Tae-ung's DNA matches the DNA found
in the Subway Ghost's hideout.
So he's definitely
the Subway Ghost, right?
I looked into it. He's not Han Tae-ung.
What?
He stole the identity
of a homeless person named Han Tae-ung.
We can't identify him at the moment.
We don't know his identity?
He's not Han Tae-ung?
We even saw his ID card.
No.
You know him.
You lived with him for two years.
Tell us anything you can remember.
Anything!
You...
You're his mother.
One, two, three. Shock!
-Go bring the epinephrine.
-Okay.
Her BP keeps dropping.
Chest compression.
More.
Ms. Choi Mi-ra just passed away.
What?
No.
You totaled the scooter.
I spent my savings to buy the owner
a new one and fixed this one.
This is ours now.
I blew the tire recently, Rookie.
The tire burst while I was racing
with Kim Wu-hyeok,
so I've been mad at this scooter.
But it's still ours...
So I gave it the most expensive tire.
RICE
I bought rice and a few side dishes,
so have proper meals
instead of cup noodles.
Here.
Open wide.
It's good.
Ae-Sim, when you miss me,
how do you deal with it?
I just...
go over the memories I made with you.
Go over the memories...
-Honey.
-Yes?
I'm full. I want to stop eating.
-Okay.
-I want to sleep.
There.
Lie down, Ae-sim.
These are the only pictures I have.
I don't have a single picture
to remember her with.
Oh, right.
Yes, Detective Lee.
Captain. You know, the man
who was tailing Rookie.
He was the Subway Ghost.
I'm worried.
It's making me anxious.
Good night.
I'd like to ask for your opinion
about Captain Ko Ji-seok's
suspension issue.
Go ahead.
We did lose one
of the Locust Swarm members,
but Captain Ko contributed a lot
to catching the other two.
So?
The disciplinary committee is saying
that he should be reinstated soon.
I agree with them, too.
-Really?
-Yes.
Then go ahead.
Thank you.
Yes, Commissioner Kim.
What?
Really?
Thank you.
Does that mean I might be able
to return to the Subway Police?
Okay. I'll wait.
Goodbye.
She must be busy, right?
Rookie.
I might go back to the Subway Police.
She's not there anyway.
Yes, Detective Lee.
-Father.
-Yes.
So you're returning
to the Subway Police, right?
Well, nothing's decided yet, but...
Probably?
Does Detective Yoo know?
No.
I haven't told her
because I thought she'd be busy.
What's going on between you two?
I'm sure it's nothing.
Hey.
It's not nothing.
So are you two dating?
Did you tell her how you feel?
No, I didn't, but...
See? They're strangers.
Hey, come on. They're not strangers.
They have this comradeship between them.
Of course.
Comradeship. That's poisonous.
Why?
You protected her,
cleaned up her mess for her,
and even got suspended for her.
This is something
even family members
can't do for each other.
But you've done those
under the name of a comrade.
So even though you two should've been
boyfriend and girlfriend long ago,
you two have just become comrades.
"Comrades"?
You're right. Yes.
A relationship is hard
to change once it's set.
-It gets awkward.
-Right.
-Love...
-Yes?
-It's all about timing, Captain.
-That's right.
You're about to blow your chance,
so go tell her how you feel now.
Captain.
You can do it.
Ma'am.
About the reinstatement
of Captain Ko Ji-seok...
Yes.
I found the perfect place for him.
He can be reinstated within a week.
Really? Where?
It's the head position
at Narang Island Patrol Station.
Narang Island?
It's an island in Namhae.
It has become well-known
as the backdrop of Korean dramas,
and it has become quite popular.
What are you talking about?
The local government wants
to pursue a project
to develop the island
into a tourist destination,
but Narang Island Patrol Station is
filled with older officers
who aren't fit for the project.
Therefore, if Captain Ko,
who's handsome enough to be an actor,
fights well and smart,
joins the patrol station,
it could encourage
the Korean police wave trend.
What kind of bull...
That's ridiculous!
Well, you see...
Captain Ko has to take care of his mother.
He can't go that far.
Namhae is six hours by car
from here and a few hours by boat.
No way.
Oh, did I tell you?
The disciplinary committee is
wondering how Captain Ko,
who was suspended,
caught the Locust Swarm.
You'd get in a lot of trouble
if they find out
that you personally gave an order
to a suspended officer to investigate
a case, you'll be in a bind.
Are you blackmailing me?
No. I'm just worried about you.
On top of that,
Captain Ko is suspended,
so if he gets into a financial problem,
he'll quit.
Once he is reinstated,
he'll be paid every month again,
so isn't this better
for his sick mother, too?
I understood what you said,
-so leave.
-Okay.
Rookie, I'll protect you from now on.
No, she wouldn't get what I'm saying.
Nothing is easy with her.
Rookie.
May I continue to be
your seat belt?
That's terrible.
That was horrible.
Get a grip, Ji-seok.
Rookie, be my girlfriend.
Yes, Commissioner Kim.
What?
I shouldn't have handed you
those handcuffs then.
I made a mistake.
-I'm sorry, Ji-seok.
-It's okay, ma'am.
I would've gone anyway.
I was careless.
By the way...
What about your mother?
She doesn't know anything...
so she'll be asking for me day and night.
If you endure it for a year
on Narang Island,
I will do everything in my power
to get you reinstated.
I'm sorry.
Here you go.
Open wide.
It's good.
-I'm going on a business trip.
-What?
Where to? For how long?
A bit far.
For a while.
So I can't see you anymore?
I do such a good job at work
that they are asking me to go.
Don't forget to eat while I'm gone...
and listen to Auntie Gyeong-hui.
Okay?
I'll come as often as possible.
Promise me.
I have a week left.
I can protect you...
for another week, Rookie.
Damn it.
He's been watching her for a long time?
SEOUN METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
Ma-ri.
You have to compare the DNA here
to the Subway Ghost's DNA.
-What?
-I was at Rookie's house
all night last night and...
-What?
-Well...
You see... I wasn't with her.
I was worried about her,
so I stayed in front of her house.
And...
A man seemed to be watching her house.
I found these from where he was standing.
If he's after Rookie,
he could be the Subway Ghost.
You look absolutely ridiculous right now.
What?
Someone was after Officer Yoo,
and you think it's the Subway Ghost?
Yes. You were right to come to me.
But...
You should've at least
calmed your breath before coming in.
You should at least try to hide
such a worried look on your face.
I heard you'll be transferred
to an island in a week.
Mind your own business.
Kim Wu-hyeok.
Go do a stakeout
at Officer Yoo's house all night.
I still have a week left.
I can't stand to listen to this.
I'm sorry.
Wu-hyeok, you must be busy
because of the investigation.
I don't have any work to do
for a week, so...
Staking out is part of the investigation.
You should go, Mr. Ko.
Fine. I'll leave.
I'll go undercover starting tonight.
-Good morning.
Good morning, Chief Ha.
What is that? Did you find some clues?
These were found near your house.
The Subway Ghost came after you last time,
so who knows?
-Let's go to the NFS.
-Okay.
Right.
You too.
The DNA test results
for the fabric must be out, too.
Okay.
Do you have the results?
The DNA from the fabric
and the DNA on this cotton swab
are a 99.9 percent match.
The DNA from the fabric
matches Ms. Yoo's DNA?
I wasn't sure, but I was right.
Your sister was indeed responsible.
My sister doesn't know anything.
She has level two autism,
so she's like an elementary school girl.
How can she be responsible for anything?
She's right.
Ms. Yoo's sister is basically a kid.
When a kid messes up,
the guardian should take
the responsibility.
So try to remember.
What did your kid-like sister do?
Remember everything
down to the smallest things
like stepping on someone's toe
and report to me.
You don't need to watch my house.
There is no reason
for the Subway Ghost to risk
getting caught and come after me.
What if he does come?
I can't let you be in danger.
So you think my sister is
responsible for this
so he will come back to get me, too?
Ms. Yoo, denial isn't the answer here.
Either way,
we must find the reason why
your sister's DNA was on the fabric
to know the whole story behind this case.
So let's face it head-on.
Captain.
You're late.
Thanks, Wu-hyeok, for walking her home.
I said I'll stake out.
Go home.
I'll be staying here all night.
What?
Both of you should go.
I can protect myself.
Ms. Yoo, we're investigating a case.
Mr. Ko, you shouldn't be here.
He knows what you look like.
He'll run away if he sees you.
Just one week.
-Can't you allow me one week?
-One week?
Either way, it's meaningless.
You're right.
Don't worry.
Go on in.
Goodbye.
If you have more people
you want to protect,
you must protect yourself first.
She's right.
You can go.
If he does come here,
I won't lose him like a fool
like last time.
I know.
You'll get him.
But I want to be by your side when you do.
Did you know
that I put an umbrella over you
when you were being rained on
two years ago?
I stood there for almost an hour
and I got soaked instead.
That day,
you looked like
a person who couldn't sense
whether it was raining or not.
I just felt a bit bad for you then.
Since that day,
I have always been curious about you.
That afternoon, the sun came out.
While I was looking at the sun,
I wondered, "Does she know
the sun's out today?"
The next day, there was
a nice, cool breeze.
I wondered,
"Does she know
there is a nice breeze today?"
Detective Kim.
I've said some harsh things to you,
but they weren't directed to you.
They were directed at myself.
Detective Kim, you're a great person.
If you tell me that now,
I can't be petty.
Oh, forget it.
Those cigarette butts...
Mr. Ko found them.
He's been guarding you
from the yard every night.
Captain did?
He saw a suspicious man
watching your house
and found those cigarette butts.
That's how I ended up
coming to watch your place.
Mr. Ko is to be transferred to an island.
An island? Why? When?
He's leaving in a week.
Once he goes, he can't return
for at least a year.
WE WILL WORK FOR THE CITIZENS' SAFETY
Did we have an appointment?
I'm sorry about barging in
on you like this.
-I have something to tell you.
-What is it?
Please reinstate Captain
to the Subway Police.
What are you doing?
I'm not asking you to do this for free.
Within a week, Captain and I will...
Within a week?
We'll catch the Subway Ghost.
Goodness.
I didn't realize the Subway Police
had such a talented officer.
If it were that simple,
you should've caught him sooner.
Stop with this nonsense and leave.
-Now.
-Wait.
Do you have an idea of how you'll do it?
Ma'am.
Even Chief Ha hasn't been able
to resolve it for the past two years.
This petty officer can't...
Officer Jeon.
It doesn't cost money
to hear her out, does it?
Sure.
I'm sure you already know
that the Subway Ghost is
one of the Locust Swarm.
It was thanks to the Subway Police
that we found out that the Subway Ghost
is one of the Locust Swarm
and we were able
to make the wanted posters.
So I'm going to go after
the Subway Ghost the same way
the Subway Police
went after the Locust Swarm.
So you will go after the Locust Swarm,
not the Subway Ghost?
Yes.
Just give me a week. Please.
That...
That would give me
the longer end of the stick.
Captain Ko would be packing up
for the week anyway.
We'll ask him to spend
that time investigating.
And if he does catch the Subway Ghost,
that would be a jackpot.
Isn't that right, Officer Jeon?
Yes, it will be a jackpot.
We're transferring Captain Ko
to Narang Island
to promote the police anyway.
What better PR is there
than him catching the Subway Ghost?
But...
This decision was made
by the higher-ups already...
It'd be a bigger problem
if the public found out
that the higher-ups sent
a competent detective who caught
the Subway Ghost to an island
to be a straw man.
Can you stop the reporters
from writing articles on that?
No.
So will you give us a chance?
Yes, do it.
I'm sure you can do it.
A week?
If you're desperate,
that will be enough time.
Thank you, ma'am!
Thank you.
Captain, meet me
at the Subway Police office.
Goodness.
I hate coming here now.
No one is here to welcome us.
It's so empty.
Detective Lee. Su-ho.
Captain!
-Goodness.
-Captain.
Are you not going to the island anymore?
No, I'm just here to see you.
I'm here.
What are you doing here?
We won't take away your desk,
so go focus on working for the RIU.
I won't work with them anymore.
-Why not?
-Were you kicked out?
Did you cause trouble?
What? No.
I quit of my own accord.
I've quit to catch the last one
of the Locust Swarm with Captain.
You mean the Subway Ghost?
I made a deal with the commissioner.
If we catch the Subway Ghost
within a week,
you will be reinstated
to the Subway Police.
I did a good job, right?
Captain.
Come with me.
Thank you for coming.
I like you a lot.
I can't hide my feelings anymore.
I can only be my true self
when I'm around you.
But...
Give your answer once we catch him.
To be honest,
I want us to be official right now,
but that would be selfish of me.
I know that you can't do anything else
until you catch him.
So give me your answer after we catch him.
Oh, that scared me.
Are you all right?
Oh, my heart is racing.
Why is my heart racing?
Oh, my.
We'll go work undercover.
We're going far away.
It'll take a long time.
-Hey.
-Okay, Father.
I miss Donna so much.
This isn't my desk now.
So we should go catch
the Locust Swarm now?
Yes. Within a week.
Oh, we must hurry.
Then first...
Rookie.
We should've just made it official today.
No way.
All right. Let's start investigating.
So we're going after the Locust Swarm,
not the Subway Ghost, right?
The Subway Police knows
the Locust Swarm the best.
Okay. Then let's call in our family.
Detective Lee.
Are you done with your coffee?
I just opened it.
Come back. Let's start investigating
the Locust Swarm.
Gosh, one week?
We should pour everything into it.
Gosh, Ms. Yoo. What was the great idea
of yours that got you cut a deal
with the commissioner?
Okay!
Gather around.
He was chased by the police once,
so I'm sure he's completely in hiding.
I thought it'd be impossible
to investigate his acquaintances
because his identity is fake.
But?
Remember how Captain and I
went after Han Tae-ung
at Seolleung Station?
Yes.
That day, Han Tae-ung was meeting
someone at Seolleung Station.
Whom do you think he went to meet?
Of course, he must've gone
to meet his fence.
Yes! That fence.
You're saying he's
Han Tae-ung's acquaintance, right?
That's right.
Captain, you told me before
that handling stolen goods is quite risky,
so they usually make
the younger ones handle it.
So I thought Han Tae-ung
was one of the lower-rank minions.
But now we know
that Han Tae-ung was the leader.
You're right.
If the leader went to handle
the stolen goods himself,
it means he's friends with the fence.
Since the fence definitely had contact
with Han Tae-ung,
it is well worth it to talk to him.
-Right?
-Gosh, Ms. Yoo.
You've become smart
after working with the RIU.
But do you think we can find him?
Ms. Yoo, there are
a little over 100 fences
on the Subway Police's radar.
It'll take time,
but if we question them one by one,
we'll find him.
Then I'll call the other Subway Police
and get the list of the fences.
Salute!
All right.
Let's talk to every fence on the list.
That's all!
Oh, come on. It's not me.
I live a hard life,
so don't ever come here again.
Don't come.
-Hey. Come on.
-All right.
Why do you cause a scene at every house?
That never happened.
-Oh, come on.
-Jeez.
I guess it's not him. Cross him off.
Go away!
Goodness.
That's not how you do it.
This is how you do it.
You should do it like a chicken.
You were good the other day.
Let's go.
Okay.
I don't know anything.
I quit doing that a long time ago.
Who is he? Is he terrifying?
I really don't know.
You have to be truthful
for me to believe you.
You said you quit this a long time ago,
but this is a stolen good, and so is that.
What?
I'm sure you removed the initials
because this isn't yours.
You don't strike me as someone
who would put a heart sticker
on a pink cell phone.
If you cooperate with us now,
I'll give these back to the owners
and not hold you accountable.
Or...
I'll investigate this properly
and make you serve
about seven years in prison.
Oh, you're an ex-con, too.
Then you'll get additional punishment.
Maybe you'll get as long as ten years.
Promise me that you won't punish me
for what I'm about to tell you.
What else did you do?
Okay. Just tell us
who the Locust Swarm's fence is.
That fence has a talent.
-What talent?
-Laundering identities.
That fence makes fake IDs
and fake passports
with the ID cards from stolen wallets.
They are flawless.
We all have gotten fake IDs
from that fence.
Since we are all involved,
no one will talk.
The identity of Han Tae-ung
could've been fabricated by that fence.
He'll need a new ID to run away,
so those two will meet again.
Where can we find that fence?
JI HAN-SEOP
What do you want?
Who are you?
-Damn it.
-Stay still!
Jeez.
We're the police.
-Let go of me!
-Stay still.
What kind of police barges
into someone else's house
without even identifying himself?
I'm a good cop,
but I don't want to be one right now.
Gosh, she's good. They look so real.
Damn it.
Listen up.
As a cop,
I should take all those IDs
to the station,
investigate who those people are,
and write up every single one
and indict you.
I would have to work hard
for at least a week.
-So?
-But...
I don't have the time
nor the will to do so.
So I'll just ask you
one question and leave.
What's that?
The Locust Swarm's leader, Han Tae-ung.
What's his real name?
Where can we find him?
This...
If we decide to investigate this,
you'll be sentenced
to 30 years in prison for forgery.
Oh, right. You're an ex-con, too, right?
Then you'll get additional punishment.
You'll end up spending
about four decades in prison.
Oh, no.
He's just one of my clients.
I don't know his real name,
so go ask him yourself.
You know how to get in touch with him?
I'm supposed to meet him
at Hwagok Station in 30 minutes.
He's coming to Hwagok Station
in 30 minutes?
Let's go, Rookie.
Chief Ha!
The DNA on these cigarette butts
match the Subway Ghost's DNA.
What?
DNA ANALYSIS
So he really did go
to Officer Yoo's place?
I didn't think he would.
It's risky to go
to a cop's place on his own
while he's on the run.
Why is he going that extra mile?
What is he trying to say?
What is it?
The Subway Ghost will be
at Hwagok Station in 30 minutes.
How do you know that?
It's a long story.
I'm sure about this, so be on the move.
Okay.
The Subway Ghost will be
at Hwagok Station.
Let's go right now.
Okay!
The train bound for Banghwa is this way.
-Let's search here.
-Okay.
Where is he?
This train is for Banghwa.
He got off on the other side.
Rookie!
-Rookie.
-Over there.
Jin.
This is Jin's.
I'll go get him.
Move.
I got you.
Jin...
Where is she?
Your sister...
She's alive.
CATCH THE GHOST
-Happy birthday to you
-She's alive.
-Happy birthday, dear Jin
-Just focus on that.
I'm a witness,
not a murderer.
Stop with your lies.
You killed her!
A mentally-ill homeless person
pushed a child
-onto the tracks at Wangsuri Station.
-Quiet!
I was so scared
that I couldn't say anything.
It will never happen again.
Tell me what's going on.
It's Jin's fault.