Shao.
Mr. Wang, about that contract, I...
Mr. Wang, well...
Why isn't your contract ready yet?
Can you do this job or not?
I quit.
Ren Zhen, don't be so willful.
Excuse me.
How long does it take to get to Wenquan County?
About an hour.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Where are you going?
Well,
Grandpa Bate's sheep is ruminating badly.
I'm taking it to the county to see a vet.
Remember to bring back my rubber shoes.
Alright. Don't worry.
I'm leaving now.
Uncle Tuoka, Aunt Guli.
Bye. Take care.
Call me Secretary.
Even if they fly to the sky, they're still kids I watched grow up.
Go, go, go.
Is it okay now?
I fed it some medicine.
It ate some grass when passing the bazaar.
It should be fine now.
That's good.
These sheep are Bate's life.
I'll make some skewers.
We can chat while we eat.
The last time we met
was when you were taking the village official exam.
Mr. Yin.
Do you think my returning to Xia Village
was a wrong choice?
Block the view.
We can't do it in front of it.
Graduated from Peking University.
The chosen one.
Regret coming back?
I... I didn't mean that.
I just feel
it's been three months,
and Xia Village is still the same Xia Village.
I've been here for 13 years.
Let me ask you.
Between a place's education and economic development,
which one is faster and which is slower?
They definitely complement each other.
Exactly.
You just took office.
What's the rush?
Keep skewering.
I'll go cut some more onions.
Hello. You must be in the wrong place.
Xiaojun.
You've grown so tall
and handsome.
You've kept in good shape too.
Wait, who are you?
This place looks exactly
like the photos.
As for you,
you've really impressed me.
Wait.
Keep your hands to yourself.
Ren Zhen.
Mr. Yin.
Guliqi.
Stop bringing me meat. I can't finish it.
My dad just slaughtered a new sheep
and asked me to bring some for you to try.
Thank your dad for me when you go back.
Got it.
It's fine.
This life will pass very quickly.
Mr. Yin,
how come I've never heard
you have a daughter?
Ren Zhen is
like a real daughter to me despite having no blood relation.
She was in the last class I taught
before I went to aid Xinjiang.
We have kept in touch ever since.
She likes to call me...
Dad Yin.
Where is Xiaojun?
Xiaojun?
He went to Shanghai for an internship.
His mother also went there to take care of him.
Still thinking about Xiacun Village?
I want to develop e-commerce
to sell all the crops in the village
so everyone can earn a bit more.
The leaders allocated some funds
to set up a professional livestreaming room for us.
But the hard part right now is
that we have no e-commerce talents available.
If there are no talents, just go find them.
Talents
won't just come knocking on your door.
Try some Xinjiang Pi La Hong.
You must all be hungry.
They are all my students.
Let me formally introduce you.
Jiao Li,
Party Secretary of Xia Village.
Hello.
Did I just assault a state official?
Ren Zhen.
I remember you've always been
working in e-commerce in Hangzhou.
Yes.
I worked at Shangle Group.
That's a top-tier
live-streaming e-commerce company.
It's alright.
Zhenzhen.
You were working day and night.
How do you have time to travel?
I quit.
Have some more barbecue.
I remember you used to be chubby.
Now you're so thin.
You've been meaning to visit me for years.
You didn't quit
just to visit me this time, did you?
I couldn't bear that.
It was just on the way.
But the difficulty right now
is that we have no e-commerce talent.
Zhenzhen.
Have you thought about finding a job?
Uncle Yin, I just quit.
I want to rest for a while.
Why rest at such a young age?
How about this.
You should go to Jiao Li's.
Sure.
Our village is just developing its e-commerce business.
We really need a talent like you.
Jiao Li is new to grassroots work.
Although his village is small,
it has great potential for development.
Look, we young people
don't necessarily have to make a living in big cities
to seek development.
The countryside is where you go from zero to one,
the most authentic place to strive.
Right, Mr. Yin?
Right.
What a dramatic thing to say.
I don't want to strive. I just want to lie flat.
Actually, Uncle Yin,
I just came to see you.
I'm flying to Urumqi tomorrow.
I want to head south to relax.
Well, if you've planned it,
I won't keep you.
Later,
Jiao Li, you see her off.
Okay.
Then I'll take you to the station later.
Thank you.
No problem.
Can I ask you
about live stream operations later?
Of course you can.
I don't quite understand
why you stay here.
There is a saying here:
'Find a Hubei teacher for studies,
and a Hubei doctor for medical treatment.'
Aiding Xinjiang is not easy.
Mr. Yin and his team came all the way here,
taking the hardest path.
I am a local,
so I should stay.
Okay.
Have a safe trip.
What do you think
if I stay?