This is my salary card.
You can spend the money from now on.
Currently, our cooperative
can't pay wages yet.
You followed me to Xia Village,
which is already a huge sign of trust in me.
I can't let you work for free, right?
From now on, my salary is your salary.
I know
this can't compare to your high salary in the big city.
But
whatever you want to eat every day from now on,
I will make it for you.
I will buy whatever you want to buy.
For other expenses,
just use this card.
I asked Teacher Yin for your birthday.
The password for this card
is your birthday.
No, no.
I can't take this.
Just consider it my technical investment.
If it makes money later,
just give me a cut.
I'm happy to be able to help you.
Take it.
This is all the commitment
I can make to you right now.
My salary card,
it's all for you to spend.
No.
Ren Zhen, wake up.
Ren Zhen.
You are here to build your career.
The Secretary is only talking to you about business.
Don't imagine a sweet romance.
What do you want to eat tomorrow?
Brother Secretary,
is that really what you told Ren Zhen?
What's wrong?
That sounds a bit weird.
You obviously went to explain the pay.
Why did it sound like a marriage proposal in a TV show?
Did it?
Yes.
It was so weird.
Well,
but those are my true feelings.
I still
haven't received my salary.
Why don't you take responsibility for me too?
You?
Your dad dumped you on me back then
and told me to train you.
You can leave,
but Ren Zhen can't.
It does seem a bit weird.
You can film more around here.
Let's go to the goji berry farm later.
Sure.
We'll film the villagers' daily lives today.
No problem.
I've already talked to them.
They are very enthusiastic
and said they'll fully cooperate.
Great.
We know about Xinjiang and goji berries,
but we've always had stereotypes
about its culture and customs.
For example,
that they ride camels to school,
or do the neck dance and stuff.
Then,
do you think so too?
Of course I don't.
As for information on the internet,
you still need to be able to distinguish it.
It's just that there are too few people like me.
We must make our voices heard
and strive to be the first to enter Xia Village.
Grandpa Bate,
Grandpa Bate, you don't need to be nervous.
Just pretend we don't exist
and do what you normally do.
Are we good?
Wrap it up.
Eat the grapes but don't spit out the skins.
Don't eat the grapes but spit out the skins.
Don't spit it.
Eat the grapes but don't spit out the skins.
Auntie Guli,
act more naturally.
Be natural.
Yes, smile.
No,
just pick them like you normally do.
Don't strike a pose.
Strike a pose?
This...
We are done shooting.
Are we done shooting?
We are not shooting anymore today.
How can we use these?
Here.
Time to eat.
Try some.
Have some meat.
I have no appetite.
The stuff we shot today,
won't it just make the outside stereotypes
even worse?
You still need to eat a little.
Come here.
You're really good at cooking.
If you like it,
I'll cook it for you every day.
Come on.
Do you all have
camera shyness?
There are so many staged videos online.
What we want is
a lively and natural feel.
You guys all
freeze up on camera.
How is this going to work?
Right.
I can just hide the camera.
Let's stop filming.
I need to hurry up and pick the ripe fruit.
The weather is great.
The goji berries are big and red.
Have another taste.
They're even better than a few days ago.
Goji berries grown in alkaline soil are the sweetest.
These drink water from the Tianshan Mountains.
A darling raised in the northwest wind.
What is this?
Nothing.
I'll leave you to it.
We're leaving now. Bye, Aunt Guli.
Bye.
Come back.
Ayijiang.
How can that thing move?
Come back here.
I left it facing Dad's desk
for an hour.
Do you think this will work?
When the green apple turns red.
That works perfectly.
By the way,
you can film me.
I can ride horses,
wrestle, and feed lambs.
Okay, we'll film you next time.
When the green apples turn red.
Grandpa Bate, how old is it?
Less than a year old.
What is that girl doing?
She... she's looking for eagles.
That machine in her hand
can detect the presence of eagles.
That's too much trouble.
I have an old friend
named Aerdin.
He can tell
where eagles are just by smelling.
That's amazing.
Of course.
Grandpa Bate,
look,
this is a photo of you and the lamb.
You're here
tricking the old man into taking pictures.
I have to say,
it looks really good.
How is it?
Do you like it?
I like it. It looks good.
Very handsome.