All right.
Everyone can have some free time for now.
Don't go too far.
Thank you, sir.
People always say
that human joys and sorrows are not connected.
But that's not true.
Our shared joys and sorrows
are all in poetry and literature.
From the most primitive epic poems
to Tang and Song poetry,
which of the stories they tell
are unfamiliar to us?
Dad Yin is right.
How could they be unfamiliar?
Jiao Li can recite a few lines of
'The Return' anytime, anywhere.
Sir, why are you laughing at me too?
I even assisted you in class just now.
I'm not laughing at you.
I just think this language Naadam
was very effective
and should be continued.
Stop laughing.
By the way,
did you distribute the money?
Yes.
I saw Aunt Guli and Uncle Tuoka
being very active on Moments.
The profits from our live streams are out.
I thought everyone has been working hard lately,
so I wanted to make them happy.
You should.
The live streaming is on track now.
We want to change its format next.
Even in our daily videos,
we want to slowly de-brand.
Besides grassroots cadres,
I hope more Xia villagers
can participate in our
publicity matrix.
These words sound like
they are missing something.
Missing what?
Expressing emotions through scenery,
and embedding feelings in the scenery.
Whether you look up or down,
all you see are people.
You forgot to look at your surroundings.
How about
we look around?
Sure, I was thinking the same thing.
Let's go.
The pace of e-commerce
can be a bit faster.
Not only should we sell good products from Xinjiang,
but also let more people know
about the beautiful scenery of Xinjiang.
I know what to do.
Bortala.
The green grasslands
have wind and grass,
as well as lakes and snow mountains.
Perhaps all far-off places
can find here
the wilderness of their heart.
Xiaerxili,
the golden hillside.
Driving all the way here
feels like entering a computer wallpaper.
Grasslands, wild flowers,
and antelopes.
It is Xinjiang's last natural gallery.
Don't forget to take a break during your journey.
The bubbling springs in Wenquan County
always welcome you for a dip.
Under the blue sky,
and in front of the snowy mountains,
experience the leisurely comfort.
Come visit the bazaar.
Like a local,
sit down, eat a few baked buns,
and drink a bowl of salty milk tea.
There is always a queue for the tandoor.
Meatball soup paired with Youtazi
is the daily romance unique to Xinjiang.
Finally,
of course we must come to see it.
It is the last teardrop of the Atlantic Ocean.
A sapphire on sunny days,
it looks like jade when the sky is azure.
Every appearance makes you feel
that the world is worth it.
Vertical cover 3:4
All set.
How is it going?
I've uploaded all the places we've been to.
Let the netizens help us choose
the location for our outdoor live stream.
With interaction and participation,
I think our promotional goals beyond selling products
have already been achieved in advance.
When I was studying in Beijing,
I also liked to look up at the night sky.
But the city lights were too bright
to see the Milky Way and the stars.
But here,
you can see them just by looking up.
Do you like looking at the stars?
I do.
Look.
That's Lyra.
The bright stars around it
form a quadrilateral.
Do you see it?
Really.
At the zenith
is Perseus.
By the way,
the news said that at the end of this month,
there will be a Perseid meteor shower.
Have you ever seen a meteor shower?
I haven't.
That's fine.
If the weather is good then,
we can pitch a tent here
and wait for it.
This is the biggest meteor shower in recent years.
The end of the month?
Yeah.
I... I think...
Is he pursuing you?
I noticed you haven't been answering calls lately.
I thought it was about a relationship.
Of course not.
He's the head of the e-commerce business at Shangle Group,
my former boss.
Is he asking you to go back to the company?
That's what he said at first.
But I refused.
I don't want to go back.
I never asked you
why you suddenly resigned and left the team to come here.
Actually,
I haven't contacted Father Yin for a long time.
Ever since my grandpa passed away,
I've been working desperately every day.
Even if my boss uses me as a tool,
I wish I could spend all my time
on work.
I don't dare to stop for even a moment.
Because once I stop,
I'll feel very empty
and directionless.
Earlier,
I asked if you wanted to send goji berries
to your family and friends,
and your former colleagues.
I didn't know about all this.
I'm sorry.
My colleagues all think I'm too competitive.
They even
secretly created a group chat to vent their frustration.
I accidentally saw it.
That was when I realized
how much they
hated me.
Who exactly is Ren Zhen?
A useful tool for the boss.
A soulless working machine.
The day I got out of the car with my luggage
was the first time my colleagues offered to help me.
Ridiculous, isn't it?
I previously
interned out of town for half a year too.
I found that the people there
lived and worked with anxiety.
They didn't like
or want to understand others.
One day,
I felt I was going to become like that too.
I didn't like it,
so I came back.
That's great.
You found a place where you want to stay.
What about you?
I plan
to go back to Hangzhou after the outdoor livestream.
The leader of Shangle started his own company.
He invited me to be a partner.
You've decided?
That's good too.
Since you'll be a partner,
you can realize your value more.
Once the livestream is developed, there won't be many variables.
With you here,
I believe whatever problems arise,
you can solve them.
The last crop of goji berries has been harvested.
It's getting cold.
It's time for me to go too.
Dad Yin, I've thought about it.
This is not the place for me to stay.
I want to wait
until the e-commerce business is stable,
and then I'll leave.
Are you sure?
I remember
when I was bullied by my classmates as a kid,
saying I had no parents,
you stood up to protect me.
Since then,
I called you
Dad Yin.
At that time,
you were so thin and small,
and so stubborn.
But you never cried.
Instead, calling me Dad Yin
made me cry.
Dad Yin,
do you know
what an empty urbanite is?
I am one.
I'm here,
really relaxed and happy.
But I know
this is just an escape.
If
I stay because I have no direction,
then one day when I meet a new problem,
I will escape
and leave again.
Who says escaping is wrong?
People can also find a new direction
while escaping.
Just follow your heart.
The Perseid meteor shower
is the most spectacular.
It's a pity you're leaving.
You won't be able to see it.
Shooting stars,
they flash by
and eventually fade away.
Just think of me as a meteor shower
that fell over Xiacun.
The sky is clear now,
and I should disappear too.
Then what if this meteor shower
falls into my heart?