Here are the steamed buns.
Here you go.
Eat slowly. They're fresh out of the pot.
Don't burn yourself.
You just ran out like that?
What else?
I couldn't help anyway.
Staying there and arguing would just make me a nuisance.
Forget it. It's not easy for anyone.
When I first came to Xinjiang,
the locals told me...
It has to go through three stages.
Want to know?
Ku, ku, and ku.
What are you talking about?
It means
the local air is dry
and it's windy all year round.
People's skin
will definitely become dry and withered.
That's the first 'ku'.
When outsiders start working here,
it's inevitable to encounter bumps and bruises.
Besides,
being thousands of miles away from home,
they must be psychologically fragile.
This is hardship.
Then there is also the cool part.
Since they are here,
and they have persisted.
Don't you think that's cool?
I just want to salvage the situation
and get things back on track quickly.
But he doesn't agree with me.
I understand.
Back then,
he didn't agree with me either.
When I first came to Xinjiang,
Teaching time is tight,
and the workload is heavy.
As for the kids in this class,
most only attended primary schools in pastoral areas.
Their foundation in Chinese is poor,
and their understanding of ancient poetry is average.
This Jiao Li
is the kid in class
who defies me the most.
Jiao Li,
can you write a few more words on the test paper?
This statue of yours,
I have seen it many times.
Don't laugh.
Nazahai is my good friend.
I miss it.
Jiao Li used to be so arrogant.
Mr. Yin, you aren't even mad about this?
There are only bad teachers,
no bad students.
He was just a child in a new environment,
feeling overwhelmed
and insecure.
If I couldn't make him feel at ease,
how could he
enter the world of literature?
But it was exactly because of him
that I
wanted to change my teaching method.
Secretary,
you should go find Renzhen quickly.
Renzhen wasn't wrong about what happened yesterday either.
Renzhen?
What is this?
This was taken when I was in middle school
by Mr. Yin.
Mr. Yin, this is...
That is
a line I gave to Nazahai
from Su Shi's poem.
It's very fitting.
(2) The author saw a large lotus leaf next to the red lotus, slowly...
I hope you
and your good friend...
Everyone can experience the joy
of literature in your class.
The old man acting like a wild youth,
hound on the left, falcon on the right.
You can recite it.
Teacher,
I really like this line.
Su Shi never visited Xinjiang,
but this line
seems to describe life on the grassland.
I understand this line,
but
there are many others I don't quite get.
Chinese,
is actually not that difficult.
As long as you bring it into your life
to identify with and embrace it,
you will resonate with
more ancient poetry.
I seem to have only thought about
embracing and identifying with Xiacun,
but I didn't embrace and identify with her.
Secretary,
what are you talking about?
Tolerance and acceptance.
Mr. Yin,
is this what you want to tell me?
I just want to share with you
some of my personal experiences.
If it can inspire you,
that would be great.
Back then,
promoting the language tutorials
wasn't smooth.
Actually, it's not that people don't want to understand.
They just need some time and space
to build a common language,
reach a consensus through trust,
and accomplish something together.
What do you think?
I...
Hello, everyone.
I am Jiao Li, the resident secretary of Xia Village.
First of all,
I want to say sorry to you all.
Our first live stream went very smoothly.
The goji berries were sold out,
and the farmers were very happy.
We packed and shipped them together.
We imagined how happy you would be
when you ate fresh goji berries
for the first time.
We also expected that
when the next crop of goji berries ripens,
they could be sent out of Xia Village again.
However, in recent days,
we have successively received returns
and refunds.
Half of the packages
had problems during transportation.
The goji berries we packed with our own hands
returned to Xia Village in this way.
As the village secretary,
I have an unshirkable responsibility.
Regarding the logistics,
I didn't listen to the team's advice.
I blindly handed over the packing work
to the farmers who were unfamiliar with the process.
That's what caused such a bad result.
At present,
we have finished processing
all after-sales orders.
We have learned from this experience.
We hope you can give us another chance.
We
will definitely deliver the goji berry products
perfectly to your hands.
Thank you again for your trust,
tolerance, and recognition.
Thank you.
P.S. When is the second live stream?
I really want to eat fresh goji berries.
Oh my.
You're making me feel so guilty.
Sorry I was too loud earlier. Please don't mind.
Face it bravely and stick to your dreams.
The fresh fruit I bought didn't go bad.
Have you made up your mind?
Mr. Yin.
How did you know what I wanted to do?
The big city is definitely different from here.
The methodology you are familiar with
would be hard to even get started here.
You are so smart,
of course you know.
Jiao Li doesn't just want the villagers
to help pack.
He wants to
teach them how to fish,
so that the fate of goji berries
is in the hands of the people who plant them.
These villagers,
Since they are new to these things,
you need to give them some time and space.
For so long,
I've been using my old work mindset
to think and act.
It was me who didn't accept them.
Mr. Yin.
I want to hurry back
and solve the problem with everyone.
Go.
I'm sorry.