(Rated 18+ Content suitable
for audiences 18 years and older.)
(There may be images, sound or content
that requires viewing discretion.)
(Viewers under age of 18
should be advised.)
(This series is fictional)
(not related to real person,
place or event.)
- Is it out yet?
- Come on!
Come on, come on.
I'm so excited.
I'm excited too.
My hands are freezing.
Hey... we...!
We made it to the next round!
Let’s practice even harder.
Yeah, also get
ready for the next round.
But can we celebrate today?
Practice comes first.
Yes, yes.
- Fine, then.
- Come on, everyone,
Let’s go.
Okay.
Nice work, guys!
We made it to the next round!
Friends From the Moon!
♪Until I discovered myself♪
♪That I secretly just wanted you♪
♪I accidentally let you into
my heart. And now you're there♪
♪When I don't see you,
my heart starts to fade♪
♪I'm confused when
you're not around♪
♪Because I miss you, is that why?♪
♪So I end up feeling lonely♪
♪I'm always alone like this♪
♪If it could be like that,
it would be good♪
♪But it would be even
better if you were here♪
♪On the day we met eyes♪
♪I found the person
I've been searching for♪
♪The world that used to be private♪
♪I've let you into it♪
♪From that day when
there was no one♪
♪You came with freshness♪
♪My heart, captivated
by you, embellished♪
♪You've changed my world♪
♪Into ours♪
=Monster Next Door=
(Last night, both I and God)
(asked each
other to be boyfriends)
(and then we…)
(We kissed on the balcony)
(under the dark sky
where we couldn't see the stars.)
(My first kiss with God)
(felt so good and excited.)
Well, well,
what are you thinking about?
No!
I wasn’t thinking about anything!
There’s no need to be shy at all.
As a couple,
it’s something you’ll have to do anyway.
Just take things slowly
with something like this.
God hasn't said anything yet,
right, Diew?
There’s a first time for everything.
It’s better to be prepared.
Whatever happens
will happen.
Prepare myself?
Hello, Grandpa.
Hello, Diew.
Have you finished the exam?
I’ve finished the exam.
How have you been lately, Grandpa?
I'm fine, don't worry.
Check out my guns.
So firm, see?
Hey, Diew,
your mom wanted to know
if you’re coming home
for the school break.
Um,
do you remember the friend
next door that I told you about?
Yes, I do.
His name is God.
Well, during this school break,
he invited me to go on a trip
out of Bangkok with him.
So, do you want to go?
I do want to go.
I’d like to try
doing something new.
That sounds good,
but don’t forget to
share your trip photos for me.
I don’t know if I will go yet, Grandpa.
Why not?
Well, the others going on the trip
are God’s friends,
but I’m only close to God...
You’re coughing?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I’m as strong as ever, kid.
Look.
Can you see?
Okay,
but, anyway
So I'm hesitating
whether to go or not.
Grandpa, are you
sure you’re feeling okay?
I’m sure. I’m absolutely fine.
I just choked on the rambutan
that your mom gave me.
The rambutan this season
are great. Look.
See?
But you haven’t eaten any of it yet.
Oh my, it’s time,
my TV show is waiting for me
Got to go.
Okay, but you need
to take care of yourself too.
I'm worried.
Don’t worry. I’m perfectly healthy.
And don’t forget to let me know
whether you’re going
on the trip with them or not.
I’m hanging up now
Grandpa!
(God:)
(Are you almost here?)
(I’ve already
ordered our food.)
Oh, God.
Come inside first.
How was the audition result?
It’s just as I thought.
It's okay. Next time...
We’ve passed the audition.
Oh,
You startled me!
Congratulations.
Can you also reward me with...
a kiss on the cheek?
Come closer, then.
Wait here for a bit.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Close your eyes too.
Do I have to close my eyes too?
No peeking.
Hurry up.
Someone really wants
his cheek to be kissed.
Keep your eyes closed.
What is this?
Can’t he also be happy for you?
God!
Someone’s boyfriend smells really good.
Stop it.
Did you just kiss me?
Thank you.
Hello?
Oh, you’ve arrived?
Just leave it there,
I’ll go get it.
Okay, thank you.
Food is here.
I’ll go get it now.
Okay.
Be quick.
Someone already misses you.
Okay.
(I think Pee is my first love.)
(I wonder if
he feels the same way.)
God, I'm back.
Did you wait long?
The deliver guy got lost.
Not at all.
What were you doing?
I was just looking around.
Let’s eat now.
Shall we?
Wow, that’s a big bite.
Yummy.
That photo from his diary
is definitely his ex.
Calm down.
Maybe it’s not what you think.
If you don’t believe me,
just ask him.
Everyone has a past,
but right now, Diew’s boyfriend
is you.
True!
What do you mean by 'true'?
This sushi is truly delicious.
It’s my favorite.
- Right?
- Right.
It's really delicious.
So much laundry to do.
Seems like no one comes here.
It's good that there
aren't many people today.
This one.
Give me.
Aah!
Why do we have to do the laundry?
Why don't clothes wash themselves?
It would be great if
that happened.
Right?
Our job is just to
put the clothes in the machine.
You’re such a dummy.
And I’ve told you so many times
that colored clothes need to
be washed separately from the whites.
We’ve put the clothes
in the machine already.
Why doesn’t it separate
the colors by itself?
You’re talking as if
you are the one doing it.
That’s true,
but thinking about it,
it would be nice
if it were possible.
That way, you wouldn’t get tired.
If you don’t want me to get tired,
then you should do
it yourself sometimes.
What will you do if I'm not around?
Hey!
you’re going
to stay with me anyway.
You’re not going
to leave me, right?
Sure,
I’m not going anywhere.
Whoever gets to be
your boyfriend is super lucky.
I don’t want you to ever have a boyfriend.
I’m jealous.
Well, well,
I can’t ever touch you anymore, now?
Fine. Won’t touch you, then.
- Wan.
- What?
Here comes
Wan.
Wan, I'm ticklish.
Exactly, you’re ticklish.
You want to go?
If I really get a boyfriend,
what are you going to do?
Oh, Beer!
I didn’t expect to see you.
And are you...
Yeah, I’m just sleepy.
and this floor looks kinda comfy...
Come on, get up.
This is Ton, my friend
from the photography club.
Uh, Ton, this is Wan.
Hey, Beer,
About the thing
you asked for my help,
any updates?
Aren't you going to introduce him?
This is my boyfriend.
Hello.
Ton has told me a lot about you.
Ton!
Did you badmouth me to your boyfriend?
Hey, easy now.
Badmouth?
You’re just like a saint.
What saint?
Just tell me what he said.
I just told you.
Nothing to badmouth about.
Are you sure?
Don't tell him.
- Ton!
- What?
Tell me, tell me now.
I told you I didn’t say anything.
♪From that day
when there was no one♪
♪You came with freshness♪
♪My heart, captivated
by you, embellished♪
♪You've changed my world♪
♪Into ours♪
Hey, guys!
Let’s call it a day.
The competition is tomorrow,
so let’s just rest and be prepared.
I'm so freaking exhausted!
Aren't you going back yet, God?
I going to stay and practice a bit more.
Don’t overdo it.
Save your strength for tomorrow.
Yeah, I know.
Save your energy
for tomorrow too, man.
Okay, okay.
See you, guys.
Well, we're going then.
Please wish me luck for the competition.
I hope everything
goes smoothly today.
I’m here to support you.
With you supporting me,
I’ll surely win today.
Got to go.
- Diew...
- Here.
- Let’s hurry.
- Okay.
(Music Competition 2024)
(To Diew: I'm getting ready
for the stage.)
Goddamn it, God.
Stay still, will you?
Why are you pacing around?
I’m getting cross-eyed.
I know you’re excited, dude,
but you’re making me dizzy.
Hey, guys!
Let’s gather here.
What is it?
Come closer.
Give it your all.
Alright, hands out.
Friends From The Moon
Let’s go!
Friends From The Moon,
please stand by.
Okay.
God.
Let's go.
Got to go.
Let’s hurry.
God, you’re drumming with those brushes?
What should I do?
Game,
are you free today?
How about we go to the music concert?
I was actually going
to ask you.
Today, Win and God are competing.
So, let’s go, then.
Let’s.
Is something wrong?
Diew!
God!
Thanks for finding these spares for me.
Even though they're a bit old,
they should be usable.
This is the best I could find.
This is already more
than enough. Thanks.
Good luck!
(Music Competition 2024)
God!
Hello, we're Friends From the Moon.
♪Until I discovered myself♪
♪That I secretly just wanted you♪
♪I accidentally let you into
my heart. And now you're there♪
♪On the day we met eyes♪
♪I found the person
I've been searching for♪
♪The world that used to be private♪
♪I've let you into it♪
♪From that day
when there was no one♪
♪You came with freshness♪
=Monster Next Door=