''Meeting You Loving You'' - Zheng Guofeng & He Manting
♫  I can see meteors through your eyes  ♫
♫  The fireworks have lit up your face  ♫
♫  The love I've kept hidden in my youth  ♫
♫  I'm finally going to tell you  ♫
♫  You are deliberately acting like a spoiled child  ♫
♫  Your gentle sweet words  ♫
♫  Carry your sincere heart  ♫
♫  I'm falling for you  ♫
♫  It's you, the one I met amidst the vast crowd  ♫
♫  We promised each other happiness  ♫
♫  To move out from the lonely jungle  ♫
♫  Into my heart  ♫
♫  I believe in meeting you amidst the vast crowd  ♫
♫  My happiness is extended indefinitely  ♫
♫  I've entered your heart  ♫
♫  My name was written on the meteor and you are my destiny  ♫
[Meeting You, Loving You]
[Episode 10]
What do we do if Director Lin still doesn't agree to it?
No ifs. There's no turning back for Huateng Land.
- Director Lin.
Have a seat.
Director Lin. We're so sorry for missing the appointment.
Besides asking you to give Huateng Land another chance,
we came to apologize to you in person as well.
If you're here for Qinghu, I suggest you don't waste your time.
I know that Wancheng hasn't decided on the final business partner.
Could you give us another chance since Qinghu holds a special meaning to you?
At least, do take a look at our latest proposal.
Tell me then. How is it that Qinghu is of great significance to me?
As far as I know, Qinghu was where you worked during the Down to the Countryside Movement in the late '70s.
You stayed there for five years.
Later on, you established Wancheng and devoted yourself to the real estate industry.
Then, you began to prepare for the Impression Qinghu project.
So far, it should have been nearly ten years now.
This is the project that you invested the longest time in since you established Wancheng.
Young lady.
Don't act as if you know me well after reading a few online news articles about me.
On the contrary, I'm disgusted with this place, Qinghu.
To me, it doesn't matter who wins the tender or what the inside story is.
As long as Wancheng doesn't lose money, it's the same no matter who gets the tender.
But after all, Qinghu is where your career started.
I don't believe you'll choose to work with a partner of bad character.
For the things that I've lost because of it...
I won't change my mind.
You may go now.
Director Lin. Please stay.
I'm sorry.
I remember you once said that in business, there are no deals that can't be negotiated.
What's missing is having the right bargaining chips.
Qinghu project may be of little value to you.
But for Huateng Land, it is the only way out.
No matter what the conditions are, we will try our best to meet them.
Young man, that's quite some claim. Okay. I'll give you another chance.
I want to see her performance again. Can you make that happen?
[Haicheng Grand Theater, Admission Ticket]
[Mei Han Xiang Ballet Tour]
Ms. Mei Han Xiang?
She has retired from the stage for many years.
If you can't do it, don't talk big.
If you can make it happen, you can come to me then.
[Dancing Romance]
If it weren't for that big box of tickets,
I really thought that Director Lin deliberately tried to make things difficult for us.
He probably really likes her.
The oil painting in his room seems pretty old.
I'm really surprised that someone his age will be a star-struck fan.
We should figure out how to get Ms. Mei to perform again.
Have you watched Ni Ping's show of searching for lost family members, "Waiting For Me"?
We can do that.
Make sure nothing goes wrong with Ms. Mei's interview.
We need to report it after that.
Okay.
My time in the media industry wasn't in vain.
I can finally put it to good use. Wait for me.
Excuse me. Could you do me a favor?
- Sorry, we're in a hurry.
- Wait.
We're in the same line of work.
I hope you can take me along to meet Ms. Mei.
I just want to convey a message from an old fan of hers.
That's why I can't let you come.
This time, we finally got an exclusive interview with Ms. Mei.
How can I take you with us?
Sorry.
Excuse me.
If it's not convenient for you to take us in,
could you lend us your equipment and credentials?
Are you out of your mind?
You may take a break over there.
How's that possible?
Do you know them?
Aren't you in the same line of work? Perhaps, they know you.
Come on.
Why are you sitting over here?
Where's our camera?
Where are our credentials?
Su Zhinian.
Have you ever seen a photographer in a suit?
Photographers carry equipment and brave the weather.
None is as smartly dressed as you.
What are you doing?
Remove your coat.
And this too. Untuck your shirt.
The tie. Loosen it.
Hurry. Why are you being shy?
You have to make it look real.
If not, Ms. Mei might see through us, and that will blow our covers.
Did you see two people with a camera?
I think they went that way. Go after them now.
What's going on? They change their minds?
That's right. What if they did? Come on.
How can they do that?
Hurry up.
How can you lose your camera?
I have no idea. We have to get it back.
[VIP Lounge]
Hurry.
What do we do?
We can't go out now.
This...
This isn't appropriate.
It's okay. They did it willingly.
What matters now is to find Ms. Mei.
You...
What do we do?
Ms. Mei.
Oh my.
Who are you?
We're reporters from Haicheng TV Station and we're here to interview you.
Is it?
But I seem to remember seeing you two at the hotel lobby yesterday.
Indeed, we're not reporters.
We took the liberty to see you today because we have a favor to ask of you.
Here's the thing, Ms. Mei. We know an elderly man who's a fan of yours.
He would go to each and every one of your performances.
His greatest wish is to watch you perform again.
I know it's a big ask.
But I hope you'll reconsider it.
Thank him on my behalf. I've retired now.
I won't be performing on stage anymore.
Ms. Mei.
Come on in.
- What's the matter?
- It's them!
It's them. They took our camera and credentials!
Didn't they offer them to us?
Here's the thing, Ms. Mei.
These two stole their credentials...
Stole? They disguised as reporters to come in here.
So sorry for the interruption. I'm so sorry.
How is it? Is it broken? You two, please come with me.
It should be fine.
[Dressing Room]
Hold on.
What's Lin Hansheng's relationship with you?
It's almost time. He should be here soon.
Let's get ready.
Okay, I'll step aside.
You can't go.
Why?
How embarrassing it is if you're not here?
What if something unexpected happens? I won't be able to handle it.
Look at you.
Go. Sit at the back. I'll take care of it.
Okay.
Hi.
I'm Wu Gangqiang.
I'm going to the gents.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Dr. Yan! Dr. Yan, wait up!
Dr. Yan! What's wrong? None is acceptable?
That's right. Totally unacceptable!
Stop wasting your time, okay?
I know what you're up to.
But there's no need for that and it's impossible.
- But...
- But?
But what?
Hello?
Why would a pregnant lady... Cerebral hypoxia and hemorrhage?
Which surgeon is in charge?
How are the vital signs?
All right. I'll be there in ten.
Go home on your own.
Dr. Yan, drive safe!
Hi. Is this your friend's wallet?
Let me take a look.
[Yan Yuan]
That's right. Thank you.
You're welcome. It's what we do.
Wait for me for three years.
I'll cheer on for you alone for the rest of my life.
Winter of 1978. Lin Hansheng.
When you return, I shall dance for you alone.
Waiting for you.
Winter of 1978. Mei Hanxiang.
I bet Director Lin couldn't forget Ms. Mei.
If not, he wouldn't still
be keeping this photo and those tickets after so many years.
He stayed in Qinghu for five years and didn't leave until 1983.
And Ms. Mei left Haicheng in 1981.
After several twists and turns,
Ms. Mei went abroad and joined the American Ballet Theater and never came back.
Why do you think they couldn't be together?
Perhaps, back in those days, they had to yield to circumstances.
Director Lin.
Where's the photo?
I'm sorry. I accidentally put it inside the file holder.
Thank you.
Hanxiang.
Lin Hansheng.
You've aged.
That's right.
We're not young anymore.
But I don't think I'm old.
I said the wrong thing.
You're still so young and beautiful.
Look at you.
You don't even know how to tell a lie.
Why have you lied to me for so many years?
I'm sorry.
I waited all these years
not to hear you say this.
I...
Han...
Stay with Director Lin. I'll go and find Ms. Mei.
Actually, it was Ms. Mei who wanted to see you.
I think she deliberately set the last stop of the tour
in Haicheng just to wait for you.
That night, it was my first time going on the stage.
I was so excited.
After the performance, I was reluctant to leave.
I didn't even get changed and went up on stage again.
The stage was completely dark.
But I wasn't afraid at all.
I kept spinning and dancing
until a beam of light suddenly shone on me.
That year,
I was just a poor kid.
So poor that I had only a few books with me.
To make some pocket money, I went to work at the theater.
At first, I just couldn't get it.
With all the dancing and jumping on the stage, what's there really to see?
Until that night, many people came to the show.
When the curtain came down, there was loud, thunderous applause.
After the show, I was carrying a torchlight and I suddenly came across her.
It gave her quite a shock and she fell down.
Later on, my foot injury was healed.
But I couldn't fit into my pointe shoes.
So he searched all around Haicheng
and spent all his money
to customize a pair of pointe shoes for me.
He brought it to me
and said...
From now on, all your pointe shoes
will be my responsibility.
Then, she...
pretended to be mad and stared at me.
"If I were to dance for a lifetime,"
"how long do you think you could take responsibility for me?"
He said,
"For a lifetime."
But not long after,
he was sent to the rural area in Qinghu.
In less than a year,
he wrote me a letter
and told me he had fallen in love with a local girl
and that he would marry her at the end of the year.
But as far as I know, Director Lin doesn't have a wife.
I only know that later on.
If this were to happen in this era,
his lie would have been exposed.
But back in those days...
Why did you lie to her back then?
[Arrogant Man]
Something happened to me in Qinghu.
I thought I would never be able to go back anymore.
So you didn't want to waste her time?
How should I put it?
Back then,
I would do whatever it takes just to come back.
As long as there was a chance to perform, I would fight for it.
No matter how dangerous the task may be,
I would do it.
That year, during the winter solstice,
I accidentally fell in Qinghu when I was working in the open air.
I even broke my leg.
It left me with a high fever and pneumonia.
I was bedridden for over half a year.
What's more ironic
is that when I was at my lowest,
it was Hanxiang's starting point.
My classmates told me
that a well-known dance troupe reached out to her.
So without hesitation, you lied to her
that you fell for someone else.
I thought this was the only thing I could do for her.
But she isn't married either.
Why didn't you go and see her?
You clearly can't get over her.
Why is it disconnected at such a critical moment?
It's okay.
Let bygones be bygones.
Thank you for tonight.
- Doctor.
Doctor, how's my wife?
Don't worry. The baby is safely delivered.
What about my wife?
But as for the mother...
- How is she?
- We've tried our best.
What? Tried your best?
Tried your best?
- My daughter!
- Mom.
- Mom!
My daughter!
Mom! Mom!
Mom. Come on.
Here.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
You left your wallet in the restaurant.
You didn't have to pass it to me today.
It's so late now, and you had to come all the way here.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I saw what happened earlier.
Don't beat yourself up.
When I got to the operating theater,
she had already given birth.
The baby was fine.
But she...
I knew I couldn't save her.
The only thing I could do was to do my best
to help her live through the day.
I don't want that child to spend every birthday
with the memory
of his mother's death in the future.
Dr. Yan. Don't be upset.
I know you've tried your best.
You're just a doctor, not a god.
You don't have to shoulder all the responsibility.
You've done a good job.
Is that really what you think?
You are the gentlest person I have ever met.
I guess there are many wonderful memories between you and your mom.
It's late. I'm on duty today.
Come on. I'll walk you out.
She knew it was a misunderstanding.
Why does Ms. Mei still refuse to see Director Lin?
Director Lin is to blame too.
He knew she was single. But he wouldn't take the initiative.
Does he still feel inferior and worried that he would be a drag on her?
Something like that.
Director Lin suffered an illness after he fell into the water.
Later on, he found out he had a tumor.
He's been going in and out of surgery all these years.
So what if I can't get over her?
I don't have much time left.
Why be a drag on her?
[Non-Performing Asset]
Is something wrong with your health?
I have a favor to ask of you. Don't ever tell her this.
It's a tumor.
Okay, I give you my word.
If I were you,
I would make the same choice as well.
He thinks that Ms. Mei belongs to the stage,
instead of staying by his side, who's a sick old man.
It's not what he thinks! It's what she thinks!
Since they're in love, they should cherish every moment that they get to spend together.
Why all the hesitations?
It's not enough for two people to love each other.
They have to be responsible for one another.
Do men enjoy these false notions of self-sacrifice?
Director Lin kept saying that it was for Ms. Mei's sake.
If you ask me, the sufferings that she endured for the next few decades were all because of him.
And now, he's doing this.
To be blunt, it's just pure selfishness.
In the future, if anyone dares to pull this "It's for your own good" on me,
I'll tell him to get out of the way!
Well, what do you prefer him to do?
Obviously, I hope
we can rely on each other and have mutual trust.
No matter what happens, we'll face it together.
Why am I telling you this?
What do you care?
That's mine!
I'm surprised you have such a high standard.
Add another criterion on top of that. Able to ward off evil.
You're so annoying.
I'm being serious. Why did you interrupt me?
Whatever it is, I'm telling Ms. Mei about it.
It's up to her to decide.
No way. I gave Director Lin my word.
That's right. You did, not me.
I'm going to the washroom. Wait here for me.
That's not right. What is she up to again?
Ms. Mei!
I was about to find you. Here are the tickets for tomorrow's show.
[Admission Ticket]
You two can come tomorrow.
Thank you, Ms. Mei.
Ms. Mei. I came to tell you something.
Sorry.
Okay, thank you.
Director Lin.
Director Lin...
From now on, you don't have to tell me about him.
Go back and rest. Don't catch a cold.
Wait, Ms. Mei. I want to tell you that...
- Qingchun is allergic to pollen.
- I'm not!
It's getting late. Rest earlier.
Ms. Mei!
Su Zhinian, I'm not done talking!
Why did you drag me here?
Su Zhinian!
Su Zhinian. Even if I don't tell Ms. Mei about it, I can make Director Lin come clean with her.
Sure.
Tomorrow is her official performance. You have until tomorrow.
Okay. I'll take my chances.
Sure. Bring it on.
Speak.
Can't find it?
That means she noticed that something wasn't right.
No worries.
Get someone to keep an eye on her and Su Zhinian.
Are you working this weekend?
I was recording a domestic violence program in the past two days.
It's a wrap today.
I heard that the American Ballet Theater has a tour in Haicheng.
My friend gave me two tickets.
Haicheng is my hometown. I'm familiar with the place.
Let's take a trip there and have a short vacation.
You still remember that I like to watch ballet performances?
Of course.
I remember there's a ballerina by the last name Mei, right?
That's right.
But the one I like is Alina Somova from Russia.
Right, she's great too.
Let's watch her performance if there's a chance.
-Sure.
- Let's go.
- Director Lin.
- Why are you here?
If you're here because of the project, I've notified my staff about it.
Just send your proposal over will do.
No. No. It's Ms. Mei.
Just now, Ms. Mei...
What happened to her?
Ms. Mei doesn't have a family.
She might not have anyone in this lifetime.
Are you willing to take care of her?
Wait. Where's she now?
Cut the crap. Tell me where she is. I'll go and find her.
She... She's all right.
I'm sorry, Director Lin. I lied to you.
I just wanted you to get a taste of how Ms. Mei would feel in the future.
You're afraid of not being able to take care of her and that you'll waste her time.
But you never thought about if all she wanted was to find someone who could take care of her,
why stay single until now?
It's true.
Besides love, two people stay together because of their responsibility for one another.
But don't neglect the fact that it's one another.
She, too, wants to be responsible of you.
What Ms. Mei wants is someone who can take care of her
and is willing to be taken care of by her.
Later, get someone to move the things over there.
- Okay.
- Don't let it get in the way.
- Go ahead.
Ms. Mei.
Do you know why Director Lin wants to see you perform again?
It's because he has never come to your show, not once in his life.
But he bought the tickets for all your performances.
But he never stepped inside because of fear
and because he couldn't.
All these years, he could only look at the oil painting in his study
of you dancing on the stage when you two first met
to make good on his promise.
That's right.
I haven't made good on my promise to him.
It's over.
I lost.
I guess he's not coming.
Let's go.
Hanxiang.
Lin Hansheng.
I owe you a dance, I've made good on my promise.
Perhaps,
it's done between the two of us.
Hanxiang.
I know.
When I was young, I didn't take care of myself and fell ill.
I had surgery last year.
Truth be told, I don't know how much time do I have left.
I would like to ask you
if I could use my remaining time
to take care of you and to keep you company?
Here, Ms. Mei. Three, two, one.
Cheese!
So this is love.
Didn't you have your heart broken? Do you only know that now?
Shut up, will you?
Ms. Mei. Look.
It's nice, isn't it?
- It's so nice.
- Not bad.
- I'll take a picture for you two.
- It's okay.
- Sure. Thank you.
- Come on.
Come on.
I'll take a picture for you.
All right. One, two, three.
- Sir, how much is it?
- 43 yuan.
It's a waste of this last piece of film.
It's all your fault. I look so awful in this!
- Give it to me if you don't like it.
- Why should I?
I paid for the film.
So what?
Well, about our bet last night.
How do we go about that?
What do you think?
Ms. Mei stayed because of you.
Director Lin showed up because of me.
But the good thing is they ended up together.
We're even then.
Even? That's boring.
How about this? We both won.
Promise me one thing, and I'll promise you one. How about that?
What do you want?
- Brother Yinan used to tell me—
- No.
You...
No point staring at me.
You poured so much vinegar. Don't you find it sour?
I like it that way.
Can't I?
You sure are a capitalist, Director Su.
You won't let yourself suffer losses even when having a bowl of wonton.
So aren't you going to reconsider what I just said?
No.
What a penny-pincher, you won't even lend me 500 yuan.
This was what you were talking about?
Why did you bring Qin Yinan up then?
Well... This is his hometown.
He used to tell me that the night market here is worth a visit.
So?
''Passing Through Your Memories'' - Zheng Guofeng
♫  In the end, I can only watch you  ♫
♫  walk towards happiness as I'm just a guest  ♫
♫  A love that I can't grasp  ♫
♫  Making promises I can't fulfill  ♫
♫  Let someone take my place  ♫
♫  The encounters we had  ♫
♫  is like a heavy downpour drenching my heart  ♫
♫  A destination not in sight  ♫
♫  Without time accompanying me  ♫
♫  I'll continue to search by myself  ♫
♫  I'm only just passing through your memories  ♫
♫  But our brief exchange is unforgettable  ♫
♫  What can tear two hearts that beats as one  ♫
♫  I'm only just passing through your memories  ♫
♫  I so naively thought we'd have eternity  ♫
♫  Let's part ways after giving each other our blessings  ♫
♫  I'm barely just passing through your memories  ♫
♫  But our brief exchange is unforgettable  ♫
♫  What can tear apart our hearts?  ♫
♫  I'll just stop passing through your memories  ♫
♫  There will be a day where I'll stay forever  ♫
♫  Fulfilling my promise without regrets  ♫