=In the Grip of Love=
=Episode 29=
Ms. Ling.
Are you...
It's all right. Get back to work.
Did my mother say something to you?
She tried to get rid of you?
Let me talk to her, okay?
It's not that.
I chose to leave.
I made a big mistake.
I must take responsibility.
Let me come with you.
I'm done working here.
Can you not be so childish?
Is everything I do
always so childish to you?
That's not what I meant.
Fine.
Put these down.
We can stay here.
Or, we can just leave.
I made this choice.
Could you respect my decision?
Respect?
All right. I respect that.
You always make me accept
the decisions you make.
You never run it by me before deciding.
Do you only see me
as an ignorant boy
who doesn't deserve your trust,
who is unreliable,
and someone who is not worthy
of having a future with you?
Calm down.
You never trusted me.
You never thought about
having a future with me
from the get-go.
The agreement we signed?
The satellite?
They were all fancy talks to swindle me.
I want to be with you
and create a future with you.
Is that too much to ask?
All I want is the evidence.
Fine.
Very well.
I'll find you the evidence you want.
I'll find Zhou Ju.
(Perhaps Mum is right.)
(My presence will cloud your judgment.)
(Zhaohe.)
(You must finish it on your own.)
Yes, she is not there.
Okay. Let me know
when you have a lead.
Yu Xiling.
Yu Xiling?
(Every satellite has its own mission.)
(Have some candy and be happy.)
(Don't just follow the orbit.)
(Fulfill your mission.)
(Beauty Mo)
Open the door.
Yu Xiling is gone.
And this is what you turned into?
She was right.
You are childish.
You got what you wanted.
Are you happy now?
Yu Xiling left the company
because I made her decide.
She chose
her relationship with you.
Wasting your life away
is a disgrace to her resolve.
You are hurting yourself.
Don't you realize how it pains me
to see you like this?
She has always envied
our relationship.
It's the one thing she never had.
She has always yearned
for the warmth of a family.
But because of her,
we grew apart.
You started to resent me
and even hate me.
She didn't want to get in the way
of our relationship.
Therefore, she chose to leave.
Don't you think her absence
is great for both of us?
I didn't want to tell you,
but look at your now.
Who knows how long you can last?
The shares she gave up
and her career that is now in shambles
will be all for nothing.
I thought you hated her.
Why would you care about her?
I stand by what I said.
I've never disliked her.
I simply didn't trust her.
However, she has proven to me
that you were right to trust her.
Why are you telling me this now?
Are you mocking me?
Is that what this is?
Mo Sanxing bested me once.
I can't afford another defeat.
Making Mo Sanxing think
I blame Yu Xiling
for all the losses
and that I am now desperate
with no cards left to play,
will lower his guard
and buy us more time
to look for an opening
and evidence.
And this is why you chased her away?
You are my son!
Of course I want you to be
with the woman you love.
But as the major shareholder
of Sanxing Group,
I must look at the bigger picture.
I must consider the interests
of the whole company.
Given the circumstances,
there were no other choices.
I'd do the same if I had to.
Very well.
Bear in mind
that no matter
how your uncle and I fight each other,
no matter what happens to Sanxing Group,
at the end of the day,
you are
the most important
to me.
I'll make us dinner.
It's been too long
since we last had dinner together.
Can't you spend a month apart?
(A month later)
(The industry powerhouse of An Jing city,
namely Sanxing Group and Xinlan Group,)
(have recently closed the deal
to acquire Tianye.)
(Xinlan Group will soon become
a shareholder of Sanxing Group.)
(Because of the deal, Xinlan Group
asked to have a third-party examination)
(conducted on
Sanxing's financial status.)
(According to our sources,)
(Sanxing Group will soon
hold a board meeting)
(to elect a new chairman.)
(But based on our info,)
(Mr. Mo Sanxing's greatest competition)
(is none other
than his nephew, Gu Zhaohe.)
(Gu Zhaohe is the son of Mo Lan,
a famous overseas entrepreneur)
(of An Jing.)
(Zhaohe.)
(It's finally coming to an end.)
(Xu Yiqing. Active two hours ago.)
(I am Xiling.)
(Lately, I've come to realize that
there are things in life)
(that are never too late to begin.)
(Over the years,)
(I've been searching for)
(the reason for your sudden farewell.)
(I've imagined countless scenarios.)
(But so far, I don't have an answer.)
(And now, there is only one outcome.)
(Xu Yiqing, you must be held
accountable for the Yingqiao project.)
(Li Daogang)
(Hello?)
(Xiaolan.)
(I might fade away soon.)
(I'd like to see you again.)
♪The candid summer♪
♪Full of warmth,
you are bathed in sunshine♪
♪Along with the boundless blue sky
and white clouds♪
♪I am but a lonely cactus♪
♪On this sandy shore♪
♪Longing for you♪
♪To soar like a white dove♪
♪If you spread your wings♪
♪And wander afar♪
♪My shoulders will always♪
♪Be here for you♪
♪If your heart holds♪
♪Too many longings♪
♪My juice shall♪
♪Remember them for you♪