=In the Grip of Love=
=Episode 18=
What's wrong?
You should step back.
Why?
Xu Yiqing disappeared
because of the Yingqiao Project.
I don't want you
to end up with the same fate.
I'm investigating the Yingqiao Project
because it has to do
with me and Xu Yiqing.
But why provoke your uncle?
Are you worried about me?
I'm serious.
You know what kind
of person Mo Sanxing is.
If pushed too far,
he'll do anything.
Don't worry.
The reason I first joined
the company as an intern
was because of the Yingqiao Project.
My mother thought my uncle
was transferring company assets,
so she sent me in.
She also suspected me, right?
I'm sorry.
I had my concerns,
so I didn't explain everything to you.
That's why I have to get involved.
Not just for you.
But would escalating the conflict
between your mother and Mo Sanxing now
be too soon?
We'll have to face it eventually.
Besides, you said yourself
that he's my uncle.
If you were my girlfriend,
he might be wary and think twice
before doing something to you.
Sit back down.
Since we've already started,
there's no reason to give up halfway,
right?
Don't worry.
You're too tense.
How about we go out
and settle your nerves?
You've improved a lot.
Have you been secretly practicing?
What's there to practice?
(Yeyu, Let's run together at night
and follow our hearts)
I really hope we can save Tianye,
especially Yeyu.
Why?
(Yeyu, Let's run together at night)
I want you
(and follow our hearts)
to always see that phrase.
What did Bian Jinxi say to you?
Nothing much. We just chatted.
We didn't mention you.
Well, I think your attitude's improved.
Didn't you say
we should start over as friends again?
But
friends are friends.
Advertising is advertising.
Then, can I start
pursuing you again as a friend?
I see you're more interested
in going back to being strangers.
(The signing ceremony for
Ankang Capital's investment in Tianye)
(will be held this Friday at 10:00 AM
in the Sanxing Group conference room.)
(Please attend promptly.)
Did you get it?
Hostile takeovers
are Lingkang's usual tactic.
If we can expose this before dawn,
we might
get the board
to vote with us against it.
What do you think?
There's nothing abnormal
about this acquisition process.
It's not really a hostile takeover.
And as long as Mo Sanxing denies it,
we don't have any concrete evidence
to prove he's the actual
beneficiary behind Lingkang.
Do you have a plan in mind?
Yes.
The white knight strategy.
We need to find a third-party company
to compete with Lingkang
for Tianye's operating rights
until Lingkang is forced
to give up the acquisition.
But what if
the third-party company succeeds?
They won't.
Think about it.
As long as the third-party company
isn't actually controlled
by Mo Sanxing,
this business move
will be meaningless
to him.
With Tianye doing so well now,
Mo Sanxing won't let it go easily.
Where do we find this white knight?
Think carefully again.
There's a suitable candidate.
What were you two thinking?
Coming here dressed like that.
Told you so.
Didn't you have something to tell me?
Come here.
Say what you came to say.
Then we can have a drink together!
What?
You want me to compete with Lingkang
for Tianye's operating rights?
Yes.
Do you really think
I can handle something this big?
And under my mother's Xinlan Group name?
Look,
if you can't pull it off, no one can.
Not a chance.
If I fail,
my mother will kill me.
You might as well tie me up instead.
Help us this one time.
Please?
How about this?
We'll handle
your mother's nagging about marriage
for you.
Deal.
How are we going to solve it?
Where were we?
Maybe you should head back first.
No way.
We have to find any and all flaws
and suspicious points
in Mo Sanxing
and Lingkang's collaboration,
as well as the cons of this acquisition.
If Bian Jinxi
doesn't show up tomorrow,
at least
we'll have a backup plan to stop it.
But you're already…
I'll go wash my face
and clear my head.
Who's there?
It's okay.
It's me.
Let's get out of here.
Who's there?
Gu Zhaohe.
Mr. Gu and Ms. Yu.
What's going on?
A short circuit in the electrical box.
The fuse won't reset.
Was it deliberate?
Hard to say.
It's fine.
Mr. Gu, Ms. Yu,
why don't you two go home for tonight?
It probably won't get fixed tonight.
All right.
Let's go.
Let's head this way.
I'll light the way for you.
Okay.
Why don't you rest?
I'll go back and continue looking.
There's no time.
Time waits for no one.
Mr. Mo, Ms. Ling and Young Master Gu
went through a lot of information
in the archives last night.
All related to our projects
with Mr. Ling over the years.
Mm.
I cut the power
to stop them from continuing.
Were you worried they wouldn't know
they were being watched?
Should I…
All they did was search
through some files, right?
Let them search.
Today's the signing ceremony.
As if them pulling an all-nighter
would stop
today's signing from happening.
♪The candid summer♪
♪Full of warmth,
you are bathed in sunshine♪
♪Along with the boundless blue sky
and white clouds♪
♪I am but a lonely cactus♪
♪On this sandy shore♪
♪Longing for you♪
♪To soar like a white dove♪
♪If you spread your wings♪
♪And wander afar♪
♪My shoulders will always♪
♪Be here for you♪
♪If your heart holds♪
♪Too many longings♪
♪My juice shall♪
♪Remember them for you♪