=In the Grip of Love=
=Episode 3=
Come in.
Hello, Ms. Ling.
I am the intern, Gu Zhaohe.
This is my resume.
(Gu Zhaohe, Intern
Student of An Jing Sports University)
A student from a sports university?
You hired a student
instead of a graduate.
Because I am outstanding.
Do you even know
what the Sanxing Group does?
Sanxing Group is
a fashion apparel company
with over a dozen independent brands,
covering menswear,
womenswear, and footwear.
Recently, it has developed
a new sportswear brand, Tian Ye.
Any skills?
My strengths are the 100-metres
and the 110-meter hurdles.
In school, I excelled in all subjects,
ranking first in the department,
particularly
in specialized physical training design
and sports nutrition.
Andy.
Give us some privacy.
Yes.
You are relentless. What do you want?
I know this is not a coincidence.
I submitted the resume two months ago.
I went through two interviews.
I got the modeling job three days ago.
I was only the substitute.
What are the odds?
What exactly
do you mean by that?
When I ran into you last night,
you were already drunk.
The staff
saw us.
If any harm came to you,
the police would've come after me.
So, I took you to a room
to settle you down.
(I knew you'd ask.)
(I came prepared.)
Is there nothing else
you want to tell me?
No.
Good.
It was an online transfer.
I withdrew the cash
and only took
what paid for the hotel room.
Here's the balance.
You study in a sports university.
It doesn't seem adequate for you
to work here
as a management trainee intern.
HR must have made a mistake.
I suggest...
If you insist on kicking me
out of Sanxing Group,
I'll have to buy everyone in the office
some candy.
You are hired.
If you fail to pass
the internship assessment,
I still have the right to dismiss you.
Very well.
The interview is over.
Don't be late for work.
You have ten points to lose.
I bought this at a pharmacy
on my way here.
I paid out of my pocket.
Hello.
Some chocolate for you.
Thank you.
I didn't expect to meet you again.
I look forward to working with you.
Certainly.
Nice to meet you.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Gu Zhaohe.
I'll be your co-worker from now on.
I remember you. A sports student.
Yes.
All right.
When we have a sports day,
you're our star athlete.
Leave it to me.
That's good enough.
Can you drive?
Yes.
Come with me
to the advertisement selection.
Isn't that our job?
Why isn't she taking us with her?
Who knows?
If the average speed is lower
than 80 km/h, you lose two points.
I just got my driver's license.
Stop the car.
Pull over by the side.
(Pure and elegant)
Come in.
Mr. Mo.
What is it?
I have news for you.
Make it short.
So,
Ms. Ling has a new intern.
He is unlike our average interns.
She took her out for work.
She is training the new blood.
Is that a problem?
But today,
Xia Xiaoqing brought her clothes back.
Ms. Ling didn't go home last night.
Did you see it yourself?
Or is this just a wild guess?
Well...
Mr. Mo.
I should get back to work.
You have one month
to reach my driving speed.
Why are you following me?
Park the car.
Yes.
Come in.
Hello.
Hello, Ms. Ling.
A little more upwards.
Try a different set.
Where is my medicine?
Ms. Ling!
Medicine!
It's not here.
Ms. Ling!
What happened?
Pollen could cause an asthma attack.
Don't you know she has asthma?
We had no idea.
♪Escaping the world
where you're present♪
♪The cold wind creates an illusion♪
♪I hold back tears♪
♪The scenes begin to rewind♪
♪With no comfort left behind♪
♪After reflection, who’s at fault?♪
You'll be all right.
Okay.
♪I shred love into pieces in the wind♪
♪Who should I confess to?♪
♪All the promises have been broken♪
Gu Zhaohe.
You are speeding.
♪The candid summer♪
♪Full of warmth,
you are bathe in sunshine♪
♪Along with the boundless blue sky
and white clouds♪
♪I am but a lonely cactus♪
♪On this sandy shore♪
♪Longing for you♪
♪To soar like a white dove♪
♪If you spread your wings♪
♪And wander afar♪
♪My shoulders will always♪
♪Be here for you♪
♪If your heart holds♪
♪Too many longings♪
♪My juice shall♪
♪Remember them for you♪