=In the Grip of Love=
=Episode 14=
Xiling.
Hear me out.
I didn't mean to lie.
I asked you, didn't I?
When did you find out?
Does that matter?
I was going to
explain everything
to my uncle
and then tell you the truth.
The truth of what?
That you've been lying to me
from the get-go?
That night at the amusement park?
The ad photoshoot? Your internship?
They were all part of your grand scheme.
Am I right?
Yes.
But everything that came afterward
came from the bottom of my heart.
I'm not lying.
I like you.
I asked you, didn't I?
You said you'd be honest with me.
But now, you're a liar.
Gu Zhaohe.
Even now, I can't tell
if you are still lying or not.
I have no idea.
I...
I didn't mean to keep you in the dark.
At first,
I was investigating you
and Xu Yiqing...
Do not bring up his name.
But I started to believe you.
But I don't trust you anymore.
You and Mo Sanxing...
One of you
is the owner of Sanxing Group,
and the other is its young heir.
Do you two really enjoy
working together
to make a fool out of me?
Sorry.
I should've told you sooner.
I didn't think
it'd turn out this way.
Sorry.
I'm breaking up with you.
I like you.
I really like you!
Could you give me a second chance?
My trust has its limits.
And you ruined all of it.
Xiling...
Stop following me.
Please.
♪Escaping the world
where you're present♪
♪The cold wind creates an illusion♪
♪I hold back tears♪
♪The scenes begin to rewind♪
♪With no comfort left behind♪
It's not you.
Where are you now?
It's you...
Yeah.
Is this...
♪I shred love into pieces in the wind♪
♪Who should I confess to?♪
This is my resume.
I went through two interviews.
I got the ad job three days ago.
(When I first met her,)
she gave me a lot of surprises.
Do you mean
Xu Yiqing?
You mentioned the name
when you were drunk that night.
(A Night Encounter. Follow Your Heart)
I have someone I like. A night jog with her
is the happiest time
in every day of my life.
Let me be your satellite from now on.
(Breaking news.)
(At 0015 hours today,)
(we launched a satellite into orbit)
(using the Long March 3B carrier rocket)
(at the Anning Satellite Launch Center.)
(The New Journey is a high-orbit
optical remote-sensing satellite.)
Sir,
could you turn off the radio?
Zhaohe.
You are not meant to be.
I did it for your own good.
You planned everything
and still claimed you did it for me!
What about Yu Xiling?
You stepped on her dignity and hurt her!
How could you be so shameless
while speaking so calmly?
Everyone lacks good judgment
when they are young.
I've been through the same thing.
It's only natural that you don't get it.
As for her,
I'll figure out a way
to make it up to her.
Stay away from Yu Xiling.
(It's been three years.)
(I went from seeking
an answer from you)
(to slowly leaving you in the past.)
(But just as I was
going to start a new life,)
(I realized)
(that everything in my life)
(was connected to you.)
(In that case,)
(I must find the answer myself.)
Ms. Ling, this is Tianye's
sales report for this month.
What about the comparison data
from Jiangqing?
Where is the sales data
after the store was upgraded?
Gu Zhaohe is in charge
of the data from Jiangqing.
He also did an analysis
of the surrounding areas
that were going through a rainy season.
He also created a new sales model.
Didn't he show you?
Send it to me
after you've collected them all.
Yes.
Ms. Ling, to be honest,
I think Gu Zhaohe is
the most diligent intern
I've seen in this office.
That is part of his job.
And you.
The data analysis has always
been your work.
Why did you hand it to him?
Gu Zhaohe.
I remember
it was Ms. Ling who asked you
to do the report.
Come in.
Mr. Mo, you wanted to see me.
Yes.
I saw your message.
I gave it some thought.
I didn't think it through.
I hope I didn't cause you any trouble.
Assigning Gu Zhaohe to work with me
is the best display of trust for me.
Of course it's not trouble.
Xiling.
Your horizon has always been grand.
There are important matters
I must discuss with you.
I am very well aware
of your contributions
to Sanxing Group.
I've always thought
you deserve authority
that is more practical.
Of course, this will also mean
you must carry a bigger responsibility
in Sanxing Group.
Mr. Mo,
I'm all ears.
Serving Sanxing Group
is my duty.
I want you to become a board member.
As long as you are willing,
I will give you three percent
of the shares that I own
with no strings attached.
I will hold a board meeting
as soon as possible
to initiate the motion.
What can I do for you?
You always read my mind so effortlessly.
I find this thrilling.
I'll be honest with you.
Zhaohe is my nephew,
and I've always cared deeply about him.
Ever since my sister
went abroad for her career,
I've been the one to look after him.
But at the end of the day,
they are mother and son.
In many important matters,
I am the outsider.
Mo couldn't care less
about Sanxing Group.
Now that the two of us
have taken the company
to new heights,
she is eager
to seize control of it.
Of course,
this is human nature.
I don't fault her for that.
You want me
to stand with you unconditionally.
Is that right?
Just the two of us.
I'll be the master of Sanxing Group.
You are the one responsible
for Sanxing Group's greatness.
We must work together.
We can't simply hand over
the fruition of our hard work
and endeavor
on a silver platter.
Xiling.
I need your support.
Mr. Mo.
Without your help over the years,
I couldn't have made it this far.
Your wish is my command.
Xiling, you never disappoint.
However, there is something
I didn't do right by you.
Mo Lan sent Gu Zhaohe into Sanxing Group
to approach you
and disintegrate the unity
within our ranks.
I let you get caught up
in this family affair
and get hurt.
I must apologize.
You don't have to.
(Relationship Agreement)
(Beauty Mo)
Hello, Mum.
(You told me with confidence)
(that Yu Xiling wasn't a threat.)
(Why is Mo Sanxing initiating a motion)
(to let Yu Xiling join the board?)
(He is even going to give her
three percent of his share)
(for free.)
(Do you know that the three percent)
(is exactly)
(what gives Mo Sansheng)
(and his supporters)
(more shares than me?)
(He would never do that)
(if Yu Xiling wasn't on his side!)
(Gu Zhaohe)
(Can we talk?)
Come to my office if it's work.
If it's something private, forget it.
Why are you joining the board?
Words travel fast.
What? Does that get in the way
of your interests?
I am a mere employee.
Of course I'd join the board.
That is our greatest goal.
Is there a problem?
Fine.
If this is about last night,
I apologize.
But think this through.
Mo Sanxing would never let you
join the board without an ulterior motive.
Anything else?
If not, please leave.
Yes.
This agreement is still in effect.
Party A, Yu Xiling.
Party B, Gu Zhaohe.
We willingly fell in love
and signed this agreement.
Party A, Yu Xiling,
and Party B, Gu Zhaohe.
We willingly sign
this relationship agreement.
Secondly,
do not let this relationship
affect our work progress.
Thirdly,
do not announce our relationship
in the office.
You must not break this agreement.
Only a child would take
this agreement seriously.
You can go out now.
♪The candid summer♪
♪Full of warmth,
you are bathed in sunshine♪
♪Along with the boundless blue sky
and white clouds♪
♪I am but a lonely cactus♪
♪On this sandy shore♪
♪Longing for you♪
♪To soar like a white dove♪
♪If you spread your wings♪
♪And wander afar♪
♪My shoulders will always♪
♪Be here for you♪
♪If your heart holds♪
♪Too many longings♪
♪My juice shall♪
♪Remember them for you♪