=In the Grip of Love=
=Episode 2=
Yes! Get moving!
Yes. That was a good move.
Make the movements more exaggerated.
Come on. You're doing great.
Yes. Great job.
Yes. Wonderful.
A different pose.
Put on a more reserved smile.
(Yu Xiling: This model is no good.)
Yes. Look at the camera.
Okay, good work.
Lean against the lamppost.
We have a problem with the model.
The hairstyle is no good.
(Not the hair, but the person.)
Xiaoqing. No, I mean, Ms. Ling.
We double-checked the makeup.
Yes.
But we have a different model now.
We need a different style too.
This is the difference
between product photos
and a customer's review.
You have a point.
Slick it back.
Not bad.
No, I mean...
Well,
the poses seem a bit off.
(How can you be this bad
at criticizing?)
(Don't look at me.)
No.
It's...
The figure is no good.
(This is on me.)
(I sent a monkey
to do a woman's job.)
Well...
He is too handsome!
Repeat after me.
The personality is too plain.
He doesn't look organic enough.
He failed to show
the personality of the brand.
We want to show Tianye's quirkiness.
We can't keep using the same template.
I suggest we use
a different model.
Xiaoqing...
Everybody, let's take a break.
Okay.
Xiaoqing, let's stay out of this.
Ms. Ling.
Ms. Ling is over there.
The payment code has your name on it,
madam.
A namesake.
You're kicking me out.
Is this your revenge?
Work is work.
I am very professional.
Okay.
I am very supportive of your opinion.
Tianye is a new brand that focuses
on urban fashion
and outdoor equipment.
We need to show the inner
characteristic of the product.
I agree with Ms. Ling's idea
to overthrow the creativity.
Getting a new model
is one way to achieve that goal.
She says I only need a new style.
We'll do as she says.
Take it off.
Enough.
Everyone, get ready!
We're starting again!
Okay.
Let's carry on.
Any news?
Ms. Ling picked up calligraphy lately.
It's for mindfulness.
I should start practicing too.
Mr. Mo, your handwriting is
already excellent.
Andy?
Are you overwhelmed by work lately?
No, it's all part of my job.
I'll ask HR to give you a raise.
Thank you, Mr. Mo.
Go on.
I should get going.
Carry a file with you.
Sure thing.
If you must act, do the whole package.
Yes. Mr. Mo, I'll get back to work now.
Ms. Ling, get changed.
I'll fetch the ride.
How long has Mr. Mo been waiting?
Do you know why he is here?
Nope. He left when I said
you were at the studio.
Very well. I'll deal with him
as soon as possible.
Yeah.
By the way,
tell the driver
to wait at the bathroom entrance.
I need to use the bathroom first.
Hand me the clothes.
One more thing.
Go back to the studio
and supervise Gu Zhaohe.
If he won't cooperate,
tell Producer Zhang to pressure him.
Ms. Ling, the car is here.
She wanted the car
to wait in front of the bathroom.
And then, supervise the photo shoot.
Sure, I'll be there now.
Am I hallucinating?
Ms. Ling, the car is here.
Ms. Ling, do you know the model?
He's the last person I want to see.
(Gu, Jie, Ben, Shu, Ke,
Gong, Zheng, Qu, Gan, Shi)
Come in.
Mr. Mo, you asked for me.
How did the photo shoot go?
It went well.
The team did great.
The results fit the branding of Tianye.
I knew I could trust you
to take care of Tianye.
I know you don't like
dining with others.
So,
I brought everything back for you.
I got this
from your favorite restaurant.
Mr. Mo.
I'm full.
Very well.
Glad to hear that.
I'll get it again
when you feel like having it.
From the same restaurant.
Mr. Mo.
The launching event of Tianye
is in countdown.
If there's nothing else,
I must get back to work.
Let the others
take care of the trivial tasks.
I don't want you to overwork yourself.
Mr. Mo, how nice of you.
I'll do my best to serve you.
Health comes first, okay?
I must get going.
The everyday work...
Take care and rest well!
Come in.
Ms. Ling, the intern is here.
A handsome one.
Let him in.
Hello, Ms. Ling.
I am the new intern, Gu Zhaohe.
♪The candid summer♪
♪Full of warmth,
you are bathe in sunshine♪
♪Along with the boundless blue sky
and white clouds♪
♪I am but a lonely cactus♪
♪On this sandy shore♪
♪Longing for you♪
♪To soar like a white dove♪
♪If you spread your wings♪
♪And wander afar♪
♪My shoulders will always♪
♪Be here for you♪
♪If your heart holds♪
♪Too many longings♪
♪My juice shall♪
♪Remember them for you♪