=In the Grip of Love=
=Episode 11=
(Tianye's brand secret might be leaked.)
(Investigative procedures
will be carried out.)
You've seen it, haven't you?
Yes.
Our department is always
in charge of this brand.
Aren't they saying that
we're the ones who leaked the secret?
They can't be doing this
without any evidence.
This doesn't involve you alone.
Well,
this will affect our entire department.
We would be made responsible for it,
making each of us a suspect.
What we need to do now is
figure out what exactly happened
before the higher-ups show up here.
We have to find out
whether it was an inside job
or
a petty trick pulled by some outsider.
An inside job, huh?
I'm Lucy from the HR department.
I'm Lin Zhiwen, the director
of the Ministry of Supervision.
I'm in charge
of Tianye's brand secret leakage.
Gu Zhaohe.
- Please cooperate with our investigation.
- Please leave your seat.
Hands off the mouse
and the keyboard.
Now.
What's the password
of your work address?
It's logged in.
Found it.
Please leave the office immediately.
We will conduct a investigation on you.
During the investigation,
please make sure
your phone is reachable all the time.
Please cooperate with us.
Can I get my bag?
Sure.
Hold on.
Which is yours?
Thank you all for your cooperation.
I have a question, Mr. Lin.
Where did you
get this information from?
Gu Zhaohe would never
leak our company's trade secrets
for Xinlan, our competitor.
Money.
That's enough of a reason.
Ms. Ling.
You're being overly subjective here.
Can I show Ms. Ling something?
I cannot tell you
where I got the information from.
Those in the pictures
are Gu Zhaohe
and the heiress
of Xinlan Group, Bian Jinxi.
Three days after,
Gu Zhaohe sent her the design of Yeyu,
as shown
in his mail box.
Well,
Gu is an intern working
in Xiling's department.
Of course we would want to
get to the bottom of it.
Yet there's no need
for such an argument you're having here,
right?
Lin is just
doing his job.
However,
he shouldn't have taken
these pictures.
You're right, Mr. Mo.
We should do
a thorough investigation on it.
Mr. Lin.
I will not get in your way
when you're performing your duties.
Gu Zhaohe would never do such a thing.
How was it, Ms. Ling?
Gu Zhaohe would never leak the secret.
Indeed. Ms. Ling, that boy...
Aren't you supposed to be working?
Get back to work.
I need to talk to you, Andy.
What?
I...
I swear to God, Ms. Ling.
I have nothing to do with all this.
Why did you want to see me?
You're close with Zhang
from the IT department, aren't you?
- No, I...
- He helped you download some games, no?
No.
I no longer play them.
I had them uninstalled long ago.
Ask him to help us
locate Gu Zhaohe's
email login IP address.
I don't think he'd be silly enough
to send that email
using the company server.
That'd be tracked easily.
Yes.
Okay, I got it.
Oh, right.
I want to confirm something
with you, Ms. Ling.
Are you trying to protect Gu Zhaohe
or seek the truth?
Finding out the truth
is the way to protect him.
You managed
to take advantage of the situation.
Wu Jiang.
Good job.
Thank you, Mr. Mo.
Have you managed
to persuade Gu Zhaohe to resign?
He has denied the claim
and refused to resign.
As time goes by, he will lose it.
I'm sure the HR department will
do their job.
You're right, Mr. Mo.
However,
considering his relationship
with Ms. Ling...
What are they?
This nephew of mine won't
put up with all this for nothing.
If he wants to stay,
he will have to disclose his identity.
Well, will Xiling still believe him
when that happens?
As Mo Ran's son,
he needs to think twice
before doing something.
Are you saying
it was Ms. Mo Lan
who arranged Young Master Gu
to work here?
The group is doing good.
It's inevitable that my sister wants
to be part of it.
She's acting like an attention seeker
in the hope of claiming
a piece of the pie.
There's nothing unusual about it.
You're right, Mr. Mo.
Gu Zhaohe.
Open up.
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
I didn't check it.
Aren't you going to explain yourself?
There's nothing to explain about.
Like I said, I didn't do it.
Why would I leak Tianye's secret?
Well,
how do you explain the pictures
of you and the Xinlan Group's heiress
having a meal?
You don't believe me either.
Is there a problem
with me having a meal with her?
Does that mean
I'm in cahoots with her?
It's not that I don't believe you.
The pictures of you eating with her
are tied to the email
of our company's secret leakage.
I'm just trying to understand what exactly
happened here. Only then can I help you.
There's no need for that.
Let them carry on with the investigation.
What kind of attitude is that?
What else can I do, then?
You were there this afternoon.
Did they even let me explain myself?
They can do whatever they want.
Fine.
I was silly enough
to have worried about you.
Gu Zhaohe.
Do you think it's that simple?
Mo Sanxing wouldn't have you
do anything
if he insisted on defaming you.
This concerns
the entire Tianye project team,
not just you alone.
What do the rest do?
How can you be this childish?
Are you talking to you
as my superior
or girlfriend?
Is there a difference between both?
I apologize for the inconvenience,
Ms. Ling.
Zhang got this video
from the management department.
It shows
our office entrance.
I managed to get this
after I treated Zhang to a meal.
I'll reimburse you for that.
You are certainly generous.
Okay, I'll get to the point.
Regarding this surveillance footage,
Zhang told me that
it's most likely that this person
got into our company network
and server
to send that email
using Gu Zhaohe's email address.
Yet this video is not clear enough.
I really can't identify this person.
That's Wu Jiang.
Isn't he...
Make a copy of this video at once.
And don't tell a soul
about it.
Not even Gu Zhaohe?
Let him cool down first.
Sure, I'll see to that now.
(Tianye ranks first in the domestic sports category)
Yeyu is going viral among shoes fans.
The pre-ordered edition
has had 30,000 orders
online.
The success of Yeyu has also
motivated Tianye's brand effect.
As of now, Tianye is ranking the top
among the domestic sports brands
in terms of monthly sales.
Well done.
Xiling, Tianye has been thriving
under your leadership.
This will also serve
as a bargaining chip for our future negotiation
with Lingkang Group.
Thank you for your hard work.
Mr. Mo.
I have another thing
to brief everyone on.
Go ahead.
(The IP address used to send
that email is indeed our company's.)
(But the MARC code
wasn't that of Gu Zhaohe's computer.)
I've looked into the company secret leakage
involving Gu Zhaohe.
What we have here is
the technical analysis result
of that email.
Ms. Ling.
What is this?
Lin.
Let's hear Xi Ling out.
Thank you, Mr. Mo.
According to my investigation,
the IP address used to send that email
is indeed in our office.
However, according to
the MARC code analysis
done by the technical expert,
it wasn't Gu Zhaohe's computer.
What do you mean by that?
What I'm saying is
someone stole Gu Zhaohe's password,
sneaked into our office,
and used a new computer
to send that email
so as to frame Gu Zhaohe.
Can we locate the computer used?
Yes, we can.
♪The candid summer♪
♪Full of warmth,
you are bathed in sunshine♪
♪Along with the boundless blue sky
and white clouds♪
♪I am but a lonely cactus♪
♪On this sandy shore♪
♪Longing for you♪
♪To soar like a white dove♪
♪If you spread your wings♪
♪And wander afar♪
♪My shoulders will always♪
♪Be here for you♪
♪If your heart holds♪
♪Too many longings♪
♪My juice shall♪
♪Remember them for you♪