=Manbo Destiny=
=Episode 3=
(The king's meeting hall
is so magnificent.)
Father.
Please allow me
to introduce to you my Princess.
(I must stay calm and composed,
absolutely must not let anything slip)
This is impossible.
Who is she?
Song Pai.
You just
introduce
this young lady.
(I am Guan Mengmeng.)
(A few days ago,)
(I was still an e-commerce girl
deceived by a jerk and my best friend.)
(Now I am about to become
the Princess of Manbo Kingdom.)
(Of course, I'm a fake Princess.)
As long as you help me become the heir,
I will naturally let you go.
(Today, facing the most powerful man)
(and his Queen)
(in this country,)
(if I say one wrong word,)
(I could lose my head.)
(I must stay calm.)
Father.
This is my Princess,
Guan Mengmeng.
She comes from China,
and is the daughter of Huasheng Group.
Really? She's the daughter
of Huasheng Group?
I've never heard of His Highness
having contact with any other women.
It can't be...
It can't be what?
You mean
I just randomly pick a fiancée
because of your betrayal?
I…
I didn't mean that.
Your Highness.
When will you hold a class
to teach us
how to be like you?
Rude and unreasonable, right?
What nonsense are you talking about?
What?
Do you only allow yourself
get to have affairs freely,
but don't let Song Pai find true love?
Such a double standard.
Your Majesty.
Song Pai and I met
while studying in China
and recently reunited.
(Keep making up stories.)
I just realized
that Mengmeng
is the one I've always
been thinking about.
She's the perfect Princess for me.
Father.
I hope you will approve
my fate with Mengmeng.
In just a few days,
you brought back Miss Guan.
Song Pai.
How can you prove
that you two are true love?
The Queen is right,
it's only been a few days.
- Could it be fake?
- It's clearly not true love.
I think the First Prince
just wants the succession.
Yes, very likely.
(If I don't take it seriously,)
(I might not fool them.)
What are you doing?
I'm here to prove to you.
They kissed.
They really kissed.
Seems it's real.
It's just acting.
Do you think just saying it
will make everyone believe?
Anyway,
I refuse.
Fifty thousand yuan will be transferred
to your account immediately.
Just 50,000 yuan.
I don't need such money.
One hundred thousand yuan.
Even...
Even 100,000 yuan isn't enough.
One hundred thousand yuan at a time.
Ahem.
Why does that sound so weird?
Since you
agreed,
(Transfer successful)
you must follow through.
Come on.
Let's start.
No.
I'll do it instead.
♪Over the rainbow♪
♪There will be the color of the love♪
Um.
I'd better go back and practice.
Let's
continue tomorrow.
♪No matter how♪
Mengmeng.
Make sure you don't mess up
in the hall tomorrow.
Got it.
♪Over the rainbow♪
(This acting is way too real.)
♪Let it love fly to your heart♪
Miss Guan.
(Now they should believe us, right?)
♪No matter how♪
Your father
is the chairman of Huasheng Group,
Mr. Guan Yongchun.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Words alone are not enough.
Miss Guan.
How can you prove
that you are the daughter
of Huasheng Group?
No need to prove.
Song Pai.
Since
the Queen suggested it,
you should let Miss Guan
prove herself.
Miss Guan.
Could it be
the heiress is fake,
and the con artist is real?
I…
(This Queen talks too much.)
Guards.
Arrest this con artist for me.
- Yes.
Step back!
Second Prince,
seems like you really hope I'm fake.
You already are fake.
(Risk brings reward, take a gamble.)
Usually
I wouldn't bother proving myself.
But for my dear Pai,
I'm willing to give up my principle.
Your Majesty.
Do you remember the meeting
in Xishuangbanna, Yunnan
ten years ago?
That was a
private trip.
How did you know about it?
Your Majesty.
My father
wanted to video call you.
I wonder
if I may have this honor?
No need.
Miss Guan.
I believe you are the daughter
of my good friend, Mr. Guan Yongchun.
I just didn't expect
my friend's daughter
to be so clever and smart
and beautiful.
Moreover,
she has a connection with my son,
Song Pai.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I will cherish this bond.
Your Majesty.
As the First Princess,
I cannot casually let a Chinese woman...
Enough.
China is developing rapidly.
It is a beautiful
and strong country.
There are many
things we can learn from and emulate.
Having a Chinese Princess
is our honor.
I hereby announce
that both princess
have my full approval.
Pai.
Ge.
You may
choose a date for your weddings.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty is wise.
The First Prince of Manbo Kingdom
even randomly picked
a woman of unknown identity
to compete for the heir.
That's your sister-in-law.
Hmph.
A foreign merchant's daughter
is not worthy of our Manbo royal family.
Second Prince, don't be angry.
Don't blame the First Prince.
It's my fault.
What are you doing?
This is an ancient Chinese tradition.
When people's energies don't align,
- we need to cleanse it.
- Pai.
She's too suspicious.
Shh.
Lin Ge.
I've seen
this mysterious power in China.
You better be sincere.
She can even perform rituals.
Pai.
You're completely bewitched by her.
If I could perform rituals,
I wouldn't let someone
who harms their siblings live.
Three days ago,
someone ordered the pursuit
of the First Prince.
Luckily, the First Prince is skilled
and escaped safely.
My engagement with Wen Shanna
is set in stone.
I will not yield
in the succession battle.
You.
You're called Guan Mengmeng, right?
I won't believe you.
This is bad.
Pai.
They don't believe our love at all.
Lin Ge.
Grow up quickly.
Stop being provoked
by those schemers.
Let's go, Mengmeng.
After planning this action for so long,
you ruined it.
He even brought back a woman.
Sorry.
It's my mistake.
Many people have switched sides
to support Song Pai.
If he becomes Crown Prince,
our good days
will be over.
I think there's something suspicious
about Guan Mengmeng.
We still have a chance
to defeat Song Pai.
Only seven days until the wedding.
This woman
must disappear.
Yes.
The wedding?
Next week.
What? Next week?
No.
I haven't prepared anything.
I'll help you get ready.
You don't need to worry about anything.
Just wait
and be a beautiful bride.
It's not that simple.
You think being a bride is that easy?
Think about your recovered company
and your upcoming reward.
And also all the resources
you might control
after becoming the First Princess.
Doesn't that make you less afraid?
This marriage
must happen.
It's possible.
♪The color of the stars♪
♪Fall in love♪
Extra payment required.
(Guan Mengmeng is interesting.)
Who is it?
Your Highness.
Get up for etiquette training.
(Oh no.)
(The banquet is here.)
♪I do this for you♪
♪The love is fake♪
♪The love is true♪
♪For you♪