If I'm with you, I can go anywhere.
What are you singing?
Wheeze!
What's Wheeze?
It means the same in English.
Does it mean the same?
You sang without knowing?
Huh?
Is it a title that means the same?
That's weird.
If it's a title, why don't we decide our team name?
Team name?
Oh, then we've already thought about it.
Ta-da!
What's that?
It's a cat with a beard.
So we've decided.
Our team name is Cat with a beard, Kamome!
Don't put Kamome in.
Then it's Cat with a beard.
Oh!
Kamome!
It's heavy.
Hey, Kamome, wake up.
They're going to kill me!
I won't!
I won't let you get away!
Arm!
Good food.
Good camping equipment that Ryoichi-kun borrowed.
Go-ren, Takahara, go!
Are your arms okay now?
Yeah, just like that.
Then let's go on an adventure to find the pirate ship!
So, how do we proceed from here?
Let's see...
Over there!
That's...
This is the starting point.
It looks like it.
Was it Wiz?
I've heard that song before.
Right?
Sorry for walking so late.
It's hard to pull a suitcase on the tracks, right?
Not really.
I made it a mountain type before I went out.
I-Is that so?
Am I the original?
No, it's fine.
I see.
Let's go.
I remember...
I remember causing trouble to everyone back then.
I'm the only one walking late.
I see. But don't worry.
Huh?
We can slowly remember things while we go, right?
Heidi...
Heidi is a good person!
Stop it, you...
Wow...
It really was there.
The meant for walking in snack time was actually чтобыAU15~!
Heidi isading right into it!
A simple escape is most avecon to that.
I see.
You're so
excited!
Is there a cave ahead of this track?
I wish I could say that.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Take a little break in the shade.
Kamome?
Hey!
Kamome!
It's so hot.
Hey, how long are we going to walk?
Kamone-kun! Hurry up!
Sorry. I'll go while enjoying the scenery.
You go ahead.
Isn't that heavy? I'll hold it.
No, I'll hold it myself.
Don't be a mess.
No!
Come on.
Stop it!
You...
Go ahead.
I don't want to cause trouble, so go ahead.
Hayri?
Hey, Hayri.
Hey, Takahara Hayri-kun.
Are you okay? You were kind of lost.
No, where were you?
I was following you all the way behind you.
I see.
I've walked a lot, but I wonder if I can still reach you.
If I can't find you walking this much...
A cave!
A cave...
There it is!
Yeah!
So noisy.
Ouch.
Hey, are you okay?
Does your leg hurt?
Yeah, but I'm okay. It'll be healed soon.
You're kidding!
Didn't you hurt since this afternoon?
You didn't give me a suitcase because you used it as a cane, right?
Yeah.
Why was I so quiet?
Good morning.
You're making me do something dirty!
I'm not.
Anyway, did you sleep well?
Thank you.
Hey, can I ask you something?
I slept well, but I sweated a lot.
Yeah, me too.
And there was a small well right there.
I see.
So I thought I'd go and take a look.
The End
Oh, a water sound?
I wonder what it is.
Just kidding.
Are you okay?
There was something!
A big one!
It was there.
It was huge.
What? What's there?
The rock there.
Maybe this is the place where he used to sleep.
You were excited because you were there.
I see. I was excited because I was there.
No, it's not about me!
No!
You didn't see it, did you?
What?
Well, a lot of things.
Oh, I didn't see it.
You're lying.
I saw it! I saw the water monkey!
What did you see?
What?
There it is!
The mysterious man Mugoh!
It's hard to say now, but isn't it dangerous to go into a cave?
Yeah, but you can't come here and worry about it.
I'm worried about it.
I'll go alone.
I knew you'd say that.
It's the same as before.
What? The same as before?
No, it's nothing.
We can go on like this.
I think so.
There's a place that's 300 meters from the entrance that's suddenly narrow.
Here?
Yeah, here.
If you go through here, you'll get to a little wider place.
Here! You can go through here!
I'll go first.
Yeah.
Have I ever come here?
Wow!
Which way do we go?
Over there. There's a river over there.
I got it.
Are your feet okay?
Why?
I just thought so.
I think you're pulling that suitcase because your feet are bad.
Why?
I'm fine.
If my feet are bad, I can't come here.
I see.
Then why are you pulling that?
I'm not going to tell you.
No, I want to ask you.
You're a friend who's been on an adventure together, right?
Adventure is dangerous.
If you get caught up in it, it'll be a bother to everyone.
Well, even if I tell everyone, it's just you and me.
Actually, my feet have been hurting for a long time.
Especially on cold days like mornings and nights.
I see.
I'm sorry. Please be quiet.
Are you sick because you were hospitalized?
I'm not usually walking.
Sometimes I can't breathe, I get sick, and I can't get any strength in my body.
Don't be silly.
Why are you doing this?
I'm sorry. I was in a good mood, so I thought I was okay.
I'll go home in the morning.
No!
Don't be stupid.
Are you going to go into the cave?
Please.
I don't want to go back because I asked you to.
I thought you'd say that.
Well, if you come this far, you'll go back and forth.
Thank you.
Let's take a break.
Yeah.
Hey.
Why are you on this island?
Why all of a sudden?
Because I feel like you're always thinking about me.
You said you were here to be healed.
So you're hurt?
Well...
Why?
Why do you have to talk about personal things like that?
Because I want to know. I don't have any secret work.
Oh, my God.
I was defeated in a club.
You were defeated?
I betrayed the expectations of others.
And then you ran away?
I ran away...
Well, that's about it.
I see.
You couldn't meet the expectations.
But it's amazing that you can get expectations in the first place.
That's right.
It's hard to betray that much.
It's hard to betray expectations.
Hey, can't you say something more meaningful?
Oh, sorry.
No, that was about me.
Not about you.
I'm expecting something.
I didn't mean to do that.
But as the goal is getting closer, I'm getting closer to the expectation.
About what?
I can meet everyone.
There's still a pirate ship ahead of this cave.
And someone else is coming with me.
I'm expecting someone to be waiting for me.
But to be honest, I don't think anyone's there.
I've been sick since I was a kid.
I've been in the hospital all the time.
I don't remember playing in the summer vacation.
That's why I only care about this memory.
But I know that's not what everyone thinks.
That summer became one of many memories.
I was buried, I was forgotten.
But it's just one of my treasures.
That's why I'm particular about it.
Well then, let's go.
Wait a minute.
A pirate ship.
I-It's okay.
I'll change the battery.
Kamoe!
Hailey!
Hey, Hailey!
It's okay.
The destination is just a little further.
I'll take you.
If I'm with you, I can go anywhere.
I don't have to go anywhere.
If I'm with you, I can go anywhere in the world.
It's light!
It's the exit!
It's outside!
I can smell the sea.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Hailey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
I'm so glad you're okay.
I'm from the water department.
Th-Thick ears.
That's right.
So you couldn't answer the machine in the water department.
I'm sorry.
You couldn't answer the machine in the water department.
Don't bring that up now.
I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry if I'm wrong.
I felt like I was kissed before I woke up.
So you did artificial respiration for me?
It's a life-saving operation.
You don't have to be so shy.
That's right.
Life-saving operation.
Look.
You can see the light over there.
Does your leg hurt?
I'm sorry.
Where's your suitcase?
It's still there when I fell into the water.
I see.
Your shoulders are thin.
It's okay.
I'm almost there, so let me go by myself.
Okay.
But you can take your time.
About what you said earlier...
What?
You said you'd forget about your memories.
You must be overestimating your summer vacation.
What?
You can't make amazing memories as you think.
For example, you're on an adventure on an island to find a pirate ship.
I'm not a kid anymore, but I'm still excited.
I see.
You won't forget about today?
I won't.
I think I'll remember forever.
The End