I was sweating a lot after playing around for a while.
I sat down on the floor and looked up at the sky.
The sun was just above me.
I saw the grass turn yellow after the sun.
A soft sensation gently stroked my head.
Was it the wind or the shadow boy's hand?
Did someone ever stroke my head like this?
I heard a voice calling us from afar.
Let's play together.
The voice I heard was supposed to be the one I was talking to.
But I turned my eyes away from the unchanging scenery.
I turned my back on the white snow that was falling.
I was so scared that I couldn't see it.
I was longing for only the white light.
The end of the notebook that writes down the summer is coming.
On the day I finally come, I'll just wave my hand with a smile.
There are things that can only be reached by walking.
I'm still searching for the warmth of your warm hands.
No matter how many things I connect, I can't reach you.
No matter how many times I look back at the summer, I'll keep going.
According to the old lady,
It seems that a champion has come to fix the broken fist on the island.
Champion?
No, champion!
Yes, champion!
OK, champion!
I'll leave it at this for today.
Maybe the old man is not in the mood as he said.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Who?
Takahara Hairi.
Takahara?
And you?
Name.
Shiroha.
Shiroha? What are you doing?
Practicing.
Swimming?
That's my line.
Yes?
Are you lost?
I want to go back to Kato's house.
Isn't it Sakahara's house?
No, Takahara's.
Sakahara?
No, it's okay to be Sakahara.
I'm sorry, I'm going.
Go back to the slope and follow the right.
Huh?
The third crossroad is on the left.
Thank you.
By the way, why are you practicing at night?
It's dangerous, so you should stop.
If you catch a foot in a pool where no one is there ...
Come on.
What?
Come on!
Huh?
Thank you for telling me the way.
Welcome.
You don't have to be so surprised.
By the way, I sold out of watermelon leaves.
I'm sorry.
Wait, wait.
I'm going to have a welcome party at the cafeteria tomorrow.
Shiroha, are you coming?
Welcome party? Who's that?
Kato's grandmother's relative is coming.
Kato's ...
Who is it?
Huh?
Well ...
I was about to be beaten up.
Huh? I'm scared.
Well, that's a joke.
It doesn't seem like a bad guy to say.
I met Ryoichi and Tenzen for the first time.
Huh? I'm scared.
If you can go, I'll go.
Yeah, I'll wait.
I wonder if it's okay.
Where?
Huh?
Well ...
Good evening.
You lost your way again.
That's not true.
Then why?
Are you going to make me a maid?
I won't!
Besides, I'm not alone or you're alone.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Well ...
Stretch your arms.
And when you stretch them, put them a little bit forward.
Just be aware of that.
What?
See you later.
What is it?
Huh?
Grandpa.
Yeah?
I'm going out for a while.
At this time?
That promise ...
With my friends ...
Is that so?
I'm going.
G-
The first one is not Geto.
This ...
Did you come?
Welcome party.
Thank you.
Yesterday, I swam a little well in the pool.
Is that so?
That's all.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please come back from the island.
I just came.
I just had a welcome party.
I'm not welcome.
Wait a minute.
Well ...
Why are you here?
No, I'm sure you'll be interested if I say that.
Well, Shiroha-san.
Eh?
Why do you know Shiroha?
I introduced myself when I first met you.
Ah, Satoshi Haibara.
No, it's Hayari Takahara.
So, Shiroha-san ...
I don't need you.
Eh?
Ah, yeah.
Then, Shiroha, what was it just now?
That is ...
Shiroha?
It doesn't matter.
What did you come here for?
On this empty island.
It's a
I remember the memory that the sun shone brightly every day no matter how much I played.
I remember the small time since I came to this island.
I wonder why.
I'm a little excited.
Is it because of that?
His embarrassing smile.
I think it's because the island is right for you.
I see.
Then it's fine.
Um ...
I have one thing I want to ask you.
Eh?
Um ...
You know ...
What is the broken fist?
Eh?
I heard that you are a champion who came to fix the broken fist.
It's just a secret.
There are many things.
How can I say ...
Um ...
I can't fight.
It's hard to say that.
Hesha ...
Hesha?
Eh?
Ah ...
It's nothing.
Hesha ...
It's strange.
Brother! Brother!
It's morning.
Morning ...
Good morning, brother.
Good morning, Umi.
Brother ...
Ah ...
It's me.
I'm not used to it yet.
Umi, what is this?
I got it from the port.
Kani-chan who used the material.
No, I used too much material.
At least I can use it after disassembly.
Umi ...
It's hard to say.
Gah ...
Umi ...
Ah ...
Eh ...
Mama ...
Oh, Kani is gorgeous from the morning.
It seems that it was grilled with elegance.
The essence of fried rice is firepower.
By the way, Kyoko-san ...
Kuranoseili ...
It's okay, so enjoy the island more.
Enjoy the island ...
Well, I can meet interesting guys.
silho ...
Shiroho...
Can you catch it?
Not really.
Why did you come?
Why?
That's because I'm your friend.
I can call you if I see someone I know.
I see.
Gohon.
So what are you catching?
Anything.
Sao, can you lend me a hand?
But it doesn't seem to be a fish here...
I caught it!
A black one.
No, but I wonder if it's talented.
By the way, I'm good at catching crayfish.
I'm good at catching crayfish.
You bastard.
It was too late.
Huh?
Could this be...
Oh, yeah.
It's like a drink.
But it's amazing.
The food is delicious.
It's my job at home.
Wow, it's really good.
Really?
It's delicious.
Thank you for the meal.
It was really delicious.
No one can cook at home.
If you're done eating,
don't bother with me anymore.
Huh?
There's nothing good about it.
When I get hungry,
I want to eat something sweet.
Do you want to go eat ice cream?
I want to thank you for the food.
If it's watermelon bar...
Okay, it's decided.
Oh...
I'm glad you're still here.
Yeah.
Oh, you're white.
What?
It's cold.
Hey, hey.
If you take off your clothes, you'll get drunk.
No, I don't care about you.
I don't care.
Normally,
tattoos are more desirable
to prevent you from sweating.
Your parents will cry.
What's wrong, white?
Are you having a fever?
It's the hottest day of the summer.
No, it's probably because of the watermelon bar.
It's okay, white.
See you tomorrow.
What are you doing?
You're so rude.
You're not just showing your skin.
It's a misunderstanding!
White, you were scary.
Are you okay now?
My precious...
You stole it.
White, you're so mean!
Hey, boy.
Stop staring at me.
Girls,
get out of here.
Take this.
It's cold.
I've been thinking about this for a while.
White,
take back the dust you lost.
Well, then.
Let's start a manhunt.
You've done a good job.
It's cold!
It's so cold!
I've been training hard on table tennis.
I'm so good at it.
Stop it, white.
My breath...
Stop it.
I've...
I've... hit you.
White.
We did it.
We won.
But I didn't expect
that we'd be gathered like this, including idiots.
Yeah.
It's been a while since I've had so much fun with you.
I-It's not fun.
White?
Oh,
I lost yesterday.
But it was pretty fun.
Yeah.
Yesterday too,
but is it okay to be in the dark?
The watermelon I couldn't eat yesterday...
What?
White!
Why were you outside until it got so dark?
I was testing it.
What did you test?
I saw it,
and I thought it was okay.
I knew someone would help me.
You saw it? You were angry?
I'm fine now.
Put me down.
Hey, are you listening?
No.
Be quiet.
I'm really fine.
I was worried.
I'm sorry.
Thank you,
Airi.
Yeah.
Hm?
Hey.
Can I talk to you for a bit?
White was
the type to draw a line around him since he was a child.
But
he was also quite playful.
Just like yesterday.
But about four years ago,
a small incident happened.
Our classmate said it.
Shiroha was cursed
and killed.
Cursed?
Killed?
Actually, he fell from the cliff to the sea.
Well, he wasn't dead, but...
Waaaaaah!
Shiroha was there.
That was
a coincidence, right?
If you think about it normally,
but Shiroha's house
was a bit...
This place
is called Naruse Shrine.
Naruse?
It's a normal town now, but
if you go back,
you can see everything about the island.
The people who were so famous
are still dead.
A special family...
Like a shrine maiden?
That's right.
They bring good and bad things.
So don't touch them.
That's the secret understanding of this island.
So I shouldn't get close to them either.
...
That's wrong.
Huh?
Even though we're old friends,
Shiroha is our childhood friend.
Takahara,
even though we just met,
you're not the one who's going to get along with them.
Shiroha seems to be going back to the past.
I'm not asking for this,
but...
About Shiroha...
Will you care about him as much as you can?
Ryoichi...
Tenzan...
Yeah,
of course.
The sound of rain
knocks on the window.
I heard it in my bed.
Even if I try to
rotate the
emu I borrowed
one day,
you were
pierced.
I can't remember
the name of the song.
On a sunny day,
it's strange
to see
the rain.
A short
break
is
a common thing,
but
the evening
is passing by.
I can't remember
the melody.
A boring
everyday
repeats
and
tears
fall.
I hide my true self
and
I wonder
when
I'll be able to
forget
the moment
I'm going to
leave the clear sky.