♪The neon lights before the French windows
shining at 3 AM♪
♪The pile of old photos is getting dusty♪
♪It's the season of reunion♪
♪The gentle breeze is brushing my cheek♪
♪You failed to see me in the crowd♪
♪The neon lights are bright,
but I can't find you in the crowd♪
♪I can sense that you're avoiding me♪
♪On the empty street♪
♪Where the neon lights are shining alone♪
♪Just like our reunion♪
♪The neon lights are blinking,
and I failed to get closer to you♪
♪Some have already forgotten♪
♪The fragments of memories♪
♪Will fade one day like neon lights♪
♪By then, can we get the spark back?♪
[To Be A Brave One]
[Episode 10]
Have you ever thought about
what you will do
if An Yu calls the police?
So, did Mr. Fu break the news to you?
Lulu,
I remember we agreed
that we have to be honest with each other
no matter what happens, right?
Fine.
Let's do it.
I'll be honest with you then.
I didn't break the news to you
because I thought it was unnecessary.
I didn't want to implicate you in it.
You didn't break the news to me
because you knew
that I wouldn't agree to it.
You're aware of how important
Yiyi is to me.
I cannot afford to lose that child.
Lulu,
I always said
that I would protect this family.
I said I would protect Yiyi
and you.
Why do you say that we're losing Yiyi?
Ever since An Yu was released from prison,
she has been harassing us from time to time.
It got worse every time she came.
Now, she has joined Zhuoyue.
It's obvious that she's here
to steal Yiyi's custody from me.
Did you know how many times
I'd mentioned this issue to you?
Was it resolved?
No, it wasn't.
Now, things have taken a turn for the worse!
However, have you ever
thought of the consequences
if you did so?
What consequences?
Are you referring to her or me?
Of course, it's you.
Are you questioning me right now?
I'm not questioning you.
I just want to resolve the issue.
After Mr. Fu left, he told me
that An Yu insisted on calling the police.
Everything will be too late
if she calls the police on you,
do you know that?
Just let her do it.
Let her call the police on me then!
I understand An Yu well.
If she says she's going to call the police,
she will surely do so.
By then,
you'll face dire consequences.
I'm sure you know that well
since you're a lawyer.
Let me talk to her,
okay?
Talk to her?
How?
Will you beg her?
Or will you threaten her?
The method doesn't matter
as long as she doesn't call the police
and implicate you in all this!
Kai,
call Lailai
and tell her to join us for a feast.
Who are you calling Kai?
She's not answering.
Let's look for her in the branch then.
Let's go.
She insists on calling the police?
I think that's pretty good.
Mr. Zhou is here.
Mr. Zhou.
Nice to meet you.
I'm here to handle
the fund embezzlement issue
on behalf of my wife, Mi Lu.
Let me talk to An Yu.
Mr. Zhou,
it's best
if you can make things clear
and settle them out of court.
After all,
it won't benefit anyone
if things get out of hand.
It'll affect Zhuoyue's reputation too.
I will try my best.
Do you need us to accompany you?
I don't think so.
I think it would be easier to resolve the issue
if I talk to her in private.
Is there a surveillance camera in the room?
Yes.
Can you please deactivate it?
Mr. Jiang.
Okay then.
I'll head inside then.
You haven't eaten anything yet, right?
Do you need me to grab you something?
Once the internal investigation is over,
I'll surely call the police on her.
It's been four years.
This is our first time
sitting together at the same table
and having a proper conversation.
Maybe this is the last chance
for us to have a conversation like this.
Can we have a chat?
This is Mi Lu's fault.
It's because she became paranoid
ever since you were released from prison.
She was truly afraid of losing Yiyi.
That's why she did such a silly thing.
It's all my fault.
I deserve it
no matter how much you hate me
or blame me for it.
Are you done?
If so, you may leave now.
Mi Lu will be done for
if you call the police on her.
I know you might be upset
after hearing what I'm about to say.
However, Mi Lu has raised Yiyi for four years.
To Yiyi,
Mi Lu is already his mother.
She wouldn't have done so
if she truly considered Yiyi's feelings!
Is she afraid now?
If she's afraid,
tell her to see me personally.
I know.
I have no right to beg you here.
I know I'm nothing
to you.
But Yiyi is still a kid.
I will tell him everything
when he grows up.
But can you please allow Yiyi
to have a complete family before then?
If Mi Lu were arrested,
Yiyi wouldn't be able to accept it
if he couldn't find his mother
all of a sudden.
Fine.
I won't call the police on her.
However, I have to know the truth.
That's my bottom line.
Thank you.
An Yu,
during the five years that we spent together,
my feelings for you...
were all true.
What are you doing?
Return to your seat.
I heard about An Yu's incident
when I went to the toilet just now.
Seems like it's related to Mi Lu's deal.
What are you guys doing?
Sorry about that.
I think I have a stomachache.
May I use the washroom?
What a nuisance.
Be quick.
Come with me.
I'll go first.
She's out.
Jingya,
what did you tell them?
Yeah.
I just told them what I knew.
Su Dayong,
come in.
What?
Right now?
Okay.
Xu Jingya, come with me.
What exactly is going on?
What do you mean?
This matter isn't as simple as you think.
You better tell me right now
if you are involved with it.
There's nothing to talk about.
An Yu brought this upon herself.
Let me ask you again.
Are you
involved or not?
I'm not.
Alright.
What are you staring at?
[Caution, Wet Floor]
What a pervert.
Are you out of your mind?
Madam!
Don't shout!
I'm going to ask you a favor here.
Can you please lend me your phone?
My ex-boyfriend is outside.
He wants to give me a beating.
He doesn't want to break up with me.
Thank you in advance.
Please don't make any sound
when I let go of you later.
Thank you, madam.
Why is it so frightening
for youngsters like you to get a date?
Can't you guys just talk it out?
Thank you, madam.
Madam, what's your password?
8888.
Thank you.
No worries.
Who's this?
Hello, who's this?
Ye Kai,
it's me.
Lailai?
Whose phone are you using right now?
I don't have time to explain myself.
My phone has been confiscated.
Even so,
you still remember my number?
Cut the crap.
An'an is in trouble right now.
She's detained by the Internal Audit Department.
Are you done?
Come out now.
An Yu is in trouble.
Where are they?
They're in Zhuoyue.
Calm down. Don't panic.
[Zhuoyue Financial Group]
It's too late! Turn back!
I'm just here to deliver some goods!
Why are you stopping me?
Open the gate!
Stop honking! Hold on!
Just let me in! I'm just delivering some goods!
-I'll be quick.
-Shao Moli!
Do you believe
that I'll break your parking barrier?
Even so, I won't let you in.
You don't have the right!
Shao Moli!
Why can't I go in?
An Yu,
just give up already.
Everyone here has already
spent the entire day with you here.
Must you be so stubborn?
Will that do you any good?
I didn't do anything wrong.
You're being stubborn here.
An Yu, as long as you're willing to resign,
we promise
that we will exclude this record
from your profile,
-okay?
-(An Yu.)
An Yu!
Let go of me!
Mr. Shao? What are you doing here?
I'm here to rescue her.
-Let go of me!
-Mr. Shao, I understand
that you're young and impulsive.
However, this is our internal affair.
Don't you think you're acting inappropriately?
I don't care!
Let go of me!
An Yu.
Do you guys know that it's illegal
to detain people in private?
An Yu is suspected of
embezzling our client's fund.
As the Internal Audit Department,
we're conducting an investigation.
Mr. Shao, do you have any other questions?
I have no questions.
I will take her with me.
Mr. Shao, please mind your behavior.
Try and touch him if you dare!
Don't fight.
Mr. Shao, how about this?
Let's sit down and talk over this.
Take out your phone.
Take out my phone?
That's right! Film this!
Film me! Hurry!
Alright, I'll film you.
I'm Shao Moli.
I swear on my career
that I will definitely prove An Yu's innocence
within 24 hours.
If not,
I will quit the finance industry.
This video will be my proof!
Can I leave now?
[The Secret Garden]
I need to head out.
Take good care of An Yu for me.
Remember to take care of her fluid intake.
Lailai said she was done with her interrogation.
She's on her way home right now.
That street is so desolate.
And you're aware too.
There's no surveillance camera on that street.
How can you investigate the case?
I have to give it a try somehow.
You said you would quit the finance industry.
Were you serious?
What else could I do?
I'd already made a promise.
Wish me luck.
Enough.
Stop drinking.
You've drunk too much.
She has promised not to call the police.
She should have done so.
She wants to take back Yiyi, right?
She'll achieve her goal
if she calls the police
and asks them to arrest me.
Lulu,
she has already promised not to call the police.
What else do you want?
Did you apologize to her?
Who told you to apologize to her on my behalf?
What have I done wrong?
Why did you apologize to her?
I know.
I know you did nothing wrong.
I just wanted to make concessions
to avoid trouble, okay?
I ran out of choices.
If she insists on keeping quiet,
you should know the consequences
since you're a lawyer yourself.
I'm sure you know how dire the consequences are.
Your future will be ruined!
Did you know that?
Why were you so reckless?
It's because I know better than anyone else
that An Yu has the right
to take Yiyi away from me!
I've raised Yiyi for several years.
But this woman,
she can steal my child away from me at any time.
I feel anxious!
I feel insecure.
Sometimes,
I can't even sleep
when I think about that fact.
I suffer from insomnia.
Zhou Yuan, let me ask you this.
Why should I suffer like this?
Listen.
Even if the entire world is accusing me
for being wrong right now,
you must never do it.
Am I wrong for reproaching you?
You are wrong in the first place!
Do you think I'm trying
to reason with you right now?
I only want my husband
to stand by me
even after I've committed a mistake!
You must side with me!
Lulu?
Lulu, where are you going?
I'll spend the night in the law firm.
I don't feel like staying here.
Mister,
have you seen this girl
at around 8 PM on the 19th?
Mister,
have you seen this girl
at around 8 PM on the 19th?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I have something to ask you two.
Have you guys
seen this person before?
No, we haven't.
No.
Alright, thank you.
You...
Mister!
I've been waiting for you the entire night.
You're finally here.
I've already asked all the shops around here.
Your shop is the only one left.
Do you want to buy something?
That's not it.
I wanted to ask you
if you had seen this girl
together with an old lady
at around 8 PM
on the 19th?
They were waiting for a bus
at the bus stop opposite here.
No, I haven't.
Are you sure?
Try to recall again.
Mister,
I can recall something
if you give me something in return.
I'll give you 1,000 yuan.
1,000 yuan?
If it's not enough,
I'll even buy all of your goods.
I'll even buy your car too.
My car
is imported, you know?
It's not cheap.
When was the last time you drove it?
Last Tuesday.
I parked it here after I unloaded my goods.
Although it looks dirty outside,
it's clean inside.
Mister,
I'll sell it to you at a cheaper price
if you're sincere in buying it.
What time did you buy your goods last Tuesday?
I remember that it was already dark
when I was back here.
I think
it was around 7 PM
Or 8 PM, I guess.
Did you install a dashcam in your car?
Of course.
I just installed it recently.
It has 512 GB worth of free space.
It has
plenty of free space.
Mister,
can you please show me your dashcam footage?
I'm begging you.
You want to take a look?
Fine.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
An'an, you're awake?
Lailai, how did I end up here?
Mr. Wolf rescued you
from them last night. Did you forget?
He rescued me?
Yeah.
Well...
Where is he then?
He's off investigating your case.
And he's out for the entire night.
Just now, he called Ye Kai to join him.
I'll go and look for him.
No way.
You haven't recovered yet.
You shouldn't get out of bed.
Don't worry.
I heard that he had found evidence.
He'll be fine as long as
he can prove your innocence.
Well...
What will happen to him if he doesn't?
He's fine, isn't he?
Yeah.
Come on. Don't worry.
He'll be fine
as long as you're fine.
It's only a huge deal to him
when you're in trouble.
Here.
Finish the porridge.
You should recuperate here.
Try it.
I don't really remember
what happened last night.
I think I fainted.
After that, Mr. Yang and Mr. Fu...
Wait a second.
Why did they agree to release me?
The investigation was already in progress.
We could sue them for unlawful detention
if they kept detaining you like that.
Now, you just need to rest here
and wait for Mr. Wolf's good news.
Have another bite.
[Dashcam]
The transaction on Mi Lu's account
was made at 19:55:54 on the 18th.
On the same night, An Yu appeared at a bus stand
which was 1.4 km away from Chuanhe Branch
at 19:56:03.
Both events were less than 10 seconds apart
from each other.
Unless An Yu is Superwoman herself,
if not,
I don't think we need
to give you guys an explanation here.
Everyone,
please clear An Yu's name for her.
Mr. Shao,
I hope you can provide
the original footage to us.
We need the unedited version
and the name of the dashcam owner.
No problem.
Both the original footage
and the dashcam owner are downstairs.
We will give An Yu
an explanation
after we verify the validity of the footage.
But why?
It's just footage from a dashcam.
Can he prove An Yu's innocence
with that footage alone?
Isn't that enough?
How do you explain the security token then?
Also,
the surveillance camera was turned off
and the transaction was made
on An Yu's computer.
In my opinion,
even if the footage is valid,
that could only prove
that An Yu didn't do the deed herself.
I think
An Yu might have an accomplice here.
An Yu created an alibi on purpose
so that we wouldn't suspect her.
That's right.
Xu Jingya took the words right out of my mouth.
This case is very complicated.
Just one footage alone isn't enough.
We have to
continue the investigation.
Mr. Shao,
you're running out of time.
You mustn't bite it!
Stop biting it!
-Spit it out!
-(I swear)
(on my career that...)
Lailai.
(I will prove An Yu's innocence...)
Have you watched this?
(within 24 hours.)
If not,
I'll quit the finance industry.
I have.
Mr. Wolf was flustered back then.
He just wanted to rescue you.
Even so, he shouldn't have
made such a stupid promise
with his career at stake.
An'an, just calm down.
Ice Cream.
Come, get over here.
Come back.
He didn't answer my call
or reply to my messages.
Where is he?
The time limit will be up soon.
Lailai,
why don't you ask Kai for me?
Sure.
I'll make a call for you then.
Ice Cream, be good.
I'll go and get my phone.
Why did you call me here?
Are you sure you want to shout at me?
Wait.
What exactly are you up to?
I have nothing to do with An Yu's case.
Don't be nervous.
I didn't say that you
were related to An Yu's case.
You!
Mr. Shao,
you have to trust me.
I'm innocent.
Of course, I trust you.
If not, I wouldn't have called you here.
Since you're so anxious,
I'll cut it short.
I could tell that there was something
between you and Jiang Haoran
from the first day you joined Zhuoyue.
Due to him
and some conflicts at work,
you became hostile toward An Yu.
After that, Mi Lu went to you.
She persuaded you to join hands with her
to deal with An Yu.
A common enemy
and the benefits Mi Lu had promised you
motivated you
to move to a remote area like Chuanhe.
You followed An Yu to Chuanhe
and became the branch manager
just so
you could stage yesterday's act,
am I right?
Mr. Shao,
I don't understand what you're saying.
I didn't hold any grudges against An Yu.
I think you misunderstood me.
You see,
I always separate public affairs
from private affairs.
I told you already.
I do trust you.
I'm sure you couldn't come up with
such a devious plot.
I'm also sure that you don't hate An Yu that much.
It was because Mi Lu deluded you.
Mi Lu was the one who gave you the cipher.
Mi Lu was the one who gave you
the time, location, and date
for you to do the transaction.
And I'm sure Mi Lu also told you
to say those words during today's meeting,
am I right?
Mr. Shao,
now that time
is running out,
you're trying to push the blame on me
because you don't know the truth.
I don't think this is appropriate of you.
Xu Jingya,
you and I had worked together before.
Since when have you seen me
engaging in an unprepared battle before?
When you were being interrogated
by the Internal Audit Department,
you said you were together
with your bosom friend, Selina,
at around 8 PM on the 19th.
You were daring enough to say that
because you guys were in cahoots.
But Xu Jingya,
you've overestimated your friendship.
You've overestimated your intelligence too.
You used her to harm someone
while she used you to secure a date.
You two are great bosom friends indeed.
I'm so jealous. I wish for such a friendship.
Shao Moli!
What exactly are you up to?
Why did you investigate me?
Why are you helping An Yu?
Why am I helping An Yu?
I wish I could tell you why.
But I don't feel like doing it.
Mr. Shao,
your story is very interesting.
I'm done listening to it.
Xu Jingya has left the lobby.
What did you tell her?
Her expression seems weird.
I told her everything.
You told her everything?
Why did you alert her to our presence?
How could I lure out the mastermind
without any bait?
Didn't I tell you
not to call me at this time?
Mi Lu,
we're in trouble.
Shao Moli knows everything!
He's found out that my alibi is fake!
What should we do?
Meet me at Swan Hill Park
in half an hour.
Okay.
What exactly did you tell Shao Moli?
Nothing.
I told him nothing.
From now on,
you need to cut off all contact with me.
Delete our conversation in WeChat
and my contact number.
By the way,
you should delete your cache as well.
Mi Lu, what do you mean by this?
Are you leaving me in the lurch?
I told you already.
Shao Moli knows that my alibi is fake.
Tell me then.
How should I explain myself if he asks
the Internal Audit Department
to investigate me again?
Just explain yourself to them in a nice way.
Good luck.
Shao Moli was right.
I was a fool
for trusting you.
However, Mi Lu,
I'm not as dumb as you think.
I've recorded all of our conversations.
Listen,
we're on the same boat right now.
If you leave me in the lurch,
we can perish together.
Since you've recorded them,
you should listen to them again.
What I had told you
was a story of my friend's.
I only gave you my opinions
and some useful suggestions.
You should listen to them again.
♪The brush depicting you♪
♪Both blurry and clear♪
♪The wind blows your dress up♪
♪You're like a poem♪
♪That captivates me♪
♪I listen to the wind and you quietly♪
♪The eraser that has removed our innocence♪
♪I ask myself♪
♪You're the reason I persevere♪
♪You broke through the darkness♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪Our future together♪
♪You broke through the darkness♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪Our future together♪
♪Waiting for you, in the future♪