♪The neon lights before the French windows
shining at 3 AM♪
♪The pile of old photos is getting dusty♪
♪It's the season of reunion♪
♪The gentle breeze is brushing my cheek♪
♪You failed to see me in the crowd♪
♪The neon lights are bright,
but I can't find you in the crowd♪
♪I can sense that you're avoiding me♪
♪On the empty street♪
♪Where the neon lights are shining alone♪
♪Just like our reunion♪
♪The neon lights are blinking,
and I failed to get closer to you♪
♪Some have already forgotten♪
♪The fragments of memories♪
♪Will fade one day like neon lights♪
♪By then, can we get the spark back?♪
[To Be A Brave One]
[Episode 28]
[Zhou Yuan: Yiyi and I are downstairs.]
[The Secret Garden]
Madam!
Eat slowly.
Come.
Let me wipe your mouth.
Good boy.
Daddy, I'm full.
I want to play over there.
Sure, go ahead.
But be careful.
Don't run.
Be careful.
Don't leave my sight.
Did you notice how Yiyi is growing fond of you?
Children are like that.
You treat them nicely.
Then they'll treat you nicely.
But Yiyi is usually afraid of strangers.
But with you...
I suppose blood relation
is at work here.
Do you still remember?
My father's birthday was three days ago.
If he's still alive,
he would be celebrating his 60th birthday now.
Let's go visit him another day.
No need.
When he left,
I wasn't with you.
Now that I think about it,
I am ashamed of myself.
Earlier on when I was tidying my house,
I came across our wedding video.
I promised your dad
that I would take care of you forever.
But I failed to deliver that promise.
I failed him.
However,
from now on,
I'll make up for you.
Hello.
Sir,
something's wrong
with Smart Desk's patent application.
What happened?
I'll send the meeting report to you
and I'll come to you to explain everything.
Okay.
[Someone else applied
for Smart Desk's patent first]
[How will Zhuoyue face the situation?]
Sir.
We
already signed the contract?
We just got the contract
and the news of Heyuan Tech filing the patent
for the electronic screen came out.
Heyuan Tech?
He Shuo.
The technical challenge
of the electronic screen was finally solved
and we were looking into mass production.
According to Wang Zirui,
he and his team have been developing
the technology independently.
There is no instance of infringement.
Patent interference cases like this
are complicated, legally speaking.
If we bring this to court,
it'll be an arduous journey.
They won't lose anything
but we
have too much to lose.
Noted.
I will find a solution
to the problem.
Sir,
then about this project...
Proceed as usual.
As for the patent,
I'll figure out a way.
Okay.
I shall get back to work.
He sure enjoys Muay Thai a lot.
Children are like that.
They are curious about new things.
Not just children.
You too.
Did you forget?
You learned cello,
cooking,
and jazz dance.
One time, you even took up carpentry
and made a chair.
Have you forgotten?
You remember the past so clearly.
I'm sure soon,
you can live like you used to.
Daddy, I'm tired.
Then have a rest.
Oh.
Your father told me
that when he founded Zhuoyue,
he had 30% of its shares.
And then, he left Zhuoyue.
He kept those shares for you.
Zhuoyue's shares?
I remember the deadline to recover
those shares is 20 years.
I think it's almost time now.
Pay attention to your phone.
Someone might call you.
Yiyi.
Why did you bring this up all of a sudden?
Come. Have some water.
With those shares,
you won't have to work as hard.
These are the shares your father held
[Shares Succession Agreement, Inheritor: An Yu]
when we founded Zhuoyue together.
He left these shares to you.
They can be your bargaining chips
to defeat Zhou Yuan.
I have a plan
that allows you to get back
what you and your father lost to Zhou Yuan.
But I need your help.
Thank you.
Thank you for caring about me.
Have some water.
Not tired? Okay.
Practice with me again then.
Come.
Hit me.
[Amateur Muay Thai Challenge]
Sir. This way, please.
Mr. He.
It's been a while.
Mr. Lin?
Have a seat.
The caller told me
that Zhuoyue's representative would come to me
to discuss the patent for Smart Desk.
I didn't expect you to come, Mr. Lin.
It's more efficient this way.
Desperation
isn't your color, Mr. Lin.
I have just one goal.
Solve this quickly
and resume production.
I appreciate your candor,
Mr. Lin.
Name me a price, Mr. He.
I know a bit about the money Zhuoyue
put into the Smart Desk project.
I have done the math for you, Mr. Lin.
This should be a fair price.
Deal.
But Zhuoyue
doesn't have a lot of liquidity at the moment.
Mr. Lin.
Give me a moment.
I will trade with you Zhuoyue's shares
of equal value.
You would give me Zhuoyue's shares
just like that, Mr. Lin?
Like I said,
I have only one goal.
I suppose your goal is not
as simple as that.
Mr. He.
If you can do me another favor,
that would be the cherry on top.
Madam.
Look.
A boy gave me this just now.
Is that so?
Yes.
We are good friends now.
Yiyi, you found a good friend that quickly?
Madam,
are you a good friend of Daddy?
Yiyi.
Madam and Daddy are not just good friends.
What then?
You just have to treat Madam
like a family member, all right?
So I will see her often then?
Whenever you miss me,
I'll appear in front of you.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's have a pinkie promise.
-Pinkie promise, forever and ever.
Bye!
Yiyi.
Say goodbye to Madam.
Goodbye, Madam.
Bye!
We had a lot of fun today.
I'll pick you up again next weekend?
Sure.
Yiyi,
I'm leaving now.
Bye.
See you.
[Mi Lu, Zhou Yuan, Married,
An Wenbin, Lin Zhanhong, Wang Kai]
If Zhou Yuan is after the Ans' asset,
does he have to go to such extreme lengths?
He abandoned his childhood sweetheart
and married another woman.
And Mi Lu
[Mi Lu]
is okay with everything?
She endured all that for many years,
but to what end?
She has a career and she's capable.
But she plays along with Zhou Yuan's scheme.
Yi.
I'm here.
Can you run a background check on Zhuoyue Group?
Sure.
[Founders of Zhuoyue Group,
Lin Zhanhong, An Wenbin, Xiao Feng]
Xiao Feng?
Kai.
Can you run a background check
on someone named Xiao Feng?
Sir.
You asked for me?
What else do you know
about Yimi Capital?
Sir.
I know earlier on,
I made a lot of mistakes.
I have been reflecting upon myself.
Now, whenever I have the time,
I go to Steven to inquire
how the young ones do things nowadays.
When did you become this humble?
The information about Yimi Capital
came from you.
Sir.
I truly have no idea
about everything else.
Sign this and you won't know about anything.
[Resignation Letter]
[Non-Disclosure Agreement]
"The signee is not to work for
any other financial companies for five years
nor is he allowed to disclose any information
regarding Yimi Capital or Zhou Yuan."
You have another option.
Bring me another proposal for Yimi Capital.
Think it through.
Leave.
Sir.
[Xu Jingya]
I need your help.
(Which cabin?)
(Coming.)
I'm at the entrance now.
Xu Jingya?
You refused to pick up my calls
and ignored all my messages.
Now that you're done leeching off me,
you ghosted me?
Oh.
You found your next target.
A fair and handsome man.
Judging from his attire,
he's a rich one.
You like this kind of man?
So,
who's buying the dinner
today?
You?
Scram.
Sorry?
Say that again.
Who do you think you are?
Who are you?
I said, scram.
Let me reiterate.
Who do you think you are?
Just you wait.
You dated him?
Yes.
Why stoop so low?
I can only find people like him.
You're a nice person.
But would you ever date me?
Thank you for just now.
I plan to go back to my hometown.
When will you return?
Never.
♪Confront each other about the roles to play♪
I have made up my mind.
♪Still saying that I love you♪
Nothing in Yuqing
can make me stay.
♪I'm forced to face two consequences♪
I don't want to wear myself out.
♪The hatred runs deep in me
but is hidden by a nonchalant face♪
You won't return?
♪I have no choice♪
♪Hurting the one you love the most♪
♪Being cruel to you and me♪
It's good.
♪We embrace but I despise you♪
I'm getting a promotion soon.
♪Why delude ourselves?♪
Once I'm promoted,
we'll be further away.
Indeed.
♪Two persons are in a turmoil♪
Congratulations.
You said you needed my help.
What happened?
It's okay.
♪Is this karma from my past life?♪
I didn't know
you made that decision.
Congratulations.
When are you leaving?
♪Two persons are in a turmoil♪
In a few days.
♪But three are entangled in it♪
I have one last question
-for you.
-Don't ask.
You want to know if I ever fell in love with you.
♪No more extra scenes, it's time to go♪
No, never.
I mean it.
Okay.
This is our farewell dinner.
Let's have a toast.
♪Hurting the one you love the most♪
♪Being cruel to you and me♪
Okay.
♪We embrace but I despise you♪
♪Why delude ourselves?♪
♪Two persons are in a turmoil♪
♪Involving a third person♪
♪Is this karma from my past life?♪
♪Granting a moment of tenderness from you♪
♪Two persons are in a turmoil♪
♪But three are entangled in it♪
♪Not seeing that I am only a guest♪
♪No more extra scenes, it's time to go♪
Here is Xiao Feng's information.
He
was one of the founders of Zhuoyue.
Lin Zhanhong, An Wenbin, and him
were good friends.
However, perhaps it was due to
ideological differences,
they split.
Lin Zhanhong stayed with Zhuoyue
while Xiao Feng and An Wenbin
founded their own company.
It doesn't make sense.
They had a good beginning.
Why would he jump to his death?
I can't find a lot of information
about what came after.
Apparently, Xiao Feng
was quite a bold investor.
His first two investments turned sour
and then for some reason,
he went insane
and put all his money into the stock market.
He even
turned to loansharks to take out
a leveraged loan for thrice his debt.
Then you know what happened.
But it's not this simple either.
This.
Read this.
The same day Xiao Feng threw himself off the roof,
An Yu's father, An Wenbin,
came with a bunch of debt collectors
to demand repayment.
It's almost the same time he jumped off the roof.
Did Xiao Feng
have a family?
He was married
and had a son.
But his wife wasn't
in good health.
Shortly after
he committed suicide,
his wife died from her sickness.
What about his son?
I couldn't find anything about his son.
I even went to the local orphanage
and social care facility
but I couldn't get anything.
I...
I ran around for you the whole day
and you're leaving just like that?
[Xiao Feng]
[Zhou Yuan]
Zhou Yuan's past
is barely available.
Maybe he has another identity?
Father and son?
[Zhou Yuan]
[An Wenbin]
[Xiao Feng]
Revenge?
Xiao Feng killed himself on January 5th.
That's in two days.
Hey, Ding.
I need your help.
Yes?
The day after tomorrow,
it's January 5th.
I need you to follow Zhou Yuan for the entire day.
Shao Moli.
Remember what I said.
Whatever you do,
you cannot harm Mi Lu.
[Zhou Yuan]
Let me hug you for a bit longer.
Don't speak.
You're still awake.
You too.
Something's bothering you?
Is it that obvious?
Oh, yeah.
I want to take part in this competition.
[Amateur Muay Thai Challenge]
Do you think I can do it?
Why so sudden?
Do you still remember the first time
you brought me to practice Muay Thai?
Of course.
Back then, I accidentally
got hit.
Back then,
I was still on my probation period in Zhuoyue
and it was stressful.
You told me that not only should I work hard,
but I also needed to show some determination.
And so, I went to learn Muay Thai.
After my training,
I felt that every problem could be overcome.
No matter what happens,
if you want to vent,
I'm always there.
Since you want to take part in this competition,
you'll have my full support.
Good luck,
An Yu.
Drink with me.
That's mine.
So?
There are eight contestants in total.
If you want to be the champion,
you need to win three matches at least.
Even though this is for amateurs,
the previous candidates are all high-caliber.
Are they the contestants?
They look professional.
If you want to quit now,
there's still time.
Impossible.
I can't quit like a coward.
An'an.
Mr. Shao.
Min?
You're in the competition too?
Yes.
Looking forward to fighting you, senior.
How am I your senior?
Mr. Shao and you brought me
to my first training session.
In a way, you're my mentor.
(First match, An Yu versus Zhou Min.)
(Please get ready.)
What a coincidence.
We're in the first match.
Indeed.
An'an.
This competition means a lot to me.
I will not go easy on you.
Me neither.
I won't go easy on you.
See you in the ring.
Sure.
I'll go get ready.
Okay.
All the best.
Come.
No hitting the back
of the head, chest, and back
with excessive force.
Okay?
Box!
An'an.
Oh, my.
It looks so swollen.
It's okay. Just a minor injury.
I was just telling you
that I wouldn't go easy on you
and the next moment, I got defeated.
The coach said I couldn't control
my strength properly.
But you have improved a lot.
I could feel your punch just now.
Really?
Yes.
And the form with which you fought just now
was so different from what it used to be.
Actually,
today is my father's birthday.
I want to use this victory to tell him
that her daughter has moved on.
But it's okay
even if I lost.
He already knows his daughter did her best.
You got out of it.
The outcome doesn't matter anymore.
So
this is why this competition means a lot to you?
Yes.
What about you?
Didn't you say
the same thing too?
I
have an important decision
to make.
I want to use this competition
to find courage.
I believe you can do it.
All the best!
You too.
Hello?
Zhou Yuan is out.
Okay. Noted.
I have an important business to attend to.
Why don't you head back and rest up?
I'll go back then.
[Beloved Father, Xiao Feng,
Beloved Mother, Xu Lihua]
♪The brush depicting you♪
♪Both blurry and clear♪
♪The wind blows your dress up♪
♪You're like a poem♪
♪That captivates me♪
♪I listen to the wind and you quietly♪
♪The eraser that has removed our innocence♪
♪I ask myself♪
♪You're the reason I persevere♪
♪You broke through the darkness♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪Our future together♪
♪You broke through the darkness♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪Our future together♪
♪Waiting for you, in the future♪