♪The neon lights before the French windows
shining at 3 AM♪
♪The pile of old photos is getting dusty♪
♪It's the season of reunion♪
♪The gentle breeze is brushing my cheek♪
♪You failed to see me in the crowd♪
♪The neon lights are bright,
but I can't find you in the crowd♪
♪I can sense that you're avoiding me♪
♪On the empty street♪
♪Where the neon lights are shining alone♪
♪Just like our reunion♪
♪The neon lights are blinking,
and I failed to get closer to you♪
♪Some have already forgotten♪
♪The fragments of memories♪
♪Will fade one day like neon lights♪
♪By then, can we get the spark back?♪
[To Be A Brave One]
[Episode 29]
Well?
Did you find it?
Yes.
Zhou Yuan is Xiao Feng's son.
His real name is Xiao Yong.
That means
An Yu's father
and Zhou Yuan's father
went way back.
According to information from that time,
An Yu's father pressed Zhou Yuan's father
to repay a debt
and the latter jumped off a building.
After Zhou Yuan grew up,
he destroyed An Wenbin.
How do you plan
to tell An Yu about this?
One more thing.
This is also related to An Yu.
When the three of them parted ways that year
and split Zhuoyue's shares into three,
Lin Zhanhong held a portion,
and An Wenbin and Xiao Feng
became custodians of the shares.
However,
the expiry date is approaching.
Therefore, An Yu
also holds Zhuoyue's shares.
Zhou Yuan holds the same amount too.
What exactly is Lin Zhanhong's intention?
Where are you going?
You exchanged Zhuoyue's shares
for the patent for smart desks.
There's more to this than meets the eye.
What are you trying to say?
Since the Smart Desk project
encounters problems,
you've started to act weird.
Not only did you take care of the issue yourself,
but you also agreed to He Shuo's demand
for a sky-high price.
However,
these happened precisely at a time
when An Yu and Zhou Yuan
inherited the shares
of Zhuoyue from their fathers.
Looks like you know everything.
How did you find out about this?
I told you
not to take advantage of An Yu's hatred.
I also said
that I must acquire Yimi,
but you wouldn't cooperate with me.
So I can only do it my way.
You made An Yu approach Zhou Yuan
and made Zhou Yuan assume,
wrongly, that An Yu would sell her shares to him
so that he'd bet everything
to buy the shares that He Shuo held.
Why?
Why create this great setup
and even take the risk with Zhuoyue at stake?
Very simple.
Only one of us
can be the winner.
If I don't vanquish him now,
tomorrow he will vanquish me.
It's between you and him.
You shouldn't get An Yu involved.
Don't forget
that An Yu has the right to choose.
You know her well.
So you should know
how much she loves her father
and how much her father mattered to her.
Correct?
Unless you want to destroy his image in her mind,
you
should give her
the right to choose.
Understand?
I'm sure you don't want to see her get hurt.
(By the way,)
(my dad told me)
that when he founded Zhuoyue,
he held 30 percent of the shares.
After he left Zhuoyue,
he left the shares to you.
He is extremely ambitious.
His next goal
is to swallow up Zhuoyue.
To him,
getting your equity will increase
his odds of winning greatly.
(He'll take the initiative to find you.)
(What should you do?)
(Pretend to agree to sell him the equity)
and leave the rest to me.
We can
join forces
to avenge your father.
[Yimi Capital]
[Mortgage Contract]
[Collateral: Yimi Capital's
Ruilong Tower Project]
Explain to me.
What's this?
This is the company's A-level project.
How could it be mortgaged?
Well,
I don't know.
You better tell me the truth now.
Believe it or not, I can fire you
in three minutes.
It was Mr. Zhou.
He mortgaged
most of the projects
of our company.
Leave.
Mr. Zhou,
can you eat Japanese food?
You're allergic to raw foods.
I'll be okay.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay.
[Dear]
Mr. Zhou,
try the Arctic surf clams.
It was air-flown from Canada.
Mr. He,
I don't usually eat raw stuff.
It's okay. You can have it.
I'll eat something else.
Why do you come to a Japanese restaurant, then?
Let me tell you.
This is very rare.
Arctic surf clams
live in the deep North Atlantic Ocean.
It is cunning.
It buries its whole body in the sand
and uses its siphons to reach outside.
It's hard to catch.
Mr. He,
I came to see you today
to tell you...
To buy the Zhuoyue shares I hold?
Mr. He, you're well-informed.
You mortgaged Yimi's projects.
It seems that you're bent on getting
my shares.
Mr. He,
this is my offer.
Take a look.
I want to buy the 7.2 percent
Zhuoyue shares you hold.
I don't remember seeing you
being impatient before.
I consider myself to be patient.
How can I reject
your quoted price?
Mr. He,
you can ask your people to look into it.
I included the next five years
of Zhuoyue's incremental
capital-output ratio and profit dividends.
Five years.
No one can say what will happen in five years.
If you sign it,
all your risks and concerns
will become mine.
Mr. He,
you are a smart businessman.
You won't reject
such a lucrative deal.
I won't reject a good deal,
but you're paying too little.
How can I get this much money?
He Shuo, you know what's the worth
of your Zhuoyue shares.
That's your business.
I didn't force you to buy.
Can't we negotiate further?
We can.
Why don't you eat all the raw stuff?
Mr. He,
are you kidding?
Do I look like I'm kidding?
Fine,
I'll eat them.
Is it tasty?
I can order more.
Suddenly, I feel
this thing is a bit difficult to do.
He Shuo,
don't go too far.
If you don't want to eat,
you can leave now.
Fine.
I need some time
to get so much money.
You better hurry up.
Next week, I will fly to Shanghai
and transit to Melbourne.
When will you come back?
I'm not sure.
Maybe in a month.
Maybe a year.
Maybe much later.
Mr. Zhou,
I think it's serious.
Take allergy medicine.
You'll recover soon.
Ding,
can you get off the car for now?
Let me sit in here for a while.
Okay.
Why are you drinking again?
Buy me more beers.
Go!
Get out!
Buy me beers!
Get me beers.
Mom,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
Yong.
Follow the address on the letter
and find this man.
After seeing Mr. Lin,
give him the letter.
You must hand it to him personally.
Can you remember that?
I'm happy
not because you made me so much money,
but because
I get to know you, bro.
This card has 500,000 yuan.
Take it.
Thank you, Mr. Qin. Thank you.
Mr. Lin.
Come on.
Yong?
Excuse me.
Yong.
What are you doing here?
Here, Mr. Lin.
What is this?
A letter.
[Lin, please save me by lending me 100,000 yuan.]
Yong,
I'm short of money too.
I'm hard up.
It's true.
Why don't you
go back
and tell your parents
that
when I have money later,
I will send it to them.
Okay?
Mr. Lin, my father...
Have you eaten yet?
Come on.
I beg you, Mr. Lin.
Lin.
Are you done?
Right away.
I'll ask the waiter to pack dishes for you
to take back to your parents.
I'm having a business talk here. Okay?
I kept calling you the whole day.
Why didn't you answer?
My phone was muted and I didn't notice.
Is Yiyi asleep?
[Yimi Capital Mortgage Contract]
We agreed earlier
that we'll sell unimportant projects
so that you can buy Zhuoyue's shares.
How can you mortgage
these A-level projects?
These are Yimi's foundations.
Have you ever thought that even if you do this,
you still won't succeed?
That's exactly why
I'm buying more Zhuoyue shares.
I went to meet He Shuo today.
He promised to sell me his shares,
but he set an exorbitant price.
So I need money right now.
What you do is very risky.
If something goes wrong,
we'll lose our company.
I am well aware of the risk...
I'm well aware of the risk,
but I need your support.
Everyone can persuade me to give up,
but not you,
Lulu.
This will be over soon.
We will be able to live a solid life.
You, I, and Yiyi.
By then, I won't think about anything else anymore.
Lulu.
I promised you
that I will take care of you forever.
I should go check on Yiyi.
[Confidentiality Agreement]
[Resignation Letter]
(You obtained all the information)
(about Yimi Capital for me.)
Sign this. After that, you don't know anything.
You have another option.
Get me a copy of Yimi Capital's proposal.
(So,)
there is another way to survive
in a workplace.
An Yu,
if I can,
I want to live like you too.
I'm surprised
that you said this to me today.
There is a saying.
You shouldn't
criticize others
if you don't know how they suffer.
[Resigner: Jiang Haoran]
[Zhuoyue Chat Group]
(Jiang Haoran resigned.)
(Was he fired?)
(I didn't expect this to happen to him.)
Sir, how much longer to the airport?
Traffic jam ahead.
About 10 minutes.
Turn around and go back.
Okay.
Sir, stop here.
Thanks.
♪The same color♪
♪In the same corner♪
♪Just like a moth♪
♪Pursuing the same flame♪
♪The same extremes♪
♪Who said two like poles would repel?♪
♪You just don't know how to embrace♪
Why are you standing there?
Come and help me.
♪How stubborn can we be?♪
♪We're all the same♪
♪But we're painted differently♪
♪We stay stoic even when we cry or smile♪
♪The flower that blooms secretly at night♪
♪We're all the same♪
♪We seek approvals♪
♪What rules are there♪
♪To stop souls from merging together?♪
♪The same ups and downs♪
♪No more strength to pretend♪
♪Unafraid of enjoying the hardships♪
♪For you are with me♪
♪The same sadness♪
♪Singing the same song♪
♪We're not afraid of setbacks♪
♪All we want is an outcome♪
♪We're all the same♪
♪But we're painted differently♪
♪We stay stoic even when we cry or smile♪
A little salty.
♪The flower that blooms secretly at night♪
Just make do with them.
♪We're all the same♪
♪We seek approvals♪
♪What rules are there♪
♪To stop souls from merging together?♪
One more round.
Can you continue?
I'm not very good at it,
but I can take it.
Good.
You can do it!
I can do it!
It's like a dream.
I've made it to the final.
But I heard
that the opponent for the final is a fearsome one.
She won last year's championship.
Tomorrow is the final.
I'm a little nervous thinking about it.
An Yu.
Promise me one thing.
Win or lose,
you must protect yourself first.
Don't get hurt.
Kai?
Hello.
Shao,
if you are free today,
go to the bridal shop with me.
Lailai has been busy lately.
I must order now, or it'll be too late.
Even if I accompany you to the wedding company,
I can't be of any help.
Go.
Just go with me.
All right.
See you later.
Go ahead.
Marriage is a big thing
and
a friend should play his role
in such moments.
If I go,
will you be okay by yourself?
Of course.
I'll get changed soon and go home.
Then...
Go ahead.
Don't worry.
I'll go now.
Bye. See you tonight.
See you tonight.
Bye-bye.
(Zhou Yuan has already taken action.)
(I expect him to offer to buy your shares soon.)
(Yu,)
(don't forget what Zhou Yuan did to your father.)
(This is our only chance.)
[Zhou Yuan]
(Are you free tonight?)
(Can we meet?)
(I have something important to say.)
An Yu,
do you remember
Zhuoyue's shares
that I mentioned last time?
The lawyer already came to see me.
Over the last two days, I was thinking.
I think I should do something
to compensate you
for what I did to you in the past.
Compensate?
[Share Transfer Agreement]
With this?
Yu,
I think what's important for you now
is to return to the life you had.
The shares
have no real value to you,
but I
can turn them into cash quickly.
An Yu,
with that money,
your life will be much easier.
You will have more time and energy
and can get close to Yiyi.
So, you think
that I need money now?
I know that you won't forgive me.
I don't expect you to forgive me either.
But I'm doing this
without selfishness at all.
I do it for your sake.
I hope you don't misunderstand me
because you hate me.
Okay?
Okay.
I'll think about it.
Busy bee.
Haven't you been very busy lately?
I asked you to pick wedding dresses,
but you were busy.
When you heard that An Yu is competing,
you excitedly came here immediately.
It's about An Yu.
The final is important.
Of course, I must come.
Isn't
our wedding important?
Well, Shao?
What does this mean?
What are you thinking?
An'an,
are you ready?
You can do it!
Is that your opponent for the final on the stage?
Yes.
She looks somewhat awesome.
What do you mean?
Isn't An'an amazing?
Yes, she is.
An Yu,
I went online and watched videos
of her competitions.
She will intercept her opponents
with subtle tricks
and disrupt their rhythm.
She has won quite a few titles this way.
Be careful later.
I will.
You'll be fine.
We'll overwhelm her with our imposing manner.
Overwhelm her!
Go!
[Final of Amateur Muay Thai Challenge]
Box!
I never saw Muay Thai
being so brutal before.
This is just the beginning.
You can do it.
Box!
Hang in there, An Yu.
Stand up, An Yu.
(This is your dad's death confirmation.)
(Four days ago,)
(he died of)
(a myocardial infarction in jail.)
(Now, Mi Lu and I)
(are the legal guardians of Yiyi.)
What are you going to say when you see him?
"Yiyi,
although you don't know me,
I'm your mom who went to jail."
♪The brush depicting you♪
♪Both blurry and clear♪
♪The wind blows your dress up♪
♪You're like a poem♪
♪That captivates me♪
♪I listen to the wind and you quietly♪
♪The eraser that has removed our innocence♪
♪I ask myself♪
♪You're the reason I persevere♪
♪You broke through the darkness♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪Our future together♪
♪You broke through the darkness♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪Our future together♪
♪Waiting for you, in the future♪