Xu Yu.
Vanie, Kachigi.
Tengyu.
I met Ji Wenxuan.
Although your faces
height,
and his voice.
are the same.
But
your temperament
and how you behave
are completely different.
And the look in people's eyes.
I'm very curious.
If he's the real Ji Wenxuan,
who
who are you?
You're interesting.
Now,
I'm interested to talk to you.
Come to this place tonight.
Wen Xuan, tell me.
Why are you so serious?
Actually,
I have something to tell you.
I have a twin brother.
named Wen Xuan.
After my parents divorced,
I followed my mother
with my mother.
And my brother
lived in Shencheng with his father.
But when I came back,
my father told me
my brother
and my mother
died of illness.
No wonder.
When I went to your house when I was little,
I met Brother Wenxuan with an old-fashioned personality.
After you went abroad, you suddenly became cheerful.
And last time,
I met you and Hit at the cafe.
That's why it wasn't you.
Before I was ten,
I was with my mother in Bao'an.
When I saw you at your cafe,
was not me.
Are you saying
your brother is not dead?
Yes.
I think my father lied to me.
Recently,
someone who resembles me has been committing the crime.
If this person is him,
everything makes sense.
In other words,
everyone here could have touched him.
But we don't know
if it's you or your brother.
Wait.
No wonder.
When you played Kongming lanterns with me
and smashing the bottle,
I thought you were weird.
Is that you?
The one who did this with you.
is not me.
So you want to use these reasons
to clear your name?
Even if what you said is true,
how can you prove that
not your brother?
Please give me some time.
I will prove myself.
So you are twins.
President Ji is so lucky
raising two sons like poison.
The winner will inherit Injin Chamber of Commerce.
The loser
like a dog.
Back then,
I became a sorceress.
I thought I could change my fate.
I'm not convinced.
Why did I bring water and make money
choose her instead of me?
I want more than a bottle of water.
I want your heart.
What heart test?
Her bottle is empty.
I...
Did I do anything wrong to make money?
Wu Yue.
Why did you bring an empty bottle back?
I borrowed a bottle of water from the Zhang family.
But I smelled a dead rat in the well water.
I couldn't drink that water.
I'll pour it out again.
Why are you so stupid?
You won't borrow another bottle of water from other places.
But that’s not the water you want.
He Miao.
Where did you get the water?
The Li family in the village.
The Li family is at the end of the village.
not in the village.
Besides the money you earned from fortune-telling,
you still have twenty and a half.
You blackmailed the villagers
in the name of the Association.
I told you to come back before 3 p.m.
When did you come back?
You're disloyal.
You broke your promise and disloyal.
and taught you skills.
You will only harm more people.
I can't afford this.
Grandma, I know I was wrong.
I won't do it again.
Please.
Let me stay by your side and continue to learn.
As your Leader,
if you have another disciple,
they won't dare to say anything.
Granny.
He Miao.
Go back to where you came from.
I didn't expect
Wu Yue became a little sorceress.
And I
become like this.
Do you dislike me?
Of course not.
We are the same.
We're both abandoned
but never give up.
I know.
The cooperation with Geng Ruilin
was just ordered by the chairman.
I'm not like them.
As long as I can see you often,
as long as I can see you often.
Of course.
This is my biggest secret.
You already know.
I'm no match for Wu Yue.
You're no match for Ji Wen Xuan.
I'm the one
in this world.
Let's destroy them together.
and replace them.
What do you want to do?
I'll use the power of the Association
to replace Ji Wenxuan for you.
As for the chairman,
the chairman.
To show my sincerity,
I'll kill Wu Yue first.
and destroy what Ji Wenxuan cares about the most.
It's okay.
It'll be over soon.
You wanted to see me all the time.
But you're only half right.
You're not as good as her.
But she...
you can't move.
Can you predict
where your brother is hiding?
Impossible.
We look the same,
but our personalities are completely different.
Wen Xuan.
Why are you here?
What are you doing here?
I...
I haven't been home these days.
Something must have happened to your family.
Ji Dinghan announced retirement.
It's said that the Injin Chamber of Commerce
is officially inherited by Ji Wenxuan.
Your brother must have controlled the Ji family
when you were away.
How dare he
so openly.
I have to ask him.
What's the use of going back now?
He's the Ji Wenxuan on the surface now.
If you go back now,
you'll be considered a suspect.
That makes sense.
He wants to blame me
on me.
Now apart from you,
no one believes that I'm Ji Wenxuan.
I'm done.
How did you get in?
Why don't you follow my brother-in-law?
You're much better than your sister.
No.
What?
Brother-in-law, go away.
Sister!
Help!
Lin Zhao Fu.
You call yourself a human?
Get lost!
Liu'er, run!
You want to serve me for her, right?
Don't worry.
It's your turn.
You beast!
Get lost!
Sister!
Young Master Wen Xuan, save us.
Do you need my help?
If you tell me,
I'll kill him right away.
Don't.
Don't kill me.
Honey! Liu'er!
Help me!
Help me.
Liu, it's okay.
Don't be afraid.
Tell me.
I solved such a big trouble for you.
How will you repay me?
You...
You're not Ji Wenxuan.
Looks like your...
Jianlan female exploration agency.
You seem to know a lot.
What do you want?
If you want money,
I'll give you as much as you want.
Take everything you like in this house.
Let us go.
I'll pretend you never came.
I won’t tell anyone
at the police station.
No.
My collection.
Almost.
I'll take
what I want.
Let her go.
By the way,
Let me correct you.
I am Ji Wenxuan.
Qing, how did this happen?
Mo Li.
Qing, are you okay?
The knife avoided important organs.
That's a relief.
Lin Zhao Fu died with one stab.
If he dares to hurt Wei Qing,
I will arrest him.
Wei Qing.
Qing.
Slow down.
Where is Wei Liu?
Have you found my Liu?
Qing.
Where is Wei Liu?
We haven't found her.
I...
I saw it.
Ji Wenxuan killed Lin Zhao Fu.
and kidnapped my Liu'er.
Ji... Ji Wenxuan?
It's Wen Xuan's brother.
Not Brother Wenxuan.
Yes.
It's that man
who looks exactly like Wen Xuan.
He said he kidnapped Liu'er
to complete a work.
He's really the real murderer of the shameless cutting case.
Could the place where he hid Liu
is the place where he hid the water?
We have to find him quickly.
Come in.
Sorry.
Qing, don't be afraid.
That's Wen Xuan.
not his brother.
I'm just here to visit him.
I'm leaving now.
Wen Xuan.
Come in.
Qing,
I apologize to you on behalf of my brother.
I promise
I will cooperate with you to catch him.
Wen Xuan.
I'm still the same.
How do we know that we're facing you
not your brother?
Wu Yue made this up for me.
Unless you cut it,
unless you cut it.
This...
I'm sure my brother doesn't have it.
Something your brother doesn't have.
Wen Xuan.
Your brother has done so many things.
Is his purpose
to replace you?
I really don't know.
We are brothers.
Logically speaking,
the successor of Injin Chamber of Commerce
should be him.
I really don't understand why he did that.
Judging from what he did,
not only because he has a perverted hobby,
but also revenge.
He wants to destroy Injin Chamber of Commerce.
You're all here.
Another face-less female body was found.
Will my Liu'er