Xu Yu.
Vanie, Kachigi.
Tengyu.
Do you remember
the noble son
who appeared with Wu Qi.
What's the connection?
Ji Wenxuan has nothing to do with the Association.
Yes.
Brother Wenxuan is upright and kind.
He hates those villains who bully men and women the most.
We're just collecting clues
and reasoning.
not to convict anyone.
[It's like this.]
This is what Han Wei
when Han Wei died.
Can you help me find any clues?
It's cufflinks.
The decoration of men's suit shirts.
This
Look at it. Look at it. Look at it.
Can you check
anything special?
Any clue is fine.
Okay, leave it to me.
I'll go tomorrow.
Ask all the suppliers
all the customized cufflinks.
Okay.
This Han Wei
didn't trust the police from the beginning.
He found this at the crime scene.
but didn't tell Captain Wang.
Even if he wanted to solve the case himself,
how did he become
a crazy bomb?
Let me see this cufflink.
Look at this.
Look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look
You two are more active after work than I am.
The diary found at Hanwei's house.
Sort it out and see if there's any clue.
Han Wei has been following Ji Wenxuan
in the last six months.
Half a year?
Why did you only do it recently?
You have to find it out yourself.
Take a good look.
We're off work.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Okay.
That day at home,
I found a cufflink left by the murderer.
I've been investigating it for a year.
this is the customized design of Ji Wenxuan.
So I decided to take revenge on Ji Wenxuan.
Ji Wenxuan goes home at 6:30 a.m.
He rarely goes out to socialise at night.
At 7:30 a.m.,
to Injin Chamber of Commerce on time.
The driver drove to work.
It's your own business. You're the one who drives.
Ji Wenxuan went to the Injin Chamber of Commerce.
Why would he meet foreigners here?
If he drove here,
why didn't I meet him?
I went to Injin Chamber of Commerce to verify it.
I found that Ji Wenxuan was working.
I'm so confused.
I can't be mistaken.
What's going on?
Definitely.
It must be because I didn't investigate thoroughly.
Han Wei is crazy.
He said he saw two Ji Wenxuan.
Young master.
Why is it a little sour?
I don't think
I usually drink.
This smell
It's cinnamon.
I'm sorry, Young Master.
I learned a new way to make coffee recently.
If you don't like it,
I won't do it again.
It's okay.
It's good to try something new sometimes.
What a coincidence.
You came right after I came home.
Have a seat.
I have something to show you.
Don't worry.
This is just a copy I made.
There's no bomb inside.
I made it
to study
the explosion mechanism of Hanwei bomb.
I was bored at the hotel.
for a few days.
I figured it out.
Explosion mechanism.
It's a time bomb.
Yes.
His bomb
was created
in the radio.
Officer Yiu should know
the three bombs
exploded at different time.
It means
a simple timer.
Indeed.
If the explosion time is fixed,
the success rate is too low.
but calculated
when someone opened it.
Yes.
The reason he calculated
is using the frequency.
When our footsteps make frequency,
When we change from weak to strong,
the bomb will explode.
No wonder.
When he was at my house,
Wenxuan walked towards the car.
Then the bomb exploded.
Fortunately, the door hole stopped.
and reduced the power of the bomb.
Yes.
According to Secretary Zhang,
Hanwei was delivering packages.
So he took this opportunity
to master the rules of my going out.
That's why he left the bomb in my car.
According to our investigation,
in the Ji family,
it was caused by the explosion
when the maid walked into your room.
Including Injin Chamber of Commerce.
There was an employee
came into my office
to sign the contract.
to get close to the box on the table.
and caused the explosion.
Why does Han Wei hate you so much?
He tried everything to kill you.
So we need to find out
why Han Wei wants to take revenge on you.
It's probably because of his sister's death.
Hanwei thinks
the person who left the cufflink at the scene
is the murderer who killed his sister.
Wei Qing asked around.
that this is custom-made cufflinks from the Ji family.
Wen Xuan.
Tell me.
Is it yours?
This is indeed our family’s cufflinks.
It's the same as mine.
Ji Wenxuan,
I suspect you're suspected of Han Jing's murder.
Wenxuan, take a closer look.
This is a serious matter.
The murderer
committed many shameful crimes.
Secretary Zhang,
This is custom-made cufflinks from our Ji family.
right?
Yes, Young Master.
It's the same. It's the same. It's the same. It's the same.
Except the family emblem in the middle,
Each pattern and decoration pattern
are different.
There's only one pair of cufflinks.
Find the other one.
Yes, Young Master.
Excuse me.
I think...
please trust me.
What about Hanwei?
I really don't know
about Han Jing.
Besides, even if Han Wei wants to kill me,
I don't want to do anything to him.
I will only
wait for the police to solve the case.
Officer Yao.
Let's give Wenxuan a chance to prove himself.
Sure.
I brought Wu Yue here
because I want to know the situation
not to arrest you.
Young Master.
I knew it.
I'm sure
because this cufflink
was customized for my adult ceremony.
I usually keep it at home.
I have no habit of taking it out.
Take a look.
Wen Xuan's pair is new.
There are no traces of using them.
Hanwei's one is exactly the same,
but there are scratches.
Ji Wenxuan, please explain.
Since this is the only custom-made cufflinks,
why is there another one here?
Or,
why the murderer still has
You can go
to find the customized cufflinks
See if anyone
make a pair of cufflinks like the Ji family’s cufflinks.
Then we’ll know.
Wei Qing asked around.
The shop said
we only customized this one.
That's why we rushed here.
to confirm with you.
I really don't know
why someone is imitating me.
Are you sure Hanwei is not a lunatic?
I think so too.
I can't confirm this through an autopsy.
Luo Zhitang is here.
He said he would take Han Wei's body first.
This case is not over yet.
We can't let him take it.
This...
I told him the same thing.
But he said
if we don't let him take away Hanwei's body first,
he wants to see
Wu Yue.
Meet me?
Why?
I think he has a dangerous scent.
It's too late for me to hide.
Wu Yue.
Do you misunderstand Mr. Luo?
Don't be afraid. We're all here.
Well...
Bring him here.
Okay.
Let's go.
It's rare to see Little Sorceress in Shencheng.
to see a sorceress in Shencheng.
or a teacher?
That's why he's scarier.
Can you see his bottom color?
I'm a sorceress.
You, a cop,
and Mo Li.
We can't tell
Is he really just a teacher?
I'm sorry.
All I think about is the seventh day of Hanwei's death,
but forgot about the case.
I was careless.
You and Han Wei are just colleagues.
Why is Mr. Luo so dedicated?
Han Jing was my student.
Hanwei is not only my colleague,
but also a talent I think highly of.
Whether the case you're investigating
did it or not,
He was
in school.
and also a good colleague and helper.
I can't bear
I really can't bear it.
It's normal to help you.
What do you want from me?
Since Han Wei can't rest in peace for the time being,
I want to ask Little Sorceress
to perform a ritual for him.
I didn't thank you
for what happened last time.
It's my treat tonight.
It's nothing.
You're welcome, Ms. Mo Li.
After all, we were volunteers in Fuyou.
Besides,
my knowledge
with my knowledge
to help ordinary people.
I admire your character.
But you seem to have something on your mind.
You're not in a good mood.
Actually, Han Wei's death
I lost a competent assistant.
I just wanted to train him
to become someone who can be more important.
He's the victim's family,
he took revenge
and hurt the innocent.
Is such an extreme person
really worth your attention?
What kind of people are there in this world?
The best.
is someone
capable and dignified.
Low-class.
Just like strong
who is incompetent and virtuous.
As for
like Hanwei.
who is capable
and immoral.
Mr. Luo classified people so thoroughly.
But I disagree.
to categorize a person.
Yes.
Only fairy tales are black and white.
But I really want to ask
If it were you,
who would use
will he use useful bad people
or a useless good person?
The reason I'm doing this
because I don't want to
It's much easier
is much easier than living people.
But I know
You need to be good at it. You need to be good at it.
is to know all his tricks.
is worse than him.
So, Mr. Luo,
You're a good person. You're a good person.
You're still so sweet.
By the way,
Wu Yue seems to have misunderstood me.
Can you persuade her
Can you persuade her for me?
There are so many monks in Shencheng.
Why are they looking for Wu Yue?
Actually, she doesn't know these things.
Like this. Like this.
She does this
just to make a living.
I see.
Close the Yang door and open the Yin door.
Don't wandering ghosts.
Open the way to the Netherworld.
What should I do?
Since we found a clue,
call the police.
It’s useless.
He is the eldest son of the Ji family.
A cufflink
can convict him.
With my current income,
I don't even have the right to file a lawsuit with him.
What should we do?
Your sister died miserably.
You always
at midnight?
As her brother,
you should avenge your sister
you should avenge your sister.
Yes.
Even if I'm smashed to pieces,
and fall into hell,
I want to avenge Jing.
But what should I do?
Use your knowledge, Teacher Han.
You can turn your knowledge
into your weapon.
Weapon?
If you need any help,
just let me know.
I hope
after that,
even if you take revenge,
you can get away with it.
By then,
you will still be my friend.
I will also be your backup.
Revenge!
I want revenge!