All characters and events in this series are fictional
and created solely for entertainment purposes.
Viewer discretion is advised.
If Sun isn’t available,
Fey can go instead.
It’s already noon. Would you like to grab lunch together?
Sure thing.
You’ll have to pick me up and drop me off until my car is fixed.
If this weren’t about work, I’d understand that you’re just worried about me.
Then… could I stay in you room tonight?
Doing this will help you relax and ease the tension
I’ve never done it.
Then, this is okay for you, right?
Then how about we swap the thank-you for a drink with me instead?
I thought you said you were going to the wrap party.
Then why are you out here dancing and teasing other guys?
Next time, keep your disgusting behavior to yourself.
Please let me go, P'Flint.
If that’s what it takes for you to trust me, then go ahead.
What are you doing?
Why didn’t you answer the phone?
Why didn’t she answer the phone?
What are you doing?
Why didn’t you answer the phone?
When you’re not wearing makeup…
You actually look like a sweet, well-mannered girl.
When you keep ringing other people’s doorbells over and over…
That does make you seem a bit rude and no manners, Win.
Seriouly!?
Dude! Are you going to red carpet or something!?
A queen.
Gotta keep the crown too right!.
Queen!?
A queen who ditches her friends at a pub?
Let me tell you something.
The only queen you could ever be is the Evil Queen.
If I really am the Evil Queen like you say…
I would’ve killed that woman back at the pub already.
What do you mean by that?
Well, last night there was some crazy woman. I don’t even know who she was…
She barged in and kissed me right there in the bathroom.
Wait wait. She kissed you!?
Damn it, Jan. why didn’t you tell me last night?
What’s wrong with you?
And what could you have done if I’d told you?
I was already kissed.
The thing is, what I’m curious about is…
Why did that woman talk like I was her girlfriend?
When I’d never even seen her before.
I think maybe you just look like someone she knows.
When you went to the bathroom last night, right?
Someone asked me if I came with a celebrity.
I think she said her name was…
Sun.
Yeah yeah. Sun Atita.
At first, I was really confused. Your names even sound kind of similar.
Sun.
and Jan.
Sun Atita...Right?
Isn’t what happened last night enough already?
Sun, could you talk to me first? Please don’t turn your back on me like this.
We were done talking last night.
You know it’s not over yet, Sun.
What is it that you still want from me, P'Flint?
I’ve already given you everything you wanted.
If you’re so sure that I’m the one at fault, P'Flint...
that I’m a bad woman.
Going out, messing around with other people.
So tell me,
what could you possibly want from a woman like me?
I'm sorry
I’m sorry for what I said to you.
But everything I did
was because I was worried about you, Sun.
Worried?
All this time, you never even paid attention to me.
You didn’t even know how I felt about you.
But now you’re saying you’re worried about me.
I’m not something you can just do whatever you want with, P'Flint.
Jan
This looks exactly like twins, Jan.
The only difference is the makeup you’re wearing.
Now I understand why, whenever we went out together…
Everyone was staring.
Check this out.
There are leaked pictures of you and me.
(Guess who we spotted. Everyone’s internet sweetheart?)
How did I never know about any of this?
That’s weird. Since when do you care about Thai celebrities?
Besides,
You’re barely ever in Thailand anyway.
You’re always flying back and forth.
Otherwise, there’d be way more leaked photos by now.
Do you think you could get me this actress’s contact information?
Honestly, it wouldn’t be that hard if the situations were normal.
But we’re the reason she ended up with a scandal.
I don’t think the agency would ever agree to let us meet her.
Wait.
Where are you going?
If the company is a dead end,
I'll figure my way out!.
Is there anything you feel like eating right now?
I’ll make it for you.
It’s okay. I don’t usually eat breakfast.
Then today, how about we go…
I have an event to attend today.
P'Mooham should be here soon.
You can head back whenever it’s convenient for you.
I’m not leaving until we finish talking.
Let go of me.
I know I was wrong.
I was wrong for not believing what you said.
I was wrong for letting my emotions hurt you.
Even though you never lied to me at all.
But if you hate me…
I understand.
But I just want to ask you one thing.
I want you to believe that,
to me, you were never just an object.
You mean so much more than that.
If it weren’t for what happened last night,
would I still matter to you, P’Flint?
Oh, Sun. I thought you were still asleep.
Sun.
Weren’t you saying last night that you weren’t in
a hurry to come back to see Khun Rafah?
Good morning. Khun Rafah.
You just went to Hong Kong, didn’t you? You’re back pretty quickly.
What event is Sun attending today?
Oh, today is the launch event for Sun as the new brand presenter.
It’s a private event. You don’t have to worry.
Is her latest presenter role the one where she’s paired with Khun Nop?
Yes.
Let’s go, P’Mooham. I don’t want to arrive late.
Please take good care of Sun for me, Khun Mooham.
I’ll come pick her up as soon as I’m done with work.
You don’t have to come pick me up, P’Flint. You’re probably busy.
P’Mooham is my manager. She’s always taken good care of me.
You don’t have to worry, P’Flint. I won’t go do anything inappropriate.
Excuse me.
Let’s go, P’Mooham.
Hello, Khun Sun. There’s a delivery rider downstairs with food for you.
Would you like our staff to bring it up for you, Khun Sun?
Do you want something to eat? I can make it for you.
It’s okay. I don’t usually eat breakfast.
(Even if you never see me, there’s never a day I don’t see you.)
Fey. Where are you?
There’s something I’d like your help with.
I can’t even take care of myself right now.
What happened this time, P’Flint?
I know you want to meet that celebrity.
But do we really have to go this far, Jan?
I think the glasses alone should be fine.
Enough?
I just went to the restroom, and I still had to run away from the fans.
This works.
If you want to wear it, just do it yourself. Why am I dragged into this?
Weren’t you the one who said you had leaked photos with that celebrity?
If we don’t dress like this and someone sees us…
It’ll turn into a huge scandal.
I’m asking you for real.
You met that star. So what? What did you get?
Have you ever heard of the doppelgänger phenomenon?
They say every person has seven people in the world who look exactly like them.
Even though none of them are related by blood.
I think you looking like that celebrity,
might just be a coincidence.
Coincidence?
And what if I told you that this celebrity was born on the same day as me?
Hello, Sun Atita.
I bought a plane ticket to Thailand just to see you at this event.
You’re really standing out with that disguise, P'Flint.
I thought you said you were keeping a low profile.
I spotted you the moment you walked in.
What took you so long, Fey?
I called you two hours ago.
Umm.
Hello Khun Rafah.
Why are you two here together?
All you have are questions, no concern for me at all.
The reason we came together is that I crashed into her car.
It was the day she invited us to dinner.
She didn’t have a car, so she asked me to…
I’ve been picking him up and dropping him off,
it’s just taking responsibility as the other party.
Don’t you remember, P'Flint?
Actually, our company has plenty of cars.
If there’s a car you like, you’re welcome to choose one and use it.
It’s okay. I’m just not comfortable using someone else’s car.
I’m more comfortable driving my own car.
Khun Sun.
Beautiful, isn’t it?
And this is the gift I prepared for you.
Sun Atita. Sun Atita.
I waited here because I want to give this for you.
I hope you like the gifts.
Thank you for coming all this way to see me and for bringing me a gift.
I’ll take good care of it.
You’re such a lovely fan.
And I love you too.
I love you.
Good luck.
Sun, the fans are watching.
I think this one’s just as scary as a sasaeng.
You can go ahead and take photos. Feel free to take as many as you like.
Sun's here.
You’re already inside?
You could’ve told me first.
Just wait at the shop. I’ll call you as soon as I’m done.
Then you could’ve just had me wait in the car.
There was no need to make me get dressed.
On top of that, it’s hot.
You sound like an old person.
Hello.
May I take a photo? Please get ready.
Thank you, everyone.
Wait a moment. There’s a joint interview as well. Please come over for the interview.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Excuse us, we’re going to clear the area.
Why is there a joint interview, P’Mooham?
Uh… the network just issued an order, Sun.
I just found out myself. Let’s go with the flow for now, okay?
Okay. You’ve got this, Sun.
Okay, is everyone ready?
Hello, Nong Nop and Nong Sun.
Regarding the leaked photos of the two of you going up to the condo, and the images reported in the news. Could you tell us what really happened?
Honestly, I was quite shocked when I first saw the news.
But just as P'Nop mentioned in his previous interview,
there were actually many of us there that day.
It wasn’t just P'Nop and me, like it appeared in the news.
Actually, the others who were there that day were even joking about it, saying,
‘Why was the photographer so mean? None of us showed up in the photos at all.’
As for the leaked photos taken at the club, I’ve seen them myself,
and I want to clearly state here that it is definitely not Sun.
Because both the outfit and the location,
There’s absolutely no way it could be Sun.
Sun would never dress like that.
And most importantly, Sun doesn’t drink alcohol.
Isn't it?
Yes.
That photo is really not me, just as he has already said.
You seem to know each other so well
should we turn this from a shipped couple into a real one?
As for the two of us, if everyone sees us as more than just a shipped couple…
I’m happy, because it means everyone is really into our chemistry.
The two of us always put our hearts into every project, for our lovely fans.
Please look forward to our upcoming drama that will air soon.
Please support it, everyone. I guarantee you’ll fall in love with Sun just like I did.
I mean, I’m talking about the character.
Ah...
Looks like someone’s getting flustered.
What do you mean? Was it really that obvious?
With moments like this,
it’s definitely going to be all over everyone’s feed for the next three days.
Looks like I’ve got some new competition.
And who told you to compete?
Why? Are you jealous, Fey?
You’re so full of yourself.
Does it smell nice? it's really nice. nice and wafty.
Where are you going?
Excuse me.
Everyone, Sun may need to step aside and stand by for a moment.
I’ll need to take Sun with me for a moment.
Thank you. Everyone.
Okay, Nop, please continue.
Nop.
Are you okay?
Sorry.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Let's go.
Win, can you bring the car to pick me up at the venue right now?
Where did she go?
What's up, Fey?
(Only I see your light)
- Earlier, before entering the event, someone gave this to Sun.
Should we contact the police about this?
Some types of sasaeng fans just want attention from the artist.
They don’t really care whether that attention is appropriate or not.
If we report it to the police,
it might only fuel their desire for attention and make them even happier.
This could actually put Sun in even more danger than before.
So what should we do in this situation, P’Flint?
What is it with today? Everything keeps going wrong.
With the interview with Nop and the whole sasaeng fan thing…
I’m getting a terrible headache from all this.
Sun.
Are you okay?
If you’re still scared about the sasaeng fan,
do you want me to stay over with you tonight?
It’s okay, P’Mooham. I’m probably just a bit tired.
If anything happens, you have to tell me, okay? You know I’m worried about you.
Then should I stay and take care of you?
My condo is already pretty close to yours.
I think it might be more convenient if I do it than P’Mooham.
How did you know where Sun’s condo is?
Khun Sun, Khun Rafah asked me to escort you.
It’s okay. I’ll open it myself.
Let’s go home.
Are you okay?
(Certificate of Name Change Registration)
Win.
Sun Atita...
She’s my twin.
Huh!?
Alright. I’ll head in today.
Tell the staff to get the car ready.
Your car’s ready. I’ll take you to pick it up today.
That was fast.
Our company works fast.
Isn’t that a good thing? I thought you said you don’t like driving other people’s cars.
I don’t like driving for other people either.
Almost got yourself another accident, didn’t you?
The car came out of nowhere. How was I supposed to see it?
Hurry and get in the car, so I can take you to pick up your car and get this over with.
So we can be done with this.
Hold on.
Before we go, can we get something to eat first?
We haven't eaten anything yet.
Aren't you hungry?
I'm not hungry.
Wow, You're not even hungry huh?
You should eat something first. At this rate, you’ll run out of energy to complain.
Not your business.
(Obsessive to the point of harassment:
exposing sasaeng behavior behind attacks on artists)
Here.
Thank you.
You still haven’t eaten? Your stomach’s going to start growling again.
If I’m eating, it has to be delicious.
Actually, you have to wait a full five minutes for the noodles to get soft enough.
If you eat noodles that hard, you’re going to get bloated.
Are you worried about me?
You're full of yourself.
I mean… are you worried about Sun?
I saw that you were looking up information about sasaeng fans.
Of course I’m worried. Sun is my only close friend.
Besides, Sun is way too optimistic.
She thinks everyone is a good person.
It makes me worry that she might get taken advantage of… or even get hurt.
You’re acting like Sun’s personal bodyguard.
Aren’t you worried about yourself?
Someone like me won’t let anyone hurt me that easily.
I’m pretty easygoing.
I thought you’d be into fancy food.
Food is food. It all fills me up anyway.
Actually, I kind of prefer this.
No formalities. No need to be careful about anything.
Even when I eat messily, no one says anything.
Are you okay? Sun?
I feel a little strange.
If you’re worried about today, I can have a guard keep watch.
I promise, no one will be able to hurt you.
It feels strange that you went to the event.
I remember that…
Didn’t I tell you that you didn’t have to go?
But I'm worried about you.
In what position?
an acquaintance?
a friend of your sister?
or the company’s presenter?
Are you still mad at me?
Do I even have the right to be mad at you, P'Flint?
Sun.
Please, do as you like, P'Flint. Excuse me.
You’re not tricking me into getting murdered, are you?
If I were going to kill you, I wouldn’t need to trick you into coming here.
Please check the car quickly so we can get going.
You’ve hugged me twice today.
I was just startled. Who suddenly sets off the car alarm like that?
Hey, you told me to check, so I did. How was I supposed to know you’d be that jumpy?
So, everything’s all set, right?
So that means I’ve fully compensated you. I’m no longer your counterpart.
Bye.
If you’d step aside, please.
I haven’t charged you for the hugs yet.
Why didn’t you put it back where it was?
If it’s no longer the same, I don’t see the point in keeping it.
So… you know how I feel about you now, right, P'Flint?
P'Flint, could you please stop hurting my feelings?
Can you listen to me first, Sun.
It’s not just me who feels that way.
I’m sorry I hurt you.
I’m sorry for causing you so much pain.
But everything I did…
I did it because I love you.
It feels more like falling in love with someone.
Well done.
We met just once, and before I realized it, they had already filled my whole heart.
What, you’re in love, Fey? I’m telling Mom.
Why would you tell on me? Haven’t you ever fallen in love before, P'Flint?
Maybe you just don’t realize it yet.
So… whose bouquet is this?
Or did someone confess their love to you on graduation day?
Oh! Sunflowers!
Flowers that always turn toward the sun. How romantic.
Everything that happened between us
I never did it out of emotion
It wasn’t about trying to win over anyone
I did it
because I truly love you.
Can you be my girlfriend?
Dear, diary.
I’m completely exhausted today.
My schedule is really packed.
There’s no time to rest my mind at all.
But… it’s kind of strange.
Every time I feel exhausted, one person’s face always comes to mind.
I don’t know how you’re doing,P'Flint…
but I hope you’re doing well.
You’re better now, right, Sun?
Then let’s go see your secret.
Hello again, sir, ma’am.
Well… I’m Sun, and I...
My girlfriend.
Why don’t we take a family photo?
Sun, this time the clip is pretty clear.
Hello, P’Peach. Thank you so much for coming to help.
It's my pleasure.
Are you okay?
I didn’t expect to see you here, Khun Paabfah.
Shall we get to know each other?
Shouldn’t you ask for Khun Paabfah’s consent first?
Hey! you.
Are you looking for me?