All characters and events in this series are fictional
and created solely for entertainment purposes.
Viewer discretion is advised.
I have something to confess to you, Sun.
P'Flint… are you about to say that the person you met...
was P’Jan?
I’m sorry…
I’m sorry for misunderstanding you all this time.
Hello, Khun Rafah. You have a package delivered.
It looks like the person who took those photos is
someone very close to Khun Rafah and Sun.
P’Sun, would you like to go rest for a bit?
Since my condo is close to yours anyway.
How did you know where my condo is?
JanJao, open the door right now!
I won’t let anyone take you away from me again.
P’Sun has to be mine. Mine alone. I won’t let anyone...
- Let go! Let go!
- Sun!
I think you shouldn’t make this any bigger than it already is.
Because if you hurt Fey,
I won’t stop at just having you put on probation.
So… who’s going to play the villain in this series?
If she’s pairing up with Sun and Nop, she has to be a big name, right?
Long time no see, Flint.
How was the fitting today?
This is just the fitting day,
and the hashtag “SunNop”
is already trending.
I can’t imagine what it’ll be like when the series airs.
The fitting went really well today, everyone.
Since Sun and I are already close,
so working together has been pretty easy for us.
Close? How close exactly? Have you leveled up yet?
I think…
you should ask Sun
when she’s going to let me level up.
So, Sun? Nop has opened up this much.
Or is the reason you haven’t opened your heart because you’re seeing someone?
Uh… Sun doesn’t have anyone.
Because if she did… I think…
Our ship’s fans would be heartbroken, right?
I heard about those dinner photos with Khun Rafah’s family.
- So what’s the real story?
- Exactly, exactly!
Believe it or not, Sun and I were just talking about how you’d definitely ask about this.
Let me explain.
Some of you may not know that Khun Paabfah is Sun’s close friend.
Personally, I don’t see anything strange
about Sun having dinner with Khun Rafah’s family as Paabfah’s close friend.
Answered everything so thoroughly. Why not just do a solo interview instead?
That day, Sun didn’t go as my sister’s close friend.
She went as my girlfriend.
What?!
Congratulations.
Long time no see, Flint.
Nong Maya… don’t tell me...
Yes. The villain everyone’s been speculating about…
It’s me.
Oh my…!
I’m really sorry, Sun.
I truly didn’t know that Maya was going to accept this role too.
It’s not your fault, P’Mooham.
Even if you had known, I would’ve still taken the role anyway.
Please don’t blame yourself.
But I still feel bad…
Even though you say it’s fine,
I know no one wants to work with their partner’s ex.
Let’s go back to our room.
Oh? You’re leaving already, P’Mooham?
Yes…
Maya, it’s been so long. You’re still as beautiful as ever.
Not as beautiful as Sun, I’m sure.
Come to think of it, you’ve really grown up.
I never thought we’d get to work together one day.
Please take good care of me.
I should be the one saying that.
If there’s anything you’d like to advise me on, P’Ya, I’d be more than happy to learn.
Maya, the number one leading lady in the industry,
probably doesn’t need to entrust herself to anyone.
Actually, I’ve been wondering… why did you decide to take this role?
Hmm… I accepted this role because the female lead
is the angel of the entertainment industry.
Anyone would want to work with her.
Right, Flint?
Uh… Maya, don’t you have another fitting session?
Maybe we should head out so you don’t get home too late.
Please take care of Sun and Khun Rafah.
That’s already my responsibility.
I’ll head back first, P’Ya. Goodbye.
You’re still using the same number.
Then… I’ll call you sometime, Flint.
Thank you for driving me home.
I told you to drop me at the house.
So why...
Where are you going?
I’m hungry.
But I’m not.
Hey.
Didn’t you say you were hungry?
I only saw you order coffee. You didn’t eat anything.
I never said I was hungry for food.
If you were just going to order coffee, you could’ve gone through the drive-thru.
You didn’t have to waste time coming with me.
It’s not a waste of time.
It’s Friday. The traffic’s insane.
What about you? You haven’t eaten anything, have you? You’ll get a stomachache.
You’re talking like you’re worried about me.
I am.
If you won’t take care of yourself, then I’ll worry about you instead.
So… are you going to eat? If not, I’m calling for the check.
Wait, are you embarrassed and pretending to be mad?
Well… I saw you weren’t eating.
I just didn’t want to waste the time.
So? Are you eating or not?
Long time no see, P’Peach.
Cute? When did you get back to Thailand?
Cute packed her bags and flew back the very morning
she woke up and didn’t find P’Peach lying next to her.
Oh please, that’s an exaggeration, Love.
Actually, Cute came to help oversee the work in Thailand for Khun Jeff.
So I tagged along as company.
Oh…
Are we interrupting your dinner, P’Peach?
I was just about to ask the same thing.
If you’re going to stand here talking this long,
why not join us at the table?
Really?
Just kidding.
We won’t disturb you any further, P’Peach.
It was nice seeing you.
Khun Jeff…
Is that the girl you’re shooting with tomorrow?
See you tomorrow, P’Peach.
Are you overthinking about Maya?
Why would you think I am?
Because if I were you…
I wouldn’t feel very good hearing her say things like that.
I’m asking because I’m worried about you.
Thank you for worrying about me.
But… you and Maya used to date.
It wouldn’t be strange if she called you, right?
You should answer her call.
I’ll only answer if you’re here with me.
Go ahead. You can say whatever you want.
I thought you weren’t going to pick up my call.
Why are you being so distant with your ex, Flint?
Or is it because… now that you have a new girlfriend,
you can’t talk to someone familiar like me anymore?
You’re awfully quiet… Are you together right now?
Sorry for interrupting your private time, Sun.
You’re not interrupting.
Please, go ahead.
Flint.
What do you want, Maya?
Don’t use that harsh tone with me.
I just got back to Thailand,
and I don’t have a car yet.
I’m thinking of buying one.
So tomorrow, I’d like you to help me pick one out.
I hope… you won’t refuse this customer.
You can think of it as helping your ex.
You probably know best which car suits me.
Hey. Can you stop looking at your phone and drive me home, please?
Or if you’re not convenient because you’d rather go to dinner with your ex,
I can call someone else to pick me up.
Ex?
If you mean Cute,
she’s not my ex.
Well, I didn’t know.
Her friend said she woke up and didn’t find you in bed,
so she rushed back to Thailand to follow you.
I was afraid that if she really were your ex,
she might misunderstand me.
Sharing a bed doesn’t automatically mean we’re dating.
Even if Sun says it’s fine,
I know no one wants to work with their partner’s ex.
I am about to finish.
Can you stay with me for a while?
Tomorrow… can I go to work with you?
Isn’t P'Maya coming to see you tomorrow?
Do you realize you’re acting like someone who feels guilty?
I’m not doing this because I’m guilty.
I’m doing this
because I know you’re uncomfortable.
You’re arguing with me in your head right now, aren’t you?
What Maya and I had ended a long time ago.
Even if you say it’s okay,
I know
what she did today
will make you overthink.
But I want you to know something.
I will never...
ever make you sad
or disappoint you again.
I’m sorry
for making you feel uneasy.
Can you trust me?
I’m sorry…
if I acted childish toward you.
It’s just that…
I went through a lot today.
You’re not mad at me, right?
How could I be mad at someone I love?
Good girl
I’ll pick you up at ten tomorrow.
As for me checking my phone…
I was counting how many rules I’ve already broken.
What rules?
Normally, I don’t have dinner with someone
or drive them home more than once if I’m not interested.
But you’ve already exceeded my quota.
But…
I never asked you to do any of that.
Exactly.
So that means… I’m interested in you.
You don’t have to pick me up. I can go by myself.
Good night.
- Yesterday, right in the middle of the press interview!
- What happened, P’Oui?
- Khun Rafah Supawaret.
- Yes.
- The famous luxury car importer made it official!
- Wow!
She announced that she’s dating a leading actress.
- Who is it, P’Oui?
- It’s Sun Atita!
And at that exact moment, viewers
because as soon as Khun Rafah made the announcement,
Maya appeared. She’s the number one leading lady,
and also Khun Rafah’s ex. She disappeared from the industry for almost two years.
Now she’s back as an actress on the same channel as Sun Atita.
You’re calling about the news, right?
I just found out Khun Maya is acting in this series too.
Are you okay, Sun?
Of course I am.
I already talked to Flint.
And… I’ve decided
that I’m going to trust her.
Don’t worry about me.
If you feel uncomfortable about anything, call me anytime, okay?
Uh, Fey…
Are you going into the company today?
I have a shoot with Peach today.
Are you coming to see me at the office?
Just asking.
We’ll talk later. Bye.
So today… do you let me go to work with you?
I have a workshop at the station today. You should go to the office, P’Flint.
I can go with P’Mooham.
Thank you… for trusting me.
Is Fey awake yet?
Have someone prepare the car for me. I don’t really feel like driving today.
Um… Khun Fey?
Yes?
Oh, perfect timing.
P’Peach has been waiting outside for quite a while.
So I invited her in for coffee.
Shall we go, Nong Fey?
- Please take her to get dressed.
- Sure thing.
I’ll wait at the set.
Uh… okay.
Hey. When are you going to stop calling me “Nong”?
Your mom told me to call you Nong Fey.
If I call you “Khun,” it feels distant.
Then this time…
why don’t you try calling me P’Peach?
No.
You two look pretty close like a photographer and his model who are very comfortable with each other.
Or… are you close in the same way you’re close with her, Cute?
You should be careful with P’Peach.
She likes breaking girls’ hearts for fun.
Don’t blame her like that.
Maybe some girls are willing. Like me.
Sorry I didn’t greet you properly yesterday.
It’s fine.
I’ll go get my makeup done first so we can finish shooting quickly.
I’ll come help
in case there’s any problem I can fix.
Maybe you should fix your own problem first.
Like how you're gonna fix it.
Excuse me.
Hello, Khun Rafah.
I’ve arrived.
Once you finish work, I’ll go pick you up.
How is everything?
Um… Khun Maya has been waiting to see you since this morning.
Right now, I’ve asked her to wait in the lounge.
Just as you instructed, Khun Rafah.
Have someone from Sales meet me in my office.
Yes, ma’am.
How did you know I was here?
It wasn’t that hard to figure out.
So that means… you still understand me like you used to?
I’d say I understand your habits more than anything.
Excuse me, the documents are ready.
Are you afraid of being alone with me,
that you had to bring an employee in as backup?
You said you came to look at cars, didn’t you?
So I had my staff assist you.
Don’t tell me you really don’t know why I’m here.
A top-tier businesswoman with a doctorate like you
should easily understand what I want, shouldn’t you?
What do you want, Maya?
If I tell you…
will you give me what I want?
What’s wrong? Are you worried about your new girlfriend?
To be honest,
I never thought you’d take your sister’s best friend
- and turn her into your
-Stop right there, Maya.
Why?
Is she untouchable now?
Do you love your new girlfriend that much?
Yes.
And what you shouldn’t forget
is that what we had is over.
The only reason I agreed to meet you today
was to apologize for dragging you into that relationship in the first place.
You’re talking as if you’re admitting that all this time, you were
just using me as Sun’s substitute.
Is that it, Flint?
How clear.
Well then… I hope you’re happy with this new love of yours, Flint.
You haven’t forgotten, have you,
why we broke up?
Be careful… or history might repeat itself.
Does Khun Rafah know that you were summoned by the executives?
I only told P’Flint I had a workshop.
At the very least, she should be aware
that what she’s doing might put Sun in a difficult position.
I’ve worked here for years
and I’ve never been called in by management this often.
I’m sorry, P’Mooham.
Hello.
We’ve been seeing each other quite often lately.
Do you know why?
I’m sorry for letting this happen.
The leaked photos
I understand they can’t be one hundred percent confirmed to be Sun.
But this time, it’s not like before.
I understand.
If you knew, why didn’t you inform the channel before acting?
I’m sorry.
And if what happened causes damage to the channel,
I’m willing to pay compensation according to my contract.
It seems both you and Khun Rafah
are quite willing to pay the penalty.
But this time, I’ll consider you lucky
the public reaction hasn’t been negative.
And I hope this will be the last time
you do something without informing the channel.
You understand what I’m saying, right?
I remember that you doesn’t eat breakfast either,
so I ordered coffee for you.
Thank you.
But lately I’ve been going to the gym,
so I’m only drinking milk.
Oh, and the references I sent, are you okay with them?
I think your work already meets high standards.
The gallery probably won’t need many adjustments.
Right, Cute?
The gallery may not need anything.
But I do.
If what you need… is me
I guess I should tell you…
I already have a date.
I’ve solved the problem for you.
What are you doing!?
Just giving you some encouragement before work.
- Hey, you
- Want more encouragement?
Thanks.
You and Khun Paabfah don’t really look like people who are dating, do they?
Honestly… you should already know
that P'Peach has never seriously dated anyone.
But whether you're dating or not…
I don't mind.
I can accept all of P’Peach’s conditions.
But I do.
I’m not comfortable dating multiple people at the same time.
Love, you already know I’ve never seriously dated anyone.
After all… you came to see me right after the night Cute stayed over, didn’t you?
Mooham, go inform PR
to prepare a workshop feature on Sun and Nop.
Okay, I’ll excuse myself.
I understand
that between Sun and Khun Rafah pairing is getting great feedback.
But this series
is co-produced with Korea.
And they agreed
because they wanted a rising on-screen couple like Sun and Nop.
If any more problems arise from now on,
I’ll have no choice but to assign someone else to manage Sun.
Please understand.
Sun,
why did you come out without waiting for me?
Did anything happen while I wasn’t there?
No.
Shall we head into the workshop room?
Let’s go.
Hello.
Yes, Sun has a workshop with Nop at the station today.
Maya isn’t at the station today.
What?
What post?
“Thank you for always taking care of me. You haven’t changed at all.”
What are you looking at?
Is that Maya’s latest post?
At first, I thought she skipped the workshop because she had something important.
Turns out she’s with Khun Rafah.
Sun, you’re so generous.
Letting your girlfriend go back to see her ex like that.
Maybe we should hurry into the workshop.
The PR team will be here soon to film a feature.
Let’s go, Sun.
Why are you up so early, Flint?
Were you secretly checking my phone?
I’m sorry for being rude.
But if I have to choose between being rude and being a fool,
I’d rather be rude.
Why, Flint?
You’ve never been jealous of me before.
No matter how good I was to you,
it was never enough to make you come back to me.
You made me feel like you were never serious about me.
And the reason you’re acting like this now
is because you’re angry you were cheated on… isn’t it?
I’m sorry for everything that happened, Maya.
But let’s end this here.
Remember this,
someone who doesn’t understand love like you
won’t find anyone who can endure you the way I did.
Thank you… for letting me know what it feels like to be deceived.
It’s done, P’Peach.
I think you look better without the glasses.
Can you please stop doing this?
Doing what?
Acting like nothing happened... when you just...
Kissed?
Go on, Nong Fey. Say it. Say that I just kissed you.
Will you stop joking?
I’m not someone who just… kisses anyone like you do.
Last time, you kissed me first. I didn’t complain.
I did not kiss you.
And I only kiss the person I’m dating.
Why don’t you fix your own problem by yourself?
What problem?
I don’t see any problem at all.
It’s you…
Who are you looking for?
Just now, Nong Fey said
You only kisses the person you’re dating.
In that case…
would you date me?
Hello?
Are you done with work, Sun? I’ll head out to pick you up.
I’m done.
Khun Jan…
You’re good. You can even recognize voices.
May I speak to Sun?
Who is it, P’Jan?
Your good girl’s calling.
Yes, P’Flint.
Why didn’t you tell me you were done?
I could’ve gone to pick you up.
It’s okay…
I was worried you might be busy, so P’Jan and P’Win came instead.
Then I’ll pick you up at Khun Jan’s condo.
You don’t have to.
P’Jan asked me to stay over tonight.
We’ll see each other tomorrow.
I hope you don’t have a problem with that.
Even my sister doesn’t have a problem with what you’re doing.
P’Jan…
That’s fine. I’ll see you tomorrow then.
Did you see it?
Yes, I saw it.
Don’t let trust turn around and hurt you, Sun.
I may have just returned to Thailand,
but digging into Khun Rafah and her ex isn’t difficult.
You didn’t have to walk me all the way in.
This is my house. I can walk by myself.
I promised your mother I’d take good care of you.
So I walked you in.
Then… aren’t you going to walk me to my room too?
May I?
These days you even walk each other into the house?
Or… are Fey and Khun Peach really dating?
Oh my...! P’Flint.
You know you and P’Peach have the same type.
How could she possibly like me?
I do.
If you don’t mind, Khun Flint, may I court your sister?
That’s something you should ask my sister.
But judging from the fact that she kissed you and lets you pick her up and drop her off…
I think she likes you too.
Try harder.
Being stubborn runs in our family.
P’Flint!!!
Consider that I've passed the first round.
See you tomorrow.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Good night.
Don’t let trust turn around and hurt you, Sun.
She disappeared for two years
and suddenly came back now.
Do you really not know what she wants?
Do you really think you can trust your person completely?
(Sweet dreams.)
Dear Diary,
My life has been so chaotic lately.
It started as just “giving it a try,”
but now I have so much work.
Some days I’m so busy I barely even have time to eat.
You must be lonely, wondering what I’ve been up to.
The truth is…
I’ve become someone’s dream.
But maybe not for P’Flint.
I worked so hard to get here.
Yet somehow, it makes me feel further and further away from her…
Sun, what’s going on with that clip?
The girl in the video looks a lot like you.
And who’s the man in the clip?
I told you before, didn’t I? Don’t let any more problems happen.
Why didn’t you listen?
If we’re going to punish someone, shouldn’t there be a clear investigation first?
How strange… running into you here, Flint.
Stop pretending.
- Sun
- I’m sorry.
That day, I wasn’t brave enough to tell you how I truly felt.
I believe Khun Rafah is probably trying to find a solution too.
Oh, Sun.
You came without telling me.
I don’t know what I’m supposed to do anymore, Fey.
What I’m most afraid of… is being diminished by the person I love the most.
Why hasn’t P’Flint gone to see Sun?
Everything I did, I did it for you.
After just publicly announcing your relationship,
and then this clip comes out. Has it shaken your relationship?