♪Having survived the winter
I'm expecting the flower season♪
♪Smiling in a spring breeze
I'm immersed in it♪
♪Whose breath warmed my cold heart♪
♪And stirred up ripples♪
♪A figure may be reflected in my eyes♪
♪Bring back numerous memories♪
♪Through my life
I've endured hardships for love♪
♪With you My mind is still and peaceful♪
♪Don't blame fate and providence♪
♪And the merciless fortune♪
♪Wandering in the world of mortals
like it's a game♪
♪Risking my heart♪
♪Isn't to be regretted♪
♪I'll exchange it
for the love of my life delightedly♪
=A Dream of Splendor=
=Episode 32=
(You know
I was a singing performer before.)
(I suffered a lot when I was a child.)
Actually, being a good dancer
isn't a blessing.
For people of pariah status like us,
the more talented you are
in serving men,
the more pathetic you are.
If you like dancing,
I'll take you
to Wazi and watch girls dance.
[*Wazi: Public place of entertainment]
People there
won't look down upon us.
(She was Yinzhang's elder sister.)
- (When we were in Wazi,)
- Don't cry.
(we always heard people laughing.)
(I ate candies and listened to songs. )
(I felt warm and happy there.)
(Only in there,)
(I wouldn't be beaten by the
instructor of the Music Bureau.)
(I could watch with pleasure)
(the girls singing
and dancing on the stage.)
The ten years during which
I was a singing performer
were the worst part of my life,
but Wazi still
left a beautiful memory to me.
Then what happened?
What happened to Yinzhang's sister?
That's why
you are always kind to her.
Forget about it.
By the way,
since you like Wazi so much,
why don't you
consider opening one?
Ah?
Didn't we agree to open a restaurant?
How come it becomes Wazi?
Isn't it all very sudden?
Who said we can't run a Wazi
in a restaurant?
Of course not.
The restaurant guild won't allow it.
Wazi is for inferiors.
It doesn't correspond
to the position of the restaurant.
Do people of the guild make laws?
Will you listen to them?
Can they discipline you?
Who said Wazi is for inferiors?
Those who think businessmen are lowly?
You're right.
I'm the head of the fish guild
and the vegetable guild.
They have to ask for my favor,
not the other way around.
Though I only ran teahouses before,
I had worked in Heyun Restaurant,
the biggest restaurant in Qiantang,
for three years.
I know what are needed
to run a restaurant well.
What are they?
Flavor and taste of the cuisines?
Those are essential.
Didn't the Buddhist sutras say
human perceives the world
by his eyes, ears, nose, tongue,
body and mind?
He sees, hears, smells, tastes, feels
and then reacts.
I dare not say
I'll serve the best cuisines
and drinks
in Yong'an Restaurant,
but I want to achieve perfection
in what our customers see,
hear, smell and taste.
I hope in Yong'an Restaurant,
there are good wine, nice food,
beautiful songs, elegant music,
as well as folk music and desires.
The singing performers and acrobats
won't feel inferior.
Common folks
will enjoy themselves
with the dignitaries.
This may be an
unprecedented beginning
for all the restaurants
in the Eastern Capital.
But we need to make many changes.
Mr. Chi, do you agree with me
to make the changes?
Yes.
I have enough money to start the work.
I'm finished.
What's wrong with you?
It's a relapse.
Chief.
Sir,
didn't you clear the congestion?
Why hasn't he woken up?
The congestion is cleared.
But Commissioner
has been in a coma for too long.
Like a drowning man,
even if you've drained water
out of his body,
he won't wake up soon.
Chief.
Chief, wake up. Chief.
Well.
Pan'er is in trouble, Chief.
Pan'er is in trouble.
Chief, wake up.
Sir.
Sir, come and have a look.
Pan'er has been tricked.
Yinzhang is in trouble, too.
Chief.
You finally woke up, Chief.
How is she?
Well...
Anyway, it was a mess
in Lin's Mansion last night.
Shen Ruzhuo really lost face,
but he insisted
he was drunk and impetuous
and mistook the maid of
Finance Minister Lin for someone else.
I don't care about them.
Just tell me what happened to Pan'er.
Why was she taken away by Chi Pan?
Why did they have a fight?
How did she get injured?
Since you care about her so much,
why don't you ask her yourself?
Chief, we can visit her now.
I dare not see her.
What happened, Chief?
I don't think
we'll get married.
Shall I take you
to try some local snacks?
The people
with the Capital Security Office.
Hey, watch out!
What if you hit someone?
Are you all right, Chief?
What's wrong with you?
Chief, Ms. Zhao is in front of us.
Go ahead.
Ask her why she is with Chi Pan.
Is she under coercion?
Chief, won't you see Pan'er?
Go ahead.
Yes.
Who is making noise?
Long time no see, Pan'er.
Isn't this Mr. Chi?
Pan'er,
don't you bear grudges
against each other?
Why are you with him?
You barely know Mr. Chi.
Everyone in the city
knows Mr. Chi.
Pan'er, I've just returned.
I didn't know anything about
the restaurant and the teahouse before.
How are you?
Where is Zhaodi? Why isn't she here?
You asked the questions for yourself
or for someone else?
Of course for myself.
It's good that you're fine, Pan'er.
By the way,
Mr. Chi isn't a good man.
You must stay away from him.
If anything happens,
send someone to inform me.
Pooh!
Who do you think you are?
Why did you say I'm not a good man?
What makes you a good man?
What makes me a bad man?
Now that we've broken up,
I can be with any man.
It has nothing to do with anyone else.
Exactly.
The rain poured down last night.
The sun shines brightly this morning.
Pan'er and I hit it off straight away.
We took up the wine cup
and chatted merrily
in Yong'an Restaurant just now.
Yinzhang and Sanniang were
our witnesses.
Ms. Zhao, are you tired?
The silk shop is mine, too.
Let's get in and take a rest.
What a useless man!
Mr. Chi,
get Pan'er a brazier later
so that she can jump it over
and get rid of all the bad luck.
Out with the old and in with the new.
Do you hear me?
Sanniang.
Shut up.
Excuse me.
We're closing.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry, we're closing.
I'm so sorry.
See you next time.
Come on.
Yeah.
Hurry up.
Chief, what shall we do?
Go back.
It's enough.
I'm relieved knowing that she's fine.
Go.
Well...
Chief.
Go!
Go.
Chief, don't worry.
I'll find out what happened.
Don't worry.
You just woke up and you're still weak.
We can't let anything
happen to you again.
Ms. Zhao, sit.
I'll get you a cup of water.
Pan'er, you feel wretched, don't you?
It's all right to cry.
Gu Qianfan, the monster,
is really a Living Devil.
He almost killed Pan'er.
Don't worry. Watch me.
Pan'er, do you know
how happy I am today?
I've been opposing Gu Qianfan
for over ten years.
It's the first time I've gained
such a complete victory.
He actually hid in the carriage
and dared not make a sound,
just like a quail.
I made a prudent decision.
In order to upset him,
you should be with me.
We'll date
under the moon and flowers
and make a happy couple.
Let's piss him off, shall we?
Look, she slapped me.
She is fine now.
I still remember the last slap.
It's all right to cry out.
Hey, Mr. Yuan.
Yeah.
In the middle
will be Qianshan Pavilion.
It's for individual customers.
On the left, Yiyuan Pavilion.
Be careful.
There will be private rooms.
On the right is Wazi.
It's for entertainment.
We'll call it Wanshui Pavilion.
Yeah, I get it.
Pan'er.
Watch out.
Are you blind?
The dust is rising everywhere.
Why don't you fan her a little?
I drew a divination stick
at the Temple of God of Earth,
which says our business will boom
after the restaurant reopens.
I'm so pleased on hearing it.
They have the working drawings.
Let them do their job.
It's dirty here.
You'll be exhausted
supervising the work yourself.
How could you be the head
of the construction guild?
If you don't keep an eye
on the construction,
something will go wrong.
Now that I'm the manager
of Yong'an Restaurant,
I'll make sure your money is well spent.
Mr. Yuan, move the board back a little.
OK.
Yes.
You're right.
Work hard, you guys.
How many days
do you think it will take
to finish the renovation?
At least ten days.
Sanniang is busy taking up
the challenges of your cooks.
None of them is easy to deal with.
It will take her great effort.
Cooks?
All right.
Don't tell me
women cannot be chefs.
It's time for us to act.
Whoever isn't convinced
should have a competition with me.
Whoever convinced come here.
Everyone makes me a fried egg.
I'll taste it.
If I'm satisfied, the cook can stay.
If I'm not, please find another job.
By the way,
those who can stay
get a pay rise of 20%.
Hurry up.
- Hurry.
- Hurry up.
- We're at your disposal.
They're not my cooks.
They are our cooks.
Mr. Chi,
could you restrain
your frivolous manners a little?
Yinzhang is looking for ways to make
the private rooms more tasteful.
If you behave frivolously
every now and then,
the scholars will avoid us
like we're the plague.
I'll definitely mend my ways.
Everyone, our humble restaurant
reopens after renovation.
Good wine gives off its aroma.
Old cups welcome new customers.
I'm looking forward
to your personal visit.
On assuming a feigned manner,
no one can beat me in the city.
Mr. Yuan, am I right?
Yes.
Mr. Chi, whatever you said is right.
Thanks.
Pan'er.
Pan'er, don't leave.
I haven't finished.
I'm going to see Sanniang
in the kitchen.
It's filled with smoke
of the cooking oil.
Do you want to follow me?
I did something.
I'm sure you'll like it.
Let me show you.
Look.
I beat the rascals
of Wangyue Restaurant soundly
and took back the 300 strings
they tricked out of you.
Here you are.
I won't take the money.
Why?
We breached the contract.
They have the right to keep the deposit.
I won't take one coin
that doesn't belong to me.
Give it back to them.
Oh.
But I appreciated it a lot
that you helped me to beat them.
Really?
Then you should buy me drinks.
No, I want to eat your pastries.
The pastries
you made in your teahouse,
I barely ate any of those.
Sanniang made all the pastries.
I didn't.
Then whisk tea for me.
I want to watch you perform Tea Art.
Mr. Chi,
would you stop sweet-talking me?
After all, three days ago,
you were one of the people
I hated most in the city.
Oh.
You were badly hurt
by Gu Qianfan that day.
I'm just trying to make you happy.
Who hasn't fallen for a villain
in younger days?
You're a young lady.
Smile suits you well.
Thanks.
When I'm free, I'll whisk tea for you.
It's a deal.
Yeah. It's a deal.
By the way,
you should keep an eye on purchasing.
As for the restaurant guild,
you'd better visit the head constantly.
After all, our restaurant
is just for temporary rest.
We have to purchase wine
from the registered restaurants.
No problem.
I'll buy you the best
and most expensive wine.
Not the most expensive,
but the most proper wine.
No problem.
I'll take all your advice
concerning our restaurant.
What you told me that day,
I'll always keep it in my mind.
We must open an
unprecedented restaurant
in the Eastern Capital.
In order to do that,
I'll try my best.
What's wrong?
I've never seen you being so serious.
I'm not used to it.
So she likes it when I'm serious.
I'm finished.
What shall I do?
How could I talk to her?
It's beautiful!
Yinzhang,
do you invite us over
because you want us
to perform here?
- We'll definitely support you.
- It's a great place.
Yes.
Not only that,
I want to sign a contract with you.
When you perform in our restaurant,
in addition to the fair payment,
you can take a 10% commission
on the wine you've sold.
We can take a commission?
- Seriously?
- Really?
Really.
Thank you, Yinzhang.
- Thanks, Ms. Song.
You've been working here for long.
The restaurant will still rely on you.
Thank you.
- We're at your disposal.
Thanks a lot.
Are you getting married?
Congratulations!
I don't deserve to be congratulated.
Because I'm still marrying Ouyang Xu.
Ouyang Xu has returned
from the Western Capital.
He managed to please Censor Qi
and got promoted.
Now he threatens
to expose my privacy.
My father forces me to marry him.
How could your father do this?
It concerns your lifelong happiness.
How could you let him
manipulate you at will?
Ouyang Xu is a calm viper now.
After he has retaliated against me,
he'll come after you.
Ms. Zhao, you must be careful.
- Excuse me.
- Please stop.
- Why do you break in?
- Stop. Stop.
Mr. Ouyang isn't home.
I'll leave if he isn't home.
Let me check.
It's unnecessary.
I'll just take a look.
- Really, just a look.
- Believe me.
Look, isn't he home?
You lied to me.
He told me you weren't home.
Leave us alone.
Changfeng, don't take offense
at a servant.
When did you return?
Why didn't you tell me?
His Majesty
requested my service.
And I just assumed the new post.
I didn't have time to pay you a visit.
Changfeng, please forgive me.
By the way, thank you for
taking care of my servant
when I was away.
When I returned,
Uncle De's leg was almost recovered.
I took care of your house and servant
because I thought you were my friend.
What about you?
You didn't tell me when you returned
and got promoted.
Now you don't even tell me
you're home.
Changfeng, are you here to blame me?
I'm not.
I just heard that
you're going to marry Miss Gao.
Didn't you tell me in your letter
that Miss Gao
sent someone to the Western Capital
to torture you?
You're getting yourself an enemy
instead of a wife.
You should think it over.
I'm afraid that you don't
worry about me.
You worry about Sun Sanniang.
Though I just returned,
I've heard
a lot of news.
Let's put our cards on the table.
You're afraid that
after I marry Miss Gao,
I'll get even with Zhao Pan'er
and her friends.
You don't have to.
When I was in the Western Capital,
I learned to let go of the past.
From now on,
I only care about my fame and fortune.
Let bygones
be bygones.
Seriously?
Changfeng, look.
I got the wounds
when I fell down the cliff
in searching for Taoist Baoyi.
It was in May.
But Zhongnan Mountain
was covered with thick snow.
Sometimes, there are
marvelous turns in life.
Maybe you'll
understand me after you
get the same experiences as I did.
That's good.
Take care.
Did he really say that?
Yes. I heard him with my own ears.
I think he was sincere.
Is his sincerity worthy of 100 coins?
Didn't he make a pledge
of three lifetimes with Pan'er?
Mr. Du, thank you for
inquiring about it for us.
Since Ouyang Xu said so,
sincere or not,
he has made his views clear.
He doesn't want to
make an enemy of us.
Sounds fair.
Ouyang Xu just returned.
He's busy marrying Gao Hui.
At the moment,
if he acts recklessly,
he'll get himself into trouble.
In that case,
it's a good thing.
We're busy with the restaurant.
We have no time to deal with him.
By the way,
Ouyang Xu
seems not to know what happened
between you and Mr. Gu.
I didn't tell him.
I want him to be afraid.
Drink tea.
Yeah, I was wrong.
We still have work to do
in the teahouse.
Excuse us.
Sanniang, let's go.
You go ahead.
I'll go after I collect the laundry.
Let me help you.
Don't touch ladies' clothes.
I...
Don't think
your short-sighted eyes
can see everything clearly
just because
you ate a lot of pig livers.
Don't mention Gu Qianfan again
in front of Pan'er, remember?
I forgot.
You're considerate.
I'm pissed on thinking of that.
Pan'er is such a nice girl.
Why is she always unlucky with love?
If Ouyang Xu hurt her badly,
Gu Qianfan hurt her much worse.
None of you men is a good thing.
I-I'm a good thing.
No, I'm not a thing.
Did I hurt you when I stepped on you?
No. It didn't hurt.
By the way,
I saw the decorating flower
on your shoe
was missing again.
Stitch this on it.
It saves you the trouble to make one.
Why do you have this?
The other day
when I was in Half-hidden,
didn't I almost fall?
You helped me.
The flower fell off that time.
So I made another one
and carry it with me.
You've been carrying it?
Yeah.
Come.
OK.
Sit down.
Du Changfeng. I'll be frank.
Yeah.
I take a fancy to you.
Ah?
I have a quick temper,
and I don't like to speak in riddles.
I'm unabashed.
I know
you've been following me around
for dozens of days,
but you dare not show your feelings.
I'm afraid you haven't
thought it over
or figured it out.
So let me ask you directly.
I fell for you.
Do you want to be together with me?
Yes.
How do you want
to be together with me?
I want to marry you and live with you.
Then you must think it over.
If you want that,
you must marry me legally.
I'm a former butcher
with a teenager boy.
I'm too busy to socialize with you.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You must think it over and over again.
I'm 30 years old.
I'm divorced.
I have a boy.
I'm hot tempered.
I don't want you
to find a wife randomly just because
you've been single for long.
Moreover,
I'm a cook, and a businesswoman.
You scholars mind it very much,
don't you?
If you marry me,
aren't you afraid of gossips?
No.
I wasn't afraid
when you threw me into the river.
Would I be afraid
that you work in Yong'an Restaurant?
What's wrong with businesswomen?
I'm an official without a post.
I'm timid and overcautious.
I shake when I'm in trouble.
I-I also...
I also...
What? Spit!
Bring my wife ill luck.
I'm tough. I'm not afraid.
That's great.
I was scared.
I love you because
you're beautiful and kind
and always take care of people.
Enough.
You've admitted
many of your shortcomings.
Then tell me,
why should I marry you?
What can I get from our marriage?
You don't have to look after
your in-laws.
Why?
My parents passed away early.
Oh.
Never mind.
I don't keep private money.
I'm not that kind of man
who dallies with women outside.
The bottom line is,
don't you want to wear
a chaplet and an official robe
on your wedding?
Then marry me.
When the officials
of the Eighth Rank and above
get married,
their brides can dress up by the ranks
of prefectures and counties.
Think about it.
You've surely thought it over.
It's like boiling dumplings
in a teapot.
I know exactly what are in there,
but I can't pour them out.
Sanniang, you're good.
You helped me order my thoughts.
I've figured it out completely.
I was wondering how to
bring it up to you,
not expecting you asked me first.
Sanniang.
Great.
It's great.
When shall I send a matchmaker
to propose to you?
Well,
wait till the renovation
of the restaurant is finished.
When the time comes,
there will be a fierce competition.
Since we've made everything clear,
I won't be distracted by other things.
But I'm more anxious than you.
Sanniang.
What?
Ouch.
I pushed you too hard.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
Don't worry. Give me a hand.
I pushed too hard.
Move over this side.
Don't step on my dress.
I didn't step on you.
Mr. Du, what are you doing?
Wh-Where are my glasses?
Where are my glasses?
My glasses got...
I'm helping him look for his glasses.
Where are the glasses?
You, get up first.
Didn't you say
you had urgent business
and you had to leave?
- Yes.
- You should go.
I got to go.
Not that way.
This way.
Zhaodi, please walk Mr. Du out.
Find him a carriage
at the entrance of the alley.
Sanniang.
Bean paste cakes.
To keep my mouth shut.
Don't even think about it.
Hurry up.
Hey!
That way!
This way.
It's the right way.
- Right.
- No.
Below.
Master.
What's up?
When I sat in meditation
in the east wing,
you know I used to practice
breathing skills,
as I sat still,
I heard something in the tree.
Is it possible that the Gao Family...
Not them.
The Capital Security Office.
- The Capital Security Office?
Gu Qianfan
of the Capital Security Office
fears that I'm going to pick on
his sweetheart, Zhao Pan'er,
so he sent his men to watch me.
What's so strange?
Anyway, they'll stay outside the yard.
They won't break in.
Fortunately, you don't have dealings
with Zhao Pan'er anymore.
We'd better stay away
from the Capital Security Office.
Who told you so?
Gu Qianfan and Zhao Pan'er,
I won't let off either of them.
But you told Mr. Du...
All warfare is based on deception.
Now,
I don't believe what I said myself.
If anyone believes it,
it's their bad luck to be blamed.
Why are you here?
Did Gu Qianfan send you?
He dares not face Pan'er,
but he still worries about her,
so instead of coming by himself,
he sent you as his messenger.
I've been away for long.
How are you?
None of your business.
I was wrong about your mother that day.
I didn't figure it out
until I left the capital.
Everyone has a different past.
I shouldn't have
judged you by my standard.
I'm sorry.
Drop it.
I'm just a lowly little girl.
I don't deserve the great courtesy
from you.
Zhaodi,
I've been missing you every day
since I left.
Could you speak nicely to me?
No.
I follow Pan'er.
And you follow your chief.
We're incompatible as fire and water.
What happened between them
shouldn't affect us.
Besides, Chief misses Pan'er, too.
Only several days ago,
he was seriously injured
because of the North Envoy.
He just woke up from a coma.
He spat blood today.
He really couldn't come by himself.
Anyway,
Mr. Chi isn't a good man.
You must be wary of him.
Even though, he is better
than your chief.
All I know is,
he is a coward
who escaped
without leaving a single word.
Because of him,
Pan'er had to kneel down to someone
and beg for money
to get us out of trouble.
Kneel down?
Something must have gone wrong.
A few days ago,
Chief asked me to
sell two of his manors
to raise money.
How could he
not give Pan'er the money?
Besides, Chief
didn't mean to avoid Pan'er.
It was a state affair
concerning the North Envoy.
The imperial court issued an order
and forbade us to talk about it.
Moreover, Chief is seriously ill.
He has to take medicine every day.
Is it a big deal?
Pan'er has to take medicine, too.
She has to take
cicada slough decoction every day
in order to get some sleep.
You said he couldn't come.
If he really cared about her,
he could always ask you
to bring a message to her
and tell her he was busy.
Is it so hard?
For what it's worth,
he is a coward who dares not show up.
No.
Actually, last night,
he came to see Pan'er secretly.
Last night?
It's true.
Moreover,
you don't have to
be afraid of Ouyang Xu.
Since he arrived in the capital,
Chief has sent our men to watch him.
If he dares to pick on you,
he's going to be in big trouble.
And,
I made this myself.
I want you to keep it.
Why are you sighing?
Isn't it good
to be the wife of an official?
It's good.
But I'm afraid if by any chance,
he's like Gu Qianfan, Shen Ru...
Don't worry.
You can mention Shen Ruzhuo
as often as you like.
Now in my mind,
he means nothing,
just like the branch.
After that day,
did he come to see you again?
I have his statement.
How dare he?
The other day,
Suniang came to see me.
She told me lots of news.
Now rumors say
he hooked up with the maid
of Finance Minister Lin.
When I caught them,
I was furious
that I broke his fingers with my pipa.
Were his fingers really broken?
Yes.
But I didn't do it.
Finance Minister Lin did it.
I made a hit at the wharf that day.
Everyone says I have a backbone.
Finance Minister Lin
dares not do anything to me,
so he vented his anger on Shen Ruzhuo.
I get it now.
Men are some kind of enjoyment.
You can have fun with them,
but don't dream of
permanent relationships.
So, Sanniang,
if you like Mr. Du,
you should marry him.
When you get bored,
just divorce him.
Anyway, he isn't ugly.
You won't lose anything.
Isn't he ugly?
Who told you I like him?
Or do you think I like him?
Yinzhang,
since you came back,
I think you've been...
Cynical and misanthropic?
I'm a lady with a backbone now.
If I don't show a strong character,
how can I convince people?
All right.
I'm going to
develop some new recipes.
You must help me name the dishes.
Rest assured.
Mourn gold and cherish jade.
Cry in wind and weep for the moon.
I can give you plenty of such names.
Did Chen Lian really say so?
I didn't change a word.
I thought it was weird before.
Chen Lian
would never lie to me about this.
Maybe the North Envoy
was the true reason
that they didn't say a word
and tell you anything about him.
But he was in the carriage that day.
Why didn't he get off the carriage
and see me?
♪A feeling of depression♪
♪Falls on those will part
just like moonlight♪
♪How can we forget each other♪
♪Wind blows and time flies♪
♪When the splendor fades away
only the smell lingers♪
♪In the corner of memories
there are sad moments♪
♪Emotions go on and on♪
♪Because time is short but love is hot♪
♪Stars wink for you♪
♪Romance is crazy about you♪
♪Who even waits for you♪
♪Until the end of her life♪
♪When I look back one day♪
♪I'll let go of everything♪
♪I'll hold your hand
and never let you down♪
♪Ah Ah Ah♪
♪When our eyes get wet with tears
for each other♪
♪Ah Ah Ah♪
♪I'll enjoy a simple life with you♪