♪Having survived the winter
I'm expecting the flower season♪
♪Smiling in a spring breeze
I'm immersed in it♪
♪Whose breath warmed my cold heart♪
♪And stirred up ripples♪
♪A figure may be reflected in my eyes♪
♪Bring back numerous memories♪
♪Through my life
I've endured hardships for love♪
♪With you My mind is still and peaceful♪
♪Don't blame fate and providence♪
♪And the merciless fortune♪
♪Wandering in the world of mortals
like it's a game♪
♪Risking my heart♪
♪Isn't to be regretted♪
♪I'll exchange it
for the love of my life delightedly♪
=A Dream of Splendor=
=Episode 14=
Sanniang is in charge of
kitchen supplies.
I'm on the operation of the teahouse.
Yinzhang is responsible
for the decoration and music.
As for the others,
we will vote
and if it's two against one,
it will be a pass, okay?
Okay.
Moreover, doing business is
more difficult for women than for men.
If we keep losing in this teahouse,
can you stand it anymore?
Yes.
Yinzhang.
If you become our signboard,
your registration
will be known by people.
No matter losing money
or being despised,
the teahouse must be opened.
Commissioner Gu has alarmed me
last time.
We must be strong
to live in the Eastern Capital.
I'll tell them frankly
that I'm the coach of pipa
in the Music Division.
Even if someone recognizes me
and talks about the past
between Zhou She and me,
I won't care.
I'll tell them that
I was bitten by a vicious dog.
It was not my fault.
Being a registered musician
is not my fault, too.
Good.
Exactly.
But the vibe isn't right.
You should
straighten up your breast
and say it more confidently.
I've straightened up.
A bit more.
Yinzhang.
You're really amazing.
We're so proud of you.
It's good.
Pan'er, Sanniang,
how about
being like this all the time?
Let's not get married,
be sisters forever,
and support each other to the old age.
OK.
OK. OK.
The yard is not big,
but the plants are meaningful.
(There is a beauty lantern.)
(Mr. Zhuoshi)
And osmanthus on it.
This is exactly as the poem says,
"Inside the door last year
at this time,"
"there were a beautiful lady
and osmanthus."
(Mr. Yuan Tuntian)
But in my opinion,
the lantern is painted with Yuanjiu.
The dark and light of osmanthus
are like different makeups.
Exactly. Exactly.
Mr. Zhuoshi.
Mr. Yuan.
- Mr. Sun.
- You've also come.
You know me.
I like music the most.
Yes, yes.
I heard from Susu in Fan Pavilion
that a new store opened.
There must be beautiful music.
Yes.
So I came.
Look.
Is this real?
Fragrance.
Beauties.
So fragrant.
Half-hidden is opened again today.
We have prepared tea and music.
Please come in.
(Half-hidden)
Half-hidden.
What does it mean?
Half-hidden is opened.
Please.
Let's go.
I've wanted to come.
Good.
Amazing.
I was wondering
why it's called Half-hidden.
- It's the description of pipa.
- Excuse me.
So beautiful.
I'll come later.
Check there.
So elegant.
Nice pipa.
Yes.
May I know who is playing it?
Miss Song, the coach in Music Division
and the best player in Jiangnan.
This is "half-hidden".
I see.
It's Susu's coach.
No wonder she spoke highly of her.
Could you please play
one more piece?
Princess Qian
liked her music
and hired her as the player.
She made the rule that
she can only play three pieces
every day.
If you want to listen more,
just stay for a while
and enjoy our Jiangnan desserts.
Sir, what tea do you want?
Make the order here.
OK. OK.
(Fragrant juice, fragrant cake)
Jiangnan desserts are really good.
Fragrant cakes.
Let's check it.
Quite fresh.
Well.
80 copper coins
for a bottle of osmanthus juice.
You must have made a mistake.
It's worthy of a hodful of rice.
Too expensive.
You're joking.
Check out the situation,
environment and music.
How can you care about money?
I'm sure that
if you've tasted the osmanthus juice,
you won't think in this way.
Really?
We must try.
Please.
Let's try it.
Try it.
Osmanthus juice.
There is osmanthus.
So fragrant.
I want a bottle of it.
I am
such a foodie.
But the osmanthus juice
is really good.
Drink without cakes
is like music without wine.
What a pity.
How about
try my osmanthus cakes?
Let's check.
Are these cakes?
They're peach blossom.
Exactly, they're peach blossom.
Smiling at Spring Breeze.
Turning Red Late.
Red Peach Blossom.
Living Beside Water.
Well.
So beautiful.
Living Beside Water.
Clear and transparent.
Like a crystal.
Tastes amazing.
It's like food for immortals.
Do they taste good?
Yes.
Miss Sun
is the offspring of Ning's military
governor in South Tang Dynasty,
These were learnt
from little Empress Zhou.
No matter it's big or little
Empress Zhou,
the taste is the most important.
I'll buy a box of it.
300 copper coins for a box.
It's OK.
So are we.
So am I. So am I.
OK. OK.
We all want them.
You really understand us.
Please come and enjoy Miss Song's pipa.
OK.
Go. Let's go.
Go. Go. Go.
Let me join you.
Upstairs.
Please.
Come.
Go.
Sorry, there's only room for ten.
We can't go?
Sorry.
I've also bought a lot.
We're not allowed to go.
Why is that?
How disappointing!
Ms. Zhao.
It's really unfair.
I was only a bit late.
But I have bought a lot.
Why can't I listen to the music?
The chance
is not about time, but opportunity.
Don't be disappointed.
Let me make you
a cup of Nine Completion Tea.
What is
Nine Completion Tea?
There are nine teacups.
Secret color.
Pink blue.
Plum green.
Red.
Black.
White.
Yellow.
Sky blue.
Hare's fur.
The china of Ming, Yue, Tang,
Deng, Yao, Chai,
Rao, Longquan, Ding.
The famous porcelains of nine colors
preferred by the Imperial Palace
from Tang Dynasty to now
are all here,
being filled with Dragon and
Phoenix Tea His Majesty likes.
It means completion.
Please.
I didn't expect that
Ms. Zhao has collected
so many treasures.
This is peerless in the Eastern Capital.
I'm wondering where do
these famous porcelains come from.
Is it from Princess Qian in Jiangnan?
Sir.
Whatever tea
will be served to the royalties
in such precious cups.
Does the Nine Completion Tea
also cost 80 copper coins?
Of course not.
Good.
250 copper coins.
We only sell ten every day.
Only ten?
I'll order one.
So am I.
Me too.
Me too. Me too. Me too.
250 copper coins.
(Qingming Pavilion)
It's almost robbery.
For a cup of Dragon and Phoenix Tea,
they earn 30 copper coins.
They just put them in different cups
and sell at such a high price.
They're profiteers.
Sir.
How's the tea in Half-hidden
comparing to that here?
They do
taste better.
Sir, check out.
What are you doing?
Sir, where is Half-hidden?
Are you still going?
Of course.
A gentleman like me
should have more expensive tea.
The liquor tasted by Li Bai
will be more expensive than others.
(Qingming Pavilion)
I've also heard that Half-hidden
has a set of
imperial porcelains
favored by the emperors.
The imperial porcelains
are so precious.
Besides, I've been drinking tea here
for over ten years.
Aren't you sick of it?
I'm already sick of it.
I have to look at
the imperial porcelains.
Just one look will be enough.
This is so-called
"Emperor's daughter doesn't worry
about marriage."
What are you talking about?
(Qingming Pavilion)
Don't be late.
Check it.
Well...
Hurry up.
Sorry for the wait.
OK, thank you.
Thank you, Ms. Zhao.
Thank you.
Try this.
Take your time.
Please come in.
OK.
Ms. Zhao.
Thank you.
Let's continue tomorrow.
But don't say that
we're better than other teahouses
in the Tea Alley.
It may incur jealousy.
OK.
Miss.
You're much nicer than our master.
Our master is so niggard.
You're better.
Are you flattering me
to get more cakes?
No.
It's just that
our master's birthday is coming.
I don't know what present
should I give him.
I have nothing to give.
Well…
I've already prepared it for you.
Wait a minute.
One for you.
As for the other,
I heard that palace guard has a lover
called Zhang Haohao.
Can you lead me to her
with the excuse
that Yinzhang was enlightened by her
and I want to say thank you to her?
No problem.
I'll take off.
Miss, you look pretty today.
So pretty.
It does taste good.
It's comparable to the cakes
I've tasted in the court.
If you like it,
I'll ask the waiter
to deliver to you every day.
What do you think?
Why does the good luck
befall on me for no reason?
Yinzhang said that you're frank.
So I'll tell you frankly.
Your guests
include rich and noble people,
as well as poets like
Mr. Liu and Mr. Wang.
If they can taste the cakes,
it will not only increase your charm,
but also promote my fame.
You're trying to gain guests through me.
But,
it's a not enough to buy me
with 300 copper coins.
You're not short of money.
Let me put it straight.
You lack uniqueness.
Last time, you were popular among people
when you sang before His Majesty.
But after that,
you've been losing your charm.
Yinzhang told me that
there are hundreds of singing performers
in the Music Division.
There are so many ceremonies now.
All of them are preparing hard for
the imperial performance.
His Majesty is kind.
If he also awards them colorful dresses,
your music
won't be so precious.
You're exactly the one
who almost drove Mr. Chi crazy.
Teach me then.
I've been worrying about it these days.
Our Half-hidden
is small but of good quality.
Think about it.
What if the guests find out
the cakes that are hard to get
even with ten copper coins
in the black market
can be tasted in here easily?
Yinzhang is now a coach of pipa
in the Music Division.
If there is a chance to perform,
she would only cooperate with you.
I see.
This is so-called uniqueness.
I was
always thinking of
being the best singer.
I didn't expect there'd be such a trick.
Pan'er.
We should meet each other more.
It's my pleasure.
As long as Mr. Chi won't disturb.
How dare he?
Have some more.
What a coincidence.
What are these?
Presents from Zhang Haohao.
The wide-opening bottle of Ding.
She said that the Eighth Prince's
inscription is on it.
I can put it in my teahouse
so that the guests
will know we're close to each other.
Are your teacups all from the palace?
This is forbidden.
It's not allowed.
It's OK.
These were collected in Qiantang.
I didn't say they're from the palace.
I just said that they're popular
in the court.
The guests said that.
It's not my fault.
You're really amazing.
You know how to take the chances.
You promoted the imperial porcelains,
and befriended Zhang Haohao.
Are you bored?
There's so much work to do
in the Capital Security Office.
Why are you following me?
What are you looking for?
You're not the sculpture in the temple.
Why do you always gild yourself?
The detectives reported that
hundreds of scholars are gathered
in Mahang Street.
As an officer
of the Capital Security Office,
I should come and check
the primary criminal.
What do you want to say?
I'm saying
don't be so high-profile.
Your teahouse is small,
but so many guests poured into there.
If any accident happens,
things would be difficult.
OK.
What's more,
don't ask your people
to invite guests in Tea Alley.
The store owners there are experienced.
Businessmen in the Eastern Capital
team up with each other.
If you offend them,
it won't be good for you.
OK.
Why are you
so quiet today?
I'd like to.
Are you mad?
Are you mad at me
for not congratulating you?
I'm mad at someone
who doesn't speak good words.
You're worried.
But you pretend
to be serious and lecture me.
Who can bear it?
If I'm not serious,
you won't listen to me.
Have you never heard that
"People would rather see
the Devil being angry than laughing?"
You're fine now?
Who was the one
who pissed off every time
when hearing the name Living Devil?
Chen Lian exchanged Fei-qian for cash
and sent it to Gu Qianfan's house
in the South Bureau.
Money and women.
Gu Qianfan
is finally giving himself away.
What?
Gu Qianfan.
Are you…
What?
Nothing.
Alright, get in then.
Well,
when will you send some osmanthus cakes
to our Capital Security Office?
I'm your debt owner anyway.
Your Capital Security Office is scary.
I have no time
or guts to go there.
I'll ask Chen Lian to get them.
The cakes have been sold out.
Tomorrow then.
It's only some cakes.
Why are you so worried?
Let me tell you,
I don't like desserts.
I just want to send them
to one of my relatives.
I'll prepare it tomorrow.
Thanks for holding it for me.
What?
Nothing. I'm just a bit tired.
A rest will do me good.
Wait.
What is it?
Ouyang Xu
has arrived at the Western Capital.
You can be relieved.
OK, thank you.
If anything happens to him,
it will be even harder
to find the painting.
Is there anything else?
No.
I'll get in then.
We've earned 7,425 copper coins.
Minus our cost of construction
and the fee we paid He Si,
we've cleared 425 copper coins.
- Good.
Don't get excited too early.
It's our first day.
Taking the cost of furniture and rent
into consideration,
we're still losing money.
I don't care.
We earned so much on the first day.
It suggests that our choice is right.
I was actually very tired.
Hearing that we earned money,
I'm so revived.
Let's try
to earn the capital back
in this month.
Well,
apart from playing the pipa,
I want to do something else,
like painting the cakes
and boxes for Sanniang.
As long as the guests don't see me.
OK, let me do it. Take a rest.
I'll go back to my room
and practice the pipa.
Just go. Rest early.
I'll go prepare the cakes.
I've forgotten to take the beans.
You go first.
Pan'er.
What?
Something is wrong with you.
Something is wrong with your smile.
Since you came back
from Zhang Haohao's place,
you've been wearing a smile
all the time.
Nonsense.
Wait.
Let me show you.
Look by yourself.
We have to smile
at the guests every day.
I'm used to it.
You're not.
I've never seen you like this.
What happened?
Did something happen
between you and Gu Qianfan?
No.
Nothing.
Sanniang.
I…
What?
I think I like him.
You like him?
That's OK.
No need to cry.
It's a good thing.
No.
I know it's not right.
Because we came to the Eastern Capital
because of Ouyang Xu.
What's the matter?
Listen.
Ouyang Xu has run away.
You and him are done.
You and Gu Qianfan
are both single.
You've suffered together
and are both in the Eastern Capital.
That's good.
These days,
I've been watching you,
and found something's going on
between you two.
I feel he kind of likes me,
but I'm not sure.
What are you talking about?
Sanniang, let me ask you.
If you like something,
like makeups
jewelries and dresses,
what would you do?
I'll buy them if I can afford them,
and save money if I can't.
Or, I'll keep watching it,
even for one more second.
He's not like that.
Sometimes he's cold,
and sometimes he's just too nice.
He says things
that confuse you
and get you unsettled.
And then he pretends
nothing has ever happened
and make you disappointed.
If you like someone,
would you do that?
He might,
probably,
must like you.
Or why has he done
so many things for you?
The capital of the teahouse.
The house.
And Yinzhang joining the Music Division.
That's like what
Zifang told me,
"Love me, love my dog".
It's love.
That's what upsets me.
When we were in Qiantang,
quite a lot of people liked me.
If he
has no feelings for me at all,
I can pretend nothing ever happened.
But I don't know how he feels.
I always remind myself,
people should know themselves.
Ouyang Xu
passed the Imperial Examination
and abandoned me.
Gu Qianfan is
a Vice Commissioner
of the Capital Security Office.
How could he have no idea
about the gap between us?
I'm really afraid, Sanniang.
I'm used to him taking care of me.
I'm afraid that my heart
is titillated by him.
And one day,
when he waves to me,
I'll come to him without knowing it.
And just like
the other girls,
love fades as I grow old.
And he will say to me,
I was just pitying you.
Gu Qianfan
won't do that.
I've learnt enough from Ouyang Xu.
So I told Yinzhang
that a girl should depend on herself.
If you want to rely on others,
you get weaknesses.
So I was upset.
And I decided
to open the teahouse
to pay him back.
I have no idea what I'm talking about.
Pan'er, you're right.
Trust yourself.
Promise me.
Remind me
to calm down whatever happens.
I can't let him despise me.
I can't despise myself.
In this world,
no one
can despise us.
Don't take a record tonight.
I want to
find out the subordinates
of the West Xia spy.
If Commissioner asked,
you can say…
Rest assured, Boss.
I'm very smart.
I'll make up a perfect story
in front of Commissioner.
Smart people die young.
But smart and lovely people
like me live a long life.
Are you lovely?
Of course.
Especially with women.
Because
I grew up among women.
I know them.
Sanniang
even takes me as her brother.
OK.
Let me ask you.
If a woman
gets along well with you,
but suddenly she gets mad.
You ask her the reason,
but she just won't tell you.
Why is that?
How's your relationship with her?
Not very close.
Just friends.
That's normal.
Women
always get mad
for a couple of days every month.
Or she deliberately gets mad
to let you know she's unhappy
so that you can comfort her.
But let me tell you, Boss.
You mustn't let her affect you.
Don't be fooled by her.
Oh, right, Boss.
Well,
Pan'er's Fei-qian has been found.
I'm afraid that the yard is not safe,
so I exchanged them into coppers
and put them in your mansion.
You can deliver it to her
in your spare time.
OK. Got it.
(Xiao's Mansion)
(The edict of Father coming back to the capital)
will be issued.
(Xiao Wei)
If the mansion
is not cleaned up as I ordered
before he comes back,
you'll end up being like him.
(Yu Zhongquan,
Officer of Capital Security Office)
(Capital Security Office)
Capital Security Office.
(Half-hidden)
Ms. Zhao.
You have to let me
hear Miss Song's music
anyway today.
I'll buy ten boxes of osmanthus cakes.
Sorry.
It's our new rule that
each customer can only
buy one box each day.
How can you do that?
That's right.
That's fair.
Sanniang.
Give me a cup of Shuangjing Tea.
OK.
Cui, a cup of Shuangjing Tea.
And a box of osmanthus cakes.
We've run out of perilla.
I've asked someone to buy some
in the pharmacy.
They offered credit
and asked us to pay back
at the end of the month.
OK, I'll have it recorded.
Do it then.
OK.
Cui.
It's done.
What do we need apart from perilla?
Check it.
What?
I knocked over a cup of tea
by accident.
It's all wet.
It's pretty normal when you're busy.
It's OK.
Don't worry.
Let's dry them in the yard later.
It's OK.
I'll get back to work.
Ms. Zhao.
When can we go upstairs
and listen to the music?
Now.
Let's go.
Please.
Greetings, sir.
Is he really my father's man?
I dare not say.
Minister Xiao treats Gu Qianfan so well.
He almost ruined
Capital Security Office for him.
I'm doing this
for you and your father's sake.
You just want to defeat him
with my help.
Don't be so pretentious.
I do not get along well with Gu Qianfan.
Now he's close to Minister Xiao,
and even Commissioner Lei
dares not offend him.
My life has been
really hard in the Office.
But in fact,
I have figured out the plan
to deal with him.
It's just…
You're afraid that you can't
defeat him once and for all,
and he'll take revenge
with my father's help.
You're right, sir.
Why should I help you
and offend my father?
Minister Xiao is blinded
by the evil person for the moment.
But he's the minister anyway.
He can't
let it be accused
by the clear officers.
Let's just kill Gu Qianfan
before Minister comes back.
Anyway,
officers of the Capital Security Office
risk their lives all the time.
Even if he's killed,
Minister Xiao won't suspect.
Besides, I've heard that
your three little brothers
are unsettled.
You're the oldest son of the Xiaos.
If anything happens,
someone else
will be the heir of your family.
If you can help me,
the Capital Security Office
will help you later as well.
What do you want me to do?
I've found Gu Qianfan's weakness.
I'll take action against him.
When he's in my hands,
please tell Commissioner
and let him believe that
Minister Xiao is sick of Gu Qianfan.
Don't worry.
Our Commissioner is smart.
You're the oldest son of the Xiaos.
Even if he knows about the truth later,
he won't dare to offend you.
You can go now.
Good.
How's it?
Mr. Tuntian.
I know you are not only
proficient in music,
but also know epigraphy.
I want to consult you on something.
Don't be a stranger, Ms. Zhao.
Spare the courtesy.
Just ask me.
Well…
We've been waiting for a long time
only to catch a woman?
What do you know?
There are a group of scholars
and some officers inside.
It will be improper to take action now.
Gu Qianfan has been fooled by me
and went to Xiangfu County.
He won't be back before sunrise.
(Half-hidden)
Miss, check out.
Thank you.
Go.
We can act now.
Remember,
the woman surnamed Sun
is good at martial arts.
We must control her first.
Be quick
and quiet.
(Half-hidden)
Who are you?
Under the command
of the Capital Security Office,
we're here to arrest the spies.
The spies?
♪A feeling of depression♪
♪Falls on those will part
just like moonlight♪
♪How can we forget each other♪
♪Wind blows and time flies♪
♪When the splendor fades away
only the smell lingers♪
♪In the corner of memories
there are sad moments♪
♪Emotions go on and on♪
♪Because time is short but love is hot♪
♪Stars wink for you♪
♪Romance is crazy about you♪
♪Who even waits for you♪
♪Until the end of her life♪
♪When I look back one day♪
♪I'll let go of everything♪
♪I'll hold your hand
and never let you down♪
♪Ah Ah Ah♪
♪When our eyes get wet with tears
for each other♪
♪Ah Ah Ah♪
♪I'll enjoy a simple life with you♪