♪Having survived the winter
I'm expecting the flower season♪
♪Smiling in a spring breeze
I'm immersed in it♪
♪Whose breath warmed my cold heart♪
♪And stirred up ripples♪
♪A figure may be reflected in my eyes♪
♪Bring back numerous memories♪
♪Through my life
I've endured hardships for love♪
♪With you My mind is still and peaceful♪
♪Don't blame fate and providence♪
♪And the merciless fortune♪
♪Wandering in the world of mortals
like it's a game♪
♪Risking my heart♪
♪Isn't to be regretted♪
♪I'll exchange it
for the love of my life delightedly♪
=A Dream of Splendor=
=Episode 21=
(Be Discreet)
When we met last time,
the moon was as round as a mirror, too.
When we meet right here and now,
the moon is even brighter.
Here. Have more beef tendon
Ms. Zhang made.
I remember
this is what you loved most
when you were little.
Here. Taste some.
Come on.
How does it taste?
Great, huh?
If you like this dish,
come often.
I've brought back the chef
who used to work for us.
Your favorite Fried Shrimps
and Ruyi Cakes...
He still remembers how to make them.
I was badly wounded
a couple of years ago.
On rainy days,
the wound burns.
The physician asked me
to eat less seafood.
Let him cook some other dishes, then.
Such as Roast Pork Ribs,
or Roast Duck.
Don't bother, Minister Duke Xiao.
I don't know why you invited me today.
But I still want to congratulate you
on returning to the Eastern Capital,
being the Prime Minister again,
and regaining trust from His Majesty.
But such a high position or great wealth
has nothing to do with me,
a deputy commissioner
of the Capital Security Office.
How can you say so?
As the saying goes,
father and son cooperate perfectly.
I'm back in charge
of the Grand Secretariat.
I'll certainly arrange
a better career for you.
I will work hard
for my own career.
You have other sons.
They'll cooperate perfectly with you.
Are you still angry with Wei?
He is just too young and childish.
I've heavily punished him already.
You're his eldest brother.
Don't let him get to you.
On my certificate, Gu is my family name.
Your other sons share your family name.
Do you want me to deceive His Majesty?
Qianfan, here.
(Qiantang County)
(Don't just eat! Say something!)
Be patient.
After I finish eating,
(Gao Lu)
I'll tell you all about it.
(Gao Fu)
Don't worry.
I'm indeed Sun Sanniang's son.
What happened
between Pan'er and Ouyang Xu...
I know all about it.
Are you from the Gao Family?
How do you know that?
My mother told me
that Ouyang Xu would marry a lady
of the Gao Family
in the Eastern Capital,
so he abandoned Pan'er.
You have the accent
of the Eastern Capital.
And this character is on your robe.
(Gao)
I can certainly tell your identities.
Umm...
Was Ouyang Xu really
engaged to Ms. Zhao?
He was.
Why do many neighbors say
that Ouyang Xu only rented
Zhao Pan'er's house?
Are you lying to me?
I'm not lying.
It's because
Pan'er has been doing business.
Think about it.
If Ouyang Xu became an official
and others knew
that his wife was a businesswoman,
he would have a bad reputation, right?
So, they were in a secret relationship.
If Ouyang Xu really succeeded,
he would take Pan'er
to the Eastern Capital and marry her.
In this way, no one else would know
that Pan'er used to be a businesswoman.
Minister Duke Xiao,
I appreciate your care and kindness.
As for the rest of the stuff,
I don't want it.
A toast to you.
Wish you good luck,
longevity, and a smooth road to success.
What if it's a rough patch of road?
Have you thought about it?
I've got a lot of political opponents.
Ke Zheng and Qi Mu hate me, too.
They all want to kill me.
And your useless younger brothers...
They're only powerless officials.
When I'm in a fatal disaster,
who
can help me?
But you're truly trusted
by His Majesty and Her Majesty.
His Majesty is seriously ill.
The Crown Prince
hasn't been appointed yet.
If Her Majesty doesn't
stay steady in power...
During a regime change,
Grand Secretaries
and Prime Ministers usually die.
Qianfan,
I need your help.
The Capital Security Office
has unexpected power.
Now that you don't want to help me,
why did you go to Suzhou
and ask me to save your life?
Who got Zheng Qingtian's vast wealth?
I got to survive.
You got a sudden windfall.
I don't owe you anything.
Very well.
Very well!
I brought you up.
But now you're calculating?
My mother brought me up, exactly.
Actually, I came today
because I had something to tell you.
I'm getting married soon.
I will
marry Zhao Pan'er
who came here with me
from Qiantang County.
Her?
Didn't you tell me
that you weren't
in a relationship with her?
You can't marry her.
She used to be
a singing performer, I remember.
She isn't good enough for me!
She is.
I'm the son of a treacherous official
and she used to be a singing performer.
A perfect couple.
Qianfan!
I haven't lost my mind.
I don't mean to annoy you
with my marriage, either.
Maybe in your heart,
she's only a humble businesswoman.
But in my heart,
she's a treasure like no other.
In the dark life I've been living
for a dozen years,
she's been the only hope
and light for me.
So, I beg you to let go of us.
Do not use your tricks of all kinds
to break us up.
Otherwise,
I swear to my mother in heaven
that I will make you regret it.
Fine.
Fine, fine.
Do anything you want.
You can do anything you want, all right?
(Be Discreet)
I will not help you.
I won't hurt you, either.
If upright officials want to kill you,
I won't let you die.
The Hat Demon case happened lately...
I'm afraid it's against you.
There's a rumor
that the state will be in chaos
and there will be a demon.
Right at this moment,
you're back as the Prime Minister.
People can't help suspecting you.
His Majesty always
believes in superstition.
So...
Are you caring about me?
I just want you
to give blessings to Zhao Pan'er and me.
I hope that one day
Pan'er and I can take our children
to visit his grandfather.
Farewell.
My 50th birthday banquet
will be held within a few days.
Could you come?
For a moment.
Just a moment.
(Be Discreet)
Shuniang,
we will have a grandson.
I hope this time
he'll be more like me.
More like me.
Wrong.
Pure, Serene Music,
not Butterflies over Flowers.
You look so languid
in the early morning.
And you have dark circles.
What?
Did you miss your lover last night
so that you didn't sleep very well?
No.
I was practicing a new song last night
and I didn't sleep very well.
Liar.
You're a pipa master.
What kind of song
did you need to practice
the whole night?
Someone gave me an ancient score.
It's a birthday banquet, after all.
I want to practice it perfectly.
You make sense.
His Majesty and Her Majesty
asked to hold this birthday banquet
for Minister Duke Xiao
who just returned.
We're ordered to perform.
We have to do a good job.
By the way, who was so nice to you
(Pure, Serene Music)
that he gave you this score?
Shen Ruzhuo?
Don't be shy.
Shen Ruzhuo
visits the Music Division
every other day
and he loves to collect scores.
If it wasn't him,
who could it be?
It wasn't him.
Someone else gave me that.
Yinzhang,
let me remind you.
Men in the Eastern Capital
can be all complicated.
Don't fall in love with a man
just for his honeyed words
or small gifts.
Otherwise, you'll suffer.
He isn't that kind of man.
He...
Fine. Do as you wish.
Young girls like you
won't be amenable to good advice
until you're taken in.
Luckily, you have Pan'er around.
You won't lose a lot.
Let's continue.
♪Plum trees blossom before dawn♪
♪Fragrance wafts everywhere♪
♪Around railings♪
♪Flowers are red and white♪
Hello.
She's so timid.
Funny. So funny.
I freaked Song Yinzhang out.
I didn't know she could be so timid.
Did you see that?
By the way,
you didn't remind her
to guard against Shen Ruzhuo, did you?
I didn't. Satisfied?
That's more like it.
When you want to revenge on Zhao Pan'er,
why don't you just go to her?
Why must you make use of Song Yinzhang?
She's just a young girl.
As a newcomer,
she doesn't know anything.
I don't want her to be deceived.
What? Feeling sorry for her?
She respects me
and plays pipa for me attentively.
I should be nice to her.
When you were out there,
you heard it, right?
When she played pipa,
I sang beautifully, right?
Quite otherworldly.
Then tell me.
Which sounds better,
her music or my voice?
If you insist,
she plays pipa better.
After all, I listen to your songs
every day.
You nearly sing my ears off.
I think you should sing something else.
What do you think?
Bad idea.
What? Trying to explain?
Too late!
I hate this kind of life.
She even tried to kill me.
(Gao's Mansion)
She wanted to see me?
The man coming with her seems classy.
He looks like an official.
(It's been months since we parted.
I miss the happy days we had.)
(We promised to grow old together.
I will not betray you, my girl.)
(After I succeed, I'll return to you.
By Ouyang Xu in the Eastern Capital)
Miss.
(To Pan'er)
Miss, what's wrong?
(It's his handwriting.)
(Hope you'll get more of this.
by Ouyang Xu)
Miss.
Take them to the backyard.
Aye.
Chuntao.
Don't let my father know it.
I won't.
(By Ouyang Xu in the Eastern Capital)
Liar.
Ouyang Xu isn't that kind of man.
So,
you didn't send the men
to Du Changfeng?
Who is Du Changfeng?
He's Ouyang Xu's friend,
a Presented Scholar of the same year.
Miss Gao,
what I just said
might be too cruel.
But it's completely true.
Your father must have investigated it.
Such evidence works better than my oath.
So, my father knew
what happened between you and Ouyang Xu
and that's why he forced me
to break off the engagement?
(Be Dedicated)
Exactly.
In this world, no one cares about you
but your parents.
They only love you and never hurt you.
But I don't believe this!
Why did he deceive me?
He's the Third Graduate.
He told me
that before he met me,
he hadn't loved any other woman.
He said that.
On high, we'd be two birds
flying wing to wing.
On earth, two trees with branches
twined from spring to spring.
The monarch could not save her
and hid his face in fear.
Turning his head, he saw her blood
mixed with his tear.
Even Emperor Xuanzong can't be trusted.
[*The author of the above poem]
Not to mention a mere scholar.
You should listen to your father.
Break off the engagement
with a man like him
will only do you good, instead of harm.
You're a good girl.
You deserve a better man.
Father.
It's all right.
You always have me.
Inspector Gao,
please don't blame us
for visiting your daughter
without permission.
Don't say that, Deputy Commissioner Gu.
I should say thank you to you.
When you get married,
I'll attend your wedding.
It'll be our honor.
We'll take our leave, then.
(Be Dedicated)
What a surprise!
According to Du Changfeng,
Gao Hui is a murderous woman.
But she turns out to be
such an ignorant young lady.
We can't judge someone by appearance.
You just met her twice.
How do you know
she isn't a merciless woman?
By intuition.
And I have you,
the clear-sighted Living Devil
who has solved countless cases.
If she were really a scheming lady,
you would have stopped me
from persuading her.
Are you being too clever
or are you just being too bold?
Whatever. I don't care.
You're clever enough.
When Gao Hu came in,
you hid behind me.
What an old man!
When he held her daughter in his arms,
he was staring at you.
Luckily, he promised
to attend our wedding.
Looks like he won't try to hurt you
for the moment.
I'll be relieved, then.
He did dirty things.
But he's indeed a good father.
What?
Nothing.
(Gao's Mansion)
When I have a day off,
I'll take you to the cemetery
and visit my mother.
(Gao's Mansion)
(Half-hidden)
Slow down.
No one will grab your food.
By the way, how is
the Hat Demon case going?
Nothing new.
But don't worry.
Chief Gu said
the Hat Demon was a human
and he wasn't a real demon at all.
I'm glad to hear that.
You...
How do you have the nerve
to come in front of me?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
You!
Why do you deny what happened that day?
Which day do you mean?
What happened that day?
Tell me about it.
Why are you holding the cover?
What are you doing?
Are you pretending I'm not here?
Come over.
Come!
I know you got an issue with him.
Pan'er told me about it.
Somehow or other,
you shouldn't have fought
in the teahouse.
If...
If you break anything,
who will pay for that?
Without Chen Lian,
we wouldn't have opened this teahouse.
He helped us and he's an official.
Show some respect to him, you know?
All right.
Get to your business.
What a girl!
Sanniang, you're the nicest to me.
If you really think so,
do me a favor.
Here. Take the pastries to the academy.
Who shall I give them to?
Du Changfeng.
Him?
So many pastries for him alone?
How much do you owe him?
Shh.
I'm giving him so many pastries
just because I don't want to owe him.
I ask you to deliver them
because I don't like to see him
behave hypocritically.
This is why I ask you for help.
All right, then.
I'll deliver them right away.
Don't take a bite.
I'll give all the pastries to him.
Stop.
You just went out. Take a rest.
Leave this to me.
What? Are you angry?
Because I defended him instead of you?
You're one of us.
But he's a guest.
You're different.
When you waited up customers
and quarreled with them,
I always defended you.
Right?
Chen Lian...
He's a little bit naughty
and numb.
Sometimes, he talks harshly.
But he's a good man.
He's far better than my ex-husband.
Come on.
Take a seat and listen to me.
The house we're living in
was borrowed from him.
He also
arranged the new furniture and quits
in your room
without telling you.
He even did this
after you splashed the water
all over him.
Now that he helped you,
could you stop being mean to him
every time you see him?
What's more,
he's Gu Qianfan's subordinate.
If you always fight him,
how can Pan'er get along
with Gu Qianfan?
Right?
Fine.
Every time I see him,
I'll pretend I see a jinx.
I'll respect him and stay away.
All right?
Come on, girl.
Why are you so unworldly?
Sanniang, you're not unworldly.
But your son
still doesn't recognize you.
Sorry, Sanniang.
I shouldn't have said that.
I didn't mean that.
Never mind.
Who told you about my problem?
Yinzhang.
Fine.
Let me tell you something.
In the past,
I was unworldly, too.
I didn't get to know how to behave
until I suffered a lot
and got heartbroken.
Zhaodi,
you're capable and clever enough.
But you're quite young.
I don't want you
to make the same mistakes
as we made before.
Sometimes, when you bear something,
and treat people and things differently,
it'll be better for you
and everyone else.
Do you get it?
Thank you, Sanniang.
No one has taught me this before.
Don't bother to pay me today.
Take it as my gratitude
for your instruction.
I'll get back to business.
A thank-you gift?
From Sun Sanniang?
Will I suffer from diarrhea
after eating them?
How ungrateful you are!
Believe it or not, I'll punish you.
An official like you wants to punish me?
I'm a Presented Scholar of this year.
Since when can a military officer
punish a civil official?
Don't listen to him.
He isn't a civil official.
Yeah. Punish him if necessary.
Give them back to me!
Never mind.
Come on. What's wrong with them?
They always bully me
because I can't recognize them
with poor eyesight.
You can't let them do this.
You're their teacher, after all.
You have to restrain them.
Who can? You?
I can't, anyway.
Tell Sun Sanniang
that I've received her gift
and I'm grateful for that.
Now that the Gao Family
no longer asks them for trouble,
we should live our own lives
and stop embarrassing each other.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'm all right. I'm all right.
I have something to ask you.
Answer me honestly. Got it?
Yes. Yes.
Yinzhang,
do you think it's beautiful?
Yes.
But I have to go home.
Or Pan'er will find out.
They're only your good friends,
not your parents.
Why must you obey them?
I find this hairpin
too plain.
Come on.
Check other hairpins in there.
I have to go home.
Come in, please.
You threw a stone at my window.
I thought you had
something important to tell me.
But you only took me here.
Your hairpin is old-styled.
I just want to buy a new one for you.
When I finally have a day off,
I rushed to see you
early in the morning.
Because you work so hard
on pipa every day,
I took you here to have a look.
But look at you.
You remain poker-faced.
Forget it.
Don't say that.
I'm not going back home.
Are you sure?
That's more like it.
This one looks good.
Shopkeeper.
Sir.
Pack it up.
All right. Ten strings, please.
Sir,
it's way too expensive. I don't want it.
Yinzhang,
it's just a hairpin worth ten strings.
You're the lady I adore.
You even deserve hairpins
worth hundreds or thousands of strings.
Let's go to Caiming Restaurant
and try the new fish dish.
Recently,
the Hat Demon panics people.
If we don't go now,
it will be closed soon.
But...
Don't always think about playing pipa.
You're so skilled.
No matter what you play in the banquet,
you'll astound everyone.
I mustn't be perfunctory.
I cooperate with Zhang Haohao this time.
When we practiced last time,
she sang better than I played pipa.
I also want to perform
in front of His Majesty
just like she does.
Zhang Haohao is no match for you.
However skilled the performers are,
they just strive for a living.
She's together with Young Master Chi
who is merely a businessman.
But my family...
With my connections
with the Music Administrator,
it's easy for me to help you
drop the performer status,
let alone offer you a chance
to perform for His Majesty.
Let's go, then.
All right. Come with me.
Oh, they're really in a relationship.
When Sanniang told me about it,
I could hardly believe that.
When I was kidnapped by Yu Zhongquan,
I didn't know this Mr. Shen yet.
But for the sake of Yinzhang,
he still went to rescue me.
So, he's an upright gentleman.
I don't like to hear you
speak highly of another man.
You also think he's nice, don't you?
If he and Yinzhang can be a couple,
that'd be great.
Maybe
Song Yinzhang likes him
just because he saved you.
Don't talk nonsense.
You saved Yinzhang, too.
Why doesn't she like you?
By the way,
Yinzhang admires you a lot.
She keeps talking about you.
Since you gave her the score,
she has nearly consecrated you.
I don't deserve that kind of girl.
I prefer a grumpier lady.
Stop teasing me, or I won't talk to you.
Knowing we're going to see your mother,
Sanniang taught me to make
some pastries of Suzhou flavor.
Look. Pretty?
You're pretty.
I know that.
Mother, I've brought Pan'er to you.
(Tomb of Ms. Gu, the daughter
of Vice Director of the Ministry of Rites)
She's nice to me.
She's clever and capable.
Rest assured.
I won't be lonely anymore.
Don't worry, ma'am.
I'll take good care of Qianfan.
However hard life can be,
I will be perfectly happy.
As my wife,
you mustn't live a hard life.
I just want you to live a happy life.
A happy and carefree life.
Mother,
Pan'er and I
have suffered too much already.
In the future,
I don't expect wealth or glory.
All we want is to support each other
and live an interesting life together.
Be ambitious, will you?
When you're promoted to the Fifth Rank,
you can make your mother mandated.
It'll be the glory.
Fine, then.
I'll leave the job
of making a lot of money
to you, Ms. Zhao.
I've got some confusion.
Du Changfeng is at least
a Presented Scholar.
Why does he only teach in the academy?
Tell me about it.
What is the Official Selection?
Why can't a man be a real official
until he passes the Selection?
Well, it's a long story.
Sanniang, I'm a little bit thirsty.
May I have some tea?
Sure.
Wait.
Can it be poisonous?
Just rest assured.
Zhaodi has changed.
From this day on,
she will be friendly to you.
Right, Zhaodi?
Tell me. What is the Official Selection?
Well,
this is a very simple thing.
Being an official is
just like growing radishes.
A hole for a radish.
The official is a radish
and the position is the hole.
Without wars,
no military exploit can be made.
The Imperial Examination is held
every three years.
There aren't enough holes for radishes.
Radishes have to be grown in turn.
Good-looking radishes
have priority to pick holes first.
Such officials have positions.
But bad-looking radishes
have to wait aside.
When the Ministry of Personnel
selects radishes,
it's known as the Official Selection.
I get it.
Du Changfeng is a bad-looking radish.
Exactly. He's just a bad-looking radish.
Actually,
a Present Scholar
usually has a position
in his first year.
But Du Changfeng is
an Associate Graduate
who ranked last.
And when he presented himself
with His Majesty,
he disgraced himself.
So, he didn't get anything.
How did he disgrace himself?
Let me imitate him, Sanniang.
First, he squinted at His Majesty.
And suddenly...
He...
He indeed...
He indeed disgraced himself.
Anyway,
Du Changfeng made a fool of himself.
So, he didn't become an official.
Then, he had to return to the academy
and serve as a teacher.
Those boys who always bully him
are from official families
and they will not respect him at all.
With your explanation,
I think Du Changfeng
can be very poor and unlucky.
He's a Presented Scholar, after all.
But he's bullied by so many boys.
God is fair, you know?
Du Changfeng must have been born
with very poor eyesight,
because God knew
he would collude with Ouyang Xu.
He wasn't born with poor eyesight.
Those boys told me
that he used to have normal eyesight.
But it has grown worse and worse,
especially when it's dark.
When I delivered the pastries to him,
I saw him
bumping into a pillar.
When it's dark?
What's wrong, Sanniang?
Nothing.
Don't touch it. It's too hot.
You told me
you wanted sweetened bean cakes.
I made some for you.
They're already packed.
Take them back
and share them
with your mother and sister.
I will. Thank you, Sanniang.
Well, thank you.
You're an official while I'm a civilian.
You don't need to thank me.
Wait.
That day...
I...
I didn't mean to hurt you, anyway.
Now that you didn't mean that,
forget it.
Pretend it never happened.
All right. I'll forget it.
I won't bring it up ever again.
By the way, this is for you.
Sweetened bean cakes.
They taste the same as flaky muffins.
Take them all.
If you give all of them to me,
what will your mother or sister have?
I...
Sanniang made the cakes.
She'll certainly share some with me.
You're right.
Aren't you a waitress?
Why do you even wash clothes for them?
When I was a waitress,
I could only live in the kitchen.
Now I live in such a good room
and wear such beautiful clothes.
What's the problem
with washing their clothes?
You also bought flaky muffins
for Deputy Commissioner Gu, didn't you?
You're quite grateful.
Then that day,
why were you so rude
to your mother at the wharf?
Let me say it one more time.
All my family members died.
I'm all alone!
But...
I... I just...
If you dare to talk nonsense again,
believe it or not, I'll still beat you.
Believe it or not?
Don't. Don't.
I won't bring it up ever again.
I just won't.
I'll take my leave.
What a coward! How can he work
for the Capital Security Office?
I worshiped your mother.
When will you propose a marriage?
Sanniang and Yinzhang
want so much to be our go-between.
Three Letters and Six Etiquettes.
[*Wedding process in ancient times]
I must complete everything.
I took you to see my mother.
But I haven't visited your parents yet.
I remember you told me
that they were buried
in Qiantang County.
I should at least
hold a sacrifice ritual
on a good day.
Then before their tablets,
I can officially ask them
to marry you to me.
Speaking of the go-between,
I suddenly think of someone.
Among upright officials,
the Vice Censor-in-chief Qi Mu
can be the most famous.
A long time ago, he promised me
that he would be my go-between.
What?
I'm just too happy.
Pan'er,
you're very clever.
You must have figured it out.
I took you to see my mother,
but about my father...
I've never said even a single word.
There must be a reason for that.
But you've never asked me about it.
Actually,
I've got some secrets.
But they're so complicated
that I can't tell you all the stuff now.
♪A feeling of depression♪
♪Falls on those will part
just like moonlight♪
♪How can we forget each other♪
♪Wind blows and time flies♪
♪When the splendor fades away
only the smell lingers♪
♪In the corner of memories
there are sad moments♪
♪Emotions go on and on♪
♪Because time is short but love is hot♪
♪Stars wink for you♪
♪Romance is crazy about you♪
♪Who even waits for you♪
♪Until the end of her life♪
♪When I look back one day♪
♪I'll let go of everything♪
♪I'll hold your hand
and never let you down♪
♪Ah Ah Ah♪
♪When our eyes get wet with tears
for each other♪
♪Ah Ah Ah♪
♪I'll enjoy a simple life with you♪