Gu Haoran.
Ziqing.
I just went to the bathroom,
and then
went the wrong way.
Keep drinking.
What are you doing?
Gu Haoran.
I don't know what's wrong with me lately.
I feel like
I'm starting to like you a little.
You like me?
Ziqing.
What are you doing?
Ziqing!
You...
Dad, Mom.
Didn't I tell you?
I drank too much that day.
Mr. Gu.
No matter what, since this happened,
the Gu Group must give us an explanation.
In this matter,
my grandson is in the wrong.
But since they love each other,
why don't they get officially engaged now?
Engaged?
The Gu family
will give 13.14 million as a bride price.
The Haitian Shengyan Villa
will be used as the marital home
and transferred to your daughter
to show our sincerity.
As expected of you, sir,
you're so straightforward.
Dad.
No, it's settled.
Listen to your dad.
Then we'll go home and prepare.
The engagement banquet will be held at Longguo Hotel this afternoon.
Okay.
Are we really getting married?
Then we won't bother you anymore.
Goodbye.
Okay.
Let's go.
I...
Hurry up.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's my fault.
Haoran and Ziqing
had a hard time sparking as it is.
After all this,
you actually helped Haoran out.
However,
I still need to remind you.
Ziqing is now Haoran's fiancée.
You need to know your limits.
Don't go too far.
Hello,
Shiqi.
Is the file decrypted?
Yes, Captain.
The decrypted content shows that
Zixi has found out who the mastermind is.
It turns out
the International Racing Alliance has been
hindering the development of new energy racing cars.
That is why
they have been secretly
sabotaging the TG project.
I've uncovered a lot of shady deals lately.
The mastermind behind all this
is Mr. S.
It's him.
Zixi, he
is trying to kill us.
Recently,
during the development of the TG new energy racing project,
an accident occurred,
and the chief designer, Song Haoming, resigned and took the blame.
It seems my guess was right.
The whole story connects.
How about this, Shiqi?
Notify Baozi.
Let's meet up tonight if we have time.
I want to reorganize the team.
Reorganize the team?
Captain.
But you are Gu Haoran now.
Don't worry about that.
I will use Gu Haoran's identity
to participate in the Dragon Country Grand Prix
and challenge for the championship.
This way,
the mastermind behind the International Racing Federation
will naturally come to me.
Young master.
The guests have all arrived.
Got it.
I'm going upstairs now.
Okay.
Everyone is waiting.
Help!
Sir.
Are you alright?
Sir,
hang in there.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Come.
Young Master,
haven't you gone upstairs yet?
I just met an old man in the basement
who had a heart attack.
I brought him to the hospital.
Hurry up.
Almost there. We'll be there soon.
Godfather.
Jingchi.
Henan.
Godfather.
Are you all right?
Doctor.
How is my godfather doing?
Thanks to this gentleman bringing the patient here in time,
he is out of danger.
Are you feeling better?
Young man,
thank you so much for saving me.
What's your name?
He is...
My name is Gu Haoran.
I am Shi Chen.
This is my adopted son,
Vincent.
Thank you,
Mr. Gu.
Mr. Shi,
I have things to do, so I'll get going.
Please rest well.
Vincent.
Godfather.
Help me see Mr. Gu out.
Okay, Godfather.
Captain.
It's been five years.
How have you been?
I only heard about Zixi later.
You've got the wrong person.
I'm not your captain.
Captain.
Don't worry.
Whatever your reason is for changing your name,
I won't tell anyone.
I guess I should thank you then.
I didn't mean it like that.
Let's pretend we never met.
Mr. Gu,
what time is it?
Where is Gu Haoran?
Mr. Chen,
have some tea first.
He has some things
that delayed him.
Chairman,
I just asked the young master,
and he said he'll be here soon.
Still waiting?
How long do we have to wait?
It's so late.
He's here.
Uncle, Aunt,
I'm very sorry
to keep you waiting.
Haoran is not usually like this.
This time,
there must be something important
that delayed him.
Right, Luo Xin?
Yes, Miss Chen.
Ziqing.
Stop speaking for him.
What could be more important than getting engaged today?
It seems the reputation of our Chen family
is not big enough.
You're exaggerating, Mr. Chen.
How could my brother dare to slight you?
Come on, Haoran,
drink three bottles as a penalty
and apologize to Mr. Chen.
You,
hurry up.
Three bottles of Maotai.
Are you trying to drink me to death?
Mr. Chen.
I am Assistant Zhao from Taichen Group.
Hello.
The chairman asked me to inform you
that Taichen Group has decided
to invest in Chen Group's new project.
At 10:00 a.m. tomorrow,
please come to our group headquarters
to discuss specific cooperation details.
Okay.
Thank you.
Our Chen Group
will not let your company down.
You are welcome.
This is all for the sake of Mr. Gu.
Understood.
This Gu Haoran really kept his abilities hidden.
Taichen had always refused to invest in us before.
Now they agreed because of this kid.
Haoran.
We will be family in the future.
Being late is a minor thing.
Don't worry about it.
My father-in-law is very reasonable.
Mr. Chen.
You're not angry anymore?
Why would I be angry?
My son-in-law is so busy.
It's normal for him to be a little late.
It's fine.
Come, in-law.
I was out of line just now.
I'll punish myself with three bottles.
Mr. Chen.
Congcong.
Have a seat.
Three glasses are enough.
Okay.
Then bottoms up.
Uncle,
I'll join you for three glasses.