Get out.
Leave.
Sir,
here's the wine you ordered.
Stop.
Wow.
How come you look so much like me?
Sir,
looking alike is just a coincidence.
Wait.
What is your name?
I'm sorry, sir.
We don't disclose personal information.
Are you my father's illegitimate son?
Sir,
if there's nothing else, I'll take my leave.
Come.
Have a couple more drinks with me.
Sorry, sir.
We cannot provide this kind of service.
They look so similar.
Damn.
Who is paying for tonight?
Mr. Ding is paying.
Ding Wen.
What are you doing here?
Brothers,
this private room is nice.
Let's sing here tonight.
Okay, bro.
You, get out.
Why?
Because my driving skills are better than yours.
Gu Haoran.
You've been racing for so many years,
and your skills are still like this.
Have you no shame?
Ding Wen.
Who do you think you are?
How dare you laugh at me?
You are not worthy.
Still not convinced?
That's good.
The Wutong Mountain Track is right next door.
Do you dare to race with me?
Of course.
The loser
has to give up this private room
and roll out of here.
Remember,
you have to roll.
Okay.
Get ready to roll.
Let's go race.
Loser.
It's still not too late to back out.
Cut the crap.
When you're rolling on the ground later,
make sure to watch your hair.
Alright.
See you at the starting line.
Let's go. We'll wait at the starting line.
Sir.
I don't have time to drink with you right now.
I have business to attend to.
Sir,
I suggest you don't race.
What do you mean?
You are bound to lose this race.
My Audi R8
is a 640-horsepower V10
equipped with the ALA 2.0 active aerodynamics system.
The ALA system of the Audi R8
in continuous S-curves
doesn't have time to switch to downforce mode.
The wind speed changes on mountain roads
will also affect its airflow sensors.
Okay, then tell me,
what is the advantage of that kid's broken car?
That gentleman,
his GTR R34
is the same model as
Paul Walker's in Fast & Furious.
Its rear-wheel steering system
can reduce understeer
by 27 percent on hairpin turns.
Not to mention its RWS chassis,
which, on bumpy roads,
gives the tires 0.3 seconds more contact time.
On these continuous S-curves,
you can't beat him at all.
Well, my car is 50 kilograms lighter.
It's light in the wrong places.
All your weight reduction is concentrated in the lower half of the car.
The center of gravity is as high as walking on stilts.
I just looked at your tire temperature gauge.
The current surface temperature is 19 degrees.
Your Pirelli P Zero Corsa tires
need to reach 40 degrees to get grip.
If you hit a slippery road,
the slip ratio of your front left wheel
will exceed 47 percent.
Cut the crap. I'm leaving.
Get out of the way.
Seal off the mountain road.
The race has officially started.
Both cars are very fast.
But for cars on mountain roads,
the downforce of the GTR34 seems more stable.
Sure enough, the GTR34 overtakes the R8 entering the first corner.
Both sides are setting new speeds.
The R8 refuses to yield.
It accelerates past the GTR34 through the third corner.
They are neck and neck with no clear winner.
The GTR34 is applying intense pressure.
The R8 is feeling the gap in vehicle performance.
The R8 has lost its cool and is actually accelerating in the corner.
There's an accident.
Something happened.
Mr. Ding.
Help me get rid of Gu Haoran.
Why should I?
I'll give you ten million. How about that?
Mr. Ding.
It's best if it looks like an accident.
I get what you mean.
How dare you compete with me.
Go to hell!
Sister Luo.
Buy the bar, delete the surveillance,
and keep everyone's mouths shut.
Yes, Sister Luo.
Sorry,
we are not open yet.
Good.
Take him away.
What are you doing?
No,
what are you doing?
Chairman, the person is here.
Who are you?
What do you want?
My name is Gu Zhenhong,
the chairman of Gu Group.
I'm sorry
for bringing you here this way.
Gu Group?
What does that have to do with me?
Let me go!
This is my grandson, Gu Haoran.
You must be familiar with him.
Because of a traffic accident,
he was severely injured.
Gu Haoran, the new CEO of Gu Group,
is in a coma due to a car accident.
The new energy vehicle project he led
is facing suspension.
This accident caused Gu Group's stock
to plummet by 10 billion.
As the CEO of our Gu Group, Haoran
has fully taken over
our family's main business.
The stock has just gone public.
Once it is exposed that his injury left him in a vegetative state,
the stock price will continue to plummet.
Therefore,
the new energy vehicle project he led
will fall through.
So...
So you want me to replace him.