Previously on Drag Race Philippines
Slaysian Royale.
It's time for your first Maxi
Challenge. In Miss Shutacca Slaysian Edition!
My name is Khianna with a K, and
that K stands for K-arabao,
I have to commend you, It was a
unique blend of masculinity
and femininity.
This is Madame Yoko
from Drag Race Belgique.
You look unfinished.
What you should do is find your chosen
family, because that's more
important than anything
else you can have in the world.
It's okay to be fun, to be quirky, but
there's also a refinement. Siam
Phusri
You had one of the
best answers in the Q&As.
Khianna! Siam Phusri! Condragulations!
You are absolutely the
top 2 Slaysians of the week!
Sum Ting Wong & Madame Yoko
you are the Bottom 2 this week.
The time has come... for you to
Lip Sync for your Legacy!
Khianna.
You are a winner, baby! Which queen have
you chosen to get the karate chop?
I chose... Yoko to go home.
Thank you, Madame
Yoko. Now... Sashay away.
Condrags,
Oh my God. Yay...
So, it's a bittersweet moment
because you won.
But then again, you crushed
somebody's dream.
The journey is not finished.
We Love you Madame Yoko
Madame Yoko just got eliminated.
Wow wow wow! This is like a realization
that the competition is on.
At first, we're all having
fun, getting to know each other.
But bitches are gonna be
dropping one by one.
Seeing her go is really
upsetting. But hopefully she never
unpacked that suitcase she came in with.
How do you feel, Sum Ting Wong?
Relieved. Like,
Thank you, bitch. Why did you save
me instead of Yoko then?
Because I felt like,
honestly, you were doing the most...
And I have definitely been doing,
I mean— I mean, I have
really been doing the most my last
season. So I definitely saw something.
in you that was me. Maybe next time
there is something right.
I gotcha... Sum Ting Wight?!
I was just like, oh, my little baby!
I'll be a little baby for
Khianna. Hahaha!
This is the game. This is what
we signed up for, so...
more to come.
Kiss! - Come here!
Let's shake things up! - Kiss!
Siam too! - So you're hugging her?
Whose lipstick did you pick?
Okay. - Yeah! We wanna know! -
I have to apologize that... -
Let me hug her before.
I picked you. - Oh.
Because I have to show how...
friendship is.
Yeah, you were close with Madame Yoko.
At the first day.
First time I see Madame Yoko, I
feel like we really have good connection
and I feel like if I was
in the position that she was
in, she’d probably choose to save me.
I think I need to pick her because if
I'm done from the show, at least
- Yeah, I'm not mad at you. at
least I can tell her that I'm her friend.
Yeah! Truly, no hard
feelings, like I understand. Like this
entire thing's a game but...
you need friends in games.
So now that she's gone... now
we can become friends.
Now we get to know each other.
We're gonna talk more,
dance more, dream more, right?
Yeah!
Let's do this girl! -
Alright! - Let's do this together!
- Slaysians, honey! - yes
Let's remove our makeup, alright.
Let's go!
You cried to my face, bitch! And you
had my fucking lipstick! I hate you! But
I don't. Because who can fucking
hate Siam? Look at her!
She's like a little princess.
Yeah, I'm thinking a little bit, right?
That if Sum Ting were like
on top, he probably would kick me home.
You're here to play the game,
girl. Okay, okay.
Pray to the mighty God above,
I'm not going home!
May the best woman win. Hahaha!
Okay, we will!
The winner of Drag Race
Philippines: Slaysian Royale will receive a
one-year supply of Anastasia
Beverly Hills Cosmetics. A coveted spot
on the Drag Race Slaysian Hall of Fame.
And a cash prize of 2 Million Pesos! Powered
by Bingo Plus. Tonight with our
extra special guest judges,
Maxie and Jimbo.
Yay!
- Yes!
- Cheers to being queer!
Wooh!
Ding Ding Ding!
Brigiding in the Werkroom!
It's a new day in the
Werkroom. And I wonder what the next
challenge is. I'm so ready, bring it on!
I finally won something!
- Oh! - Yay! Wow!
We forget you at the back.
Prance, my queen!
Where's Sum Ting Wong?
Oh, my God! For the first time ever, in
the first episode, I got crowned,
Oh my God! I can go home now. Kidding!
Never!
Congrats! Miss Shutacca!
Congrats!
Congrats, sis!
- How does it feel to win?
Coming from your season, you know?
Yeah! You won the Mini and the Maxi.
- Mini Maxi, girl!
- Of the Maxi.
- That's what happened on
her season as well.
- Now she’s rich!
She won the first one,
and then mini, maxie
What happened
throughout the rest of the season?
That's her only.
That's her only RuBadge.
Yeah.
- Ooh.
Why are you looking
at me like that, girl?
That could be your only one! Khianna.
Congrats for the win
last week. But this week,
it's gotta be an international queen.
Girl, we didn't fly over here
to be safe!
What about you Arizona, how do you feel?
Were you expecting to be in the
Top 2?
Yeah, but... I'm used to
like, not winning.
I was almost at the Top 2.
I'm so fucking pissed!
I want to do better
because I want to lip sync.
I'm excited to send home a queen.
I want that power.
- Girl, I'm like- -
It was horrid. Being in the
bottom, I'll tell you that. So it's never
gonna happen again. And if it does,
then I'll see you later, bye!
Right, Bottom 2, Episode 1. Fantastic!
Fantastic, it's fine. It's fine! These
queens were actually handpicked.
We'll see what happens when
other people pick lipsticks, won't we?
Ohh girl
Hello, hello, hello.
Loosen up your buttons baby Because
it’s time to ring the alarm
If you wanna be my idol
you need to blink twice
and put a cherry on top.
Now, how you like that?
- Oh, my God! - We're doing
the Girl Group!
RuPaul is so beautiful
and we’re like, okay idol.
Ahh..
Is it a Hotdog?
Girl Group!
Hello, hello, hello!
So gay.
Hi, Queens!
Come on, bebe! Come on, bebe!
Give me that after!
Hello, hello, hello Queens.
Well, as you embark on your
journey to be the first Drag Queen,
to be anointed in Slaysian Royalty...
You must hop, skip, and sashay your
way to the crown. So Queens,
are you ready to leap into greatness?
- Yes! - Yes!
Alright. For our Mini Challenge,
You will do just that, okay? So I
will give you 15 minutes to slip in to
your Cock-Hoe-Nut
looks. So go, grow, and glow.
Come on! 15 minutes! Go,
Queens! Cock-Hoe! As in right now, yes.
Oh, amazing, Queens.
15 minutes to get in to your
natural state. Right?
Pit Crew!
The trees.
We will call this
game, “Why Not, Coconut?
Oh. Okay.
And this is inspired by the
classic Filipino game, Kadang-Kadang.
Kadang-Kadang with a K. Kidding!
Everything has a K!
So in this race, you will be running,
and skipping, and hopping,
and hustling to the finish line.
While balancing on those coconut stilts.
We will have 3 rounds.
Each queen will draw a paper to determine
which group they will
be in.
We have Group Cock,
Group Hoe, and Group Nut.
And all together, what group do we have?
What did you say? Cock-Hoe-Nut?
Putting nuts on our feet
and we have to run with it.
Well say less.
Cock-Hoe-Nut.
The Mini Challenge is
Cock-Hoe-Nut! I'm gonna speak to Human Resources
about this. Because the name
is very, very rated R!
The queen who finishes the
race first, will win magnanimously!
- Magnanimously?! -
Magnanimously?! - Such a big word! - Magnanimom
win! I love it! So, are you ready?
- Yes! - Yes!
For group cock we have
Bernie, Kitty Space, And Suki Doll.
Are you hoes ready? Cock-Hoe-Nut.
Go!
This is a race, okay?
Sorry!
Bernie and Kitty, the two smallest girls
in the group against my long
legs. They did not even stand a chance.
That was my first time!
For Group Cock, we have Suki Doll.
Thank you.
I am actually a man.
Alright, Group Hoe we have
Siam Phusri, Yuhua,
Arizona Brandy, and Ivory Glaze
Are you ready?
- Yes!
Cock-Hoe-Nut, go!
Go Yuhua!
I'm trying!
I'm fucking old!
- Winner for the Hoes- -
I'll get there, okay? - Don't you
worry. - Okay. I'm coming.
We'll wait. Wait for you auntie.
Go, Auntie! Grandma!
Grandma!
Ooh baby, it was a
workout. I'm not gonna lie.
I'm too old for this shit.
For Group Hoe, we have
Ivory Glaze!
Yay! I’ve never won anything
before. So winning a round in a race? I'll
take it. Is there pesos with that too?
No? Only for the... only for the
... final round? Okay, fine.
For Group Nut, we have Khianna,
Brigiding, Viñas
and oh, Sum Ting Wong.
Is there Sum Ting Wong?
This round is a test of
strength. My opponents are bigger
than me. They're big gay men.
Cock-Hoe-Nut, go!
This is a race!
The winner for the third group is,
Khianna!
Why is this fun for anyone?
We thought it was gonna be a fun
childhood game. No, no, no, no,
no! This is worse than wearing heels.
For the final round, we have Khianna,
Ivory Glaze, and Suki Doll.
Hi, it’s me.
Cock-Hoe-Nut, go!
We have a clear winner!
And our Cock-Hoe-Nut Queen is,
Khianna!
You're a real hoe!
You're a bad bitch!
Damn, bitch! Khianna won again?
Honestly, like, I don't think you even
need the rest of the Filipinos
to defend the coast.
Khianna is just gonna keep winning
everything. You
could have just sent her.
Khianna wins! Again.
I'm so fierce, I love it.
You won a cash tip of twenty
thousand pesos.
Khianna wins.
Now for your Maxi Challenge, Queens.
Get ready with your A-Pop fantasies.
Because you will be
forming your very own Girl Groups!
Brought to us by Cream Silk, the number one
hair care brand in the Philippines.
Yes! Girl Group!
Finally! A challenge that I'm very
excited. I had a great memory
from my Girl Group in Season 1.
It's one of the most iconic.
I'm excited to create another history.
With my Asian sisters.
You'll be writing your
own verses, Queens. Your own
lyrics that will be
representative of you. What your brand is.
And what it means for you to be
a strong Asian Drag. In Drag Race
Philippines’
biggest bop yet.
Asian EYYY! Werk!
Of course, you'll be doing your
choreography. And Khianna,
since you won our Mini Challenge,
you will choose your own queens,
for your group. You may choose 4 or 5.
And the remaining
queens that are unchosen,
will unite together. And form a
group with hostility that will be your
rival group.
Okay. I will pick Brigiding.
Brigiding?
First. Yeah. Ding,
Ding, Ding come over here.
Next, Arizona Brandy because...
we need her drunk ass in our group.
I'm actually just gonna choose
my Filipino girlies.
Oh.
That's gotta be where this is going to.
Yeah. That's how it's
gonna go. So yeah, I made an all
Filipino group to be... Uniteam.
Kidding! I'm just kidding!
I'm kidding!
That's about it.
Yeah! That bitch!
And then she picks all the Filipina
girls. And I was like, oh,
that's nice. That's really
cute and really like, that's really
homely and like fair. And
then I look around and I'm like...
Oh, fuck! None of these girls can dance.
Shit.
So it's Filipinos
versus... the international girlies.
So... No worries!
Yeah. It's a war.
Okay.
We're really in the competition now.
It's Filipino against
international. So we really feel that we are in
the Philippines.
Tomorrow on the Runway, category
is... Tech Couture!
- Oh! - Oh, my gosh!
Tech Couture. So gag us with your
futuristic, animalistic,
automatic, animatronic, moving,
avant-garde couture.
Okay, Queens?
#SlaysianRoyale Racers, start your engines.
And may the best Slaysian win.
Eeeeeyyyy!
Bye, Queens!
- Bye! - Bye, Mama Pao! - Kadang-Kadang.
- Ey! Ey! Ey! Ey!
- Ey! Ey! Ey! Ey! Ey! - Ey! Ey! Ey!
Ey! Ey! - Ey! Ey! Ey! - Ey!
Ey! Ey! Bye, Mama Pao!
Your Mama Pao is so so easy to egg on!
Okay. Let's focus now.
Let's listen to the whole song.
Okay.
Rhyming... Asian.
It's a bop. It has an Asian sound to it.
It's so nice! I was dancing
while listening to it. I had a feeling
that, oh, my God!
This will be a bop!
It's kinda slow.
Yeah, it's a little sexy.
We are gonna rap and rhyme.
You can do half time.
I love the sound. I love the
beat. I love the energy.
And it's not too fast. It's not...
And I can't do...
You know, I prefer to be like...
Okay, girls. Hey, girls.
How do you feel?
Okay, girls.
Okay, girls. Hey, girls.
How do you feel?
I feel fine.
Yeah? I like the team.
Okay. I think this is interesting.
I think it's good because you
know... they're Filipinos. We know they
can dance. We know this. But we are
different. We can bring more
originality and bring
more diversity. You know? Yes.
yes.
She started a war. She's picked
all of the Filipina girls in one team.
And left all of us
international queens in the other.
Girl, I don't know if that's
like the smartest move to do, to be
honest. Because, you know, eventually...
You guys are
gonna have an
international queen on the top.
She's just set herself up to be a
big target when things start heating up.
We'll see how this goes, but you know...
I think that's making it very clear
where the alliances lie.
That’’s pretty obvious now.
That's okay.
We, as an international group-is gonna be
fucking fierce. Because you know why?
We have all different cultures. We have
Thailand, we have Canadian, we
have UK,
we have the USA, France,
and Australia. All the cultures
together is gonna make a fierce group,
baby! - Let's go around,
Let's go.
and look for each other's
strengths and weaknesses. So we can,
Yeah. assign roles for each other.
So we have different roles, right? We have
choreographer, we have the leader.
We have Stylist?
Yeah, we can do styling. Do we have
that? We'll all do styling.
Yeah. Leader, choreographer, and also
lyricist. Sum Ting could help
with that. Lyricist, yeah. And
that's the overall of it.
So who is... A dancer or who can dance?
I've watched plenty of Drag
Race. Whoever's like, who's good at
doing this? And everyone's
scared to put their hand up because if
you put your hand up, and you do shit,
they're gonna kick you
out. So everyone's just like...
Are you a good dancer, or a bad dancer?
I saw your last dance.
As long as it's choreo, absolutely fine.
But, I'm familiar with it, but
like, I think, I could probably be better
at making
the choreo. But if someone else
could block it to make it look better.
And we can make sure that everything.
We can work together.
Yeah, yeah. Let us work together.
You can do the K-Pop movement. -
And I'll do the placements. -
Yeah, yeah. - The
whole like scenography.
Lots of blocking. -
And choreography, okay?
- Exactly.
Girl Group is so fun. We have to
dance, we have to do our singing, we have
to choreograph. There is so many like
talent and skills we have to
put together. And it also challenges
us as a group.
And we will have to see if we survive as
a group. So that's gonna be exciting.
Why did you choose us for the group?
Because I wanted us to show them
why we Filipina Drag Queens...
Why we're here.
I chose the Filipino Queens because I
know we'll understand each other.
So there's less for us to
worry. We'll be able to focus on the
challenge better, than worry.
In all fairness to Khianna, she made
a smart move. But it just looks
a little, you know...
because it's like team Philippines,
versus International Queens,
it's like...
a cockfight. It just kinda
looks that way.
You could've gotten 6 queens, why
didn't you pick one of them?
Is it because it'd be hard
to fly them over?
I see the other team. They were all
serious. Like they're having a
hard time. But us, we're just laughing
because for the first
time ever we get to speak in Tagalog.
We were all like, "yes, we can
speak our language, " we get to joke
around with each other.
Here in the Philippines, Drag is like
all about production numbers
and all that. So I know that
we work well in groups.
Sisters!
Hi!
We have something to say.
Oh, we’re sisters?
Okay, girls. We have something to say.
Boys.
Say it girl! We're ready.
I'm gonna say it.
Umm
- Bye, Felicia! - Thank you very much.
That was the message for you.
Good girl!
I'm just gonna say that we
are... two, three...
PI-NICE!
Peanuts?
Penis?
We're nice! We're so nice.
Oh! Pinays!
What? You can make the
Philippines proud. But we will make
- Asia proud!
Asia and the world proud!
- Wow! - Wow!
We're going international!
You may make Asia proud, but
we're gonna make the universe proud.
proud.
proud
The universe is an illusion!
Hello.
Meow.
Hello!
Hi!
We are about to record the new song
“Asian EYYY! ” With Maxie!
Wow!
Welcome to Maxi Challenge!
Joining us is the founder of Tarsier
Records, Drag Race Philippines resident
music producer, it's Moophs.
Hi! -
Hi!
Uh-huh. Are you ready, Siam Phusri?
Yeah, I'm ready!
Okay. One, two...
Hi Siam, Sawasdee ka, Mabuhay!
Let Siam Phusri serve you all night.
What you did here is just safe. I wanna
hear some impact on all of them.
Drama?
Let Siam Phusri serve you.
Yes. More drama.
all night!
Yes! Do it.
Yeah, shit like that.
Yes do it, please.
I feel like, sometimes I put a lot of
like man energy during recording.
I feel like if I put more
Siam energy, that would be more
like fierce, more soft, more sexier.
Runway slayer, Asia's top player, Came
to shut it down, taste my true
north flavor.
Okay. If you're singing, do
not you know, do not move a lot.
Sing it with the mic. So we can hear it.
Perfect. Okay.
Come take a sip of
delicious milk tea, yeah. I'm a mixed
breed, still got Asian in me.
Feel the beat.
Take your time.
I'm getting a bit like,
disorientated. But I'm trying to smash out my
verse. I know what I wanted it to
sound like. I know I need to
give it some energy and a build-up.
Are we good?
Yeah, thank you very much.
Ni hao ma! I'm Yuhua with the red and
yellow. I think I started too
late, sorry! I know my ABCs so
don't you dare go herro?
Yuhua! Yuhua!
Who's talking to me?
I know my ABCs so don't you say herro!
It's more relaxed.
I'll give it a try, but I think I still like
my version better. But I'll give it
a try. This is my verse, not your verse.
I'm gonna take it...
put in here. And out the
other way. But this is my verse.
Hello Asia bite me, I came to slay
here. Just landed from space,
and ready for the queer.
Wow!
That's really nice.
That was dope.
I just want you to sing the first
part on the mic. Because it's not clear.
I'm impressed because and I'm
really happy that the two of them like
really teach me because they are really
professional and I can really
learn more, you know. About how to sing
better and, how to be better.
I’m slaying with my Asians... Let
me hear you say EYYYYYYYY!
Come on, vocals!
We have a code. When a singer sees
another singer, and a singer
knows that you— It's like when
you see another gay, you're like...
Can I... Go harmonize with my own voice?
Yes. - Sure! -
Can you start playing - Okay. - from
grew out with Asian. Sorry, I
haven’t got much time, I'm just like,
I wanna do this, and this,
and this.
She said, it's not your first
time in the studio.
Alone without you Maxie.
Uh, ok! I just want you
to punch on that last part.
Let me hear you say eyyyyyyyy!
Yes!
Wow! - Wow!
That's going to be like it.
Me, Maxie, Moophs can sit there in
the studio for an hour and just whack
this shit out. I can't wait!
Now we got the power
serve it up with extra rice!
Sum Ting, she's kinda like this.
Sum Ting, calm down. It's
not an opera thing.
Ooooooh
Eyyy!
Okay! Domination Eyyy!
Oh, Sum Ting.
I know you have a beautiful
voice, Sum Ting. It's fine. When she's
gonna stop? Like, and I
think she wanted to show that.
You know like she wanted to show,
yeah I can do it. Like, I
think she was too... overconfident.
Thank you, girls!
We served it!
You killed it,
good job!
That other bitches better
watch out, girls!
Welcome to Maxie... Challenge.
Brigiding, one, two, three!
Fly high, mabuhay! Brigiding, I’m the
queen-A! Winning, shining like a
star Asian pride, let’s make it clear-A
At first, I was a little nervous.
Because I was up first. I was
trying to get the vibe, should we be
jolly, relaxed, or serious?
I just want you to sing the first
part as loud as you can.
Fly high! - Yes.
You are proud, right? -
Yeah.
Let me hear it then.
Morena from the Eastern side, Diday
stands with fearless pride
Show the fire of Team Philippines!
Yes! Team Philippines, one more shot!
It's really my dream to have an album.
Photo album.
The funny and the fierce, hear me roar!
Smoking out the competition,
vape couture!
Perfect!
I want to showcase my singing
abilities. When someone asks, "Can you sing? "
I can!
So, Will we like it or not?
I'm not sure.
Vape couture!
That was so smooth, right?
That was smooth.
So smooth!
Yes me, that bitch,
Khianna with a K K for Krazy. -
One more time, sorry.
It has to be sure. It
should have steady dynamics. Like,
"Yes me, that bitch! "
Okay.
Yes me, that bitch!
Big bold mouth, she doesn't miss, endless
airtime for this missus. -
Let me do that again, sorry.
Do you want to exercise your
your vocal chords.
Go, sis!
Go, sister! Yes.
Let's Go!
Let’s go!
When I stepped in front of the mic, I got
nervous. So I had multiple takes,
but…
I hope I nailed it.
One, two...
Runs! - Oooh! - Oooh!
Okay, girls... Congratulations!
When we're joking around, my good voice
comes out. I hope
you had fun! Thank you!
Thank you!
Bravo!
Take care! Bye!
Alright! Let's
practice and slay this week!
It is finally time for us
to rehearse. We have to do the
choreo, we have to do the
blocking. There's a lot on our plate, girls.
It was decided that I do the
blocking on stage. And when the song start,
you and I, we s— We do— We go here.
And Sum Ting do the whole choreography.
You forgot the first choreo.
- No, no. - We'll block— -
I think—
We'll block first, yes.
We'll block first.
And while we are doing this, Sum Ting
was like, okay we can do... this
and this, and this... And I was like,
Sum Ting, can you wait? Like just first
do the blocking, and then we do
the choreo.
Wait. Let them choreograph it
first before you learn it.
Yeah, let them
decide first and then we...
Yeah, because if you
start learning, you mix it up.
Should we break for tea, then?
No.
Shit.
It went fucking shit.
Kitty will say something, and
then Sum Ting will cut her off, with
something else. And then
Kitty will try to say it again. And
then I'll be like, guys this is not
gonna work. It's too confusing.
You and me,
we need to think about - where we go.
I got an idea, so... Before it
goes to the second, the first eyes on
the prize, which we know a little choreo
for, I'll let you girls...
We know the choreo, we know you're really
excited because it's your choreo.
Too much energy! Too much!
Everyone's looking at me was like...
And I'm like, I only picked this to
make sure we look good, okay? I'm not God!
I can't just all of a sudden turn you all
into the members of BLACKPINK, okay?
I'm a little confused—
We don't have it ready.
One second, no I just mean like,
so, when we're done our solo, where are
we going? Where's the next
person standing?
Oh, we're fucked. We're
so fucked, girls. Oh, God!
As we say in French,
It means like, the choreo is still in
the oven. We will show you later.
One, two, three, go.
P-P-P-P-NICE.
Our choreography session was just
fun. It was just light. And everyone is
well-trained in bars and
performing. Khianna is well-trained from
the streets. Kidding!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
Fly high, - Mabuhay! -
Are we going straight down?
Let's do this position.
Should we do an airplane position?
No! That's too comedic.
Arriving is mother, Bernie for another
My buzz today says
that I will win the prize
We were all laughing during our choreography
because like, this is
a challenge that the judges and the
audience needs to see that we
had fun.
- Slaymix! - Slaymix!
Girl!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! That was so much-
- P-P-P-P-P-NICE. - P-P-P-P-P-NICE.
Are you excited for
this challenge, - my sister?
Yeah! Why?
This challenge is one of the most anticipated
episodes. Girl Group.
By who? Do you remember our
season's Girl Group song? When we were at
the viewing party. I know! That was fun.
The crowd was screaming. It
was so fierce. I hope we get the
same reaction with this Girl Group.
Now I feel the pressure, Sis!
Drag is about finding the stuff
you needed - on our—
No, actually no. I'm just saying.
Because I was holding my tongue on it.
Because it's about team dynamic.
But... Yuhua, the reason
we changed the choreo so many
times is because you kept fucking it up.
I kept fucking it up?!
Then this little fucking bitch,
Yuhua comes up and tells everyone, "Oh we
changed the choreography
like 7000 times. " "It was really
difficult to learn. " I was like, we
only changed the fucking choreo
Because you fucking couldn't get the
steps. It doesn't matter if like
3 people could smash it, if you guys look
shit, we're all gonna look shit.
No.
Yes.
Specifically me?
Yeah!
Sum Ting's supposed to give choreography.
But she gave like,
10 choreographies. So like...
Girl, we need a game plan. And
we need to stick to it.
You are one of the weakest on the team.
Was I?
Yeah.
Was I the weakest on the team?
Girl, I was focusing on me. I'm staying—
I, I am like— So... Not a
performer and it's
like - I'm known for it.
I asked for you to decide, girl.
I will mind my own business.
Girl, we have decided and you
couldn't do it. That's why we had to keep
changing it.
I couldn't do it? I thought that the majority
of the team couldn't do it.
Nope.
I mean, there were changes done when
I also raised that I couldn't
do it. And they were done but, I was
I was one of them— Yeah!
So the changes were done
because people couldn't do the choreo.
But you knew that...
most of us are not dancers.
No, we knew what you would
do in the choreo,
You knew that most
of us weren't dancers!
We need to get started,
time’s running out it’s ticking.
Yes!
Mabuheeey! I am your mothertucking host.
And welcome to the Main Stage of
Drag Race Philippines: Slaysian Royale!
Let's meet our judges for this week.
First up, the crowned winner
of Drag Race Philippines, Season 3.
Asia's live singing Drag Superstar,
Maxie!
Hi, Mama Pao!
Hi Maxie, you were the winner of the
Girl Group Challenge in your
season. What's your advice
for the queens?
Just be present. Enjoy the moment.
And do your best!
Okay? Alright!
Okay, alright! Thank you, Maxie. Next,
from Canada's Drag Race Season
1, UK vs. The World Season 1, and the
winner of Drag Race All Stars 8.
The very funny and
super talented, Jimbo! Jimbo,
what is your favorite Girl Group?
My favorite Girl Group? Well,
of course, it's BINI!
Ah! - Oh! BINI Jimbo!
Yeah!
This week, the queens formed Girl
Groups and unleashed their Slaysian anthems.
Asian EYYY!
A chart-topping spectacle in the making.
And tonight on the Runway, category is
Tech Couture!
Racers, start your engines.
And may the best
Slaysian queen win!
Are you ready for the newest Slaysian
chart topper? Presenting
the world premiere of the A-Pop song...
Asian EYYY!
- Slaymix! - Slaymix! Eyes on the prize
Do it extra nice
Now we got the power
Serve it up with extra rice
Eyes on the prize Do it extra nice Now we
got the power Serve it up with extra
rice
Domination EYYY
Hi, Siam! Sawasdee ka!
Mabuhay! Thailand, we all have what
you like. Somtum, mango sticky
rice or pad thai.
Do it extra nice
Now we got the power Serve it up with
extra rice Eyes on the prize
Do it extra nice Now we got the power
Serve it up with extra rice
Better say just what you think
I’m a mother fucking— If you think I
don’t belong—
there’s SUM TING WONG Asian
food I'm serving And a takeaway I’m
working I’m slaying with my Asians...
First letter of the alphabet let
me hear you say EYYY Big tsunami here
we come EYYY EYYY Werk it on the Runway
Domination EYYY
P-P-P-P-P-NICE Eyes on
the prize Do it extra nice
Now we got the power
Serve it up with extra rice
Fight for the crown, with Boogsh transpower
Morena from the Eastern
side, Diday stands with fearless
pride Show the fire of Team Philippines!
Eyes on the prize Do it extra nice
Now we got the power
Serve it up with extra rice
Eyes on the prize Do it extra nice
Werk it on the Runway Let me hear you
say Asian EYYY Domination EYYY
PH pride here comes the tide Red, blue,
sun, get ready for the ride
K for Krazy, fresh from S3
I made it to the top
But I know you wanna top me. Big bold
mouth, she doesn't miss Endless
airtime for this missus
Represent-Asian all we need Perfect queen, we've
got Viñas Get your popcorn watch me slay
Eyes on the prize
Do it extra nice
Now we got the power Serve it up
with extra rice First letter
of the alphabet let me hear you say EYYY
First letter of the
alphabet let me hear you say EYYY
Big tsunami here we come
EYYY EYYY Werk it on the Runway
Let me hear you say Asian EYYY
Domination EYYY
Time to roll the dice Eyes on the prize
Go, Queens!
Domination EYYY
You want it?
Come and get it!
Big tsunami here we come EYYY EYYY Werk
it on the Runway Let me hear you
say Asian EYYY
Domination EYYY. Let's go!
Asian EYYY!
Now available on
music platforms everywhere.
It's time to broke-back
to the future. Category is,
Tech Couture, starting with Suki Doll.
Your woman tonight, I can go all-white!
We are offering you obviously the most lightest
fabric that is from Japan. The
Amaike Organza.
Flowing at the back, handmade,
custom from Suki Doll. Very showgirl.
What else can you ask for?
I'm a fan. An electric fan.
Sum Ting Wong.
She is ready for a hand job!
I've got hands for you, girl. Hands in
my ass, hands in my head. Hands in
my titties. Hands covering my private
parts. I've got Lizzo rings
on as well because I wanted
to decorate it. Well, I think I
look cool. I think I look cunty.
Come on, teletubby. Teleport us to Mars!
Kitty Space.
My costume is inspired by the freak
show, the circus clown,
from the 19th century in France. Boom.
All my costume is inflatable. And
my hat, just open like this.
Cirque du Slay!
Siam Phusri.
She's ready to be deflowered.
My Tech Couture is the Queen of
the Lotus. Serving fierce,
serving beauty. Serving
culture. Because I am the culture.
Lot-lotus and friends. Oh, I love it.
Yuhua.
Robo-cunt.
During this Runway, I am
feeling what?! Very extra bootleg. My
outfit broke down, so... My bootleg brain
came on. It went to my luggage.
I pulled out a costume that
kinda looks like a robot. But I know,
the judges were going "What
the fuck is this bitch thinking? "
Artificial Intelligence ! Thank You!
Khianna
She's root-iful, isn't she?
For this Runway, the concept
of my look, is the modern world
meets nature's anger. This look
simply means nature reclaims the Runway.
A white, futuristic vision where
wild beauty conquers the
concrete jungle.
Brigiding.
Salamin, salamin, sa
dingding-ding! (A song by P-Pop Girl Group, BINI)
Reflections shimmering, feathers
fluttering. A vision
of duality, where the
physical meets the spirituality.
Mirror, mirror, isn't this the look,
the best you've ever seen?
Viñas DeLuxe.
Fishes, fishes, fishes, fishes!
(In the tune of Misis by Viñas DeLuxe)
I wanna celebrate, our market missus.
Freshly-caught, just like me.
Oh, my gosh! They're alive!
What a catch!
Let there be fish on Earth.
Find the pearl, on the West Philippine
cheeks! Kidding.
Bernie.
This is a kind of metamorphosis.
A cocoon, that
transformed into a butterfly.
Because I am Diday, who used to
be a sweet little queer but
now, is a full-blown queen.
A fierce Diday!
I wanna have in-sex with her.
Arizona Brandy.
I think her lace is untied.
I'm walking like as a ball of fire.
You've never seen Arizona be
this couture! This Arizona has evolved.
And, is ready for all
the Runways.
She looks too hot to handle!
Ivory Glaze.
I'm seeing double! Double D.
I am hypnosis-inspired. I've got wheels spinning
on each breast, and on my head
as well. I'm selling it to the
judges, I'm like, you're gonna look, into my
wheels and you will let me be safe. Hey,
I’m just hoping anything works at
this point. I just don't want
to be in the bottom.
Welcome back, ladies.
I have one thing to say.
That was yummy.
Eyy! - EYY!
This week you performed as two
teams, but you will be judged individually
by the Lord God, Almighty. No, by us.
When I call your
name, please step forward.
Ivory Glaze.
Yuhua.
Yes, Sum Ting Wong.
Brigiding.
Arizona Brandy.
Viñas DeLuxe.
You, Queens, are the tops and
bottoms of this week.
Condragulations.
Oh, my God.
The rest of you, are safe.
Please head back to
the Werkroom and untuck.
Shit. It's drink o'clock, Bernie!
Before we begin the judges' critiques,
Queens,
you must first answer this
question, honestly.
Is there anyone,
in your group,
that was dragging your team down?
I want names, I want details.
Let's start with, Ivory Glaze.
There was a lot of back and forth,
and switching choreography. And that was
mostly coming from Sum Ting.
I'm sorry, girl.
It was Sum Ting, as well.
Unfortunately, we
changed the choreography a lot.
And we didn't have enough time.
I should have just said “fuck it”, if
you can't learn it then... You're
just gonna have to look bad. But then,
that's my fault for trying
to help.
Sum Ting.
I'd probably say, Yuhua.
Because when we did choreography, everyone
had it set, and the one that
was dragging us all down, was Yuhua.
But I was speaking on behalf of
half of the group, though.
They all got it, girl.
I spoke on behalf of
the girls, so I don't think
I should be punished,
because I spoke up.
Brigiding.
All of us, the five of us,
helped each other to have the best
choreography for our performance
earlier.
Okay.
Arizona.
I don't think anyone's dragging
us down as well.
I think we were lifting each other
up. Lifting?! Kidding.
Okay.
Now, Viñas, shutacca.
If I have to name a name,
I didn't learn anything from Bernie's
lyrics about her. I just
noticed that it's about trans power,
but other than that,
all of us gave our best.
And that's the answer we want to hear.
Then why didn't we just ask
Viñas, right?
Now, let's start the judges' critiques.
Let's start with, Ivory Glaze.
I'm not the best dancer, myself,
so I sympathize. You know, whenever
you got some fear going
into the challenge, just bring
your personality on the stage, because,
sometimes if you don't know all
the moves, at least if you're showing
with your face that you're really having
a good time, it helps kind
of make up for the fact that you're
a bit afraid, or unsure.
I think a bit more stage
presence would be helpful next time.
But
on your runway I loved it.
You looked expensive.
I like the thing thats rolling
rolling in the deep deep blue sea like that.
And because of that, this is your score.
Yuhua.
So, I really thought that you came out
of the gate with a lot of energy
behind you. And I didn't really care that
you didn't necessarily know all
the choreo. I was
there with you, having fun.
Well, for me, personally,
I loved your energy duing the
Girl Group Performance.
Your Runway tonight, was a
little bit confusing. Is this what
the original concept was, or did you
encounter some difficulties?
Girl, I'm not gonna lie. This Runway
is bootleg as fuck, girls.
So, my original concept was to come
out with the Drag Race flag.
Checkered. Huge. This tall,
and I'll wave it. And then I press
the button, all the cars
start moving. But,
I had to get bootleg and grab
everything that I had in my luggage and made
it work.
You have a beautiful story
behind it, but, unfortunately, this
is what we are judging.
Right.
Thank you very much.
Now, finally. Yes, Sum Ting Wong?
Hello.
It was nice seeing you elevated
and put-together. This kinda reminds
me of like an AI nightmare or something.
In your Girl Group
performance, you started so strong.
But,
it dips in the end. A little
messy in the end.
And also, it's a missed chance that
you didn't sing your adlibs.
Yes.
Your vocals! There's a hint
of Beyoncé. And a lot of Jay-Z.
Yuhua, do you think she's the
Beyoncé of the group?
I don't think so.
I just think that she was
also very excited,
and she meant well. But I just
don't think that it was
executed in the perfect way possible.
Alright.
Now, Brigiding.
Filipina power. You guys were
absolutely amazing.
Cohesive. I loved all your
looks together. I could tell that as
a team, you were
having a really great time.
In this Runway, you look incredible.
I'm obsessed with
your headdress.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You look great. - I'm obsessed with you.
Why don't you just live
together already?
Stop teasing, Mama Pao.
We'll have time for that later.
Thank you,
Brigiding. Arizona Brandy.
For your look on the Runway tonight,
I love it. It's very avant-garde. It's
also very powerful, almost
like a dragon.
Thank you.
I think the only critique would be
the shoes, for me. Other than
that, it's just nitpicking, because
you look so stunning. So,
Thank you.
congratulations, great night.
I really, really loved your confidence.
It really translated on
your performance.
I loved the lyrics, the
performance, the choreography. You really worked
hard for that. It's just
like, you were born to do drag. I'm
teasing! Yeah, that's Mama Ru's line.
Is Mama Ru here? No, don't
take that back!
I'm claiming that as part
of my critique.
Thank you very much, Arizona.
Thank you so much.
And last but not the least,
Viñas DeLuxe.
Your Runway really surprised
me. It was like a reveal when you
emptied your hat and all the
fish splashed out like a big catch.
It looks like you met a friendly seaman.
Tonight, you've shown us that
you really are a star.
I didn't know you could still split!
OMG!
Just for the right men.
You gave us everything.
Stunts, beauty,
and the Viñas brand of confidence,
and comedy.
Thank you, thank you, Viñas.
So based on your
performances in Tech Couture Runway,
we have made some decisions.
Viñas DeLuxe.
Arizona Brandy.
Condragulations, Queens.
You are the Top 2 Slaysians of the week.
Condragulations.
Brigiding.
Yuhua.
You two, are safe.
That means,
Sum Ting Wong and Ivory Glaze,
you are the Bottom 2 queens of the week.
Viñas DeLuxe and Arizona Brandy.
Each of you needs to decide which
of the bottom queens you'll eliminate.
If you win the lip sync. Now while you
queens deliberate in the Werkroom,
the judges and I will eat snacks.
Alright? So don't disturb us. You may
leave the stage and evaporate.
So who do you think is gonna be Top?
You know what, I loved Viñas'
lyrics. Viñas' lyrics were very iconic. It
was good, no?
The Runway that I loved was Viñas'.
Amen. No, I love Arizona's verse.
What was it?
Yes. Arizona's verse.
What was she saying again in the song?
What was she singing?
I don't know. Kidding!
I liked it.
That was perfect. And who do
you think would be at the bottom?
I think the Bottom is...
Now, It's Sum, and
Ivory.
Why do you think they are in the bottom?
Oh, you mean like it was boring?
Or the same silhouettes
were not really interesting to you?
Oh, wow, she's adding all of that.
I think that's your comment, girl.
No!
Cause like, well, Oh, yeah.
She was not good, no silhouette,
very repetitive...
No, because I could— she's the
one who, like, struggled and then...
Yeah. The most. You need to be,
like, 1-2-3-4-5. You have to be exact.
Yeah.
But in the live,
It's not like that.
Everything is not the same.
Yeah.
Girl, on the live scene, if something
happens, you don't...
But this is show
business, you know what I mean?
Yo, this fucking bullshit!
Girls.
Guess who's in the fucking bottom again?
Could I not just be safe?
Huh?
Please, please. Why do I have to
be so chaotic, that I gotta be... the
judges either loved it or they
fucking hate her and she's going to be in
the Bottom 2. And that's
happening again!
Are you gonna be at the Top? Sister?
Are Pinay girls at the Top?
And Arizona, I think.
Yas! - Yas!
I'm proud of my girls!
I'm so happy because
this is a really great chance for
me to show how I sing, and this is one
of the challenges that I dreamed
to be on the Top. And
it happened, so. I'm so happy.
Congratulations, Sis.
It really is a different
feeling, being on Top for the first time.
And, I don't know which to focus on.
I have to learn a song, I have to
win. I can’t just be on top, I want that
money, too.
How about you, Arizona?
It feels nice, because, people
were appreciating my
look because,
Like what I've said, I've never been
told, "Oh, my God, you're dress
is nice! "
This is my first time
having that appreciation but,
it also feels sad because we have to,
somehow, end somebody's run here.
We don't just get to eliminate. We
have to. It's a requirement.
Can we eliminate two?
Bernie. We were asked by Mama
Pao to mention someone who we think
is dragging the group down. I said
that there's no one in our
group who was bringing the group down.
She's been telling us, "I
don't want that answer. " "I need a
real answer. " and I'm like,
there really was no weakest link, but
if you really want one, Bernie
was... like, the only thing I
understood from her lyrics was about trans power.
If I really needed to answer, I mean, we're
in a reality show, I won't give
some showbiz answer. So, I mentioned who
the weakest link is from my point
of view.
No, it's okay. I know that...
You know I love you.
Sum Ting and Ivory, I
already knew from rehearsals,
that Ivory was struggling with Sum Ting.
For me to decide, like I also wanna hear
the group.
Me and Ivory are Bottom 2.
The problem was, because it took so
many iterations to - land where
But without me there wouldn't
have been a single fucking iteration
we were.
to start off with.
That's what I'm saying.
I think the group does owe a lot to Sum.
We wouldn't even have a choreo
without him. But Sum did
modifications to all the blockings, and all of the
choreos and that
really set everyone back.
So, Ivory and Yuhua mentioned Sum
Ting Wong to be like least
By the way, within seconds...
When the Pinoy girls were asked, who
was in— "Who dragged down your
group? " they were like, "No one
dragged our group, we were
all fantastic. " And
I'm standing there, like...
You motherfuckers took three
seconds to throw me under this fucking
bus. Snakes, all of them. Both of them,
snakes. Bitches. Hoes. Never
gonna talk to them again.
And without me,
there wouldn't have been
a fucking dance.
And then soon as they got the opportunity
they were like, "You
know what, fuck it. " "Let's throw
Sum Ting under the bus. "
And I was like, we were all
friends here. When it comes to saving
your own ass, I was just like, oh, okay.
Oh, I see what you're like.
I see what you're doing. Okay, cool.
Play the game.
It was pretty obvious. The other group took
their time, because they couldn't
pinpoint anyone right away. We knew right
away who it was. We didn't have
to think about it. Of course, it
was gonna take less than five seconds.
I don't wanna fucking go home, right?
If you want to put it down to who you thought
did the worse in this, and you
pick my name, I'm gonna think
you're weird for it, but, I'll respect
your decision.
If you wanna save for a different
reason, that's
completely valid, too. You can
pick depending on track
record. I've already been in the bottom.
Maybe you wanna pick on that.
If you want to pick on who you
want to have more time in the spotlight
to really showcase their drag,
you can do that as well. Or, if you
wanna pick specifically on this challenge,
you can pick to save me.
But tonight, it's up to you, completely.
Because at the end of the day,
I'm proud of our work. I'm
proud of my work. And I'm proud of
the work that the girls put in.
How do you feel, Ivory?
I'm just,
like, upset. Like frustrated, to
be honest. I've come in as
the, statistically... the worst queen.
You know, I was 8th place on
my season. Earliest out.
My time last time, was horrible.
It's kind of
burdened me for a long time.
I just wanted a chance to, like, shine.
I just wanna be there one time.
To like,
show people
that I can
do good drag. And like...
And so this time I wanna just,
I wanted to stick around.
I wanna stick around.
To show people that I'm not trash.
I'm sorry to say this in
front of you, Sum Ting, but, I
hope you guys pick my lipstick.
Because, wait, no, that means I go home.
I hope you don't pick my lipstick.
I hope you pick to keep me. I think
I've pleaded my case well.
I have a lot on the line, so I just
need, I just want... Please,
save me, girls. Please, save me.
I chose this person
because I know that she will do
better or best outside the competition.
Because she's
been feeling some type of ways here.
So I want her to be free.
It's getting real. Because we really get
to decide. We have their... We have
their fate upon our hands,
and it's hard.
Oh, wow!
Big bad bananas?
Jimbo, why are your bananas
so, so long? Why is mine so short?
Mama Pao, you have a problem?
Maxie, that's not
"bananacue". That's "banana-cute"!
Banana-cute?!
Okay! Enough with these bananas! These
bananas are making me hard.
Bring back my A-Pop girlies.
Two Top Slaysian Divas stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare a
lip sync performance of “XL”, by
Thai-Italian superstar, Silvy.
Ladies. This is your chance
to impress me,
Win 80, 000 pesos, and earn the
power to give one of the
Bottom queens, the karate chop.
Hi-ya!
The time has come
for you to Lip Sync
for your Legacy!
It's the battle of the singers.
I can feel that...
there’s a lot of tension.
Arizona, give this to me. You're
not a singer anyway.
If I lose, it'll be embarrassing.
I'm kidding.
Good luck, Queens.
And don't fuck it up.
I've got the baddest ass
you've ever seen Be your own kind of
beautiful. Fuck it we're all beautiful
Call it a win
No need to hide it Show me some skin Be
your own kind of beautiful Fuck it,
we're all beautiful
S M L but I like it XL
Bitch, I'm still here. The booty
queen I've got the baddest ass you've ever
seen
Be your own kind of beautiful
Fuck it we're all beautiful. S M L but
I like it XL XL
Oh, my God!
Ladies, I have made my decision.
Viñas DeLuxe.
You’re a winner, baby!
Condragulations! You have won a cash tip worth 80,
000 pesos, courtesy of Cream
Silk, the number one haircare brand in
the Philippines.
My God! Thank you, Lord! Thank you, thank
you, Lord, for this. For giving me
this win, this
episode. So I'm so, so happy.
Lord, I'm going to
Quiapo and donate, I swear.
And you will also receive a RuBadge.
Hand her a RuBadge!
Wear it with Slaysian
pride. With your live tilapias.
Arizona Brandy, you are safe.
You may join the other queens.
What a waste! Come on.
It's okay.
Now,
will the Bottom 2
queens please, step forward.
Viñas DeLuxe,
with great power,
from our Slaysian
ancestors, comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you
chosen to get the karate chop?
The queen that I've
chosen to get the karate chop...
it's purely based on track records.
That's what I wanna do in
this competition. So...
It’s...
Sum Ting Wong. I'm so sorry.
No, it's fine. It's fucking
fine, don't worry.
As it is written, so it shall be done.
Sum Ting Wong.
Our British Bombshell.
You are, and will always
be, a true, Slaysian Sensation.
Sum Ting Wong, do you have
anything to say?
You're all bastards! No, I'm
kidding! I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I had an
amazing time. You've all been
incredible, and you
know what? It's my time to go.
I know you will understand this.
Horrible bitch.
Sum Ting really went Wong. Bye!
I love you all!
Love you, too!
My voice is gonna be on that track. I
tell you the fuck now. And I leave
the sickest verse.
Thank you for having me.
Condragulations, Queens! You all
made your mothers proud. Your mothers are
all queens!
Your mother is a queen, too.
And remember, always be true
to yourself, in your thoughts, in
your words and in everything
that you do. All heart. Always and in
all ways. Can I get an eme up in here?
Eme! - Eme!
Now let the music play!
Party party!
Next on Drag Race Philippines:
Slaysian Royale.
Queens, for this week's Maxi
Challenge, you'll be creating jaw-dropping
couture looks using fossilized
cacao leaves.
A Design Challenge? For me?
Khianna, you almost won last season.
Yeah. Last year we had a lot of
things And I don't have any of those, so...
Oh, my God, this is it! So many
bitches are stressed out.
This is a million-dollar look, baby!
I am not gonna sit here and be like,
"Oh, it's amazing! " when I
can clock details
that needs to be fixed.