Your Highness,
last night,
you and Liu Chu...
From this moment on,
you are his true concubine.
Rank doesn't matter.
What matters
is that he keeps loving me.
I’m sure he will.
By the way, Your Highness,
Yes?
I'm leaving the palace today.
So soon?
Yes.
Lan said she has found
a place for me to stay.【】
She hopes I can leave as soon as possible.
Well...
Don't worry.
Now that you and Liu Chu
have shared your wedding night,
I can finally be at ease.
What if I miss you?
I told you.
I’ll come back to visit you
as soon as I can.
Really?
Yes.
Such a beauty—
who could help but fall in love?
Then in the future,
I’ll have to find you the perfect husband,
and marry you off in grand style.
I still prefer
Changmo men.
Then...
Lord Fei has no chance, right?
Because Miss Jin Xi
is Consort Ling's female official.
the Grand Princess specially ordered
the palace gates opened wide
and personally saw her off
with the highest courtesy.
Not everyone gets this kind of treatment.
Then please, Miss Lan,
convey my thanks
to the Grand Princess for me.
I certainly will.
When I'm not around,
if anyone dares to bully the Princess,
I definitely won't
let them get away with it.
Consort Ling is the person
the Emperor cares about the most.
In this palace,
who would dare to bully her?
Okay.
Then I am relieved.
Jin Xi,
take good care of yourself.
Take care.
Bring Miss Jin Xi’s luggage.
Jin Xi,
you must come back to see me.
Where are you going?
I'm going to see Mo.
Don't worry.
Liu Xiyang will take good care of him.
Do you need something from me?
Follow me.
Where is this place?
This is a warehouse.
It holds some goods.
I want you to help me do an inventory.
I have a feeling
you’re trying to trick me.
How could I ever trick you?
Let's go.
This isn't a warehouse.
It's clearly a pharmacy.
Take a look at these herbs
and see if they are still usable,
or
if you need anything else.
Jewel orchid!
This is the king of herbs!
And reishi mushrooms!
And so much ginseng!
Are these all yours?
Yeah.
This is top-quality medicine.
You've struck it rich?
I...
If I gave it to you,
what would you do?
If you gave it to me,
I could definitely treat more people.
In that case,
I'll give you both the herbs and the shop.
Are you really giving them to me?
Of course.
Do you have an ulterior motive?
What ulterior motive
could I have with you?
You’ve been treating me
all this time,
so after I returned to the capital,
I wanted to give you something in return.
But I felt
that gold and silver jewelry
are too tacky.
Then I thought
you'd probably like a pharmacy.
How can I accept
such an expensive gift?
Once I give it to you,
won't you be able to treat more people?
Then I'll really accept it?
Accept it.
I'll accept it then.
From now on, I'll be here
treating the people.
Then later,
I'll write an inscription for you.
Save the world
and bless the people.
I never thought General Xiao
could be so sweet-talking.
You have something on your mind.
I just feel the incident
at Huangpi Village
is not that simple.
The symptoms this time are the same
as the great plague back then.
It reminds me
that our Han family
might have offended someone
during that plague
and
got persecuted.
Wait.
Have you thought of something?
We need to investigate
among those who survived
that plague.
Do you have any targets?
The senior officials
who survived the plague
include Zhang Ruizhong, Lord Zhang,
and Wang Ruhai, Lord Wang.
Are you saying
they are all related to
the massacre of the Han family?
Yes.
It's highly possible.
But the details
can only be known after investigation.
This Wang Ruhai
is idle at home.
It just so happens
we can try starting with him.
Okay.
Injustice!
The Prince's family is going too far!【】
Let me in!
Who
dares to trespass into
the Prince's mansion?
You lawless thugs
kidnapped my daughter in broad daylight!
I...
I will sue you at the government office
and let you get the punishment
you deserve!
Sue me?
Do you think the government office
will accept
the lawsuit of a commoner like you?
How ridiculous.
Justice will prevail!
I will let everyone in the world
know of your evil deeds!
Give me back my daughter!
You...
Fine.
I'll let you sue me.
Let everyone see
what a crazy old man you are.
Give me back my daughter!
My lord.
This old fool
has a death wish.
How dare he sue me.
Yes, my lord.
If no one was instigating this,
who in the capital
would dare to cross you?
Makes sense.
I've been recovering at home these days.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Who could I have offended?
Could it be that brat Xiao Chi?
After all, our young master
had a feud with him before.
Xiao Chi?
Xiao Chi!
It was because of him
that His Majesty made me
stay idle at home.
He...
Now he wants to mess with me again.
He thinks
that just by doing this,
he can threaten the Wang family?
Xiao Chi!
Take that for threatening me!
My lord!
I spent a fortune
to borrow this
from the Ministry of Justice.
I still have to return it.
Xiao Chi!
I am not done with him.
Why would I have such a nightmare?
What's wrong?
I had a nightmare.
A nightmare?
What did you dream about?
I dreamed that Huangbei Village
was engulfed in flames.
The villagers were all slaughtered.
Come with me.
Run!
Hurry!
How could this happen?
What did these villagers
do to deserve this?
We must make them pay.
The hidden weapons are poisoned.
Xiao Chi,
hang in there.
Bear with it a little longer.
I'm fine.
I'm glad you're okay.
Bear with it, Xiao Chi.
I'm sorry.
Bear with it.
Just a little longer.
Hang in there.
I'll go prepare some medicine for you.
Boss.
We don't have it.
No.
Lord Fei.
Physician Wang,
what kind of poison is on the dart?
Have you found out?
The dart is coated with
the venom of a krait.
Krait venom?
Is there a cure?
Blue snake tail
and snake herb can cure it.
But these are just legends,
and cannot be trusted.
Physician Wang,
you have been a physician for many years,
and are the best physician
in Jinglan.
I believe you must have other ways.
As long as Xiao Chi can wake up,
no matter what herbs,
I, Fei Zheng, will not hesitate
even if I go bankrupt.
To detoxify this,
using medicine won't work.
Try using poison against poison.
It might be effective.
Poison against poison?
Physician Wang, please elaborate.
We are good at using medicine,
but when it comes to poison,
none of us are good at it.
Fortunately, Physician Han
protected General Xiao's heart meridian.
Even if he doesn't wake up,
his condition won't worsen.
So,
our hope can really only rest on
Physician Han.
The herb you need is not available
in the entire capital.
The Emperor
has also ordered
the Imperial Medical Academy's
physicians to do their best to find it.
I wonder if Physician Han
has any other solutions.
Before we find the medicine,
I'll try using other medicines
to stabilize Xiao Chi's condition first.
I found out.
It's Wang Ruhai.
Wang Ruhai?
Why did he want to kill Xiao Chi?
Since the general returned to the capital,
he impeached Wang Ruhai,
causing him to be dismissed
and ostracized by his colleagues,
so
he wanted to kill the general.
Lord Zhang
is also targeting the general.
Are they targeting Xiao Chi,
or our Han family?
This is the evidence
that Xiao Chi gathered
of Wang Ruhai's crimes
before he was injured.
So much?
Are these all the evil deeds
done by Wang Ruhai alone?
This is only a part of it.
There are even more
petitions accusing
him and his son of bullying,
running amok,
and coercing trades
stored in the boxes outside.
I really can't figure out
why the late Emperor kept
someone like Wang Ruhai by his side.
The late emperor suddenly
fell seriously ill and passed away.
There must be many things
that were not thoroughly considered.
However,
although Wang Ruhai
has done all kinds of evil,
he indeed has prestige in the court.
For a man like him,
who is greedy and entirely selfish,
if anyone touches his interests,
he will inevitably
fight to the death to stop them.
Then tell me,
what should I do?
Evil people
should be punished.
Since he dares to
secretly harm the Third Brother now,
who knows
what outrageous things
he might do in the future.
The court
will decide my fate.
It is not your place to question me.
Go back.
Can you tell me
the truth about
the extermination of the Han family?
As for the truth
about the extermination of the Han family,
even if I knew,
I wouldn't tell you.
You!
By imperial order:
all unrelated personnel
are to withdraw.
Investigation reveals
Wang Kun, son of Wang Ruhai,
kidnapped a commoner woman.
Wang Ruhai failed to discipline his son.
His past crimes
are too numerous to count.
It is hereby ordered
that he be dismissed and investigated,
and his son Wang Kun
be imprisoned pending trial.
This is impossible.
Father,
I'm innocent!
they framed me!
Father!
I know.
Father.
Save me, Father!
Take him down.
Don't panic.
Father, save me!
Father!
Save me, Father!
Impossible. They framed me!
Stop!
Let go!
Who dares to cause trouble in my mansion?
We cannot disobey the imperial order.
Take him away.
Son!
Father!
Save me, Father!
I know.
I know you are investigating
the Han family matter.
I
will tell you the truth.
Let my son go,
and I'll tell you the truth.
What is the truth?
The truth is...
Tell me now!
What is the truth
behind the massacre of the Han family?
The truth is...
Wang Ruhai, tell me now!
What is the truth?
Eldest Princess, Wang Ruhai is dead.
How did he die?
When the Emperor
ordered the capture of his son,
he fainted,
and never woke up again.
His crimes were enough
to have him paraded through the streets.
Dying like this
is letting him off easy.
The regent left by the late Emperor
is just gone like that.
This is just the beginning.
Lord Zhang is getting old.
He probably won't last for
many more years.
Then,
should we secretly befriend Li Shichang?
A Princess having close ties
with a minister
will definitely cause gossip.
Not just him.
Xiao Chi has been sick for so long,
and we didn't visit him either, did we?
As long as the Emperor is obedient,
all of Jinglan
will be under my control.
By the way,
how is that female official?
We've already arranged for her
to stay in our outer residence.
Everyone there belongs to
our Xie Shadow Guard.【】
The tribute ambassador
from Changmo is coming soon.
Keep a close eye on things.
Understood.
I'll take my leave now.
Even though you haven't woken up yet,
I believe you can
hear what I'm saying.
I'm going to the North Mountain
to pick an herb.
With it,
you will definitely wake up.
You must hold on.
Wait for me to return.
This journey has been full of hardships,
and you have always been
the one protecting me.
Now it's my turn
to protect you.
Xiao Chi,
wait for me.
Lord Fei.
Chengfeng,
you've been guarding for quite a while.
Go back and rest.
I can take it from here.
I wouldn't be able to sleep anyway.
Being here
actually makes me feel more at ease.
Alright.
Take a seat.
I'll stay with you for a while.
Sit.
Physician Han.
Physician Han,
you're back.
Physician Han!