I just saw
a figure flash by.
There's nothing here.
Commander,
you must have got that wrong.
If you don't trust me,
you can come and check for yourself.
Now that Lord Fei has already checked,
there's no need to check again.
Let's patrol elsewhere.
Thanks for your hard work.
Well,
Lord Fei,
it's so late.
Why are you still in the palace?
Don't even mention it.
Although the marriage ceremony is over,
Consort Ling's consummation
is also part of the royal etiquette.
As long as it's related to etiquette,
I, the newly appointed Minister of Rites,
have to supervise it personally.
It's so troublesome.
Then, why are you in the Imperial Garden?
Didn't you know that
Lord Zhang also
entered the palace tonight?
His Majesty needs to
discuss something with him.
So, he asked me to wait for him here.
What Lord Fei says makes sense.
You've worked hard.
We will patrol with greater caution
to protect His Majesty
Lord Zhang, and you.
Thank you.
Let's go.
The palace is heavily guarded.
If you barge in like this,
you might get caught.
So what?
I can deal with them myself.
If someone is killed in the palace,
security measures will be tightened.
At that time, it will be
more difficult for you to take action.
If you have any other tasks coming up,
you can just tell me.
Maybe I can help.
I've explored the palace pretty well.
But
I need the defense maps of
the Tianlang Pass
and the capital.
I'll have to trouble Lord Fei for that.
The defense maps of
the Tianlang Pass and the capital?
Do you think a civil official like me
can get hold of such military secrets?
Even if I can,
how can you send them back to Changmo?
After the grand ceremony,
the envoy for the marriage alliance
will arrive in the capital,
and the Hall Master will come too.
The Hall Master is coming in person?
Alright.
I'm leaving.
Remember to get me the defense maps.
Jin Xi,
you can leave first.
I will serve Her Highness.
Yes.
You slept alone last night?
Yesterday, Liu Chu was
called away by Lord Zhang,
and didn't come back.
I fell asleep by myself.
On the first night of the wedding,
he didn't
consummate the marriage with you?
Greetings, Your Highness.
Before His Majesty went to court,
he specifically ordered me
to come and see
how you slept.
These were also
ordered by His Majesty last night
in the Imperial Study.
See.
I brought it to you
first thing in the morning.
Thank you, Mr. Shen.
Then, when will His Majesty come?
Well,
I don't know.
But I believe
after His Majesty finishes court,
he will come to see you.
I shall take my leave now.
Alright.
General Xiao.
Lord Fei.
After days of comparison and analysis,
we found the plague in Huangpi Village
indeed bears a striking resemblance
to the great plague eight years ago.
They are just similar
but not the same?
No.
Although this disease
is very similar to
the great plague eight years ago,
we still found some
subtle differences.
Please look at the examination report,
My Lords.
An unknown toxin was found
in this plague.
I haven't found out
what exactly the poison is yet.
Poison?
Yes.
That is to say,
this epidemic
is not a natural disaster.
Not a natural disaster?
Could it be man-made?
You mean someone spread the poison?
We will find
the source of the ash as soon as possible
to help Lord Fei uncover the truth.
Thank you for your help.
Jin Xi.
It's so late.
Do you think Liu Chu is still coming?
No emperor visits a concubine's palace
every day.
If he doesn't come,
we'll just rest early.
Alright.
I'm sleepy anyway.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, it's so late. You still...
I was just discussing with
Zhang Ruizhong and Li Shichang
about the expansion of the army
in the capital.
I came to you as soon as I finished.
Your Highness,
I'd better wait for you outside.
Call me if you need anything.
Who is this?
That's Jin Xi.
She accompanied me from Changmo
as my personal female official.
We grew up together.
For a moment just now,
I felt like I had seen that look of hers
somewhere before.
You're familiar with her gaze?
Yeah.
It seems like
when Fei Zheng
entered the Prince's Mansion.
What are you talking about?
Lord Fei is a man.
Jin Xi is a girl.
How can they be the same?
Really, I'm not lying to you.
Forget it.
It's not important.
Tonight,
I will stay here with you.
Really?
Of course it is.
When have I ever lied to you?
Right?
Your Majesty.
Damn Lord Zhang.
I
will be right back.
You didn't come back
last time you said that.
I swear.
This is the last time.
It won't happen again.
All right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Then,
I am leaving.
Okay.
Your Majesty.
Lord Zhang.
Okay.
Lord Zhang,
today isn't any special occasion.
Besides,
with so much wine,
how can the two of us finish it?
You may not know this, Your Majesty.
Today is the anniversary of
my first military campaign
with the late Emperor.
Don't you think we should celebrate?
Of course, we should.
Lord Zhang,
without the battles you
and the late Emperor fought,
Jinglan wouldn't be what it is today.
Yes.
Come on. Let me offer you a toast,
Lord Zhang.
To Your Majesty.
Cheers.
He
left again.
He said he would come back.
I highly doubt it.
I saw Lord Zhang at the door earlier
with a lot of wine.
I don't know what he's up to tonight.
I will wait for him anyway.
Alright.
Then, I'll accompany you.
Come on.
Let me fill your cup, Lord Zhang.
Back then,
I followed the late Emperor
and fought our way
through the battlefields.
I deeply understand
how hard-won this empire is.
The late Emperor passed away suddenly
and asked me to be your Chief Minister.
Actually, Your Majesty,
at my age,
I should have retired long ago
and enjoyed my twilight years.
To be honest,
I should have lived a carefree
life with my grandchildren.
Really, Lord Zhang?
With this glass,
I wish you
many children and grandchildren.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
After you, Lord Zhang.
Please.
Your Majesty.
You can really hold your liquor,
Lord Zhang.
Your Majesty,
I am truly not clinging to
the position of Chief Minister.
I just worry about you, Your Majesty.
I also worry about
Jinglan's land
Lord Zhang.
and its people.
I cannot do it without you.
Jinglan
needs you even more.
Lord Zhang.
You flatter me, Your Majesty.
Come on.
Your Majesty,
I invited you out tonight
not only to commemorate the late Emperor,
but also because I don't want you
to lose yourself
in Consort Ling's tenderness
and be unable to extricate yourself.
Rest assured.
I will definitely be
a wise ruler who knows
how to judge and use people.
Good, Your Majesty.
Remember to cherish this hard-won empire
and the people of Jinglan.
I believe
you will certainly be
a wise and just emperor.
To Your Majesty.
Then, with this cup,
we toast to the land of Jinglan,
and to the future of Jinglan.
Lord Zhang.
Please.
Your Majesty.
It is all for Jinglan.
Judging by the Your Highness's look,
the treasury must be full again.
The weather has been good,
and the land is peaceful this year.
Both the national and royal treasuries
have 30% more than in previous years.
This is truly worth celebrating.
However,
this is all thanks to you, Your Highness.
I heard
that His Majesty spent the most
on his royal wedding
compared to all previous monarchs.
I only have one brother.
It's his first marriage.
As his sister,
how could I be stingy?
You are so good to His Majesty,
Your Highness.
I hope His Majesty will always keep
this kindness in his heart.
I heard that
His Majesty and Consort Ling didn't
consummate their marriage last night.
Lord Zhang
is such a stubborn old man.
The ceremony is only complete
after the marriage is consummated.
Why is he
standing in the way?
Should we help His Majesty out?
No.
It's their own business.
Let nature take its course.
By the way,
did Consort Ling say anything?
Consort Ling is fine.
But Jin Xi,
the female official beside her,
is indeed a hidden danger.
We can't let her stay in the palace.
Find a chance to drive her out.
Go prepare a courtyard.
The palace
must be clean.
Don't you think
Chu has something on his mind?
General Xiao, you are so clever.
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Chu...
Don't ask.
I'm fine.
I'm good.
Chu,
it seems that since the marriage alliance,
you haven't been very happy.
I am quite happy.
Then, why do you look so exhausted?
Chu,
are you and Consort Ling
not sleeping well?
What kind of question is that?
It's mostly Zhang Ruizhong's fault.
Lord Zhang,
that stubborn old man,
every night,
when Wanyu and I are together,
he insists on eavesdropping at our door.
He either wants to discuss
national affairs with me,
or wants to drink
and have a heart-to-heart talk.
He is a veteran minister.
It's inappropriate if I don't go.
But I can't outdrink him.
I really don't know what to do.
General Xiao,
can you tolerate this?
I cannot.
Lord Fei,
can you?
I can't either.
Do you have a solution, General Xiao?
That depends on what solution
Lord Fei has.
What are you two talking about?
Chu,
rest assured.
Tonight, we'll let you and Consort Ling...
We shall take our leave.
Where are you going?
Wait.
Tell me.
Tell me where you are going.
Where are you going?
Jin Xi.
Did you pick all these from the palace?
Yes.
I took one branch from every tree,
and three blooms from every flower,
and got this many.
You just came to the palace.
Why are you so familiar with the palace?
Not really.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Greetings, Xie.
You may rise.
Xie, what brings you here?
I came to see you.
How is it?
Are you getting used to
living in the palace?
I eat well in the palace,
and sleep well.
I am doing very well.
Good？
I heard you and His Mahesty
haven't consummated your marriage yet.
Liu Chu has been a bit busy lately.
Good things take time.
You two will be together for a lifetime,
so there's no rush.
Rest assured.
With me here,
you will
have a happy life.
I came today
mainly to talk to you about Jin Xi.
Jin Xi?
I heard
Jin Xi is very loyal to you.
She accompanied you
from Changmo to Jinglan,
and into the palace.
Now that you are with His Majesty,
I'm thinking of
finding a good home for her.
Outside the palace,
I have a courtyard.
I plan to let her live there.
And every month,
I'll allocate some money from the treasury
for her living expenses.
But
Jin Xi and I are like sisters.
If she is not here...
Precisely because you are like sisters,
she shouldn't stay by your side forever
to serve you.
She needs her own residence,
her own life,
and her own husband.
Don't you agree?
Your Highness's good intentions
are surely meant well.
Since you've said so,
there must be no chance for negotiation.
I can leave the palace.
But after I leave,
who can take care of Her Highness?
Rest assured about that.
I will arrange for
more clever maids to serve you.
As long as I have time,
I will also come see you.
Besides,
you're not forbidden from
entering the palace forever.
Whenever you miss Consort Ling,
you can come see her anytime.
Okay.
Then, I am relieved.
I will follow Your Highness's
arrangements.
Then,
it's settled?
Okay.
Who is it?
Keep your voice down.
Lord Zhang
has been looking for me all night.
He's so annoying.
If Lord Zhang is looking for you, just go.
He has no real business with me.
It's all nonsense.
Or he's just lecturing me.
I think
he just doesn't want me to come here.
But I'm not going anywhere today.
Your Majesty,
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Let me deal with him.
Your Majesty.
Lord Zhang.
Why are you here?
I have something to discuss
with His Majesty.
Backup is here.
Lord Zhang.
You brought so much good wine.
General Xiao and I are just about to
have a drink together.
Why don't we go together?
No. No. I really have business
with His Majesty.
Lord Zhang, come on.
Let me tell you something interesting
about the Tianlang Pass.
No.
The wine...
Let's go, Lord Zhang.
I want to drink with His Majesty.
What's the point of drinking here?
Let's drink at Tianxiang Restaurant.
I really have business with His Majesty.
They won't come back, will they?
They won't.
Although Xiao Chi can't hold his drink,
Fei Zheng can hold his liquor.
Huh？
What's up?
Anyway, tonight,
I'm not going anywhere.
Your Majesty.
Who is it?
Your Majesty,
Her Highness sent nuptial wine.
Thank you, Xie.
Can you leave it at the door?
Go out and have a drink.
Drink again?
Drink what?
Your Majesty.
Stop shouting.
But we have to attend the morning court.
Wait for me.
I will accompany you after the court.
His Majesty has arrived.
Your Majesty.
At ease.
Rise.
Is she still sleeping?
Yes.
Your Majesty, why are you here?
Jin Xi, why didn't you tell me?
I did it on purpose.
I told them not to wake you.
I just wanted to see you sleep.
So cute.
I haven't washed up yet.
Then,
get up and wash up now.
I'll take you somewhere.
Then, wait for me.
Okay.
I'll wait for you outside.
Sorry to keep Your Majesty waiting.
Please wait for me outside.
Okay.
Why haven't you left yet?
Hurry up and get out.
Get out.
I don't want to.
I don't want to go out.
It's daytime right now.
So what?
I don't care.
But I need to wash up.
Okay.
But I think
you look beautiful no matter what.
Aren't you going to take me out to play?
Yes.
Then.
I'll let you off today.
Thanks.
Then, I'll wait for you outside.
Okay.
Hurry up and wash up.
I'm waiting for you.
Okay.
Jinglan has a vast territory.
It has nine provinces
and eighteen counties.
It faces the sea to the east,
has grasslands to the west,
and borders Mount Jing to the south.
To the north
is your Changmo.
If Changmo and Jinglan can
maintain good relations for generations,
then the whole world
will be at peace forever.
The King of Changmo has already sent you
to Jinglan as a hostage.
How could the two countries
not be on good terms forever?
I came here voluntarily.
All right.
I swear,
from now on,
Jinglan
and Changmo
will be like one family,
and there will be no more wars.
I will also
teach our children
and all the descendants of Jinglan
to keep this promise.
Okay.
You have sent many spies
in the past years.
Now, your Caidie Hall
is finally being useful, huh?
Jinglan's national strength is
stronger than Changmo's.
They have more talents.
Many members of our Caidie Hall died.
Finally, we managed to
plant a few spies there.
General Gan,
didn't you fail to defeat Xiao Chi?
On the battlefield,
there aren't many
who can fight me for a few rounds.
Let alone
fight me to a draw.
As they say, heroes appreciate heroes.
Besides,
I didn't kill him
because I wanted to play a little longer.
Then, be careful, General Gan.
Don't risk your life.
You!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
This marriage alliance went smoothly.
Caidie Hall made a great contribution.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Rise.
I'm thinking that
Fei Zheng
has been in Jinglan for years.
It's time he made himself useful.
Yes.
I will go to Jinglan
with the marriage alliance envoy.
I will officially activate him then.
Your Majesty,
we don't need to
go through all that trouble.
Just attack Jinglan directly.
Wouldn't that be more satisfying?
Tianlang Pass is
a key stronghold of Jinglan.
It is easy to defend and hard to attack.
General Gan,
you only want the thrill of the kill,
completely ignoring
the lives of our Changmo soldiers, huh?
Using venomous insects and poison
is despicable.
Even if we win,
it will be an unfair victory.
Whatever methods are used
or schemes are played,
they are all reasonable.
General Gan,
do you think a war between two countries
is just a fight between two kids?
Do you know
how many soldiers
will die in the flames of war?
Victory
is the most important.
Well said, Military Advisor Modu.
We must win with the lowest cost
and the most secure method.
Gan Yi, continue training the troops.
Rest assured.
There will be a time for you
to fulfill your ambitions.
I accept the order.
Military Advisor Modu,
next time,
you should go to Jinglan
with the tribute envoy.
Yes.
I have already prepared
a surprise for Liu Chu.
As for you...
I know what I need to do.
Good.
Excellent.
Liu Zheng.
The day I conquer Jinglan,
in front of your grave,
I will kill your son, Liu Chu,
to keep you company.