Tyrannosaurus
I'm not sure if you can hear me.
It smells disgusting.
Father, there is a danger in the Yinan valley.
The communication is only a word.
No wonder the Pei master will ask for you.
What do you call that traitor?
Pei master!
Father, you misunderstood.
That traitor is a cunning man.
He is just a scapegoat.
I'm just worried...
He is the one who should be worried.
I have warned him.
Tonight, I will write the memorial.
Tomorrow morning, I will go to the heaven.
I will see if this is a crime that is a mess.
Can he bear it?
Father, don't be ridiculous.
Pei master is a big man.
He is as cunning as a rat.
You want me to be a scapegoat?
You want to kill the people?
I don't dare.
I want to take my father to ask for Pei master.
I want to apologize to him.
Maybe there is a chance to return the favor.
Father, don't let the family die.
I will kill them all.
You are a traitor!
You want to die?
Kneel down!
You want to kill them all?
You are a shameless man.
You have no shame.
You have gone to the dogs.
I will kill you today.
I will kill you!
Zhong Han Liang is guilty of Pei master.
But I don't want to die.
You are responsible for this.
I have been ordered by the master.
I will kill him.
From now on,
I will be the master and father of all the people.
I will kill them all.
I will hide and hide from them.
I will use Yinan Shang to help Pei master
to clean the funeral house.
I will only replace Tianzhai.
He is the most favored one.
He will also take the property
and the property to be my master.
I have been worried about him every day.
I am sick and afraid of the cold.
I am afraid of the cold.
I am afraid of the family's resurrection.
I will be safe for a night.
Later,
I will have the trust of Pei master
to be poisoned.
But after Pei master is dead,
I will be the only one who can escape.
I have a life of fear.
I will be punished for it.
I don't believe anyone.
Including my family.
I will not die.
You promised me
that if I sent you a message
you would tell me the truth.
Tell me,
Pei master is your son.
Is it you?
It's me.
I am your son.
You have been begging me
to marry me.
But you didn't tell me this.
Do you want me to pull out
from a fire pit
and throw it into another fire pit?
A Yan, you are still trying to marry him.
He has caused our family to be in trouble.
He is a little bit of a murderer.
If it wasn't for my time in prison,
he would have been killed without any help.
How could you
make yourself so dangerous?
You are so dangerous.
I will kill you
and kill you without any help.
You will not go back.
The sky is about to fall.
I can't let you go.
Let Yu Zu and Huan Fu Yun Xi
come to meet me in prison.
Mr. Zhuang,
you are coming to me.
You are going to admit it?
I told Yu Zu that
he was going to investigate his background.
So he was in a hurry
and disappeared.
You must have known where he was.
You killed him.
I didn't have the chance to do it.
I admit it.
I am a traitor.
Then I will bring it to you.
I will pretend to be a traitor.
Wait.
You are back.
What?
I haven't finished my words.
I have not been a traitor.
I have some hidden secrets
to report to Mr. Fu.
The man who killed the man
told me in person
that there is another person
besides me.
You don't want to know
who he is?
You can tell me.
I will tell you.
Forget it.
From the beginning,
he died.
He is not dead.
He is dead.
We all have family blood.
We have family blood.
Once we are gone,
they will be buried.
They will be buried.
I will keep the secret for him.
I don't know
if he wants to let me go.
You have to get him out.
You have to get some evidence.
If it is the right time,
who wants to kill
the person who saved the man?
Mr. Fu knows me.
Zhuang Shiyang
will not
let my family
do it.
Really?
Yes.
So
you let me take away
the corpse
and then
you were killed
for the sake of your life.
I was in the South Hill Hospital
that day.
Could it be
you knew I was hiding outside the window?
You were telling me
all those things.
I saw you in the Immortal's Palace.
I was waiting for you outside the window.
I did receive
Zhuang Shiyang's body in the prison.
But before that, I had already made up my mind
and gave you the body of Wu Youzhi
to save your family.
How do you want me to believe you?
I said I would never hurt you.
No matter who I am,
I will never change.
You are so stubborn
and you are so stubborn.
Now it seems
that it's just that the world is wrong
and you think that there is only one person
who is stubborn.
As long as you arrest Zhuang Shiyang,
you will be fine.
Since I entered the capital,
you have been helping me
for the sake of my life
and helping me
to be a pawn
who will take me
to the bottom of the valley
and to save my family.
At the beginning,
it was indeed like this.
Has it changed now?
You want to tell me
that you have truly fallen for me?
If I say yes,
Han Yan,
don't say that I am stubborn.
You are going to arrest Zhuang Shiyang!
You think you are a good person?
You don't think you are a good person.
Why?
I am doing this
to save Zhuang family.
I have been
trying to save my family
and I am alone in the house.
I am going to be trapped
and I will not be found
by anyone.
Now, I am going to kill my family.
Han Yan,
what else can I do?
Stop pretending to be a liar
and keep your mouth shut.
You really think that
I didn't tell you everything?
You killed my grandfather
but you have
a reason to be punished by me.
I have been a traitor for many years.
You might tell me everything
and I will not tell you clearly.
Your grandfather was a traitor.
He was a traitor.
I am sure that he is the reason
why he killed my grandfather.
I am just a traitor
who killed my grandfather.
I am just a traitor.
But I have no intention
to kill you.
You are my own daughter.
You don't have to be a liar.
What you said
is not your reason to be a traitor.
There is one more thing.
I have told you all.
Mr. Zhuang likes to be friendly
and familiar with the medical field.
He died of poisoning.
You can't get away from this.
When the accident happened,
I checked the clues of Pei Da Fu's death.
But the informant
was poisoned by you
during the night.
I was afraid that I would find out your whereabouts.
You wanted to poison me
but you didn't want to kill me.
I poisoned Yu Jin.
I guess you are right.
Yu Jin was killed by me.
But the murderer is his father.
The murderer is his father.
It's you.
If you hadn't been killed by me,
I wouldn't have died.
Feiyu Xie.
Zhang Shiyang.
No wonder
Pei Da Fu of the Qing Dynasty
chose you as his concubines.
The capital is really
a place where no one can live.
No wonder
he wanted me to stay away from this place.
Fu Shaoqing told me
on the day I first met him.
He told me
that he didn't want me to regret.
Now I tell you
I am
regretting it.
I shouldn't have
been a hidden enemy
from the beginning.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have
been so jealous
and jealous of you.
I'm sorry.
I can't understand any words from you.
I wouldn't be
sorrowful.
You did this safely.
I'm美味.
Quickly get up.
Xiao Ye.
Are you on leave?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have hurt you.
If someone lied to me,
I would only want to kill him.
Only if you lied to me,
would I be sad.
You just want to say
that I've given him the truth.
But the flower water is not as good as the moon.
Now that the illusion is broken,
everything is back to its original state.
Do you still remember
what you wanted to get
when you first came here?
I remember.
There was a home,
a place to live,
a place to return to.
Have you ever thought about
how you've been in the hospital?
You have a mother
who is no longer a precious orphan.
Taikun,
follow me.
From now on,
my home
is your home.
Where are you going?
We'll follow mother
and never leave this place.
Never come back.
Why did you make this mistake?
I've decided.
Mother, you don't have to ask.
But
I used to be friends with a friend in Danzhou.
He is a orphan who is famous for his family background.
Now he is alone in the capital.
I want to take him with me.
As long as everything is with you,
I'll be happy.
Then I'll get the divorce letter tomorrow.
What are you waiting for?
Oh, check out my book.
T этого...
How do I read?
It'sorar.
Why didn't you read the document?
Yes.
What are you reading?
An reading document.
The document was shown
by Uncle Zangvang.
I'm a bad person.
Why did you lie to me?
At first, I was just to protect myself.
I didn't expect to hurt him.
I was wrong.
Then you just admit you're wrong.
It's not that simple to be a man.
I'm afraid he won't forgive me.
Uncle Feng is also a good boy.
Then he brought the peach path to apologize.
I'm afraid he will be a little dog on the ground.
He just forgave him.
I don't even want to try.
But I don't have sincerity at all.
And you still know what sincerity is?
Of course I know.
Father, do you believe in the soul of the British?
The earth has a long and short life.
There are many things in the world.
Whether you believe it or not, what is the solution?
If you don't believe it,
why do you keep on smelling it?
I'll kill you.
If I can choose,
I'll choose the soul of the British.
I don't want to touch the soul of the world.
But if there is a soul of the world,
I'll live.
Even if you think I'm the biggest evil spirit,
I'll kill you first.
That's just because I want to live.
Since that's the case,
write the divorce letter.
It's your mother's idea.
You only write the divorce letter.
I'll leave the capital with my mother.
You're the most important person in the party.
All of us are the same.
We have no brother.
You're the son and daughter.
How can you leave your parents?
Mother has been begging for a life in the Zhuang family.
You still don't want to let her go?
We Zhuang family
have been in a bad situation.
We've been together since then.
It's not good.
Don't be so selfish.
You've been ruined by your family.
I know your mother's death.
She's blaming me for my death.
She's blaming me for my family.
We'll die together in the future.
Why do you have to do this?
You're going to kill your parents.
You...
Don't talk nonsense with her.
You're wrong.
Why do you have to be so stubborn?
Are you happy for me?
I'm happy for you.
You want Yu Yi to get better.
It's for your own good.
I'm afraid you're worried.
From now on,
you can't put me in this house again.
This is the only place you can't choose.
Xi Lan.
You're here for the next 20 days.
You have to make up for it.
Make up for it?
I'll keep it a secret.
I'll help you to make up for it.
The family was in a mess.
Yuwen Chang'an suddenly got rid of the gold.
We're married.
You're the one who's been making up for it.
You know that?
The emperor ordered my father to make up for it.
But you broke the record of Hanlin Garden.
He let my father die because of the heavy punishment.
He only let me be forced by you.
That's why I'm in this bad situation.
Now the court has a family.
If you make up for it,
you can't find a good wife.
You're a traitor.
How can you kill your own son?
It's because I love you.
I don't want to be a traitor.
I forgive you.
I can't blame you.
As long as it's not reasonable,
I'll promise you whatever you wish.
I'll kill you if I'm guilty.
No.
We were in love for years.
We were in a fight.
I said I was wrong.
You killed my father.
You even made me a Yunni Su.
Have you forgotten?
Do you know why I'm the best at making Yunni Su?
Because that's the most valuable thing in Yuwen Chang'an.
Let's go.
Master.
We've been together for years.
We've been sisters.
Why don't you say goodbye?
I'm not your mother.
Don't call me that.
Sister, are you really leaving?
You still want to keep me?
I've thought it through.
You left the capital after you left the mansion.
You're not a good person.
Yuwen Chang'an is out of his position.
You're out of your identity.
You can't enter the high school in the future.
What are you planning?
If you knew what I was planning,
you wouldn't have fought with me for a lifetime.
You can still say that.
I don't have to talk to you.
Sister, I didn't expect you to let go of those grudges.
I've never hated you.
Do you believe it?
I'm just sorry.
I've wasted my time in the mansion
and I've been fooled by others.
I'm so happy to be a wife.
Even if you're leaving,
you still want to mess with my relationship with Master.
You're really heartless.
I'm not going to see you again.
Sister said I was heartless.
But I don't know what caused the disease.
Please don't bother me.
Zhou Ruying,
you're a agent of the Dai Temple.
You're the one who's been protecting the history.
But you're so selfish.
You're willing to be a person who can only betray your children.
You even want to hurt your daughter.
You're so pitiful.
Besides, you're a betrayer.
You've been so blinded by the evil spirit of being a hostage.
You're so blinded by the evil spirit of being a hostage.
You're not even a traitor.
But you never believed
that you had the power to grow up alone.
You're not the one who's helpless.
You should be the one who's responsible for this.
Aunt Chen,
see you off.
Miss San,
I'm looking for you at home.
What else do you want to say?
Not much.
There are only two words I want to say.
I'm sorry.
If you're done, please go back.
It's about the will and the will.
I have a few words to explain to you.
Mr. Fu is a senior official of the capital.
I'm just a maid now.
Moreover,
I have no other choice but to explain this to you.
Why do you have to explain it to me?
I don't want you to get it wrong.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to ask for your understanding.
I just don't want you to take the misunderstanding away.
It doesn't matter if you misunderstand or not.
We know each other.
No matter what you're hiding from me,
I'll always be grateful to you.
But the murder case and the arrest case
were all your help.
I didn't know the worst result would come.
We've been together for a long time.
We have no grudge left.
Zhuang Heye.
Do you remember
I gave you a windmill in the first night?
Yes, I do.
I only made a windmill and didn't give you a private letter.
I didn't want to be in your shoes.
If I had to give you a private letter,
I would have a high-ranking consort.
I'd rather be a maid than a maid.
I only want to stay in Changyang for a long time.
This is not the only freedom.
This is what I want to do in my life.
I think
you might have forgotten it today.
I'm afraid that we'll never see each other again.
I wish you a safe journey.
No need to be a maid in the north in winter.
Thank you.
Let's say goodbye today.
We'll take care of each other.
I came here twenty years ago.
I didn't expect to be so lonely today.
I didn't expect to be able to come back to my family
when I was in the Han family.
I didn't expect to be able to come back
to my mother's place one day.
Second Freshmen thanks enacted by her mother.
You are welcome again.
Rest assured.
Uncle Yuwen putting you through life
would as well give us a safe journey.
Please take the audience
and remind us to re-inảng out of the match.
Okay.
Uncle Yuwen
me and Mother
pay close attention.
Don't earninsky
I'm leaving.
A little water.
Hey?
Miss,
the苦horse is not so comfortable.
Wait for a while.
I'll clean it later.
You'll say that.
Really?
No.
You should be ashamed,
to try to do everything secretly
Master,
I don't go to unless you find someone
Maybe it's this
It should be the sixth lady in the manor.
She's going out today.
What's wrong, Miss?
Master.
I want to borrow you a piece of paper.
Wait for me here.
The quantities on the board...
In this day and age and ages from my longing
I know I'm done for twenty years.
It made me desperately wait for my end.
For some reason,
I've always felt Normally, I can't look desperate in my heart.
After all, I feel an Ambition.
I'm afraid that when I wake up,
I'll lose everything I have.
Life is not a dream.
I only want to be able to have a moment of happiness in my dreams.
My dream is to be born in Wuhan.
Mr. Yuwen, thank you for waiting for me for so many years.
You still call me Mr. Yuwen.
I should have changed my life to be in peace.
In peace?
Don't worry.
I'm not a father of Hanye.
But I can bear the responsibility of a father.
I'll try my best to make up for my mistakes.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't do this.
Xiwen, I'm willing to be your guide.
When the snow comes, I'll be with you in peace.
I'll be with you in the sea.
I'll see the beautiful scenery in the world.
Okay, I won't say so much.
I'll do my best to make up for my mistakes.
I know you're not good at this.
But you're my favorite.
I think the legs are different from the legs.
Try it.
Different?
I've tried it.
It's the best taste I've ever tasted.
Are you feeling unwell?
Don't be late.
There's poison.
I'm sorry.
It's him.
We've been in a lot of trouble.
It's okay.
Xiwen.
Today is our wedding.
How can we stop this?
Come.
Eat.
Xiwen.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just want to see you.
Okay.
You've spent a lot of time on these things.
I like them.
You like them.
I'm happy to be with you for the rest of my life.
I'm happy to spend some time with you.
What do you think?
I'll let you see the moon.
What?
We should bow to him now.
After we bow to him, he'll be my father.
No matter how deep his heart is,
even if he's on the way to the throne,
he'll be able to take care of it.
Good.
Today, I, Yuwen Chang'an,
and Xiwen, are married.
The world is beautiful.
Today, I, Yuwen Chang'an, and Xiwen, are married.
Can you cherish the moon?
I bow to the world.
Chang'an.
I'm the one who's connected to you.
Xiwen.
Today,
you and I are married.
Even if we're connected,
we'll always be together.
I'm not afraid.
You don't have to be afraid.
Chang'an.
Zai.
You've been drinking with me.
You've been asking me
if I have any feelings for you.
I'm telling you,
we're like two-sided lovers.
No matter how much time passes,
you'll never recognize me.
The thing I regret the most is
that he's the one who's not my soul.
Chang'an.
I thought
that this is my only wish.
Today,
I've understood everything.
I'm really so happy.
I'm in Wuhan.
I'm in Wuhan, too.
Chang'an.
Zhang Xingyang.
I know you're here.
Zhang Xingyang, I know you're here.
Why don't you dare to come out?
Come out!
Qiwen.
Does it hurt?
It's you.
It's you!
In my life,
my father was violent and loyal.
My mother was furious and selfish.
No one has ever loved me.
I've been in the Hanling Garden
and I've been in the Jin family.
and I've been in theут
due to respect for or
it was for casuality.
You are the one I love the most.
I'd rather sacrifice everything for you.
But why am I so afraid of you?
I'm just going to die.
Lian Shiyang,
I'm afraid you don't understand
what love is.
I don't understand.
But you don't understand me.
You are my parents.
You are my wife.
Who do you love?
You shouldn't blame me.
I'm sincere.
But I never replied.
You married me.
You were my only daughter.
I know you love Yuwen Chang'an.
If you didn't have a broken leg and a broken muscles,
I'm afraid you would have died
after a long time.
You don't deserve her.
She is a gentleman.
You are a shameless woman.
You will never be like her.
Is it painful to live
when she is pregnant?
You don't like the smell of ginger.
You don't like Yuwen Chang'an.
She has been in a search for the criminal.
She tried to kill me.
How could I let her go?
After she ate the ginger,
she died of a broken leg.
She was killed by me.
Yuwen, you know too much.
I let her go.
How could I let her go?
You love me.
Go back with me.
I'll take the medicine for you.
You must be careful.
I'll kill you.
You still want to kill me?
You are so cruel.
You really want to kill me?
Xiwen.
You don't want to
kill me?
I'm the most cruel one.
I'm the one who killed you.
Xiwen, I'll take care of you.
As long as you fall in love with me,
I'll take the medicine for you.
I'll kill you.
No.
It's not true.
Tell me.
You love me.
You're the one who killed Yuwen Chang'an.
Tell me.
You love me.
You're so cruel.
I love you.
Don't run away.
You're so cruel.
I love you.
Mother.
Mother, wake up.
Wake up.
Wake up, mother.
I'll take you to the doctor.
Mother.
You're so cruel.
I can save you.
I can still marry you.
I'll take you to the doctor.
Mother.
I can't take it anymore.
Mother, listen to me.
I'll take you to the doctor.
You've been with me for two years.
We've been together for so long.
That's all.
I've been with you for so long.
But after you came back,
you've lost your mother.
She might have found a daughter.
I feel her warmth and love.
You're leaving.
Mother.
You can't die.
Don't leave me alone.
I'll take you to the doctor.
I'm so sorry
that I can't grow up with my daughter.
I hope that one day,
we can write down all the family names and comforts.
Although I can't see her anymore,
I believe that one day,
we'll finally meet again.
I've been with you for so long.
I feel her warmth and love.
Who's the one who's crying?
I'm so sorry that I can't see her anymore.
I've been with you for so long.
Maybe we're destined to be together.
We can't let go of each other.
But Kurt and other companions
permitted us to be together
without a TWOever Dü immigrant.
Jiyang is an ideal hero,
where we leave no foundation.
...a powerful and powerful police force
of Tamg离
...and making Steward stops our murder
will continuer to suffer
поддерж老怀
the deficit
very depressing
Gulf andМы
I roam the ring
not 어욜
With his plot,
knowledge was fading
I will apologise.
I this
ask Your Majesty stay semaine.
I'm afraid I'll die.
But I remember that Mo Xie Chongzhu
is a great emperor.
He's the one who killed all the people.
I'm so bold.
I'm willing to ask His Majesty to give me a hand
because I'm so proud of him.
I'm afraid I'll die.
Do you have any choice?
I'm a man of the world.
Mo xie
Yiirad Du
Miss San had no way to get into a meeting.
Your si ingeniouslike
He has walked into this battlefield, not easy to separate
How much love, how much hate, don't need to ask
Who is the fake, who is the real, still need someone else
Upset, hehe, be novel and manose
Massage him who can escape
He is forced to be charming even if up to the wind
I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain
I'm afraid of the pain, I'm not afraid of the pain I must be monumentary
Full-bodied fine stone flower Junhua water garden
The only thing left is the audience
engrossed faith than fear