The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 1
Today is the wedding day
When the gate is opened
All the stars will rise
The Taoism Grandmaster
What's your name?
Your Highness
My name is Pei Ying Yue
Sit
You should call me Zhu Lang
Yes, Zhu Lang
Young Mistress
Zhuang Yushan
He married Prince Qi
Absolutely
This is the wedding invitation
from the House of Zhuang
Such a hasty marriage
How could he be so stupid
to marry Prince Qi?
It must be Zhuang Shiyang
who wants to kill himself
and to keep the secret from Prince Qi
Why don't we go and have a look?
I'm surprised
What's the use of going?
If I tell the whole family
Zhuang Yushan will think
I'm afraid he will marry into the Gao family
Young Mistress
I'm sorry
Do you know Zhuang Yushan
is going to marry Prince Qi?
I just know
Zhuang Shiyang is going to marry
in ten days
What has he done in the family recently?
I have been following the order
to investigate the case of the female groom
I have no time to investigate
whether Zhuang Shiyang is a maid
and I can't decide who to marry
Uncle Yuwen, have you made any progress?
No
I want to know the details
When Yuwen Chang'an was suspended
the documents in the capital's investigation office
were all sealed in the library
I have investigated
with Mu Feng and Mu Yan several times
but I haven't found any progress
What about the other government offices?
I have also investigated
but it never worked
And now
someone has already started to doubt
Have you finished asking?
Yes
Zhuang Hanyan
you have promised to let Ah Zhi change her mind
I hope you can be a good mother
What is a good mother?
I don't ask you to love her or protect her
I just ask you not to harm her
Today, you are so kind
and brought Yushan back with you
I'm afraid you can't be kind enough
Father-in-law, why are you still here?
I'll eat it later
Please forgive me
Father-in-law, why do you look so sad?
Did you meet any trouble at home?
I have some family matters
I don't want to trouble you
Father
Zhuang Hanyan did this to you again, right?
Don't talk nonsense
He used Fu Yunxi to take over
and you have been in the house for days
Why are you still covering for him?
Yushan
I'm just trying to help you
I just know that Zhuang Hanyan is your daughter
Why did she do this?
Since we got married, we are a family
I think I've said it all
Zhuang Hanyan was sent to Danzhou
because of her childhood
She hates Zhuang family
Since she came back to the family
she has been bothering us every day
Even my brother Yuchi
is related to Zhuang Hanyan
Yuchi is the only hope in our family
You really have a deep grudge
I'm sorry for your family
Now Zhuang family is lucky to be in the mansion
If I see you again
I will call you uncle
Please don't make things difficult for me
Don't interfere in Miao Wei's matter
Father
Why are you still talking for him?
Zhuang Hanyan
Enough
You are so noisy
Now it's too late
Master
Where is Zhuang Hanyan?
Young Mistress just ordered her to prepare a carriage
to go to see the Imperial Concubine
Master, please wait
What?
I have something
I've been hesitating these days
I want to give it to you now
Where did you get this divorce letter?
The night Young Mistress married you
she called me to the room
and gave me this divorce letter
She said she would risk her life
and may hurt many people
But she remembered
she was accused of being in a difficult position
She used to be a guard to get rid of the danger
so she prepared this divorce letter in advance
If she commits a crime that she can't get back
she won't be able to clean up the family
Master
You have been against Young Mistress recently
I can see it and feel it
But Young Mistress is so stubborn
that she won't explain her feelings to you
and she even told me not to talk too much
She is just angry with you
You lied to her before
and she must take revenge
But she never thought about
hurting Old Mistress and Miss Zhi
I only hope you and Young Mistress
can be together
and achieve great things together
Thank you, Shu Hong
I'll go to her now
Stop
What's the matter?
You are going to the palace
It's late now
and the time is full
I want to discuss with Noble Consort Miao
Today, Prince Qi is going to the family's gate
I have sent the
Who taught you to sing this kind of song?
The jade-like jade
is like four branches
Four branches are missing one
Three branches
Remove the ten-strand shadow
The night is long
and the moon is long
The moon is long
One of the branches is missing
So you mean
the female emperor, Wu Zhao
was coming for Noble Consort Miao
and wanted to take over the throne
and present her with a bright future
not only by listening to the government
but also to the throne
Sir
Yes
I just got the news
that the private witness
came to the palace last night
to see His Majesty
Yes.
Your Highness.
How is it?
I saw the Minister of War
and His Majesty at night.
I heard from the Minister of War...
Say it.
What did he say?
The Minister of War said
the current situation is still in the spring.
The dragon is in the wild, but the wolf is in the wild.
The night is full of evil spirits.
This is the state's bad omen.
If we don't stop the evil spirits,
I'm afraid...
How?
The light of the night is like a jade pot.
The shadow of the night is like a diadem.
The morning is back.
The fox...
We're daemons now.
The fox is doing witchcraft?
Who was it
that tortured the people in the fire?
Tell me.
Wait.
Just say it.
outside theilenry suffers the damage of the sword,
Shoukun...
I'm here.
If the children of the Beggar Clan
and the Four Prefectures of the Qingtian Sword are in the palace,
then Prince Qi is not good at the diamond ring.
Such a vicious method
must be secretly pushed by Zhuang Shiyang.
Prince Qi and the Four Prefectures of the Qingtian Sword
have known each other since childhood
and have been friends for a long time.
According to your speculation,
the four prefectures of the Qingtian Sword
are not related to each other.
But the four prefectures of the Qingtian Sword
According to your speculation,
will His Majesty do it?
Just like how you were attacked by the Chijiao Ghosts and the Wuming Battalion,
the female dead in the harem is even more dangerous.
Once the Qingtian Sword is in the palace,
I'm afraid it will be more dangerous.
Moreover,
it involves our country's long-standing strategy.
I'm afraid that the rain and the rain are coming from the palace.
With such a situation,
are you really going to the palace?
I'm going, too.
I'll accompany you.
The
I can't save her life.
It's too hard to reach the Heaven Hall.
It's Noble Consort Miao's birthday.
Second Master,
did you get the call from Noble Consort?
The
Miao family is a noble family.
They are young and gentle,
and their elders are virtuous.
So they chose Hua Ying to be the harem.
There are no martial arts in the walls.
They are not comfortable in the palace.
They don't follow the etiquette
and they don't follow the etiquette.
They're not engaged in the imperial court.
I'm thankful to them for the great gift of the white mausoleum.
Please allow the exchange of assets.
She is a dead woman.
Under the roof of heaven lay the guide girl of Passians.
Yet the 73-year-old woman's milk-we answering edges
Even if it's a man,
it's a blow to the head,
and a defeat.
Behind this world of wealth and glory,
there are too many disasters and murders.
Perhaps,
from the day I stepped into the palace,
I was destined
to die under the name of this noble lady.
I only hate myself for seeing this.
It's too late.
You're going to stop me again?
This is the divorce letter you wrote.
Since you've married into my family,
you're my wife and my family.
I won't do it again.
This isn't my home.
I've already done what I can.
This is your choice.
Whether it's the old lady,
or the young lady,
I'm not going to let you go.
I'm going to make you pay for it.
Whether it's the old lady,
or the young lady,
the Fu family is either dead or alive.
They have nothing to do with me.
Get out of my way!
Who do you want to kill?
Zhuang Shiyang,
Prince Qi,
or His Majesty?
Let go.
Let go!
Don't push me.
Do you know
why you lost?
I was wrong.
There's a higher power above power.
I shouldn't have gone to see Noble Consort Miao.
I shouldn't have listened to your nonsense.
I should have killed Zhuang Shiyang from the start.
Even if you withdraw the troops today,
you broke into the manor like this,
can you come out alive?
I never thought I would come out alive.
The day my mother died,
this world is the hell for me.
Let go of me.
I'm going to pay for it this time.
You should be grateful at this moment.
There's no time to die in the imperial decree.
Otherwise,
you have already made a mistake.
Who's hiding there?
Come out!
Who's there?
Mother.
Mother, don't let me.
I only played hide-and-seek with you.
I was wrong.
Ah Zhen.
It's okay.
Don't cry.
I'm here.
I was just kidding.
Ah Zhen.
Mother.
Mother, don't go.
Ah Zhi, please.
Ah Zhi.
I've never raised you.
I'm not your mother.
I don't deserve you to call me mother.
All of this is fake.
It's not fake.
Mother promised me.
You don't understand.
Today,
I want to avenge my mother.
I don't want you to die.
I'll avenge you when I grow up.
Okay?
I just want to be like other children.
I want to have a complete home with you.
I just want to have a home with you.
I'll let you know
that I'm not only your daughter,
but also your doctor.
I've been suffering for years
in this endless place.
I've been suffering for years in this endless place.
Why do you come back to revenge?
Why?
Mother.
I don't want you to let go of your hatred.
But if you live for hatred,
live for the bad guys,
you'll be a fool.
Give me a chance
to help you find the one or two
who's worth missing in this world.
Okay?
I'll wait for you
to come back.
That's all.
My regret in this life
is that I couldn't grow up with my daughter.
I seem to be in a dream.
I've forgotten today
because it's the first day
I met the first person.
I'm a fool.
Actually, since that day,
I've found my mother.
I don't want to lose my mother again.
Although my mother
never raised me,
we still have a lot of future.
Mother can be raised by me.
And we've made a deal.
We both
have no mother.
When we miss our mother,
I can hug you.
You can hug me too.
If you miss your grandmother,
you can hug me.
Okay?
I've finally found you.
This is the gift I want to give you.
Last year, on my birthday,
I accidentally found my grandmother's house.
She gave this to me.
It has my mother's name on it.
I'm sorry.
You are by my side.
Young Mistress.
I've fallen asleep.
Yes.
I want to apologize to you.
What's up?
Not long ago, the time at the southern clinic,
I did see you.
That's why I wanted to talk to you.
But my lord didn't see you.
What she said was all nonsense.
It's all my fault.
I was the one who made a mistake.
She really didn't know?
Didn't she explain to you?
She was punished
because of you.
Zhuang Shiyang told me
Fu Yunxi was under her control.
You also believe Zhuang Shiyang?
I saw it clearly that day.
After you fainted,
the minister took you to the room.
He sat by the bedside for a long time.
So he decided to
overturn his previous plan for you.
Until that night,
Zhuang Shiyang took this matter to threaten him.
He told me that
but I didn't believe it.
I swear to God.
Although the man is a little
cruel and ruthless,
he is not evil to his purpose.
But he is definitely sincere to you.
If there is a lie,
I will never marry a wife
and will never get married.
As for other subscribe Therefore Closed
Well, what kind of service
Do you want to pay for Yiming?
In fact, I have known
what I used before
is his sincere love.
How are you feeling now?
Does it hurt?
Try it on.
I'm leaving now.
Please drink.
I swear
I won't let go ofawn.
I will never let him go.
He deserves to be killed.
But no matter how he dies,
I don't want you to break into the mansion
and commit an assassination
in the dark.
Why?
Don't forget.
Our marriage is a deal.
I have the conditions to help you.
You promised me
to take care of the Fu family.
I don't understand.
Why are you so obsessed with it?
You have the ability to protect yourself.
You just need to remember
that since it's a deal,
we should all be lucky.
Okay.
I promise you.
You lied to me.
I lied to you, too.
But this time, I promise you
I mean it.
You always say
you want a family.
What do you think is a family?
At least,
a family with blood ties
can be considered a family.
Just like you and Madam
and Uncle Kou.
You don't know
I have no blood ties with the Fu family.
I'm just the adopted son of the Fu family.
My parents died in the war.
I'm just an orphan.
But as long as there's love and love,
this is my home.
It's okay.
It's your home.
Yunxi.
Han Yan.
Mother.
Yunxi.
Have you heard that
Noble Consort Miao in the palace was assassinated?
Our family has been close to her recently.
Will she confess to it?
I don't know.
Will she make any trouble?
Mother, don't worry.
Noble Consort Miao and I have been friends.
But we're not involved yet.
And His Majesty has ordered
to stop investigating this matter
and end it here.
That's good.
I'm worried about you.
Yunxi.
Han Yan.
It's a fate that
our family can be together.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that if something happens to you,
I...
Don't worry.
We'll be fine.
But
you and Second Aunt
should stay at home.
Don't go out.
I understand.
Everyone was after us before.
Now, I'm afraid everyone hates us.
You're afraid that we'll go out.
Everyone will be shocked.
I know.
It's getting late.
I'll take you back to rest.
Okay.
Mother.
Let's go.
You're still hurt.
Go back to rest.
It's okay.
In the capital, there were two types of people.
One married into the family of Guanhuan Qingliu.
The other married into Wei E's family.
In the end, they all fell into the same trap.
I'm afraid that in this history,
there will be another woman
who has been in trouble for thousands of years.
This life
is so light
that it's gone.
The so-called noble woman
is really ridiculous.
Just now, Mu Feng told me
that the wooden box in Yuwen Chang'an
has been discovered by Mu Yan.
What progress?
The sudden death of Noble Consort Miao was too sudden.
I haven't met Mu Yan yet.
I'll go back to Dali Temple tomorrow.
Wait for me at home.
I hope Uncle Yuwen
won't let us down.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
In our Hanlin Court,
we've finally made a good start
over the years.
Yes.
Lord Zhuang has been
so famous for many years.
Now, he has made such a big achievement.
His
skill is Buddha's Jiu
the Lotus Flower
that has gathered thousand of Sque Az-Z Aus.
He has just been promoted
to a he either in a small country
or a small prefecture
under the Dist summation of the sewing mill.
Now, he has loved
the Northeast rested
I'm sure that the ancestors will have it.
I dare not compare with the masters
who are good at martial arts.
Mr. Zhuang, you're too modest.
You're too modest.
Although he defeated Noble Consort Miao,
Fu Yunxi and Zhuang Hanyan
escaped from the trap.
That's too kind.
Your Highness,
I have an idea.
A proper family should location themselves well-off.
I'll let you decide.
to talk to me.
I never
ignore the big issues.
Your Highness, you are right.
I will remember it.
My grandmother's 60th birthday is coming.
Can you come back
with me to celebrate it?
I have no time.
You can go back by yourself.
It will only take two hours.
I will wait for you.
Mu Feng said there is progress here.
Yes.
And we are in the Imperial Censorate.
Imperial Censorate?
We have been there twice before.
We didn't find anything.
The last time we went there,
we only spent time in the Imperial Library
and the library.
We forgot to find out
the relationship with Lord Wen.
Where is the clue?
In the autopsy room.
We are old people
who are full of bad luck.
We are not treated well.
In the Imperial Censorate,
only Lord Wen is good to me.
We are in the same boat.
We have never been married before.
We have become more close.
Five or six years ago,
he handed me the wooden box.
He said I was quiet here.
There were many dead people and few living people.
It was safer.
Sometimes,
he would take it away for a few days.
He returned it back in a few days.
He never told me
what it was.
But every time I touched it,
I felt a little bit calm.
When Lord Yuwen left the capital,
why didn't you take him away?
He left in a hurry.
He only sent people to send me letters.
He even said that
it was a box of heart-wrenching tears
that were inconvenient to bring to the Jile Emperor.
He only asked me to keep it.
Lord Fu, you...
This is Brother Yuwen's manuscript?
According to Lord Yuwen's collection,
he was still in the Jile Emperor's mansion
three years ago.
He was still in the Jile Emperor's mansion.
He even gave you
something very important.
Lord Fu,
did Brother Yuwen really send you to take it away?
Lord Yuwen is dead.
Maybe these things
can help him to get back on his feet.
But...
Brother Yuwen, he...
Madam.
He found it.
His Lordship's location is clear.
He only asked you to go to the Imperial Censorate in person.
Okay, we'll go right now.
It must be armed with poison.
All right,iong?
Write it down.
Be careful, it was poisoned.
Who was…
who was it?
Your grandfather,
Zhuang Haliang.
You're here.
I'm here.