=The Glory=
=Episode 21=
(Deng Mansion)
The messenger's identity is unknown.
Make sure to watch
over Mr. Deng's every move.
Alright.
Be careful.
Watch over both the gates.
Keep an eye on anyone suspicious.
Yes.
(A Virtuous Legacy)
Come on, higher.
Come on.
Alright, that's enough.
Good.
Master, we have a guest.
Who is it?
Why haven't you invited them in?
Alright, alright.
Grandfather.
It's Ms. Zhuang Hanyan.
She's come uninvited.
She must be up to no good.
I've seen her before.
She's a clever and proper young lady.
Grandfather, haven't you heard?
She's full of schemes
and is good at currying favor.
At this year's Lantern Festival,
Noble Consort Miao
even gifted her a jade bangle.
She's even associated
with Noble Consort Miao?
Greetings, Mr. Deng, Young Master Zaiye.
We didn't know you'd come.
Sorry for not welcoming you sooner.
Zhuang Hanyan,
we didn't send you an invitation, right?
I've long heard that Mrs. Deng is known
for her virtue and chastity,
and now she's been praised
by the Emperor.
(A Virtuous Legacy)
So, I wanted to pay my respects
and came uninvited.
Mr. Deng, please forgive me.
Mrs. Fu, how considerate of you.
Your admiration for virtue and chastity
is indeed a comfort to us.
Please have a seat and enjoy some tea.
Mrs. Fu, this way, please.
Congratulations, Mr. Deng.
- Wenzheng.
- Mr. Deng.
(Quelling the Rebels)
(A Virtuous Legacy)
Very good.
This is the Emperor's own handwriting.
What honor for your family.
Mr. Deng, how fortunate you are.
Wenzheng,
that's not true.
Who in the court doesn't know
that Mr. Deng cares most
about family reputation and integrity?
It's only natural for him
to receive this honor today.
- Yes.
- Congratulations.
Miss Deng Chan.
Miss, this is Mrs. Fu.
A woman's virtue
lies most in her chastity.
Mr. Zheng, you're quite fortunate.
Once your son marries
Mr. Deng's granddaughter,
as she will inherit her mother's will,
your family will also
enjoy this great honor
soon enough.
Wenzheng, stop this nonsense.
Are you cursing my son?
Of course not. Come on.
Of course, I dare not.
Greetings, My Lords.
Today, you're the star.
Please take your seat.
Take your seat.
- Yes.
- Everyone.
Come on.
Have a look.
Take a look.
Congratulations.
- A virtuous legacy.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
Mrs. Deng is here.
Hurry. Please sit inside.
Everyone, please take a seat.
Alright, sit down.
You've been a widow for years,
living in solitude.
It must have been difficult for you.
In my opinion,
there is no easy life for any woman.
Being a widow is painful,
but caring for the husband and kids
is also hard.
Each has its own struggles.
At least Mrs. Deng has received
a plaque from the Emperor.
But what about us?
What's happening?
Today is a day of celebration.
Let's all raise a cup
to Mrs. Deng.
- Here. To Mrs. Deng.
- Yes. To Mrs. Deng.
To Mrs. Deng.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
Please.
One more drink.
Alright, alright.
Let's drink.
One more drink.
Fill it up.
Sure.
One more drink to you.
A virtuous legacy.
How talented.
Good.
Qing,
did you see Zhuang Hanyan?
Young Master,
Mrs. Fu said she was going to change.
I feared she might get lost,
so I followed her out,
but I couldn't find her.
My son,
your mother has been
bedridden for years,
praying for your well-being in heaven,
so that you may protect our family.
Now,
she's finally had her wish fulfilled.
For 16 years,
Zhang has devoted herself to chastity
(Spirit Tablet of Deng Xiangzhao)
and has been filial and dutiful.
Today,
she's been honored
with a chastity plaque
by the Emperor.
(Outstanding Descendants)
This is an honor for our family
and for you.
Grandfather.
Zaiye, come here.
Come here to talk to your father.
Grandfather,
I just saw Zhuang Hanyan
sneak out from the banquet.
I followed her,
but somehow, she vanished.
Did you hear anything unusual?
How is it?
I didn't see anything wrong.
The banquet is almost over.
Could it be that your info was wrong?
Who are you?
That should be my question.
Sir, who are you?
Why did you sneak
into the Dengs' inner chambers so late?
I am Cheng Lei, a student
of the Directorate of Education.
I came tonight
to deliver something to Mr. Deng.
So, it was you.
What do you mean?
It is improper for an outsider
to trespass into the inner chambers.
Mr. Deng ordered me
to wait for you here.
Give me it.
This...
This is extremely valuable.
I must deliver it to Mr. Deng in person.
Grandfather,
you've always been reserved,
yet you drank so much tonight.
Let's go.
I'm glad.
I'm so glad.
I thought we'd leave empty-handed,
but after a twist of fate,
we still obtained it.
(Legend of Huayue)
Why is it a novel?
Where is the joint memorial?
It seems the man from earlier
wasn't the messenger.
Then why did he sneak
into the Deng Mansion
in the middle of the night?
The small regular script is clearly
written by a woman.
Look.
This novel has
a lot of red comments.
They're probably from a man.
There's a name signed in the comments.
Cheng Lei.
Didn't the young master just say
his name was Cheng Lei?
Yes.
That's it.
(By Chan Zhixue)
The author is Chan Zhixue.
It must be Deng Chan.
Those two...
They left these comments to each other.
Let's take a look
to find out how they met
and what their relationship is.
At the lantern banquet,
I found this book by accident.
(Lantern Banquet)
Chan.
Coming.
At the lantern banquet,
I found this book by accident.
I carefully read it,
but it was not enough.
I boldly added some comments in red
and left it at Linjiang Pavilion.
(Legend of Huayue)
If you happen to collect it
and continue the story,
can you still leave it
at Linjiang Pavilion?
I'll visit every day to ask around.
Hopefully, I can read the rest.
Ms. Qu is a charming woman.
She's unconventional and brave,
(Legend of Huayue by Chan Zhixue)
breaking out of the mundane world.
You must be like this too.
I admire you,
and my heart longs for you.
(Legend of Huayue)
I hope we can meet.
(They ignore the moon)
The world loves appearances,
but I alone cherish the soul.
Mr. Meng and Ms. Qu
are meant to be together.
Ms. Zhixue, we know each other
through literature.
Is it also bound by destiny?
(Dressed in simple attire,
she went to offer advice.)
Like Mr. Meng,
I've fallen in love with a woman
who is unique in this world.
She haunts my dreams,
and I can't sleep at night.
I've fallen for you,
but I wonder what you think of me.
I am Cheng Lei, a student
of the Directorate of Education.
I don't have a prominent family
or much talent,
but I have a sincere heart.
I hereby propose to you.
I'll wait for you
at Changle Pavilion.
Thanks to your encouragement,
Legend of Huayue can continue its story.
(Legend of Huayue by Chan Zhixue)
Yet it's just a fleeting illusion.
I've been long trapped
in the inner chambers.
To meet someone who understands me
through literature
is already a stroke of luck.
You're a student with high aspirations
of the Emperor,
while I have been engaged.
I'm not the right one for you.
Today, this is my farewell letter.
Chan Zhixue no longer exists.
I hope you will return
to the right path,
and may your future be bright.
(Breeze Under Moonlight)
These two met through literature
and fell in love,
but could not be together.
So, Deng Chan wrote
this farewell letter.
Tonight,
Cheng Lei was there to meet Miss Deng.
She's been engaged
to Young Master Ziyan,
but she has met someone
who understands her.
This is truly a dilemma.
Mr. Deng values honor
and integrity above all,
and today their family has received
a chastity plaque from the Emperor.
But Miss Deng
has a secret relationship with a man.
You mean...
My Lord,
it seems something is wrong
at the Deng Mansion.
Mr. Cheng,
my family is of a reputable lineage.
Today we've just received
the plaque of "A Virtuous Legacy".
Yet here you are,
unconscious in my inner chambers.
If this word gets out,
how will I ever show my face?
My Lord, please calm down. I'm sorry.
Why did you sneak into here?
Tell me.
I came tonight to see...
Grandfather.
Why have you come to my house?
Chan.
Is Mr. Cheng here to see you?
Grandfather.
Let's get rid of this man first.
Greetings, Mr. Deng.
The banquet is over.
What is this about?
After the banquet was over,
we found a novel on our way out.
So, we came to return it.
Cheng Lei.
Chan Zhixue... Chan.
This book is filled with filth.
Did you write all of this?
Answer me.
Yes.
Yes, it was me.
Miss Deng,
don't speak nonsense
and ruin your reputation.
Chan Zhixue isn't you.
Who's speaking nonsense?
Why did you come here today?
Do you want to ruin
my family's reputation?
Chan,
you're engaged to Young Master Ziyan.
How could you do such
a disgraceful thing?
Grandfather, please calm down.
I...
I know I was wrong.
Thank you.
This is our family matter.
Please leave.
Mr. Deng,
if this gets out,
it will surely damage
your family's long-standing reputation.
But don't worry.
My wife and I will
keep this secret.
We won't say a word.
What do you mean?
To keep a secret,
of course, there are conditions.
Apart from you,
who else also signed
the joint memorial?
As expected,
you two
are here for this.
Miss Deng Chan and I
have met before.
I would never harm her.
About this, we will...
Shut up.
As a woman,
instead of staying home
and observing your duties,
you're constantly out in public,
even associating
with a notorious consort.
Do you have any sense of shame left?
Grandfather.
You...
Mr. Fu.
Mr. Deng, I'm afraid
her behavior
is not for you to judge.
You...
I've dedicated
my whole life to serving our country
and contributed everything I can.
How can I be coerced
by you two?
Tomorrow, I will go to the Zhengs' place
to apologize and cancel the engagement.
Since you two have made such a mistake,
you must marry immediately.
It can't be delayed.
You can't do this.
You can't do this, Father.
Father, please reconsider.
How dare you come here?
Is this the daughter you raised?
Father,
I'm willing to be punished
at the ancestral hall,
but Chan
can't marry Mr. Cheng.
She's been engaged since childhood.
This is known throughout the Capital.
If we suddenly
let her marry someone else,
how will she
face others in the future, Father?
Chan.
Mother,
I'm willing.
- Miss Deng.
- Mr. Cheng.
What? In just a few days,
have you fallen for another woman?
No, I haven't.
Then marry me.
- I...
- Chan.
Don't be foolish.
Mother, I know
you went to great lengths
to choose Ziyan for me.
But now, I only love Mr. Cheng.
Don't persuade me anymore.
This might be better for all of us.
Cheng Lei isn't a good match.
You will regret it if you marry him.
Since you say I'm not a good match,
then what do you consider
a good match, Mrs. Deng?
You...
I...
I've heard of you.
As a student
of the Directorate of Education,
you have little real talent.
When your parents were alive,
they were lowly merchants.
You donated your family wealth
to get into the Directorate of Education
and became an extra student.
You'll amount to nothing in the future.
How can my daughter
give up Young Master Ziyan,
her childhood sweetheart
equal to her in status,
and marry you?
Mrs. Deng, I've long heard
of your good reputation.
Everyone says you are virtuous,
knowledgeable, and well-mannered.
But I didn't expect you
to be so arrogant and rude.
- You...
- So what if my parents were merchants?
In every class,
there is a place for everyone.
My parents died early,
leaving behind land and shops.
Though I can't hold an official post,
I can still support my wife and kids.
Shut up.
When did this family
fall under your control?
A virtuous legacy.
- The Emperor wrote this.
- Father.
As a mother,
you've failed to teach your kids.
How dare you kneel under the plaque
and say those shameless words?
Father...
You two
won't get your way.
My family's long-standing reputation
wasn't built through deceit.
It was passed down with respect
and righteousness through generations.
Even if we're shattered to pieces
and have to die for principles,
the Dengs
will bear it gladly.
Leave!
- Grandfather.
- Father.
Father.
(Calligraphy and Painting)
I didn't expect
that Mr. Deng would be willing
to let Deng Chan marry Mr. Cheng.
Don't you think
there's something more
between Cheng Lei and Deng Chan?
They were both supposed to be happy
as they were allowed
to marry each other,
but one was in tears,
and the other was filled
with shame and anger.
It's really strange.
Should I have Mu Feng and Mu Yan
keep an eye on them?
Alright.
(Two days later)
What's this?
Mu Feng just reported
that someone from the Deng family
sneaked out.
It was Deng Chan.
Tomorrow is the wedding day.
Is she trying to run away
from the wedding?
My Lord, Cheng Lei also sneaked out.
He seems to be heading towards the east.
Maybe he's going to see Miss Deng.
Mu Feng said
Miss Deng was heading towards the west.
Let's split up.
Alright.
You should go.
Leave the Capital tonight.
I'm begging you.
I won't go.
If I'm leaving, I'll leave with you.
You've suffered so much in this life.
It's enough.
You don't owe anyone anything.
Why are you being so foolish?
I've already closed my heart.
I'm shackled.
Please stop being so childish, alright?
Ask yourself.
In your dreams of flowers and moonlight,
have I never appeared in them?
I love only Chan Zhixue.
I don't care if you're young or old,
beautiful or ugly.
Don't you understand me?
I was wrong.
You can't take back
the token of our love once it's given.
Let me break it for you.
Just consider that I've betrayed you.
Please forget me.
I don't understand.
We've known each other since childhood,
and we're supposed to get married.
How can that lose
to your relationship with an outsider?
I don't believe you've fallen
for someone else.
Don't ask me anymore.
I've wronged your family.
Chan, what's the real reason?
Tell me.
We'll figure it out together.
I...
I never loved Cheng Lei.
I've only loved you.
But...
It concerns my family.
I...
I have no other choice.
Ziyan,
if you truly care for me,
stop questioning me, alright?
Miss, we should go back now.
It's wrong.
Everything's wrong.
It's my fault.
I didn't follow my duties as a woman.
I've damaged my reputation.
I shouldn't have written
such absurd things.
It's me.
I've ruined you.
I've ruined Chan.
(Legend of Huayue)
Mother.
Coming.
(Hopefully, I can read the rest.)
(Dressed in simple attire)
(Legend of Huayue by Chan Zhixue)
(As it turns out,)
(this is the truth.)
It's been widely spread in the Capital
that Mrs. Deng, Lady Zhang,
is a woman of great chastity and virtue.
I once thought
you were a silent statue,
free from sorrow or joy
and love or desire.
But that day, I realized
you are Chan Zhixue
who wrote the Legend of Huayue.
Do you know
how I felt?
I don't want to know.
- I don't want to know.
- When my father was around,
I once talked about abandoning
the scholar path.
But my father
locked me in a dark, suffocating cellar
for three days and nights.
After three days,
I walked out in a daze
and looked up to see
the morning glow in the sky.
You are
that morning glow to me.
But I'm a widow.
I'm a widow
who is 12 years older than you
and just received a chastity plaque.
A chastity plaque...
Did you really care about that?
I...
Ms. Qu in your story
gave me the courage to abandon
the official path and enter business.
But now,
why don't you dare
break free from your cage?
As long as we're in love,
what does age, status,
or the eyes of the world matter?
Madam, we must leave.
Someone's following us.
Who's there?
Someone's here.
Let's split up.
Alright.
Be careful.
Father.
The servants reported
that you left the house so late,
but I didn't believe it.
Did you really have an affair
with an outsider?
Father,
I didn't.
Then who was that man talking
with you just now?
Tempting a chaste widow
is punishable by skinning
and dismembering if he were captured.
Father,
it's my fault.
I failed my duties as a woman
and went out without permission.
It has nothing to do with anyone else.
Father, please discern the truth.
You're still making excuses for him.
You can't even protect yourself.
- Come.
- Stop.
My Lord, it was me
who forced Mrs. Deng to meet me.
It's my fault.
No, Father.
Cheng Lei...
You...
So,
this obscene book
was your secret connection?
- No, Father.
- Have you no shame?
- Father.
- Shut up.
You shameless, immoral woman.
Mr. Deng, what is a woman's duty?
Why is it that a widower can remarry
but a widow can't?
Why can men have multiple concubines,
but women must be loyal
to one man forever?
Why is a man's flirtation praised,
while a woman seeking happiness
is nailed to the pillar of shame?
We're all human.
Are women born
to suppress their desires?
If this is your so-called women's duty,
then there's no need to carry it out.
Zhuang Hanyan, it's you again.
It must've been you
who instigated them to commit adultery
and ruin my family's reputation.
You wicked woman.
Before you got married,
I could tell you were no good.
Now, after marrying Mr. Fu,
you often show yourself
in public, ruining morals.
If Fu Yunxi refuses to discipline you,
I will do it for him.
- Mother.
- You...
Chan.
Mr. Deng,
a couple is united as one.
Are you going
to slap me in the face?
Fine.
The public morals are falling apart.
Rituals and laws are doomed.
Chan.
Grandfather,
for the sake of my mother's years
of loyal service to our family,
please
spare her.
You're also defending her?
Are you also going to become
a shameless, immoral women like her?
I...
Chan, Chan.
Let me see it.
If my daughter had a choice,
I'd rather
she never became
a good woman like I was,
praised by everyone.
Zhang,
how dare you speak
such reckless words?
I just spoke the truth,
and you can't bear it?
Get up, Chan.
Today,
let me tell you all the truth.
It's been 17 years.
I've never missed
my late husband day and night
and adhered to a woman's duty.
I never truly loved your son.
I've even forgotten what he looks like.
- You...
- Between him and me,
there was never any warmth or affection.
He despised my poetry and literature
and burned my books.
But I know
he was just jealous
and afraid.
He was a mediocre man
who was born
into a scholarly family like yours.
You...
Do you know?
The essays of your son
that you highly praised
were written
by me.
He stole my talent
while suppressing me.
Whenever he felt inferior,
he would ignore and torment me.
I've had enough.
I don't want to endure this any longer.
Nonsense.
How can you accuse my son without proof?
You can't believe the words
of a shameless woman.
What is a shameless woman?
If breaking free from chains
makes me a shameless woman,
and trapping myself
makes me a virtuous woman,
what's wrong with being
a shameless women?
You...
It's been 17 years.
I've sacrificed
17 years of my life.
For an empty reputation,
I've locked myself
in a cage
called chastity.
I've been tied to it
like it's part of my flesh,
and it's hard for me to break free.
But today,
I no longer wish
to keep that chastity plaque
for you
and for your vanity.
I want to reclaim my name.
My name is Zhang Wanjun,
the eldest daughter
of the Zhang family
in Jiying Alley.
For my brother's career,
for the prosperity of my family,
and
for my children's future,
I've endured for many years.
But today,
I want to live for myself.
I want to live well.
You've gone mad.
Yes, I've gone mad.
For 17 years,
I've shaped myself into a revered,
untouchable figure.
Today,
I'm going to shatter that figure
with my own hands.
Even if it breaks,
I can still piece it together.
I can do it.
I can do this.
Even if I'm bleeding
and covered in wounds,
as long as my name remains,
I am
a complete woman.
Why can't I
have someone who understands me,
respects me,
and cherishes me to love me?
Why can't I?
Why can't I
live without fear
for once?
Someone.
The madam is delirious,
speaking nonsense.
Take her back immediately,
and confine her for treatment.
Take the young lady back
and watch over her.
Tomorrow, she'll get married
at an auspicious time.
Whoever obstructs my family affairs
will face my wrath.
Go.
- Grandfather, I won't marry him.
- Go.
- No.
- I won't marry him.
I'm not afraid.
I won't marry her.
I love only Chan Zhixue.
Let me go.
(Deng Mansion)
(Wedding procession, Zheng Mansion)
- This...
- Master.
Master, bad news.
The inner chambers are on fire.
Let's go.
Go fetch water. Water!
The imperial edict is in her room.
The edict is important.
Put out the fire.
Mr. Deng,
if you want peace in your home,
the fire you truly need to extinguish
is the stubborn,
obsessive fire in your heart.
It's you.
You let her go.
From now on, there won't no Mrs. Deng
or the student Cheng Lei in this world.
When did you let her go?
Where are all my servants?
I've served
in the Judicial Review for years.
This is just a piece of cake
for me.
Fu Yunxi,
you and your wife are very bold.
Don't you fear
being imprisoned or executed?
Your chaste daughter-in-law,
after receiving praise,
remembered her late husband
with deep sorrow,
so today, she set herself on fire
to join him in death.
Is Noble Consort Miao
behind all of this?
It's an act for the sake of justice.
No one is behind it.
What crime have I committed?
Would the heavens destroy me too?
You knew the importance
of a woman's reputation,
yet you still insisted on tarnishing
the name of an innocent childless woman
in the Palace.
Is this
not a crime?
Mr. Deng, you've repeatedly said
that you must protect your family's
long-standing reputation and foundation
even if you're shattered to pieces
and have to die for principles.
Zhang Wanjun has left the Capital,
and her name for chastity and virtue
should be burned clean
in this fire.
No, no, no.
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you everything.
We're all ears.
I know that everything you've done
is to help Noble Consort Miao,
but there's no need to involve others.
So, who should we involve?
Only one man is to be blamed for this.
The others
only did some paperwork.
The one who wants
to kill Noble Consort Miao
is Yao Zhidong, Grand Secretary
of the Hall of Literary Glory.
What I can do
is withdraw from this petition.
But Mr. Yao
has a great influence on the scholars.
As long as he doesn't stop,
more people will follow him
to submit petitions.
I've said everything.
You must guarantee
not to reveal Zhang's whereabouts.
As long as your words are true,
we won't breathe a word.
Let's go.
Ancestors above,
I've preserved our family's
long-standing reputation.
I've preserved it.
♪She hides away her past♪
♪Covered in scars♪
♪She forgets who she is♪
♪Disguised as one returning home♪
♪When night falls, in the yard♪
♪Mist rises in swirls♪
♪She steps onto the battlefield♪
♪No distraction is allowed♪
♪A touch of love, a trace of hate♪
♪No need to question♪
♪The truth and falsehood♪
♪Needs to be discerned♪
♪Seeking warmth in peril♪
♪Only to be mocked as naive♪
♪War drums sound, beacons flare♪
♪Who can break free♪
♪She is willing to become a blade♪
♪Moving forward without retreat♪
♪Charging into this lonely fortress♪
♪Even in a fateful clash♪
♪With eyes stained with blood♪
♪She holds no grudge♪
♪She does not trust fate♪
♪She does not pray to gods♪
♪She grips the blade♪
♪As geese fly south in winter♪
♪She alone journeys north♪
♪Seeking truth in falsehood♪
♪She'd become the blade♪
♪With love as her shield♪
♪Plunging into this mortal world♪
♪Shattering mirages♪
♪And illusions♪
♪To pay respect to the fallen souls♪
♪She does not trust fate♪
♪She does not pray to gods♪
♪She grips the blade♪
♪As geese fly south in winter♪
♪She alone journeys north♪
♪Seeking only a trace♪
♪Of warmth♪