♪Ah yeah♪
♪Does anyone♪
♪Make me like and care for him♪
♪The moment we meet♪
♪Where we stay together♪
♪Name the price of time♪
♪Make an appointment tomorrow♪
♪Who will be nervous♪
♪How to handle a crush♪
♪Oh yeah♪
♪We’re on a level♪
♪I’m never scared♪
♪Whatever fantasy it is♪
♪I’ll get it♪
♪I love you♪
♪So I need you♪
♪You make me no longer lonely♪
♪Until we feel the same♪
♪Regardless of trouble and setback♪
♪We’ll be there for each other♪
=Once We Get Married=
=I Want Nothing But You=
=Episode 22=
(More than two months later)
What if they haven’t fallen asleep?
They must be asleep at this time of day.
Surprise!
Grandma, Mom, why haven’t you slept yet?
We haven’t.
We’re holding a welcome party for you.
It’s getting late.
We’re going to sleep.
You shall go to bed, too.
Yes, yes.
After a long flight, you must be tired.
Get back to your room and sleep.
Mom, you made sense.
Let’s have the welcome party tomorrow.
We’re going up to sleep now.
All right. All right.
Leave everything to tomorrow.
Get to sleep.
At this rate,
my lady, you’ll soon
have a great-grandson.
Don’t disturb them.
Keep your voice down.
Get going. Go have some sleep.
Go, go.
Come on.
Let’s go.
Mrs. Yin.
- Mm?
- Time to sleep.
I’m unpacking the suitcase.
If you’re sleepy, get to sleep first.
Without you lying here,
how can I fall asleep?
Get something to do, then.
Fine.
What? I’m in the middle of something.
Didn’t you ask me
to get something to do?
How about unpacking with me?
Yes, sweetheart.
You want to settle in Why Mall?
Why didn’t you tell me?
This was the subject of the courses.
However,
through the learning of three months,
I indeed found out a problem.
CICI needs a bigger platform.
So,
you prefer Why Mall?
I’ve thought about it.
But I don’t think CICI
has reached the standard of Why Mall.
Gu Xixi,
you’re now the hostess of Why Mall.
All its standards
can be reset for you.
I reject it.
I’ll make it
the final task of my learning.
So, don’t ever try to help.
All right, then.
Do whatever you want.
Good boy.
Wait. Wait.
Time to get our real business done.
Yin Sichen!
You love learning after the courses?
Why are you so sleepy?
You must have learned
with Yin Sichen late last night.
Shall I send you to check the inventory
in the storehouse?
I just did that.
Looks like you have nothing to do.
I have some clothes to iron.
You do?
(Sichen)
You’ve got a call, boss.
Hello?
Darling.
Now?
Fine. I’ll be right there.
Bye-bye.
Xiaoya, I’ve got an emergency.
I gotta go. Bye-bye.
Take care of the store.
I want some bonus, then.
In your dream!
Gu Xixi, how cruel you are!
Xixi isn’t in?
She just left.
Shall I call her?
No, no.
Come on in, girls.
Mm.
Is this the store?
Come on.
Browse around as you wish.
- My daughter-in-law
- Looks great.
is an emerging fashion designer.
She has unique taste.
Look at this.
Oh.
What fabric is this made of?
I’m allergic to cheap fabric.
What are you talking about?
How would my daughter-in-law
make clothes with cheap fabric?
Come on.
We all know your daughter-in-law
is beautiful and competent.
You don’t need to praise her
all the time.
Now that you know, do something.
Look, you didn’t give her any gift
when she got married.
How about this?
Invest in her store
as a gift for her.
- Don’t you invest too?
- It’s a deal, then.
- It’s a deal.
- Fine.
All right.
Have a browse around.
- Shoes are over there.
- All right.
All right.
Xixi’s mother-in-law is so nice to her.
- Hello? Mom.
- Leave it to the Law Department.
The Marketing Department
did such a bad job.
I’m with Sichen.
We’ll have to work overtime.
I’ll have Xiaoya entertain you.
We can’t finish it.
Have fun.
What did Mom say?
She is shopping
with her friends in CICI.
Let’s get back to business.
Sichen,
I haven’t finished the application yet.
Why are we talking
about settling already?
Your application is already formal.
I just asked them to enrich it.
By the way,
ask the Marketing Department
to verify CICI’s application first.
But Sichen...
Don’t worry.
I’m not interfering.
Everything is done
according to the rules of Why Mall.
He didn’t force us.
He just asked us
to complete the three-month work
within a day.
Besides that,
he has done nothing.
They’re just working overtime,
with the highest overtime pay
in the industry.
After the project is over,
they’ll also have
a two-month paid leave.
Isn’t it too exhausting?
What?
Feeling sorry for your husband?
I mean for your employees.
It’s us who are suffering.
If you keep doing PDA,
I’ll apply for compensation.
Well,
go to the Finance Department
and get your pay for this month.
You don’t need to come tomorrow.
Come on. Look at this.
Mrs. Yin,
come and check the details
of the contract.
She doesn’t need to.
You just need to remember.
This is the project
of Why Mall’s hostess.
Without disobeying the company rules,
you shall handle the details.
Do you get it?
Yes.
Sichen...
All right. Work is done.
I miss you.
I’m just beside you.
But we are at work. It doesn’t count.
I want...
Are you out of your mind?
We’re in your company
and they’re watching.
Looks like we have to
work overtime tonight.
We must work overtime for the proposal.
We can’t finish it in the day.
Xiwei, you came for Sichen?
If you need any help, tell me.
No, aunt.
It’s just about business cooperation.
Sichen is back.
I came to talk with him about it.
Young men like you
should often visit each other like this.
When you can help each other,
we feel relieved.
Aunt,
when Sichen and I were little,
we often had discussions.
Now we’ve grown up and got to work,
whenever there’s a chance
of cooperation,
we usually try our best to get it.
So, many people
misunderstand our relationship.
There’s nothing to be misunderstood.
We’ve been a family.
You must be kidding me.
Sichen has got married.
How can we be a family?
Don’t sound like a stranger.
Sichen is married.
But it doesn’t stop him
from treating you as his sister.
Sister?
Yeah.
Xiwei,
I watched you grow up.
In my eyes,
you’re just like Sichen.
In my heart,
you’ve been my daughter.
By the way...
Look.
A friend of mine works on new media.
He knows much more than Sichen.
You’ll have no problem
cooperating with him.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Xiwei,
if you have any problem at work,
tell me directly.
I treat you as my child.
I’ll help you.
Don’t hesitate to ask me for help.
Mm.
(Zhang Xinyu, Guangxuan New Media)
I was so stupid
that you thought you could use me
and abandon me as you wish.
However,
I won’t be stupid anymore.
Mom,
we’ll get CICI to settle in Why Mall.
We’ll hold an opening fashion show
in a couple of days.
Come and support Xixi with Grandma.
I’ve reserved the best seats for you.
All right.
By then,
I’ll attend the fashion show
in the dress Xixi designed.
Don’t worry.
I’ve prepared the dresses for you.
You have?
Mm.
You’re the best girl, Xixi.
I don’t agree.
Ah?
Why?
Don’t always interfere with their stuff.
Xixi is a very talented
emerging designer.
Why Mall also needs
new brands like CICI.
I’m certainly aware
that Why Mall needs
young brands like CICI
to expand the market.
But to Xixi,
she needs a bigger platform
where more people
will get to know her talent.
So, you don’t trust Why Mall?
You’re my son.
I trust your ability with no doubt.
But today,
my friends and I visited CICI.
They speak highly of CICI
and want to introduce you
to global department stores.
If it works,
CICI can start
directly from the international market.
By then, Why Mall
has to beg you to settle in it.
Mom,
we’re going through
the contract already.
Don’t interfere, will you?
After all,
it’s Xixi’s brand.
She decides
which she will pick.
What do you think, Xixi?
Mom,
it’s always been my dream
to get CICI to the international market.
Yin Sichen,
if you have a sore throat,
drink more water.
Xixi, ignore him.
Go on.
But I think
CICI suits Why Mall better.
Because CICI hasn’t reached
the standards
of the international market.
So, I want to work hard with Sichen.
They have their own plan.
We should let them go
so that they can develop.
You’re full?
I’ll have some hawthorn juice
to cleanse the palate.
Let’s enjoy the meal.
Mm.
Sichen.
You’re awake?
Mm.
I’m going to work.
Work hard.
Be a good girl at home.
Mm.
This is the surveillance video
for the Fashion Celebration
you asked me to find out.
It was revised.
It took me a long while,
but I finally got it back.
Thank you.
According to the surveillance video,
it was indeed Miss Ran
who copied Miss Gu’s diary
into the player.
I’ll take care of it.
What about Miss Gu?
I’ll explain to her
after I take care of it.
By the way,
when you find that
Ran Xiwei meets Gu Xixi in private,
tell me immediately.
Got it.
Oh,
how’s the contract for CICI going?
I urged the Law Department.
They’ll complete it in a day or two.
When I get to my office,
ask them to see me.
I’ll cancel the contract with Gu Xixi.
Cancel?
Do you think we still need that?
(Prenuptial Agreement)
Fei’ang.
Miss Ran has come.
Why did she come?
What did you come for?
I want to talk with you
about some cooperation.
I also have something
to ask you.
We think so alike.
Not really.
Who did you cooperate with
at the Fashion Celebration?
What else did he tell you?
Why did you ask about that?
I had no partner
for the Fashion Celebration.
Are you sure?
What else would you like to explain?
Yes.
I played the VCR.
I did that
simply to expose Gu Xixi’s true colors.
I want you to see her through
so that you won’t get hurt again.
This is Gu Xixi’s privacy.
Why do you think you could do that?
Because I wanted everyone to know
that Gu Xixi was a liar.
She married you for money only!
Why can’t you understand?
Gu Xixi isn’t a liar.
She’s my wife.
If you defame her again,
don’t blame me for not taking you
as a friend again.
Yin Sichen,
we’ve known each other
for a dozen years.
But how long have you known her?
Half a year?
Why are you threatening me for her?
Do you even care
a little bit for me?
Please be sensible!
Gu Xixi doesn’t deserve
your care for her!
Why do you think you can say this?
You claim that Gu Xixi lied to me.
What about you?
At first,
Gu Xixi rejected Alex.
Then she was attacked
after being interviewed by you.
And her diary was exposed
at the Fashion Celebration.
You arranged all this, didn’t you?
There are more things I know
or I don’t know.
Do you need me to list them?
I don’t care what you think of me.
I’ve done everything for your own good.
I don’t want you to be deceived anymore!
But I don’t need you to do that!
For the sake that you’re my friend,
I let you go for the last time.
One more time...
If you hurt Gu Xixi one more time,
I’ll make you pay the price.
I’ve got a meeting.
Sichen.
(Prenuptial Agreement)
You have a fake marriage?
Yin Sichen,
now that you abandon our relationship
over a dozen years for Gu Xixi,
I’ll help you
as you wish.
Hello? Huahua.
You wrote a nice news report last time.
I need you to write another report.
The president of Why Mall
had a contracted marriage
for business cooperation.
Isn’t it breaking news?
When they first got married,
didn’t they promote
their fairy tale love story?
Readers love such a big twist.
Why did you come so early?
I was eager to see you.
I spent my lunch hour
finishing all my work.
I haven’t had lunch yet.
What would you like to eat?
My treat.
You rarely treat me to lunch.
I’ll pick a nice restaurant.
Come on.
Could you restrain yourselves?
I’m still here.
We’re leaving immediately.
Take care of the store.
How cruel you are!
You’re going on a date,
but I have to work alone?
It’s okay.
There’s little work on a weekday.
You may leave, too.
You’re the best, Xixi.
You love me most.
No.
My wife can love me only.
Love you.
Here. Here.
Mr. and Mrs. Yin,
is the online news true
that you have a contracted marriage?
Did you fake your marriage
for the contract with Alex?
Isn’t that business fraud?
- Mrs. Yin.
- Mr. Yin.
- Please answer our questions.
- Please answer.
Are you really doing business fraud?
- What’s your real relationship?
- Please answer.
Why did you start a fake marriage?
What’s your real relationship?
Please answer our questions.
Answer our questions.
Mr. Yin, could you answer us?
Please explain.
Are you married for business?
Mr. Yin!
Make way! Make way!
(Closed)
Please explain.
Back off.
Reporters.
Reporters, please be quiet.
Be quiet.
Mr. Yin.
Listen to me.
I’ve got the latest news.
If you have questions, ask me.
Miss Mu, from beginning to end,
you’ve known about that?
Are they doing business fraud?
Everybody, listen to me!
I, Shang Ke, decide
to get engaged.
Engaged?
But...
But,
what does it have to do with them?
It has nothing to do with them.
They’re over there!
Let’s go!
- Be quick!
- Go, go, go!
Go after Mr. Yin.
Mr. Shang wasted our time.
Quickly.
They haven’t gone too far.
(The liar couple put on
big business fraud)
The liar couple put on
big business fraud.
The netizens are too realistic.
A couple of days ago,
they just said you had fairy tale love.
They changed so quickly.
Wait. Wait.
So, you...
You...
You were just pretending?
But now it’s true.
But...
Even she knew it.
Why didn’t you tell me?
Yin Sichen,
we’ve been friends for years.
Are we real friends?
It’s not time to argue about this.
You knew it, too?
So, you all knew this,
but me?
Weren’t you bullying me?
I’ve communicated with the reporters.
They won’t take further action
for the moment.
Sichen,
who exposed your secret?
Do you have an idea?
Ran Xiwei did it.
- How did she know?
- What?
At the Fashion Celebration,
it was also her.
No matter what exactly she wants,
we’ll handle this problem.
No way.
I must call her
and ask her about it.
Why did she...?
Come back.
When she did this,
she showed her stand and attitude.
What’s the point of asking her now?
Sichen made sense.
By now, 0.12 billion is suddenly off
the market value of Why Mall.
The stock price keeps declining.
Our top priority is
to solve this problem.
You’d better gain
the forgiveness of Alex.
The pressure of public opinion
will be reduced by half.
I’ve sent an email to Alex,
explaining the whole story.
I’m waiting for his reply.
I’ve got an idea.
I think
we can arrange an antenatal examination.
Let Sichen accompany Xixi
for an antenatal examination
and post the photos on the Internet.
Then Granny Yin can clarify that
you’re only preparing for a baby.
Then the attention can be shifted.
No way. Grandma is innocent.
We can’t get her involved.
This isn’t the best solution.
But it’ll shift others’ attention.
Forget it. I have an idea.
I have a paparazzo friend.
He has dirt on many stars.
When he posts it,
netizens will be excited about stars.
And your news will die down.
Right?
I agree!
This isn’t simply pink news
like it was at the Fashion Celebration.
The contracted marriage
has a direct influence on Why Mall,
CICI and even the stock price
of the Yin Group.
I can’t try to let the problem slip by
by leaving things to chance.
I agree.
We should take the initiative
to explain the truth to the public
and gain their forgiveness.
But in this way,
you’ll fall into a passive condition.
After all,
when you’re in such a crisis,
you have to pay the price.
It doesn’t matter.
No matter what happens,
I’ll bear it with Sichen.
I won’t get you hurt.
Mr. Yin, shareholders
hold an urgent meeting
to ask you to be accountable.
They’re waiting for you
in the meeting room.
I get it.
All right.
Get to your business.
I’m all right.
Take good care of yourself.
Mm.
Why is he leaving?
Done?
I’m serious.
Next, some people
may have some radical behaviors.
So, Xixi,
you have to calm down
and don’t act on impulse.
Don’t worry.
I won’t act on impulse!
Come on.
Come on!
So far, three companies asked
to terminate the contract with us.
Among them, Deli asked us
to compensate for all the losses.
As of just now,
our stock price has declined by 9.7%.
I’m still a bit worried about Xixi.
Send someone to check in her store.
All right.
How do I look?
Quite confident
and fully prepared.
Tell me as soon as Alex replies.
Mm.
There won’t be a problem, will there?
There won’t.
I’ll leave you here.
Mm.
You’ve got a shooting job, right?
Go ahead.
I’m going right away.
And I’ll be right back after that.
Mm.
I gotta go.
Don’t worry.
She’s there!
She’s Gu Xixi!
Just as in the news.
That’s her!
It’s because of her fake marriage
with Yin Sichen
that the stock price declined
and we lost all our money!
Liar!
- Give me my money back!
- Pay me back!
Liar!
- Smash her!
- Liar!
- Give me my money back!
You cheated us of our hard-earned money.
You heartless couple!
Give the money back to us!
Our money is all gone!
Yeah!
We earned it by hard work.
I’ll smash you! Give me my money back!
Give me my money back!
How dare you defend her! Smash them!
Give the money back to us!
Give it back!
Liar, give me my money back!
Liar!
Give the money back to us!
Give it back! Give it back!
It’s been three hours
since Mr. Yin’s contracted marriage
was exposed.
Director Gao, what’s the direct loss
in the past three hours?
By three o’clock this afternoon,
and estimated by the closing price
at Shanghai Stock Exchange,
0.12 billion is off the market value
of Why Mall.
Three companies may terminate
their advertising cooperation with us.
One of them has submitted
the request for compensation.
It’s estimated to be
about 73 million.
I’ve asked the Marketing Department
to approach this company.
The compensation Deli asked for
isn’t reasonable.
So, the loss of this part
can be reduced.
As for the stock market,
I believe,
when I gain the forgiveness of Alex,
and he makes a statement,
the stock price can get back
to its original standard.
What’s Alex’s attitude?
I’ve sent an email to him.
He hasn’t replied yet.
I’ll try my best
to gain the forgiveness of Alex.
Mr. Yin, I trust your judgment.
I trust your business strategy, too.
Honestly,
we don’t care
if you have a real or a fake marriage.
But this has
severely influenced
the interests of the company.
You’re not the only one
who has lost money.
So now,
you must give us a perfect solution.
Right?
Mr. Chen made sense.
Before Alex makes a statement,
the stock price will keep declining.
Who will be responsible for the loss?
Under such circumstances,
we should also explain to investors.
In my opinion,
how about this?
Let’s give Mr. Yin 15 days.
In 15 days,
all of us will have
another shareholders’ meeting here.
By then, we will decide
how to deal with Mr. Yin’s problem.
But within 15 days,
let’s suspend his administrative post.
What do you think?
Let’s do this, then.
Alex has replied?
It’s Miss Gu.
She was in trouble.
I’m so sorry, Zixin.
Sorry for getting you involved.
It’s a new suit we just launched.
If you don’t mind,
take it as my apology.
With such a chance,
I’ve got your new product.
I’m profiting.
Why did you come today?
I read about the news on the Internet.
I was worried about you.
So I came.
Those investors lost a lot of money
in the stock market.
You’d better close your store
these days.
I can’t close it.
Don’t worry.
You can still run the online store.
Our Publicity and Marketing
Departments will help you.
What if they make trouble in Why Mall
when I close CICI?
Sichen is already stressed out.
I want to share some pressure for him.
What about you?
Luckily, I was just passing by.
What about next time?
Those investors
may be more violent.
I don’t fear their violence.
I fear that I can’t help Sichen.
Gu Xixi!
Sichen?
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
Alright, Sichen.
I’m fine.
But Zixin defended me
and his suit was stained.
I’m glad that you were there.
Thank you.
When I can hear you say “thank you”,
my suit wasn’t wasted.
Don’t worry. I’m all right.
I’m indeed all right.
Sichen.
Mm?
It doesn’t look like the way home.
We’re not going home.
I’m taking you somewhere.
Where?
The end of the world.
Here we are.
Why is this place the end of the world?
When I was little,
once I quarreled with my mother
and then I ran away from home.
As I walked,
I came here.
To me at that age,
this was the end of the world.
I don’t know where
the real end of the world is.
So, I can only take you
to my end of the world.
Look.
How did you know the timing?
By accident when I first came.
After that, every time
I have trouble or difficulty,
I come here
and do such a boring trick.
Sichen,
you’ve worked too hard.
From now on, I’ll always be with you.
Life is always filled
with many things
we can’t control or handle.
Before I met you,
I could have handled this.
As I stay here longer,
I’ll have enough courage
to confront those problems.
Take it as charging.
Let me charge you, then.
This is a big problem.
Unless I’m fully charged,
I can hardly solve it.
It doesn’t matter.
If you can’t, let it be.
I have CICI, anyway.
The income of CICI
will be enough
for our ordinary life, won’t it?
No way.
You have some hobbies that cost a lot,
such as the garage kit.
But it doesn’t matter.
You don’t need to give it up.
I can make some for you by hand.
I can make...
Xixi.
I want nothing,
but you.
♪Like a meteor streaks♪
♪The night sky is lit up♪
♪I never want you♪
♪To fall like this♪
♪The road winds♪
♪But light sparkles♪
♪Because love♪
♪Indeed existed♪
♪When it starts all over again♪
♪I won’t shrink back♪
♪You touch my nerve all the time♪
♪Because my heart is blank♪
♪I’m firm but not dramatic♪
♪I just want to give you♪
♪The best of the world♪
♪It’s me who loves you♪
♪The fairy tale is true♪
♪The Achilles’ heel♪
♪Is the soft corner of my heart♪
♪We attract each other♪
♪Simple and stubborn♪
♪It makes your dream more complete♪
♪And makes it tough♪
♪For you and me♪
♪Love breaks the rule♪
♪Because in love we need♪
♪Light and heat from each other♪
♪I protect you quietly♪
♪Leave everything to me♪
♪Turn into the Milky Way♪
♪In my night sky♪
♪You never fall♪