♪Ah yeah♪
♪Does anyone♪
♪Make me like and care for him♪
♪The moment we meet♪
♪Where we stay together♪
♪Name the price of time♪
♪Make an appointment tomorrow♪
♪Who will be nervous♪
♪How to handle a crush♪
♪Oh yeah♪
♪We’re on a level♪
♪I’m never scared♪
♪Whatever fantasy it is♪
♪I’ll get it♪
♪I love you♪
♪So I need you♪
♪You make me no longer lonely♪
♪Until we feel the same♪
♪Regardless of trouble and setback♪
♪We’ll be there for each other♪
=Once We Get Married=
=I Like Adorkable Men=
=Episode 19=
Mr. Mo, this is a family matter
for Yin Sichen.
You shouldn’t get involved.
Do you want me to watch her
being humiliated?
I can’t.
Yin Sichen will protect his wife.
But she’s also my friend.
Yeah, it’s handwriting.
Isn’t this Mrs. Yin?
Marry a rich man?
God.
She’s a material girl.
Can’t believe it.
Sichen.
Don’t worry.
I’m here.
To be rich.
What a material girl!
Unbelievable.
This is scandalous.
Ladies and gentlemen,
whatever you think about
this woman next to me,
in my eyes,
no words can describe
her virtue.
She’s not a liar,
but the woman
I, Yin Sichen will
protect for my lifetime.
I love you.
♪It’s me who loves you♪
♪The fairy tale is true♪
♪The Achilles’ heel♪
♪Is the soft corner of my heart♪
Looks like I’m not needed here.
Let’s go.
Over there.
Mr. Yin, a comment, please.
Did Mrs. Yin marry you for your money?
Did she cheat your family?
What is Mrs. Yin’s true identity?
Say something, Mrs. Yin.
Gu Xixi’s true identity
is my wife,
Why Mall’s President’s dearest.
♪Because in love we need♪
I don’t care who defames
my wife with this.
♪I protect you quietly♪
But my wife’s business
is my business.
I will find the truth.
(Tencent News:
WHY-MALL President’s wife is a gold-digger)
This is absurd.
Yin Zecheng, get out of there.
- I can’t believe it.
- What’s up, honey?
If it were not on news,
how long would you keep it from me?
I was curious why you were so nice
to come here with me for recuperation.
Honey, it’s just expediency
to close the deal
with Alex, you know.
You shouldn’t have supported
him in the first place.
Do you and our son
have any respect for my opinions?
I’ve called Sichen.
He’s trying to figure out a solution.
You have to trust he can solve it.
Alright, stop.
I give him too much trust
that leads us to this point.
Say no more.
Book a flight.
We’re going back now.
Calm down.
Let’s talk inside.
Oh, what...?
Get in.
Come on. Sit down.
Let go.
I can’t leave in a couple of days.
Mr. Duan of the Yunjing Group
is here on vacation recently.
I want to talk with him
about cooperation.
Look,
Sichen is an adult now.
Give him space to deal with
his personal affairs.
Besides,
he’s the president of the company.
But I...
Don’t get up.
Alright.
Go back if you insist.
I’ll buy a ticket for you.
Is that OK?
By the way,
as for Gu Xixi,
find everything about her.
Leave nothing behind.
OK, I got it.
I’d like to see what kind of person
my daughter-in-law is.
Try harder and thrive.
Bless Xixi with fortune
and bless us with sweet love.
Did you hear that?
The negative news about Miss Gu
has been taken care of.
It won’t appear on any major websites.
You can rest assured.
The external problems have been solved.
Now it’s time to deal with
the internal ones.
There must be
a mastermind behind this scandal.
For one thing,
how did this man
get Gu Xixi’s diary
and bring it to the venue?
Leave it to me.
(Fashion Celebration becomes
Mr. Yin’s show of love)
You knew what kind of girl Gu Xixi is.
But you protected her.
What an insane man!
(Mrs. Shang)
Hello, Mrs. Shang.
Ruona,
Shang Ke left something home.
He didn’t answer my call.
Would you please come
and get it for him?
Sure.
I’ll be right there. Just a moment.
Sorry, Mrs. Shang.
I’m late.
There was a bit of traffic.
I’m making soup.
Can you pack some for him?
It’ll be done in a while.
OK.
I’m sorry
to take up your time.
It’s OK.
Honestly,
- Thank you.
- I think my son
is weird somehow lately.
He’s not the same.
I guess
he’s got some kind of secret.
Secret?
What kind of secret can he have?
Ruona, I’d like to be frank.
Are you and my son dating?
Ruona, let’s cut to the chase.
I already know everything
about your relationship.
You don’t need to hide it.
Please take the card
and the money in it.
Tell me if it’s not enough.
Mrs. Shang,
are you trying to ask me
to stay away from Shang Ke?
No.
I mean
the absolute opposite.
Yes, there are quite some scandals
around my son,
he has dozens of ex-girlfriends,
and he’s simple-minded and naive.
Except that, he’s perfect.
I don’t expect him
to be as considerate as you are.
All I’m hoping is that he can
get married as soon as possible.
If he can marry you,
I’ll wake up laughing in sleep.
After marriage,
you can bring your parents over
to live with us.
We have a big house.
How happy it’ll be for a family
to live together!
I’m happy to even think about it.
Mrs. Shang, you’ve planned
for the future?
Yeah.
After you get married,
you and Shang Ke will have
a boy and a girl.
How happy it will be!
When they grow up,
the boy will take care of the business
and the girl will take care of the home.
Then you and Shang Ke can...
Mrs. Shang,
I don’t
consider marriage for now.
Does what I said offend you?
No, not at all.
But
Mrs. Shang, I think
it’s between me and Shang Ke.
Mrs. Shang, please
let us take care of it ourselves.
Have some tea.
I...
What’s wrong with you?
You’re so grumpy. Is something on fire?
Did you tell your mom
about us?
No, I didn’t.
How dare I without your permit?
I swear I didn’t.
She offered a large sum of money
for me to stay by your side.
Wait a minute.
She gave you a large sum of money
and told you not to leave me?
That’s not right.
In TV works, a girl is paid
- Shang Ke, be serious.
- to leave.
I am serious.
I mean
last time when we were kissing here,
she saw it.
That’s how she knew.
I... I didn’t tell her.
Ruona,
forget about the scoring system.
Let’s get married.
What did you say?
You can’t keep a lid on it.
They’ll find out sooner or later.
Instead of letting them
tell us what to do,
I think we should take the initiative.
I really love you.
I don’t want to leave you.
Marry me.
Shang Ke,
I...
I don’t want to get married actually.
Why not?
I don’t trust marriage.
When I was a little girl,
my parents were not on good terms.
They often quarreled,
and even fought.
It wasn’t until they got divorced
that they both were relieved.
I didn’t understand
why a man and a woman
who didn’t get along
put up with each other.
You know what?
My mom told me later,
before they got married,
they weren’t like that.
So you’re afraid of
getting married, right?
Mu Ruona,
I’m serious.
So am I.
OK.
So tell me,
what is the scoring system for?
Because I know
you will not reach the standard.
Fei’ang, a cup of coffee.
What brings you here?
I can’t find Ruona.
What’s happened?
We had a fight.
She texted me about going on vacation.
Then her phone is turned off.
Did you
cheat on her
which she found out?
I would never do that.
I’m like her shadow.
I wouldn’t have a chance to.
So what happened?
I proposed to her.
You proposed?
Yeah.
How did you screw it up?
I didn’t. It was her.
She has gamophobia.
Fear of marriage?
Then help me analyze it.
Do I still have a chance?
From what I know about Ruona,
you two are done for.
Hold on.
Where are you going?
To find her.
Sit down.
Can you use your brain?
What’s your first response
to a love obstacle?
Coming to you.
That’s what I’m saying.
It’s the same with Ruona.
Whether it’s a man or a woman,
when they run into an obstacle in love,
they’ll
talk to someone they trust most.
That’s what you’ll do.
So will Ruona.
That you can’t find her
doesn’t mean
her best friend can’t, either.
I’m sorry.
Ruona?
What are you doing here?
Do you have time
to have a cup of coffee with me?
Sure.
So you think Shang Ke
can’t meet the standard?
(Love Scoring System)
He scores 61 in just a month.
At this rate,
Shang Ke will definitely pass it.
I know that too.
So,
I chose to run away.
What’s your plan?
Keep running isn’t like what you’ll do.
I thought about it in the last few days.
I want to resign
and go somewhere tranquil.
You can escape
and go somewhere else.
But will the problem
between you and Shang Ke disappear?
If you think it could disappear,
you wouldn’t have come to me.
The fact that you came
implies that you’re not sure
about running away, are you?
You just want to get either of
the two answers from me.
One is the reason to stay,
and the other
the encouragement to leave.
Am I right?
So?
Are you going to give me the reason
or encouragement?
Forgive me.
I can’t give you either.
As your best friend,
I’m going to lend you a little courage.
Maybe that little bit of courage will be
the sword for you to defeat gamophobia.
But Xixi, I want to tell you.
Everyone is independent.
Perhaps your way of life
doesn’t work for me.
How can you know if you don’t try?
Do you have any other options now?
No.
Then why don’t you try my way?
Look,
no rush to leave in few days.
I’m on call, OK?
What are you planning?
Sichen, is your way gonna work?
- Would Ruona...?
- Can you sit down?
Sichen, you’re back.
- Can you help me...?
- Xixi.
Look, um...
- Ruona, she...
- Stop.
No worries. She’s here.
I guess I was right.
Mu Ruona has gone to you.
Mm-hmm.
Well, how is she now?
Better than you anyway.
That’s good. That’s good.
But Xixi,
can you ask her out for me?
What are you going to do?
I know she and I are not possible.
But I have to make things clear.
How do you know you and she
are not possible?
He said it.
You consulted him?
First, he doesn’t know women.
Second, he has basically no knowledge
of human feelings.
That’s true.
- Hey, don’t.
- Gu Xixi, what did you say?
Are you saying you have an idea?
What’s not possible you mean?
To be together.
To be together?
Do you want to marry her?
Marriage?
I’ve been
thinking about it for the last few days.
In fact, I just simply
want to see her
and stay with her every day.
When she’s in danger,
I’ll be the first to protect her.
It doesn’t matter
if we get married or not.
If you say so, it’s possible.
Really?
Yeah.
I have a plan
that includes both of you.
What plan?
This idea of mine
might make you unhappy,
or even angry.
Will you try it even so?
If it gives me courage
to face this problem,
then I’ll give it a try.
As for if I will get angry...
Never with you.
I was afraid I’d lose my best friend
after this.
Alright, I can’t go in with you.
Promise me.
No matter what happens in there,
don’t run away from it.
Trust me.
Mm-hmm.
Go ahead. Good luck.
Gu Xixi,
I have gamophobia, not wedding phobia.
What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
Sichen.
Hmm?
What are you doing?
Just watching.
How did you get the surveillance?
It’s peeping.
I’m afraid Shang Ke would screw it.
That’s not an excuse.
It’s so unethical.
Would you like to watch it with me?
Sure.
I’m all ears.
Xixi told me
to come to the root of the problem.
She asked me to help you
find your courage back.
But she doesn’t know
I don’t have any courage myself.
When I proposed to you that day,
I put all my strength into it.
And you turned me down in the end.
So now I have no courage at all.
So,
you’re blaming me?
Yes, I am.
You didn’t want to get married.
But you gave me a scoring system.
Your affection wasn’t strong.
But you dated me for the so-called duty.
You could...
Is that what you want to tell me?
Wait. What’s going on there?
Why didn’t Shang Ke say
what I told him?
It was my idea.
Why?
I thought you said
I didn’t know anything about love.
I admit it.
And
what you asked Shang Ke
to say to Mu Ruona
is very touching
and it can soften things off.
Mm-hmm.
But Mu Ruona is the same type as me.
I know her better than you do.
Trust me for once.
I know you’re in love with me.
But you keep avoiding it.
Xixi told me
I scored 60 already.
But you know what?
In my scoring system,
all you have is 10.
Why?
Why do I only have ten points?
Your attitude.
You’re playing cat and mouse with me.
Ten is a lot for you already!
OK.
Good. That’s great.
In that case,
I can leave without hesitation.
What is he waiting for? Go after her.
He cannot do that.
Or it’d all go south.
Listen,
if for your reason,
my plan ends up a failure,
and my friendship with Mu Ruona
is ruined,
you’ll be very sorry.
Just hang on a little bit.
Look.
Well,
from now on,
we’ll reset the score.
You mean
clear the score out?
Yeah.
From now on,
we reset it.
I agree.
But let me be clear.
Even if you score more than 80,
I still might not marry you.
It doesn’t matter
if we get married or not.
What matters is
that the man who gives you
a sense of safety
must be me.
I love you.
I win.
It’s pure luck.
What’s my reward for winning?
I do
have a reward.
What is it?
Clean up the auditorium with me.
What kind of reward is that?
I rent the auditorium.
We have to clean it up
so that I can return it tomorrow.
Can’t Fei’ang have it done?
I got it.
You just don’t want to be with me.
Let’s go.
Shang Ke owes me a great deal for it.
He probably has no time for you.
Why can he go have fun with his girl
while I’m cleaning up for him?
When you give someone a rose,
your hand has its fragrance.
Fragrance?
I can smell nothing
except for sweat.
Don’t you think
it’s full of the fragrance of happiness
even after they’re gone?
Gu Xixi, is our wedding not happy?
What do you think?
I was forced.
Would you like a dance with me?
I’m not dancing with you.
Gu Xixi,
is our wedding so lame for you?
Absolutely.
Then I’ll give you one more chance.
Will you marry
the man in front of you
for richer or for poorer,
in sickness and in health?
I will.
Mr. Yin Sichen,
if you’re given another chance,
will you marry the gentle, kind,
and intelligent lady,
Miss Gu, as your wife?
Which Miss Gu are you referring to?
I don’t know her.
Gu Xixi.
Hello, Mom.
I’m coming back.
What?
You’re coming back?
(Intensive Italian Course)
(Get Started With Learning Italian)
What are you doing?
Aren’t these the books
I gave you before we went to Milan
to meet Alex?
Why did you get them out?
Does your mom know about us?
She said she was coming back.
Nothing else.
What? Scared?
Not at all.
I just haven’t met her.
She’s not some kind of monster.
Besides,
I’ll be there for you
if anything goes wrong.
What is she like?
She was very strict with me
when I was a kid.
No tolerance for mistakes.
She arranged everything for me
to her likings.
She likes to have everything in control.
But she loves me very much.
So don’t worry.
She loves you, not me.
I’m here.
I’ll always be there for you.
Look,
I’ve made you like me.
So I’ll make her like me too, right?
Definitely.
By conquering me, you’ve conquered
the whole world.
That’s gross.
Don’t worry.
Mm-hmm.
Why hasn’t Xixi come down?
I’ll go take a look.
Mm-hmm.
If she’s occupied,
tell Madam Song to bring the breakfast
to her room.
OK.
So fat?
I don’t think you’re fat at all.
You scared me.
I think you could
even be a little fatter.
Listen,
there are two creatures in the world
whose abdomen you cannot grope.
One is the cat,
and the other is me.
Then you’re my cat.
Alright.
Come down to eat with me.
I’m not eating.
I had a hard time
having you eat healthily.
And now you’re on a diet?
What kind of power does my mom have?
I can eat fat-free food.
Come downstairs
to have breakfast with me.
Don’t give Madam Song more work.
I’ll watch you eat it
until you finish the last bite.
Go.
Um...
Did you get another wife behind my back?
She...
Is she Gu Xixi?
I’m wondering about it, too.
Maybe the etiquette training
has been delayed for too long.
She hasn’t gotten out of it.
Don’t look at me.
Help yourselves.
You...
Use serving chopsticks.
Are you still Gu Xixi?
If not me, then who?
Then let me ask you.
Where are my figurines?
They’re hidden in the closet.
They’re not hidden.
I put them in the closet for you.
That’s all.
Grandma, don’t laugh at me.
Well,
I love to see you two
quarreling at home.
It’ll be great if you have a baby.
Grandma, you’re so right.
But this is not something
I can do on my own.
Grandma, look at him.
Don’t take his side.
Look at him.
By the way, Sichen.
Can you do me a favor?
Anything for my wife.
I heard your mom likes golf.
So I’m thinking
if you can rent a golf course for me
so I can practice.
Sure.
I’ll have Fei’ang see to it.
You can go practice at any time.
I’ve arranged the golf for you.
Should you put
what Grandma said on agenda?
Enjoy the breakfast. I’ve had enough.
Grandma.
Go on.
Gu Xixi,
you don’t think I’m not trying
hard enough, do you?
I’m full too.
Grandma, wait for me.
Hey!
Grandma.
Why...?
Why are you coming down?
To have a break.
Allow me.
Did Ms. Yang take our offer?
No.
In my opinion,
we could just accept hers.
You never let up
for Yin Sichen.
Why do you go soft on her?
She’s different.
Different?
Well,
you owe her a favor?
How could I owe her anything?
I just want to get it over with
and go on a date with you.
I made a reservation
at a limited Japanese restaurant
3 weeks ago.
Their crispy eel
is unbeatable.
Don’t you want to
spend the night with me?
Alright.
Ms. Yang.
Don’t say anything later.
I’ll take care of her.
Ms. Yang, you’re a real negotiator.
You’ve driven
our profit to the bottom.
I admire you, Miss Mu.
You convinced me in just a few words,
and I have to accept your offer.
Then let’s hope we work well together.
Happy cooperation. Happy cooperation.
Don’t worry, Ms. Yang.
We promise the promotion
will be fantastic.
Well, it’s getting late.
I’ve arranged someone to drive you back.
Let’s say goodbye here.
It’s been long
since the last time we met.
Don’t you want to offer me dinner?
I...
You know each other?
She was a client.
Not just a client.
Mr. Shang owes me a huge favor.
What kind of favor?
She and I...
It’s private.
Is it too much to ask for dinner?
Not at all.
Mr. Shang has booked
a Japanese restaurant.
It’s said their crispy eel
is delicious.
Roasted eel?
My favorite. You remember!
I... Um...
Sorry, this is my boyfriend.
You like him?
I like adorkable men.
Problems?
♪Like a meteor streaks♪
♪The night sky is lit up♪
♪I never want you♪
♪To fall like this♪
♪The road winds♪
♪But light sparkles♪
♪Because love♪
♪Indeed existed♪
♪When it starts all over again♪
♪I won’t shrink back♪
♪You touch my nerve all the time♪
♪Because my heart is blank♪
♪I’m firm but not dramatic♪
♪I just want to give you♪
♪The best of the world♪
♪It’s me who loves you♪
♪The fairy tale is true♪
♪The Achilles’ heel♪
♪Is the soft corner of my heart♪
♪We attract each other♪
♪Simple and stubborn♪
♪It makes your dream more complete♪
♪And makes it tough♪
♪For you and me♪
♪Love breaks the rule♪
♪Because in love we need♪
♪Light and heat from each other♪
♪I protect you quietly♪
♪Leave everything to me♪
♪Turn into the Milky Way♪
♪In my night sky♪
♪You never fall♪