Physical: 100's team match.
Team Nam Kyung-jin
versus Team Jang Eun-sil.
-Let's go!
-Go!
The game will now begin.
-Grab three each.
-Let's go.
Don't get hurt.
Go up.
We may be considered the weakest team,
but we can win.
Bag as much as you can.
I struggled with the sand for 12 minutes.
Go.
I really wanted to win.
Careful.
-Okay.
-Fill it up more.
This is fun!
Let's do this!
Kyung-jin is really strong.
Move them quickly.
We're definitely going to win.
How could we lose?
Go!
One minute left.
Quickly!
Let's make one more trip.
Last one!
Damn it.
Forty-five seconds!
Slowly.
Game over.
Physical: 100's second quest.
Team Nam Kyung-jin…
versus Team Jang Eun-sil.
Please!
It'll be an utterly perfect win.
I want to prove that we are stronger.
I wanted our team to win,
and I wanted to help us win.
Whoever we took on,
I was sure we could win.
Let's win. There's no way we'll lose.
The winning team is…
We won!
We did it!
Well done!
TEAM JANG EUN-SIL
TEAM NAM KYUNG-JIN
-I told you we could do it!
-We did it.
-We actually did it.
-We won.
-We did it!
-I knew we'd win.
-Good job.
Everyone thought our team was the weakest.
It was a revolt of the underdogs.
My teammates all did so well.
I ended up letting them
carry me through this game.
You told us to get ready to go home.
You can pack up your stuff and go on home.
It's okay.
It's over.
We did it.
Is this for real?
We lost to the team we chose
thinking they were the weakest,
so it was quite upsetting.
After setting up the bridge,
I should have moved more quickly
to help move the sand.
I think that's the biggest reason we lost.
That makes it even more upsetting.
Losing is…
something I don't even
want to think about.
But we lost.
As the team leader, I feel terrible.
If only I had moved one more bag,
we would have won.
But since Jang Eun-sil,
my fellow wrestler, won,
wrestlers will get more of a spotlight.
If she stays hungry for the win,
I think she might win this competition.
I hope she does, and I'll root for her.
TEAM JANG EUN-SIL
PHYSICAL: 100
THE UNINVITED GUESTS
TEAM KIM SANG-WOOK VS TEAM MA SUN-HO
Some may disagree,
but I thought we might be
the strongest team.
Kim Kang-min,
KIM KANG-MIN
BODYBUILDER
Song A-reum,
SONG A-REUM
BODYBUILDER
Miracle,
MIRACLE
DANCER
Jeong Han-saem.
JEONG HAN-SAEM
MUSICAL ACTOR
Overall, they're quite strong.
They have good strength and endurance.
When comparing the strengths
of individual members,
my team definitely had the upper hand.
I don't think that's right.
I really don't.
I believe we have the advantage
over the guys on the other team.
I mean, we have a few MMA fighters.
KIM SANG-WOOK
JOO DONG-JO
OVAN
When it comes to tasks
that require stamina or speed,
I thought we were much stronger than them.
Let's go.
So it involves climbing stairs.
I'm confident at climbing stairs.
Be careful not to fall.
There's a bridge.
-We have to build a bridge?
-So we have to build this?
A good strategy will be the key here.
We have to plan really well.
There was just half a bridge.
Do we have to walk on the ropes?
The first thing I checked out was
the height that we might fall from.
I was a bit worried.
When I first saw it,
I found it very interesting.
But I still couldn't figure out
what the challenge was.
Physical: 100's team match.
-Do you get it?
-The second quest will now be revealed.
The second quest is…
"Moving Sand."
Both teams must cross the bridges
and fill the tube with sand.
We'll win this.
OVAN
SINGER
If the bridge sways,
it's a mission that requires
a good sense of balance.
We would do much better than them.
It's not just about strength.
It requires overall agility and balance.
My mind was suddenly racing.
How should I distribute the tasks?
What should be our strategy?
You go down and keep bagging sand.
You and I should
install the bridge quickly.
I think that'll be best.
We'll build the bridge.
I immediately thought I could do well.
That I should put the bridge together.
As soon as we start, you two run down.
-There's only a few planks.
-Right.
-Bring them all up and build the bridge.
-Okay.
While they do that,
the three of us can bag the sand.
First…
While he builds the bridge,
we bag the sand and get ready to come up.
-As soon as Dong-jo builds it, we will…
-You want me to build the bridge?
-I think that would be best.
-Got it.
-While you do that…
-I'll try.
Physical: 100's second quest.
Losing is not an option.
We'll win at all costs.
We're determined to survive at all costs.
We have to win today's mission.
Team Kim Sang-wook…
I want to win this competition.
… versus Team Ma Sun-ho.
I feel bad for them,
but I think it's only right that we win.
The game will now begin.
-Careful. Be safe.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
Don't overdo it. Take it easy.
Keep your pace.
Let's do as much as we can.
The team to build
the bridge first will win.
We have to win.
Dong-jo, I'll put them right behind you.
Just hand them over right away.
-What?
-Just hand them to me.
Let's go.
Damn it.
Are they heavy?
-They are.
-He says they are.
It's okay. Don't even look.
Dong-jo has good balance
since he's smaller,
so I asked him to build it
as fast as he could.
Good.
-Hand them over with the velcro off.
-I will.
Bring more planks.
Keep them coming. Quickly.
My job is to build the bridge.
If everyone does their job properly,
that team will definitely win.
Quickly.
I was in too much of a rush,
and I started making mistakes.
I need help with the planks.
It's okay.
Undo the velcro on the back of the planks.
-No more planks!
-I'm right behind you.
No more planks!
TEAM MA SUN-HO'S BRIDGE IS COMPLETE
You got this.
-Done.
-Quickly.
Okay, move.
Move.
Let's go!
TEAM MA SUN-HO
It's shaking.
It's okay.
-We're doing well.
-Damn it.
-Careful.
-Sang-wook, we have to go quickly.
Hurry.
I think the other team's bridge
was completed first.
I felt very rushed,
but it was too early to say.
We could still turn the tables.
It's almost done.
Careful.
TEAM KIM SANG-WOOK'S BRIDGE IS COMPLETE
You have to bring back the bags.
TEAM KIM SANG-WOOK
What about this one?
Give it to us and we'll fill it.
Damn it. Sang-wook.
Slowly.
The bridge moved a lot,
so it was difficult.
Careful.
I was a bit slow
building the bridge in the beginning.
I thought I could make up for it
if I ran harder.
Bring back the bags.
Throw it.
He's here. You go first.
The bags.
You have to bring back the bag.
Nice.
Careful. Go ahead.
I'll hold the bridge steady.
Go.
Careful.
We'll win.
Take it slow. Don't rush yourselves.
Both my teammates and I were
faster than the other team
in climbing the stairs
and crossing the bridge.
Let's show them
what we MMA fighters can do.
We have to move these two faster!
A little faster.
We worked really hard.
-There's more behind you.
-I thought we would win.
-Let's fill the big one.
-Okay.
Honey, come here and fill this.
I was completely fired up.
I couldn't lose there.
The big one.
Give me one more.
When it came to strength,
I thought my team was superior.
Han-saem. Move!
-Okay.
-Move.
This is fine.
Safety is important right now.
You can really fall down now.
Don't run into each other.
Let's go.
Let's keep it up. We got this.
I thought we'd won.
I was confident we'd never lose.
We came a long way to get here.
We have to survive.
Good. Go this way.
You got this!
-Go.
-Let's go!
There are many variables in a team match,
so there's no absolute overdog
or underdog.
One minute left.
One minute left!
-It's the last run!
-The last!
Come on! You got this!
Seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
Game over.
Everything was difficult.
You can't play this game
if you don't have a lot of stamina.
I think I got tired
from the moment it started.
Keeping my balance and
crossing the bridge was very difficult.
What a well-made game!
I mean it.
This is crazy. I never imagined this.
You did so well.
Well done. We won.
-Well done, Sang-wook.
-Good job.
-Well done.
Are you okay?
Physical: 100's second quest.
Out of the two teams,
the winning team will survive,
and the losing team's bridge will break,
and the team leader will fall.
I'm going to fall?
No, it's okay.
You won't fall.
We lost.
Now,
The winners…
will now be announced.
I really couldn't guess who would win.
I'm sorry, but we'll take the win.
Physical: 100's second quest.
Team Kim Sang-wook…
versus Team Ma Sun-ho.
The winning team is…
Please.
I really want to win,
and I want to show a good outcome.
TEAM MA SUN-HO
TEAM KIM SANG-WOOK
It was so thrilling.
I didn't know I'd be so happy.
It was a magnificent victory.
Wait, let me…
While completing the quest,
even though it was super chaotic,
I saw the face
of each and every team member.
My teammates did their best,
and I can't thank them enough.
Good game.
-Good game.
-You too.
I felt mostly disappointed.
I was too slow to build the bridge.
It's a shame.
-Good work.
-We were the best.
-Well done.
Good effort. We were the best.
It's not that I didn't believe in my team.
I didn't believe in myself.
It was my strategy
that wasn't good enough, not the team.
TEAM MA SUN-HO
TEAM YUN SUNG-BIN VS TEAM JANG SEONG-MIN
TEAM LEADER YUN SUNG-BIN
-Let's do this.
-Let's move on.
TEAM LEADER JANG SEONG-MIN
-Let's go.
Jang Seong-min's team.
Me?
Let's go!
I was going to pick yours, so thank you.
-Feisty!
-Good one!
Obviously, it's important that we win,
but I wanted to pick a team
that we could have a fun game with.
The last one?
The last team has three women.
The team with Yang Hak-seon
and Park Hyung-geun.
-They have three women and only two men.
-Yes.
But I don't think the second to last team
has great members either.
-Jang Seong-min's team?
-You have a point.
Let's just pick them.
Should we really pick that team?
I was slightly unsure
because he was on the national rugby team.
He has strength and agility,
so it was a bit intimidating.
When Yun Sung-bin picked us,
it hurt my pride so much,
so I really wanted to win,
and I wanted to beat him.
He must have underestimated us.
I thought it was for the better.
We have a rugby player, a fencer,
and a CrossFitter who owns a gym.
I thought we had an advantage.
-Let's kill them for real, okay?
-Let's kill them.
-Let's kill them!
Let's kill them.
I didn't care who I was up against.
I just wanted to have fun.
What will the game be?
-Let's do this!
What is all this?
-Sand.
-What's this?
-There's sand.
What is this?
What is all this?
The high staircase and mounds of sand.
It's carrying sand.
If it's about moving it without rest,
we're at an advantage.
Right.
-I think we have much better stamina.
-Yes.
-We do.
-I think
if we build the bridge faster, we can win.
I think we have better stamina.
I thought the game itself was favorable.
I had high expectations.
We should win this for sure.
-This is the last game, damn it.
-Let's focus.
Win this, and we'll win the competition.
It's basically about building a bridge
and moving sand across it.
It's shakier than you think.
If you fall, it's done.
-It's harder to control than you think.
-And there are five of us.
I thought we had it over them overall.
Speed, stamina, power…
I thought we all had
a good balance of those traits.
So I thought it would be
an easy win for our team.
I thought we'd absolutely win.
Because we obviously had it over them.
You could see that at a glance.
Physical: 100.
Team Yun Sung-bin…
If there's no accident or mistake,
there should be no problem.
…versus Team Jang Seong-min.
Our pride is at stake, so we can't lose.
I'll make them realize
they made the wrong choice.
The game…
will now begin.
-Go.
-Don't rush. Slowly.
-Do you want to put those on here?
-No, I'm fine.
It's going smoothly.
To build the bridge quickly,
a minimal number of people
brought up the planks.
And while one person built the bridge
as fast as possible,
the rest bagged the sand.
This is good. Let's go.
We thought it would require cooperation
more than individual capabilities,
so two of us worked on the bridge
while two bagged the sand.
Let's go. Nice.
How's it going up there?
I can't see from here.
I'll go and see.
Shouldn't we just ask?
He's going already?
Good.
It was a bit of a variable.
It took much longer than I thought
for one person to build the bridge,
so I got a little anxious.
Thank you.
We're almost there.
Go.
-Move.
-Go!
-Sung-bin, two planks!
-Let's go.
-Go.
Move.
Good.
Pour it quickly.
-Pour it quick.
-We're leading.
When I looked over to our opponents,
they looked discouraged.
I thought we would definitely win.
Good.
We'll win. Keep going!
Keep going!
Good.
We're leading.
Look ahead.
If I mess up here,
I could screw over my team.
To be honest, I felt pretty anxious.
I was surprised.
We finished the bridge first,
and I thought it was well-made.
I felt a bit dejected.
-Nice
-It's okay.
I thought I taped them tightly.
I was pleased.
I thought we could make up for the delay.
Sung-bin, two planks!
Two planks.
Let's go across. Let's go!
Go.
-We need more.
-One at a time.
Hey!
You can come.
It's okay, come.
Slowly, a little slower.
We can't run too hard.
-One by one.
-Almost there.
Quickly, good.
Don't run.
-Walk one at a time.
-I'll go slowly.
Slowly.
-One at a time. Go slowly.
-Steadily.
-Nice.
-Let's go.
-I'll go slowly.
-Okay.
There's time.
We're leading.
Don't run.
Things seemed kind of confusing at first,
but after that, I emptied my head
and decided to just do my best.
I'll just do my part.
Come.
Take those.
The man with the crazy physique,
Yun Sung-bin.
I could see how strong he was
in terms of willpower
as well as physical competence.
Let's go.
Pack the sand faster!
Let's go!
Don't give up! Keep going!
-Hey, this is dangerous.
-Just go.
When the siren went off
to tell us that we had three minutes,
I thought, "12 minutes went by so fast."
That's when I felt a bit rushed.
Just come.
We can't do anything about that.
It's dangerous. Be careful.
It's okay.
I'm coming.
Come quickly.
-Go first.
-Just jump over this.
It's okay, I'll make it.
Two minutes and twenty seconds!
-Okay, nice.
-Let's cross.
-Let's do this!
-We got this!
Damn it.
-Give it to me.
-Go quickly.
Keep going!
Don't give up!
Let's go.
-One minute!
-There's only one minute left!
Fill them all up.
Only one minute left!
-We're almost there.
-Just fill them all up.
-Only one minute left!
-We're almost there.
Forty-five seconds.
Hey, we have 40 seconds.
Let's go all at once.
-Quickly.
-Let's go.
-Take these.
-Go.
This is the last one. Let's go.
Thirty seconds left.
Thirty seconds!
Let's go once more.
We have to go now.
Let's go together.
Don't come, stay there.
We got this.
Ten seconds.
-Move.
-Run.
-Go now.
-Five.
-Quickly.
-Four.
-Run!
-Three.
Two.
-Nice!
-Game over.
-All right.
-We won!
We won. 100 percent.
We can't lose.
Once it was over,
I was relieved because I was exhausted.
Forget winning or losing.
I was just happy it was over.
That was good cardio.
Good job. You did a lot of running.
It took us a while to bag the sand.
It's okay. We did our best.
Are you okay, Seong-min?
It was kind of like
when I played in the playground as a kid.
Both teams worked hard, and I liked that.
I had a lot of fun.
Physical: 100's second quest.
The winning team will now be revealed.
Team Yun Sung-bin
versus Team Jang Seong-min.
The winning team is…
We all worked together,
and I think we moved faster.
We got off to a good start,
so I think we're the winners.
-Well done.
-Good job.
-I thought we actually lost.
-I was so damn scared.
-We worked really hard.
-We really did.
We did well.
To be honest, I thought we'd win.
We lost by a really small margin.
If I had made one more trip,
it could have ended differently.
I feel bad about that.
First of all, congratulations.
I hope you finish the remaining missions
without injuries.
I'll root for you from afar.
This is heartbreaking.
TEAM YUN SUNG-BIN
TEAM CHOO SUNG-HOON VS TEAM TARZAN
I like this kind of tension.
It's true that we're more vigorous.
I came here to succeed.
I'm here to be number one.
They've already made it.
They're already stable.
We're all young.
-They're not desperate.
-But we are.
I was really determined to win.
I'm still hungry for more.
They are younger,
so they may have better stamina,
but we have a lot of experience
in various contexts.
We'll need to use our brains.
This is where the battle of wits begins.
Let's say the game's started.
And for instance,
-the team that gets more small balls wins.
-That could be it.
If it's something of that sort,
don't get too greedy and bring too many.
Put your greed aside.
We must move fast.
It's very likely
that it'll be something like that.
At least in my opinion.
I was looking for a way to win somehow.
I felt like there was a 50-50 chance,
so I kept an eye out.
Physical: 100's team match.
The second quest will now be revealed.
The second quest is
"Moving Sand."
We have to move individually.
Should the lighter person go?
It has to be fixed. Who should do this?
-Jeong-yun and I will do it.
-Two people set it up.
The three of us should bag the sand.
-We'll pile them up.
-Yes.
Physical: 100's second quest.
Team Choo Sung-hoon…
versus Team Tarzan.
The game…
will now begin.
Let's go.
My team's strength
is that we're all young
and have a great fighting spirit.
I was sure we could win
as long as we move quickly
and do our jobs properly.
Leave it and go.
-I'll put them right behind you.
-Okay.
Don't move. You can do this, right?
-Yes.
-Go slowly.
I tried to build the bridge faster
than the other team.
It'll be hard to carry if it's too heavy.
Bring as much sand as you can
to the top of the stairs.
That was my plan.
Seong-hyeok, lift one side.
No, it needs more sand.
No, let's go as is.
You have to carry one in each hand. Wait.
Wait…
Is it too heavy?
-Should I take some out?
-This is so heavy.
Where is it?
Is it done? Is it taking a while?
-Just a second.
-Should I wait?
Can I come through now?
Is this it?
Don't rush. Make it sturdy.
-Hang on, I'll go by slowly.
-Okay.
We should stay on our toes.
Is it done?
Careful.
Is it done? Wait, the sand…
TEAM CHOO SUNG-HOON
I was worried.
I felt a little anxious.
-I'll bring some more.
-Okay.
-Go, Seong-hyeok.
-Go.
Is it done? Wait, the sand…
BANG SEONG-HYEOK
TRAINER
I felt a little uneasy.
Careful, be calm.
To be honest,
since Seong-hyeok is quite big,
I expected it could be a problem.
It could be dangerous for him.
Go on.
Go.
Is it done?
One is mine up there, so wait.
One is mine.
As long as we move quickly
and do our jobs properly…
-Coming through.
-Yes, go through.
-Sorry, sit.
-Yes, go on.
Go on.
Crap, what was that?
The ones in the back fell.
It was a little scary.
Go.
There's no sand.
Awesome.
NIPPERT
BASEBALL PLAYER
Choo Sung-hoon thought
really quickly on his feet.
Crawling on my knees didn't look so great,
but if I ran, the planks would fall.
So moving like a baby was
much faster and less scary.
Let me get this out of your way.
-Take it.
Hey.
I felt rushed and I ran,
but then the bridge fell apart.
They fell off.
So I thought, "No, this is bad."
Without the bridge, we couldn't move sand,
so we filled in the holes one by one.
We fixed the bridge on the spot.
Quickly.
I'm coming.
-Got it.
-Don't jump.
You're rushing.
Yes, right.
Wrap the opening.
Stay calm. Go.
We can do this!
What the hell?
Three minutes.
Hey, you can't pour in sand anymore.
We have to go.
Tarzan, we have to go. It's not over.
I didn't understand the rules completely.
He thought it was over.
So I said, "No, Tarzan, it's not over."
I got a little flustered because of that.
Here, one more.
This one.
Use the pink bag.
-Only use the pink bag.
-Got it.
If this is done, go ahead.
-Hey, take the full ones.
-We don't have any.
Here's two.
-Give it to me.
-You can take these.
"We can't give up."
I kept telling myself that we could win.
-One minute.
-One minute left.
Let's do our best to the end.
Let's go!
A bit more. It's better to take this one.
No.
We have to play
like our lives depend on it.
Like our lives depend on it.
We need to bag more.
Don't rush.
Thirteen seconds, twelve.
Bag this one.
-Just this one.
-Ten seconds.
It's okay. Ten seconds.
A bit more.
Four, three, two.
-It's done.
-One.
It's over.
All right.
Well done!
At the end, with three seconds left,
he crossed the bridge
with three big steps.
I was surprised at the end.
I want us to win.
-Well done.
-Good job.
Well done.
Damn it.
Now that it's over, it's scarier.
We won, completely.
-Good job sticking to the plan.
-Yes.
My team did really well.
Like I said earlier, it was 50-50.
but the longer we played,
the higher our chances got.
Everyone on my team did their job
as best they could, and I'm grateful.
And I think our chance
of winning is 80 percent.
Physical: 100's second quest.
Team Choo Sung-hoon versus Team Tarzan.
The winning team is…
Wouldn't we naturally win
unless we did something too drastic?
I think our teamwork was perfect.
The winning team is…
-Good effort.
-Well played.
You all did well.
I think it was a sweeping victory.
TEAM CHOO SUNG-HOON
TEAM TARZAN
We got off to a good start
and made up
for each other's small mistakes.
I think that's why we won.
They trusted me one hundred percent
and followed my lead.
I'm so thankful for that.
I'll treat you all to a nice meal.
I just feel so bad.
I want to say I did my best, but I…
But I don't think I tried hard enough.
TEAM CHOO SUNG-HOON
TEAM JO JIN-HYEONG VS TEAM KWAK MYUNG-SIK
I think they underestimated us,
and I don't care for that.
You chose the wrong people.
They looked like easy opponents.
That's what we thought.
It won't be easy to beat us.
Physical: 100's second quest.
Team Kwak Myung-sik
versus Team Jo Jin-hyeong.
The game will now begin.
We all came here to win,
but the winner will be
Team Kwak Myung-sik.
You might have thought
our team would be easy to beat,
but you'll regret your choice.
JUNG HAE-MIN
CYCLIST
Let's go.
-Let's go!
-Let's do this!
Go straight up.
Shall we do the big ones first?
What's this?
This is…
What is this?
This is hard. This is difficult.
Go. Take this.
Carry them like this.
I was building the bridge,
and things were going well at first.
I thought I would finish the bridge first.
The opposing team was ahead of us,
and I felt nervous.
But working as a stuntwoman,
I learned a huge lesson about safety.
I thought that even if we lose,
we shouldn't get hurt.
So I tried to build it very thoroughly.
-Do you need more, Han?
-No, it's okay.
-I think we can go.
-Wait, one more.
Hey, tell them to come up!
Go.
TEAM KWAK MYUNG-SIK BRIDGE IS COMPLETE
Move aside.
Man, it's shaky.
Careful.
-The velcro came off.
-Careful.
TEAM KWAK MYUNG-SIK
-Leave it and go.
-Is it done?
Yes, leave it and go.
-Jin-hyeong, do I go up?
-Yes, go up.
-Are you going?
-Yes. Please go.
-Safely.
-Please go.
-Move aside.
-This is dangerous.
Slowly.
Careful.
Be careful.
This shakes much more than you think.
Wait.
Damn.
TEAM LEADER JO JIN-HYEONG
CAR DEALER
I shouldn't have eaten breakfast.
I hadn't gotten the feel of the game.
I was a little flustered then,
to be honest.
Hey, I'll fill the sacks.
Nice, we're doing well.
Let's go.
I'll go first.
Come on.
Come through.
We should cross one at a time.
It's too shaky.
Hey, move.
Gosh.
-We have to fix this properly.
-We should do it again.
-Fix it first.
-Do one plank.
I should have set up the bridge better.
Frankly, I was annoyed.
-Let's go!
-You can do it.
You got this!
Just go.
Hey, these…
They're falling down. They fell down.
My heart sank with a thud.
I felt really bad about that.
We tried to do well,
but we focused so much
on laying down the bridge quickly
that we didn't think of the fact
that the planks might fall.
Hold on.
I think we should fix this up first.
I looked at our opponents.
We were all running across,
and they were stuck.
Da-young had fixed our planks so well
that they didn't come loose once.
So that's when I started to think,
"I think we could win."
Go up.
-Go up again.
-I'm coming!
No, not this.
We should stop
spending time on this and just do it.
Let's do it.
I got really competitive.
We have to just persevere.
Do it as if our lives depend on it.
We can do it!
-Let's go!
-Damn.
Move.
Damn it.
Three minutes!
Quick.
What was that?
-This isn't tiring at all.
-Not at all!
We're almost done.
Nice, Hae-min.
-Third place in strong man!
-You're amazing!
There you go. You're Jung Hae-min!
Let's go!
-Yes, go quickly!
-Go, Hae-min!
Keep them coming. I'll keep coming back.
-We have to do it together.
-I'm not tired yet.
If you're tired, bag the sand.
-Okay.
-You can't rest.
-I'll bring four at a time.
-It's okay.
It's 50-50.
If we win, we survive.
If we lose, we're done.
So let's survive and go all the way.
Thirty seconds.
You have to go.
-Take two each.
-Okay.
Go slowly, it's the last run.
Cross the bridge.
-Slowly.
-It's the last one.
-It's the last run anyway.
-Right. Go slow.
-We have to take these.
-Slowly!
-Yes, take it slow!
-We got this!
-Just go, ten seconds!
-Move.
You have to come quickly.
Ten, nine, six…
-Han's the last one.
-Big bag first.
Dust off all the bags!
Dust them off.
Is it over?
Game over.
I feel like we did well.
Well done.
-Well done.
-Good job.
-We did it.
-Good job, Da-young.
The game was 12 minutes long.
While we were doing it,
it was really hard work,
but once it was over,
I regretted not trying harder.
-Da-young was awesome.
-I did well, right?
This part was shaky,
but the rest was sturdy.
I had a good feeling about you
from the moment you joined our team.
You set it up so well.
-It was amazing.
-How did we not lose a single plank?
-You just have to be thorough.
-That was seriously awesome.
Physical: 100's second quest.
Team Kwak Myung-sik…
versus Team Jo Jin-hyeong.
The winning team is…
Good job.
TEAM JO JIN-HYEONG
TEAM KWAK MYUNG-SIK
TEAM YUN SUNG-BIN
TEAM CHOO SUNG-HOON
TEAM MA SUN-HO
TEAM JO JIN-HYEONG
TEAM JANG EUN-SIL
Nice.
-The winners get to relax.
I survived again
and got to return to this space.
It felt different to be a winner again
and go back there.
I thought that if I kept doing well,
I could even make it into the top ten.
I'm kind of hopeful
that I could even win the competition.
I hope one of us wins it.
That would be great.
There are definitely much fewer people.
Seventy-five have been eliminated.
Twenty-five left out of a hundred.
CHA HYUN-SEUNG
DANCER
Did you think we'd survive? Be honest.
-Honestly, sorry.
-Right?
I was surprised
that Jang Eun-sil's team won.
We all thought they'd lose
no matter which team they went against.
I was really surprised by your team.
We're writing a real-life drama over here.
Okay. Excuse me, everyone.
I see you're having jovial conversations
with your teammates.
We have a show host here.
-What a smooth host.
-He's a show host.
I think it would be nice
to warm up with a game.
First off, the Sargent jump.
It's elementary.
This isn't a team event.
Think of it as an activity
to show off your basic abilities.
Who here thinks they can do this well?
"I think I can beat this person."
All right.
-Don't be shy.
-Me?
Jump. Just land on top.
Okay, just take turns and show us…
What was that?
I was really surprised.
-Shall we all take turns?
-Let's.
Come on out. Just give it a go.
Come on, everyone. It's no big deal.
Come on over, everyone.
Nippert.
Unless you've had bad experiences
with this, everyone take turns.
Okay, nice.
-Very good.
-What if I can't do it?
If you can't… Nice.
It would be funny
if someone couldn't do it.
Yes, good.
You missed your chance to be funny.
Okay, very nice.
Good.
It seems easy for everyone.
-Let's make it a bit higher.
-I'll help you.
Okay, shall we start off with this much?
5 MATS ADDED
CURRENT HEIGHT 64CM
Come on, you have to add more.
No one wants to try?
You think this height is nothing?
Okay.
Let's move on.
It's getting higher.
5 MATS ADDED
CURRENT HEIGHT 74CM
CURRENT HEIGHT 84CM
-Is that even doable?
-This will do.
It's high now.
This is high.
It's a battle now.
Anyone who thinks
they can do it can come up.
-Okay.
-Iron Man can do it.
I knew that Yun Sung-bin
had a great Sargent jump record.
South Korea's…
-He got up there standing.
-He was just standing.
-He didn't even bend his knees.
-Who wants to challenge Iron Man?
Well?
Kang-min's good at this.
Nice, it's Kang-min Man.
That was light.
Physical: 100!
Ki-kwan Man.
-Ki-kwan Man?
-"Ki-kwan Man."
This is high.
It's almost at my chest. I can't do this.
It's quite high now.
-They're good.
-Ki-kwan Man!
Add 40cm.
Add a lot of them.
Hang on. It's so much higher.
-How many mats did you put?
-How do you jump onto that?
Okay, let's stop here. We'll give it a go.
I can't do this.
I should sit down now.
I'll give it a go.
-Kang-min.
-Okay.
-It's quite high now, Kang-min.
-Hang on.
He's surprised.
This is…
It is a bit high.
-Give it a go.
-Here I go.
My legs are my strongest body parts.
He has a nice spring.
You're cute.
It's high, though.
Ki-kwan Man.
This is no joke.
I expect to be the first to fail.
"The first to fail is…"
Ki-kwan Man.
I barely made it.
-"Who will be the first to be eliminated?"
-It is quite high.
"The two teams will now be…"
That was really awesome.
He's amazing.
-How do you do this?
-How is that possible?
He's really Iron Man.
He goes up like this.
I think he can jump on the whole stack.
-We'll find the last man standing.
-Let's make it serious.
The last man standing.
Okay, Iron Man.
Iron Man's got to show us.
It's really high.
A round of applause for Iron Man.
-You have to raise it by 20cm.
-What is that?
Is he a monster?
You could add all of them on top.
There are springs right here.
He has springs in his ankles.
-Add some more.
-We'll add more.
This is really…
It's as tall as Da-young.
This is high.
-He couldn't do this.
-There's no way he can.
Now it's tough.
Let's cheer for Yun Sung-bin.
Go, Yun Sung-bin.
-Yun Sung-bin.
-It's doable.
-It's really high.
-This is unheard of.
This is really high.
I'm too scared to jump.
I think he can do it.
-It was crazy earlier.
-He'll make it.
I think he'll make it.
But it's really high.
Be careful.
That's crazy.
He's amazing.
That wasn't easy.
His physique is no joke.
As a fellow athlete,
I thought he was really nimble.
If we were to become enemies,
it would be really tough.
Okay. We have a second game prepared.
It's thigh wrestling!
MINI GAME: 2
THIGH WRESTLING
Our everlasting star.
Our hero we all respect.
Choo Sung-hoon!
Then the person I think
is the strongest here is…
JO JIN-HYEONG
CAR DEALER
I'd like to challenge him.
I'm not that strong.
-How much do you think he weighs?
-How much do you weigh?
I weigh 127kg.
How much do you weigh?
-I weigh 90kg.
-Right.
-Okay, 90kg versus 127kg.
-Wow. 90?
Choo Sung-hoon has never seemed so small.
-My knees go inside.
-Yes.
-And open.
-I'll shut mine.
-Okay.
-And then…
Relax.
How about a round of applause?
Ready.
Go!
You little…
Come on.
He's so freaking strong.
"Freaking."
I mean, it felt…
I felt good.
Pure strength is different from fighting.
Okay, that concludes the warm-up.
Now the real games will begin.
-Good luck!
Let's do this.
We're back here.
So many disappeared.
It's down to just a few.
There aren't many left.
So many people are gone.
There are still 24 other people.
I don't feel great about that.
What do we do here?
Right?
I didn't know what kind of game
we were going to play there,
so I was as nervous as I was excited.
What could it be?
I hope they tell us.
Physical: 100.
What the heck?
It's blabbering.
After the second quest,
there are 25 remaining contestants.
Those of you who survived
the fierce competition, welcome back.
Before the third quest begins,
an important fact will be revealed.
What is it?
-It's important?
-Important?
Besides the contestants standing here,
there are additional survivors
who will participate…
-What?
…in the next quest.
Additional?
How did they survive?
Why would they bring them back?
I don't get it.
The consolation match came too soon.
We worked so hard to eliminate them.
Why bring them back?
-They're tenacious.
-Yes.
They'll do anything to survive.
-It's unbelievable.
-I got goosebumps.
The five additional survivors,
please come in.
Oh, dear.
No way!
-What is this?
-This is crazy.
This is crazy!
I got goosebumps.
I got goosebumps too.
So they're the survivors.
How did they survive? I'm so curious.
Subtitle translation by: You-jin Lim