According to the police,
whoever this Marie Armani is,
their prime suspect is Shari.
She’s going to jail.
Good.
I want them to arrest Shari on the
same day as the showdown,
[VELMA] for the whole world to see.
Maybe it’s better for Shari
to go into hiding for now.
[SHARI] Sylvester.
The Imperials are planning
to have you arrested during the event.
Wait.
So why are you telling her?
[SHARI] I am your boss.
We don’t have time for this.
You need to go into hiding, Shari.
They are expecting me at the event!
We’ll make it look like you’re attending,
[NOREEN] and that’s when
we’ll reveal everything.
[NOREEN] We would like to
call to the stage the woman of the hour.
Miss Velma Imperial!
[EVERYONE CLAPPING]
[KRISELDA] She’s not supposed to be there.
She’s not part of the program.
[NOREE] Everyone, get your cameras ready!
[NOREEN] This revelation is
all about Velma Imperial.
Play the video.
[SYLVESTER] Play it.
[ON VIDEO] It’s me, Shari.
What’s happening?
[SHARI] Let’s apply primer
while I tell you the truth and nothing
but the truth about the cruelty of the Imperials.
Stop this video now!
[VELMA] Go home!
[NOREEN] Nobody goes home!
Velma Imperial murdered Helena Alfonso
after finding out that her husband,
Eddie Imperial, had raped
Helena, my sister!
[JANA] Noreen might be in
danger because of what happened.
[NOREEN] Now, I’ll make sure
you rot in jail where you belong!
Let’s put an end to this already.
Don’t you dare touch me.
[CHARING] We see Noreen
more than just a neighbor.
We’re her family.
[GARDO] A family that
cares for her, protects her,
and loves her even though
she’s not related to us by blood.
[GANDA GANDAHAN BY DIA MATÉ PLAYING]
We are prepared to do everything
to protect Noreen from anyone
who wants to hurt her.
We don’t want to see Noreen crying.
[JANA] Every tear Noreen
sheds has a consequent slap
and hair-pulling.
And if she starts crying,
punches and kicks are
going to come from me.
Why are you looking at me that way?
Because I am warning you, girl.
The moment you hurt Noreen,
I will come after you.
Don’t worry.
You can pick from the choices I said earlier.
This is a special offer.
Just for you.
Jana.
[NOREEN] No matter how many times you
try to wash your hands of what you did to my sister,
you will never wipe her
blood off your hands!
[WAILS]
You ungrateful little witch!
[VELMA SCREAMS]
[NOREEN GRUINTS FROM PAIN]
[ALEX] Are you okay?
[EDDIE WHISPERS] We’re supposed
to be the victims, right?
[EDDIE] Please.
Relax.
Let’s go.
Ladies and gentlemen, please.
Thank you so much for coming,
but the show is over.
Exits are over there.
Leave!
Please make your way to the exits!
[KRISELDA] Everybody, please, this way.
I’m so sorry.
[WHISPERS] Are you okay?
[GARDO] Jana, that’s enough.
That’s too much.
She’s also going through difficulties.
No.
I don’t trust this woman at all.
She became one of Velma Imperial’s minions.
Then she stole Noreen’s serum.
For all I know, she might have a hidden
agenda for suddenly switching sides
and siding with Noreen.
I’m just protecting my friend.
I gave up everything.
My career, my reputation,
my life,
to make up for all the wrongs
I’ve done to Noreen.
I’m not just doing this for Noreen,
I am also doing this for myself.
Girl, I may not have finished my studies,
but I understood what you just said.
Don’t hit me with those
Miss Universe answers,
because you're not even in my top five.
Try switching sides,
and you’ll find out real quick that
I’m an expert at crushing and
biting back at two-faced traitors.
Biting back at two-faced traitors.
[JANA HITS THE TABLE]
Understood?
[GARDO] Jana.
[CHARING] Jana. Calm down.
Calm down.
We have to go.
I need to go home.
I need to make sure that my mother’s safe.
And maybe, you need to go home, too.
You just exposed yourself to them.
[MIGOY ON TEXT] Just arrived.
- Migoy is already outside.
- [MIGOY ON TEXT] Are you and Noreen on your way out?
Go, he will take you home.
What about you?
I need to stay.
I know that Eddie and Velma are up to something.
And I want to find out what it is.
I will call you later.
[SIGHS]
Alex, you don’t need to get yourself
involved with my problems.
It’s too dangerous.
Noreen, you mean so much to me.
And I really want to help you.
You really don’t want to listen to me.
You’re so stubborn.
I don’t want to put you in danger, Alex.
So please, can you just go home?
[IN KOREAN]
I am ready to do everything
I can to protect and help you.
You will find out why later.
So just trust me.
[IN ENGLISH] Migoy is waiting.
Wish me luck.
I did not kill Helena!
You know that!
I am innocent!
How dare they!
Hon-
They destroyed me!
You have to calm down!
Calm down?
They tarnished our name in
front of the whole world!
It’s because you
foughtwith Noreen!
Your inability to control your emotions is
precisely why were in this situation.
We need solutions, hon.
So, please.
I need you to calm down.
Do you have any idea how
we can clean up our name?
I do.
By you telling the truth!
How many people have told me
about you assaulting Helena.
That’s why I’m going to ask you one last time,
and you better tell me the truth!
Did you do that?
No, I did not.
They’re all lies, Velma.
Designed to destroy us.
Tell me the truth!
This is the truth!
Velma, we’re both victims
of their defamation!
I’m your husband!
Why won’t you listen to me?
Why won’t you believe in me?
I didn’t do anything wrong,
I didn’t do anything to her.
Velma, believe me.
Please.
We made a vow to protect each other.
To support each other, no matter what.
No one could destroy us.
Especially, not that Noreen.
She is the true enemy.
I will only calm down if I get to talk to Shari.
Migoy.
Noreen, are you alright?
Dad sent me here.
He’s worried about you.
Where’s Alex?
He chose to stay.
He said I should trust him in
what he’s about to do.
I’m scared, Migoy.
He might be in danger.
Alright. For now let's go
back to Ahon Pinay, first.
Ma’am Eva is waiting for you.
I will return here for Alex.
Alright.
Boss, Noreen already left.
We need to talk about my new plans.
Copy, Boss.
[CHARING] Are you alright, Noreen?
Yes, Ma’am Charing.
But we need to be cautious.
For now, they haven’t realized yet that
we’ve been hiding out here in Ahon Pinay.
But sooner or later,
they’d be able to find out.
Migoy, what about Alex?
Gino, please take care of Noreen.
I will help Alex in his own investigation.
It’s better for us to find more
evidence against the Imperials.
Migoy.
Take care, my son.
Mom, listen to me.
You can’t get out of this place.
You should stay inside.
How about you?
How come you can keep going out?
I need to attend to some matters.
But don’t worry,
after I finish those things,
we can go out again.
Where’s Shari?
Shari.
How are you?
They cut the live feed broadcast earlier.
[PHONE RINGING]
It’s Miss Velma.
I wonder what employee-killer
wants this time.
[PHONE RINGING]
[NOREEN NODS]
Hey there, my prodigal protégé.
The nerve of you to challenge me.
What do you really want?
I just want everyone to know the truth.
And the truth will be your downfall.
[VELMA ON THE PHONE] So you
really want to start a war?
Isn’t it obvious with the way
I drop my airstrikes in your war?
[VELMA CHUCKLES]
[VELMA ON THE PHONE] And do
you think that scares me?
Well, you since you started it,
I’m going to finish this.
I will destroy you,
and that pale gremlin Noreen!
[VELMA ON THE PHONE]
And you know what?
You better hide, because I’m going
to hunt you and take you down.
Is that a threat, Miss V?
Is that how you threatened Helena
before you pushed her off the building?
I didn’t do that.
Nevertheless, you’re the one
who signed that contract
and said to keep your mouth shut.
So...
you just breached it.
Mm.
So you will sue me?
You won’t, will you?
Because you already said so, Miss V.
It will open a can of worms.
Shari.
[SHARI ON THE PHONE] Whatever.
[SHARI] I wholeheartedly
accept the challenge,
Velma.
[SHARI] Why don’t we just see who can
shove the other into hell first?
Whoever falls first loses.
I will see you in hell.
[SHARI] I won’t.
You’re on your own.
[VELMA EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SHARI EXHALES SHARPLY]
Well, then...
I guess we don’t
have any more time.
I’m sure Velma and Eddie are
planning something to put this all on you.
So you’ll ruin your reputation,
and nobody believes you.
Let’s move.
I have an idea in mind.
What is it?
I’m a social media influencer.
My influence is still strong towards
the people who believe in me.
My followers are my power.
They believe in what I say.
They copy what I do.
I’m not Shari de Jesus for nothing.
Are you sure about what you’re planning to do?
I have no other choice,
and I’m not turning back.
We’re seeing this through to the very end.
Hello to all of my loyal followers.
I’m here to finish what I started.
I’m sure everything that happened
in what was supposed to be my showdown
with Miss Velma is already
spreading on social media.
But I’m no longer afraid to speak the truth.
A few years ago, it was reported that
a Velma Beauty employee died by suicide.
[NOREEN] Maybe you know
something about my sister’s death?
Well, let me try to remember.
I think I remember something.
I think she died in this building.
On her own volition.
[NOREEN WAILS]
Maybe you can check the
contacts on my sister’s cellphone?
There might be a clue
there on who killed her.
Miss, no one killed your sister.
How could you know that, Sir?
You didn’t even properly check
what happened to my sister.
Don’t be like that.
Is someone giving you orders to not
investigate on my sister’s death?
The investigation states that suicide
is the cause of your sister’s death.
[POLICEMAN] And it won’t be classified as a
murder without any irrefutable evidence.
That is not true.
No, that’s not true!
That’s not true.
You told me you’ve become
friends with my sister.
What do you know aout her death?
She killed herself.
Isn’t that what’s on the report?
- And you believed that?
- Yes.
Because that’s the truth.
Is that what you’ve been told?
Or it’s what you’re telling yourself
because you’re hiding something?
Did you tell her we know
everything about her sister?
[VELMA] It’s going
to open a can of worms.
Helena Alfonso didn’t take her own life.
She was murdered by Velma Imperial.
[ALEX] And I want to find out what it is.
[CEDRIC] Boss, we have a problem.
[EDDIE] What is it?
After what happened earlier,
I don’t want to deal with another problem.
Chairman Jang’s son followed me here.
[EDDIE] No wonder Noreen
has the guts to fight me.
It’s all because of that Alex.
[EDDIE] Gentlemen.
[MAN] If it isn’t the man of the hour.
It’s now viral on social media.
[MAN] When your name was mentioned,
the headcount of people here
in Axis declined.
They’re scared that the scandal
might finally expose our little group.
Appetizers, gentlemen?
[MAN] If only we could silence them right away.
So, what’s your next move, Eddie?
I don’t have a choice.
It’s time to play my ace.