[VELMA] Hush!
- [HELENA] Let go of me! Let go!
- [VELMA] Come here!
I’ll fight you until death!
[HELENA GASPS]
Just remember that nobody
wins against Velma Imperial!
[VELMA EXHALES SHARPLY]
Helena.
You’re evil!
- [EDDIE GRUNTS]
- [HELENA GROANS AND GASPS]
[NOREEN] I knew it.
I knew it all this time.
[KRISELDA] Eddie is the leader of
a huge prostitution ring.
What?
[KRISELDA] The fee is high.
It’s exclusive.
What’s worse is that the women and the men
do not know that they’re being sold.
Took advantage of me.
They trashed me.
I died that day.
I looked him in the eye, Noreen.
Yet he couldn’t remember me.
He didn’t know me at all.
[KRISELDA GIGGLES]
How can you forget the face
of the person you took advantage of?
Only someone evil can do such a thing.
[GANDA GANDAHAN BY DIA MATÉ PLAYING
When I discovered
the prostitution ring.
I found out that I wasn’t the only victim.
There were many of us.
[SOBS] There were so many of us.
But then I realized, [CHUCKLES]
it would be lucky for
him if I just killed him.
[CHUCKLES] That would be too easy.
He should suffer first.
Right?
I thought Eddie and Velma
were working together.
Is that why you created Marie Armani?
[KRISELDA BREATHES DEEPLY]
This is the reason why I went
undercover as Velma’s assistant.
I started as an intern [SNIFFS]
and I made sure to become the best. [CHUCKLES]
She liked my work as I was very efficient.
I made sure she would notice me,
thinking that she knew about
Eddie’s side business.
Then I finally got the job.
I dug deep.
I tried finding out the
secrets of the Imperials.
In the hopes of finding something.
Any damn thing that could potentially ruin their lives.
In exchange for the
way they ruined my life.
And then, I came across Helena’s case.
I pieced everything together.
Connected the dots.
Until you showed up.
It feels like fate itself stepped
in to bring us together. [CHUCKLES]
Miss Velma, we need to speak about Shari.
You again?
I'm so sorry about this.
- Sir, please handle this.
- [GUARD] Yes, ma'aam.
Hello?
That was Miss Velma Imperial's assistant.
She wanted to set up
a meeting for a job offer!
[NOREEN CHEERS]
[KRISELDA] @noreenbituin?
Kriselda Hoffman, Miss Velma's assistant.
Welcome to Velma Beauty.
[NOREEN] Where is Shari?
She's like a boss around here,
but because of what happened recently...
who knows, you might replace her.
I'm not thinking of that.
You don't want that?
So what's your business here?
[MARIE ARMANI] Hello, Noreen.
And fate brought us together.
So we should continue this alliance.
[NOREEN IN VIDEO] And now all of
a sudden there's a Pantasya Serum?
[SHARI SHRIEKS] Noreen!
What did you do?
Why did you take a video
of that and upload it, huh?!
Does it look like I was
the one who took the video?
Can you check Miss Alfonso's
phone for any incriminating videos?
Rummage through my phone.
But don't break it, I don't
have money to buy a new one.
Okay, miss.
This isn't the source of the leaked video.
Were you the one who leaked Shari's video?
Yes, it was me.
[KRISELDA] By the way Miss V.,
there's a parcel for you.
I never ordered anything online.
Excuse me.
[VELMA SCREAMS]
[VELMA PANTS]
I already emailed the video I edited.
It's here.
This was made by a friend,
who's knowledgeable on AI.
[VELMA SOBS]
Whoever did this
knows me so well.
They want to hurt me.
- [LOUD THUD]
- [VELMA SCREAMS]
[VELMA SCREAMS]
[WRITING ON WALL] “I KNOW WHAT
YOU DID TO HELENA! -Marie Armani”
Find out how that Marie Armani got in here!
- [KRISELDA] Yes, Miss V.
- [VELMA] Work on it now!
Yes, Miss V., I'm on it.
[TEXT MESSAGE] “I’m here watching
you, Velma. Love lots, Marie Armani.”
Marie Armani?
[EDDIE] What are you doing?
I know it's you!
Face me, you coward!
[KRISELDA SOBS]
[NOREEN SOBS] I’m so sorry.
[SNIFFLES]
I’m so sorry about everything
that happened to you.
[SNIFFLES] You didn’t deserve it.
Nobody should go through
what you went through.
But Kriselda,
thank you very much.
Thank you for staying strong.
Thank you becase you endured.
[SNIFFLES]
Eddie is the real enemy.
That bastard Eddie is rotten to the core.
I’ve been alone in this for a while now.
I've been alone in this, Noreen.
Noreen, help me.
Fight with me. I can’t do this alone.
I understand you.
[NOREEN SOBS]
But I am so scared, Kriselda.
We might lose another innocent life if we continue.
I don’t want that to happen. [SOBS]
I know you’re scared.
[WHIMPERS]
I am, too. I’ve been scared for a while now.
But [SOBS]
more people will suffer if we
don’t put an end to Eddie’s cruelty.
Noreen, think about your sister,
think about me, and Alex.
[STAMMERS] The people who lost their lives.
The people he took advantage of.
[MUTTERING] Noreen...
[SOBS AND SNIFFLES]
[STUTTERS] What about...
What about Velma?
What are we going to do with her?
[NOREEN EXHALES]
[SIGHS AND SNIFFLES]
She’s also a victim.
She’s blinded by love.
She’s bound by her
husband’s the web of lies.
Noreen.
She needs our help.
We need to free her from it.
Then we need to convince
Velma to side with us.
But Eddie’s hold on her is too strong.
We need to think of another
way to convince her.
We’ll go straight to the devil.
The answer is with Eddie Imperial.
You, me,
and all of us women,
we will play his game.
You know Helena,
I learned a lot about you.
[SOBS] I can’t even begin to imagine
how painful
and difficult everything you and
Alex went through must have been.
[SOBS] I wish I had been there.
So I could’ve saved you.
Helena, is there a problem?
Nothing.
[SOBBING] Where was I then!?
[SIREN WAILING]
[ALEX GROANS]
[EDDIE] Who the hell do you think you are?!
[ALEX GASPS]
[CAR WHEEL SCREECHES]
[CAR CRASHES]
[SOBBING]
[NOREEN BREATHES HEAVILY]
[NOREEN SNIFFLES
AND BREATHES HEAVILY]
[NOREEN EXHALES SHARPLY]
[NOREEN BREATHES HEAVILY]
It's time
It’s time that demon pays for everything he owes.
For everyone he has wronged.
For Kriselda.
For Alex.
For Mom.
For Helena.
Eddie Imperial, you’re about to meet the real Noreen Alfonso.
[NOREEN] Okay, alright.
I'll talk to you later.
Where’s Ma’am Clara?
Noreen.
Have you decided?
Are you going to be the new
CEO of Velma Beauty?
[CLARA] I want someone to
replace Velma as the new CEO.
And I want that someone to be you.
You said so yourself.
Soon enough I'll be able to call the shots.
And one of the shots I want to make
is the one where you're beside me.
I'll accept the offer, only if,
you accept to be my partner.
Yes.
I accept the offer to be
the CEO of Velma Beauty.
That’s perfect.
Great news.
Welcome!
On one condition.
[SIGHS]
And that is?
We checked out Noreen's tip
about the prostitution ring,
but we didn’t find any evidence.
Everyone had already cleared
out from the location.
They managed to pack up and vanish
before my team even got there.
And Alex’s report is final.
They’re saying it was an accident.
Looks like someone inside
has been paid off.
He’s in a rush to close the case.
Eddie Imperial is a master
at covering up his crimes.
By the time we make a move,
he’s already ten steps ahead.
I’m sure Sixto is backing him.
I can only think of one way now.
Someone from our side
has to go undercover.
Let me do it.
I can handle this.
Ma’am, you have a visitor.
Oh.
Guess who the cat let in.
A snake.
Shari, you're really shameless
for showing your face here!
Get out!
Everything she threatened to do,
she did it.
She’s the one who pushed her to her death.
She pushed her off!
[EDDIE ON THE PHONE] From the very
beginning, I have been manipulated.
See, my wife and I, in our marriage,
I am powerless!
You and me, we are Velma’s
victims, and it has to stop!
Do you want to be freed
from Velma’s hold on you?
[SCOFFS]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Well, it’s about time.
- [VELMA SIGHS]
- I got you.
I got you. Don’t worry.
You’re looking at the new CEO of Velma Beauty.
If that gets out,
you can have a press release
that the reason why you let her go
is you finally found out what really happened.
And you will have her arrested.