I know this is hard for you,
that's why I promise
to protect you.
So don't worry.
[CHIEF SIXTO] It's now viral in social media.
When your name was mentioned,
the number of people
at Axis dwindled.
They are scared that that scandal
finally exposes our little group.
They're drugging these women.
[EDDIE] I need to play my ace now.
Keep an eye on Chief Sixto.
Every move he makes
take videos of him.
I'm sure I'll need his cooperation.
Copy, Boss.
Migoy.
- Eddie is-
- [CEDRIC GRUNTS]
I want someone to replace
Velma as the new CEO.
And I want that someone to be you.
I waited for you at home until morning!
You didn’t even reach out!
Did you watch Shari's
livestream?
She's going to reopen
the case of Helena.
It's time Eddie,
that you do something about this.
[GANDA GANDAHAN BY DIA MATÉ PLAYING]
The truth is, I need your face.
You need my face?
After all the shame that Velma
has brought to our company,
she's no longer helpful
and she's no longer good for us.
I need to dispose of her quickly.
Velma Beauty will undergo
a major brand revamp.
And I want you
to be the face of that brand.
And you to publicly spearhead
the new era of Velma Beauty.
So, you want to make me a puppet?
You catch on very quickly.
But isn't that exactly what you want?
So,
are you going to accept it?
I need to think about it carefully
before I make a decision.
Okay.
I'll give you time to think.
But meanwhile,
I'll have to get back to the office.
To clean up all the
trash that's left there.
Ma'am,
can you tell me,
of all people,
why me?
Why would you want me—
Someone accusing your son of rape...
to be the CEO of your company?
Does that mean you believe me?
[CLARA CHUCKLES]
Don't flatter yourself.
You're just a pawn in a bigger war.
Have a good day.
What?
It's that video.
[SHARI] Velma Imperial and Eddie Imperial are
involved in the death of Helena Alfonso.
Helena Alfonso didn't commit suicide.
She was killed by Velma Imperial
after Helena told Velma that
she was raped by Eddie Imperial.
What Shari said just got me thinking.
I have nothing to do with Helena's death!
It was a suicide.
That's right.
That was what the
investigation ruled. Back then.
But is that all that really happened?
Hmm?
You really didn't do anything
when you found out
that something happened
between me and Helena?
How dare you doubt me?
How dare I?
You asked me about Helena before.
Well, now I'm asking you the same question.
Is that wrong?
Can you blame me?
You saw the video, right?
And plus the fact that you made her
sign a document so she wouldn't speak.
Because I didn't want a scandal.
She saw me at the roof deck.
But I know, and God knows,
that I didn't kill Helena.
You know what?
You're supposed to protect
me the way I protected you
and the way I believed in
you when Helena accused you.
After all,
this all started with you.
You're the root of all this mess!
"Dear Velma, Enjoy. Love, Marie Armani."
[VELMA SHRIEKS]
[VELMA WHIMPERS]
That's why I'm throwing
the question back to you!
You know I watched the video, right?
That’s why I won’t turn a blind eye anymore.
You raped Helena, didn't you?!
What are you saying?
That I need to force a
girl to sleep with me?
Is that it?
No.
You know very well that it's not
about your charisma, my dear husband.
It's about you exercising your power.
[VELMA SCOFFS]
This is my fault.
Because you can't be more powerful
than me and your mother,
- that's why you're forcing yourself
- That's enough.
On others!
- That's enough!
- No!
Go ahead, try it!
I thought so.
So now, you do something about this!
So we can end this mess!
You're going to be the
CEO of Velma Beauty?
Noreen, you're a big idiot if you
do not take that offer.
Shari, they're going to make me a puppet.
And so?
[SHARI SCOFFS] Noreen,
soon enough, you'll be the
one who's gonna call the shots.
Because you're the CEO and
they won't be able to do anything.
Noreen, isn't this your dream?
To be successful.
This is it.
They're giving you the shortcut, Noreen.
[NOREEN SIGHS]
And Noreen,
do what your sister couldn't.
[CORA] She liked your pitch.
She wants you to work for her.
Your dreams will finally come true!
Our dream, Noreen.
It's our dream.
[CHARING] Looks great!
You’re clearly used to doing this!
That’s because my sister and
I used to make soap before,
but we did it all by hand
since we didn’t have a cutter!
[NOREEN GIGGLES]
[CHARING GIGGLES]
[NOREEN] Mom, I promise
I’ll finish my studies,
just like I promised Helena.
One day, we won’t just be
selling soap on the street...
Your daughter got an award in Korea.
Best
Product Award.
It's my glow serum!
Really?!
[NOREEN INHALES DEEPLY] Thank you!
That sounded like good news.
That was Ms. Velma Imperial's assistant.
They want to meet me for a job offer!
[EVERYONE CHEERING]
Who is she?
Helena,
my sister.
My inspiration for Healing Helena.
[CLARA] I want someone to replace
Velma as the new CEO.
And I want that someone to be you.
Fine, let's do it together.
Huh?
You said it yourself.
Soon enough, I'll be able to call the shots.
And one of the shots
that I want to make
is that you'll be by my side.
If we want to bring Miss Velma down,
I'll accept the offer.
Only if you accept to be my partner.
So you mean,
we're going to take over
Velma Beauty together?
[CHUCKLES]
We'll show Velma Imperial
that we've stolen everything
she's worked hard for.
We will rule Velma Beauty together.
[SHARI BREATHES DEEPLY]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello, Migoy?
What's up?
What's the news about Alex?
Have you found him?
[SHARI STUTTERS] Alex is missing?
Migoy, what did you say?
Noreen, what's happening?
Huh?
Okay, let's meet.
Noreng!
Noreen.
I'm going to meet Migoy at Alex's bar.
I'll come with you.
No, Shari.
Just stay here.
You'll be safer here.
Uncle Chief is here and
you have a lot of company.
You’re in good hands.
But Noreen-
-Shari, please listen to me.
I'll take care of it.
Okay.
Just make sure that Alex is safe.
Please, bring him home.
Please.
What is this?
We're talking!
Excuse me, ma'am, sir.
[JOHN] Um, as of this morning,
top management has
officially banned you,
Miss Velma Imperial from the premises.
What?
You're gonna ban me
from my own building?
[SCOFFS]
Is this one big joke?
John,
I hired you.
Don't forget that.
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I'm just following orders
from top management.
Please collect your things and let's go.
Wait, wait.
Which top management do you mean?
Why don't you ask your freaking mom?
I knew it.
Your wonderful mother really wants me
to disappear from this company.
And now, she has this huge opportunity.
Velma...
Sorry, ma'am,
but you need to leave.
No, no, no.
Just try it!
I'm not leaving!
I built this empire!
And you're not going to humiliate me!
Eddie, do something!
Eddie...
Just try it!
Do not touch my wife!
Let go of me!
What the hell is even written on there?
I'm sorry, sir, I'm just following orders.
Eddie, do something!
I got this! I got this!
I got you!
Let go of me!
[VELMA GROANS] Let me go!
Hon...
Let go of me!
My hands are tied.
I'll talk to my mom.
[VELMA GRUNTS]
You're useless!
Don't you show your
face to me later at home
because I don't wanna see your face!
[JOHN] Alright, let's go.
[VELMA] No!
Let go of me!
Help!
Let me go!
Help! Let me go!
[VELMA GROANS]
[VELMA] Let go of me!
You can't do this to me!
I built Velma Beauty!
- You're all so shameless!
- [KRISELDA] Sir, where are you taking Miss Velma?
- [VELMA GRUNTS]
- [KRISELDA] Sir, let go of her!
- [VELMA GRUNTING]
- [KRISELDA] You're hurting Miss Velma!
They succeeded in ruining me.
Everyone who wanted me to fail.
My protégé, my mother-in-law,
even my own husband
is suspicious of me.
And he couldn't do
anything to defend me!
They're all so shameless!
Miss Velma.
Miss Velma,
you have to help yourself, okay?
You fell.
You made a mistake.
But there's nothing
else to do but get up.
Do you hear me?
- Okay?
- [VELMA BREATHES DEEPLY]
[KRISELDA] Do you hear me?
- Okay?
Okay.
- Go ahead.
- [KRISELDA] Okay.
Let go of me!
- Let go of me, I said!
- Sir please be gentle with her.
Hey, you're hurting Miss Velma!
[VELMA] Kriselda, do something!
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Gasco, what happened?
The storage room caught
fire early this morning.
The owner got hurt.
The owner?
Alex?
Alex Jang?
Yes, ma'am.
[NOREEN EXHALES]
No...
This is not true.
I want to see him. Where is Alex?
Ma'am, the victim's body is
already with forensics for an autopsy.
But according to the initial investigation,
the body is said to
be Alex Jang's.
No.
This already happened.
To you.
I thought you were dead.
But here you are still alive and well.
Just like Alex.
Alex is not dead.
It's impossible.
[NOREEN] Alex, you don’t need to
get yourself involved with my problems.
It’s too dangerous.
Noreen, you mean so much to me.
And I really want to help you.
I don’t want to put you in danger, Alex.
So please, can you just go home?
[IN KOREAN]
I'll do whatever I want for you.
To help and protect you.
I'm sure you'll be proud of me.
Noreen, trust me.
I will see you again.
Chief.
How did the fire start?
Initial impression is that
there was a gas leak.
Maybe someone lit a fire and
then it spread to the area.
And coincidentally Alex was inside?
[NOREEN SCOFFS]
What was he even doing
inside the storage room,
when his bar was already closed.
This was not an accident.
Someone did this to him.
First of all, the owner of a bar would
not be left alone inside the storage room.
But why was he found here
when the fire happened?
It might help if you can find
out where and what Mr. Jang was
doing before the incident happened.
He called me.
He just mentioned Eddie's name.
Then the call got cut.
We both only know one Eddie.
Eddie Imperial.
I'll investigate.
[PHONE RINGS]
Wait.
Chief Sixto.
What?
What do you mean the
investigation is over?
But, sir.
Hello?
Sir?
Let's go, men.
We'll go ahead, Migoy.
[MIGOY] Chief.
[RAUL] Go.
Chief.
[NOREEN SNIFFLES]
[NOREEN WHIMPERS]
Noreen!
What's up?
Is Alex okay?
Did you two see each other?
He's gone.
[CLARA] If you're going to talk to me
about getting rid of her...
You did the right thing, Mom.
What?
Did you wake up from your nightmare?
Seems like it.
What is happening, Eddie?
Why the sudden change?
One thing's for sure,
though, Mom.
Velma killed Helena.
It's all because of me.
Just because I slept with another woman.
I did this.
It is my fault my wife is a murderer.
[EDDIE] You know what to do here, right?
The message I'm sending needs
to stick in Noreen’s mind.
[ALEX GRUNTS]