[CLARA] Where is your wife?
Isn't this the big launch of Velma
that she was bragging about?
[EDDIE] I can let her know you're here.
[NOREEN] Did you run into a problem?
No.
We just made sure that no one saw us.
[JANA] I'll take care of the main switch.
[CROWD GASPS]
[PA ANNOUNCER] Please proceed
to the gazebo for the
unveiling of Miss Velma's newest baby.
[VELMA] We just need to show that
you're the one
who killed me so that Eddie can't escape.
Don't worry, Shari.
You'll get out of this quickly.
I assure you that my sister's death
won't be the only thing
that I'll get justice for,
but also all the women who suffered
injustice at the hands of your husband.
And that includes you, Miss Velma.
Enjoy your quick visit to the afterlife.
You!
[CLARA] What happened?
[SHARI] I couldn't possibly kill her!
- [SHARI] I'm not a murderer!
- [EDDIE] What did you do?!
Velma, no...
[SHARI STUTTERS] I admit that
we always fight,
but I can't bring myself to kill her!
I'm not a criminal!
I'm not a freaking criminal!
Maybe you forgot.
You threatened Miss V
if she didn't keep
her promise to you-
[EDDIE] Can someone get this girl out of my sight?
Call the cops!
[SHARI] I didn't kill Miss Velma!
[CEDRIC] I got it before they found it.
[EDDIE] My fingerprints are there.
No one must know that I held that.
Okay, Boss.
Whoever did this will pay.
[KRISELDA] Sir Eddie,
here is Miss Velma.
She's come home to you.
Right away?
Those are Miss Velma's
last will and testament.
I guess your wife decided not to entrust
you with the final days of her life.
[EDDIE SCOFFS]
What?
Why?
[GANDA GANDAHAN BY DIA MATÉ PLAYING]
Good day, beauties.
Today we are mourning
the loss of an icon.
It is a sad day for the beauty industry.
Miss Velma Imperial.
The Queen is dead.
Miss Velma is not just a CEO.
She was a mother to us.
And we're very heartbroken
about this.
Our hearts go to the
bereaved family, condolences.
Let's have a moment of silence first, bestie.
[NOREEN SIGHS]
Sir Eddie,
where is Madam Clara?
Miss Noreen.
I know Mom called you
here on short notice.
It's just that she is
currently preoccupied
convincing our investors
not to pull out.
Because apparently, even if...
Velma no longer has a presence here in the company,
her...
untimely death has seriously
affected the image of the company.
I love my wife.
She's my lifeline.
Now that she's gone, I feel like I died as well.
I wish I was the one who died.
Hon,
wherever you are,
I love you.
Miss V's final days are filled
with glamour and controversy.
And because there are
so many unanswered questions,
we have invited a very special
person to speak with us today.
Our new Queen Noreen's
confidant and
self-proclaimed BFF.
As in Martika,
she's a level that knows
the twists and turns of
Noreen's life and career.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Miss Janina Bulaklak.
Jana!
[JANA] Oh, hello!
Oh, welcome, welcome to The Beauty Parlor.
Hi. Hello!
How are you?
I'm okay.
You really dressed for this!
Miss Martika!
[JESSIE CHUCKLES]
Sit down, sit down.
Hello,
- Yes.
- [MARTIKA] Welcome.
- Hello. Hi.
- [JANA] Hello.
I used to just watch you before but now,
I'm here next to you!
Auntie Charing, Uncle Chief,
I'm a celebrity now!
[JESSIE CHUCKLES]
To those who are asking
why we invited Jana today,
she's here because she's our resource speaker.
[BOTH JANA AND JESSIE] "Resource speaker"?!
[JESSIE CHUCKLES]
[JANA CHUCKLES]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let's get back to business.
Shall we?
[JANA] Yes.
Well, Jana,
maybe you have insights
that you can share
now that Miss V's gone.
Is it really confirmed that
Noreen is taking over?
That's true, now that Shari is being
accused of killing our mother,
I mean, what will happen to her?
First of all, it's really messy.
It makes me dizzy.
Huh?
[BOTH JANA AND JESSSIE] "Dizzy"?!
And here's the hot gossip.
My best friend, Noreen, seems to
be the owner of this beauty empire.
[JESSIE] Huh?
Oh, my God! That's crazy!
Yup, that's right.
And my best friend also
went through a lot
to get to her position.
And for Shari,
all the evidence points to her.
[JESSIE] Mmm.
But let's not judge the book by its cover.
The investigation is still ongoing.
Right? Right?
You're right.
Excuse me.
Oh, here you go.
But what happened to
Shari is a fall from grace.
Imagine, from being the princess.
Now,
she's a pauper.
And if it's proven that she killed Miss Velma,
legit,
cancelled Pro Max.
[JANA AND JESSIE] "Pro Max"?!
[YLORNA GROANS]
[YLORNA BREATHES HEAVILY]
My condolences.
[EDDIE SCOFFS]
[EDDIE CHUCKLES]
I don't know...
I don't even...
[EDDIE SCOFFS]
I can't even believe that
all of this is happening.
I know that
in cases like this,
the first suspect is your spouse.
Noreen, I did not do this to my wife.
I would never suspect you.
You'd be really stupid if you're going to
kill your own wife in front of everyone.
[EDDIE SOBS]
[YLORNA GROANING]
Please stay with me during my final days.
[SHARI SIGHS DEEPLY]
You'll get better.
You'll get better because we will start over.
I just hope that we still have time, dear.
But Mom,
I just have to leave for a bit.
Please, you need to get better.
I'll be back.
[SHARI AND YLORNA SNIFFLES]
[HEART MONITOR BEEPS]
[YLORNA SHUDDERS]
[HEART MONITOR BEEPS RAPIDLY]
[PHONE RINGS]
Station 13.
Hello.
De Jesus, you have a call.
It's an emergency.
Prasco.
[METAL CLANGS]
[SHARI] Thank you, sir.
Hello?
[MOMO OVER THE PHONE] Shari...
[MOMO SOBBING] Shari, it's Mom...
Shari, Mom's dead.
[SHARI BREATHES HEAVILY]
[MOMO OVER THE PHONE] Shari, Mom's gone.
[MOMO SOBBING OVER THE PHONE] Mom's gone.
Okay. [SNIFFLES]
Okay.
Do you really think that Shari did this?
All the evidence points to her.
No one else.
And one more thing, Shari's
anger towards Velma is big.
[EDDIE] And you?
Since the absence of my wife, how...
[EDDIE SIGHS]
How do you feel?
Part of me
is relieved.
Then,
a part of me
wishes that I still could have done something.
I wish that I could've ruined her more.
But no, I guess fate got
to Miss Velma first.
Noreen,
I'm really sorry your sister died.
And I'm sorry
that you're going through this.
I'm just thinking that
no matter what, at least,
your sister's death was avenged.
The person who killed her is dead.
I mean, it's not a...
it's not a happy ending.
But at least you've got your revenge.
I hope you’re at peace now.
You want the truth?
Here's the truth.
I loved your sister!
I was planning to leave my own wife!
She threatened me, Noreen.
If I leave her, she
was going to kill Helena.
Velma is a monster.
It has to stop!
She needs to be put in jail!
I'm just waiting for the right time.
I'm just a woman who loved.
You're a woman!
Nothing can stop a determined woman
from confronting a dishonorable man.
Your ball is all set, Miss V.
And Eddie wants you to be arrested there.
Criselda is still working on getting
the CCTV footage of Eddie killing my sister.
That's why we need a big distraction.
Tell us the plan.
You'll die during your ball, Miss Velma.
He's neck-deep in my trap.
He believes that we're really partners.
Thank you for saying that.
You're right.
Finally, I'll have peace.
[NOREEN CLEARS HER THROAT]
What about you?
How do you feel?
Finally,
the wife that you hate so much is now gone.
What's next for Eddie Imperial?
Do you have a plan to leave?
Well, it's not like I can
leave the country, you know?
That's not an option.
It's just...
I don't want to
raise any more suspicions towards me.
So,
I'll be sticking around.
And if it's true that Shari killed my wife,
I want to see her judged
and imprisoned,
just to make sure that
my name is clear.
[STAMMERING] Sir, can I...
make a call?
[SHARI PANTING]
Sir, please.
Sir,
Sir, my mother died. [SOBBING]
Please, Sir.
Alright.
I have to go.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Noreen,
listen, I don't want to pressure you
but it's a big responsibility
to save this company.
Especially now that my wife
is literally,
officially gone.
But I trust you will find a solution.
The same way that you
found justice for your sister.
[NOREEN SOBS]
[NOREEN WHIMPERS]
[NOREEN WHIMPERING]
[TABLE SLAMS]
[NOREEN WHIMPERS]
[EVA] You know, I dreamt of Noreen.
She's sad.
It's as if she's going through a lot.
Don't think about Noreen anymore, Mom.
But she might need my help.
Noreen, my mother died!
Shari?
[SHARI SOBS] Please, I'm begging you.
I need your help in getting out, Noreen.
Noreen, please!
[GARDO] I heard that you have some
information about Eddie Imperial.
I've been following Eddie Imperial for a long time.
[REPORTER] Shari de Jesus was released from prison.
Who was accused of killing the CEO,
Velma Imperial.
What the hell?
Is this for real?
I also don't know, Miss Velma.
We need to prepare for this.