Let's kiss once while there's nobody around.
Huh?
Let's do it.
Hedgehog, it's a foul play. This is your first warning.
-If I have to give you a third warning...
-Out.
I'll give a chance to go on a date to Won Il...
Then, let's just kiss three times,
and go see Won Il.
It's alright. I'm not an easy woman.
I'm not an easy man either.
Are you going to...
marry me?
What...?
If we kiss once, twice, three times,
after we do it again and again, you might say"it's not fun anymore, it's going too slow."
Then, we'll be doing everything.
Still, we won't marry?
Why is it so hot all of a sudden...?
Are you going to marry me?
Why don't you get up?
I'm Jajangmyun, right?
What?
It's an easy menu. The one you can decide easily if you want to eat.
It's always around, not burdensome, and take care of your hunger like Jajangmyun!
Talk sensibly. I just asked to kiss once. Why are you talking about marriage and Jajangmyun?
Don't do it if you don't want to.
Go ahead.
You wrecked the mood. What do you want to do?
If you have the confidence to be the best dad to our children, then you can kiss me.
See! I'm Jajangmyun!
Episode 9.
How dare does he want to kiss me randomly? I am speechless.
There are proper steps to follow. There's a time and place for everything.
After talking about Eun Bi...Won Il...does it make any sense to kiss once?
Is he always aggressive with girls?
If it's a first kiss, then why can't we do it inside where it's cozy,
or under an umbrellla on a rainy day,
or under a  romantic moonlight.
There's nothing memorable for a lifetime here.
My sister's upstairs, and people passing by can see through the wide and open windows.
Does it make any sense to kiss?
Why not just do it during rush hour at a subway station?
Why did she bring up having kids all of a sudden?!
I am really speechless.
Everything has proper steps to follow.
Just decide on marriage without kissing?
Is it panda's way?
Of course,
if she likes me, would she have me compete against Choi Won Il?
Why is the first round necessary? Why do we even  have to do three rounds?
If there were more, we would have to schledule a tornament.
Aishi, really...Is she a panda or a fox?
Why did he call it a peck? Just call it a first kiss!
Does he think I'm a child, not to even have kissed?
And, I already had my first kiss in the first grade.
With whom?
Weren't you sleeping?
Who did you kiss?
The baker's son in the neighborhood.
Then, how come I don't know him?
Because it was before you were born.
Oh...
But, do you consider it as a kiss if you did it in the first grade?
All of a sudden, he said he'll definitely marry Noona,
then he suddenly
did it intensely for a long time.
It must have been really intense since you, who have a bad memory, can still remember it.
Of course I can't forget. How could I?
His fate might have changed because of me.
Why?
They had a bakery.
The bakery burned down in a fire, so the police took his mom.
I had been admiring the cakes in the window at the time
and wound up acting as his guardian.
-Mom!
-Since his father didn't come for him,
he lived us for a while.
-Mom!
After a while his dad came for him,
but he came back, saying he wanted to live with me instead.
Our father said no, and told him to go back to his father. He was turned away.
But according to the neighbors, he never went back  to his father and just disappeared.
What do you mean he disappeared?
When he came to find me because his father abandoned him,
I never got to see him. Because he was rejected by our father, he went away somewhere alone.
How old was he then?
He was 6 years old.
Where could a six year old go?
Unni, you didn't do anything about it after hearing that?
What you mean I didn't do anything?
I looked for him everyday crying.
I didn't eat. I didn't go to school.
So?
Our parents thought I would be wrecked this way, so they decided to have a sibling for me.
That's why...I was born...?
Was I born so that you could stop crying?
Instead of the neighborhood's baker's son who you had the first kiss with?
Is it important to know why one is conceived?
Some are conceived while their parents are drunk.
Some are conceived during a one-night stand when their parents cheat.
There are many different reasons that aren't too proud.
Do you think that would make me feel better?
How many would be conceived after a holy prayer?
Eventhough the beginning may have been precarious,
isn't it good enough as long as they grew up with love?
Did I grow up with love? Dad was always trying to please you, and I always came in second.
My whole life has been a supplement to you.
You misunderstood!
I thought I was the supplement to you, all this time.
Don't be silly!
I'm seriously mad at Mom and Dad.
Why did Hedgehog want to kiss me, and
ended up talking about one's conception.
So, what is "the best dad"?
Does he have a lot of money, education, and comes from a good family background?
A director of a big company? Or,
a president?
You choose Choi Won Il.
You're beating around the bush, right?
Aishi!
Why did things have to get so messed up that I can't even sleep?
What are you going to do about this?
Are you going to take responsibility, Hedghog?
Perhaps, thinking that I dumped him,
could he be crying?
Perhaps, he ran away...?
Oppa will give it to you.
How old are you So Hee?
24 years old?
Love shot?
Love shot, fine.
Where are you?
What are you doing?
Are you mad?
I did wrong.
It's not because I hate you.
Calm down. Calm down.
I have to think through why I'm so nervous.
Is it because I imagined Hedgehog with another woman?
Ah...
What other women would Hedgehog have?
If I go there, wouldn't I just see Grandpa?
Then, that's that. I'll sleep with my legs straight. Why
did I talk about kids?
I'm not a fish who's hatching her eggs in her mouth.
Hedgehog even told me to kiss him three times and just date Won Il. He is not being greedy,
And I even talked about marriage,
of course, he could leave home from the shock.
Why is it like this?
Perhaps,
Is it Hedghog...?
Am I not in between Hedgehog and Won Il?
Love shot.
-Ah...
It's bitter. Give me a side dish.
I don't have any feelings for Won Il.
All my thoughts are for Hedgehog.
Am I already in love with Hedgehog?
What is this?
Why is this bastard sleeping here?
Do you know who this is? It's grandpa, grandpa!
Aigoo...
I hope she'd know he likes her this much.
Hey, here.
Why do you look so tired when you are in a vacation?
Your friend, Beom Soo Young, he became a district attorney, right?
Yeah, so what?
Did Ko Seung Ji not drop the makeup macaron thing?
In the 2006 prisoner patissiers' competition, Ko Seung Ji was listed as the first prize winner.
I couldn't find him when I searched
the directories listing all the
graduates of the patisserie schools.
That's why.
Can we ask Beom Soo Young to find out?
Is it against the law?
I'll ask.
Of course, he knows not to do it if it's against the law.
Find out about Choi Jae Gyum also.
When you ask me to find out about Ko Seung Ji and Director Choi,
there is a big difference in your facial expression.
You're doing this so you can understand Ko Seung Ji, and to fire Director Choi, right?
No matter what evidence we can find to fire him, he won't quit easily.
Don't forget that even for a minute.
Are you doing well with Pan Da Yang?
Instead of PanDa, I'm hanging out with Hedgehog
Why?
Are you blocking his way, so he won’t get closer to PanDa?
No, just that it’s fun being around him, and he likes having me around too.
So, Da Yang is jealous.
Are you guys elementary school kids or something, playing around together?
Ah, its because of you.
What's my fault?
You said that your business comes before your private life.
What does that have to do with it?
Making cake with Hedgehog first, playing with PanDa last.
Because you told me that, I became friends with Hedgedog.
You might lose your romance with Panda while trying to protect your friendship with Hedgehog.
Never!
Whatever!
Before you get too friendly with Ko Seung Ji, confess to Pan Da Yang.
Girls like that kind of stuff.
Is that so?
I don't care about those stuff, you just tell her by yourself!
It's Beom Bo oppa.
He asked if you two had a fight.
What do you mean by fight?
He slept over there?
Ah, that's what happened
Please regard Seung Ji pleasantly. He never dated before so he doesn't know and makes mistakes.
So please don't misunderstand.
Yes!
Goodbye.
I think Pan Da Yang somehow likes Ko Seung Ji now.
When I told her to date him, her voice suddenly changed and said "Oh, really?"
You did well. That's so nice.
It's been a long time since I've seen you smile.
You were concerned about me.  I'm sorry.
Did something happen?
Now you can comfortably tell me
If you don't, I think I'll be disappointed
If someone comes by when my father and I are not around, can you call me right away?
Who would come?
Detectives.
Detectives?
Why?
It has to do with my child's dad.
A child?
Do you have a child?
I used your phone really well.
I do it, sis.
Don't laugh, I'm still mad.
Hey, what's the use of being mad at our parents who are in heaven?
My lips did wrong. Hit it once.
So Hedgehog oppa would punish me for hurting your lips?
My lips are not Hedgehog's, why would he punish you?
Anyway, I think Hedgehog will take care of them.
Why do you think like that?
Unni, you like Hedgehog oppa, too.
Those dark circles are evidence.
Instead of dark circles, don't you have any other evidence?
I really want to know if I like him or if we are just friends...
Should I introduce a girl to him?
A girl who Hedgehog oppa can kiss with?
You will die if you do that.
Would a confused person talk decisively like that and want to kill her sister?
I totally fell for Hedgehog, right?
That's right, so you better make the first move tonight.
How?
Just smack him with your lips!
Where?
Here.
When no one is here.
Won Il will be coming, though.
Ah, tell him not to come today.
Hurry up and figure it out. If you take more time it'll become complicated
How would I find that...?
How will I do it?!
Where's Hedgehog?
Huh? He's not here!
He went to his grandpa.
What about the Jajang cake? Did he finish it?
There was no way he could make it last night
Did something happen last night?!
No! What are you talking about?
You're really strange acting all like this!
What did I say?
The cake is all ready?
Ye Won!
You came?
What are you doing?
I was going to make dumpling soup for you. I was making the dough.
Ah, I can't think of food right now. I'll eat later tonight.
You're going to be here tonight?
Yeah.
Did you get dumped?
What happened? You're admitting to it readily.
It's the truth.
Ah, how did that happen?
She said I can date her if I have the confidence to be the best dad.
How can I be a good dad when I don't even know how!
So I just...
Hey, look!  Why can't you do it? It's not too hard.
You couldn't handle an easy situation, and get dumped?
You idiot!
You're doing well.
You know a lot about love...
Right, you punk! You do whatever
you need to do in a  war or in love.
It's a national common sense!
So, where did you learn about such a common sense?
Only the ex-convicts don't know it then?
Why are you talking about jail... all of a sudden?
Until when are you going to live like this?
Huh?
What about me?
You're telling people not to come close to you. You're hiding in your shell.
I don't know who gave your nickname, Hedgehog. It suits you well.
Hedgehog doesn't mean that!
I don't know who gave me the name. Ko Seung Ji is Hedgehog.
Hey, get out!
I have to use the bathroom.
For someone who doesn't know how he got the three characters of his name, he's being too greedy.
Because Panda was nice, didn't make a good judgement.
It was a mistake.
What woman would choose an ex-convict over an American college graduate?
Pan Da Yang is smart.
You see, she talked about me being the best dad. That makes it easier to decide.
The kind of man that Panda wants...
What score would she give me as a boyfriend?
Are you going to do that?
What kind of score do you think I got?
A zero.
How can you say that in front of me?
To my eyes, you're the best guy, and you'll be the best dad.
Do you think I'll see wrongly with my eyes that are 70 years old?
Even a ghost cannot win over an old person's eyes.
I'm not going to wear old peoples' makeup. I'll wear Noonim's lotion.
This jerk...
Why are you looking at me like this?
You're the one who put it on.
You like it, what are you complaining about?
What's good about it? It's just damp.
You said you're better looking than Jang Dong Gun. Why don't you date?
There is no problem.
This is not for you, Grandpa. Do it for Noonim.
Would she start over again even if she gets a lover, and leave you behind?
She'll get horrified if you talk about men.
Why?
She didn't have any luck with men?
Her dead husband was the worst kind.
She's pretty. How did a guy like that win her over?
Who won her over?
He almost kidnapped her.
He didn't even live long, and why did he put a nail through your heart?
They say he could be alive.
Did he come back alive after he died?
Something like that.
Then what is that?
Then, did he pretend to die?
If I come to think about it I don't really know...
A guy acts all like that.
Did you tell her?
We both met with the detective.
What?
The police are in our neighborhood?
Ah, really, we went to the police station because we felt so wronged.
It seems like there are more than one or two victims.
The detective said he will get him for sure.
Then, it means they'll be coming to your house soon.
They're not coming to get you. Why are you worried?
Grandpa.
I probably have to tell Panda that I'm an ex-convict, right?
I feel bad... that I didn't tell her something that I should have told her from the beginning.
I couldn't get myself to talk to her about it.
I ended up doing stupid things to her,
and just thought about running away.
What are you doing?
Praying.
Why are you praying all of sudden?
So Pan Da Yang can hear all the things that you couldn't tell her.
So she can accept you.
To me it's great.
Pan Da Yang is not someone who can't decide well for herself.
Hello.
Ah, I'm busy right now. Call back later.
Hey. Are you Bo Ram?
Who are you?
I'm someone Ye Won knows. Let's talk for a bit.
How did you find our house?
You're living with Ye Won so let's talk.
Hey, I brought you this. Why are you not eating it?
You're someone that I don't know, how can I just eat it?
I told you I'm someone Ye Won knows, you brat.
How can a person trust everyone?
Then why are you eating now?
I'm someone that you don't know!
You don't seem like a bad person when I talk to you.
Hey, I'm not a bad man.
I came here to make a good cake without getting paid.
Are you a patissier?
How did you know I was a patissier?
My dad is also a patissier.
So, you've already eaten a lot of normal cake,
so you want to eat a black bean noodle cake?
What's a black bean noodle cake?
They said you like Jajangmyun the best.
I was asked to make your birthday cake with Jajangmyun flavor.
They asked me to put in the flavor of that candy as well.
Do you think making a cake is that easy?
You're totally a patissier's son.
When you're done, call me.
I won't have my birthday celebration.
Hey, you tell her.
I'm scared of Ye Won.
I got it.
Goodbye.
Hey.
What you like black bean cake, do you want me to do it for you?
Black bean cake is not what I like the most!
Then what do you like?
You're a patissier's son!
If a patissier doesn't make a cake that his customer is happy with,
do you know how that is?
Hurry up and talk, you brat.
I can't be treated badly by Ye Won.
I like meat.
I like beef.
This is all money. Hurry and eat.
Are you poor too?
If I was poor, would I be this way?
I thought you were poor because you talked about money like my mom.
Is your dad having a hard time selling his cakes?
He's a patissier that can't make cakes.
Why can't he make cakes? He's a patissier.
He didn't learn very well.
He doesn't have skills.
Then, he has to find another job.
He has to come to his senses first.
Hey, you shouldn't talk about your dad that way.
That's what my mom used to say.
He has come to his senses first, then she would allow him to meet me comfortably,
and allow him to come home for visits.
Where does your dad live?
I don't know.
The creditors would be after him if they knew.
They would find my dad.
I was told it's better not to know.
Not everyone can be a dad.
I'm not talking about your dad.
It's because I got a girl unexpectedly.
I just asked to kiss once. She asked me if I could be the best dad.
It sounds like she is not interested in dating you.
Don't just trust people by what they say.
Does that mean I shouldn't trust
that you like Jajangmyun the best?
My dad could only afford to buy things like Jajangmyun.
I had to tell him I liked Jajangmyun.
I couldn't have told him that I like beef.
After eating Jajangmyun with my dad, whom I have not seen for a while, I met Ye Won.
She told me she has never seen me cry so much before.
I just told him that I like Jajangmyun.
It was my first time seeing my dad like that.
I can't say I cried because I was happy.
Is it good?
Am I eating because it tastes good?
I just want to spend my time.
Why are you like this little miss?
What is that?
You're the little miss.
What?
Because you're pathetic, Oppa.
Why am I pathetic?
You don't do much, and you're not very helpful.
Unni doesn't like you either.
That's why you're spending time with me.
That's not it!
What not it?
Unni is not interested in you and keeps waiting for Hedgehog oppa.
Did Unni tell you this?
Oppa, can you not see it?
But, I like Hedgehog oppa more than you, too.
Why?
Oppa, you're not much fun to be with, and you're not that attractive.
Ye Won. Oppa is a very fun person.
And, am I not attractive enough? My legs are much longer than Hedgehog's.
I'm taller, too.
If having long legs is attractive, then why don't you wear a skirt?
How can a man wear a skirt?
That means having long legs is not an attractive feature for men.
Then, what's attractive about men?
Player one.
Is Bo Ram like that?
Of course he is.
If I do something slightly wrong, he'll give me a piercing dirty look.
He's really so cool.
Women don't know anything.
You're going to have a hard time if you meet a guy like that.
He will always give you those piercing looks.
How are you going to live comfortably?
You'll always be on your guard, nervous, and try to feel  him out.
That's why one starts to like a guy like that.
What?
'Why is he like that?' You would think about him that way when you get home.
And still, you think about him when you go to bed and, when you wake up in the morning.
Because you constanly think about him, you miss him more.
Because you don't know these things, Unni is not interested in you.
So you lose to Hedgehog oppa.
Don't eat it. Don't eat it.
I ate well.
Because I was able to eat meat today, my spirits are up.
Other than meat should I show you how to have strength all the time?
What is that?
A song.
Cake song?
Not that dude. A real song that will give you strength.
What kind of song is that?
Maculinea teleius. Aspidomorpha transparipennis. Rhyssa persuasoria.
Homotropus tarsatorius.
Rhyssa persuasoria.
I don't really know what that means!
What the heck?
Cartoon drawings for ugly Choi Won Il
You wouldn't know what they are if you hear about them.
It feels like you would never have anything to do with them in your lifetime: butterflies, bees,
and insects, which can have such long and beautiful names...
Who gave those names?
They were given with a lot of care and thought.
If their lives were precious,
then, how are our lives?
We're probably better off than them, right?
No matter how bad things are. The fact that we were born as human beings...
Right, we should not be worse off than them.
Wake up and live well.
Doing our very best.
Is that what it means?
No.
When I'm alone...
That's the only thing that helps me.
Things that I like...
Favorite snack:
Cake.
Favorite flower:
Hydrangea.
My favorite thing:
Jewelry.
I don't remember anything about my childhood. Why I was here alone?
Who am I? Who is looking for me?
I can't ever forget that.
That's what I told myself everyday.
That was the only thing that gave me strength when I was alone.
Aspidomorpha transparipennis.
Without parents and not even knowing who am I?
I told myself that I can do, I can do.
Be strong.
Homotropus tarsatorius.
Maculinea teleius.
Aspidomorpha transparipennis.
Rhyssa persuasoria.
Homotropus tarsatorius.
Wow, your brain must be really good.
How can you sing it that well?
I have a good head.
So I understood everything that you told me.
Thank you.
I'll make you a really cool cake.
Is that good?
I'm leaving, goodbye.
What do you like, brat?
I believe you. You will make an amazing cake,
and my dad is amazing.
Gil Dong Goo, that punk, you're dead.
Dad!
Oh! Bo Ram!
Let me give you a hug.
Did you miss me a lot?
You grew a lot!
Gil Dong Goo is his dad?
Did you eat well?
Yes.
Please leave carefully.
Please come again.
Just talk to her in the coffee place when no one is there!
I saw Won Il all day.
But I missed Hedgehog.
It's the right thing to tell him.
Let's talk!
You too?
What you too?
Let's sit first.
Okay.
It's not an easy thing for me to say.
No matter what, I think I should talk first.
No, I'll go first.
Nowadays, is it a trend for the girl to go first?
What about it?
I mean I lived in United States so I don't really know about here.
Since you lived in the United States for so long, you might not understand what people say very well.
So, you don't like talking to me?
When did I say that?
Then why did you leave the kitchen when I went into the kitchen?
Then when I left the kitchen to find you, why did you come out here?
Are you mad?
Yeah!
Are you really in a bad mood?
Of course I am, it's not like I can avoid it.
Because I felt pricked (Korean saying: meaning "by guilt") by you.
Am I Hedgehog?  I don't have spines.  Why would I prick you?
You really lived for so long in America.
I should have come just one month sooner.
Why would one month have made a difference?
Then I would have gotten to you before Hedgehog.
Da Yang.
Let's...
Oh?!
How come you guys are together?
I caught a taxi...
...it happened to my car, wouldn't you know.
It's not like I couldn't give her a ride.
It's not like she couldn't give me a ride, so here I am.
Thats okay. Lets go inside. You come inside too, aunt.
Okay.
Oh!  You're looking good.
Are you dating?
What were you talking about?
Why was your expression like that?  What did Won Il say?
Just talking about how long he lived in America.
Is there a problem because he lived too long in America?  Is it hard for him to adjust to Korea?
Is he fnding it hard to be President of the company?
Is he sad his vacation is over?
You ask by yourself.
I want to.
But I can't speak as easily when Won Il is around.
When I open my mouth I sound like a fool.
It's not easy.
I really don't know what to do.
I must really like him a lot.
Why?
Do you like him, too?
WON II?
No! Hedgehog.
I knew you wouldn't erase my hope.
My dear friend who looks like a lovely pumpkin
and takes care of her friends.
You did good!  So how is it going with him?
We kissed.
So, you did it?
No not the kiss...
It was a mistake!
Why are you doing this? You stupid!
What should I do?
Our thoughts, their thoughts. I wish there was a way to reveal them all at once.
All at once?!
Of course all at once.  Would we do it one card at a time then?
Are the four of us playing Go Stop (Korean card game)?
Revealing everything at once is the only way Won Il will realize you two aren't meant to be.
A public relational conference.
So, the four of us should have a cake together?
Of course not, Won II can't eat that cake.
Why can't Won Il eat cake?
He has some trauma.
What kind of trauma?
Well, that's,
something Ahjumma taught me I can really tell you.
Anyway, think of something else besides cake.
Isn't it a problem if the president of a cake company can't eat cake?
You just worry about Hedgehog.  I'll worry about Won Il.
So annoying really...
Why are you smiling? Why?
You got the date.
Why did you appear in front of me at the time...? Really!
Its been a while.
Huh, why are you with him?
He will work today, so you can go home.
What?
The Jajangmyun cake should be ready by tomorrow. What would you do with such a trouble maker?
Gil Dong Gu!
What on earth are you doing? Why are you bringing someone like him here again?
Bo Ram's dad, is Gil Dong Gu.
What did he say?
Hedgehog said that the dad should make
the best birthday cake for his son personally.
He asked me to come.
So I won't cause any trouble. Don't worry.
Hedgehog let's go together.
Then the worst patissier was the best dad?
The best dad?
Da Yang is regretting that she didn't kiss you.
She likes you, Hedgehog.
But she said that she doesn't know what to do.
That's really good, I don't know how I can do that either.
Do you like me?
Why would I like you, when Won Il's right here?
Do you think I'm a strange person like Da Yang?
Have you seen Notting Hill?
What is that?
Why does she like this kind of man?
It's a movie. If you watch it,
they leave a brownie
for the most unfortunate person to eat.
There's a scene where the characters play a truth or dare game and
they reveal their true feelings and thoughts like their hand in a Go Stop card game.
So, then what?
Please make one like that for me. It's an official order. I'll pay.
If you're done talking...
Get out, I will change.
Aren't you leaving?
You're timid. Does he think he's going to get eaten?
I'm trying to decided if I'm going to give him additional information he may need.
What was that?
Choi Won Il can't eat cake.
So, make a cake that isn't a cake.
And please kiss Da Yang.
Fighting.
He can't eat cake?
Kiss her?
You can do this much right?
I know! I'm a patissier, too.
Is that for real that you're a patissier, huh?
I'll try my best!
Put your heart in making it. Think about the face of the person who will be eating it.
I miss Bo Ram's happy face.
Go back safely.
Go.
Let's go.
Why are you sighing?
Is your love life not going well?
The ordered Jajangmyun cake is not.
Why is it hard? You just have to make it like this.
Without worrying about it that much, just do it!
If it's that simple,
why didn't I think of it?
Because you are a notch below me.
Don't fool, huh?
No, I'm not fooling around.
Because Hedgehog came back, it feels like the world is brighter all of a sudden.
Hedghog is like the sun during rainy days, and the strong rain during a drought.
We can't live without Hedgehog, right?
I am a comfort cushion.
You can lean on it if you need to.
If you don't need it, you can just leave it next to you. I'm that kind of cushion.
If you press me, I can also talk.
What will you say?
Have you seen Notting Hill?
Yes I did.
Typical~
Then let's have a brownie time.
You, Me, Hedgehog, Panda, the four of us. Let's have a brownie time.
Da Yang said that she couldn't say it herself, so she wanted some help.
Here.
I like Jajangmyun,
This cake.... Who made it for you?
Someone who makes cakes.
What?
Does it taste bad?
No... It's good... I just think I know who made these.
What the heck?
Why are you suddenly talking with an accent?
You eat one too.
You must have spent a lot of money, from buying all these.
He wouldn't take the money.
So technically, I didn't get a birthday present for you...
It's the same thing, whether you paid for it or not.
Thanks for the birthday present.
Close your eyes.
Why?
No reason. Just close your eyes for a moment.
What?
What kind of father watches his sons kiss scene?
Come on let's go. Hurry hurry.
How long are you going to ignore me like this?
We need to talk.
There's no one here...
So what?
Let's do it. The kiss...
I take back what I said about getting married and being the best dad in the world.
The bags under my eyes are becoming worse.
There's no medicine for bags.
What the heck are you babbling about?
My eyebags are about to come down to my belly button, since I'm busy thinking about you... You take charge of it.
Then cover it with the cosmetics I bought you.
Let's just kiss..
I have something to tell you...
Tell me.
But I need some time to think.
So just wait a bit longer.
Can't you just give me hint about what it is?
I think my eyebags are going to come all the way down to my ankles if I don't know.
Do I, have the right to like you?
I need time to think about that.
Oh, hello~
Hello Da Yang-ssi~
Come on.
Ayo Hedgehog~
You're here.
Is there some kind of disease going around in this neighbourhood?
Panda is down, you are gloomy as well...
The two people at Mozart are also down and gloomy...
Boss and Noonim... They're gloomy because they met detectives.
Detectives?
WHy would Detectives suddenly appear out of nowhere? It makes me nervous...
It's because of noonim's husband.
Husband?
Gramps has a grandson?
I don't know if it's a grandson or a grand daughter...
All I know is that detective will come soon.
Aish then they'll come here as well...
Did you meet them already?
No. Not yet.
Does Panda know?
Know what?
The fact that Seung Ji once went to jail. That's what.
If a detective came, would he only see Seung Ji?
He'd also give Panda a hard time.
What does Seung Ji, and Panda have to do with Noonim's husband?
Even if they have nothing to do with them, they bother them anyway. That's what all detectives do.
And it's always guys like us who get caught.
Hyung!
Your break ends tomorrow! Why are you here?
Did you get dumped by Panda Noona?
Did you get fired by Hedgehog hyung? That must be it!
Hedgehog hired a new assistant.
New assistant?
Then what happens to you?
Gil Dong Gu came back..
WHAT?!
Has he gone crazy?! Why would he accept him?!
He said he changed.
And you, why are you here?
Well you're on vacation, and mom and dad are at the photoshoot..
They told me to protect the shop.
They went to the Macaroon photoshoot?
Not Macaroons! Cosmestics!
Don't you think it makes zero sense?
Wow! OMG.
Ah, excuse me!
How can I help you?
Uh, we came for a photo shoot.
Ah, which newspaper company are you from?
Newspaper? Ah, we aren't a newspaper company..
We're from Saint Horone.
We are the people who made the macaroons.
The celebration shooting is as negotiated with the advertisement company.
In our efforts to not to burden the model, we came to shoot here.
Ah please wait a moment. She's getting dressed.
She'll be out in a moment.
What the...? I don't think I've seen her before! Is she a model?!
She's the Japanese top star Mina!
Oh really?
Since you can speak Japanese, translate for us!
With the macaroons I made, let's take a picture to celebrate them and promote them!
We'll put it up at out door and promote you!
If you take the pictures with me and the macaroons I made...
We'll hang a really big copy of it at the entrance of Saint Horone and promote you and our macaroons!
Are you done?
Yes
Tell her that there are a lot of well known customers,
That it's going to be an advantage for her as well.
In Saint Horone, we have very well known, and rich customers... So it'll be good for you as well.
Yes.
She says she can't do this photo shoot.
Why?
Tell her that we've talked to the advirtising company and everything!
I am a model for the company 'Macaroon'. I am not a model for Saint Horone's Macaroons.
What the? I thought she was Japanese! Is a Japanese person imitating a Korean?
Are Japanese people not allowed to speak Korean?
No! That's not what I mean!
Let's just say this person is in a bad mood and say she apologised..
Then if you don't want to advertise, let's just take a celebration picture!
Why do I have to take pictures for Saint Horone's macaroons?
It's not you that's the main point, it's me!
Excuse me, please leave.
Ah, wait a moment!
All we want is one photo shoot! It's not rocket science or something!
What the heck... What a rude Japanese girl...
Isn't that cafe panda's packaging box?
I like Cafe Panda.
1999: age 13~age 16 juvenile detention center/arson, attempted murder,
2006: age 20~age 22 prison
2000: middle schoolxtance exam2005: high school graduation (juvenile detention center)
2007: the first prize winner of the event 1.
HYUNG!!!! OMG THIS IS AWESOME!!!!
Why are you so excited?
Look at this! Mina repayed Hedgehog!
Japan's top actrees; Siratori Mina, falls in love with Korean Macaroons. The best macaroons that the prettiest lady chose. 'Ko Seung Ji's Macaroons were the best that I ever tasted."
Hedgehog! Hedgehog!
Look at this!
Siratoria Mina, falls in love with Korean Macaroons.
The best macaroon that the prettiest actress chose.
Did something happen?
I came for Grandpa's help...
I can't tell her where she's from... so I'm afraid they might fall apart..
If I was hard I'll take care of it.
How poor that guy is..
How lonely he is, how kind he is... Do you want me to tell you everything?
She's a good kid, you can't lost her brat.
I went to look for him...
We can't even imagin where he's gone through.
What were you going to say to Hedgehog?