Your ugly face became uglier.
Is it Choi Jae Gyum again?
The macaron for the makeup product advertisement....
They copied mine again?
We suddenly got the advertisement work. We never even received a macaron project.
Yeah, I became a very important person to Choi Jae Gyum.
How can you joke right now?
Hedgehog, is it possible for you to make 22 servings by 4 PM?
What?
A customer asked if you can get a cake or macarons ready as presents for his guests who couldn't attend.
How pretty could she be!
He'll hear!
Yes. I heard it.
My girl friend is pretty.
Is it possible by 4 pm?
Do you think it won't be possible?
I must have thought it would be possible because I ordered.
What are you doing, Assistant?
Follow me.
Episode 8
Ja...
Heh, we'll prepare it perfectly so don't worry and leave, customer.
What are you doing, Assistant?
Why aren't you following him?
Did you forget about the round? One, two, three, go.
I'm going to buy some flowers for the table setting so don't fight and prepare it well!
If the business keeps on doing this well, then we might pay off my debt and my aunt's.
Maybe we can give a loan to the bank?
Wash your hands and put an apron on.
It's not the time to bake right now.
Then,
should we even lose the order because of Choi Jae Gyum?
Right now, with me, let's go...
Go there, then what.
Oh, You're here again?
I left my cell phone.
Oh, yes.
Would you go to the president of the cosmetic company, and tell them that
Choi Jae Gyum copied Ko Seung Ji's macarons?
And, tell them to use Ko Seung Ji's macarons, not Saint Honore's, would you?
If not,
would you go to Choi Jae Gyum, and ask him to tell the truth?
Because you think they'd do whatever you tell them to do?
We have to do something. Should we just stay still?
In a fair competition, Choi Jae Gyum cannot win over Ko Seung Ji.
What did you just say?
The representative from the advertising company said that as he left.
I knew it would turn out this way at that time.
If it's not a fair competition, then you'll keep on losing and you will keep getting beat up.
What is a fair competition?
Is there such a thing?
Even if this repeats, you would still stand it for the day to get a fair competition? Is that what you want?
Yes.
Even if I want to beat up Choi Jae Gyum and set fire on Saint Honore, I'll still grit my teeth and bear it.
Why are you holding it in? I'm mad too but you're probably more mad.
You used to turn everything upside down when you were wronged!
Why are you willing to go this far to bear it all?!
Why are you letting them just take from you?!
Why?!
Compared to you,
I don't have much.
I had lost so much.
I know what would happen if I don't bear it.
I can jokingly fight with you, but if I fight with others,
I have to be ready to give up everything.
So just go get some almond powder, now.
Tell Da Yang to cancel the order. Tell him to have the event somewhere else.
Your mood got ruined and what cake can you make?
Right now and in the future...
The most important thing to me....
Is the customer who ordered trusting me.
A patissier who can't please a customer, is not a patissier.
A patissier who prioritize his mood over customer,
even if he is in a fair competition, do you think he'd be able to please the judges?
So just go get the almond powder.
If you're not going to work, leave. It's bothersome.
Maculinea teleius.
Aspidomorpha...
Because you work at Saint Honore, I'm holding it in.
Because I know you are trying to help me. But I...
I still haven't found a way to protect you.
I came to meet Representative Ha In Ho.
The Representative is in an important meeting right now.
Where could I wait?
I would have to know who you are...
Saint Honore's President, Choi Won Il.
Hello.
I'm Ha In Ho.
I'm Choi Won Il. You were in a meeting so..
We were in a meeting about Saint Honore.
Choi Jae Gyum gave me a box of the macarons from where you are sitting.
Panda, hedgehog, turtle like... they were macarons of animals.
Did you give the makeup macaron opportunity to Ko Seung Ji only or to us also?
I originally asked Choi Jae Gyum to do it.
But, it was so bad that I asked
patissier Ko Seung Ji.
Then why were Saint Honore's macarons selected?
Not as President of Saint Honore, but you're here as a friend of Ko Seung Ji.
Are you here for Ko Seung Ji?
Yes. You're right.
What happened? What do we have to do?
Maculinea teleius.
Aspidomorpha transparipennis.
Rhyssa persuasoria.
Homotropus tarsatorius.
Director Choi Jae Gyum got a connection with the cosmetic company.
To send the pictures of Ko Seung Ji's macarons before the final meeting,
he used me.
The problem was that the cosmetic company
has people similar to Choi Jae Gyum.
I cannot abandon my advertisement work to be on the side with Ko Seung Ji.
Moreover, considering Ko Seung Ji's current circumstances,
he cannot win over Choi Jae Gyum's connection and power.
Even if President Choi Won Il helped, it would still be breaking a stone with an egg.
So why don't we just let it go for now,
and wait for an opportunity to help Ko Seung Ji.
Maculinea teleius.
Aspidomorpha transparipennis.
Rhyssa persuasoria.
Homotropus tarsatorius.
You came?
Yes.
What is she doing?
Hedgehog is showing off magical macaron making techniques.
He said not to bother him because he needs to concentrate.
So they are spying on him.
And not working.
I'll help you so don't worry.
A man's good looking face is important, after all.
The shining face of a genius who is indulged in his work.
Should I go inside and just bite it?
Bite where?
Nose?
Cheek?
Lips?
Hyung!
Where are you going?
Where do you think? To assist Hedgehog.
The touching round one is still ongoing.
Pleasing to see that way,
and pleasing to see that way as well,
What should I do?
A credit card with no limit on one hand, and a bank account with a full balance on the other,
the touch of holding them together?
I've never had that experience before,
It's hard to imagine that.
Ah, don't worry.
It's seems to me that those two servants will soon let you know strongly what that's like.
Really?
I think in my previous life,
I must have saved a country twice.
Seeing these,
makes me want to quit the presidency at St. Honore and be a president here.
Seeing you,
I want to stop being a patissier here,
and become a patissier at Saint Honore.
Really?
Can't you understand a joke?
Your head is used to look tall.
Really? Do you want to try?
What?!
Yeah.
Are you all ready?
The girlfriend of the customer is coming shortly.
They come when they come.
It's not even 4 pm yet.
What's the matter?
They came!
They came! They came!
Ah,
You can run upstairs as fast as you want.
But your eyes are already leveled for me.
Wouldn't it be just a disappointment?
This is not what I imagined...
You listen carefully!
Don't forget that you're in the first round.
Don't get into a fight.
Do your best to get ready for the event.
Are you listening to me...?
You are still in the first round to determine who will date me.
Move away!
Won Il, this is your opportunity. Don't forget that you're in the first round.
Why don't you go in and get the beverages ready, hurry.
You... do it.
You two...
You're dead!
Oh...
Aish...
You stay here, don't move!
The customers came. How can we just stay here?
This isn't even my room. Why would I stay here?
To both of you, because of a large crowd of customers,
even though I have a bomb ready,
you should understand that I'm trying my best not to explode it.
Understood?!
I asked if you understood!
Unni! Unni!
The customers are looking for you.
-Me?
Hey, why would customers look for you?
Is this Saint Honore?
Ah, both of you.
This is Ko Seung Ji patissier's present to you.
Ah.
And this one is for you.
I get one too?
Wow.
It's pretty!
What could mine be?
I guess I like it.
Everyone is on their way.
Let's introduce ourselves.
This is the person you've been curious about. My girlfriend, Sinatori Mina.
Ah! Japan!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Choi Won Il. It's nice to meet you.
Thank you for visiting our cafe.
I heard you're not from this cafe.
I am not employed at Cafe Panda...
But,
are you Korean?
No, I am Japanese.
She is a very famous actress in Japan.
Ah! That's right!
Sinatori.
Crazy! I knew you were familiar!
Do you know me?
I saw the movie you were in.
You are an amazing actress.
Thank you.
But, how can you speak Korean so well?
I learned, diligently.
I wanted to be able to speak with this man.
Do you still feel it was too much for you to make the cake and the macarons?
What do you mean?
I never said that, right?
I never complained, did I?
If the cake and the macarons are not to your liking,
I will have them go back into the kitchen and make them again.
You don't like it, do you?
It's not that I didn't like it...
I feel like I received such a wonderful present,
that I think I owe a present back.
Please give me an autograph.
Oh, sure.
Ahh. She was really pretty.
That's the first time I've seen such a beautiful woman.
How pretty is she?
Lets see...
It's like her eyes are made of the stars in the sky. Her eye...
A luxurious mousse cake has a beautiful cherry
on the top.
Then what about Panda?
Why are you suddenly asking about Panda?
Yeah?
What is it?
What are you doing here?
Won Yi said,
said that you two are in a danger.
She asked us to come see you.
What danger are we in?
You got kicked out by Pan Da Yang.
After she kicked out both of you,
Pan Da Yang said that
whether it's round one, or whatever,
you're both out.
That's what I heard.
You don't care if she said that or not, do you?
Before we really get kicked out, let's hurry back to
See mina one more time?
Yes. One, two, three. Go.
Let's go too!
Don't get left behind.
Run faster.
Wait a sec.
What?
Car.
What about a car?
It was here.
Hot-wire it.
What?
You're a pro.
Hot-wire it, hurry.
I've been clean for a long time.
You skill worth of three stars don't go anywhere.
Do you not have the key?
Gil Dong Goo took it.
You have another one, don't you?
Panda had it in her wallet and he took that too.
Haaa... that jerk. Why couldn't he leave one behind?
Call the insurance company.
You do it.
I have to hurry and
see Mina's  face.
You want to see by yourself, you bastard?
I have eyes too.
I want to see pretty women, too.
So why don't you hot-wire it fast?
Huh?
It'll be dangerous if we get caught.
Hey. This car is mine.
Why would it be dangerous?
We have no instruments.
If we take the car, we get to see Mina.
But if we run, we won't be able to. What are you going to do?
How pretty is she that,
you two who were crazy about Panda,
put Panda aside,
and make a fuss about Mina?
Give me a minute.
Let's go see Mina, let's go see Mina.
What are you upset about now?
Choi Jae Gyum made another trouble?
He's probably worried that Panda will scold him.
Think about that later. Now, we go to see Mina.
One, two, three. Go!
Okay!
I am driving as fast as I can.
Mina, mina, mina, mina, mina, mina, mina, mina...
Where did the car go?
This is where I left it.
Where did the car go? Did it just roll away?
Where did the car go?!
Aish! Im going crazy!
Aish! Hedgehog is going to kill me.
Aish! I should have  returned it sooner.
Aigoo!
Who stole the car? I'm really going to go crazy...
Will you keep them over the night?
If you have something to say, then hurry up and dismiss them!
That's right, Noonim.
They are probably tired today from being excited over Mina.
-Ah really!!
-Don't you dare look up!
We found the car, isn't this too much?
Car is a car, and I am me.
You guys were the ones who kept saying you loved me to death
and asking to be picked?
It's not me!
Why are we also being scolded?
We even helped find the car.
You know I'm really thankful.
Please go ahead first.
Goodbye.
You still don't get it? Go back in position!
We have been in position since long ago. What do you mean?
I mean you two got back in your previous position.
Hedgehog is a business partner, and Won Il is Bbang Il, Byun Bing Geo.
You two are unattractive bastards who won't be treated like a man to me. Okay?
I say this because we are back in position. The touching round one, you got it.
Why?
You didn't tell on me about how I brought the car to Panda.
That little shot wouldn't have me just back in position, but permanently erased.
You... What is your real identity?
The worst man you can think of.
Same here.
You are also the worst man?
If you told Da Yang that St. Honore copies your macarons and takes your advertisement work,
I would also not stop at back in position but at a permanent erase.
I guess two stinky men stuck to Panda.
So you want to get back in position together?
Maybe if Mina would give up her boyfriend and come to me,
that's probably not possible.
The first round is still ongoing.
I can't remain flat when Panda has it in for me.
That's right. I won't live as a piece of Byun or Bbang.
I mean, I can't.
Then do round 1 again, OK?
Don't want to? Give up?
But seriously, what is your real identity?
Are you guys dating?
Your share the same taste of woman, and hang out together all night.
If you like each other so much that you guys are still face to face, why don't you two just go out together?
It's gonna be tough from tomorrow.
Should I stop coming from tomorrow?
What? Do you think you will be lonely without me?
Yes.
I don't think I can live without you.
Let's go out together.
-What are you doing?
-Let's date.
I was too nice to you. I'm leaving!
Let's date! Uh?!
See you tomorrow, Assistant.
Ah, that's good. Stop taking pictures.
Pictures are not only for me to take.
With who?
With me?
Should I schedule a photo shoot right after President comes back from the vacation?
Why call someone having fun while I am working my ass off?
How come you guys are so thoughtless?
If it's neither me nor Won Il, then with whom?
Thank you, Chairman!
Why would you be in it?
I'm sorry, Chairman.
Whose macaron is this macaron?
It's a macaron for a cosmetics advertisement, isn't it?
Then, who should be on the cover of the magazine with me?
The cosmetic company's president?
Do you think the public would recognize the cosmetic company's president?
Stop playing twenty questions.
With whom do you want to take the pictures?
Won Yi?
What do you mean, Won Yi?
What is the flower of advertisement?
Wouldn't it be a model?
A makeup model would fit perfectly with this flowery macaron.
The macaron would shine. I would also shine!
Wouldn't that flatter Saint Honore as well?
That's right!
Then if that model falls for Won Il, I'll get a beautiful daughter-in-law!
Unbelievable.
She would fall for him alright.
You saw that, right? That other girl got jealous too, right?
It's not just In Ha Gyum. Shin Se Min was even worse.
Then there is In Ha Gyum, Shin Se Min and even Vice-Chairman.
Chairman has three women in this company?
Doesn't he have even more than that?
You too?!
Are you crazy? I'd rather tell President or Vice-Chairman and quit.
Why do In Ha Gyum and Shin Se Min stand it?
They are patisserie beginners.
The beginners who can have their future ruined just by the breath of Chairman.
Do you think my Won Il would know this truth?
I doubt it. He's a beginner.
Then this is a chance to send my Won Il to the throne.
This isn't the time for me to be like this.
I will go have a talk with his cousin, so you go find out about In Ha Gyum and Shin Se Min. Okay?
President sitting on the throne,
doesn't mean you will sit on the queen's.
It's too obvious that you are buying time not to go to the kitchen.
You're being noisy.
We should have a talk. Urgently.
Please tell me.
Urgently, I said.
Not in public, but behind anyone else.
Then, you should talk in President's office.
He's not here, so you should go.
Let's go.
Are you making that face because you don't believe me?
No, that's not it.
If that's not it, then for my Won Il...
for President to sit on the throne, I am making nonsense?
That's not it.
If that's not it, then what is it?
You keep on interrupting me so that I can't explain!
Gyun Woo sshi, I thought you had a prickly moustache, but it seems you have a prickly temper as well.
It's not something I haven't been aware of.
Won Il also is aware of it to some extent.
Then it was a public secret that only I didn't know?
It's not that much.
Of course, I didn't know it even included our kitchen staff.
This is impossible. It is unbelievable and unacceptable.
That's right.
Whether it is a company or an organization, a boss reaching an evil hand to powerless young women,
should be revealed to the public and be punished from the divine.
You're right. You're right but,
the problem is, the person who deserves divine punishment and should never come near,
is the father of Won Yi,
whom Won Il favors the most.
However, isn't keeping St. Honore which is left behind by his own father,
more important than trying to help a sister who only shares the half blood?
It is right that she is only a half sister.
Won Yi decided at such an early age to call him hyung for him.
What is such a big deal about it?
She called out to be a man
because Oppa, her favorite person is a man.
No. That's not it.
- It's okay, I can do it!
- You will sweat a lot, I will do it.
Won Il was a lost child.
It was a child that Chairman Choi brought for a moment because his ex-wife had some situation.
Like the current Won Yi,
he was very attached to Won Il,
and those two held on to each other.
But one day that kid suddenly disappeared.
Grandpa! What are you doing now?
- It's too hot, so let's eat some ice cream!
- Oh, okay.
- Tada!  Won Yi's signature Bibimbob!
- Won Il thought that was his fault,
and from that moment on,
whenever he ate cakes which were that kid's favorite,
he couldn't stop retching.
So, now, he can't eat cakes after all.
As he avoided cakes,
he even avoided Won Yi.
That was probably because the young Won Il thought
caring Won Yi was
a kind of betrayal to that lost child.
Master! Hyungnim! I will help you guys!
Won Yi found out
why Won Il kept the distance with her,
so she started to call him Hyung,
instead of Oppa.
Looking at her changing
from a really feminine girl to a really boyish girl,
Won Il finally opened his mind to Won Yi.
Although they are half sister and half brother,
those two became a brother and sister
who care for each other so much.
That's why it's not easy to cut off
Chairman Choi Jae Gyum.
Just like Won Yi likes Won Il the most in the world,
Won Il also cares for Won Yi the most in the world.
Losing that child is something that the
Chairman must suffer,
not something that Won Il should take the blame for.
That's why it's Chairman Choi,
and that's why it's Won Il.
I didn't know that,
so asked I him why he's not eating cakes,
and if he had been sick from cake before.
I was so thoughtless....
Why didn't you tell me that before?
I'm not in the position to tell you this,
and I shouldn't tell this either,
but the reason I told you this story without getting a permission from Won Il is...
I know.
It means I need to understand Won Il better
and to treat him better.
No. That's not it.
When Won Il was having a hard time here,
I was studying in France,
so I couldn't help him.
I'm still sorry for that, so...
I'm telling you this
to act as his old brother even if it's a bit late.
Won Il,  thanks to Pan Da Yang,
can endure in this country Korea,
no, in this Saint Honore.
That's what I think.
So...
Don't butt in, don't interfere?
Because a kid who grew up in pain
could finally become happy and get out of the guilt?
Your heart to give me warnings and advices
considering your cousin,
and my situation which is far behind Da Yang
in many points,
and that President is not interested in me at all.
I'm asking you a question, considering all of these.
If the relationship between him
and Da Yang doesn't work well, then,
will you help me get the President?
A woman who can understand President
and his situation
better than me...
Do you think you can find her?
Shall I give you more explanation
so that you can answer more easily?
Do you think Da Yang likes the president
or do you think she likes Ko Seung Ji?
Oh, I'm hungry. Food, food!
-Welcome.
-Why is he eating in here?
Why not eat here and eat at the cafe?
He can eat with his loving Siratoni Mina
or Choi Won Il.  Why is he eating with me?
It's so petty to be hard on a person about food.
Oppa, sit down.
Ok.
No, I will eat later.
Just eat.
Unni, stop it.
Stop what? I can still see his dazzled face
looking at Siratoni Mina clearly!
I can't forgive him.
If others see you, they would think you were betrayed by a husband whom you had supported for decades.
I wouldn't be this angry if it had been only a week since he confessed.
He said he loved me to death and
after just one day, he gazed at other girl?
Is it a mayfly (its Korean name is "one-day-life")?
I mean it's okay for you to be mad
when you're dating him even for a day.
Why are you jealous when you're not even his lover?
Unni, you're not in a relationship
with either Hedgehog Oppa or Won Il Oppa.
Don't kid yourself.
A girl who is nagging even before starting a date?
If it were me,
I wouldn't have started that relationship.
I'm saying I would have ran away,
very quickly!
Grandpa!
Grandpa. Is he not here?
Where did he go in this early in the morning?
It's not even time for the shop to be open...
I wanted to get his advice about dating...
Oh, I'm hungry. I better go eat.
I am hungry.
Pan Da Yang
Oh, Gil Dong Goo!
Hello?
It's me. Right now..  it.. it wasn't intentional...
It's for real that it wasn't intentional, huh?
The car was stolen.
How will you deal with me?
That's why I'm saying this,
but I found a way to compensate
by contributing a lot to your love life!
Of course, this must involve me, though.
You want me to believe that?
I can feel you, grinding your teeth and holding your anger against me, so I'm even more sorry.
I know the credit level of Gil Dong Goo is dropped on the ground now, but I also have some conscience.
So, can you trust me for one time, please?
Then how will you help me?
A relationship between a man and a woman
follows the rule, 'out of sight, out of mind'.
So?
So you must ascend from the underground world to the overground world.
Ascension sounds random in this situation.
Moving your place to the second floor across from
Da Yang's room will decide success or failure of dating.
What difference does it make whether I am in the basement or the second floor?
It is not just different.
A relationship between a man and a woman
Feeds on facing each other
after the sunset and the moonrise.
If you want to create an evoking atmosphere
in a late hour,
Then your room should be
right in front of Da Yang's room.
Therefore you can have more chances to face each other even while going to the bathroom.
Staring at the ceiling from the basement,
Hello? Hello? Did you hang up?
By the way,
why does it matter to you if I move to the second floor?
That is a very good question.
It does matter.
You need me to come back to Cafe Panda, so you can yield your room and move to the second floor!
With a perfect reason!
Am I wrong? Huh?
To be honest, who else but I,
will create a commotion asking to have a room.
Isn't that right?
Hello... I don't have money to charge this phone and it's dying. So why don't you hurry and ...
Oh really...
Hello?
Seriously, why would you stop in the middle of help?
Face her with an evoking atmosphere at a late hour.
Gil Dong Gu could be better than Grandpa.
Do you know who they are?
I don't know.
I don't know this person, either.
Then what about this person?
Answer me please, is it a person you know or not?
You know he is dead. Why do you have to show us a picture of a dead person?
You know both of them?
I know only this person!
Only this person!
Do you also know only this person?
Yes.
Who is he?
Hello, Detective. Isn't it too much?
She has paid for her fault. Why do you treat her like a criminal?
She was serving her sentence that she found out the death of her husband after a long while.
How can you do this?
Sir, you should decide whether to be angry or not after hearing what I have to say.
It has no regard with us. Why should I hear it?
Park Mi Yang has served 20 years. To be precise, 10 years for the death from injury,
and 10 years were added for an attempt to breakout to find her young son.
That long suffering might not have been her obligation.
What are you talking about?
So, Miss Park Mi Hyang, please answer. Do you know this person or not?
I have never seen him before, but he is not unfamiliar.
These two men are Jang Byung Cheol.
What?
What do you mean, they are the same person? They have different faces. How can they be the same person?
According to the testimony of a victim, Min Kyung Soo, who appeared after twenty years,
Jang Byung Cheol has been changing his face through plastic surgeries and changing identities,
and has committed kidnapping, assault, and even murder.
Min Kyung Soo was once on the same side as Jang Byung Cheol,
after surviving a fatal injury from head to toe, which was caused by Jang Byung Cheol's attempted murder,
he was accommodated in a mental hospital and finally recovered to his normal state,
and came to the police asking to find Jang Byung Cheol.
Jang Byung Cheol has used his identity to commit a fraud,
and took all his properties,
and that has distressed his parents to death.
Only the known identities he used are five.
This is a mere assumption, but Jang Byung Cheol must not be dead, yet.
So I ask for your cooperation.
I have definitely got to catch Jang Byung Cheol.
Gift number one for Won Il, secured.
What took you so long?
Why? Did you miss me?
Why would I miss you?
Then why do you whine as soon as you see me?
There is a customer...
Say hi to her. She is a pretty girl customer which you really like.
This is a customer?
My name is Yea Won. Do you mind having me as a customer?
I don't not like it. It's my first time having a little kid as a customer and it surprises me.
I am not a little kid. I am a junior.
She has an unique order.
What is it?
Junior menu?
Do you think a junior only has junior menu?
That disloyal looking oppa is the one who makes cakes, so explain it to him.
What is disloyal?
Liking one girl and immediately turning around to another girl.
How awful. You as well?
Who else is like that?
It is Bo Ram. Because of him, I brought all the money I collected all my life.
I think she came because of the troubles with a love affair.
Will you be disloyal in making cake as well?
I am not disloyal with making cakes.
You don't become disloyal with making cakes?
What do you want? What kind of cake should I make for you?
A cake that tastes like Jajangmyun (black bean noodles).
What?
I asked you to make a cake that tastes like Jajangmyun.
Oppa isn't a person who makes Jajangmyun. I am a person who makes cakes.
That's why I am asking you. If I needed Jajangmyun, I would've have gone to a Chinese restaurant.
Why would I ask here?
That is true, but...
If you wanted to eat a Jajangmyun flavored cake, then you can eat Jajangmyun and then eat a cake.
Why would you eat a Jajangmyun flavored cake?
Bo Ram said he liked me,
and immediately turned around to Sae Rom.
Sae Rom said she will give him a fried pork flavored cake for his birthday.
Are you telling me to just sit still?
Ah, you are also in a love triangle.
Are you also in a love triangle, ahjusshi?
I'm not ahjusshi, I'm an oppa too!
Forget that. Make me a Jajangmyun flavored cake for Bo Ram's birthday next week. Got it?
Got it!
Got what?
You should get it. Do you want Yea Won lose Bo Ram to Sae Rom?
Ohh really...
When you make the cake, please clean your hands very carefully.
Okay. I will be watching him. Let's go. I'll take you.
Are you and that oppa and that ahjusshi in a love triangle?
I said I'm not an Ahjusshi!
Why are you yelling? You look like a lollipop.
What?
Right! Bo Ram likes to eat lollipops after eating Jajangmyun, so include lollipop flavor, too. You must!
Wow!!
Why did you talk back to her and make the job more difficult?
What was that? Are most kids these days are like her?
How would I know kids these day? I don't even know them from old days. Move out!
Why does he not know kids from old days? Wasn't he one once?
That Ahjusshi for real... How do I appear like...
Yae Won, take care!
-Bye!
Da Yang!
How is Hedghog doing? Is he alright?
Did Hedgehog talk badly about me?
What are you talking about?
Why would he talk badly about you?
I didn't treat him nicely.
He probably is not in good mood because of what happened with the advertisement work.
Why did you treat him badly?
What do you mean the advertisement work
didn't work out?
Weren't they suppose to
use Hedgehog's work?
Hedgehog probably didn't tell you because he didn't want you to get upset.
Representative Ha called.
He said he was sorry that it didn't work out.
He even apologized to me.
Why won't he use his work?
He did such a good job!
They decided to use those of a patissier that the cosmetic company is close to.
Looks like representative Ha
couldn't win in the end
because he just works and gets paid by them.
Hey, Hedgehog is coming out!
You came?
How are you?
"You're going to look at girls instead of working?"
That's what you're thinking of when you're looking at me, right?
No. Where are you guys going?
To a Chinese restaurant.
We'll return after eating Jajangmyun.
Alright. Return safely!
Hey! Don't leave them together like that!
If they become friends,
it'll be hard for you to choose one.
They became friends already.
What?
You don't have an appetite because you're worried about making a cake?
Why does that Bo Ram like Jajangmyun?
Don't normal kids like chocolate, candies, ice cream, right?
Whether the kid is normal or abnormal, he's in a better situation than us.
Why is he in a better situation?
We're eating Jajangmyun to look good in front of her, hoping to get a date with her.
When two women are in competition for Bo Ram, spending their lifetime savings.
He is better off.
Of course, at his young age.
Should we get coaching from that kid?
Hey...I said that first.
No, I said it first!
Hey, I'm the one who said first that Bo Ram is better off than us!
I wouldn't have known it if you didn't tell me?
Huh? Really!
You'd better take me when you go to meet Bo Ram.
Are you crazy? He's my rival.
You, reallly...
You always do this in important situations.
All of a sudden, Jajangmyun is tasty.
If you don't drop it, I will tell her to change it to Pal Bo Chae(a dish with luxurious ingredients) flavored cake.
Pal Bo Chae, of course.
How would the kids know what Pal Bo Chae tastes like, to order the flavor?
I can buy Bo Ram a dish of Pal Bo Chae.
And say, "isn't it better than Jajangmyun?
then tell Yae Won."
Alright, let's go together!
Are you satisfied now?!
You can't even win and you always try to crawl up.
Aish!
What? What? What?
You would know if you get pierced by this.
You don't have to eat it again. I was just wondering if this could help you to come up with ideas.
Does it bother you...? Should I take it away then?
Why are you so friendly all of a sudden?
You were yelling, 'back in position!'
Why didn't you tell me?
What?
That the macaron cosmetic advertisement went to another patissier.
Who told you that?
Representative Ha called Mi Ra unni to apologize.
Aish...
I forgot to thank her.
I did it already. You didn't tell me because I'd get upset?
Getting rejected is just nothing to brag about.
I don't know who that patissier is,
but he got the job because he is friends
with the cosmetic company.
So, the fact that your macarons
are the best never changes.
Siratoni Mina who stole your heart
was also impressed by your macarons.
Of course, if I was even acknowldeged by Mina...
It must be great.
My compliment that you are the best didn't make an impression on you.
And Siratoni Mina's compliment out of politeness makes you feel like winning a gold medal?
Hedgehog, don't live like that!
What a big mood swing for a panda!
Calm at this. Calm as that. Isn't that panda?
It's so annoying!
Why does she have to date like that?
Ahh!
That's it!
Ommo! What's all this?!
Our Panda must be happy because she has a man who cares about her this much.
That's because he did something wrong.
Do you think all the men will do this because they did something wrong?
Most men, when they do something wrong, they'll do the opposite.
They will just give you a hard time. Think of this as a gift.
Really?
Really! You naive Panda!
Anyways, he's talented.
Not only is he talented, but it looks like he applies himself as well.
What's this?
I was going to write the answers, but I thought it would be better if you did.
Scored zero?!
So what if the score is zero?
This scored one hundred.
Auntie!
My goodness.
Ah, what?
How can you eat me?
What do mean? You just have to tell him to make more!
The taste
scores 120.
Should I try and see if it tastes better than that of Siratoni Mina?
What is Siratoni Mina?
Hello.
How come she always shows up when I'm here?
Of course, I didn't want this to happen, but it happened this way.
Don't you have work? Why are you here in the morning?
I have to something to report to the boss.
What can I do when he's around here all the time.
Choi Won Il is here?
Yeah. He is here as Hedgehog's assistant.
How come?
What?
Why did Won Il become Hedgehog's assistant?
Is he being punished for the macarons?
Why would Won Il be punished for the macarons?
Huh? Oh...um the m-macarons that Hedgehog made before... As an appreciation? My words came out wrong.
Ah, it's not that.
Then, what's the reason?
Ah, Won Il and Hedgehog are competiting in their first round.
Why are they competing?
Huh?
Perhaps,
Are they in a competition for you?
Would that be possible? They became friends and they are just fooling around like kids.
Is that right? Then, I'm relieved.
Yeah?
You should have called if you couldn't make it.
You were rude as an assistant.
I have something to do today. I'm sorry, I'll be there tomorrow.
The Jajangmyun cake is due the day after tomorrow.
So be ready to stay up the night. Alright?
Alright. Take it easy.
Okay.
August 14th, the 6th prisoner patisserie competition being held.
The first prize winner of the event 1 of 2007: Ko Seung Ji.
What shoud I do?
You don't want to fight Kang Eun Bi, so you want to date me?
No thanks.
Are you still fallen for Siratoni Mina?
Do you think then I would make the macarons all night long?
That's that, but what should I do?
When I didn't have a man, things weren't complicated.
But now I'm asked if this is a friendship or love...
My torment began...
Ah! Why did this story begin all of a sudden,
and I became the female star of this romance?
So you just have to like me. Why are you involved with Choi Won Il, and suffer like that?
That's right! Why didn't you show me you like me?!
Why did you wait until Won Il to like me,
and give me such a headache?
Let's kiss while there is nobody around.
Huh?
Let's do it.
Hedgehog, it's a foul play.
This is your first warning.
If I have to give you a third warning...
Out.
I have to give Won Il a chance to go on a date...
Then, let's just kiss three times, and then go see Won Il.
It's alright. I'm not an easy woman.
I'm not an easy man either.
Did you sleep here?
Yeah
What happened?
He doesn't even know the three characters of his name.
He is too greedy. Just because Panda is nice to him, he doesn't know what to do.
Let me think through why I'm like this.
Do I already like Hedgehog...?
Do I have any right to like you,
I need time to think.