Star Media presents
Dmitry Fomenko
impressive
Team
What's wrong, Mudan? Did you cut your hand? Let me see.
It's okay. It'll be fine in a while.
Did you see the clouds?
So delicate.
I'll go and check.
Okay.
I need to make a pattern.
When the pattern is done,
I can print the clouds on the sachet.
And put a good meaning on it.
You didn't know before
that you can do it.
My mother taught me.
Mudan, now the square is
covered with the red color of your fork.
And the lady in the heaven
will be proud of you.
If I can't have an enemy,
how can I bear the expectation of my mother?
Jiang Changyang came to the square today to find you.
Liulang said you were in a bad mood and didn't want to see the guest.
So he threw her away.
I thought
I knew him well enough
to get along with him for a long time.
I knew his feelings for Wu Bo.
But I didn't expect
that in front of Master and A'Fei,
he would actually protect a murderer.
I didn't understand.
I was also surprised.
I was afraid that Jiang Changyang
was a short-tempered man.
He was nice to us before.
But we forgot that
he was a bird-fisher.
He was a corrupt official.
I forgot that
he was good at acting.
Let the past be the past.
Wu Bo is a poor man.
Wu Dan,
let it go.
All these years,
Wu Bo has been suffering.
He has been atonement.
Little lady.
Wu Bo,
don't say anything.
Not only Jiang Changyang,
why did Wu Bo seem so calm when he saw me?
It seemed that he knew that I would go to him.
And my mother.
Why didn't she mention this to me?
The symptoms of severe poisoning and infection are very different.
When I was examined,
I had to tell the doctor the truth.
When Xunyin was examined,
my mother always looked at me.
No.
I must find out the truth.
Wu Dan!
I've found out everything you told me to.
Wu Bo has been atonement since he returned from Luoyang.
He only met with children.
Now he has no other relatives.
This is...
This is the names and ages of all the children in the house.
I only know some of their names.
I need to ask the villagers who live around here.
What are you doing with these children?
I want to know
if any of these children came from Luoyang.
A Kang!
Why is he not here?
He comes here every day.
Stop!
Are you A Kang?
Where are you going? Does it hurt?
Hey!
Let me go!
Come here!
It's A Kang.
Let me go!
You're a thief!
Don't move!
Stand still!
Give it back!
A Kang,
I want to ask you.
You're the most obedient and sensible person in the world.
Why did you hit me today?
You hit me so hard?
You always give me clothes and food.
You're so heartless!
You're a bad person!
I don't want your things anymore!
Let go!
Why did you say that?
You're so cruel, Wu Bo!
I saw it all.
You're a big bad person!
How do you know that it's not Wu Bo?
Wu Bo is a good man.
He's my savior.
Slow down!
You have a fever.
Drink some water.
Come on.
What are you doing?
I don't want your things.
If it wasn't for Wu Bo,
I would have been dead by now.
You're the one who's to blame.
You're my enemy!
Akan, tell me.
You're talking about the disaster in Luoyang four years ago.
Are you really from Luoyang?
Yes.
Many people were killed there.
But only a few people survived.
My parents and my sister
were all killed.
But I was the only one.
Wu Bo's family was already dead.
He was lucky to get the medicine.
But he was already dead.
He gave me all the medicine when he met me.
That's how I got my life back.
So many people died in the disaster.
Akan, tell me.
Where did Wu Bo get the medicine?
He said he got it from a merchant's house.
Merchant's house?
I didn't say it, but I'm sure it's not.
Why are you so sure?
The medicine wasn't for him.
It was expensive.
He needed a rare peony.
They say the biggest medicine shop in the city has this kind of peony.
But the shop owner...
He sold all the peonies to the rich people.
Did you remember it wrong?
No, I remember it very clearly.
My parents took me and the whole village
to the pharmacy for a few days.
But they didn't tell me that they used up all the peonies.
But I saw them carrying the medicine on their back.
I saw it.
I'm asking you.
What's the pattern on the medicine bag?
It's a cloud.
A red cloud.
I was hoping that my parents could get a cloud of silver.
But they knelt at the door of the pharmacy and no one understood.
The people in the village fell one by one.
The village was destroyed.
The land was buried.
Too many people died.
Too many.
If we say that the people who were given the peonies were killed,
the peonies in his hands were poisoned.
It wasn't the devil who killed everyone.
But it wasn't the murderers who killed people.
It was our enemies.
Stop talking nonsense.
Akang.
After Uncle Wu saved you,
why did you come to Chang'an?
Brother took us here.
To Jiangchangyang?
I took the medicine.
At night,
I woke up in a daze.
I saw him hang himself.
Uncle Wu!
Brother came in time to save him.
Mother!
That night, Uncle Wu cried for a long time.
Brother went away for a long time.
Brother told me that
I would be his child from now on.
Only when my siblings were safe and sound,
Uncle Wu could live well.
The skin of this flower
can cool the blood and relieve the pain of the pig.
It can be used to treat the body,
the body, the body, the body.
It can relieve the heat of the lungs.
It is the most necessary medicine for this purpose.
The ice crystal peonies we planted
are hard to find.
The most valuable.
When the disaster happened,
a pearl was worth a thousand gold.
I grew up with my mother.
I know my mother best.
She is not such a cruel person.
Is there any misunderstanding?
My mother knows medicine.
If someone poisoned her,
she would have noticed.
But she knew that Yan Qi did not mention it.
Why would she know?
I want to go back to Luoyang.
Coming.
What?
I can't go into this house?
What do you mean?
Our deal has been settled in Chang'an.
Is it okay?
Do you want to go back?
I came to Luoyang to see my father.
It has nothing to do with you.
Get out of the way.
But you are not related to the family.
You should be careful.
Don't come to the master again.
Okay?
Mudan.
It's really you.
Why didn't you come home in advance?
Yes.
Come in.
Come.
Why did you mention the old things?
You just told me that my mother fell ill.
But no one told me that it was a poison.
Why would I think so?
Your mother is not...
You don't have to hide it.
I already know.
It's not my fault.
Why?
You said you would go home to talk to your family.
But you went to Chang'an to see Mudan.
Are you blaming me?
You don't look after the He family.
Now they are all gone.
Since Mudan is the daughter of the He family,
what's wrong with helping the family?
Who is she?
She is my mother.
I don't know.
What's wrong with you?
Who are you to decide?
Mudan, I don't know that it's your money.
Two years.
Within two years, I will return it to you.
What do you mean?
Why do you want to return it?
Shut up.
As the daughter of the He family,
it's natural for Mudan to raise her parents well.
Moreover, she is pregnant now.
You didn't see that.
She is the owner of the shop.
She deserves a lot of money.
She is so stingy.
How can she see it?
Shut up.
I...
Father, I didn't come to ask for money.
If it wasn't for your notice,
I'm afraid I wouldn't have been able to find out what happened.
How much did you find out?
A lot.
Luoyang was in a terrible state.
The ice crystal Mudan that my mother planted could save people's lives.
Father, did you sell the skin to the high-ranking officials?
I've been thinking on my way here.
I've been raising my parents since I was a child.
How could I be a greedy and ungrateful person?
No.
You can't say that about your mother.
She doesn't know about this.
What do you mean?
I'm the one who sold the skin to the high-ranking officials.
Your mother doesn't know where the medicine is.
I told her that I had sold the medicine to the people who were infected.
Why?
So that they could make more money?
The disease was so severe that the high-ranking officials were afraid of it.
They forced me to sell all the medicine to them.
But after the flood, people drank water and ate.
They were contaminated, which caused the disease.
The high-ranking officials stayed in their houses all day.
They ate and drank.
They were so poor.
How could they get sick so easily?
How could they care about this?
The servants who were bought from the outside,
if one or two of them got sick,
they were scared to death.
They were so poor that they couldn't afford to buy medicine.
They were so poor.
They were so poor that they didn't want to save anyone.
How could they have agreed to this?
I'm just a merchant.
If someone is in trouble,
they will search every shop we have.
By then, you and your mother will be involved.
Mudeng, I don't dare to take this risk.
So you were hiding it from us.
Your mother was a kind person.
She loved to eat and drink.
She was young.
It's just a worry for you.
I can't let you and your mother suffer with me.
I can't bear it.
Then mother...
Mother found out later.
Wu Hong told me.
After the disaster, someone was mixed up in the house.
Your mother pitied him.
She gave him food and money.
This person is Wu Hong.
How could this be?
If you take the medicine on time,
you will recover in a few days.
Only rich people can afford this expensive medicine.
We are poor people.
How can we afford it?
The single products of the He's Pharmacy are all out of stock.
It's not fair.
Madam, do you really know the price of this medicine?
Did my single product
sell at a high price to the people?
It doesn't matter if it sells at a high price.
Your medicine won't sell to ordinary people.
It will be delivered to the rich people.
How could this be?
It's a good opportunity to make money.
It seems that the owner of the He's Pharmacy didn't tell you the truth.
Outside...
It's already dark outside.
If the He's Pharmacy was full of people half a month ago,
they would have been begging for a pack of medicine.
But now, those people have already gone to hell.
Among those souls, there is my family.
I've been wandering outside the house of the nobles for half a month.
But no one is here.
If the owner of the He's Pharmacy was home today,
he would have driven me away.
It's a good opportunity.
But I met you.
This is what you get.
They would never make this kind of thing.
So isn't it better to see from outside?
I wanted to avenge my family.
But who knew that you were the source of this poison.
But you didn't know it.
You don't need to find someone to kiss me.
I won't run away.
Now I have no more body.
And no more will I live.
I'm sorry.
This is the last day.
I'm sick and tired.
I don't know if anyone needs me now.
What do you mean?
Go.
You don't report to the police?
It turns out that the fire was not an accident.
But my mother did it.
Your mother told me to keep it from you.
But I know that one day you will realize it.
I'm sorry.
Taobao Shenzhou
Father.
I want to discuss something with you.
I want to find the deceased's family.
If I need help, I will help.
I will list the deceased's name.
And I will help them.
Let me do it.
You didn't know it.
I'm sorry.
I will do it.
You didn't need to apologize to me.
I'm a member of the He family.
I have the responsibility to make up for the victims.
I think you will want me to do it.
Mudan.
I know you're smart.
But as a woman, you shouldn't worry about this.
There are many hardships in the world.
Women are hard to bear.
You went to Chang'an and suffered a lot.
Fortunately, you married a good husband.
Although Jiang Chengyang is not a good man, he is a noble man.
He can guarantee that you won't suffer and be bullied.
You need to look ahead.
You need to take care of your family.
You need to serve your husband and have children.
Only then you can have a long life.
Father.
I'm talking about the game.
But you told me that I should have a good life.
You're a woman.
This is your home.
Father.
Do you know why I ran away from home and returned home late at night?
Why didn't I go to my home and ran straight to Chang'an?
Because I was in the far place when the Liu family came to arrest me.
I heard your conversation.
You said that the only place for women is the wedding.
If you find me, you will send me back to the Liu family.
In your heart, I married the Liu family is a great honor.
I left my husband and humiliated myself.
I didn't know that the Liu family was going to kill you.
I...
Mudan.
Now you are different from before.
What's the difference?
You are now the concubine of Jiang Chen'an.
I was wrong about you.
Now I heard that the general admires you.
Jiangfu has no wife.
You should work hard.
Don't repeat the Liu family's mistakes.
Father.
Do you know that you love me and protect me, but you despise me?
Do you know that I ran away from home and didn't care about my family?
I tried to survive in order to live a life of a concubine.
Mudan, you are too simple.
You don't know how difficult it is to support the family.
Besides, you are a woman.
You are talking like this because Jiang Chen'an is supporting you.
Do you really think so?
In your eyes, a woman can only rely on a man.
At least he can make you feel better.
Am I right?
In your eyes, maybe you are just a woman who only knows how to make a living.
But in my heart, you are the most courageous and the most powerful woman.
In fact, when you are in the most difficult time, you also care about the refugees.
You use the medicine of the single-person family.
When you are in the most difficult time, you burn your favorite flower and
you have to put down your dignity and make a deal with the powerful.
I can understand you better.
In order to pass on the message of the family, you can only choose to put your daughter behind the horse.
But until today, you have never really understood what kind of woman your mother and I are.
I can't understand what you think.
So you want me to do it, but I can't do it.
Mudan, why are you so stubborn?
I did it for your own good.
I have decided how to use the woman's body to make a living.
I don't need to talk about it anymore.
It's getting late.
I'd better go back first, in case my auntie is not happy.
Didn't you say you'd stay a few more days?
No, I have a lot of things to do.
Father, you are old.
You don't have to worry about the pharmacy.
I asked Zhoran to bring the money and come here.
It will be changed in two days.
These money should be enough to live in He's and rise again.
From now on, you can live in Luoyang with your mother and daughter.
I will remember your kindness.
I will take care of my own affairs.
Please rest assured.
Mudan!
Why don't you go back after dinner?
I want to eat pancakes tonight.
Okay, I'll make it for you.
No, father, take care.
I will go back.
I'll go.
Your Majesty, the young mistress is back.
So soon?
I thought she would stay in Luoyang for a few more days.
Father said that the young mistress sent the guest away.
She closed the door in advance.
She was in a state of shock.
She knew it.
I hope that my mother can get a bunch of clouds.
But no one cares about them.
The villagers are dying one by one.
The construction site of the mountain is buried.
Too many people died.
Too many.
Wu Bo said that Mudan was killed.
The skin in his hands is different from poison.
It's not the devil who killed us.
It's our enemy.
What happened?
Tell me.
Tell me if you are nuclear.
Vud vars.
He never saw you.
He didn't know you were the daughter of He Dianzhu.
He had a fight with you.
It was all because of his admiration for you.
But he did harm your mother.
It's right for you to hate him.
Does it still hurt?
I know.
You stopped me from killing Wu Bo.
It was all because of me.
You're afraid that I'll find out the truth about the 4 years ago.
You're even more afraid that I'll find out about the water crisis.
I regretted it before the marriage.
I'm sorry.
There's no need to say these three words between us.
But those words...
...are not heard by those who died 4 years ago.
As a drug dealer,
...if you don't give up power,
...you can't protect me and my mother.
As a beneficiary,
...I have nothing to say to him.
But what did those people who died because of the disease do wrong?
I wanted to find out the truth and avenge my mother.
But in the end, I found that...
...no one can hate me.
No one can avenge me.
I always thought that I could do this...
...to bring good and good fortune to others.
But there are so many people...
...who are not only being rewarded,
...but also being forced to live.
The world is full of people.
I suddenly don't know...
...how to be a good dealer.
I don't know how to be a good dealer.
Even if I can be a good dealer,
...what's the point of all this?
Wu Dan.
Ever since you were a dealer,
...you've never earned any money.
You've never done anything wrong.
You've reopened the circle...
...and made those women who are not worthy of being loved...
...to have a place in the world.
Why would you do this?
I've trapped myself in this square.
I can't see the true face of the world.
How can I know what's the truth?
I don't understand.
It's all gone, right?
The accounts for this month are cleared.
All the money has been cleared.
The last one is for you.
Da Fu, Xiao Chun, come with me.
I've summarized the good deeds of everyone...
...and the work experience.
Madam Tang, after I leave,
...I'll arrange everything properly.
I'll make sure everyone has a suitable position...
...in the branch.
If you want to stay in the square,
...you can do it.
Sister, you are...
After this last order,
...the square will be closed for now.
The contract for the flower-pattern house and the bookshop...
...are all in there.
Madam Sun, I'll leave it to you.
I'm also relieved that you'll manage the shop.
The square and the flower-pattern house are all in the capital.
You've given your best effort and achievements.
Yes, Mudan, have you really thought it through?
After this incident, I've reflected on many things.
My previous obsession with the Red House...
...was not a good idea.
I need to clear my mind...
...and understand the real meaning of this business.
Where is the flower?
Mister, the guard has arrived.
He has something important to do.
Let's go!
The flower has bloomed.
To be continued...