Star Media presents
Dmitry Fomenko
Yulia Gavrilovna
For the love of your life.
prefix
Love it Can be etc.
Having patience
To invite the bubbles
And now, in the rain outside the window,
a lot of workers are already standing here.
As long as I drink,
I will shoot arrows and break through the window.
The person I want to kill is Liu Chang.
As long as you leave,
I won't involve the innocent.
You think I will believe you?
Master Liu,
our people are all on the streets.
The market is surrounded by the city.
But there is no blood.
Bullshit.
Fine.
Since you want to stay and die with Liu Chang,
I will help you.
Wait.
Master Liu,
this is not the order of the king.
We can't die here without a reason.
Please forgive us.
Let's go.
Tell me.
I'll see if you dare.
Liu Chang,
it seems you are really not afraid of death.
If what you said is true,
I can't escape death today.
Why not die with you?
Even if I die underground,
I won't let you and Jiang Changyang live well.
But if you are a fake,
I have to think about how to change your fate.
Liu Chang,
do you think I dare not kill you?
Your legs are broken.
Your heart is broken too.
Now you are different from the king of Ning.
You are a bad man.
So what?
Kou Weifeng,
I won.
You are the one who was asked.
And I didn't hear the Jiang Changyang in the mud.
I gave you a chance.
Don't force me.
Liu Chang,
do you think you won?
You wanted to get away from me.
But in the end,
you are just a dog with a bad temper.
Shut up.
Even if you catch me today,
I will kill you every moment in the future.
I told you to shut up.
Do you think I dare not?
Liu Chang,
you can't take me away.
stop.
Ziya.
Xuexi,
this has nothing to do with you.
I advise you not to interfere in the end.
Mudan is my wife.
I don't want to see you.
I will protect her.
This is the family of the traitor.
You are the one who did it.
Do you know the consequences?
You know he is the family of the traitor.
I will tell the king about it in person.
But you,
you are a man of no value.
How dare you hide yourself from Mudan?
How dare you hide yourself from me?
I will kill you.
I will tell the king about the secret of hiding Mudan and the transfer of troops.
Go.
The situation in Jin is very bad.
Father didn't want me to come.
But I'm worried about your safety.
No one will hurt you again.
If you are sad,
cry.
There is no use in crying.
I have more important things to do.
Xuexi,
how did you know I was in Huanyun House?
I was entrusted by my father.
I lost my wife.
My wife was in trouble.
I will die.
Get up, Chuan Yu.
I'm fine.
Get up.
But I didn't...
But I didn't save you.
I didn't protect you.
I was in danger.
But I survived.
Get up.
Get up and talk.
Hurry up.
Get up, everyone.
Get up.
Xuexi told me that
you gathered the secret guards
and hid in the city
to find me.
You saw the light in time.
That's why you told Xuexi to come to rescue you.
I will never forget
your kindness.
If Jiang Changyang has a job,
he will thank you.
You are a great man.
We have no one to blame.
Chuan Yu will follow you
and take you to the police station.
Chuan Yu will follow you and take you to the police station.
Mudan,
the situation is not clear now.
It's too dangerous for you to stay in Chang'an.
Why don't you come back with me?
Your Majesty,
the He family is a very dangerous country.
We can't let them go.
A woman is a woman.
If she kills her husband,
what else can she do?
But those secret guards
are all old foxes.
They are all smart.
Only the Xiao family
is willing to put a seal on the letter.
I have to
make a contribution to the He family.
I will never offend you before the city is built.
But Your Majesty...
Don't think I don't know
what you are thinking.
I dare not.
The most important thing now
is how to get to the throne.
The Ministry of Revenue and the Treasury are in control.
How to subdue those
unstable secret guards.
I don't need to teach you.
I understand.
The pulse is stable and the internal and external are not injured.
I told you to keep your mouth shut.
It's good that you are fine.
Look, you are in a hurry.
I told you I'm fine.
Are you all okay?
Did you get any kind of involvement?
Don't worry.
We are businessmen.
We don't like those powerful people.
Liu Chang is just a巡-women.
He came to check on us.
But he didn't make it difficult for us.
I'm sorry.
Where is my cousin?
How is he?
Li Qing is struggling in the court now.
It's not easy to live.
But luckily, he is alive.
He heard that you are safe.
He told me to keep an eye on you.
I'm fine as long as I'm safe.
Mudan.
Everything is done according to what you wrote in the letter.
Liu Lang, Madam Tang, Madam Sun.
They are all staying in Chang'an to look after the store.
And the gardeners and the gardeners in the garden
are all working in the garden with my father.
As for us, we must go with you.
Don't think that you can just leave us a letter.
It's your fate to live.
It's the fate of Mudan.
But it's a very dangerous trip.
We are still alive.
I don't want you to get involved.
We are not afraid.
We have been defeated.
We have agreed to live and die together.
And the more difficult it is, the more we have to live together.
Now we are both free.
We have been talking for a long time, but we still can't say it.
If we don't go,
how can we be at ease if we stay in Chang'an?
That's right.
Okay.
Then we will go together.
I will definitely protect you.
The three of us will go together.
We will come back together.
We can't miss any of them.
Okay.
We must protect each other.
We will be together forever.
We will never separate.
Never separate.
Da Fu.
In fact, there is only one person in this trip, except the three of us.
Look.
Chunyu.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you hurt?
Mudan.
Have you really thought it over?
If you come back to Hexi with me,
I will definitely protect you forever.
A person and a life,
only for misunderstanding.
And I want Xuexi to help me hide the truth.
Don't worry.
In the future,
I will make everyone think that you are going to stay with me in Hexi.
Take care of yourself.
Take care.
I didn't expect that I would hide so many things from my heart.
But it's really too bitter.
It's not easy to have such a good wife like you.
Now, you are so brave.
And I haven't even seen her for the last year.
Aunt.
Although I'm trying to save myself,
I'm still worried.
I'm afraid that I will be more selfish.
I don't want to see you cry because of her.
Those traitors.
They killed her.
They killed her and her life.
What can I do?
Aunt.
I have a favor to ask.
Mudan, get up and talk.
I'm sorry.
I'm not here to ask for trouble.
I want to ask you to help me avenge Jiang Changyang.
I want to take revenge on the King of Ning.
I want to make all the dead people of the King of Ning suffer.
The two of you will get 50% off.
The little brother will take you to see the beautiful scenery.
A few weeks ago, I sent Chuan Yu to the East of the River to meet General Yu Zheng.
His father was ambushed by the Queen and killed in Chang'an.
He wanted to avenge his father and take revenge on the Emperor.
But General Yu didn't finish his work.
And the East of the River Army was already good at fighting.
So I want to use my business to help them to build their army.
I want to build a great army and gather good weapons.
I want to get more powerful weapons.
When the time comes, I will come back to Chang'an.
I will take the King of Ning and the King of Qing.
The King of Qing will die in the end.
Mudan, I know you don't want to risk your life for him.
I'm not doing this for Jiang Changyang.
When I decided to open the Wu Yongtang, I understood one thing.
Only the Ming army can fight in this world.
Only the valley can be independent and the people can live in peace.
And Jiang Changyang died to see the peace.
I will go for him on the road he hasn't finished.
If I die on this road, I will not regret.
Okay.
I will be with you.
Tell me what you need.
Thank you.
I have some gold bars with Suizhi.
But these are not enough.
Aunt.
I heard from you that you were going to sell gold bars.
are not enough.
My lady,
I heard from you that
you have been to cárceas
and nobles for many years.
Could you go for a taste of it?
Old Hades water pours
As the dry yellow summer reacts
ission of the net
merges with the season
It turns out theide wine was used to be observed by the living people.
They asks for it.
and ask for it again.
I can't explain.
The world is full of the evil.
The world is full of introduces.
Amazingly enough, in fact, it was actually me in the preferences.
You're TEspeaking to me...
I'll not do it again.
Mudan...
I'm afraid it's a little bitter.
It's okay.
It won't be bitter if you drink some tea later.
How is it?
The wolf has been selling the
pit for five days.
Have you not received your monthly salary?
Go and tell the owner.
The tax is getting heavier.
There are not many companions in the account of the owner.
I went to their house a few days ago.
Their female wolf is also selling the pit.
I've got it.
I've got the rice.
Really?
Where is the rice?
At the dock.
Go and see.
What's wrong with my son?
It's just a skin disease.
Dear Hong Kong people,
the rice is sold out.
It's only 50 cents a bag.
We don't have money.
If you don't have money,
you can use the local clothes.
It's hard to find a full-fledged wheat here.
Where did you get the local products?
Yes.
Madam, look.
The dragon-leaf grass you're wearing
is not only a decorative plant.
It's very good for your health.
It can help you to get rid of the disease.
Please take it.
Look here.
There are many kinds of fish.
We've got them all.
If you need,
you can get them.
You can get them.
Do you understand?
Thank you.
It's okay.
We've got them all.
It's your turn.
I want a bag of rice.
Okay.
The fish is poorer than the porridge we ate.
We gave them some money,
but it's not a loss.
Now we need to prepare food for the He Dong Army.
We can't do nothing.
We can help a little.
Come on.
Let's go.
What do you want to buy?
Mom asked me to buy a bowl of oil.
It's good for the body.
But I...
You want to buy this handkerchief for mom?
Mom asked me to find a good citizen.
It will be a good day.
I want to live a comfortable life with my father.
He gave me a bag of rice.
I don't think I can break it.
Take it.
I can't break it.
I only have five cents.
It's the same as buying me a bowl of rice.
Who said it was for free?
You bought this handkerchief.
The oil is equivalent to my money.
You can return it to me in the future.
You and I are not related.
Why did you take it?
Because I'm like your mother.
I hope you can be a good citizen.
When you grow up,
You can pay me five cents.
Take it.
Thank you.
I will study hard.
I will pay you back in the future.
Thank you.
I hope you can be a good citizen.
I will remember.
Thank you.
Don't be afraid.
The people are not treated in time.
Fortunately, they didn't come to me.
The medicine is ready.
Three times a day.
Take it back quickly.
It's a good medicine.
Thank you.
Mr. Yang.
Mr. Feng.
I have no money.
I bought your goods.
I'm sorry for letting you go.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Yang.
What happened here?
Just now,
The army of the Juebei Manzi came to rob.
They told the people in the city
that they would come again tomorrow.
They told us to put all the food and money
in the door.
Isn't there a Hedong army here?
The Juebei army should be afraid.
Didn't you report it?
We reported it.
But we are not familiar with the Juebei army.
The Manzi people
are like the wind.
When the Hedong army arrived,
they had already robbed and left.
The Hedong army
also bought goods.
But they were killed.
A few months ago,
another army came.
Now we are also willing to die.
As long as we don't kill people,
we will rob.
Mr. Feng,
you should go.
If they catch you,
they will rob your goods.
The Juebei Manzi
Who are you?
I am a merchant.
I want to make a big deal with you.
You look like
not the Juebei Iron Banner,
but the hunter.
What do you mean?
I am a hunter.
You look down on us.
I didn't mean that.
Tang is a country of etiquette.
It is more tolerant to other countries.
You only rob and don't hurt people.
It's not a murder.
I'm afraid it's because
there is no food in the family.
I have to do this.
What do you want from us?
I know a Juebei woman.
She told me
that your land is not good for farming.
But cattle are raised very well.
And there are very good horses.
And in our country,
horses can be used to farm and transport goods.
Sheep can be used to eat.
Sheep can be used to make food.
The common food in your country
can be used for a very high profit.
And the cattle can be used to feed.
The sheep can be used to make food.
The common food in your country
can be used for a very high profit.
And the cattle can be used to feed.
Why don't you trade with me?
With money,
can't you buy rice?
We can rob
and get food.
Why do you have to buy it?
General Yuzheng is in charge of the contract.
How long do you have to rob?
And how many people have died
to rob food?
This city
will only get poorer and poorer.
The food you get
will only get less and less.
This is not a long-term solution.
If we trade well,
except for rice,
you can also bring
more good things to your family.
When you get sick,
we have medicine and food.
We can meet and talk.
Isn't it a great joy?
Let's go back and discuss with the people.
I'll give you the answer in three days.
I'm waiting for your good news.
They are gone.
Come out, everyone.
It's safe.
Come out.
Great.
Master Feng is right.
Please accept our bow.
Thank you.
Please get up.
If this is successful,
it's a good thing for me.
I just don't know
if they will agree.
But you don't have to worry too much.
Yesterday I sent a message
to the Hedong Army.
If the people in the north are obsessed,
General Yu Zheng will talk to them in person.
He will solve this problem.
Don't worry.
Thank you, Master Feng.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Go.
Sister.
No need.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I won't take it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you, Master Feng.
Go.
Season 1
The final hospital,
hospital B group
Und reader
Go.
Damn it.
cotton
start
It can't be.
It can't be combination.
What does it take?
Which division would occupy you?
Each division.
from the place in siewir's palace
they don't,
they can't go to
his place.
The blue told her
they come to live with the excellency Life
Princess,
It's important.
Mudan asked me and my father to get it.
I haven't seen Chuan Yu for days.
Where is he?
Mudan asked Chuan Yu to do something.
He'll be back tomorrow.
Why do you send a post?
The drug store's head
thought it's good to work in our business.
He heard I have a capable niece.
He asked me to work with Mudan and his brother.
I'm sorry, live lines are missing.
You look professional.
I'm eating like your brother.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Baiげ Sheng ciento.
Give this to you, come figure.
They're my endlich parents.
They're all really nice.
Take the medicine quickly.
Yes, your highness.
Sit down on this chair.
Sit down.
If Mudan is really released,
Sister Han Yi won't stop us.
She will be the only one to remember.
The great Buddha and the川芋 have made an appointment.
They will be born as the dead.
The川芋 has finally opened its doors.
I've made up my mind again.
I will not let you go.
But who is Jiang Dashan?
I don't have such a bad name.
Then why did you give me the name Jiang Xiaohua?
You are now a traitor.
How can you use your real name?
Just use it together.
Your blood
has reached the ground of Han Yi and Chi Chi.
Even the king of the king can't find them,
so he just divided them up.
You are a traitor.
How can you suffer like this?
You are the best at acting.
You just have to act again and lie to the king.
I can lie to the god of ghosts.
But you,
don't lie to yourself anymore.
I'm not here anymore.
I should let go of the past
and start over.
I...
I've changed my name.
I've traveled to all directions.
I've been to the north of the Jue.
I've seen many vast lands
that you have never seen before.
Why don't you start over?
I'm here tonight
because you are so stubborn
that you can't stop.
Have you forgotten?
You said on the boat
that even if I'm not here,
you can still live a good life.
I'm having a good time these days.
I'm not making money
to save the people,
but to help the He Dong Army
buy military equipment.
I've never let down my wish.
But at this moment,
you in front of me
is not good.
It's just that
I'm a little sad.
I'm sorry.
I'm just a little upset.
I'm sorry you're not here.
You can't see what I've done.
Mudan...
Don't say it anymore.
You grew up in my heart.
I can't put my heart in one place.
I promise you
to be together forever.
Don't go.
Why can I touch you?
Is it a boat?
Zhichuan sent you back to me.
Mudan...
This is in a dream.
The road is on the cute cloud.
The fire-graowaou
with the Stars in the sky
will eventually reach out to you.
But my secret is still hidden.
Shush, ssh.
Walk like a knife in your own eyes.
I'm sorry.
Master, the goods are here.
Coming.
Mr. Du, this is Master Feng.
He came to deliver the goods.
The
goods are here.
Why don't you come in and talk?
You're so generous.
Come on.
Mr. Du, please.
Master, you can take my men to deliver the goods.
Okay.
Chunyu.
Deliver the goods.
Master Feng, you must know a lot of things.
No matter which merchant is in charge of the goods,
I must be filial.
I heard a little bit.
But I only brought two carts of goods today.
I can't afford to buy the goods you have.
After this order, you still have to go north.
The other goods are in the city.
The county magistrate is really well prepared.
Let your men go.
No matter if you take the money or the goods,
you can't leave me without 500 yuan.
Why bother the county magistrate?
I've already prepared a gift for you.
Chunyu, you can go.
I'm going.
Master Feng, you must be filial.
Chunyu.
You have a new fish-trap?
I have a common business with the new fish-trap.
I never touch any of the goods.
County magistrate, you don't look familiar with this fish-trap.
It came from your house.
You didn't recognize it.
How dare you steal from the official's house?
I'll tie you up.
The county magistrate is a fish-trap.
Not only the fish-trap,
but also the poster on your body is a gold-trap.
Of course, I have a lot of evidence.
If I can't leave the city today,
my men will hand over all of these.
Do you know that there's someone in the capital?
Be careful not to get caught in the fire.
I found out that your distant relative is on the side of Prince Ning.
But everyone knows that
the governor of this state is a good official.
I'm afraid that the people in the capital haven't had the chance to intervene.
You've been fired.
The governor of this state is a good official.
But everyone knows that the governor of this state is a good official.
I saw the governor's report.
The good days of the county magistrate are over.
From now on, the people of Zhang County and Shanggu
will not be suppressed by the government.
The city is under the control of the government.
The End