Release arrows.
Defensive formation!
Charge!
Attack!
Archers, loose!
Reload and fire!
Form the formation!
Cavalry, charge!
Your Highness.
It seems Yu Zheng
has truly inherited Yu Chang's legacy.
50,000 soldiers held out this long.
Add fire oil!
Charge!
They deployed hundreds of crossbowmen
in the beginning.
The Central Army's fire oil consumption
is faster than I thought.
At this rate, Prince Ning's fifty barrels
of fire oil will be depleted by nightfall.
The battlefield aligns perfectly
with your predictions.
We'll raid their rear under the cover
of darkness for a surprise attack.
My lady.
The Central Army's flaming arrows
came faster than anticipated.
Mr. Jiang will lead the raid tonight.
Success hinges on this moment.
Reports say Prince Ning's flaming arrows
ravaged the Hedong Army.
Did Mr. Jiang foresee our disadvantage?
Hence, the planned night strike
against Prince Ning.
This raid must proceed
regardless of battlefield developments.
Firstly, capture the leader to cripple the foe.
If Jiang Chang Yang can infiltrate
and capture Prince Ning,
the war could end swiftly,
sparing countless soldiers' lives.
And secondly, the Central Army's camp
between Twin Peaks gives escape routes.
Even if the Hedong Army wins this battle,
Prince Ning could retreat
through the mountain passes.
That terrain favors defense over assault.
He's prepared an exit strategy.
Should he reach Chang'an and twist the narrative,
endless troubles would follow.
Our troops lie concealed at...
Report. Mr. Jiang.
The Central Army halted the flaming arrows,
and crossbowmen were withdrawn.
What of their commanders?
The imperial general and two military governors
are still leading the assaults.
But Prince Ning retreated
to the rear under escort.
Perfect timing.
He quit the field before nightfall.
Seems like he is overconfident of victory.
Prepare arms! Bring my warhorse!
Yes.
Hide hooves.
Yes, hide hooves.
- Yes, hide hooves.
- Yes.
Report. General.
What happened?
When our light cavalry approached Prince Ning's
main camp, they encountered a crossbowmen ambush.
Fire oil ignited simultaneously,
and flaming arrows rained down,
all targeting the light cavalry squad.
Mr. Jiang reacted promptly, leading the vanguard
to raise shields and deflect arrows with sabers.
However, many soldiers' clothing
caught fire and horses fell.
Only a dozen men remain in the squad.
Did they retreat according to plan?
Yes. During the retreat, Mr. Jiang
shot three consecutive arrows at Prince Ning.
Unexpectedly, Prince Ning used a soldier
as a shield to block the first two arrows.
The final arrow hit Prince Ning's shoulder.
How severe is Prince Ning's injury?
Seeing him retreat to the main camp,
I rushed back to report.
His exact injury remains unclear.
Crossbow fire persisted during my return.
The squad may not return soon.
Rear units, keep up!
Mr. Jiang, look.
Accelerate return to camp.
Water! Bring more water!
More water! Fetch more water!
Hurry!
Around three-quarters past the hour of Yin,
shortly after the commander left,
we saw warning smoke rising
in the Central Army's rear.
Then, death warriors
suddenly broke into the east side of our camp.
Mr. Jiang warned never to
underestimate enemies at night,
so we doubled the night guards deliberately.
We quickly captured the death warriors.
But two warriors, seeing their failure,
forced their way into the supply tents
and set fire to provisions.
The fire was too fierce.
Nearly all stored grains were destroyed.
Did they poison themselves?
Yes. They swallowed poison
after being captured, but we kept one alive.
Any interrogation results?
They were hiding on the east side
of the mountain before the battle began.
Small numbers and hiding in bushes
kept them undetected.
Death warriors said Prince Ning
ordered them to wait for the signal.
When our army weakens,
they'd sneak in to assassinate
our commander, but...
Our night raid alarmed Prince Ning,
forcing him to improvise.
Warning smoke rose early tonight,
forcing their desperate charge.
These death warriors have been lurking nearby.
Had they attacked when our morale was low,
the consequences would be dire.
Now, with Prince Ning's sudden order
and our tight camp security,
we have actually minimized the danger.
This was Prince Ning's
final assassination strategy.
However, Prince Ning's current panic
has prematurely revealed his hidden plans.
This may not necessarily
be bad news for the Hedong Army.
However, our night raid failed to capture him,
and this battle may likely drag on longer.
Mr. Jiang, you mustn't blame yourself.
If Prince Ning becomes desperate, it will directly
impact the main battlefield situation.
The Hedong Army still has hope.
Our initial strategy for a quick victory
is now compromised by lost provisions.
Even the bravest Hedong warriors
cannot fight hunger and cold indefinitely.
Recheck our remaining grain reserves
to determine how many days they'll last.
Starting tomorrow, portion sizes
will be halved at every meal.
We must defend the Dongwei Pass at all costs.
Yes!
Madam, Mr. Jiang has instructed me
that if an accident occurs, I must take you all
and leave Hedong for Xinluo as soon as possible.
The cargo ships are docked. We'll depart tonight.
I will ensure your safety and well-being.
If the empire falls into chaos
with the people suffering...
How can any Tang citizen
speak of safety and well-being?
But men need food, and horses need fodder.
If this war prolongs, wouldn't the Hedong Army
be driven to extinction?
Prince Ning secured his own escape route.
But what about us?
The Hedong Army's camp
backs against the Fan River.
If we can't win, could we escape by boat?
Yu Zheng and Jiang Chang Yang aren't cowards.
They'd never flee battle.
Moreover, Prince Ning has smeared
the Hedong Army as rebels.
Fleeing would confirm these false accusations.
What would become of the Hedong civilians then?
The Hedong Army
stands ready to die honorably in battle.
They wouldn't prepare escape vessels in advance.
We have cargo ships
that can carry thousands of tons.
If we load provisions and transport them
to the Hedong Army...
Are you suggesting we cross the Fan River?
But the camp lies on the southwest bank.
Crossing would require
sailing upstream against the current.
The Fan River is wide with treacherous rapids.
If we encounter hidden reefs or rough waves,
we could die and vanish without a trace.
But if successful, delivering provisions
could turn the tide for the Hedong Army.
It would significantly
improve our chances of victory.
I await your orders, Madam.
I'll immediately inventory our stored grain.
I'll have the crew
load the provisions onto the ships.
Wait, this won't be enough.
Yun Niang, take people to borrow grain
from Hedong shops using promissory notes.
- Grain, fodder, collect whatever's available.
- Understood.
Remember to stamp our shop seal
and promise tenfold repayment.
Slow down.
Ms. Feng.
Mr. Yang? What brings you here?
This fishing boat belongs to my father-in-law.
Though not large, it can still
carry over a dozen dan of millet.
Furthermore, the northern regions are cold.
The soldiers exposed to the elements
are prone to catching colds.
I've brought medicinal soups and pills
for the Hedong Army as emergency supplies.
The turbulent Fan River makes crossing perilous.
I appreciate your kindness,
but please, don't take further risks.
It's fine, you drove away
the Juebei bandits for us,
then guided us to prosper through commerce,
ensuring ample food and clothing.
Now it's our turn to repay you.
Don't refuse our help.
Moreover, Hedong faces a crisis
and General Yu is fighting on the battlefield.
We Hedong citizens can't stand idly by!
Exactly! That's right.
Ms. Feng, you set an example of integrity
and righteousness as a merchant.
Though not from Hedong, you are willing
to take risks and deliver provisions for our army.
How could we locals
not contribute to our frontline soldiers?
- Exactly!
- Let's all do our part!
In that case, I gratefully accept your assistance.
Fu, load the ships.
- Yes!
- Loading now!
Come with me.
- Come, pass me one!
- Over here!
- Careful, the deck's slippery!
- Ms. Feng.
My wife preserved many pickles.
They'll arrive shortly.
Thank you. Thank you.
Ms. Feng, our shop has prepared
a small cargo vessel too.
It can carry substantial grain.
Our staff will deliver it soon.
Excellent, thank you.
You're welcome. Let's go.
Thanks.
Mr. Jiang, Prince Ning's flaming arrows
are coming incessantly.
We're running out of even rice gruel.
This can't continue...
Order the light cavalry to prepare arms
and assemble in 15 minutes.
Do you intend to lead the charge personally?
Mr. Jiang, you've lived in Chang'an for years
without battlefield experience.
I may lack Yu Zheng's military prowess,
but I have martial skills.
Each enemy slain is a life saved for our side.
Two kills mean double the gain!
- Mr. Jiang...
- The night raid strategy failed.
With General Yu fighting at the front,
how can I hide in camp like a spectator?
Understood, sir.
Report!
Suspicious boats sighted
on the Fan River behind camp!
Look! We've arrived!
Mu Dan!
This shipment contains rice, flour,
and pickles made by Hedong locals.
It can sustain the troops for two to three days.
I'll find more if needed.
Thank you so much.
Tell the soldiers that the people
of Hedong stand with them.
Urge them not to lose heart.
We await their victorious return!
What's this?
Thank you.
Of course, Lady He.
Fu, Mr. Yang's small fishing boat has no shelter.
If we encounter waves and collisions,
these grains will definitely get damp.
Return to the shop and bring the Juebei
fire-resistant cloth we stored to cover them.
This will help waterproof and protect the grains.
If the boat rocks and accidentally
knocks over oil lamps or torches,
it can also prevent flames
from reaching the provisions.
Alright, I'll go get it.
Go ahead.
Fu,
did I say fire-resistant cloth?
Yes, we still have some stockpiled. Why?
The night raid failed due to fire attacks.
If we make protective gear
from these tough fireproof fabrics...
Protective gear? I'll fetch them.
Hurry!
Our warehouse holds much fire-resistant cloth
from trade with the Juebei Kingdom.
But these cloths are mainly sold
to taverns and kitchens in small sizes.
So I led the Hedong villagers
to stitch the fabrics overnight,
sewing them into large combat cloaks.
We also made face curtains
and chest armor for the warhorses,
specifically designed to counter fire attacks.
I increased the material usage
based on sizing comparisons.
When worn, they can withstand frontal flames.
They won't hinder soldiers
from controlling reins or riding.
Reorganize the cavalry without serious injuries
and prepare for a second night raid.
Light torches and approach the warhorses.
Accustom them to flames
to prevent panic when encountering firewalls.
Yes.
Where is Prince Ning now?
Frontline scouts report Prince Ning
is still recuperating in camp.
We must race against time and reach
the Central Army's rear before dawn.
Understood.
Report! An enemy squad
was detected ten li from our main camp.
They are approaching rapidly.
Overestimating themselves.
Your Highness is truly farsighted.
Jiang Chang Yang indeed won't give up easily.
Ignorant brat! Like an egg striking a stone.
How's the preparation?
Rest assured, Your Highness.
The trenches are now refilled with fire oil.
They'll surely perish in flames.
Make it swift this time. Leave no survivors.
Bring me Jiang Chang Yang's head when you return.
Yes!
Release arrows.
Again!
Summon the cavalry!
Don't let them approach His Highness.
Inform the frontline troops to return
for reinforcement immediately.
Understood!
You're quite adaptable, aren't you?
Jiang Chang Yang, what does it matter
if you've knocked down my army's banner?
The Hedong Army has fewer than 500,000 soldiers.
You won't hold out much longer.
Prince Ning, your army's banner has fallen,
and communications have been severed.
Why must you persist in your futile resistance?
These remaining troops
guarding the rear are already in disarray.
Do you really expect them to win and rescue you?
Fine, let's keep dragging this out then.
Until the Hedong Army is wiped out.
What do I have to fear?
I am His Majesty's elder brother.
What can you possibly do to me?
Moreover, you're the rebel here.
It's true you're His Majesty's brother,
but who's the real traitor remains unclear.
By His Majesty's decree,
all soldiers heed the command!
Prince Ning Li Xian has slandered the Hedong Army.
He persecuted loyal officials
and conspired to rebel.
His treacherous heart deserves execution.
Military Governor Yu Zheng of Hedong
is ordered to apprehend the rebel.
Those who resist shall be deemed accomplices
and executed immediately.
Prince Ning is the true traitor to the nation!
The fundamental nature
of this battle has now shifted.
No.
It's all over.
No!
Central Army troops, listen!
You've never been
a righteous force quelling rebellion.
His Majesty's decree has arrived.
Continued resistance will fully brand you
as treasonous scoundrels
to be executed without pardon.
Let's go.
Come back!
Don't fall for his lies. Return!
Prince Ning, you've always looked down
on merchants and women.
But do you know who delivered this decree?
General Yu and his son are loyal to the throne.
They'll never submit to Prince Ning.
War between them is inevitable.
I must give the Hedong Army
a legitimate justification.
It'll prove at the frontline
that Yu Zheng fights to protect the sovereign.
But they must win this battle.
Only through victory does this become
His Majesty's true edict.
If we lose, it becomes worthless scrap.
The camellias are blooming splendidly.
The azaleas here are also quite beautiful.
The wind's picking up.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
Since all's quiet in the capital,
you should return to Hexi soon.
Take care, Noble Consort.
Do you think waving this so-called decree
will shake my army's morale?
The authenticity of this decree
remains unverified.
Soldiers! A general in the field
may disregard imperial orders.
Here, you obey me!
Jiang Chang Yang, I ask you this.
With less than 500,000 troops,
how can you possibly defeat me?
Even if you capture me now,
the Hexi Army and Jiannan Army
won't stand idly by.
To prove they're not rebels,
they'll fight to the death to save me.
Boy, remember this.
The victor of this war
writes the narrative of justice.
Look. Reinforcements are coming!
My troops have arrived. What did I tell you?
Your Highness!
Li Xian!
It seems justice favors the Hedong Army.
Prince Ning, haven't you always
wanted my list of allies?
Today, I formally introduce you
to a crucial ally of mine.
Xiao Wen Yan, you traitorous rat!
Soldiers! You are the fiercest
warriors of the Central Plains!
You should share glory and shame
with your commander!
Take up arms! Follow me to retake the capital!
When we succeed,
your descendants will bask in eternal glory!
Prince Ning, are you finally
dropping the act and openly rebelling?
So what? Fight! Let the battle commence!
Your Highness, our troops are demoralized,
and we've lost allies.
We can no longer fight.
I misjudged you all along.
Despicable! Repaying kindness with betrayal!
You lost not just a leg,
but your backbone and courage!
I merely adapt to prevailing circumstances.
My earlier loyalty followed the greater trend.
Now, my rebellion aligns with the new trend.
My principles remain unchanged.
It's you who no longer
represents the tide of history.
You...
I, Liu Chang, Assistant Minister of War,
voluntarily surrender.
I acknowledge my grave crimes deserve death.
At great risk, I captured the rebel leader.
Prince Ning conspired
to eliminate loyal officials.
I hold evidence of all his crimes.
I'll fully cooperate
with General Yu Zheng's investigation.
Let's purge corrupt officials
and restore imperial order.
Hedong Military Governor Yu Zheng is ennobled
as Prince Jun for quelling rebellion.
You'll remain in the capital
to oversee investigations
and eradicate Prince Ning's faction completely.
I accept this decree.
Thank you for Your Majesty's mercy.
Liu Chang, Vice Minister of War.
I am here.
A rebel accomplice deserves death.
Yet, your battlefield confession
and capturing enemies are merits.
Given your sincere repentance
and merit-earning surrender,
I'll show leniency.
You'll be stripped of position
with your property confiscated.
But your death sentence is commuted.
I kneel in gratitude, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I have one final request.
Go on.
Your Majesty, I beseech you
to grant County Princess amnesty.
Although she is the daughter of Prince Ning,
she was never involved in the rebellion.
The Li imperial lineage is precious.
The County Princess shares your royal blood.
I implore Your Majesty's mercy to spare her life.
We are but powerless commoners
with neither status nor heirs.
We pose no threat to stir any waves.
May Your Majesty show compassion
befitting the Heavenly Family's benevolence.
Master, General Yu,
Brother Zhang Qiu, She Yan,
and all fallen comrades,
now that calamities have ended and reforms begun,
may you all rest in peace.
As for your dearest friends,
I shall dedicate myself to protecting them.
Please rest assured.
May Heaven bless
the Great Tang with enduring peace.
Are you truly determined
to abandon the identity of He Wei Fang?
These extraordinary experiences
can't be explained logically to outsiders.
Moreover, the treacherous
Floral Envoy has already perished.
Why shouldn't I remain
as this carefree shopkeeper Xiao Hua?
Whether I remain Jiang Chang Yang matters not.
I merely lament losing my Jiang Mansion.
Exactly! Those flower-cultivating soils
I painstakingly nurtured...
Why don't we sneak in and steal that soil back?
I'm homeless now,
and you're still obsessing over soil?
A corrupt official should've anticipated this day.
But the Fragrance Garden
has ample space and many rooms.
Pick any chamber you like.
I won't disdain a live-in husband.
Though you left Chang'an, your remaining staff
proved remarkably capable.
Within just over a year,
they managed to reclaim the Fragrance Garden.
With such expanded business,
numerous visitors will come calling.
I must teach you some trickery arts.
Should we encounter old acquaintances,
escaping won't be so awkward.
Keep your petty thieving tricks to yourself.
My silver tongue suffices for protection.
And if that silver tongue gets occupied?
What do you propose?
Taking liberties in broad daylight, aren't you?
Mercy, my lady!
Having left Chang'an so long, I've yearned
for the palace-brewed Mulberry Wine.
Exhilarating!
Fortunately, Li Xian coveted that allies' list.
Had he truly sought your death...
Without mortal peril,
how could we find hope in desperation?
I should thank his precise bladework,
taking half my life yet sparing a breath.
Having cheated death once,
how can you remain so reckless?
To sacrifice for the nation's crisis,
I meet death as homecoming.
Master's teachings stay with me.
Even had I perished fulfilling duty that day...
I'd have no regrets.
You needn't blame yourself, Your Majesty.
Sui Zhi, you know that.
I never saw you as a subject, but as a brother.
So no matter how you died, I will...
Don't think I don't know what you're scheming.
You want to get me drunk
so I'll grant your request.
Now that power is returned to the sovereign,
peace reigns over land and sea.
Our wrongfully deceased colleagues and the people
of Mengzhou can finally rest in peace.
Now, we'll witness Mr. Third's
grand ambitions unfold.
My childhood wishes are all fulfilled.
One shouldn't be too greedy in life.
You've always been loyal and righteous.
Why not clear your name and restore your status?
Mu Dan and I have complicated identities.
If we publicly return from the dead,
there'd be too much to explain.
It's too much.
Besides, I don't care
about high positions or eternal fame.
If you don't care about family reputation,
what about Mu Dan?
She naturally shares my view.
The empire is vast,
and officials across prefectures
can't monitor everything.
While Mu Dan trades across the lands,
I'll be your watchful eyes.
We'll ensure no corrupt officials or bandits
remain wherever we pass.
You clearly just want to travel
and enjoy life with Mu Dan,
leaving me lonely and desolate.
Mr. Third, dare you repeat
those words before Consort Shu?
Mr. Third.
Sui Zhi.
Your shop is reopening soon. Why the long face?
I still don't know
how to tell everyone about leaving.
Rather than face tearful farewells,
how about we slip away quietly?
We'll sneak away on your flower boat...
That won't do!
After finally returning safely,
leaving like that would hurt everyone.
How are the preparations coming along?
Don't worry. Yun Niang's got it.
Everything will be ready soon.
Mr. Lv, come here.
Mr. Lv. Over here, Mr. Lv.
Our previous plan isn't perfect.
What do you think they're doing?
♫ In endless Chang'an,
the zither's melody distant ♫
♫ Plum and willow trees bask in the sunshine,
as splendor returns with the year ♫
♫ Copper palace battlements,
songs and dances, glass goblets ♫
♫ Idle clouds and duckweed,
a thousand flowers burst forth ♫
♫ Time passes gracefully,
affairs settle like fading smoke ♫
♫ Let the years go by,
carried by the wind to early desires ♫
♫ If the heart is like water,
the bloom is ever-present ♫
♫ Still cherish the moon of my hometown,
to meet for long ♫
♫ The distant night sky strewn with stars,
reflecting the lovely moon ♫
♫ The peony's magnificent beauty
fills the Fragrance Garden ♫
♫ With a heart as my lantern,
I don't mind the distant mountain paths ♫
♫ The flute's sound,
a fleeting life's wishes fulfilled ♫
♫ Time passes gracefully,
affairs settle like fading smoke ♫
♫ Let the years go by,
carried by the wind to early desires ♫
♫ If the heart is like water,
the bloom is ever-present ♫
♫ Still cherish the moon of my hometown,
to meet for long ♫