Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
Peony Whispers Team @Viki.com
You saved my entire family.
I originally thought you did it for justice, and I was grateful.
I didn't expect that you had known my daughter for some time.
You even encouraged her to practice medicine and open a clinic.
If it weren't for a customer of the flower guild informing me, I'd still be in the dark.
Chun'er's reputation was almost ruined by you.
We didn't do wrong. Xiao Chun sincerely likes healing and helping others.
Guild Master, Xiao Chun has a talent for medicine.
Even Master Physician Fu from the Imperial Medical Bureau has praised her.
If you forcibly keep her at home and force her to marry and have children,
I'm afraid she'll suffer for a lifetime.
Marrying is the right path for a woman!
I wholeheartedly want the best for her and to find her a good family!
But you two? Indulge her mischief!
Pushing her into a pit of fire!
You may leave. Stay away from Chun'er!
- See the guests out!
- Yes.
The clinic and practicing medicine were my own ideas, not influenced by others.
Master, she smashed the betrothal gifts the Hu family sent, and we couldn't stop her.
You were gentle and obedient before. How did you turn into this?
This is my true nature.
Previously, I was afraid of upsetting you, so I pretended to be gentle and decent.
Father, I don't want a blind marriage. I want to keep practicing medicine.
A woman practicing medicine is looked down upon. It's a disgrace to feminine virtue.
Respectable families will look down on you. Do you intend never to marry?
As for a so-called good husband,
if he looks down on me because I'm a female physician, he isn't worth marrying.
You can't distinguish right from wrong, uttering wild words.
Just look at you,
if your mother saw this, she wouldn't rest in peace even in the afterlife!
May I ask, Father, was my mother not virtuous enough?
Where was her happiness?
Because you said appearing in public was a disgrace to family values,
- she was confined and died in melancholy!
- Are you blaming me?
Do you know what she truly loved? Do you know what her ideals and ambitions were?
You buried my mother's life. Are you going to bury mine too?
You love flowers, so you can make a career out of it.
Why can't Xiao Chun do what she loves just because she's a woman?
Isn't that too tyrannical?!
Xiao Chun's skillful hands and open heart make everyone in Huamanzhu respect her.
The patients she has cured respect and love her even more.
We were wrong to hide our actions from you.
But there's nothing wrong with Xiao Chun practicing medicine.
Shopkeeper He, you deviate from convention.
You became a concubine for an official. I can't let my daughter take that path!
Father.
Chun'er, you've grown up now.
Now that you have friends and confidence, do you no longer need this family?
Let me ask you one last time, do you want to stay and be my daughter
or step out of this door to pursue your so-called path of medicine?!
I really can't have both?
No.
From now on, the Lu family doesn't have an unfilial daughter like you!
My father once said that dandelions scattered by the wind are unlucky in a home.
Because I liked them, we planted them anyway.
But he didn't know that I regarded this as medicine.
It was for the roots once the flowers fell, to treat his throat pain and lung abscess.
But now, the words have come true, and we are indeed scattered.
It's because he cares so much that he would be this stubborn.
Xiao Chun, for the next few days, stay at Fragrance Garden.
Give your father some time, so he can think it over.
Yes, we'll come back after Guild Master's anger subsides.
He can't bear to not acknowledge you.
Young Master Liu has never seen 100 boats set sail together.
I want to take him to broaden his horizons. You don't mind, do you?
Of course not.
You don't ride horses, do you? Would you like to share a horse with Chuan Yu?
You can enjoy the bright spring scenery of Chang'an along the way.
I've always treated you with respect. Where did I offend you?
What's wrong?
The Floral Envoy won't let me on this carriage, sending me off to ride a horse.
Perhaps he thinks I'm too sickly and fear I'll spread illness.
But how could I possibly ride such a tall horse? What if I accidentally fall?
Are you so intolerant of me?
Arguing or joking is fine, but falsely accusing me of endangering you isn't right, is it?
If you want to share the carriage with me, just say so. Why lie and slander others?
This isn't the behavior of a true and virtuous gentleman.
I know I was wrong.
Since you know you're wrong, shouldn't you apologize to your brother-in-law?
I'm sorry, I won't do this again in the future.
It's okay.
I won't go to the dock today. Sister...
Sister, you and Brother-in-law should set off now. Don't miss the time.
All right. Since we've promised you, how can we break our word?
I'll go with Chuan Yu and get the horse.
Get on the carriage.
Your sister has always been like this.
She still explains the principles, and also fears you may actually get hurt.
Just ride with us in the same carriage.
No need to thank me. Being a brother-in-law, it's the right thing to do.
Candided haws.
Fragrant sachets!
This river is wide, and the dock is extraordinary.
Pitch-pot for prizes!
Young Master Liu, look.
There's a pitch-pot for prizes stall over there. Let's go and play together.
Pitch-pot for prizes!
My arm strength is insufficient. I'm sure I'll miss the target, so forget it.
I understand.
I'm a humble servant while you're Young Madam's younger brother.
You definitely wouldn't want to play with people like us.
- That's not the case, I…
- Then you're willing! Let's go.
Young Master Liu, go play. Give that to me.
Let's go! Come on.
Have fun.
I just said you're not scheming and magnanimous.
Why are you teasing Young Master Liu now?
I just gave Chuan Yu a glance. Chuan Yu used his methods against him.
Your bias is strong, you're blaming me now.
Young Master Liu is sensitive in nature and somewhat biased in his actions.
I actually know all his little tricks.
But I believe that with careful instruction, this can be changed.
We're all family, naturally, we should be more tolerant.
Why are you arguing with a child?
Okay, okay, it's your good brother.
In the future, I'll be more patient and teach carefully, okay?
Previously, the sailors represented them in discussions.
Now the letter says it's the bowman who wants to see me.
I don't know who the other party is.
I don't know if he'll be satisfied with the gifts I brought.
Make way, make way.
Make way.
- Hey, watch your step.
- Make way.
Make way.
What are you looking at?
The prosperous scene.
The finest spring tea!
Here it is, please enjoy.
Miss He.
I'll head in then.
Please come inside.
You're here.
What does this mean? My husband is still waiting by the shore.
If he sees that I haven't returned for a long time, he'll definitely cause a scene.
I know your temperament.
If I make any move, you'll jump into the river to leave.
When does it need to come to him?
Since we're here, why not have a cup of tea?
Let's discuss business before leaving.
What exactly does Prince Ning want to smuggle?
Normal merchant ships can't hold it, so he needs to privately build such a big ship.
It snows in the winter, and the docks freeze over.
The boatman told me the rules of the ships.
When the snow melts and sailing resumes,
the first block of river ice is kept to brew tea.
To bless the new year with calm seas and smooth journeys.
I didn't originally believe it. But since I thought I'd see you today,
I decided to seek some good fortune.
You invited me here today, what exactly for?
It's been a long time since I last saw you. Let's reminisce first, then talk business.
After my grand wedding, I made up my mind
to handle my duties well and achieve political accomplishments.
Then greet you with a new version of myself.
These days I've been dredging silt, expanding the river channels,
forming a fleet, and expanding navigation.
I've won public praise.
It's because I thought of you,
that I designated this pier for both official and civilian use.
A market is open for crew purchases.
Merchants became wealthy, and the people found convenience.
Today's prosperity is also due to your contribution.
Congratulations on achieving your past vision, but this has nothing to do with me.
It wasn't easy for you, so I hope you'll cherish it.
Let's talk about matters related to you then.
If you transport goods here, you can be exempt from taxes and enjoy priority departure rights.
Thank you for the kind offer, but I can't accept a reward without merit.
I hope you'll treat me the same as other merchants.
You're indeed the same old He Wei Fang.
But I'm no longer the Liu Chang I used to be.
Now I have nothing but patience for my goals and the people I seek.
I'll break next year's river ice with you and brew tea together.
We can't be a couple, but I hope for a long-lasting companionship.
Abducting a married woman, neglecting husbandly virtues.
If Prince Ning heard your words, what would he think?
Liu Chang, I originally thought you would've realized something.
I didn't expect that you've not only made no progress, but still indulge in delusion.
You and I have long been unrelated.
If you act willfully, it'll only harm others and yourself.
I've said my piece. If there's nothing else, please dock.
Mu Dan.
We have a long future ahead of us.
- Dock.
- Yes, Sir.
Young Master Jiang, you seem quite free today.
Accompanying us and waiting here for me.
There's truly no other purpose?
Liu Chang was meeting with you. As your husband, shouldn't I watch closely?
Since you knew it was him, why didn't you tell me in advance?
I only knew he had built this pier.
Who would have thought he would disguise as a bowman and secretly meet someone else's wife?
Don't talk nonsense.
I didn't have a secret meeting with him. My relationship with him is innocent.
I was here to discuss business.
You didn't even present the gifts. Seems the discussion didn't go well.
Just now I happened upon this item in the market.
I heard the mother-of-pearl bracelet can reflect light.
By day, it shows wealth, and by night, it lights up with beautiful people.
In the future, it'll be more convenient for you to tend flowers and plants at night.
This is nice.
Isn't this like an affordable and portable night pearl for commoners?
This is a good business opportunity.
In your mind, there's nothing but business?
Just now on the boat, you two...
I saw that this fruit wasn't ripe. Fortunately I didn't eat it.
Enjoy the sourness.
He Wei Fang, even His Majesty never asked me to taste poison, you…
Young Master, the merchants appreciate your kindness and have sent you another batch of tea cakes.
Young Master strolled around the newly opened market at the pier after work.
Then, he returned to the Taoguang Courtyard.
For dinner, he had two pieces of Hu cakes and a bowl of soup.
He also ate cherries after the meal.
Cherries? He never liked eating this fruit.
But the young servant said not only did he eat it, he ate a lot.
Maybe this year's cherries are big and sweet, so he wanted something fresh.
I understand Zi Shu. He's stubborn,
it's very difficult to change what he likes or dislikes.
How could he suddenly change his taste?
After Zi Shu falls asleep, secretly call over the people who were with him one by one.
- I want to interrogate them.
- Yes.
The Princess has made herself very clear. What are your plans?
Your Highness, Floral Haven has always conducted business properly without any errors.
Now, Miss He is on good terms with Consort Shu, and the Floral Envoy's beloved wife.
I'm incompetent and really don't know how to handle this.
Is it incompetence or unwillingness to handle it?
I dare not.
Your Highness, I heard He Wei Fang incited the Guild Master's daughter to leave home.
She even exposed herself in her clinic to diagnose illnesses for people.
He Wei Fang treated the Lu family like this, yet the Guild Master endures it.
I'm afraid it's truly incompetence.
How can the position of guild master be held by someone incompetent?
When this flower withers, if Floral Haven is still around,
there's no need for the Lu family to exist.
Your Highness, please allow me to report!
Stop the carriage!
Who is so presumptuous and dares to run into the Princess' carriage!
I'm from the flower guild and am willing to share Your Highness's worries.
Go and make arrangements properly. Act cautiously,
don't say what you shouldn't.
I understand.
Once this matter is handled well, the guild will change.
My daughter, you've been so wronged.
Everyone!
After taking the Tranquil Health Clinic Yunbin Pill, Madam Wu died.
Ruthless merchants manufacture fake medicine, harming lives!
Today, we must give justice to the victim!
Hundreds of Yunbin Pills have been sold without any incidents.
I took Madam Wu's pulse.
Her constitution suits Yunbin Pill. There would definitely be no problem.
There must be other reasons.
As a woman, what do you know about medical principles?
You've just being tricked by He Wei Fang to do business.
- Don't make mistake after mistake!
- No.
The real harmful scoundrel is He Wei Fang! Come out, He Wei Fang!
- Come out!
- Harmful scoundrel!
The harmful scoundrel is He Wei Fang!
There's nothing wrong with the clinic's pills! I have evidence!
Everyone, I know the sale of medicine involves the health of the people, so we must be cautious.
A part of every batch of medicine from the clinic is stored in the storeroom.
- That's right.
- This is the sample on the day Madam Wu bought it.
The storeroom records the dates of deposit and withdrawal on a slip.
There is a seal on this brocade box, which can prove that I've never touched it.
I will hand over this box sealed intact to the authorities for inspection.
To prove that there's absolutely no problem with our clinic's pills.
Madam Wu's death has nothing to do with Tranquil Health Clinic.
She's willing to let authorities inspect it. She must have a clear conscience.
- There definitely shouldn't be a problem.
- Exactly.
- Better to investigate thoroughly.
Miss He, what's the point of proving the pills are harmless?
If the medical skill is poor and misdiagnosis occurs, even good medicine
can still cause death.
The coroner's report is here,
proving Madam Wu's stomach was extremely weak and died from food consumption.
But her diet was no different from usual, except for the recently bought Yunbin Pill.
This medicine is the culprit!
Do you believe the arguments of a deceitful merchant, or the words on paper?
Give me back my daughter's life.
Madam. Calm down.
- This is the Yunbin Pill.
- Xiao Chun!
The harmful, life-taking medicine cannot be kept.
Stop hitting her!
Tranquil Health Clinic can't stay!
- Give it back to me.
- Take them away!
- What are you doing?
- Stop!
- Move!
- This has nothing to do with the clinic!
- You've got the wrong person. It wasn't us!
Give me back my daughter.
Don't cry, Xiao Chun. I'm all right.
Don't worry about me.
I dragged you into this today. I'm sorry.
If you hadn't helped me open the clinic, Cao Yu Ying wouldn't have found this excuse.
I just don't know who the person behind him is.
They even bribed the County Magistrate.
We'll know sooner or later.
What's most important is how we prove our innocence.
If I could closely examine Madam Wu, I could find why she died.
Unfortunately, we're trapped here,
I can't do anything.
I don't know if my father has heard about this.
Would he be worried?
When people are in distress,
the first person they think of is the one they care about the most.
You were angry with him before, but now he's still the one you worry about most.
Don't cry anymore.
After we get out,
you should go home and have a good talk with him. Okay?
Don't cry.
Half an incense stick time, finish speaking, and then leave.
Thank you, Sir.
Father...
Hurry, go on.
Chun'er.
Father.
How did you get injured like this?
It was Mu Dan protecting me,
- otherwise, it would've been worse.
- If you had listened and stayed home to get married,
you wouldn't have to suffer like this.
Shopkeeper He, you protected my daughter in times of trouble.
I'm immensely grateful.
But you women doing business ultimately caused trouble.
Do you also think that my poor medical skills caused someone's death?
That's not important. Rescuing you two is what matters most.
This is important. It's the most important thing to me.
Today's disaster wasn't because of my practice. We were deliberately framed.
I researched the prescription for months. Hundreds have taken it without adverse effects.
Patients whom I've never met were willing to trust my medical skills.
Why is it worthless in your eyes? Why won't you trust me?
- You're my father.
- Xiao Chun.
Guild Master, it's really not Xiao Chun's fault.
It started because of me. I implicated her.
I'll definitely find a way to prove Xiao Chun's innocence.
The key to this case now is whether there's a problem with the medicine.
You're already in such a condition. How can you prove her innocence?
I told you not to push her into the fire pit.
A woman practicing medicine will constantly encounter problems.
Since you're convinced that my medical practice caused a disaster, dishonoring the Lu family,
in the future, you don't have a daughter anymore.
Guild Master, please go back.
It's come to this point, and you're still so stubborn.
Do you really want to die in prison?!
Guild Master, can you really bear to let Xiao Chun bear a murder charge?
Will you let it end like this, unclear and unresolved?
Calmly think it over.
If we really caused her death, why won't the County Magistrate hold a public trial?
Why would he rather violate the law to use private punishment against us?
Why force us to confess and sign?
Only by clarifying all these issues
can Xiao Chun truly be exonerated.
It really can shine at night.
Jiang Chang Yang didn't lie to me.
In times of trouble,
was the first person I thought of... really you?
Xiao Chun's father had to bribe all around to get in.
You came in so easily, you're indeed the Floral Envoy.
The case hasn't yet been clarified, yet they dare torture you.
Who gave the order?
In Chang'an, who else can pin such a crime on me without due process?
And ignore your dignity to accuse me of such a great crime?
Naturally, it could only be that person.
Where are we going?
Taking my wife away from here.
No, if I go with you,
it would truly make me a profiteer who relies on official power to take lives?
Someone is putting pressure on the Magistrate. He won't handle it impartially.
I must thoroughly investigate this case
and find irrefutable evidence to bring it to trial.
I want Cao Yu Ying and the County Magistrate to see.
Let the entire city's people and the person behind this see.
Xiao Chun and I will walk out of this cell with dignity, innocent.
All right.
However, if I do nothing when my wife is in trouble, isn't that suspicious?
You must already have a plan in mind.
If there's anything you need, just let me know.
Thank you for your righteous support.
Although I can't leave this cell now,
I've already planned all the matters regarding the investigation.
Just pass on a message for me.
How is it?
Envoy Jiang, Madam Wu had previously given birth.
It wasn't the weak stomach that led to her death.
When she should've been nourished, she consumed large amounts of toxic cold food.
This resulted in continuous bleeding and blood deficiency, leading to death.
I'm worried that the coroner had been bribed. We changed the person inspecting,
but still couldn't diagnose the illness. Why is this?
Most coroners are men and naturally understand common illnesses,
but many women are too embarrassed to seek treatment when ill.
They haven't seen as many female patients as we female physicians have.
It's common for them to overlook hidden ailments in female corpses.
No wonder Mu Dan asked me to message Consort Shu to find a female physician.
The Yunbin Pill is mild and harmless.
Madam Wu must have died from consuming something else.
I understand.
Please convey my gratitude to Consort Shu upon returning to the palace.
Young Master.
Da Fu has followed Madam's arrangements and gathered all the evidence.
Madam Tang learned from the flower guild's floriculturist,
Madam Wu was Cao Yu Ying's concubine, usually hidden in Dingzi Alley.
He doesn't understand medicine, so five days ago, he found a physician,
said his concubine had just given birth and asked about dietary restrictions.
Next, he went to a pharmacy and bought some cold items for postpartum women.
Someone in Dingzi Alley saw him carrying crabs and bezoar to Madam Wu's home.
The next day, her death was reported.
Da Fu has obtained testimony from all parties.
There's a purchase receipt from the pharmacy, and food scraps from Madam Wu's kitchen.
Tomorrow in court, Madam will surely be able to clear her name.
Young Master, rest assured.
To ensure no future trouble, there's still someone I must meet with.
Why did you have the time to grace Prince Ning Residence today?
These days, my concubine was framed and suffered imprisonment.
I was so furious that I made a scene at the government office.
However, I unexpectedly found something missing from your residence, so I came to return it.
So, you're here to demand justice.
He Wei Fang caused me to fall from my horse.
I didn't kill her, that was already merciful.
Your plight invokes sympathy, but what's done cannot be undone.
Now you've married your beloved as you wished.
His Highness sought justice for you and promoted Zi Shu to Deputy Transport Officer.
Now he's flourishing like the rising sun, and His Highness has gained a valuable person.
It can be said that everyone is satisfied and got what they wanted.
Why do you keep holding onto my wife?
How can the justice my father sought for me
make up for the heart-wrenching pain I suffered?
I can't say whether it can be made up for or not.
But since His Highness promised me at that time, I don't regret this decision.
If you insist on regretting the move,
I don't mind being a scoundrel and making a scene in front of His Majesty.
The granted position can be withdrawn.
What exactly do you want?
You suffered from falling off the horse, and my concubine was seriously injured in prison.
In my opinion, let's call it even and put this matter behind us completely.
From now on, I'll continue to maintain a close relationship with His Highness.
However, you and Zi Shu should have less interaction with us two,
so as not to trigger distress.
After all, the most important thing for you two is the harmony between spouses.
What do you think, Princess?
Let's do as you say.
Returning the lost item was not easy.
A slightest negligence may result in losing it again. I hope you'll cherish it.
Your Highness, are you really going to let He Wei Fang go just like that?
Jiang Chang Yang cherishes Miss He so much, and she has no interest in Zi Shu.
It seems Zi Shu doesn't have a chance.
Let it be.
Yes.
What about Cao Yu Ying?
Rest assured, Your Highness. He still has a family.
No matter what crime he's convicted of, he'll bear it and won't speak carelessly.
I'll handle everything properly. Young Master won't find anything out.
Cao Yu Ying poisoned a civilian woman and framed others.
The evidence is conclusive. He ought to be executed!
The execution will take place after autumn.
The two from Tranquil Health Clinic are innocent and are to be released immediately.
- Great!
Animal! Give me back my daughter!
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
Peony Whispers Team @Viki.com
'Fragrance Recital' - Zhang Zining
♫  On the endless road to Chang'an,
the zither and lute's melody echoes from afar  ♫
♫  Plum and willow trees greet the Spring,
as splendor returns this year  ♫
♫  Copper battlements shine as songs, dances, and glasses fill the palace air  ♫
♫  Idle clouds and drifting duckweed, with a thousand flowers blooming  ♫
♫  Time flows gracefully, with moments gathering in the fading mist  ♫
♫  Let the years pass, carried by the wind toward long-held desires  ♫
♫  If the heart remains as still as water, youth becomes eternal  ♫
♫  Still cherishing the moon of my hometown, yearning to meet again  ♫
♫  The distant night sky, scattered with stars, reflects the gentle moon  ♫
♫  The peony's exquisite beauty fills the fragrant garden  ♫
♫  With my heart as a lantern, I fear not the journey through distant mountain paths  ♫
♫  The jade flute's music fills a fleeting life with meaning  ♫
♫  Time flows gracefully, with moments gathering in the fading mist  ♫
♫  Let the years pass, carried by the wind toward long-held desires  ♫
♫  If the heart remains as still as water, youth becomes eternal  ♫
♫  Still cherishing the moon of my hometown, yearning to meet again  ♫