I'm not sure if I can get the first one, but I'll try.
Episode 1
Looks like you're the first one here.
You're the first one here.
Hu Di!
Hu Di?
I've heard of him.
Three years ago,
In the martial arts
哎,你是因为这个鼻子喊灵才叫虎底的吗?
嗯,将虎没有散,不过我的能力不仅仅是鼻子。
你这个面具是在哪儿做的?
你听上了增上,也给我来一个。
这才是那是西域悬铁,天下寒有,仿造不了。
侯大人,看我这儿,我这儿也不有意思。
I'm a good friend of the world.
I can't make up for it.
Lord Hu, I have to remind you.
Don't take it easy and take it easy.
Be careful and come and kill me.
Who is this?
You're joking, Hu Di.
I'm just a simple and pretty girl.
Why are you laughing?
In the coffin, everyone is calling me old fox.
I didn't expect that.
I can still recognize you as a little fox.
What a nuisance.
I know how to teach a fox.
You have no strength.
Now, start.
Run!
Take this.
Thank you.
This is the Taoist Master.
Let me introduce you to him.
This is the first time in a month.
If we win, we can let the three-eyed demon
invite the people who want to fight us.
Three-eyed demon?
Yes.
It's said that he has 30 points.
With my experience,
the battle is not suitable for the enemy.
It's not a clue anyway.
So, what should we do?
The winner is...
Gui Shu Cheng.
Do you have any more challengers?
You have a wound.
It's not suitable for you to fight again.
You have more?
Of course.
It's time to fight.
Okay.
The winner is in the arena.
The game begins.
You are laughing too much.
I won't fight again.
What's your goodwill?
I don't have goodwill.
Use my sword.
Take it.
Didn't you owe me a life?
I have no regrets.
I lost.
There is no way you can lose in the ghost world.
Since you are here,
you are my opponent.
This is the last fight.
If you win,
you will be the leader.
I will win.
You are the leader?
Let's fight till the end.
The late emperor.
Okay.
Let's fight till the end.
You are so good.
I can't believe I lost.
Winner is...
The winner is...
The Golden Knight.
Hurry up.
Let's go to meet him.
Yes.
What's going on?
My old friend.
You are too scared.
You can't talk about it.
I am not a coward.
How about it?
You won the battle.
You are a loser.
As long as I am with you,
I will be fine.
I won't give up.
I will laugh.
Why don't you come to me?
How dare I not fight?
What rules do you have?
You know him again?
He is my old friend.
Then why did you let me fight?
Friends are friends.
He has to follow his rules.
Since he is your friend,
why didn't you fight the rules?
Why didn't you fight the rules?
What do you want to ask?
Feng Huan.
Who is the real brother behind this?
You are looking for...
Pan Honghao.
The mask.
What do you mean?
There are many people like you in the martial world.
The martial world is all about the mask.
People in the martial world are not people.
Are you the one who is the real brother?
Did you ask the victim's family name?
Chief.
Two seniors from Daoist School.
Is it convenient for you?
We are.
Who is the real brother?
Duan Man is his.
He wants to define me.
This.
The day just now.
Who killed my daughter?
He must let this person die.
You are a master.
Why are you talking like that?
I am a master.
I have been practicing martial arts for a long time.
I think I understand.
I have been practicing.
Well.
I have been in the Demon Realm for a long time.
Really?
But I have been in the martial world for a long time.
Have you ever been in a fight with anyone?
Well.
I have been in a fight with a girl named Xue.
And a girl named Fada Yuxue.
My daughter mentioned Xue Yu Dafa and Xue Shenjiao.
Xue Shenjiao?
Have you heard of it?
It seems that the breakthrough is here.
Those dead bodies have a strong blood smell.
It seems that they were in a place where they bought blood.
By the way.
The girl mentioned that she found a pair of shoes.
She wanted to harm people.
She said that she needed to investigate.
I told her not to interfere with the blood.
I didn't expect that.
Everyone.
Please remember to love the weapon that the murderer used.
It should be the highest.
God of Heaven, blood and fire.
Protect the world and the world.
Remember to be with us.
Always be with us.
God of Heaven, blood and fire.
Protect the world and the world.
After the love was gone.
People escaped the trap.
But they thought that there was blood on the weapon.
They couldn't understand the blood.
They lost their lives.
Finally.
They died in the door of the Dali Temple.
How could this be?
I have already tried.
I hope you can understand.
Chun Yang Qian was found by Ling Ai.
Now, I will return it to you.
You can stay here.
I hope that Hu Di Dai can protect you.
He will be the murderer.
My daughter.
Look.
The one you picked.
What else do you want?
I want this one.
It seems that
as Dao Xing and your master said,
the murderer is related to the blood god.
They need a lot of blood.
There will be a death.
And the red robe that the three eyes said.
The blood god.
It's a little sad.
Shen Xuan's secret box.
Mr. Hu.
There are so many weapons.
Don't be confused.
Don't worry.
I have prepared.
Hu.