The Cool Wire
requirement
must beислable
signing
Isn't she?
You are our
rather unscrupulous butterfly
up in the sky.
You are my
butterfly等你
my beautiful butterfly.
Miracle Log
Però
maybe
you don't bothering to tell
When you find it,
you can't pull it out.
You keep doing as planned.
Yes.
Xiao Beiming.
This chess
is getting more and more interesting.
The King's Avatar
Episode 16
When Master was young,
he killed enemies on the battlefield.
I don't know how many wounds he got
and how many sick spots he got.
Usually,
he used these tonics to take care of his body.
But he was killed by a man.
He was killed by a man.
What Miss Huo said
has no doubt about it.
Miss Huo is the only daughter of the Huo family.
Is there anyone in this mansion
who can hurt you?
a woman who is unquestionable.
It seems that Madam Feng is awake.
Since Madam Feng is awake,
is it convenient to see her?
Madam Feng is not in good health.
She has been over-sad these days.
I'm afraid...
No.
Please wait a moment.
How is it?
I can't see anything for now.
I need to take all these drugs back for testing
to get a conclusion.
Where is Zhong Bukui?
Zhong Bukui and Tong Bukui
are asking around in the Eastern Courtyard.
Tong Bukui?
You've met him before?
Tong Shuang?
Let's go.
Take me to see them.
Wait.
I'll take a few more bottles of drugs.
To test them more.
Take that too.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Why hasn't she come yet?
It's almost time.
It's time to see Xiao Man.
Wait!
Madam Feng, what's wrong?
I think I forgot something.
What's that?
The token of the Divine Camp.
Why don't you two
go back and get it with me?
Let's go.
Go back by yourself.
Please.
Ouch!
Madam Feng, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Look at me.
I'm so careless.
These are all objects.
What should I do?
It'll be fine soon.
The Demon King
You are...
Mr. Chu Ge, are you okay?
Where's Mao Zao?
I'll take you there.
That way.
I'll...
Hurry up.
Madam Feng is so sad for General Huo.
It seems that you two are close.
Yes.
When General Huo came back from the battlefield,
he took me as his concubine.
It's been 23 years.
These years,
we've been close to each other.
We're very close.
Now that he's gone,
my heart
hurts so much.
I'm so worried.
Madam Feng.
My mother is very weak now.
If there's nothing wrong with you two,
then...
Thank you, Madam Feng and Miss Huo.
Sorry for the interruption.
We should leave now.
We're sorry for the inconvenience.
Take care, sirs.
Li Xiao took her to the toilet.
I'm afraid it won't be long.
You should leave now.
We'll hold off Zhuge Kongyun.
We'll meet at the third floor.
Tong Bukui.
Miss Huo.
Didn't Tong Bukui
stay with Zhong Bukui?
Why are they acting separately now?
I have something important to do.
I need to go back to the camp.
Miss Huo,
you're here.
You have something to ask me.
I've been thinking.
I'm afraid the person in front of me is not Tong Bukui.
She's the old friend
I mentioned earlier.
Miss Huo,
we haven't met before.
You must have mistaken her for someone else.
I'm not good at learning
and I'm not good at martial arts.
But I know a little bit about dressing up.
Besides,
your eyes
are so familiar to me.
So...
Miss Huo,
you've mistaken me for someone else.
It's been a long time,
Xiao Beiming.
We've met before.
I'm a little embarrassed to say this.
I was not very fond of
Xiao Shen before.
I know your case
very well.
I've secretly
seen you at the gate of Shen Buying several times.
Since you know my identity,
aren't you afraid that I'll kill you?
I don't believe you're Ye Sha.
Why do you say that?
Because Zhong Xue Man has been by your side.
You're really something.
You can even think of this.
Brother Xiao is amazing.
He's always thinking about
the person in front of the camp.
He's amazing.
Here it comes.
Mr. Zhuge.
What's wrong?
Mr. Zhuge,
what's wrong with you?
This is called the
I did it.
The pill.
Look at my memory.
I forgot to tell you.
That Juewei Pill
can seal your sense of taste and sense of smell.
But some people
have other symptoms.
What symptoms?
I don't know.
How can you
give Mr. Zhuge
this kind of food?
I don't want to give it to him either.
He can't stand the smell of the wet food.
That's why I gave him food.
But it's just wet food.
Everyone is happy.
Yes.
You can't stand this.
And you have to take medicine.
You...
It's okay, Mr. Zhuge.
You just need to clean it.
When you're clean tomorrow,
we'll talk about the case.
No matter who hates you the most
and wants to kill you the most,
it's not him.
But he's been with you
and taking risks with you.
It means you've got his trust.
Since he can do it,
why can't I?
You're really smart.
I'm so honored
to be praised by you.
But
I have something to tell you.
I hope you can tell me the truth.
Please.
You're a criminal now.
Why are you so sad
about my father's case?
You even risked your life
to investigate the Huo Mansion.
There must be something wrong with it.
Could it be
that my father's case
is related to Feng Bo Lake?
Yes.
We found out that General Huo
is related to our clues.
When we first came to Huo Mansion,
General Huo died.
It's too coincidental.
It's hard to avoid people's doubts.
But...
But my father
killed himself.
He also took the blame.
He might not be the one to blame.
Mr. Li.
Someone's here.
Someone's guarding the front.
There's a
I have an idea. Come with me.
The Huo family has a lot of mothers.
Especially that Miss Huo.
She's very quiet.
Really?
I think it's okay.
I found that you always
spoke for Miss Huo.
No.
Hmm.
Why didn't Brother Xiao come back?
He said he would come back
earlier than us.
Did something happen?
Brother Zhu found out?
Young Master, are you feeling better?
I'm fine.
Brother Zhu, go back and rest.
I'll be with you if you need me.
Uncle Wu.
Why are you here at this time?
Okay, okay. Let's go.
Why are you dressed like this?
Huo Dai Rong dressed me up
to avoid the tea sweat of the Chinesechina.
Huo Dai Rong?
He...
He exposed my identity.
What?
He recognized you
and helped you escape?
You two are really good friends, aren't you?
I...
I really haven't seen him before.
I swear I really haven't seen him.
Brother Xiao,
why did he help you?
He asked me to help him find out
the truth of his father's death.
His words are not reliable.
That's right.
Huo Pu Shui Zhen.
Huo Dai Rong is very smart.
It's hard to understand.
But at present,
he shouldn't have done anything to harm me.
And he also told me
some clues about his father's death.
What clues?
Since Miss Huo also thinks
General Huo's death is strange,
with Miss Huo's intelligence,
there will be no one who doubts it.
Mrs. Huo.
Mrs. Huo?
That's right.
Although my father is a tempered person,
he never hurt anyone.
But half a year ago,
my father suddenly became weird.
He was always violent.
He was a little impatient
and would hurt people.
My aunt's illness...
If my aunt was too sad,
it's better
to say that my father tortured her.
Then why do you suspect Mrs. Huo?
I asked the doctor.
If a person is wise and wise,
he will never be so cruel to his people.
So I suspect
my father was poisoned.
The food and medicine
my father ate
were all under Mrs. Huo's control.
She is the most suspicious.
But I just suspect
I have no evidence.
So I want to investigate it.
Huo Derong said
Mrs. Huo was married to General Huo five years ago.
She was 16 when she came to the mansion.
What about Mrs. Yuan Pei?
Mrs. Yuan Pei died five years ago.
She didn't leave any children.
I observed Mrs. Huo that day.
She was light-hearted
and didn't look like a noble lady.
Huo Derong also said
Mrs. Huo's father was a military man.
After Mrs. Huo got married,
the military man became the designated partner.
She exchanged her daughter's happiness
for the wealth of the family.
It's a good deal.
I don't know whether it's a deal or not.
But Mrs. Huo was not happy
after she got married.
She was depressed all the time.
She didn't go out and didn't talk to anyone.
Until three years ago, she got better.
She smiled a little more.
Three years ago?
Huo Derong has a deep resentment for Mrs. Huo.
We can't just listen to her.
We still have to find a way
to see Mrs. Huo.
Miss Huo is unpredictable.
You'd better not show up in the mansion again.
If it's really Mrs. Huo,
General Huo's death
has nothing to do with the night kill.
General Huo died in the middle of our investigation.
Maybe it's really a coincidence.
Anyway,
let's find out.
General Huo's death
was caused by the drug he had been taking for a long time.
So the murderer is locked in the mansion.
But there is one thing
I really don't understand.
It has nothing to do with the night kill Xiao Weiming.
That's right.
Maybe it has nothing to do with him.
Yan'er,
you and I have made a military order
in front of His Majesty.
We can't waste time for nothing.
But I feel
Xiao Weiming is right next to him.
Do you have any evidence?
Not yet.
But father,
please give me a few more days.
Maybe we can find the night kill
if we solve General Huo's case.
If we can't catch Xiao Weiming,
even if we solve a hundred cases,
we can't make up for it.
If His Majesty blames us,
we can't take the responsibility.
But now
we have more clues.
We shouldnever let our j pupils sit alone!
Why isn't anyone from Jiu部分 coming back?
Is something going on?
Nothing happens.
Peie Li said
People get together to see each other's sacrifices.
Interestingly,
in the pastOld Orchidville boxers
He asked someone and he was born a wafer.
He's also a great martial artist.
If there's a fight between him and I,
he'll just be a wolf.
Yes.
Don't be too anxious.
Don't be suspicious.
He's sneaky.
He's not doing anything good.
Let's go.
It's a secret place.
There are tall buildings
and a special guard at the door.
There must be something fishy.
According to the police report
I found in the capital city,
it's likely to be a black gambling house.
A black gambling house?
It's different from the gambling houses outside.
The gambling houses outside are under the supervision of the court.
People who gamble
will be registered.
But the black gambling house is not used.
Not only is it not under supervision,
the gambling house is also not small.
It seems that Xue Shan Shan is not only good at gambling,
but also plays well.
That's strange.
He's a disciple of the daily calendar.
How could he go to such a gambling house?
Where did he come from?
Someone is coming.
Come on.
Give me back my stuff.
Okay.
If you get another 500 taels,
I'll give it to you.
This business is a bit out of place.
What?
It's him.
Not only 500 taels.
You...
Let me have some fun.
I'll go with you.
Keep an eye on Xue Shan Shan.
I'll follow him.
We'll meet at the summit.
Be careful.
Zhao Mu Guan.
So handsome.
It doesn't matter.
Zhou Mushan.
This guy...
You'll find a way tospeaks.
Zhou Mushan is airport 실행.
Zhou Mushan.
Is he a big pick yet?
No.
Zhou Mushan set up a scheme.
Try to come to this.
Yes.
Zhou Mushan.
How about we come to this Party.
Really?
What are you doing here?
I'm asking you.
Are you following Xue Qian Shan?
I ran into Xue Qian Shan on my way to the mansion.
I remembered that she was not around today.
So I came to see what she was doing.
So it is.
Wait.
You went to the mansion alone.
You didn't call me.
You want to act alone again.
Isn't your stomach hurting?
No.
Do you want to go to the mansion too?
I want to go to the mansion alone.
I can't.
Do you want to go to the mansion too?
You didn't call me.
I...
He is a man.
Why does he need to buy rouge?
You ask me.
You dress like this every day.
It smells like a coriander.
You should know it best.
Be serious when you fry it.
Let's go and have a look.
This is the powder.
Ten taels.
Just a small powder like this
costs ten taels of silver.
This powder is called West Stone Pond.
It is made of 100-year-old incense
and western red and blue.
It is extremely expensive.
Not to mention ten taels of silver.
When it comes to making money,
someone has to grab twenty taels of silver.
You don't even know this, do you?
How can I know this?
I don't need it.
But you are a big man.
You can't just take it.
You know a lot.
As a cashier,
you have to know a little bit about everything.
It seems that
you are not qualified
as a woman or a cashier.
The ten taels of silver
Mr. Zhuge spent
is not just to mock me, is it?
Of course it's for the investigation.
Xue Qianshan's rough and reckless husband
should not be free
from this kind of expensive powder.
That's right.
Smell it.
The smell of this powder is very special.
I think I've smelled this kind of smell
in someone in the household.
I've smelled it too.
When we were interrogating yesterday.
Are we talking about
the same person?
Let's go to the household.
Now?
The border is sacred.
Do you have anything else to do?
No.
I'm not in a hurry.
Do you feel
that you've changed a lot recently?
What?
Not like the old one.
You don't look so serious.
Especially the murderous spirit in your eyes.
You were so aggressive
until three years ago.
Time is so short.
The changes are so big.
I'm not in a hurry.
Not in a hurry?
Did you meet something happy?
And the person?
I've always been like this.
It's just that we have a deep communication.
You don't know me.
Really?
I don't want to talk to you.
I'm going to the household now.
You can come or not.
Mr. Zhu Ge.
You're late.
What's the matter?
Miss Huo.
We found the key clue
to General Huo's case.
I can only visit him at night.
Sorry to bother you.
I'm really sorry.
What's the new discovery?
You want to see me at night?
Miss Huo.
I'm sorry.
Miss Huo, do you recognize this?
This is the blood of the West Division.
This blood of the West Division
should be the one
Miss Huo uses every day.
I'm really using the blood of the West Division.
It's not you who bought it.
It's from someone else.
Do I need someone else
to give me some cosmetics?
I went to the butler
and checked Miss Huo's money.
I found that the household requires
extreme strictness
for food and clothing.
Especially for you.
Especially for you and Miss Huo's money.
I'm afraid it's hard to afford
these cosmetics.
Even if this blood of the West Division
is from someone else,
what's the point?
Today, we found that
Xue Qianshan's situation is suspicious.
After following up, we found that
she bought this blood of the West Division.
The blood of the West Division is expensive.
There are only a few bottles
in the whole capital for a month.
If it's an accident,
this blood of the West Division
was given to you by Xue Qianshan.
I don't know what the relationship
between you and your mother is.
Xue Qianshan gave me
this blood of the West Division.
But we have no relationship.
I can't
have anything to do with her.
She has been pestering me.
I just don't want to
get too close to her.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing wrong.
Since Xue Qianshan
has a clear intention to Miss Huo,
will Miss Huo
help us?
Help?
What help?
Bao relaxing
service
Thanks.
It's windy tonight.
I'll shut the windows.
Just for a take.
Let me go with you.
Bueno, follow me to the front
The assessments in the city
Wait for the three years
You can earn the money
Do not question me
Damn me
Tong Shuang
If
I mean, if
Because you made your fault
I got you and your people
That made them suffer
What would you do?
You're the only one I have.
We're like a chain of bones.
If I made a mistake and got you into trouble,
you wouldn't blame me, would you?
Of course not.
I...
If it were someone else,
even strangers,
you'd have to make it up to them.
Make it up?
Look.
If it were your house,
and you accidentally ordered a house for someone else,
you wouldn't have to watch others sleep on the street.
You'd have to make it up to them to get the house back.
You're so right.
Hurry up.
Don't cause trouble for the neighbors.
You've been through a lot.
Brother, did I say something wrong again?
No.
You said it very well.
Thank you.
Rong Mei?
Why did you come to me?
I was so worried.
I was walking around.
I didn't expect to come to you.
It seems that you've been in trouble.
Tell me.
I'll help you solve it.
I'm sorry for what I've done.
My father left suddenly.
He didn't help me look after others.
You know that
you can't tolerate me and my aunt.
My mother and I
don't know who to rely on in the future.
You're crying so easily.
Miss Huo is not easy.
Rong Mei, don't worry.
As long as I'm here,
I won't let you suffer.
Thank you for your kindness.
But the daily food and drink of our women's house
are always very expensive.
I know your thoughts.
I'm afraid that my mother and I
are also very worried.
Rong, why are you bothering Brother Xue?
Rong Mei, don't worry.
I've been lucky recently.
I found a way to make money.
I made a fortune today.
This number.
50 taels?
500 taels.
There will be more good things in the future.
I don't know where Brother Xue got the money from.
I'm afraid that the money he got from luck is not enough.
I have a treasure.
I can't rely on him to make money.
Treasure?
What treasure is so valuable?
This treasure is not valuable in itself.
But it can bring me a lot of money.
Rong Mei, as long as you are willing to follow me,
I can guarantee that you will live a life of endless glory.
Really?
I don't believe it.
Brother Xue, are you lying to me?
Rong Mei, you don't believe me?
I'll get the treasure for you right now.
I'll let you see.
Wait for me, Rong Mei.
He didn't tell you what the treasure is.
Where did he go?
He hasn't come back for so long.
He's killing me.
The Wind and the Five Sages?
Why are you here?
What happened just now?
What's wrong with you?
Wake up.
What's wrong with the knife in your hand?
Knife?
He's dead.
How did Xue Qian Shan die?
I didn't kill him.
I don't know.
Stop him.
I didn't kill him.
Take the murderer away.
Wait.
We haven't figured it out yet.
What are you still investigating?
Are you going to see the whole family
of Huo's Mansion?
Mrs. Huo,
we don't want to see
another murder in Huo's Mansion.
I know Feng Wu Zuo.
He doesn't even kill a chicken.
How could he kill someone?
There's something wrong with this.
Give me some time to figure it out.
Don't arrest the wrong person.
Are you going to kill him?
Of course not.
I don't know.
But it won't be easy to convict.
There are still a lot of doubts
about this case.
The knife is in his hand.
He's also dead.
What are the doubts?
Is your case
just a mouth?
Mr. Zhuge,
it's hard to say.
Actually, it's not complicated at all.
There are no big traces on the scene.
And Xue Qian Shan
was stabbed in the heart.
This means that he was
stabbed in the face
and killed.
Xue Qian Shan is very good at martial arts.
And the murderer can be killed with one stab.
Either the murderer
is a master of martial arts.
Or...
Or the murderer
is someone very familiar with Xue Qian Shan.
He can sneak attack
without any guard.
Feng Wu Zuo is not familiar with Xue Qian Shan.
Do you think
he will sneak attack?
Maybe
he's a master of martial arts.
What master of martial arts
doesn't run after killing people
and sit on the ground
and let you guys
catch him so easily?
Shut up.
I don't have the right to talk to you.
Miss Huo is right.
The most important thing is
Feng Wu Zuo has no reason to kill Xue Qian Shan.
Who knows?
Anyway,
we can't just let him go.
Feng Wu Zuo is a member of our Shen Buying.
Even if he is a suspect,
he has to be handed over to our Shen Buying.
He has fainted now.
Please let me take him back.
But you are a team.
Mrs. Huo,
please don't point at me.
I'll say it one last time.
Teach people.
Li,
I have a reminder for you.
The case is not cleared yet.
It's a serious crime to torture him privately.
Recently, there are enough things
in our Huo Mansion.
You...
Take him away.
Thank you.
We'll take Feng Wu Zuo back
to interrogate him
and give an explanation to the Huo Mansion.
But before we find out the truth,
please don't leave the Huo Mansion.
As for the body,
I'll keep it for now.
Thank you for your kind words.
It's nothing.
I didn't expect this to happen.
How are you going to deal with him?
According to the law.
Don't worry.
We'll figure it out.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I'll go back now.
Take Feng Wu Zuo back.
I'll go back and find someone to deal with the body.
You're not going to interrogate him?
It's not complicated.
There's nothing to interrogate.
And you said it.
The murderer is either a master
or a familiar person.
It's useless to interrogate him.
What did you find out?
I did a lot for your Feng Wu Zuo today.
I'm tired.
I'm going back to rest.
But you...
Don't worry.
I'll come back tomorrow morning.
The night is deep in the valley.
The mountain is dark and the clouds are dark.
The shadow is thin and the shadow is thin.
The night is silent but I want to...
The blood is so bitter.
The heart is so sad.
The flowers are blooming.
The wind is so strong.
The body is so heavy.
Where can I go?
If I can't get my heart back,
I can't get my heart back.
Who can stop me?
If I can't get my heart back,
I can't get my heart back.
Look at the beautiful scenery.
The bright and bright sky.
The beautiful scenery.
I heard the sound of the flute in the boat.
Where can I go?
If I can't get my heart back,
I can't get my heart back.
Who can stop me?
If I can't get my heart back,
I can't get my heart back.
Look at the beautiful scenery.
The bright and bright sky.
The beautiful scenery.