=The Rebel Empress=
=Episode 18=
His Majesty has become more and more
ruthless these days.
The ministers don't dare
to advise anything.
If this continues, what should we do?
Someone, comes in.
Uncle, I'm Ci'er.
Nonsense!
Uncle, listen to me.
When I was young,
my father was busy with his duty,
so I live here all the time.
Do you still remember when I was five,
I took you as a tree and climbed on top.
The both of us then fell down together.
There's still a scar on the waist.
How do you know about these?
Brother, sister,
come and play with Dabao now!
Dabao.
You recognize the wrong person.
I didn't.
They are brother and sister.
The person who stole medicine
at the drug institution that day
is the one who wrongly recognize others.
How you know the way
to open the Jiuqu Intricate Box?
Only the Empress...
You are really Ci'er.
Ci'er.
But why do you look like this?
What happened?
It's the work of Xiao...
Dabao, come outside to play with brother.
Sister will come and find us later.
Let's go.
Ok.
Uncle.
It's a very long story.
I will explain to you after this.
The reason of me coming today
is to ask uncle something.
Does uncle know
Xiao Mo altered the posthumous edict
and claimed the throne back then?
It's most likely that
father knows about the posthumous edict,
which led to him being killed.
Your father was always healthy and fit.
However, he died from serious illness
all of a sudden.
He must have been murdered by others.
If back then, uncle was able to realize
something suspicious earlier,
maybe your father wouldn't be...
Seeing it now,
Xiao Mo is truly a nasty person.
Uncle.
It's not your fault.
Regarding the posthumous edict,
do you know anything else about it?
Your father was always cautious.
He will never say anything
that he's not supposed to say.
Regarding the posthumous edict,
I really don't know a single thing.
Dabao likes to play with these?
Oh, father likes it.
Sister likes it.
Dabao also likes it.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
Alright.
Uncle.
I still need to ask for a favor from you.
The Emperor has arrived.
Welcome the arrival of Your Majesty.
It's my fault too.
Ci'er treats you well.
Something bad happened to her.
You must be really sad.
But till today,
only I'm here to visit you.
Thank you for Your Majesty's concern.
I only hope that
the culprit will be caught
as soon as possible.
Recently, Prince Duan
spread rumors and created a hassle.
Regarding the authenticity
of the posthumous edict
left by the late Emperor,
the rumor had spread
and made a mess throughout the city.
Do you know anything about it?
Your Majesty should know.
This is a baseless joke,
I've never heard anything about
a fake posthumous edict.
Rise up.
I don't mean to blame you.
Come, drink some tea.
Why didn't I see Dabao today?
Previously, as long as I'm here,
he will ask me to play with him.
Dabao is tired.
Why grandfather hasn't come
to play hide and seek with Dabao?
Brother-in-law, can you
play hide and seek with Dabao?
Dabao.
Alright, we'll play hide and seek.
Turn around and don't peek.
Count to eight.
Alright.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
It's alright now.
You come down first.
I think I'm stuck.
Alright, Dabao.
Brother-in-law
has other stuff to do today.
I will play with you another day.
Okay.
See you again, brother-in-law.
It seems that the old minister
really doesn't know about
the posthumous edict.
If that's the case, why is he nervous?
(I was in great danger.)
(My niece is alone,
with no one to rely on.)
(I wish to propose that)
(there're a lot of doubts
in the Empress' death.)
(Hope Your Majesty
can think twice before acting,)
(Don't trust others easily
nor make judgement lightly.)
Is it because of the punishment
I've given to Prince Duan and his family,
he wishes to impeach me?
How is the search in the city?
Is there any news about Prince Duan
and Princess Consort Duan?
Not yet, but recently,
there's always people from Wuqing Sect who
went missing without reason.
Arrange more men to guard the palace.
Enhance the defense of the outer city.
It's better to kill innocents,
than to let go of one.
The Under the Moonlight Action continues.
Change the spies that were in the palace
for more than three years
into the important posts.
Get rid of the filthy ones
and keep the clear ones.
Remember, don't harm the civilians.
Long live
the Emperor.
Your Majesty.
I think that there are some doubts
in the case of Prince Duan
murdering the Empress.
The death of the Empress has valid proofs.
Xiao Che had admitted his crime
and ran away that day.
This is fact.
No further discussion is allowed.
Since when Prince Duan admitted his crime?
Why did he run away?
And the three institutes' joint hearings,
why do we not know anything?
Isn't it because the court
wished to end the case fast
and forced Prince Duan to admit?
Hope Your Majesty investigate it well.
Old Minister Wang's pain
in losing your niece, I can understand it.
However, this can't be the reason for you
to cause disruption in the palace.
Guard!
Your Majesty, what do you mean by this?
Take him.
Who dares to move?
Protect the Emperor!
How dare you!
Xiao Che, are you trying to rebel?
Xiao Mo, you are the rebel!
The royal order is here.
Posthumous edict of the former Emperor,
it's the same as facing the Emperor.
=The Rebel Empress=
=The End of Episode 18=
♪Let the winds blow,
blow at you from behind♪
♪I do not yet have
the courage to call you back to me♪
♪Snow is falling again,
but it is all about you♪
♪Melting on my cheeks
into tears rolling down♪
♪We were truthful
to each other at the beginning♪
♪But later allowed ourselves
to struggle in our lies♪
♪Words that hurt you
could be untruthful♪
♪I cannot keep you by my side
and can't let go of you♪
♪You trap me from going further
and prevent me from forgetting♪
♪Your words make me panic,
it is unknowingly ridiculous♪
♪The two of us seem to
have just been a show after all♪
♪You trap my desire and my past♪
♪Every breath in desolation,
luckily that among crowds♪
♪It is not yet over for us♪