=The Rebel Empress=
=Episode 4=
Let the funeral begin!
Moan.
End.
Here comes His Majesty!
His Majesty is here
to pray for Her Majesty,
praying for her soul to last forever
and rest in peace.
Yunci,
I'm sorry for being late.
Here are
our letters from the past
and my unspoken love for you.
You haven't seen them yet.
We are not prepared to be separated.
I want to cry but have no sound.
I regret that papers are limited,
and unable to write down my feelings.
(Your Majesty!
You have finally returned!)
Her Majesty reigned over the consorts,
being virtuous and kind.
In light of her sudden passing,
the Empress is specially conferred
to titles of Mercy, Virtue, Harmony
Honesty, Grace, and Erudition.
Fengxi Palace is to be restored.
And the Bureau of Garment Production
will replicate
the Golden Butterfly Flower Dress,
in respect of the Late Empress.
This is His Majesty's edict!
From this day on,
all Imperial Consorts and Royal Ladies
are to moan for the Late Empress
for three days.
Your Highness,
please look here.
These are the gray powders
found in Fengxi Palace during the fire.
It's the same as what
Princess Consort left in your chamber.
As you guessed,
the fire was not an accident.
I went to the mortuary
to investigate the bodies
and found that only
seven people died from the fire
while the rest were strangled to death.
Jiang Jinli!
Your Majesty!
When have we been so estranged?
A few days ago, you...
You were frightened a few days ago,
so take care of yourself.
Alright, stop crying.
You are making my heart ache.
I know you feel wronged.
It was my problem that night.
It won't happen again.
What are you saying?
Aren't you angry with me
that I sent servants
to save the Empress
and just left you alone?
There were a lot of people back then.
I had to do that.
Moreover,
the reason why I arrived late
before the Empress and court officials
was all because of you.
Today is so important,
but you're still here
to fool around with me.
Aren't you afraid of
messing up the important thing?
What's that?
You are the only one important now.
(I can't believe the nightmare I had
while unconscious is true.)
(The Emperor and Princess Consort
are having an affair!)
I still fall to your tactics.
Unlike the Empress,
who is plain and boring.
But aren't you being too impatient?
Choosing the Empress's birthday
to add such a large amount of cotton
laced with saltpeter dust in her dress,
then switching Prince Duan's present
and lacing it with yellow phosphorus.
But what if someone realizes it?
How should I protect you?
Alright, don't cry.
Don't be afraid,
Everything is over.
I also put the people
of that palace to death
for you.
(So the accomplice
is right in front of me,)
(and someone I love the most!)
You! How dare you!
So what?
You adulterous couple!
I will make you die with me!
So, how are you going to thank me?
What do you want, Your Majesty?
What's wrong? Why is your face so pale?
Are you feeling unwell?
Or do you miss me again?
It is inconvenient today,
but we do not need to have fun
at Prince Duan's Mansion later.
When the Empress's funeral is over,
I will confiscate Prince Duan's Mansion
and confer you as the Empress.
Are the things in place?
Why is this here?
(So this is a whole planned trap)
(to make me die in an accident,)
(and push the blame onto Prince Duan.)
(What a brilliant scheme
of hitting two birds with a stone!)
Your Majesty,
Prince Duan is highly suspicious
and wary,
and the door of his chamber
is locked day and night.
I haven't been able
to find a chance all this time.
What a cunning fox Xiao Che is.
It doesn't matter. I'll find other ways.
(Xiao Mo.)
(You have bullied me,
wronged me, and hurt me,)
(causing misfortune
to people around me.)
(You'll die a tragic death!)
So you are here.
I come to seek her to discuss matters.
Please allow me to excuse myself.
Alright.
(Turns out that I am
just a pawn for Xiao Mo.)
(We had been married for seven years)
(but he had parted with me already.)
(Yunci,)
(What a sad joke.)
My life is complete to have you.
But the daughter of the Jiang Family
is unparalleled in beauty
and enjoys great prestige
in the capital.
She also looks similar to me.
If she enters the palace and serves you,
it will also become a beautiful talk.
You are obviously getting jealous,
but still want to pretend
it doesn't matter.
Rest assured,
she cannot compare to you.
I will not allow a daughter of
the Jiang Family to enter the palace.
I think she can be granted to
Prince Duan, Xiao Che.
(Although my body is buried now,)
(you'll end up like me one day.)
(Xiao Mo, I will make you pay
with your life!)
What are you acting up to again?
Stop acting.
Xiao Che!
Your Highness.
Please calm down!
When Fengxi Palace caught fire,
there were about 20 people,
among which seven died from the fire,
while the rest were strangled to death.
I also put the people
of that palace to death
for you.
(As expected, Prince Duan is also
investigating my death.)
People know that you
are jealous of Empress Wang,
and you dare say
you are unrelated to it?
It's Your...
(If I confess now,)
(I'll be able to get my revenge.)
(But I cannot die now.)
(I must get revenge
for everyone in Fengxi Palace.)
(But if I step out
and disclose Xiao Mo in my identity,)
(who will believe me?)
It's not me!
If I planned this accident,
why would I enter Fengxi Palace that day
and put myself in danger too?
If you hadn't arrived in time,
I would have...
You dare to still argue.
The fire in Fengxi Palace
was the result of yellow phosphorus.
And how do you explain sneaking into
my chamber yesterday
and leaving yellow phosphorus powder?
I did that yesterday
to improve our relationship
and serve you wholeheartedly
in the future.
As for the yellow phosphorus powders
you mentioned,
I really have no idea!
The truth has yet to be revealed,
but you want to use punishment
on me in the palace...
Jiang Jinli!
I'm warning you.
I will continue to
investigate this matter.
If I find out you are related to this,
I will make sure you
and the Jiang Family
die for Empress Wang.
(Go and investigate it thoroughly!)
(Xiao Che, I support you!)
=The Rebel Empress=
=The End of Episode 4=
♪Let the winds blow,
blow at you from behind♪
♪I do not yet have
the courage to call you back to me♪
♪Snow is falling again,
but it is all about you♪
♪Melting on my cheeks
into tears rolling down♪
♪We were truthful
to each other at the beginning♪
♪But later allowed ourselves
to struggle in our lies♪
♪Words that hurt you
could be untruthful♪
♪I cannot keep you by my side
and can't let go of you♪
♪You trap me from going further
and prevent me from forgetting♪
♪Your words make me panic,
it is unknowingly ridiculous♪
♪The two of us seem to
have just been a show after all♪
♪You trap my desire and my past♪
♪Every breath in desolation,
luckily that among crowds♪
♪It is not yet over for us♪