♪I collect everything about you♪
♪Play scenes of you again and again♪
♪Try to leave a deeper impression♪
♪Calling my name is enough♪
♪In this world only I understand you♪
♪I care the most about you♪
♪In this world only I’m here with you♪
♪Yet I’m still confused♪
♪I wish to hold your hand
just for one second at this intersection♪
♪I might’ve said that 100 times♪
♪Maybe I’m clumsy in your eyes♪
♪Maybe I haven’t done enough yet♪
♪I wish to close the gap
to prove myself to you♪
♪Sweet romance slowly fills the air♪
♪Love is never an accident♪
♪No need to uncover the truth♪
♪The answer is right there♪
=Be With You=
=Episode 1=
We’re about to graduate.
There’s something you need to know.
I like you. And you?
(I)
(also)
(like)
(you.)
(I also like you.)
(Insensitive)
That’s my answer.
(I also like you.)
New stage, new relationship,
and new excitement.
Coming soon.
That’s a wrap!
Finished the whole thing!
Get up. Proofread it before going home.
I haven’t had any sleep for two days.
AC at home stopped working,
but I can’t afford to fix it.
(Qi Nian, 24 Years Old)
The office is cool.
(Pseudonym: Baby Seven)
Don’t wanna get up.
(Reading Comics: 13 Years)
I really need a nap.
(Occupation: Cartoonist on the bottom rung)
(Is there a kiss?)
What the hell is this?
That’s an unexpected twist.
Can’t they have a romantic confession?
That love line sucks!
I’m just glad it ends.
I like the drawing and everything,
but the romance part stinks.
Those two have been through everything
and only won at the last moment.
There’s no contact from nose down.
Parents’ guide is unnecessary.
Comments were few at first,
but now they’re
flooding into the last chapter.
Isn’t that normal?
Readers are under huge stress.
They need to blow off their steam.
Really?
Baby Seven’s work
has been serialized for over a year,
but neither she nor her work has made on
the list of Best Authors or Best Works.
What’s your explanation
as her executive editor?
She’s been on the list of Most Updates.
Her best record is three times per week.
Why bother if no one is reading it?
Kids these days can write Mary-sues
or draw something romantic.
Is it really that hard?
As a matter of fact,
it is to Baby Seven.
She started from comics for boys.
I don’t care about her past.
Commercial comics are
all about popularity.
If she
doesn’t jazz up her next work,
then don’t bother to show up again.
-What’s that noise?
-What happened?
Baby Seven!
Didn’t you hear what Chief Editor said?
You can’t afford
to make more mistakes.
If your next work still fails,
that’s likely to end your career.
You’ll be doomed.
There’ll be no second chance, got it?
I know.
I won’t let that happen.
So I’ve announced in my next work...
Hold on.
Didn’t you say couples are into
physical contact?
So I’ve arranged that
since the very beginning.
I call it Wrestling Love.
Wrestling my foot!
That sounds crude instead of romantic.
Who’d read it?
And,
why are all your male characters
muscular?
Muscles are the best to show
sexuality and strength.
And drawing a six-pack is super easy
by simply making
a cat sticking its tongue out.
Shut up.
Let’s say I’m fine with your style,
but add some sparks between the couple.
That’s how you create a best seller.
Yet you have them spar.
How is that romantic?
What do you feel if someone hits on you?
Your heart starts racing.
You... You’ve never felt
your heart racing?
I’ve heard of heart attacks.
How can a heart race?
What are you doing?
(Wolf Girl and Black Prince)
(Kamisama Love)
I’m an editor,
not a relationship counselor.
Read these yourself.
But you asked me
to stay away from them
to not affect my inspiration.
I wish they could knock
some sense into you.
If you could model
your characters on them,
that’d be a relief!
Listen,
new works selection of this month
is your last chance.
If you botch that up,
you’re screwed!
But...
No buts.
5 pm tomorrow.
Hand in your new design
of the male character.
If I see another muscle man,
I’ll crush your head with my biceps.
Got it, got it. Ouch!
Ow…!
You... You’ve never felt
your heart racing?
Heart racing, aside from
the abstract meaning,
normally refers to
heart beating too fast.
Caffeine and sports can do that.
What’s it to do with me?
And I mean, if someone
does make my heart race,
I’ll be in trouble.
Beef jerky.
Where’s your owner?
Do you want this?
So adorable.
Qi Bao.
I’m also surnamed Qi,
so we’re sort of family.
Are you asking me to
help you find your owner?
Fine.
I have no inspiration anyway.
It’s better to take you home.
Finished.
Let’s go.
Qi Bao. Qi Bao. Qi Bao!
(Red Joy)
Qi Bao!
Qi Bao! Slow down!
(Jiulianshan Rd.)
Where are you going?
Slow down. I can’t keep up with you.
Where are you taking me?
(Lijiang West Rd.)
Slow down. Don’t run so fast.
Qi Bao.
Where were you?
Thank you.
The leash.
Sorry for troubling you.
No, not at all.
Don’t mention it.
Did it eat your snacks?
It needs more food to grow.
Is it a boy or a girl? How old is it?
A 5-year-old boy.
Are you raising him alone?
That must be hard.
What was that?
♪Pretend I don’t care♪
♪Pretend I don’t miss you♪
I’m sorry.
It’s OK.
Just an accident.
Luckily, we...
♪Pretend it’s natural♪
♪Then accidentally♪
What’s going on?
Why is my heart beating so fast?
Do I have a congenital heart disease
that acts up after being kissed?
Are you OK?
I’m fine. I’m good.
Qi Bao!
Let go.
Sorry.
I’ll pay for these.
I don’t need your money.
Can you give me your number instead?
The one I can reach you directly.
Excuse me.
I don’t care where you are.
Get your ass back.
ASAP!
What is it?
I was wrong about the deadline.
It’s today.
You mean 5 o’clock this afternoon?
There’s less than one hour.
I’m hanging up.
Could you wait here for me?
I know it’s abrupt
but I really need a huge favor
from you.
It’s OK if you say no.
Well, I gotta run.
Just forget about everything I said.
I’m sorry.
(MC)
I’m here!
How long do I have?
30 minutes. Where’s your drawing?
Haven’t started it yet.
What?
It’s in my head. Let’s go.
How long do you need?
Almost done.
Baby Seven.
I didn’t ask you to not
interrupt your work.
Are you sure you got it covered?
Although it’s only a sketch,
I’m sure
the story about him
is gonna be good.
No, it’s gonna be a hit.
Yes.
Where are you?
By the lake waiting for someone
who might not show up.
I’ll go back to the firm
after walking Qi Bao.
♪I care the most about you♪
♪In this world only I’m here with you♪
♪Yet I’m still confused♪
♪I wish to hold your hand
just for one second♪
(Ji Yanxin)
♪At this intersection♪
♪I might’ve said that 100 times♪
♪Maybe I’m clumsy in your eyes♪
♪Maybe I haven’t done enough yet♪
All done!
Take a look.
Go away. Move.
What you just said
has convinced me.
Is it good?
Better than good!
Did you suddenly grow a magic hand
that could draw other than muscles?
I’m surprised your character is so hot.
And this heart-melting kiss
is text-book romance.
What’s gotten into you?
Have you and your style both changed?
It was exciting.
I mean the heart attack you said.
It’s heart racing.
I’ve felt it.
So this heart-throb
and the kiss…
They’re real.
And he looks hotter in person.
Hey, girl,
listen, you must publish this.
Use what you have
to build the character.
Materials can be gathered easily.
So where is he now?
Let’s go meet him.
Maybe...
You...
No way is he still here.
What am I thinking?
But if there’s the slightest hope,
I want to see him again.
I knew it.
Hello.
Have you found that heart-throb?
Send me a video of him.
He’s gone without leaving a number.
What now?
Listen to me.
You must find him
at all costs.
God, please,
don’t let him leave the city.
-Mr. Ji.
Mr. Ji.
Mr. Ji, Mr. Shao is waiting inside.
Your tie is worn backwards.
I’m off work already.
Finally, we can leave.
Did you make this puzzle box?
Where’s the opening?
I tried but didn’t find it.
What is this?
This is a mortise-tenon box.
Not for amateurs.
Architects are indeed dexterous.
But what’s the point of making
so many boxes if only you can open them?
None of your business. Now, shoot.
What brings you here?
What else other than your marriage?
Miss Li called earlier.
Your grandpa is in rage
and he’s gonna
give you a good talking-to.
You’d better lie low.
He made that decision without asking me.
That’s not my problem.
Then do something.
If you were seeing someone,
he wouldn’t
rush you every day.
Who says I’m not?
You are?
Then tell me,
when was the last time
you had physical contact with a girl?
Do you remember that?
This afternoon.
What? Am I... Hearing it right?
Who was it? How close were you?
That was an accident.
Just a simple touch.
She...
Touch? Where?
You two... Kissed?
She... She kissed you first?
The other way round, I think.
What does she look like? How old is she?
Is she hot?
Not interested.
You’re looking for someone? Who?
A heart-throb.
My hero of the book, to be accurate.
Is he dead?
Does he exist?
(Datong Sliced Noodles)
How like-minded are you!
Are you really my friends?
But how is it possible?
I thought your heart is made of steel.
No one and nothing can melt you.
Were love your thing,
you wouldn’t still be single.
I don’t believe you either.
The thing called love
isn’t in your gene.
Or, you’d fall head over heels for me
before being taken by Liu Xia.
You...
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Laugh all you want.
I couldn’t believe it myself
that I’d have a crush on a stranger.
I’m probably drowsy.
Somebody better wake me up.
Who was it?
(Datong Sliced Noodles)
Sorry, sorry.
My... My friend got dumped
and drank too much.
I’ll make her apologize to you.
Come here.
Come. Sit back.
Sit down.
-There, there.
-It’s OK.
It’s OK.
Uh... Madam,
did you get dumped?
No, it’s my friend.
She got rejected. Sorry.
I’m sorry.
I see. That makes sense.
Excuse me?
What’s wrong with me?
Let’s go.
(Department of Architecture,
Chunming University)
Hold on.
Department of Architecture,
Chunming University.
You too?
I’m sorry.
Never mind. Take care of your friend.
She’s been through a lot.
I’m sorry.
You know her?
No.
But I know
who hurt her.
Who?
Chunming’s unique asset,
the hotshot in our department,
Prof. Ji.
Who is that?
Every year when freshmen arrive,
he’ll give lectures
as the visiting professor.
Girls all over the campus
are crazy about him,
but he drives lecturers and TAs crazy.
Why?
As charming as he is,
he’s cold as ice.
He never
remembers students’ names
but only their IDs,
and there’s no
communication between them.
TA is the messenger.
How did you know all that?
Because I’m the one
who has to get him TAs.
I’m a guidance counselor,
not his babysitter.
And now,
all his students hate me.
He doesn’t like any of them.
My life is hell!
You know, my boss is no better.
He’s a walking iceberg.
There’s no human touch
in him or his work.
But he’s already
won the highest award
in the industry this young.
His look and talents top others’.
So his temper can be tolerated.
Qi Nian, is your heart-throb like that?
Of course not.
What are you doing?
Looking for a lost dog.
At 5 pm on May 5th,
I lost a Golden Retriever
by the lake in Huangdao,
named Qi Bao.
He’s five years old,
gentle and loves snacks.
The man who walked him
is charismatic.
If you see that man and the dog,
please contact me.
You’ll be rewarded handsomely.
Is that too obvious and brazen?
Hope others can tell
that the man is the whole point.
(Lost Dog)
At that time, I thought
as we lived at
opposite ends of the city,
we wouldn’t meet again anytime soon.
But the encounter came
sooner than I expected.
(I might’ve seen him
at Chunming University…)
Chunming University.
(Library)
(Chunming University)
The campus is huge. Where is he?
Good.
No guards in the neighborhood.
Excuse me.
I’m not taking photos
of others but the view.
Don’t be nervous.
I’d like to ask you about someone.
Go ahead.
I know everyone here.
Have you seen a handsome man
with a Golden Retriever?
There are enough competitors on campus
and here comes more from other schools.
So do you want retouched photos
or raw ones altogether?
What?
If you aren’t here to buy photos,
why are you asking about him?
To be my prototype.
That might sound complicated.
I should make it simple.
I’ll be blunt.
I want him to be mine.
I’ve met tons of hardcore fans,
but they aren’t as blunt as she is.
Did anything happen
between you guys?
Does a kiss count?
Kiss?
On what?
On… the lips.
There she is!
That freshman again who snaps pictures.
-They’re worse than flies.
-Over there.
Come here. Come.
Come here.
Lecture theater, Floor 1,
Architecture Building. Take a front seat.
Why?
Trust me. You’ll thank me later.
Stop! I’ve had eyes on you for long.
Stop!
He’s hot!
So cool!
It’s him!
Who?
Do you regret it now?
Yeah. I should’ve known it.
Who else deserves
to be called a hotshot?
OK.
The class is full. Let’s begin.
No roll call?
I’ve told you already
that his class is always full.
Roll call is unnecessary.
Here it is. That’s it.
That’s it.
What’s happening?
Why are they so excited?
This is the once-in-a-year bonus.
Of course everyone is thrilled.
Are those who took this course last year
also here?
Me.
Why are they
taking the same course again?
To challenge ourselves.
I failed last year
and I have to try again.
What did she mean?
Chinese Mortise-tenon
is widely used in structures
in ancient buildings,
such as beams, pillars and brackets.
It’s also a clear proof
of how skilled
the ancient architects are.
The puzzle box I’m holding
is one example.
You’re welcome
to try to open it.
Like last year,
whoever succeeds
will be granted a request.
Extra points in the exam?
Your WeChat account?
That’s nothing.
I’d ask for individual tutoring.
In your dreams!
I want one-on-one tutoring.
I want an exclusive bonus.
You’re hot, Prof. Ji!
Sit down!
This year’s box
must be more difficult.
Those girls have to wait another year.
What to do?
I can’t help drawing muscles
whenever I’m excited.
Leave me alone. I’m busy.
Professor, I’m taking notes.
So you must’ve written down
everything I said.
Alright. Class is over.
Come to my office later
for a quiz.
Bring your notebook.
Congrats. The first-ever
detention winner.
This is your first day
and you’ve already enjoyed so much.
Shut up.
Now, you can try to open it.
Prof. Ji, Director Shen asks to see you.
I see.
Wait here for me.
What? What did he say?
He asked you to wait here for him.
Give me. Give me. Give me.
Can’t open it.
Is there a way?
Let me try it.
I’ll have them put together
profiles of guests at the symposium.
Thanks. There will be a huge crowd.
You got this?
I’ll do my best.
It’s open!
I’m about to get married.
Congratulations.
Aren’t you gonna ask who the groom is?
We’re in a relationship,
but why am I suddenly
marrying someone else?
We aren’t that close
as to have a relationship.
If there’s nothing else...
What do you not like about me?
What’s wrong with me?
Your grandpa has accepted me.
You want an answer?
Qi Bao doesn’t like you.
If I remember correctly, that’s your...
Yes, that’s my dog,
a Golden Retriever who greeted you
when you first came to our place.
You avoided him by instinct
which made him
lose his appetite for a while.
Is that a serious problem?
It is.
But we’re talking about a dog.
Correct.
Let’s call it a day, Miss Lin.
It’s Li.
Whatever.
Yes?
Qi Bao is missing?
♪We’re like the North and South Poles♪
♪The never-crossing heaven and earth♪
♪My world♪
♪Doesn’t open to others♪
♪But you fill the entire space♪
♪I opened my heart to you♪
♪You invited yourself in♪
♪Love isn’t just about affection♪
♪There’s anxiety too♪
♪I’m greedy♪
♪Our relationship is a miracle♪
♪Everything is calculated
Don’t run away♪
♪Fate will work out the puzzle♪
♪Let love continue to grow♪
♪However hard you try
Feelings can’t be controlled♪
♪From two hearts to one mind♪
♪Love is irrational♪
♪Just because I♪
♪Want to be with you♪