♪I collect everything about you♪
♪Play scenes of you again and again♪
♪Try to leave a deeper impression♪
♪Calling my name is enough♪
♪In this world only I understand you♪
♪I care the most about you♪
♪In this world only I’m here with you♪
♪Yet I’m still confused♪
♪I wish to hold your hand
just for one second at this intersection♪
♪I might’ve said that 100 times♪
♪Maybe I’m clumsy in your eyes♪
♪Maybe I haven’t done enough yet♪
♪I wish to close the gap
to prove myself to you♪
♪Sweet romance slowly fills the air♪
♪Love is never an accident♪
♪No need to uncover the truth♪
♪The answer is right there♪
=Be With You=
=Episode 19=
It hurts!
Hello?
May I speak to Qi Nian?
She?
She’s on the floor and can’t get up.
What?
She suffered a dislocation yesterday.
Possibly because
she had a sprain in her waist
because of big move.
Move?
What move?
I’ll put her on the phone.
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Qi Nian.
Was that Ji Yanxin?
Did you make up with him?
He’s with you so early.
Did you sleep with him?
That’s awesome, girl!
But what did you do?
Dislocation and sprain?
So violent?
Couldn’t you restrain yourselves?
Don’t have such complicated thoughts.
We’re pure, all right?
I had a dislocation
because Ji Yanxin...
Well, forget it.
Let’s get to the point.
Fine. I’ll get to the point, then.
On the momentum
of Dress for the Beauty,
our company will hold
an Autograph Session for you.
The promotion theme
will be love across three-D.
Next week.
Autograph Session?
But Mr. Ji...
He’s the prototype...
That’s just the package.
Who will try to figure it out?
What should I prepare for that?
Get yourself prepared.
Tell Ji Yanxin
I need an energetic you.
If he dares to make you like this again,
I’ll go and tear down his office.
I see.
I’ll take good care of her for you.
Let me have a look.
It hurts!
It hurts! It hurts!
Seems like you can’t walk now.
Why don’t you stay in bed today?
I’ll take good care of you.
But... But I need to paint.
You can do it here.
Isn’t it a hotel room?
We need to extend our stay.
It bothers.
Who told you it was a hotel room?
From now on,
it is your exclusive room.
Mine?
There are more rooms.
Would you like to have a look?
This is…
Your studio.
You can paint here,
instead of working in the company
just for AC.
When you have an assistant,
ask her to work here.
Here are prepared tools.
It’s better than sharing
the small apartment with Siqi.
You feel too painful to stand?
Thank you
for considering so much for me.
You’re welcome.
I think I’m an idiot.
I shouldn’t have suspected you.
I should have a time travel
and slap myself.
That’s not necessary.
But I should really deal with
your messy imaginations.
Deal with?
How?
(Jin Xianyu)
(Follow)
(Unfollow)
(Confirm to unfollow? Confirm)
Fine.
He has nothing to do with me now.
Let me post a toast online.
I have just closed a big fan club
of hundreds of thousands of fans
for my previous idol.
I’m feeling blue.
Please comfort me.
My boyfriend said he would deal with me
and I’m not allowed to get off bed.
What should I do?
Anxious for the answer.
Wow, sounds exciting.
Let me care for the poster first.
Are you alright?
Is your boyfriend a snake?
He’s pestering.
It’s a long story.
Over the morning,
I’m forced to remain useless.
I believe
this is what he wants.
Morning.
Well,
this is my self-criticism.
(Prof. Ji, my love.)
(This is my ever first self-criticism.)
May I go have breakfast now?
Stop.
I can’t go?
I warned you
that I would control
the rest of your life.
This is your own choice.
But I have work to do.
My informer told me
you fulfilled your last two weeks
with work.
You have days off from today on.
You wasted time imagining things.
Now, you’ll make up for that.
I told you
I wouldn’t let you go.
Be prepared, then.
Let’s go have breakfast.
(MC)
Negotiation failed.
I feel I’ll be totally controlled
in the next three days
and I’ve given up.
Don’t give up, girl.
If you do,
you’ll always be controlled.
Fine, then.
This is romance, understand?
You must be a young girl.
If I can have such romance,
I’ll even wake up laughing.
Who is she?
Why is she talking like an adult?
Help!
My young boyfriend
is more conservative than me.
How can I
finally get him?
Looks really like an adult thing.
How conservative?
Be specific.
A day with him
starts like this.
Hello?
Why are you calling so early?
Miss me?
Early?
Employees usually arrive at company
at this time,
all right?
You have half an hour.
I’m waiting for you downstairs.
Hurry up.
Hello?
You’re so slow.
Bad boy.
Do you know how much time a girl needs
before she leaves home?
Half an hour is only enough
for my foundation make-up.
Look.
I haven’t combed my hair.
I’m too ugly to go out.
No.
You look good to me.
Really?
You look simpler.
Why are you wearing so little?
Don’t you have a common sense?
It’s for me?
The diurnal temperature is huge lately.
Don’t you know?
I guess you only wear beautiful dresses.
Take the shawl to work,
just in case.
Why are you staring at me?
You waited for me in the early morning,
just to give me this?
What?
You don’t like that?
Not really.
But you look like
you would take out a thermos cup
from your bag.
Fine, forget the thermos cup.
I have them.
What are they?
Kneepads. They’re for you.
What do I need such ugly things for?
To protect your knees.
You’re no longer young, anyway.
What, bad boy?
Say it again!
You don’t like them?
I have the thermal underwear.
Would you like it?
Get away.
Would you like cotton-padded trousers?
Am I really in a relationship
with a young boyfriend?
Anyway,
he’s a vulgarian.
But I just want him to stay around.
Unfortunately,
he doesn’t accept that
at all.
Live in your home?
No.
Why?
You don’t need to wait for me, then.
We can also go to work
and come back together.
Isn’t it great?
No.
We have family rules.
We can’t live together
before getting married.
But we have...
Shut up.
Didn’t we agree
to follow the prescribed rule?
What about agreed happy life?
When can we have it next time?
Seriously?
Must we wait until we get married?
What’s the family rule?
Why do you consider so much?
What’s the problem with that?
(Legal age of marriage for Chinese men)
(Legal age of marriage for Chinese)
(Men shall not get married
before 22 years old.)
22 years?
Two years to go.
In this way,
I’ll be an old leftover woman.
(myfun.com)
(Residential)
If only I could keep him!
Who?
What?
Want to buy an apartment
to keep a young man?
What are you talking about?
I’m not that unrestrained.
By the way,
where did you go
after the welcome meeting?
I called you, but you didn’t answer.
What happened?
The new cartoonist you recruited...
He’s Ji Siqi, right?
He’s arrogant.
When he first came,
he beat a colleague.
He did?
Several group leaders
complained about him.
Do you want more enemies in the company?
Enemies?
They can do nothing,
but sing dis rap in the distance.
See if they dare to complain
in front of me?
Why didn’t they ask
the reason that Ji Siqi beat them?
Before interfering with someone else,
they should ask their subordinates
to behave themselves.
Well,
sounds like you think highly of Ji Siqi.
I think highly of my respect.
I’m his boss, anyway.
(Fancy Dream Shop)
(Listen to your heart)
(Target for This Week)
48 pages within one week?
So much work?
Can she finish it alone?
Miss Lu never does such rough work,
as painting.
What do you mean?
This is Lu Qingwu’s Studio.
All comic books
are her works,
no matter if she draws any.
We just
work for her.
We can be replaced at any time.
Unlike you who can represent her.
I’m also a cartoonist,
like you.
What?
You look handsome.
Aren’t you her assistant?
Didn’t Jia embarrass you?
They enjoy suppressing cartoonists.
Jia?
What are you listening to?
Hush!
A quarrel is breaking out.
Mr. Xiao and Miss Lu are arguing.
Well,
I’ll transfer him
to logistics downstairs,
as an explanation for others.
When they’re no longer angry,
I’ll get him back.
Are you kidding?
I hired Ji Siqi!
I promised to offer him
the best working condition.
But you want to get him to logistics?
Aren’t you embarrassing me?
Why are you so angry?
He’s just an assistant of Baby Seven.
Many other cartoonists
draw better than him.
He’s different.
I owe him a future.
And I owe someone else a promise.
Don’t bother about Ji Siqi.
Fine.
I’ll see
how much he can do
under your leadership.
Did I see you somewhere before?
Mr. Xiao.
He’s Ji Siqi.
Oh, I see.
That explains.
You have a loose tongue. Huh?
Come on and have a word with me.
Come on.
You...
Where are you taking me?
I didn’t mean that.
Without consideration,
it just slipped it out.
I didn’t mean to hurt you.
What are you nervous for?
I didn’t say I would beat you.
You deserve that, though.
What do you want, then?
Whatever,
I’m the chief assistant of Miss Lu.
If you beat me,
you’ll be...
Disrespecting her, right?
I know.
You’re one of Lu Qingwu’s assistants,
aren’t you?
You should be aware
of her things.
Sure.
I know everything
about Miss Lu.
Does she have substitutes?
Others even draw storyboards
for her.
In the name of chief painter,
what did she draw?
She drew something.
Something like covers, color pages
and frontispieces.
But the content...
Then she has substitutes!
She’s awesome!
What’s the problem with that?
It’s weird
if a famous cartoonist like her
draws personally.
But she’s a cartoonist.
You just watch when she sinks?
You sound too serious.
Miss Lu can draw.
She just likes to delay.
Delay?
You don’t know?
Whoever experienced that
got crazy or exhausted.
That’s why Mr. Xiao uses substitutes.
If you don’t want her to sink,
ask her to submit her works in time.
This is the color page and frontispiece
for next volume.
Get these from her first.
Are you flooding this pot of flowers?
You keep watering them at the same spot.
What brings you here?
To urge you to paint.
Urge me?
You’re a cartoonist,
not an editor.
Listen.
You’re an ordinary cartoonist now.
But I’ll apply
for your independent creation
as early as possible.
Don’t bother.
I’m not experienced enough.
I’ll first learn from you.
Me?
You don’t like the way I draw
and my stories,
do you?
Do you know
people always change?
I began to love your comics.
Accurately speaking,
I’m now a fan of yours.
I’m crazy about your comics now
and I want to observe
your painting skills
at close quarters.
Close?
How close do you want?
It depends on you.
I’ll follow your work for this week.
I’ll stay
wherever you paint.
Really?
Well,
what about my home?
No problem,
as long as you finish the work in time.
I will, I will.
I will do that.
Why don’t we do it now?
Move to my home today.
Fine.
Enjoy them.
You’ve ordered all the cakes,
haven’t you?
You want the sense of ceremony, huh?
Getting full
can be better than getting bald.
Who’s bald?
Fine, then.
You’ll pay the bill, anyway.
It’s considerate of you.
You still remember my favorite.
(Maths final of Grade 3)
(Class 3, Grade 3, Ji Qiu, Mark, 30)
Stop crying.
You just failed a math exam.
What do you know?
My parents should sign it.
My cousin will scold me to death.
Sign?
Easy job.
Let me help you.
Who are you?
You’re only a friend of my cousin’s.
Why do you want to sign for me?
Because I don’t have parents?
I’m your follower.
I should certainly share your burden.
Whatever you want,
come to me as you wish.
As long as you want something,
I’ll make it for you.
But why?
There’s no reason.
This is my duty as your follower.
You don’t believe that?
My boss Ji Qiu.
I’m Shao Zui,
and I’ll always be here
to help you.
Now you believe me?
Weirdo.
Boss.
Your mouth.
Come on.
We’re not making a sesame paste ad.
Disgusting.
Well,
leave such a small thing to me.
Just stay and sit.
Before I realize it,
I’ve known him for nearly ten years.
Look at you.
You’re no longer young.
But you still get something
around your mouth.
Ji Qiu?
You don’t have a fever.
What’s wrong?
Why are you so obedient today?
Do I have something on you?
I just don’t bother to argue with you.
That’s fine.
As long as
my boss can be happy.
You finally remember I’m your boss?
You respected me in the first few years.
Lately,
you’ve become more arrogant.
Because you’ve also grown up.
I can’t always treat you
like a little girl.
You no longer treat me
like a little girl?
You’re turning 20 in a few days.
You’re an adult
who can take responsibilities alone.
Sure.
From today on,
I’ll focus on my career.
Idol is fake.
So is love.
You finally begin to understand,
after all the time.
Here is a chance for you to work hard.
Would you like a try?
What is it?
Dress for the Beauty
will be made into a TV series.
Do you want to be a part?
Really?
Dress for the Beauty
will be made into a TV series?
Are you sure?
It’s only under a small discussion
on the forum.
According to inside information of MC,
it’s very likely to be true.
Mr. Xiao.
It hits our film plan, doesn’t it?
Flower & Romance has just...
Lately,
MC has been the limelight.
Yes.
Next week,
Baby Seven will have
an Autograph Session.
An unknown cartoonist
got famous for a comic book,
after working ineffectively
for three to five years.
What good luck she has!
Baby Seven?
She’s really
a stubborn girl.
Mr. Xiao, you know her?
Kind of.
She’s someone I should let go of.
It’s not too late
to do it now.
Go prepare a press release
about Baby Seven.
You know
what I mean.
Don’t worry, Mr. Xiao.
Wait.
Where’s Miss Lu?
Why didn’t I see her today?
She said she would paint at home
in the next three days.
She...
Paint?
Is this how a boyfriend should behave?
I’m sorry,
but your boyfriend Ji Siqi
has been locked in the cupboard.
Today, I’m your editor and assistant,
Key.
Let’s work hard for the day.
Key, huh?
Where’s your luggage?
Are you sure you come empty-handed?
I believe you will complete today’s work
before dawn,
for the sake of your efficiency.
So, I’m not going to stay for tonight.
Do you still remember this place?
Would you like to do it one more time?
Fine.
But not before you complete
the frontispiece and color pages
for next week.
Seriously?
And twenty pages of rough sketch.
All of them.
Twenty pages?
Are you kidding me?
How can I finish them within one day?
You can also continue them tomorrow.
If you want a reward,
pay the price.
Sit down.
You think you have one day.
But only six hours left.
Miss Lu.
Are you still wasting time
in our conversation?
Ji Siqi, you...
You have five hours, fifty-nine minutes,
and fifty-four seconds.
You’re determined
to be a cruel urging machine, huh?
You want paintings, right?
I’ll give them to you in no time.
Wait.
Bad boy.
I know you can’t restrain yourself.
Are you kidding me?
With so many burdens on your nails,
how can you draw perfectly?
Cut them.
Fine. Fine.
I’ll cut them in the shop tomorrow.
But let me go today.
No, cut them now!
But I...
These are files for your paintings.
Call me if you need anything else.
I want to go out and be happy.
That’s simple.
After you complete your work.
You’re serious?
Do I look like I’m kidding?
Ji Siqi.
I understand your intention.
But such ways don’t work for me.
Others tried them before.
Continue?
Not until you complete the frontispiece.
You can’t do this to me.
I’m going to buy some water.
Why?
Leave after you flirted with me?
Solve the problem yourself.
When I’m back,
I’ll see the drafts, anyway.
I nearly trapped myself.
I’d better not play this trick again.
I gotta go.
Bye-bye.
See you.
-Bye-bye.
(Dress for the Beauty is a love TV series
adapted from the comic book)
(Content, Project Instruction, Casting)
(Project Instruction)
Looks good.
Sure.
I used to make all promotion materials
for my idol.
Isn’t he the most popular actor?
What’s his name?
Su...
(Proposed actor for Mr. J)
Su Xuran.
He’s the new best actor.
A young actor with a promising future.
He’s my new idol.
Come on.
You pick someone you like again?
No.
He’s suitable.
Mr. Shao?
Why are you still here?
I was held up.
What about you?
Left something?
Oh, Mr. Shao,
I’ve decided the place
for Baby Seven’s Autograph Session.
I mailed you
related websites.
I received that.
Oh,
I’ve got a proposal.
Come and check it for me.
Come on.
What do you think of it?
You want me to be frank?
Sure.
The pattern looks better
than the content.
Seems like
the author only knows about films,
but doesn’t have a specific plan.
She also hasn’t further studied
the IP value of Dress for the Beauty.
If I were you,
I would let her do it again.
If it can be done again,
does it mean the proposal can be used?
Sure.
Obviously,
the author worked hard on this project
and has deep feelings
for Dress for the Beauty.
I think this matters a lot.
But, Mr. Shao,
why are you suddenly interested
in this project?
Look.
I want you to take care of this project.
What do you think?
Do you want me
to take care of this project
or the author of this project?
You’re good at guessing.
How about a promotion for you?
You heard it, didn’t you?
Modify it, then.
She’s really experienced.
She saw the problem at a single glance.
Sure.
Or,
I wouldn’t have her take care of you.
You should
learn carefully from her.
When I’m away...
Away?
Where are you going?
Nowhere. Nothing.
Forget it.
You must be hungry.
I’m going to modify my proposal.
You suddenly work hard?
Wait and see.
I’ll make a perfect proposal
that everyone is satisfied with.
I’ve been out for one hour, huh?
But you drew nothing?
I have no inspiration.
Why don’t you continue it
to inspire me?
How would you like me to inspire you?
Hold my hand, at least.
It works.
Hurry up.
You can hold my hand
for five more minutes, at most.
How mean you are!
Miss Lu, you’re old but still vigorous.
Bad boy.
Take back that word!
I’ll take back my hand, too.
Wait a second.
Let me have more inspiration.
Time is up soon.
Why... Why?
Charging up.
Done.
Thank you, my little battery.
I’ll go have a nap.
(To Jia)
Oh, my God.
Miss Lu completed her paintings in time!
How did you make it?
Instruct me.
I can’t and I won’t!
Never think of it!
How mean!
But it’s not time to celebrate yet.
You just sent me the frontispiece.
Inside pages can be the hell.
Be specific.
Look at the eyes
and just feel it.
You went for a nap, didn’t you?
I couldn’t fall asleep.
I’ve completed my work.
Can’t I have a little reward?
You’ve pretended to be cool for long.
You must be tired.
Who pretended?
I was doing my duty as an editor.
Fine, Mr. Editor.
Do you dare
to stare at me for fifteen seconds?
What’s the trick?
You think you’re Cheon Song-Yi?
Let’s get started.
My eyes are dry.
It’s so hard when I can’t blink.
Don’t go.
Try it again.
Enjoy yourself alone!
I failed to kiss him.
What makes him angry?
♪We’re like the North and South Poles♪
♪The never-crossing heaven and earth♪
♪My world♪
♪Doesn’t open to others♪
♪But you fill the entire space♪
♪I opened my heart to you♪
♪You invited yourself in♪
♪Love isn’t just about affection♪
♪There’s anxiety too♪
♪I’m greedy♪
♪Our relationship is a miracle♪
♪Everything is calculated
Don’t run away♪
♪Fate will work out the puzzle♪
♪Let love continue to grow♪
♪However hard you try
Feelings can’t be controlled♪
♪From two hearts to one mind♪
♪Love is irrational♪
♪Just because I♪
♪Want to be with you♪