[The Story of Xing Fu]
[Episode 22]
As to how others asked for your help to get a job,
don't tell a word to Yani's father.
I heard from Guan Tao
that it's against the law.
For real?
Why are there so many laws nowadays?
You...
Xingfu.
Qinglai.
You're here.
Xingyun, you are here.
Your apartment is well-decorated.
Not another gift.
Yani and Qingzhi came
with plenty of gifts too.
We are more than comfortable here.
Oh, come on.
I just received my commission.
Besides, this is the latest rice cooker.
You can preset the cooking timer.
It's very useful.
I can't come in empty-handed.
Xingyun.
How much is your commission?
Oh, Qinglai.
With me, it's alright.
But when you're out there,
don't ask
anyone this kind of question,
including their salary.
It's rude.
Is that so?
We weren't aware of it.
No worries.
Xingfu,
how are you coping in Fangyuan Law Firm?
I heard
that they have been running a deficit.
If that carries on,
it won't last long.
You need to have a plan.
Haven't I told you
that my work there with Guan Tao was fine?
Also,
it's not right to leave them
when they are in a crisis.
But even a puppy
needs to be fed.
It's just a kind reminder.
I'm not a puppy.
That's not what I meant.
But
Xingfu,
what are you wearing?
Do I look good?
It's my working attire.
You do look good
but this is not the right moment.
Why would you don your working attire
at night back home?
I want to be a businesswoman.
Sure.
Businesswoman.
[Fangyuan Law Firm]
(Hi.)
(I'm here for legal consultation.)
(I've made an appointment.)
You're...
Sha.
Miss Sha.
Yes.
You booked a meeting with Mr. Guan Tao.
-Yes.
-Okay.
Here.
This way, please.
Mr. Guan.
This is
[Fangyuan Law Firm]
Miss Sha. You have an appointment with her.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Hi, Miss Sha.
Mr. Guan.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
Please come in.
Okay.
Xingfu.
Can you
accommodate her for the moment?
Please have a seat.
This is my document. Please have a look.
Sit here too.
Okay.
Miss Sha.
Don't worry.
She's my intern.
You need not worry
about confidentiality issues.
Okay.
Eh?
Why is she allowed in at the meeting again?
Right?
It's fine if she's just sitting there.
Last time, I was meeting with a client.
She then proceeded to give her input.
Really?
She did?
What did she say?
I don't want to mention it.
She was more emotional than my client.
However,
when the client just came in,
she was mentally vulnerable.
Xingfu talked with her for half an hour.
And when the client was about to leave,
both of them were like sisters.
Interesting.
Do you have any questions?
Not at the moment.
As for the texts and video evidence,
I'll try
to find more.
Definitely.
See you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Guan Tao.
This is not right.
When we're meeting with the clients,
you let
Xingfu sit here.
What
is going on?
Besides,
she's very keen on offering her opinions.
Well,
this is a law firm.
Not a wet market.
Xingfu is very hardworking.
We should acknowledge that.
Mr. Guan.
Your pen.
Thank you.
Come.
I mean, what kind of mess
will she create?
Besides, we're all here
supervising.
If there's a problem,
we nip it in the bud.
Go back to work.
Let's go.
Our boss has said so.
[Common Legal Jargon]
[Fangyuan Law Firm]
Here, please,
Mr. Liu.
Thanks.
Mr. Zhang.
I'm Zhang Weicheng. Hi.
Hi.
Have a seat.
Please be seated.
This law firm
looks new.
The three of us
were all working for some big law firms.
But then we thought
that it's better to establish our own firm
than work for someone else.
Therefore, the three of us
decided to start a business.
You see,
I have a friend.
He's very close
to Mr. Guan Tao.
Have some water.
Thank you.
Stay hydrated, Mr. Liu.
But the working condition here
is a tad too rudimentary.
It's because we just started.
We start small.
Exactly.
Well,
Xingfu.
We need a moment with Mr. Liu.
Can you go outside for a while?
You can go back to your work.
Go.
Okay.
Don't mind it, Mr. Liu.
It's okay.
Carry on without me first.
Xingfu.
In a moment,
I'll need you to refill the water.
Bring this in as well.
Okay.
Yidao was working with us
to handle the company's legal affairs.
Do you know
Mr. Han?
We have heard of him.
Is that so?
Yes.
Guan Tao used to work for him.
So...
What do you think of Mr. Han?
That's a complicated matter.
Guan Tao doesn't usually discuss
other lawyers behind their backs.
So we aren't too sure.
I see.
Because my friend
said Mr. Guan Tao
was a very decent person.
You two look young.
Have you handled
any major cases?
Mr. Liu,
you probably weren't aware of this.
Age
has nothing to do
with whether one has taken part
in major cases or not.
Yes.
Truth be told,
we have dealt with cases
that involved more than ten million yuan.
Can you tell me
more about it?
Unfortunately, it's confidential.
Yes.
We signed
an NDA.
I see.
Then
can you tell me
who you represented?
I'm afraid we can't.
Yes,
we signed
an NDA.
We have to respect
our clients.
You see.
The cases themselves
is confidential.
The clients involved
are also confidential.
Yes.
It's quite unheard of.
Well, here's the thing.
A law firm
has its own rules.
We
are very serious
about our clients.
Xingfu,
refill, please.
Okay.
I know the firm isn't that big yet, Mr. Liu.
Right.
We just started.
Here,
Mr. Zhang.
What is this?
The court verdict.
The court verdict?
The court verdict
of your previous case is out.
We won.
Oh, that case.
That was a tough case.
Very tough.
Mr. Wang here
took on
a lost case
and finally
won the appeal.
But isn't this...
Xingfu.
Go back
to your work.
That's quite impressive.
I'm flattered.
You won the appeal
of a lost case.
You see,
our country
has put in place an appeal system.
It's like
a second hearing.
For this case,
the other lawyer
was a bit careless during the first hearing.
He missed one key piece of evidence.
We used it
in the court of appeal
to turn the tide.
Exactly.
Then,
as to my case...
Why don't you tell us more?
We need
more details.
Sure.
You see.
Please
have a look.
Sure.
This is...
Don't worry.
We'll do our best.
Come, Mr. Liu.
Okay.
Thank you. Bye.
Take care, Mr. Liu.
Sure.
So?
This might be the highest-paid case
since the establishment of this firm.
Xingfu.
It's all thanks to you.
Without you,
Mr. Liu
could never be convinced.
What?
What do I have to do with it?
You didn't get it?
You see,
One of Guan Tao's friends
recommended our firm to Mr. Liu.
Guan Tao
thought
he wouldn't pick us.
But we two
believe that if we can convince Mr. Liu,
it'll be our best chance
to turn things around here.
So both of us decided
to meet with Mr. Liu.
The rest is what you saw.
He wasn't too happy with our firm.
He thought it was too small
and we were too inexperienced.
Right?
But it's okay.
Weicheng
was my shill.
He said I was experienced
and efficient.
And you put up the perfect show.
Oh.
Especially you, Xingfu.
You
look trustworthy,
natural,
and graceful.
That dispelled the doubt left
in Mr. Liu.
You have contributed tremendously
to our law firm.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
We got Mr. Liu as our client.
That's all.
Are you sure?
I remember
he's hard to please.
He is.
But we have a secret weapon.
What secret weapon?
You extorted him?
What?
We would never do that.
Our secret weapon
is Xingfu.
Come with me to organize the documents.
Ask Xingfu if you have questions.
Hey.
Xingfu.
What happened?
They
met Mr. Liu who's recommended here by your friend
to talk about a case.
Then Mr. Zhang asked me
to send in a court verdict halfway through.
He then claimed that he won
an appeal.
But in fact,
I delivered
the court verdict
of the traffic case last week.
Mr. Liu suspected nothing
and proceeded to entrust them with the case.
Mr. Guan,
they lied.
Do you think it's right for us to do this?
Guan Tao.
I think
you're overreacting.
This is not a big deal.
Exactly.
No matter whether we took on big cases before
or won any appeals,
it won't affect him at all.
Once we take his case,
we'll do our best.
Won't that cut it?
Do you believe a word
you said?
If this won't affect anything,
why did you two
lie to him?
Because we're inexperienced
and he
might lose confidence in us.
If they don't have confidence in us,
we should do something
to inspire confidence.
I'll call
Mr. Liu
to explain this to him.
Are you two okay with it?
No, Guan Tao.
I think
you're out of your mind.
Why can't we work on this case
to solve our current crisis first?
Once we have enough liquidity,
you can show your integrity then, all right?
No way!
You're lying.
Should we earn money by lying?
When the going gets tough,
you choose the easy way out.
Some deeds
are to be avoided forever.
If you commit it once,
it'll become a habit.
Right.
Yes.
I agree with you.
We understand.
But we're doing this
for our law firm.
All right?
Once we take on Mr. Liu's case
and the cash flows into the firm,
your salary will increase too.
Also, Guan Tao.
If you call him,
everything will be ruined.
Do you think it's worth it?
Why did we establish
our own firm?
Because we didn't like the work?
We didn't like the pay?
It's because we didn't like
their ethics.
We established our own firm
so that we can do what we think
is right.
But now, to get a big case,
the end justified the means.
So why did we even open this firm?
You're right, Guan Tao.
But who'd have thought
that it would be so hard at the start?
No one trusts us.
We don't even have
a proper case.
If this carries on,
this firm will be closed down soon.
What's the good of persisting
with your principles?
Then I'll quit!
If you don't want to stay, let's break it off here!
Also,
the decision has been made.
Before we sign the deal,
I have to clarify
everything to Mr. Liu.
Even if it means we can't get this case,
Fangyuan Law Firm
will not be a cheat!
Mr. Han,
Mr. Liu is waiting for you in the office.
[Yidao Law Firm]
Mr. Liu.
You sure are a busy man.
Zhao,
you're dismissed.
Okay.
Why are you here?
I thought you handed the case
to another law firm.
Mr. Gong
from Xiyan
recommended Guan Tao
to me.
He used to work here.
Guan Tao?
He left
not too long ago.
He established a small law firm
with some young lawyers.
I like to experiment.
I want to give the youth a chance
so I visited his law firm.
But I never heard of
any impressive cases
under his belt.
Well, I actually
know something about that.
You know, everyone
starts somewhere.
If you guys like each other that much,
why did you come here?
Truth be told,
before I headed to their law firm,
I hoped to use this case
to establish
a long-term partnership
with them.
Mr. Liu.
I gave you an inch. Do not take a mile.
You have signed the contract
and you came here.
Are you trying to brag?
If I
signed the contract with them,
why would I come here?
What do you mean?
I was thinking
that you
should handle this case.
It sounds like
there's more
to your story with Fangyuan.
I thought
the young ones should be
straightforward
and honest.
But guess what happened?
They
tried to con me.
Con you?
Please. Tell me everything.
They tried
to con a sly fox like you?
What did they say?
I want to learn from them.
They made things up.
They told me
they had worked on big cases.
I asked them what kind of big cases
but they couldn't answer.
And they claimed
that they had won the appeal
for a lost case.
Honestly,
I can understand
that young people
are less experienced.
But
if they think
they can always take the easy way out...
Once this becomes a habit,
it'll be grim.
Also,
when I was there,
I never said I wanted to look
at their achievements.
So...
I thought about it
and decided
to give you the case.
At least, I know
what you're capable of.
As expected of someone shrewd like you.
Sure.
A fine choice, it is.
You know what?
I'll let
He handle it.
She's familiar
with your company.
Deal.
Dig in.
Mr. Guan.
What are you doing?
Why are you buying me a meal?
Can you guess?
Is it because
the firm is closing down
so this is like a farewell meal?
Can you be more positive?
I...
I'm just worried that I won't receive
my salary this month
and I have to look for jobs again.
You
work very hard
but you don't get paid a lot.
Why are you so adamant
about doing things the right way?
My mother-in-law said the same thing too.
That I'm adamant
and headstrong.
But I don't think
it's a bad thing.
We should know
what's right and what's wrong.
Don't you think?
So
I treat you to this meal
to thank you.
For what?
I kept thinking,
if you weren't there to keep an eye on me,
to question me,
and to ask for justifications,
or if I knew about this
in a more private setting,
would I have acquiesced in their decision?
After all, this case
would bring in
a lot of money to the firm.
And we need money.
So you're thanking me for this?
Would you have condoned it then?
I don't know.
Do you think I'd have done it?
No.
Starting your own business
is as difficult as it is.
But you remain
a man of integrity,
a man of his word,
and a man who's hardworking.
You're trustworthy
and you can give people a sense of security.
I don't think you will do such a thing.
Xingfu,
you're more resilient than me.
You're an amazing person.
Don't you make fun of me.
If I'm amazing,
then everyone else
will be spectacular then.
Let's eat.
Hello, Xingyun.
What's the matter?
Senior.
Did Mr. Liu
[Archive]
go to your firm?
Yes.
How did you know?
He came to Yidao today
and has signed the contract.
I thought about it
and I felt the need
to inform you.
When Mr. Liu came today,
he left
scathing remarks about your firm.
I see.
It's just a reminder.
It's not good to get on a client's bad side.
I know.
Thank you.
I'm eating with your sister.
Do you want to talk to her?
No, thanks.
This is not a convenient time.
We can have a chat when we meet.
Sure. See you.
All right. Bye.
Xingyun told me
that Mr. Liu's case would no longer
be handled by us.
And it's their firm
that took over.
What?
Why?
I don't know.
Apparently, Mr. Liu
wasn't very happy with the meeting.
I didn't notice.
He seemed very happy
when he left.
He even said he would bring more documents.
What a sly fox.
It's okay. It's all in the past now.
Forget it. Just eat.
Here.
This soup is good.
Why are you on the bed?
Don't you have a night shift?
You came back late.
I sent you a message
and said I'd be late.
Guan Tao treated me to a meal.
And then we went back
to do some paperwork.
He treated you to a meal?
Why?
Just to talk about some business.
You haven't had dinner yet, right?
Let me cook some noodles for you.
Get up now.
Why would Guan Tao treat you to a meal?
It's about a case.
A businessman wanted us
to handle a case
but then something happened
and everything went sour.
And he treated you to a meal for that?
Is he crazy?
You won't understand anyway.
Guan Tao just said
that thanks to me,
he avoided doing something wrong.
You're just
a janitor.
What did you do to help him
to deserve a free meal?
You...
What's wrong with me being a janitor?
Not only did I clean,
but I did a lot of other stuff too.
The three young lawyers there
don't have an assistant.
I helped them
with many things as well.
Don't you underestimate me.
I'm an important member of the firm now.
And maybe one day,
I'll become a receptionist.
And you'll be shocked.
You make yourself sound so capable.
You might think that you are important to them.
But they are probably thinking otherwise.
I don't care what people think of me.
I just have to do my duty.
I even wondered
when we could head back to the village.
Then I can ask around
and recommend our law firm
to those who need a lawyer.
You're even helping them
to look for more clients.
Will they pay you more?
You cannot think it that way.
If the firm declares bankruptcy,
I'll lose my job too.
I just think it's odd
that he treated you to a meal.
I'll invite you next time.
Then it won't be odd, right?
For this month,
the rent is 18,000 yuan.
The utility bill
is 4,200 yuan
in all.
The administrative expenditure
is 5,600...
I'll round it up to 5,700 yuan.
Xingfu's salary
is 1,500 yuan.
[Utility, Administrative Expenditure, Salary]
How much is it in total?
29,400 yuan.
We only had
a few small cases this month.
We'd be considered lucky
if we could earn 20,000 yuan.
See?
Another month in deficit.
The beginning is the toughest.
Oh,
after Mr. Liu
left,
he never came back.
I called him
and he never gave me a clear answer.
Did something happen?
His case
is now handled by Yidao.
We need to find a way
to look for new cases.
I never knew looking for clients
was this difficult.
Come in.
Mr. Guan.
Hi.
Madam,
this is Mr. Guan.
He represented my family
in the land dispute case.
Mr. Guan.
-Hi.
-Hi, I'm Guan Tao.
Please have a seat.
Okay.
Take a seat.
Please sit here.
Xingfu.
Serve some water.
I'm not thirsty.
Don't go.
Stay here.
I...
I'll sit here then.
Have you encountered any problems?
Are you really from Wan Village?
Well, I couldn't tell at all.
I'm just in my work uniform. That's all.
I just started
working here.
Madam,
can you tell us
more about your problem?
Mr. Guan is here.
You know, Shiqiao Village...
It's just
when I mention it,
I get overwhelmed.
Calm down.
There's no outsider here.
Just tell me.
We plant apples there.
A few years ago, thanks to good sales,
a company came
to sign a bought deal.
They offered 1.5 yuan for one jin of apples
and they wanted all our produce.
We thought
even though it was lower
than the market price,
it saves us the hassle
and the risk.
So everyone
in the village
converted their farmlands
into orchards.
Now that the apple trees have matured
and the apples are ripe,
everyone has their land decked
with heaps of apples.
Not long ago,
they told us
apples weren't in high demand anymore
so they decreased the price
to 1.2 yuan per jin.
We thought to ourselves
that there were just
too many apples to be sold by ourselves.
So we agreed to it.
But then
they never came.
We were so desperate
and we went to them.
Then they told us
that apples were unsalable now
so they would withdraw from the deal.
We were at our wit's end
so we turned
to our previous clients
but they wouldn't buy from us again.
They had already bought enough apples.
It's so unfair.
A year of hard work
is now rotting
at our home.
They violated the agreement.
Madam,
did you guys sign a contract?
Yes, we did.
Of course, we did.
But they refuse to acknowledge it.
Why is our life
so tough?
Right.
I sympathize with you.
But we have Mr. Guan here.
He'll help us.
I'm so worried.
One year of hard work
is rotting at home.
My baby still needs to be breastfed.
Due to my anxiety,
I stopped lactating.
Now that I cannot breastfeed my baby,
he cries every day.
It pains me to see it.
Wipe your tears, madam.
Why are they crying?
I know, right?
Why...
Why are they both crying?
You idiot.
This is Xingfu's strategy
to bond with the client.
A strategy, you say?
Maybe you can pull it off in front of me
next time.
Being with you here
and ranting to you
has made me feel better.
Actually, my family
was against my signing the contract
with the company.
But I insisted
that a sales and purchase agreement
with a large company like that
would be very reliable.
That's why I signed it.
Now that this has happened,
my family resents me.
I don't have a space to vent.
Do you think I can be helped?
Of course.
There must be a way.
You
came here
to look for a solution, didn't you?
Like
talking
to the lawyers?
Yes.
But I don't know anything.
That's precisely
why lawyers represent us
in a legal case.
Madam,
if you trust me,
you should trust Mr. Guan too.
He'll definitely help us.
All right.
If you say so,
I believe you.
But I don't have a lot of money.
Don't worry
about the money.
We can discuss it
once the case
is settled.
But now,
I want you to give me
the name of the company you signed
the contract with
and the content
of the agreement.
Here, madam.
See you.
Take care.
Xingfu.
I'm so glad
that I found you.
I'll let them
handle this case then.
We're from the same region.
Keep an eye on my case, will you?
Don't worry.
They
are very hardworking.
I'm sure they'll handle it very well
without any supervision.
All right.
I'll leave then.
If you ever head back,
do take a detour
and drop by my place.
Of course.
Please keep an eye on my case.
Have a safe trip.
Okay.
Bye.
Mr. Guan.
How much is this case worth?
Not a lot.
But it's okay.
It's not a lot
but it's for the greater good.
Can't...
Can't win an argument against you then.
But you save money
little by little.
I earn 1,500 yuan per month
and you don't see me complaining.
Talking about money again?
If you want a raise,
just tell me.
Xingfu.
Don't worry.
You just
found us
a huge case.
What?
Didn't you just say
it's a small case?
Her case alone
is a small one.
But what comes after
is a lot.
If we win this case,
more farmers will turn to us
for legal affairs.
Slowly but surely,
we'll get the money rolling.
Right.
Oh.
Be prepared.
You have a business trip
to Shiqiao Village in a few days.
What business trip?
It's just like
what I did with your sister last time.
We went to your hometown.
We'll go to Shiqiao Village
to understand
the difficulty they face.
What can I do there?
A lot.
Okay.
Then
did I make
a contribution?
Will I be allowed
to visit my child on my way back?
What do you say,
my friends?
I...
Stop pretending.
That's a yes.
Yes.
Qinglai.
You said Mr. Xu was your uncle
but he always
ignores you.
Are you sure?
Am I supposed to show you
how close we are?
My brother keeps pestering me.
Is the favor he asked for
feasible or not?
Of course.
Definitely.
The Provincial Bureau
asked our department
to do the report this time.
I had my secretary
send you the report materials yesterday.
Have you looked at it?
I have.
Actually,
you didn't need to go through me.
Just report
the facts.
Right.
But
this is a serious matter.
If I have the support from you, the mayor,
it'll be safer.
Uncle.
How is Mrs. Xu?
Lift the bar up.
Are you sure Mr. Xu is your uncle?
Apparently not.
Once you're an official,
you become too lofty for your relatives.
[Serve the People]
Who's that?
My rela...
Not even a relative.
A distant relative
from my hometown,
at most.
You gave him the job?
Back then,
several guards complained
about the low wage
and left.
We needed people
so I recommended him to them.
But of course,
the security department decides
if he's up for the job.
Be careful.
Don't make others think
it's nepotism.
Thanks for the reminder, Mr. Mayor.
I will take note of it.
Hey.
Qingzhi.
Tonight,
if you're free,
come visit.
I need to talk to you.
Dear.
You're back.
You're off-duty now?
I have left some dishes for you.
Eat them.
Why are you packing?
For a business trip.
What?
Business trip.
It means the company pays me
to travel to another place for work.
It's near our house
so I can visit Little Dou.
Look at you.
What can you do?
To help with a case, of course.
I helped the law firm
get a big case.
Guan Tao asked me to tag along.
Look how happy you are.
He could be trafficking you
and you would still be clueless about it.
I'm not worth a lot anyway.
Why would someone traffic me?
You're paid 1,500 yuan per month
and you have to handle cases too.
I think he's treating you like a slave.
You're being taken advantage of
and you happily comply.
Wang Qinglai.
Why are you so distrustful?
He thinks highly of me.
Also, what do I have?
What do I have to be taken advantage of?
They like to bully people from rural areas.
Other than those born in the city,
even those who came from the rural areas
turn into a different person
once they become rich
and powerful.
Who are you talking about?
Who else could it be?
Qingzhi's father-in-law.
He thinks he's all high and mighty.
He travels around
but he just ignores me.
I went to greet him
with a smile
but he didn't even look at me.
Isn't he just a director?
Back then, I thought he was someone important
in the county.
But now I know
that he's no one major in the city.
You're a security guard.
Why do you have to approach him?
I can't?
Because I'll bring disgrace
or shame?
In that case,
just fire me.
I...
I wanted to help
but now, it's a problem.
Sorry,
Mr. Xu.
If you think it's inappropriate
for him to work there,
I'll find another job
for him.
If you could,
I wouldn't have to help you.
I just need you
to tell him
that he and I
are two individuals.
We have no relation whatsoever.
All right?
I don't want any trouble.
Don't worry.
I'll make it clear to him.
I'm sure you know
my wife disapproves
of you
and Yani.
And I have been having your backs.
You know why?
Because I believe in you.
I know you'll be successful.
Yani will have a happy life with you.
If you let me down,
then it'll reflect badly on me
in front of my wife.
I understand, Mr. Xu.
I do.
Did the Organization Department
get in touch with you?
They assigned me
to be the secretary
for Deputy Mayor Xiang.
This is an important step
in your life.
Life is quite simple
when you look at it.
There are only
a few turning points
in life.
Pick the right turn
and you'll have a bright future.
Before you take up the post,
I have
a warning for you.
Mr. Sun
of the Provincial Bank
is under investigation.
Are you aware?
Yes.
Including his secretary
and his driver.
Secre...
That's why
secretary
is a risky job.
Do it well
and you might get promoted quickly.
It's a fast track.
But if you are not careful,
you lose
everything.
Deputy Mayor Xiang
is young and competent.
I personally have high hopes for him.
Working for a capable leader like him
is a blessing.
Be smart.
Don't worry, Mr. Xu.
I never do anything
illegal or inappropriate.
Maybe your life was broken
Maybe you were rendered silent
by disappointment
Even so, you need to move forward bravely
And live as you persevere
Who can stop you
From living your best life?
Maybe it has become even harder
to pursue your dream
Maybe it's not all smooth sailing
throughout your life
Even so, you need to move forward bravely
And learn to be stronger
Who can stop
Happiness from blooming?
Even if I will have my ups and downs
I will never back down
My crushed dreams are being reborn
How could you know the broadness of the land
Without climbing the tallest peaks
And diving into the dark abyss?
Don't admit defeat
Fight with all you got
Even if I will have my ups and downs
I will never back down
My crushed dreams are being reborn
How could you know the broadness of the land
Without climbing the tallest peaks
And diving into the dark abyss?
Don't admit defeat
Fight with all you got