♪ Inside the state a city is built ♪
♪ Where a benevolent emperor resides ♪
♪ Court officials are brave and able ♪
♪ The empress is fair ♪
♪ Princes died too young to ascend the throne ♪
♪ Princesses are spoiled and fragile ♪
♪ Commoners are also the emperor’s children ♪
♪ All are living peacefully ♪
♪ Wish I could live a day for myself ♪
♪ Follow my heart and ethics without distractions ♪
♪ To be a good husband ♪
♪ To be a caring father ♪
♪ We were close when we first met ♪
♪ I hope I can control my desires ♪
♪ To be a worriless emperor and father ♪
♪ Prudence tops all virtues ♪
♪ People build the state ♪
= Held in the Lonely Castle =
♪ May the world be peaceful ♪
= Episode 16 =
If Your Majesty agree,
I can take charge of the Institute.
I’ll discipline
all the girls strictly
and teach them rules and manners.
You've apologized
and I’ve watched the dance.
You should
discipline this girl after you go back.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Disciplining her
isn’t your responsibility.
You're the head of the harem
and shouldn’t do everything yourself.
It’s late. You may leave.
We still have other things to discuss.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Let’s go.
- Today... - Today.
You first, Danshu.
Your Majesty,
am I
too strict and rigid
when managing the harem?
That girl
was passionate and energetic.
Perhaps in your eyes,
members led by me in the harem
are as dull
as puppets.
Danshu.
I have no discontent with you.
Shortly after you took charge at 18,
you were respected
and supported by all.
I don’t manage the harem,
but I’m not ignorant.
Had you lacked lenience
or talents,
and only followed in others’ steps,
others wouldn’t have respected you.
To be honest,
I didn’t follow the rules when I was little.
I...
I know.
You were well-versed in riding and fencing
and you sneaked into the Nanjing Academy
to attend lectures.
Rules couldn’t restrict you.
Danshu.
I also understand
that in this palace...
Danshu!
Guards! Protect His Majesty!
Your Majesty, Your Highness,
as Your Highness requested,
I had men go to chambers and storages
where cotton silk, clothes,
books and paper are stored
to check.
A few places did catch fire.
Luckily, Your Highness was meticulous.
Guards and servants arrived in time
and put off the fire.
Other than the chambers,
check the Six Bureaus and
the Imperial Kitchen closely as well
and see if the furniture is moved
or the beams are loose.
Yes.
Treat the injured as soon as possible
if there’s any.
I’m on it.
Your Majesty, Your Highness,
in the two senior consorts’ places,
other than a few broken frames and porcelains,
nobody was hurt.
Their carriages have been moved
to the open ground
in front of the hall as you ordered.
They're resting inside.
I’ve also checked Princess, too.
Madam Miao and the babysitter
are outside the chamber with Princess.
She didn’t get startled
and was in warm clothes
and a cloak.
She was quite calm
and even smiled at me.
Like father, like daughter.
Your Highness,
if there are no other orders,
I’ll continue the inspection.
= Liu E =// Emperor Zhao Zhen.
Your Majesty,
your father has passed away.
Minister Ding, Minister Wang.
Yes.
Please write down
His Majesty’s edict
made orally.
Officer Lei.
Yes.
Once the edict is complete,
open the Inner East Gate
and let the royal members in.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Bureau of Calendar and Directorate of Astronomy
sent messages to the Cabinet.
= Chen Yaozuo, courtesy name Xiyuan =
The calculation shows
the epicenter
should be Jingdong West Province.
We had sent officials
to check all the provinces.
Once the calculation result was out,
officials were dispatched immediately
to the local transportation agency.
Once the situation is confirmed.
we’ll evaluate the disaster
and arrange the relief.
Check the river dikes
for damages.
If there is, repair it immediately.
The flood season is a few months away,
so no inspection has been conducted.
But heavy rains always follow the earthquake.
If river dikes are damaged
and collapse,
people will suffer more
than they already have.
Your Majesty is wise and considerate.
We're ashamed.
Disasters and the epidemic are frequent.
The earthquake struck Jingdong West Province.
And there’s the landslide
and the Yellow River flood.
Yet officials of both Ministries
are indecisive.
No useful decisions have been made.
People in those areas are homeless.
Relief supplies
haven’t arrived.
The homeless broke into neighboring counties
and the disease is spreading.
Zimei.
= Liang Huaiji =
Censor Han, Chief Fu, Scholar Su,
these are proposals from the past ten days
the Cabinet ordered
to be polished
before handed in to His Majesty.
Bring them in.
Are you new here?
I don’t recall seeing you before.
I came to the palace a few months ago.
After learning the rules
and passing the test,
I was assigned to the Imperial Academy.
What’s your name? How old are you?
My surname is Liang, Liang Huaiji.
I was born in 1027 A.D.
and I’m 11 years old.
I see.
Huaiji.
Come here.
It’s raining heavily.
We’re shorthanded.
Copy a few proposals for me.
Here you are.
Yes.
You can do it over there.
= Bao’an’s Report about Shanyu=
= Yan Shu, courtesy name Tongshu =
You’ve become more composed
and careful with words
when giving advice.
I’m almost 50 years old
and have served two emperors.
Right now, as the head of Censorate,
I’m responsible for monitoring all officials.
Your Majesty trusts me,
so whatever I say and do
are considered as standards,
as well as
references to Your Majesty’s preferences.
How could I not be careful?
The Dragon Ball Tea just arrived.
Before I invited you here,
I especially
asked Maoze to come from the Inner East Gate.
I remember when I lived in the Eastern Palace,
it was snowing outside.
You watched me practicing my handwriting
and told me where I should improve
while teaching Maoze
how to pick the coal, boil water and make tea.
I thought
out there at court,
you were Deputy Censor Yan
and behind these curtains,
you’d always be my teacher
and be completely honest
with me.
You’d never tiptoe around me.
I choose my words carefully
because
I am in awe
of Your Majesty day by day.
I've never punished anyone
because of wrong advice,
not to mention you.
What do you fear?
Fear comes from respect.
Your Majesty
has become an excellent emperor
and can make your own decisions.
You’re no longer
a child who needs my protection
and guidance.
If I treated you as before,
that would be disrespectful
and redundant.
You're right.
When I was six,
you taught me The Book of Rites.
Of course you couldn’t act against it.
Alright. Enough of the past.
Let’s talk business.
Please have some tea.
Zhao Yuanhao’s uncle Shanyu
brought his family, treasures and horses
to Bao’an for asylum.
He claimed that Yuanhao would revolt
and promised
that he’d work with his old allies against him.
Bao’an didn’t accept him
and sent him back.
Yet, Yuanhao ambushed
and killed him on the way.
What do you think?
Yuanhao will soon
rebel against us.
All provinces
should be well-prepared.
Send spies to collect information
and strengthen the security at the border
in case of attacks.
All departments should discuss
the response
if Yuanhao proclaims himself emperor.
You saw
the date on the report.
After the report
arrived at the Ministries,
it was buried
with other unimportant files
for over a month.
When it was about to be discussed,
the earthquake happened,
so it was delayed till a few days ago
that Wang Sui
and Chen Yaozuo finally processed it.
You saw
what they wrote.
Ministries are unable
to come up with relief strategies
or military tactics
to cope with the emergency in the west.
After Song Qi
and Su Shunqin expressed their complaints,
Wang Sui claimed to be ill.
Medicine is boiled in the Cabinet every day.
The cabinet
has become
a home for the old and sick
where their students can visit.
Internally, the administration
failed to provide disaster relief.
It’s even worse externally.
Zhao Shanyu killed by Yuanhao
is a huge matter,
yet the Ministries only said
that since Yuanhao’s father Deming
surrendered,
others seeking asylum due to internal strife
have all been rejected.
Bao’an only followed the precedent.
Yuanhao killed Shanyu at the Sheyi Slope.
That’s all.
No other arrangements were made.
They’re shortsighted.
You know both Minister Wang and Minister Chen
believe that Yuanhao’s father Deming
surrendered himself sincerely,
stating that Zhao Deming was clement
and unwarlike
who was completely different
from his father Jiqian.
Also,
they said Deming
was cultivated by our rules and ethics
and became all virtuous.
Zimei,
you...
The Jingdong West Province earthquake
was actually
handled according to the rules.
The Cabinet followed the precedents.
There was no delay on purpose
or embezzlement.
Dilatoriness and inadequacy
reveal the lack of decisiveness.
Besides...
Besides,
Ministers Chen and Wang are inexperienced
and not thorough enough.
Officials didn’t follow their relief plans.
The result isn’t unexpected.
The one who’s thorough
and supported by all officials
was accused
of arbitrary
and nepotism by censors
for years
and just left the Capital due to his demotion.
Now, Wang Sui and Chen Yaozuo are incapable.
Wang Zeng and Lv Yijian are old
and have left the Capital.
Fan Zhongyan, although supported by scholars,
doesn’t fit to be Prime Minister.
If I may,
could Your Majesty write something for me?
What is it?
More is as bad as little.
Since Wang Sui was appointed,
he’s shown no talent
at court
but is known for his addiction
to religion and witchcraft.
How ridiculous!
When the state was struck by the disaster,
and His Majesty needed advice,
rather than contributing to it,
he claimed to be ill to avoid court appearances,
rested in the Cabinet
and promoted his friends and family.
Zhigui, that's sharp!
With such officials,
won’t His Majesty fear
that others will follow suit?
If our neighbors hear this,
they’ll look down on our state.
It’s all true,
but,
if Prime Minister is deposed,
who can take that position?
In this time
of internal and external crises,
officials qualified for that post...
are no other but one.
My...my father-in-law?
Deputy Censor Yan is the best fit
and he’ll lead the Ministries sooner or later.
He’s also on the top of His Majesty’s list.
But given the current situation,
the timing is still not perfect.
“I understand why the rules aren’t clear.
The wise know too much, yet the unwise too little”.
“I understand why the rules aren’t followed.
The able are above them; yet the unable below”.
Confucius is right.
Some have too much; the others too little.
Fan Zhongyan is selfless
but inflexible
yet Xia Song isn’t selfless enough.
Lv Yijian is wise
and sophisticated
but manipulative.
Chen Yaozuo isn’t his match.
In other word,
Lv Yijian is a successful
and decisive politician.
Xia Song is good with people.
Fan Zhongyan is righteous
and completely loyal.
Not to mention
Han Qi’s insight,
Fu Bi’s thoroughness,
Su Shunqin, Ouyang Xiu
and Cai Xiang’s talents.
The court is full of talents.
All I see is hope.
That does
make sense.
Officials have their strengthens
and weaknesses.
They can be too much or too little,
But appointing officials
according to the situation,
and even having them complement each other
are up to Your Majesty.
Lv Yijian?
We gave it our all
to finally have him...
Zimei,
why did we try so hard
to impeach him?
He sided with allies to act against his enemies.
And he abused his power
to win officials over to control the court
and establish his authority.
As for how he dealt with allies and enemies,
if allies are those who are like-minded
and enemies the opposite,
whoever becomes Prime Minister
will do the same.
When Minister Lv was in charge,
what worried us most was
that he controlled the court
and outshone His Majesty.
Yet a decree of demotion
made him leave the Cabinet
and the Capital.
That proves he wasn’t that powerful.
Back then,
he survived the impeachment only because
His Majesty didn’t want to dismiss him
not because he dared not
or he couldn’t.
What’s with the rush?
It’s still early. Lie down with me.
My wife
wouldn’t find this place.
You’re afraid of her
but I’m not.
That girl Bihan
needs to be watched closely.
She is clearly in love
and she’s bold.
I don’t want her
to cause me trouble.
He’s seen all kinds of people
and been through all sorts of things.
What can't he get?
But true love is rare.
If not for that,
however beautiful she is,
she’d be ignored.
This pendant is cheap.
I couldn’t afford a better one before,
but I gave you expensive ones afterward.
You’re too careful.
You fear others will notice anything?
= Xia Song, courtesy name Ziqiao =
People all say Empress is tender.
= Jia Yulan =
I don’t think
she’s as soft as she seems.
Bihan
is so childish.
She only met him once years back,
but she was eager to find him.
And now,
she’s obsessed with love
and is clueless about other things.
Obsession is what matters.
In terms of talents and wisdom,
other than the late Empress Dowager,
no one is better than Cao Danshu.
All members of the harem,
concubines
and servants included,
all listen to her.
Other than that,
the late Empress Dowager
didn’t have a decorated grandfather,
an uncle with the title Wumu
or a teacher
who’s considered a spiritual leader.
Do you mean
that stubborn girl
has no chance at all?
In this world,
wisdom is most useless
in love and relationships.
Who can read His Majesty’s mind?
Lv and Fan are enemies for years.
Fan seems to be on the moral high ground,
but he’s promoted and demoted three times.
Lv seems to be invincible
but who’d know
he’d be embarrassed
by a waiter.
Fate is fickle.
No one can predict the future.
We’re only helping
your adopted daughter
to realize her dream.
Thank you for your kindness.
I'm leaving.
If you need help,
Yang Huaimin can be trusted.
The rain is annoying.
I feel cold.
I have an appointment with Wen Yanbo
and the landlady of the Restaurant of Breeze
to discuss business.
We can
have some warm liquor
to warm the body.
This boy
must’ve practiced calligraphy.
Few at this age
have his calmness.
His family must’ve collapsed or be punished
that he ended up here.
What a shame!
Censor Han, I’ve finished.
Your handwriting is good.
You’re focused
and I like your personality.
I’ll tell Officer Ren tomorrow
to transfer you to the Imperial Study
to handle the paperwork.
It’s not heavy labor,
but you need to read more books,
so you won’t be free.
Do you want to come?
I’ll listen to Officer Ren.
♪ Have no mood to color the eyebrows ♪
♪ Pack up the clothes for your trip ♪
♪ Dare not make you sad ♪
♪ Struggle to hold tears back ♪
♪ Have no mood to color the eyebrows ♪
♪ Pack up the clothes for your trip ♪
♪ Dare not make you sad ♪
♪ Struggle to hold tears back ♪
♪ So that I wouldn’t know when you leave ♪
Years back,
when first hearing this poem about separation,
I was overwhelmed.
“I’d rather get myself drunk first
so that I wouldn’t know when you leave”.
One would rather be drunk
when parting with
the loved one.
All to fool the broken heart.
How sentimental!
Those feelings of separation
are penetrating.
Xia Song is talented.
Most of his early poems
are masterpieces,
= Wen Yanbo, courtesy name Kuanfu =
especially those about separations.
They’re quite touching.
Sadly,
when I met him in person
at court,
I only saw a shameless,
greedy and lascivious chunk.
No one is better than Su
who’s as graceful as his work.
When I first met you over a decade ago,
I still wasn’t in charge
and you were only a commoner.
You talked freely with me.
Farming supports the state; business enriches it.
If comparing farming, mine and machines
to rich lakes and mountains,
business will be the channel
that links those places together.
Then fish in one lake can eat grass in another.
Trees of this mountain
can be planted at other places.
That way, all beings will prosper.
I’m ashamed.
I was too young and naive before.
What about now?
I still believe
no business, no convergence,
hence no prosperity.
About your ambition,
your thoughts and plans,
I understand them
and I have eyes and my own judgment.
The core
of the traditional laws
emphasizes the national and public interests.
If that can be achieved,
what kind of trees should be planted,
whether business should be supported or not
can be decided accordingly.
All that can benefit the state and the people
fit traditional laws.
I’m honored to serve you, Your Majesty.
But only with
the right time
and people
can the laws be made properly.
Success requires unity.
What I’ve learned most
over the past 16 years of ruling
is to be patient.
You're intelligent and talented.
You're more capable
than most people.
If you can have more patience,
I’ll have one more pillar at court.
Zhigui,
three days ago,
your proposal criticizing ministers
was submitted.
His Majesty said yesterday to discuss it today.
So this is it.
Criticizing four ministers in your proposal,
you’re bolder than Fan Xiwen.
I wonder what will happen
later at court.
As long as His Majesty
won’t throw me out and imprison me,
I won’t kill myself to send a message.
I simply expressed my views.
It’s up to His Majesty to decide.
I admire your calmness most.
I’m faking it.
I’m unlikely to be imprisoned
but a demotion is possible.
If that’s the case,
remember to see me off with liquor.
I’m speechless.
Miss,
let me call an Imperial Physician.
I simply caught a cold.
After the earthquake and heavy rains,
I was too worried to sleep well.
I already prescribed
myself medicine
and took it with the meal.
I’ll be fine in a few days.
You know my condition.
Thanks to my martial arts practice, I’m strong.
There’s no need to call the physician.
You're strong
yet already became sick.
His Majesty...
You have your job
and mine is to manage the harem.
There’s nothing to complain about.
I only take care of the harem
but His Majesty is much busier.
He probably hasn’t had enough sleep lately.
Indeed.
Over the past few days,
he’s been reading reports till midnight
and got up at 2 a.m.
Although he didn’t come here,
no other women has he met.
And he had no time
for that dancer, either.
Who taught you to gossip around
behind others’ backs?
Was it Liaozi?
Or you taught him?
I...
I just noticed
that His Majesty didn’t come
even when you fell ill,
so I...
I...
First,
stop calling me the way you did
when we were at home.
Call me by the title
as others do in the palace.
In front of you is the Empress of Song,
not Miss Cao anymore.
Second, reflect on yourself.
Don’t go outside
or serve me.
Don’t do anything
except for copying the chapter Learning Rites
in Principles for Women.
Yes.
Censor Han.
Your report
criticized four ministers’ nonfeasance.
That’s unprecedented.
In the end,
they either resigned or were demoted.
One report dismissed four ministers.
That will be remembered by history.
I have no personal grudges against them
and I’m only doing the job
that I’m paid for.
I simply expressed my views.
Only His Majesty has the right to decide.
A few days ago, I found broken bamboo slips
with some characters.
I looked into ancient records
and racked my brain
but failed to recognize them.
Censor Han. Censor Han.
I thought today’s court discussion
would be
fierce and filled with hostility.
It would take at least a few hours.
We wouldn’t be able to leave before sunset.
Yet the four ministers were deposed yesterday
and today’s morning court got canceled.
Today’s discussion
was only to tell the officials
to learn from their lessons
and to discuss detailed rules and regulations
about internal and external affairs.
Minister Wang and Minister Chen are old
without serious mistakes.
They’re only unqualified for being ministers.
His Majesty wouldn’t allow them
to be humiliated
in public.
Gentlemen can rise above their disagreements.
Arguing in public is impolite.
Words can be hurtful.
If that becomes a routine,
manners will be lost.
His Majesty doesn’t want to see that happen.
= Chen Mansion =
Is there a decree for me?
Only a message.
His Majesty says
you have always been righteous
and fearless.
As the local governor,
you were excellent in managing the water.
= Chen Yaozuo, courtesy name Xiyuan =
You stopped the Qiantang tide and the Yellow River flood,
built dikes and planted willows to prevent floods,
which benefited countless people.
Your merits can’t be ignored
and you’re definitely not incapable.
Although you didn’t fit to be a minister,
when Lv and Wang left
and the Cabinet was leaderless,
you filled in at your old age
and worked tirelessly.
Censor Han’s report
was only about the current situation.
It was nothing personal.
Please don’t take it to heart.
I failed in my duty
and should be demoted,
yet His Majesty sent you
to comfort me.
He’s too kind.
I could only
do my utmost to serve the people
in Zhengzhou to repay his kindness.
♪ Loved you a gentleman yet got abandoned ♪
♪ Peach blossoms color the city ♪
♪ Spring breeze purified dusty memories ♪
♪ The gate of the vast palace opens ♪
♪ Bid farewell with wine after the glory ends ♪
♪ Outside the city a beautiful world unveils ♪
♪ Long-standing distance doesn’t alienate us ♪
♪ Keep you company behind the gate ♪
♪ Four seasons come and go ♪
♪ We only have each other in this cage ♪
♪ Wish to fly freely in the next life ♪
♪ Willows turn green flowers red ♪
♪ Sing aloud with wine ♪
♪ Hold your hands and go home together ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Life is long yet joy is little ♪