♪ Inside the state a city is built ♪
♪ Where a benevolent emperor resides ♪
♪ Court officials are brave and able ♪
♪ The empress is fair ♪
♪ Princes died too young to ascend the throne ♪
♪ Princesses are spoiled and fragile ♪
♪ Commoners are also the emperor’s children ♪
♪ All are living peacefully ♪
♪ Wish I could live a day for myself ♪
♪ Follow my heart and ethics without distractions ♪
♪ To be a good husband ♪
♪ To be a caring father ♪
♪ We were close when we first met ♪
♪ I hope I can control my desires ♪
♪ To be a worriless emperor and father ♪
♪ Prudence tops all virtues ♪
♪ People build the state ♪
= Held in the Lonely Castle =
♪ May the world be peaceful ♪
= Episode 42 =
Scholar Ouyang
is brazenly partisan in court.
I’m friends with Prime Minister Yan, Han Qi,
Fan Zhongyan, Fu Bi
and I detest Prime Minister Jia and Chief Xia.
That’s no secret.
I have nothing to hide.
But
gentlemen are bonded by the belief their share
while the corrupted gather together for profits.
That’s all.
Scholar Ouyang, you regard yourself
as a selfless gentleman.
But you’re defending
and going around, crying for help
for Fu Bi and Fan Zhongyan
so that they could be reinstated
in their key posts.
Isn’t that
for your friends’ interests?
Power and interests
are indeed inseparable.
The corrupted covet power
for their own interests.
You...
Gentlemen, once in power,
will work for the well-being of the public.
I support Fan Zhongyan and Fu Bi
and loathe the greedy and corrupted
not for my own interests
but for the law and order of the state
and public interest.
I demanded a conversation with Your Majesty earlier
not for any selfish purpose.
Fan Zhongyan, Fu Bi and Han Qi
are bosom friends
but they don’t always share the same
political views.
Zhongyan was once certain
that the Khitans would invade Hedong,
and asked to strengthen the border.
Fu Bi firmly believed
there would be no such invasions.
Besides, Yin Zhu
and Zhongyan are the closest.
In terms of building Shuiluo City,
Han Qi supported Yin Zhu instead of Liu Hu
while Zhongyan was the opposite.
The three of them
are what History of the Han Dynasty called
loyal officials with disagreements.
The wicked claim that’s cliquism.
It’s a false accusation.
Your Majesty should
be close to the loyal and away from the corrupted.
Recall Fan Zhongyan and Fu Bi to the Capital
and reinstate them
to continue the reform.
Investigate Shi Jie’s case thoroughly.
Punish the rumormonger
and clear Shi Jie’s name.
I appreciate that Your Majesty
allowed the court debate.
Please double the punishment
for my rudeness.
Your Majesty, I have a question.
What if
a self-proclaimed gentleman
lacks virtues?
Gentlemen should be virtuous.
I was told
that Scholar Ouyang’s niece, Mrs. Zhang,
who grew up with him, fornicated with a servant.
Kaifeng Municipal Government
heard her case last month.
Chief Xia...
After Mrs. Zhang
admitted to her shameless deed,
Scholar Ouyang
bribed officials in secret
to reduce her sentence
and convinced her husband to drop the lawsuit.
Isn’t it appropriate
to discuss a woman’s fidelity
in court?
It would be if the case
was only about her adultery with a servant.
But there’s more.
Yesterday, during the second hearing,
she confessed
that before she got married,
she had been in love with Scholar Ouyang
and intimate with him.
That’s why
she and her husband couldn’t get along well.
And Scholar Ouyang
tricked her into giving her late parents’ estate
to him.
Is that enough to be judged in court?
Your Majesty,
after my niece
lost her father at seven,
she and her mother came to live with me.
I raised her myself
and regarded her as my own daughter.
She and her husband did have problems.
I scolded her, talked to her
and tried to help them make peace.
I was worried about her
but...but my hands were tied.
I didn’t know until last month
that...
she...
she was arrested
for adultery.
I knew she was guilty
but she’s one of my family members
after all.
So I did pull strings
to not let her suffer in prison
and convince her husband to withdraw the lawsuit.
Later,
the Kaifeng Municipal Government
didn’t dismiss the case
but decided to hear her case again.
I assumed the judge
still had doubts
so I didn’t oppose.
As for
her latest confession Chief Xia just said,
I had no prior knowledge.
About the incestuous adultery
between you two
and your encroachment of her property,
what do you have to say?
Your Majesty,
as I just said,
I treated her
as my own daughter.
Judiciary authorities
can follow the legal procedure and investigate me.
Frame-up!
This is a purely malicious frame-up!
Ouyang Xiu is a loyal patriot.
He’s honest when giving advice, making himself
= Cai Xiang, courtesy name Junmo =
a long-standing eyesore to the corrupted,
Your Majesty!
Is he innocent?
= Wang Zhi, courtesy name Zhizhi =
If Ouyang Xiu is as decent as he said,
how come he’s a regular at brothels
and he’s written so many obscene poems?
Wherever he governed,
he was close
to the top harlot there.
Whether the incest is true or not,
Ouyang Xiu’s Dreaming of the South
has become the most popular song
in every restaurant in town.
The affair between the leading Scholar Ouyang
and his young niece
is most favored
by storytellers.
Everyone knows that.
Chief Xia,
= Sun Fu, courtesy name Zhihan =
how could you
trump up charges in front of His Majesty
when you weren’t sure about the truth?
Censor Sun, do you have evidence
to prove
that Mrs. Zhang framed him?
About the incest,
their confessions were the opposite.
How could he prove his innocence?
A court official
is unable to prove himself innocent.
And he did bribe prison guards for his niece
and convince her husband to drop the lawsuit.
In the eyes of the public,
he’s already ruined the court’s reputation
and violated the law and order.
Prime Minister Yan, Prime Minister Yan.
Prime Minister Yan.
Yongshu failed the exam twice
but topped the list
when you were in charge of the provincial exam.
I’m sure you value his talent and ambition.
And he also regards you as his teacher.
Right now, he’s in trouble.
How could you not help him?
Prime Minister Yan,
Xia Song is evil
and always against loyal officials.
He’s most likely the mastermind
behind Yongshu’s frame-up.
And Jia Changchao,
that coward...
So far, the incest case is still
under investigation.
Further argument
is meaningless.
Meaningless...
After ten days
of interrogation,
the defendant Ouyang Xiu
insists that he didn’t do it.
Mrs. Zhang’s confessions weren’t consistent
or clear.
Some details were contradictory.
In the end, she just cried.
Based on the evidence and confessions,
we can’t find him guilty of incest.
But in court,
officials no longer care about the result.
Both sides are condemning each other.
They all believe they’re righteous.
This complicated ethical issue
enables them to attack each other
from where they stand.
No conviction
or clarification.
The result of the case
won’t pacify either side.
The end must be drawn here, or chaos will arise,
leading to another round of power struggle.
I suggest Ouyang Xiu
should work outside the Capital for a while.
Aren’t you going to speak for him?
The case is closed.
The evidence and confessions have been submitted.
During the past days of argument,
Your Majesty,
you have heard everything they have to say.
I have nothing to add.
There’s something that hasn’t been announced.
My uncle, the Eighth Prince, passed away.
His funeral will be held
in a few days.
On his deathbed,
he called you sophisticated,
disloyal and dishonest.
After the funeral,
his last proposal will be exposed.
Then the whole court
will know
his reprimand of you.
I suggest
Ouyang Xiu should work outside the Capital
for a while.
= Duke Jing’s Mansion =
Prime Minister Yan mourned deeply,
but it’s no secret
that the Eighth Prince always hated him.
He knew who His Majesty’s biological mother was
but he and Lv Yijian kept the secret.
Before the Eighth Prince passed away,
his dying wish was to have His Majesty
dismiss that liar.
I used to admire his talent
and respect him
for promoting Fan Xiwen,
Ouyang Yongshu,
Fu Bi
and other talented, honest and loyal officials.
Who’d know
he’s spineless!
They seemed to have left the Capital
for disaster relief or border inspection
but actually, they were kicked out of the court
and suspended from their previous posts
to halt the reform.
As the Prime Minister,
he didn’t say anything in order to protect himself.
Other than that,
you know he proposed
that Ouyang Xiu should be transferred
out of the Capital?
Yongshu remonstrated with His Majesty
about overly promoting
Empress Dowager Zhangyi’s family.
So, to pander to His Majesty,
he stepped on Yongshu.
If we don’t take any action,
won’t we be the same as him?
Since Ouyang Xiu left the Capital,
disagreements and criticisms
have been flooding in.
Sun Fu’s and Cai Xiang’s are extremely sharp.
They condemned Xia Song, me
and called Mr. Yan evil.
They praised the Eighth Prince
for telling the truth before death.
Loyalty and honesty are really...
Never mind.
Once Zuixinglai’s death is made public,
they’ll no longer focus on Ouyang Xiu.
The fight among officials will stop
and they’ll unitedly advise me
to adopt sons again.
Your Majesty...
That’s understandable.
But
I don’t want Mr. Yan
to join them to persuade me.
He was the one
telling me not to meet with my birth mother.
When I meant to go to the battlefield,
he accused me of being heirless.
Yan Shu is sophisticated.
Is he?
Who died?
Who is this grand funeral for?
The Eighth Prince.
When he was in critical condition,
His Majesty had him treated
in the palace.
Of course his funeral is grand.
Cai Xiang’s proposal.
Sun Fu’s proposal.
This...
Do you remember this, Mr. Yan?
Lofty are the Five Mountains.
Jade is from Mount Kunlun.
Vast are the Four Waters.
Gold is found in River Li.
I wrote this eulogy
for Empress Dowager Zhangyi.
This eulogy
is beautifully written with profound meanings.
It praises the two Empress Dowagers
without revealing my background.
Your analogies are excellent.
But one thing
is missing.
That is honesty.
I knew who Your Majesty’s biological mother is
but I didn’t say anything.
I’m disloyal
by deceiving Your Majesty.
Why didn’t you defend yourself?
I’m not a blunt person.
Had it been Fan Zhongyan or Ouyang Xiu,
they wouldn’t have written like this.
But I chose you.
Back then...
Back then,
I wasn’t ignorant.
They didn’t know the whole truth
and assumed you lied to me.
I didn’t know the truth
until the Empress Dowager passed away.
But I know you well.
Had you been disloyal, why
would you have acted against the Empress Dowager
when I was young?
Why would you have pointed out that I had no son
to stop me from joining the battle
at the risk of infuriating me?
Mr. Yan, you should leave the Capital
to govern Yingzhou as the Minister of Works.
Thank you for Your Majesty’s generosity.
Is that sarcasm?
I understand
you are protecting me, Your Majesty.
Yingzhou is wealthy.
Schools there, state-run or private-run,
aren’t as good as those in Shangqiu or Kaifeng.
The excesses are reduced slowly
but educating the public can continue.
It’ll benefit generations to come.
Ouyang Xiu might not understand
your intention to get him
out of the Capital
but you always understand me well.
Actually,
there’s one more thing.
My son,
no, the heir of Song,
your future emperor...
He...
left us.
Prime Minister Yan.
What happened today
is unfair to you, Prime Minister Yan.
How could they rake up the past
and use it against you now?
Obviously,
they intended to harm you.
That eulogy was written 11 years ago.
Nobody said anything then,
but now,
it’s regarded as the proof of your disloyalty.
Unbelievable!
It’s the pretext
for taking revenge for their clique.
They were disgruntled
at Fu Bi’s and Ouyang Xiu’s demotion
but they had nothing on you.
So they dug up
the eulogy for the Empress Dowager to attack you.
Shame on them!
His Majesty
trusted Fu Bi and assigned him
to relieve the people in disaster.
That shows His Majesty’s kindness.
I suggested Ouyang Xiu
should be transferred to Hedong
to assist Fu Bi
in accordance with
His Majesty’s benevolence.
How is that a demotion
or revenge?
My own kitchen made this congee
with five kinds of grains,
wolfberries from Tibet
and osmanthus sugar.
When I was little and fell ill,
my mother would make this for me.
She said it could nourish my body.
Have a taste, Your Majesty.
Very good.
I’ll tell Lusi to copy the recipe
and bring it to your chamber.
No need.
Others can’t cook it well.
I’ll come here
to eat this.
From now on,
I’ll have breakfast with you every other day.
Your Majesty, you are too busy.
Don’t worry about me.
Really?
I hope we can
have breakfast together more often.
Father, you know,
mother always cooked for me and...
Let me bring you
the plums I made.
I’ll come here more.
I’ll spend more time with you.
To me,
this place feels like home the most.
Here
I can have fun without worries.
But I need to take care of
all sorts of problems and troubles first.
Only when I couldn’t continue
would I allow myself to come here to rest.
I never thought
my sweet home
would be shattered
beyond repair.
I’ve failed
to spend enough quality time
with the three of you
and I won’t do it again
to you two
to leave more regrets.
Mr. Han.
Prime Minister Yan,
you’re only bringing Jidao to Yingzhou?
He’s too naughty.
Without me at home,
he can lie to his grandmother and mother
as he pleases
and drives his teacher away,
so I have to bring him with me
to teach him myself.
Board the boat with Uncle An first.
Yes.
= Yan Jidao =
He must be talented
in your eyes,
so you don’t trust others to teach him
other than yourself.
I do favor him more
not because he can achieve something big.
He doesn’t like reading
educational books
but prefers art, especially music.
He can think outside the box
and surprise me with his words occasionally.
Now, I realize
there’s nothing more important
than seeing him enjoying
a happy and carefree life.
If your mother and wife
need any help in the Capital, they...
We’ll leave first.
They’ll sell the house in the Capital
and pack up.
My second and third sons will escort
their grandmother, mother and younger sister
back to our hometown Fuzhou in Jiangxi Province.
Sell the house?
Why?
Your other two sons are working in the Capital.
His Majesty trusts Fu Bi.
I’m different from them.
I won’t come back here.
You should reconsider it.
His Majesty
removed you from the Prime Minister
due to a decade-old incident.
Cai and Sun
used that against you
only to vent their anger.
Even they couldn’t believe
His Majesty accepted their advice.
His Majesty’s intention is unclear
but all these years,
he clearly trusts and depends on you
the most.
His Majesty has no one to depend on.
All emperors in history
are loners.
That applies to us, too.
Speaking of that,
what supports His Majesty, you, me
and everyone here
is nothing but a stable
and peaceful nation.
Your Highness, what did Imperial Physicians say?
They said Madam Feng will give birth
in a few days.
The position of the fetus is good.
Madam Feng is healthy, too.
If it goes smoothly,
she and the baby should be fine.
What’s wrong?
I meant
if they took your pulse.
Me?
They already took it last time.
I’m fine.
I called them
to know about Madam Feng’s condition
and the Eighth Princess’s.
She’s been weak since she was born.
Lately, her condition’s worsened.
Physicians hummed and hawed.
Madam Zhang is having monks
chanting the sutra every day.
I hope she will be fine.
Why are you only caring about others?
You seem fine
but still cough at night.
You should be checked by physicians again
to be relieved.
Only if Madam Feng gives birth to a son
will I truly be relieved.
His Majesty’s only son died.
Once news gets out,
proposals will soon roll in,
persuading him to adopt sons.
He lost his only son,
but those officials
are only concerned that the state is heirless.
He can’t even mourn
his son’s death.
And the Eighth Princess...
By downsizing officials,
combating corruption and promoting the reform,
achievements have been made
but there are threats under the water.
Opponents are still many.
In the palace,
the only prince
and three princesses died in a row.
Other than
those vicious speculations,
I can’t image how heartbroken
His Majesty is.
His Majesty accused Your Highness
of only caring about the state
and your responsibility as the Empress.
Actually,
you act like that because you know
His Majesty and the state
are a whole.
Your Highness’s heart is filled with His Majesty,
meaning the state
also fills your heart.
Prime Minister Yan,
I’m overwhelmed.
I don’t know what to do next.
Among officials leading the reform,
only you
are still in the Cabinet.
The three excesses have been lessened.
Those suffering huge losses are pushing back.
To restore the balance,
His Majesty will slower or suspend the reform
to make necessary adjustments.
I understand that.
I’m not clinging on to the reform
but right now, His Majesty
is surrounded by officials
like Jia Changchao and Xia Song.
The loyal are replaced by the corrupted.
Losses of the wild Ouyang Yongshu
and the blunt Fan Xiwen
aren’t too big,
but Prime Minister Yan,
you always put the greater good first
to ensure the balance.
Yet His Majesty...
Jidao,
behave yourself!
Don’t fall into the water.
I’m going to learn swimming in Yingzhou.
Both His Majesty and the masses
are longing for a stable
and peaceful nation.
His Majesty
allows loyal officials
to act against his will
for that purpose.
He tolerates the mediocre and the corrupted
yapping before him
also for that purpose.
Zhigui,
I chose to serve the court
not to be remembered by history.
All my previous dissuasion
was part of my job.
I’m old.
After so many years of service,
I can live with a clear conscience.
♪ Life will end eventually ♪
♪ Every separation is sorrowful ♪
Mr. Yan, are you teaching me plum blossom poems?
You once told me
lotus and plum blossoms are kings of flowers.
They top others with their elegance.
Lotus after the rain and plum blossoms
in the snow are the best.
Good verses are inspired by nature.
We aren’t going to study them today.
Let’s enjoy their fragrance in the snow.
We can pick some flowers
and collect snow on the petals.
Tell the kitchen to make tea with the snow
and bake pastries stuffed with flowers.
Pastries stuffed with flowers?
♪ Grieve over falling flowers and short spring ♪
♪ Better treasure the ones you still have instead ♪
What about my mother,
the one who carried me for ten months
but I didn’t get
to bow to once?
Mr. Yan.
You’re back, Mr. Yan.
= Yan Shu passed away in 1055 A.D. =
= Court adjourned for two days =
= His stone tablet
is headed by “Former Imperial Tutor” =
Mr. Zhang.
What brings you here today?
Please go upstairs.
I’m out to run an errand
and need to bring food and desserts
back to the palace.
How’s your business?
With the help
of those 3,000 taels from the court
to buy the restaurant,
and thanks to the stability these years,
I’ve finally paid off the tax
the previous owner owed.
Your room is on the second floor.
It’s the best place to overlook the entire city
and enjoy songs and dances inside.
You can give me dividends
for my investment.
I seldom come here.
No need
to empty a room for me.
You’ll lose money.
Guests here all know
you have a room here,
so no one dares
to cause me trouble.
You’re using me as a shield.
This way, please.
Mr. Zhang.
Are you alright?
= Bitao =
Mr. Zhang,
she can’t speak.
My adopted mother brought her back from the market.
When my adopted mother saw her,
she was sick and hungry
and was beaten by a waiter for stealing buns.
My adopted mother pitied her and brought her back.
She’s hardworking
but timid.
She’s afraid of strangers.
You can leave.
Take the order to the kitchen
and tell them to prepare the food quickly.
Ask Deshun to bring
fresh fruit and liquor, too.
When did she
come here?
♪ Loved you a gentleman yet got abandoned ♪
♪ Peach blossoms color the city ♪
♪ Spring breeze purified dusty memories ♪
♪ The gate of the vast palace opens ♪
♪ Bid farewell with wine after the glory ends ♪
♪ Outside the city a beautiful world unveils ♪
♪ Long-standing distance doesn’t alienate us ♪
♪ Keep you company behind the gate ♪
♪ Four seasons come and go ♪
♪ We only have each other in this cage ♪
♪ Wish to fly freely in the next life ♪
♪ Willows turn green flowers red ♪
♪ Sing aloud with wine ♪
♪ Hold your hands and go home together ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Life is long yet joy is little ♪