♪ Inside the state a city is built ♪
♪ Where a benevolent emperor resides ♪
♪ Court officials are brave and able ♪
♪ The empress is fair ♪
♪ Princes died too young to ascend the throne ♪
♪ Princesses are spoiled and fragile ♪
♪ Commoners are also the emperor’s children ♪
♪ All are living peacefully ♪
♪ Wish I could live a day for myself ♪
♪ Follow my heart and ethics without distractions ♪
♪ To be a good husband ♪
♪ To be a caring father ♪
♪ We were close when we first met ♪
♪ I hope I can control my desires ♪
♪ To be a worriless emperor and father ♪
♪ Prudence tops all virtues ♪
♪ People build the state ♪
= Held in the Lonely Castle =
♪ May the world be peaceful ♪
= Episode 25 =
I knew it.
Someone is cursing Chuyue.
No wonder she has been suffering.
Who has such an evil mind!
Find it out!
Find who went to the lakeside of the backyard
these days!
If you can’t find it out, I’ll tell His Majesty
all of you cursed Chuyue together.
Yes, madam.
Aunt.
I have checked
with the eunuchs in charge.
Servants who passed the lake
these days
are all here.
Take a close look at each other,
see if you can identify
the one who put the curse doll
under the stone.
If no one’s identified,
all of you are suspicious.
Madam Zhang will tell His Majesty immediately
and chuck all of you out.
Aunt, aunt,
I just passed by that day,
I didn’t see anything.
Aunt,
the three of us were just chatting
at the lake.
We were lazy,
but we would never curse the princess.
That’s right.
So no one knows?
Alright.
If you can’t identify who did it,
then all of you are suspicious.
All of you should be sent out.
Aunt,
there’s another one who went to the lakeside
but is not here.
Who?
Actually
not everyone who went to the lakeside
is here.
That day I went to pick some new bamboo
by the lakeside.
You know,
I like to do some handwork
with bamboo.
When I was there,
I saw someone.
Tell me!
I saw someone
who ran to the stone by the lakeside.
Who?
Madam.
Who are you talking about?
I dare not say it.
If I tell you,
I am being disrespectful to superior.
Besides,
I’ve offended you before.
You won’t believe what I say.
Being disrespectful?
Tell me.
If you can tell the truth,
you are helping my daughter.
I will forgive what you did before.
Say it!
I saw
Princess Fukang.
Huirou?
Right.
That makes sense.
If it’s some ordinary maid,
how could she plot against my daughter?
Huirou, Huirou.
She is exactly the one who hates my daughter most,
who worries most that
my daughter would take away His Majesty’s love.
Who else can it be except her?
Huaiji,
you’re summoned by Her Highness.
Yes.
What’s your name?
Liang Huaiji,
Your Highness bestowed me my name.
I was young and ignorant,
and broke the taboo.
Your Highness forgave me
with your kindness and benevolence.
It’s you.
After a few years,
you’ve grown so tall.
His Majesty asked me
to pick some rare medical books in collection
and find someone to transcribe them.
I’ve shown the part you transcribed
to His Majesty,
he spoke highly of your handwriting.
If he knows
it’s written by
Liang Huaiji with calm character
and high sensitivity
who His Majesty praised before,
he would be more pleased.
When he praised you,
I totally forgot what happened before.
Madam Zhang,
Her Highness is meeting someone.
What thing can be more
important than the life of His Majesty’s daughter?
Silk and money are not proper awards for you,
but I think you might like these.
Madam Zhang,
this is the Hall of Peace.
No one is allowed to enter
without Her Highness’s permission.
Your Highness,
my daughter and I were cursed,
but you don’t punish the evil,
and even don’t allow me to see His Majesty.
Let Madam Zhang in.
Yingzhou (today Hejian in Hebei)
and Mozhou (today Renqiu in Hebei)
have been part of our territory for years.
They were ceded by the traitor Shi Jingtang
to Khitan.
Emperor Shizong of Zhou
has resumed them.
It is extremely rude
to ask Song
to return the land.
= Du Yan, courtesy name Shichang =
Besides, more than 30 years ago,
after the Treaty of Alliance of Song
and Liao was signed,
they have given up that land
for the annual tribute.
Now
they suddenly claimed the two places.
They are purely looting a burning house!
Indeed, they are.
= Wang Su, courtesy name Zhongyi =
The war in Shaanxi just ceased.
Yuanhao retreated,
but we also lost a dozen of
experienced generals like Ren Fu,
which sapped our strength.
Now they are stationing troops by the Baigou River,
claiming the two places.
Put the result aside,
if the message is spread out,
it will bring instability to the people.
Chuyue gets so ill,
can’t you let His Majesty take a look at her?
Yesterday,
after Physician Hu who’s specialized in pediatrics
checked Chuyue,
I asked him every detail.
Physician Hu said,
Chuyue is still
having asthma this time.
With the medicine applied,
she is out of danger now,
but it is still very difficult
to be cured radically.
It needs time and patience.
Don’t panic too much, Lady Zhang.
Panic?
You have never been a mother.
How can a mother
not panic when she
sees her child is suffering?
Madam,
you would panic, of course,
but a mother
can’t be a girl
who would cry over some emotions.
At least learn to control yourself,
learn to protect your child.
Like now,
Chuyue is having a fever.
You shouldn’t bring her out
in case she would catch a cold.
If she’s just ill,
I will do what the physician told me to.
Just let her rest.
But Your Highness, you know
her disease is caused
by someone’s curse.
To cure Chuyue,
the one who did this to her must be punished.
You are worrying too much.
She had the asthma
when she was born.
Recently the weather changed a lot,
and she accidentally caught a cold.
She will get better
after taking some medicine and having a good rest.
It’s not relevant to anyone.
It’s not relevant to anyone?
= Zhao Chuyue, 8:00 am of 30th =
This doll
was found two days ago
under the stone in the backyard.
I reported it to you that day.
You didn’t bother to
care about it
or investigate it.
Now we have solid evidence,
but you claim it’s not relevant to anyone?
This kind of witchcraft
is strictly forbidden in the palace.
I’ve sent someone to look into it,
and haven’t found anything.
But this kind of fallacy
doesn’t hold water.
Chuyue’s sickness is not relevant to it.
But I just heard
two days ago,
Huirou was mumbling to the moon
by the lake in the backyard,
and this is found
where she went.
I just asked Huirou in person,
and she just admitted
she went to the backyard.
= Territory of Song and Foreign Countries =
It is impossible to cede our territory.
But to cope with this,
we can learn from Han and Tang.
Learn for Han and Tang?
Marriage.
The currently leader of Liao
is not a fan of wars.
He has expressed his intention repeatedly
that he wants to be closer to our country.
Now their prince is almost the wedding age,
but has no legal wife yet.
I guess
if we refuse to return the land,
they are going to have a cross boundary marriage.
Chuyue has been cursed by Huirou,
but you don’t want to give the order
to investigate it.
Why?
Alright.
I’m not hoping you to give any care to it.
I just want you
to let Ren Shouzhong move away
who’s blocking in front of the Hall
of Happiness and Tranquility.
I’m going to see His Majesty.
His Majesty is unwell,
and he has a lot of state affairs to attend to.
His Majesty gave the decree
not to meet any concubine these days.
Huirou
is such an evil,
and you protect her like this.
Aren’t you worried that
His Majesty would blame you after he knows?
I will look into this thing.
The evidence is here.
The witness is Maid Xu.
She’s willing to testify too.
Your Highness always value rules.
If you don’t take swift actions against
that evil girl,
you can hardly convince the people.
Your Highness,
I have something
that might be relevant to
what Madam Zhang is talking about
to tell now.
How’s that possible?
Bring Huirou here.
Madam Zhang,
for the girl Huirou you are talking about,
is she about 5 or 6 years old,
this tall?
Yes.
She just turned 5,
and is that tall.
Madam Zhang,
Maid Xu saw Huirou
praying in the backyard
at about 21:15, am I right?
Yes.
The other night,
when I left the Hall of Peace
after I sent the medical book transcripts,
I accidentally went into the backyard
because I doesn’t know the way.
I saw
a barefooted girl in white dress
praying to the moon.
When I was trying to find the way,
I heard the sound of night watches of 21
before I met her.
So I must’ve met her at about 21:15.
Did you hear
what she’s praying?
She said
her father was sick,
she was willing to
suffer ten times more than her father
for the well-being of her father.
Why would you go to the lakeside?
Mother,
you are having my sister or my brother
in your belly,
you shouldn’t worry about other things.
Now Madam Zhang is telling Her Highness
you are cursing Chuyue.
How can I not worry?
Chuyue is my sister,
I love her.
How would I curse her?
Did she ever use witchcraft
to curse others?
Absolutely not.
I saw her at the South Gate that day.
I saw this girl
running to the lake with barefoot
and tears on her face.
I thought she’s a maid
who’s been wronged
and wanted to kill herself.
So I followed her to the lakeside.
But then I heard her
praying to the moon for her father.
Later, she was found by others,
so she left immediately.
She didn’t curse others,
nor bring this thing.
Nonsense!
A maid praying for her father?
What a great show!
Who are you?
Why did you make this up
to protect the murderer?
If you did meet a
maid you don’t know at the lakeside,
why can you still remember
what she said
and did
after few days?
That day, I
followed her
because she’s young
and it was dark,
which made me worried.
Besides, her praying for her father
with tears
and sincerity
impressed me deeply.
That’s why I remember it so clearly.
Okay.
Suppose you did meet such a person.
Many concubines in the palace
and stewardesses
adopt daughters.
It can be any girls.
Are you so sure
that the girl is Huirou?
I am not entirely sure
that the girl I met the other day
is the Huirou Madam Zhang is talking about.
But I
have a distinct impression on
the girl who prayed for her father.
In case it is wrong,
can you give me a moment,
some pen and paper
to paint the girl
and the scene I saw
the other day?
You say you didn’t curse her,
then why did you go there?
For what?
= Princess Huirou =
Tell me!
If you don’t feel guilty,
why can’t you say it?
Tell me!
Don’t be angry, mother.
I didn’t do anything bad.
I swear if I lied,
the love from father, Her Highness and mother
will be taken away from me forever.
Madam Zhang is very overbearing.
If you don’t tell the truth and show the evidence,
she won’t let you go.
I must see Her Highness
and explain it to her.
I can’t let her wrong you.
She is the princess.
Who lets you
give false evidence
and lie to the imperial family?
I didn’t know
eunuchs in the palace
are so good nowadays
that can just draw
such a painting easily.
Who would believe
that he’s not trained and taught by someone.
Tell me,
who made you do this?
Huirou,
Concubine Miao,
or someone else?
I dare not lie.
What I said is the mere fact.
What about now?
Still the mere fact?
Do you really think you can do everything you want
with someone’s protection?
Don’t you fear that I’ll tell His Majesty
and sentence you for deceiving him?
Enough.
It is very disgraceful
to slap a eunuch.
He’s Liang Huaiji,
who is working in the Imperial Academy.
He doesn’t even know
Huirou is Princess Fukang.
How can he be instigated to do this?
Princess?
I don’t know
she’s a princess.
I called the princess’s name directly.
Please punish me.
What a great show!
Ignorance can be forgiven.
Ask Princess Fukang to come here.
No need to let Madam Miao know.
If she asks,
tell her I want to
test what Huirou learned these days.
Yes, Your Highness.
Among all the daughters of the imperial families,
the daughter of Duke Jian is the best candidate.
I’ll draft the proposal now.
His Majesty woke up for two hours
after lunch yesterday,
and fell asleep again.
It’s 9 a.m. now and he still hasn’t woken up.
Physicians said
he’s out of danger,
but
The proposals from Xia Song, Han Qi
and Fan Zhongyan asking for punishment…
Keep them here for now.
Especially the one from Fan Zhongyan.
Xiwen was impeached for communicating
with the enemy
and giving demoralizing speech just before the war,
but his management over military
and civil affairs in Yan’an
is flawless.
He went there for just a year,
but he solved the water depletion in dry season
by digging a dozen of wells
and opened schools.
He won his reputation.
I think this time His Majesty
is sadder than angry.
Some people
will be demoted,
but will also be reused again.
Madam Miao has arrived.
Why do you come here?
Your Highness.
I told Ms. Xiu to ask Huirou to come here.
Stand up.
Your Highness, I heard what’s going on here.
Huirou is so young.
How would she know witchcraft?
Besides, she loves her sister so much.
She would never do that.
Please find the truth
and justify Huirou.
You believe Huirou,
then what are you worrying about?
Do you think I’ll be biased?
Sit down.
I lost my mind.
I rushed here
when I heard Lady Zhang wronged Huirou.
Wrong?
Did I?
Besides,
who else in this world
is more afraid that
Chuyue will share His Majesty’s love.
She is young,
so I think she’s not capable
of doing this alone.
If no one told her to do this,
someone must’ve helped.
Just now I’ve sent someone
to bring Huirou here.
She must’ve missed you on the way.
But now since you are here,
just stay a bit longer.
Let’s find out
the truth
in front of all of you.
Both Huirou and Chuyue
are the apples in His Majesty’s eyes,
and my children.
I won’t let anyone of them
be wronged.
= Gao Taotao =
Do you think
Huirou will be jealous
for His Majesty
loves her sister?
Huirou is bright and outgoing.
And she’s young.
She’s surrounded by
dignified people
= Zhao Zongshi =
like Her Highness and Madam Miao.
Her maids are upright and honest too.
How can she know witchcraft?
I’m not saying
she did this.
I was thinking
if Huirou
is a bit jealous of Chuyue.
After all,
Chuyue’s mother is Lady Zhang,
who takes His Majesty’s attention away
from Concubine Miao.
Concubine Miao must
hate Lady Zhang.
Then it is understandable for Huirou
to be jealous of Chuyue.
Madam Miao is gentle and magnanimous.
She won’t hate others.
Huirou,
greet Lady Zhang.
Yes.
I do not deserve your salute.
Today
I just hope Princess Fukang
can tell us what happened in the backyard,
and clear the curse on Chuyue.
If it can cure my baby,
she doesn’t need to give salute to me,
I can even
salute to her.
Huirou,
did you go to the backyard
the other day before yesterday at night?
Yes.
What for?
Is father getting better?
He is much better.
He does not need acupuncture treatment anymore.
That’s great.
You prayed to the moon in the backyard.
The heaven must’ve
been moved
by your filial love
to your father.
How did Your Highness know?
Heaven shows his mercy.
He happened to see
the princess praying for His Majesty
in the backyard.
Otherwise
her love to her father
would be wronged and humiliated.
Good boy,
how should I thank you?
If it were not you,
princess would be blamed
for a crime she never committed
at her age.
and have her reputation ruined.
If that happened, what can I do
as her mother?
You saved me and my daughter!
I just told
what I saw.
Besides, the princess is noble,
innocent,
and filial.
She’s loved by His Majesty and Her Highness,
protected by the heaven.
She will always be happy, safe, healthy,
and lucky with or without me.
Alright.
Tell me,
why would this appear
right after you went
to the backyard?
Why don’t you say anything
if you are not guilty?
Huirou,
if you have nothing to do with it,
explain it to Lady Zhang.
I won’t do it.
Do what?
Huirou, say something.
Now Lady Zhang wrongs you,
and you went to the lakeside.
That doll was also found there.
If you didn’t do it,
you have to explain it!
Huirou, what’s wrong with you?
You went to the lakeside to pray for your father,
if it were not Huaiji,
who can testify for you?
Now you don’t even want to
explain for yourself?
Madam Miao,
Huirou is so young
and got wronged,
and questioned today.
She must’ve been scared.
How can she figure it out now.
Take your time.
Don’t worry.
You are lucky.
Just now the princess is born,
and brought amnesty to the whole palace.
Your Highness,
princess has answered
Madam Zhang’s question just now.
Your Majesty,
how do you feel now?
Feel uncomfortable?
Where’s Huirou?
I hear Huirou is calling me.
In the past, Zhao Feiyan
accused Madam Ban of cursing.
Emperor Cheng of Han interrogated Madam Ban.
She answered
“I know that the life span is destined,
and that the rich and the poor
are doomed by the heaven.
Being virtuous has not yet been blessed,
how’s there any hope for being evil?
If the ghosts know,
would they believe prayers without faith?
If the ghosts are ignorant,
would curse do any difference?
That’s why I won’t do it.”
This kid is right.
Huirou is young,
she didn’t read this much.
She can’t quote the classics
and can’t explain it right now.
Or maybe she doesn’t want to
explain in front of so many people.
But what she said
is the same meaning
of what Madam Ban’s
said.
Are you comparing me to
Zhao Feiyan who wrecked the country?
No.
Your Highness.
His Majesty is awake.
He wants to see Princess Fukang.
Go, let’s go to see your father.
I just saw
Huirou vaguely
in my dream,
calling me father with a sad face.
I can’t move my body,
can’t walk
or see clearly.
But I know
you were being upset.
So I used every bit of my strength
to go towards your direction.
Then I woke up.
Just now Physician Zheng just checked.
He said His Majesty is fine now
and prescribed some medicine.
But I remember Physician Zheng said
this time His Majesty is attacked
by three diseases at the same time.
Physician Fang is dealing with
His Majesty’s heart disease.
Ask him to check on His Majesty again.
Yes.
Huirou is my most important treasure.
You don’t want your mother to know
even if you were criticized by her
that you went there to pray for me.
Let me guess,
it must be because I was too sick
that the Empress didn’t tell your mother
for fear that it might hurt her baby,
but you knew it.
You were worried about my condition,
so you went to pray to the moon for me.
But you didn’t want your mother to know
that I was so sick.
Am I right?
Huirou,
I wronged you.
There, there.
Why does she
have your personalities?
There, there.
Don’t cry.
= Di Qing, courtesy name Hanchen =
Sir.
You asked me to come
to give me a test
or there’s a war to fight?
Take a seat.
= Fan Zhongyan, courtesy name Xiwen =
I want you to eat some porridge.
Porridge?
The porridge is made with
Champa Rice from the first harvest
grown here.
The harvest is 30 percent
more than the grain before.
Farmers sent us a cart
of this grain
to thank us for giving them
the new seed of grain a year ago.
Tastes good.
I’ll go to Yaozhou soon.
Yaozhou?
You are demoted?
Why?
You made extraordinary contributions to Yan’an.
You’ve resumed forts nearby,
repelled the enemy,
reassured the people, built farming land
and opened schools.
Who here does not respect you?
Why on earth can you be demoted?
Sit down.
I’m just doing my job somewhere else,
what’s the difference?
There must be a reason.
The losing war
has nothing to do with you.
You firmly stood against the attack.
The truth shows
what you said is completely right.
It is my mistake.
If His Majesty is not a kind emperor,
what I did
can be regarded as fear for the enemies,
or even collusion with the enemies.
I always push for a peaceful settlement,
and had been in contact with Yuanhao.
For one of my poems, Pride of Fishermen
I was impeached
by many people,
saying I am weary of war.
The chief commander hit the morale
right before the war
by composing such a poem.
You are being sympathetic.
Sympathetic or weary of war?
That’s hard to tell.
I, Fan Zhongyan
can’t say I don’t care about my reputation.
But I dare not want
everyone in the world to know me.
Before I took the position,
I did want to win a huge war,
kill the enemies, take down places,
and show our power,
so that I can settle down the west with my credits.
But after I came here,
after I saw the soldiers
and people
regardless of Song’s and Xixia’s,
my heart
and mind have changed.
I want to give them the peace.
In the letter I wrote to Yuanhao,
I said both armies are serving their leaders.
They are all loyal people.
I don’t want to see loyal people
killing each other
having blood flood.
I mean what I said.
If you say this is the fear of wars,
and it affects subordinates’ morale,
it might be.
I have nothing to explain for myself
if I am demoted for this.
Chief Fan,
someone called Zhang Zai wants to see you.
Tell him
I’m on my way.
Yes.
General Di.
Are you…
It is your duty now
to protect our land and people.
To cease the war,
does it really
cost blood
and lives?
That’s a question for you to answer.
Joining the army is not the only way
to serve the state.
People should make the best of themselves.
= Zhang Zai, courtesy name Zihou =
Zihou,
your father named you Zhang Zai
with courtesy name Zihou,
I think because he hopes
you can undertake great tasks with high morality.
Your writings
also show gentleness
and broadness.
Confucian scholars have their own famous belief,
why do you have to serve the military?
I give you the book the Doctrine of Mean,
hoping in the future
the court can have a great scholar
who has thorough study on the Confucius
and who can carry it forward.
Yes, sir.
♪ Loved you a gentleman yet got abandoned ♪
♪ Peach blossoms color the city ♪
♪ Spring breeze purified dusty memories ♪
♪ The gate of the vast palace opens ♪
♪ Bid farewell with wine after the glory ends ♪
♪ Outside the city a beautiful world unveils ♪
♪ Long-standing distance doesn’t alienate us ♪
♪ Keep you company behind the gate ♪
♪ Four seasons come and go ♪
♪ We only have each other in this cage ♪
♪ Wish to fly freely in the next life ♪
♪ Willows turn green flowers red ♪
♪ Sing aloud with wine ♪
♪ Hold your hands and go home together ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Life is long yet joy is little ♪