♪ Inside the state a city is built ♪
♪ Where a benevolent emperor resides ♪
♪ Court officials are brave and able ♪
♪ The empress is fair ♪
♪ Princes died too young to ascend the throne ♪
♪ Princesses are spoiled and fragile ♪
♪ Commoners are also the emperor’s children ♪
♪ All are living peacefully ♪
♪ Wish I could live a day for myself ♪
♪ Follow my heart and ethics without distractions ♪
♪ To be a good husband ♪
♪ To be a caring father ♪
♪ We were close when we first met ♪
♪ I hope I can control my desires ♪
♪ To be a worriless emperor and father ♪
♪ Prudence tops all virtues ♪
♪ People build the state ♪
= Held in the Lonely Castle =
♪ May the world be peaceful ♪
= Episode 49 =
During the painting for a dozen days,
Cui Bai had a crush on me.
Because of his painting,
I adored him, too.
He expressed his love with a painting,
and I accepted him.
I promised to marry him
after I left the palace.
I swear.
I don’t dare to conceal the truth.
I pledged to marry him without permission.
I broke the imperial rule.
But we’ve been courteous
and we never have inappropriate intimacy
I...
I’d like to have the Imperial Recorder
check my virginity.
You tell me this,
because you want me to keep my promise,
to let you leave the palace
instead of punishing you?
No.
Your Majesty, I tell you this,
because I believe you’ll judge it wisely
after you know what really happened
and you won’t let others
make groundless accusations
or blame anyone wrongly.
I broke the imperial rule
and I should be punished.
I won’t complain about that.
Then why do you come
and ask me to keep my promise?
Your Majesty, it took you more than one hour
to listen to my
story.
This is exactly what I want.
As for the investigation and judgement,
I’m afraid too many rules or laws
are involved,
I don’t dare to coerce you
with an old promise.
Thank you, Your Majesty,
for keeping your promise.
You come to confess to me,
regardless of your own punishment.
Do you fear to put Cui Bai into trouble
or to get the Empress involved?
However,
don’t you fear
it’ll confirm that Cui Bai is unrestrained
and the Empress isn’t strict with her maids,
and even wants to draw officials over
with her maids?
I just fear you don’t know the truth.
Since you know,
I won’t complain,
however hard you punish me.
And I believe.
Since you know the truth,
you’ll vindicate Her Highness.
Seems like you trust me
more than the Empress does.
Her Highness loves you.
So, she’s anxious.
When closely involved,
she can’t see clearly.
Well, look at you.
You’re an interesting girl.
No wonder she likes you.
Fine.
Since you’re frank,
let me tell you the truth, too.
Recently, people are talking about
what happened between you and Cui Bai.
Some said
everyone involved must be checked carefully.
Some even wanted to imprison you.
But...
I wasn’t going to
investigate on it.
After you explained to me,
I’m sure about it now.
You know what?
I remember the Empress told me that
some maids would leave in a few days.
You’re one of them, I guess.
Yes.
But I’ve decided to
beg Her Highness to let me stay with her
instead of leaving the palace.
Since people are talking about it,
if I leave at this moment,
someone will track me down.
I don’t...
I don’t want to get Cui Bai involved.
Besides,
I don’t want to leave Her Highness.
I’d like to stay with her for the rest of my life
and take care of her.
I’m even jealous of
your loyalty to her.
I keep making trouble for Her Highness
all the time.
I’m sorry to her.
Instead of blaming me,
she always helps me.
I think
in the palace,
I can continue to
make crowns and hairpins,
and stay with Her Highness,
learning from her.
It’s my luck.
Your Majesty.
Her Highness must be considerate
and remain graceful
so that people will respect her.
She can let nothing go wrong.
But in fact,
she has passions
and she can be weak, too.
However,
she can’t tell her families
about her grievances.
Nor can she tell her husband.
To her husband,
she’s not only a wife,
but also a subordinate.
She thinks she must work for Your Majesty.
She doesn’t dare to bother you.
On the day of coup,
she didn’t want to
die with you.
She would only die alone to protect you.
She took herself
as your subordinate.
Madam Zhang disobeyed the rule
and get out of her chamber.
Instead of punishing her,
you comforted her gently.
You spoiled her, regardless of right or wrong.
Your Majesty.
When Her Highness saw that,
she was sad and aggrieved.
Could she...
Could she believe that
you would handle this problem
in a fair way?
She punished Ling’er,
according to the rule,
and in this way,
no one could use Ling’er for more accusations.
But in my heart,
I’ve got a better plan.
I hate her for not trusting me.
But you’re right.
I’ve been so bad to her
over so many years.
How can she trust me
with her whole heart?
Your Majesty.
Her Highness is very lonely.
I’m begging you.
Let me stay with her all my life.
Okay.
I promise you.
Stand up.
Go to Imperial Office Bureau,
and take a message to Zhang Maoze.
He did hard work
for days.
Ask Liaozi to go with you.
Take the case
to him.
And...
ask the Empress to bring me
two jars of peach wine.
I didn’t enjoy it last time.
Mr. Zhang.
I know you do everything,
for His Majesty and Her Highness
and you don’t like what Madam Zhang does.
But...
Do know
how the former empress
Madam Guo died?
Wasn’t...
Wasn’t she dead
in her self-cultivation?
His Majesty didn’t like Madam Guo.
But he didn’t want her to live alone,
and wanted to get her back.
Yan Wenying helped most
in dethroning her.
For fear that Madam Guo might come back
and take revenge,
he took physicians to cure her
when she had a cold.
Then, she was sicker.
She was poisoned?
No.
She was buried alive.
Yan Wenying didn’t dare to
poison Madam Guo.
That would be obvious.
He just changed the prescription
and made her sicker.
By then,
His Majesty was coming back
from the fast in southern suburbs.
In case that His Majesty visited Madam Guo
after he came back,
Yan Wenying put her
in the coffin
before she was dead.
I...
I won’t let Her Highness
suffer the same thing.
But...
But His Majesty...
His Majesty cares for Her Highness.
I know.
But His Majesty cares for
so many people and things.
He may not take care of them all.
He only wants a balance
between the imperial court and imperial harem.
But you’re doing this.
His Majesty has warned you.
I’m investigating by myself.
No one asked me to.
His Majesty is wise.
He certainly knows.
He won’t blame others
because he is unsatisfied with me.
As for myself,
I won’t complain
even if His Majesty punishes me.
What are you looking for?
I have two more jars.
I’ll ask a maid to get them.
Being drunk is harmful to health.
Liaozi asked the maids
to make some hangover-cure soup.
I’m not drunk.
I’m never drunk.
You didn’t behave like this.
Am I...
Am I disgracing myself?
I don’t think so.
You’re in your husband’s room,
why are you afraid of disgracing yourself?
Danshu.
Even when you’re disgraced,
it won’t be screwed.
On the day of coup,
you struggled not to
disgrace yourself.
But in fact,
were you really that calm?
Were you not scared
or worried?
Are you blaming me
for punishing Ling’er?
Do you really think
she must be killed?
I just wanted to get rid of it,
in case of getting involved.
A mere maid.
But did you really get rid of it?
Do you know
Yang Huaimin’s killing
the last treasonous guard
against my rule
and the Empress’s killing a maid
who had fornication with a guard
were mentioned in the same breath?
Both of you are considered
as destroying the evidence.
Your Majesty, if you want to investigate it,
interrogate me,
ground me,
or imprison me,
I won’t complain.
Can’t you listen to me once?
It’s been over ten years.
When we argue, you always say
“Punish me, Your Majesty”.
When you say you’re sorry
and you’re wrong,
do you really think
you’re wrong?
When you say you’re wrong,
you mean I’m muddleheaded.
I’m wrong, Your Majesty.
I’m absolutely wrong.
I’m merciless and stupid.
I didn’t show any mercy,
and there’s more trouble now.
You don’t need to humiliate me.
Why don’t you repudiate me?
Cao Danshu.
It’s so stupid of you!
Do you think any man
wants to marry a living Buddha?
I didn’t know
what Ling’er would get you involved in.
She really did capital offence.
Well...
you weren’t merciful enough
and you weren’t wise enough.
So, there is trouble now.
But who doesn’t make mistakes?
I made a lot of mistakes
didn’t I?
When I was self-willed at a young age
and quarreled with Empress Dowager,
I accidentally got a common family
lose their lives.
In Haoshuichuan Battle, I misjudged
and supported Han Qi’s rash advance.
Over ten thousand soldiers
lost their lives.
Your Majesty.
Don’t always
blame yourself.
I asked the physicians.
You always have the heart disease,
mainly because you’re too anxious.
Stand up.
Danshu.
You’re a subordinate.
But you’re also my wife.
When you’re in trouble
or make a mistake,
as long as you aren’t against rules or laws,
don’t always try to
argue with the Emperor
or ask for punishment.
You still have your husband to share with you,
defend you or mend for you.
You’re funny.
You’re an evil official.
You’re supposed to be sensual and greedy
who drink and enjoy
with your concubines every day.
But look at you.
You exchanged
all the treasures
into these metal scraps,
bamboo slices
and tortoise shells.
And for those women,
they used to
live a poor life in theatres.
But after they came here,
they’re enjoying themselves.
I hate saints the most.
I especially hate
those guys who claim to be kindhearted.
Fan Zhongyan and Ouyang Xiu
can dismiss redundant officials,
but they always threaten with the benevolence.
That’s disgusting!
Yulan.
Do you know
why I like such antiques?
You liked them since you were little, didn’t you?
You didn’t have enough money then,
and you swindled everywhere.
Since I turned nineteen,
I never believed
Yao, Shun and Yu were perfect emperors
or Duke of Zhou was a perfect man.
I wanted to find such antiques
and read the characters on them
so that I can see
if perfect emperors also manipulated power
and were self-willed
and if Duke of Zhou
was also greedy and sensual
just like me.
Have you found any evidence?
It’s hard to find antiques.
It’s also hard to read ancient characters.
I haven’t found any evidence
on imperfect saints.
But from a word or two,
I see that
scriptures passed down by scholars
may not be real.
Interesting.
Quite interesting!
In the revolt of Qinghe County,
Ming Hao failed to break into the town.
Scholar Wen, you went there to fight.
In less than two months,
you broke in and killed the traitors.
You even gave right rewards and punishments.
You placated common people,
banned the cult
and allowed local people to borrow money for seeds
in case of missing the farming season.
You’ve made great contributions.
= Wen Yanbo, courtesy name Kuanfu =
I took down the town,
with the blessing of Your Majesty
and the help of brave generals.
Before I left,
you taught me how to
ban the cult and instruct people
so that I knew
I should treat the cult members
as ignorant common people,
instead of traitors.
It’s kind and farsighted of you, Your Majesty.
I really admire that.
Don’t be modest.
I’m not.
Deputy Military Governor Ming Hao
failed to take down the town,
only because most of his proposals
were held back
by Xia Song.
And the war was delayed.
I have something to say, Your Majesty.
Scholar Wen was modest.
= Chen Zhizhong, courtesy name Zhaoyu =
But he was telling the truth
that Xia Song interfered
with the battle.
Xia Song is always jealous of virtuous officials
and gets rid of dissidents.
In the coup, he sheltered Yang Huaimin
and framed Her Highness up.
Haven’t I already
approved of your proposals
and banished Yang Huaimin from the Capital?
I don’t think
= He Tan, courtesy name Shengcong =
banishing Yang Huaimin is enough.
Blaming Xia Song is the right way.
Yang Huaimin often colluded with Xia Song.
Xia Song isn’t a good man.
He’s greedy and extravagant.
Your Majesty,
he is good at
flattering you.
But he never does his duty
to give honest advice.
I was absent-minded.
I didn’t hear what you said.
The other day,
the Empress and I took Princess Fukang
and some madams to the temple.
We stopped on the way,
to buy some osmanthus cakes
and pine nut candies.
The wrapping paper
is the tabloid of the Capital.
Princess Fukang read it curiously
and told me that
it was about officials,
but its writing is better than the court bulletins’
from Bureau of Reports.
Since Su Shunqin and Wang Yirou
were demoted and banished.
Bureau of Reports lacks talents.
And the reports are more vulgar.
I think
Su Shunqin and the other were unrestrained,
disgracing scholars.
You punished them right, Your Majesty.
But they weren’t rebellious
or corrupt.
They just made an indiscreet remark.
It’s been three years since they were banished.
In their poems and letters,
they have regretted.
And they don’t write as wildly as they used to.
I think
it’s a pity
if a talent like Su Shunqin
can’t work for the imperial court.
What do you think, Scholar Wen?
I think
He Tan makes sense.
I think so.
How about...
How about discussing about
reinstating Su Shunqin
as the adjutant of Huzhou?
I was speaking of Xia Song.
But His Majesty...
He was digressing.
When he mentioned Zimei,
I forgot about
Xia Song’s problem.
Zimei was truly unlucky.
Wang Gongchen was so stubborn
and he totally fired Zimei.
That was heavy punishment.
But now he’s back to work.
It means His Majesty has cooled down.
That’s great.
As for Xia Song,
don’t rush.
How can I not rush?
Xia Song is such an evil guy!
He was ruthless to Shi Jie.
And for Su Zimei,
Wang Gongchen apparently
didn’t let go of him.
But didn’t Xia Song
stir up trouble secretly?
Xia Song never likes any honest official.
In this case,
when His Majesty
reinstated Su Zimei,
could he mean something else?
You really are sick?
Leave us. Let me do it.
What’s wrong with you?
You think I pretend to be ill
and you still come to see me?
I come out to take a message
to Wang Gongchen’s wife and Wang Zhi’s wife
and check on you on my way.
Tell me.
Why is Madam Zhang
struggling for promotion?
She has realized that
without a status,
no love
can last long.
I heard
Wang Zhi and the other
advised His Majesty to promote Madam Zhang.
His Majesty also told some officials that
on the night of coup,
Madam Zhang rushed out
and protected him.
If Lantiao can have a son
and he can be raised up by Madam Zhang...
His Majesty doesn’t like the Empress.
By then, you can report that
a maid of the Empress has fornication with a guard.
If rumor goes out that
Her Highness’s favorite maid Qiuhe
had a relationship with Imperial Artist Cui Bai.
Maybe, our plan will work.
But Yang Huaimin
was already banished.
Imperial Security Agency
is under the control of Zhang Maoze again.
This is due to those censors.
It’s okay.
He’ll be back in a couple of days.
Back in a couple of days?
You never know.
Wen Yanbo seldom discusses much.
His wife is close to Madam Zhang.
He is on good terms with
Madam Zhang’s uncle.
Yeah.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
I just didn’t expect that
the revolt in Qinghe County was put down so soon.
When Wen Yanbo broke in town,
he
placated the cult.
He only executed some heads of the cult.
He ran official schools to destroy the cult.
And he didn’t even treat followers of cult
throughout the country as traitors
because of the revolt.
What does that concern us?
Anyway,
he won’t object to the promotion of Madam Zhang.
Cult followers weren’t tracked down
in or out of the imperial court.
His Majesty even let go of the coup
in the imperial court.
I don’t know where to start the plan.
All right.
See?
I bought you a pair of
opal earrings.
Do you like them?
No.
Looking forward to your next visit.
All right.
Go. Go. Okay. Okay.
Excuse me. Step aside.
It’s been only two months.
Seems like
you’ve sold all the old goods out.
I sold them out yesterday.
I sold the last ones
to Khitan merchants.
Did you?
Now,
the fashion of silks and brocades
changes quickly.
Girls of our nation
are picky.
I won’t sell old-fashioned styles to them.
I have to sell them
to Khitan people.
The worst goods
can only be sold to Xizangs, Xixia people
or Cantonese.
Double-color silk from the south
and camel hair blankets from Uighur.
I only keep them for you.
Double-color silk?
Which do you mean?
These two look similar.
And they both look good.
Well,
pack these two
and send them to my place.
Okay.
I’m sure
Madam Zhang will like them.
Okay. Okay.
All right. Thank you.
Last night,
you said in the routine inspection,
you found him carry a tea cup
and a silver cup
without any record.
= Zhang Chengzhao =
And he failed to explain where he got them.
You sent him to us, then.
We searched his room immediately
and found these, including
powder of five minerals and aphrodisiac.
You didn’t alert anyone, did you?
You told us to keep a low profile.
We were very cautious.
We confirmed
no one was in his yard.
Do you want to confess
and get a chance to make amends?
Or do you want me to ask physicians
to check these prescriptions
and see what dirty things
you have brought into
the Pavilion of Luan?
And these treasures.
Will you tell me honestly
where you got them
and why you got them?
Or shall I
give them to Officer Ren
and let him check up on them?
Mr. Zhang.
I’ll confess.
I’d like to atone for my crimes.
Go get my pickled plums
and haws.
Your Majesty, you’re coughing lately.
The plums and haws
were boiled.
Drink it after meals
and it stops coughing and helps digestion.
Huirou and I tried it.
You always know how to keep in good health.
You haven’t changed much in the last ten years.
What are you talking about?
You always know how to make me happy.
Huirou is even engaged.
Huirou.
What are you thinking of?
Father.
I’ve been reading
Tao Yuanming’s poems.
I love them.
You like Tao Yuanming?
That’s great.
What have you read?
Which are your favorites?
The Story of Five-willow Gentleman,
Ah, Homeward Bound I go!
Thirty Poems on the Classic of Mountains and Seas
and Ode to Leisure.
Which parts do you like the most?
Recite some to me.
I like...
I read them from time to time.
I don’t know
if I understand them correctly.
Father.
What?
You want me to explain to you?
No. No. No.
Father, you work so hard.
You’ve got so many things to do.
It’s a little problem.
Why don’t you let Huaiji
explain to me?
Fine, then.
I’ve got some
important proposals to review.
I’m going back.
You’ve made up your mind?
Yes. Yes.
Uh...
Let me calm down.
That’ll be fine.
Be careful when you talk to Lantiao.
Don’t let her see you through.
Aye. Aye.
Wait here.
Aye.
I wish I could be the collar of her blouse
so that I would smell her.
What a pity that she takes off her blouse at night!
I hate it when the day doesn’t break yet.
I wish I could be the belt of her dress
so that I would cover her body.
What a pity that the weather changes!
She will put on new dresses.
I wish I could be the pomade on her hair
so that I would smooth her hair.
What a pity that she takes showers!
I must suffer in the hot water.
I wish I could be the makeup on her eye brows,
so that I could shine when she looks around.
Princess.
What?
Which sentence don’t you understand?
How could I not understand?
I understand every sentence.
But...
I asked father to leave you to me
and read Ode to Leisure with me
from the very beginning.
Huaiji.
Do you think
Tao Yuanming is handsome?
A romantic celebrity like him
always makes people admire him.
So...
could he be as handsome as Cao?
Huaiji.
Look.
Cao gave me this
after the banquet the other day.
Together with the jade comb.
I wish I could be the pomade on her hair
so that I would smooth her hair.
When she said Ode to Leisure,
and I noticed her look,
I knew something must be wrong.
I’m right! I’m right!
You...
If I didn’t ask you,
you would even hide it from me!
♪ Loved you a gentleman yet got abandoned ♪
♪ Peach blossoms color the city ♪
♪ Spring breeze purified dusty memories ♪
♪ The gate of the vast palace opens ♪
♪ Bid farewell with wine after the glory ends ♪
♪ Outside the city a beautiful world unveils ♪
♪ Long-standing distance doesn’t alienate us ♪
♪ Keep you company behind the gate ♪
♪ Four seasons come and go ♪
♪ We only have each other in this cage ♪
♪ Wish to fly freely in the next life ♪
♪ Willows turn green flowers red ♪
♪ Sing aloud with wine ♪
♪ Hold your hands and go home together ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Life is long yet joy is little ♪