♪ Inside the state a city is built ♪
♪ Where a benevolent emperor resides ♪
♪ Court officials are brave and able ♪
♪ The empress is fair ♪
♪ Princes died too young to ascend the throne ♪
♪ Princesses are spoiled and fragile ♪
♪ Commoners are also the emperor’s children ♪
♪ All are living peacefully ♪
♪ Wish I could live a day for myself ♪
♪ Follow my heart and ethics without distractions ♪
♪ To be a good husband ♪
♪ To be a caring father ♪
♪ We were close when we first met ♪
♪ I hope I can control my desires ♪
♪ To be a worriless emperor and father ♪
♪ Prudence tops all virtues ♪
♪ People build the state ♪
= Held in the Lonely Castle =
♪ May the world be peaceful ♪
= Episode 13 =
Xinhe has been in the palace for 6 years,
yet she’s still just a Lady of County.
She deserves a higher title.
Now Madam Miao
is pregnant with your child.
She made an undeniable contribution.
Once the baby is born,
she should be promoted accordingly.
I think
censors won’t raise any objection to it.
I don’t want to wait till the baby is born.
I am going to promote Xinhe
to Zhaoyi (a title of concubine)
before the baby is born.
Well…
This never happened before
to promote a Lady of County (a title of concubine)
directly to Zhaoyi.
Censors will stand against it.
Xinhe has been in the palace for years.
She is pure, kindhearted and gentle.
After six years,
she’s still a Lady of County.
That is extremely unfair to her.
Now
she is pregnant with a royal child.
It is already late for me
to give her what she deserves.
Madam Miao is not the only one
who hasn’t got promoted.
In the past 5 years,
no concubine has been promoted.
There are three ladies of county
who came to the palace earlier than Madam Miao.
Xinhe is different from them.
She is different in your heart,
but to others,
she is the same with the other
three ladies of county.
Everyone says you are close with her.
Why don’t you trust her?
Besides,
even if she’s been promoted to a Consort
rather than Zhaoyi,
her child will still call you mother,
and call her sister (the title that a concubine's
child used to call birth mother in Song).
Danshu.
After I became the Empress,
I proposed to promote
three ladies of county
including Madam Miao
in 1034 A.D.,
and you approved.
But
censors objected it,
saying concubines
already enjoyed the offerings from the people
and a luxurious life.
Promotion out of no reason
would only create arrogance.
I was criticized
for showing grace with public welfare.
That was because the farce
made by the former empress with
Lady Shang and Lady Yang
caused unexpected turmoil at the court,
and I just took the throne,
I didn’t want to hear the court
arguing about harem all day long.
I did wrong to you.
But this time, even if someone disagrees with it,
you won’t be involved.
It’s Lv Yijian’s proposal
to promoted Xinhe to Zhaoyi immediately
at the court in front of everyone.
The Prime Minister Lv?
It is an exception
to promote Madam Miao to Zhaoyi.
It is my idea.
It won’t involve you.
You…
I have to say something
to Your Majesty.
Say it.
My objection to the promotion
before the royal baby is born
is not because I’m afraid of
being criticized by censors,
but because I consider it inappropriate.
This is about the harem.
So it is within my duty.
I have to tell Your Majesty
the reason
of my objection.
The thing happened in 1034 A.D.
made me feel
wronged,
but then I realized I made three mistakes.
First,
at that time, I just took control of the harem.
I did need support
and had the intention of associating with concubines.
My intention was not wrong.
But I should let them see
my sincerity and virtues
in daily conversation
and contact,
instead of
using the concubine positions which the court paid for
to build up my reputation.
This shows my wrong morality.
Second,
before the fight the former empress
had with two ladies
caused turmoil at the court.
Many officials were involved.
From this,
I should’ve realized
things in the harem
is not just Your Majesty’s family business.
Officials are concerned with
the promotion and demotion of concubines
just as the state affairs at the court.
I wasn’t in the palace for long
and didn’t understand the circumstance
nor had any authority,
yet I was so anxious to exercise my power.
This shows my insufficient planning.
Third,
three ladies of county all stayed
in the palace for long
with merits and cautiousness.
It was not wrong to promote them.
They didn’t ask for promotion.
It was out of my intention
and they accepted it without declinature,
which is natural and normal.
But officials were very strict with
concubines because of the former empress.
The three of them were questioned
about their morality
and wronged because of my selfish motives
and insufficient planning.
That was what I felt most ashamed of.
This shows my inadequate consideration.
= The Silver Gate =
That’s all about daily etiquettes and rules on duty
for today.
= Liang Quanyi =
Now let’s talk about the most important rules
that can cost your life if you break them.
I invited the Manager of the Inner East Gate
Mr. Zhang Maoze
to teach you.
You must pay
all your attention
to his lecture.
Please, Mr. Zhang.
Thank you, Quanyi.
I am the Manager of the Inner East Gate.
Today I’m going to tell you
the important rules related to
the gate.
First of all,
what you always need to keep in mind is that
all the gates of the palace
must be closed after dark.
No one can open before sunrise.
If anyone wants to open gates
at night for some emergencies,
he must have
the fish tally endorsed by His Majesty.
Rouge.
It’s packed.
Here you are.
We are not open till noon.
Foster mother!
= Liang Yuansheng =
Yuansheng!
Yuansheng is back!
Foster Mother!
You are back!
= Landlady of the Restaurant of Breeze, Zhang Lihua =
I haven’t heard from you for so long
that I thought something happened to you.
No.
Foster Mother,
we did have some unexpected troubles
in Dingzhou.
But blessed by you,
we were not robbed by thieves.
The money for selling goods,
raw lake salt you wanted,
and the recipe
of the grape wine in Dayuan,
I’ve taken all of them back.
Excellent!
If the gatekeeper opened gate without verifying,
with unmatched tally
or tally without endorsement,
he shall be severely punished according to the law.
- Officer Ren. - Officer Ren.
= Ren Shouzhong, courtesy name Jichen =
Understood?
Understood.
What’s your name?
Zheng, Zheng Ye.
Repeat what Mr. Zhang said.
Gate…
Gates, gates should not be open
after, after dark.
I, if anyone wants to open the gate
at night for some emergencies,
he must have
the fish tally endorsed by His Majesty.
It should have the time and reason written on it.
Enough!
That’s completely a mess!
If you can’t even remember a few lines,
how can your work in the palace?
Some of you
will take the key
to the gates of the palace.
If you made any mistakes,
you will lose your life for that.
Officer Ren is not joking.
Gatekeepers
who let people in or out against the law
shall be at least exiled
or even hanged.
You, go out
and kneel to reflect on yourself.
No dinner for you today.
What about you?
Did you remember everything?
Yes.
Repeat what Mr. Zhang just said.
Yes, sir.
Just now Mr. Zhang said
all the gates of the palace
shall be closed after dark.
No one can open before sunrise.
If anyone wants to open the gate
at night for some emergencies,
he must have the fish tally endorsed by His Majesty.
He must write down the time
and detailed reason,
the gate that needs to open,
the number and identity of people
who need to go in and out
and send the information to the Cabinet.
= Restaurant of Breeze, Closed =
Yuansheng can come back safe and sound
with the recipe
of grape wine.
What a blessing!
Today, we
just eat and drink
to celebrate his return!
Great!
Yuansheng has helped a lot this time…
Foster mother!
- I just got a good son so easily.
- Foster mother,
mother!
Why don’t you go to take a shower
and change clothes?
I, I have to go to my uncle’s house now.
Aren’t you going to rest a few days
before you take your mom and
your brother here?
I’ve already arranged the rooms for you.
This is the letter
my brother Yuanheng sent to me.
What happened?
He said due to the pandemic,
my uncle and mom were infected and critically ill.
And there was no more news from him.
The tally is carved with a shape of fish
and the name of the gate.
Every tally is divided into two parts.
= Liang Yuanheng =
Gatekeepers and the guard leads of each gate hold
one of the two parts.
Before opening the gate,
the gatekeeper
needs to prepare the guards of the gate
to line up on both sides of the gate,
and light up the torch.
Both the guard lead and the eunuch
need to check the tally
and make sure nothing is wrong
and then they can open the gate.
Even if the tally does match,
if the gatekeeper opened the door without verifying,
with unmatched tally
or tally without endorsement
shall be severely punished according to the law.
Every word is correct.
What’s your name?
Liang Yuanheng.
Yuanheng from Yuan Heng Li Zhen
(Benevolence, courtesy, righteousness and integrity).
Officer Ren.
What a reckless bastard!
How dare you say the name of His Majesty!
Officer Ren,
this kid
should be 8 or 9 years old.
Before he came here,
his family must haven’t taught him well.
A wild child
who knows nothing about taboos.
He seems literate,
unlike an untaught kid.
How old are you?
Who do you have in your family?
I... I...
I am ten years old.
I was born in 1027 A.D.
I have no one left in my family.
No one?
What about your parents?
My...
my father died of an illness
in the year of my birth.
My mother took me
to my uncle’s place in City Liao.
Not long ago,
there was an outbreak of pharyngitis in City Liao.
My mother and uncle
died from it.
If you were just some naughty kid from rural area,
it would just be a mistake to forget the taboo
and earn yourself the cane.
But now you are in the palace
serving for the royals.
Breaking the taboo will cost your life.
Officer Ren,
Madam Miao will deliver
the baby soon.
Imprison him first.
I’ll look at the palace rules
before I report this to Her Highness
to see what punishment he should receive.
= Restaurant of Breeze =
Yuansheng,
send me a message
about what happened
once you reach your uncle’s home.
If there’s anything we can help,
just tell us,
you hear me?
You allowed me to go back to visit my mother
and prepared horse and money for me in such a hurry.
I don’t know how I can repay your kindness.
I just wish my mother and uncle can recover,
Yuanheng can stay safe and sound.
Once I take them here,
I’ll focus on
the business
from the Capital to Xixia.
Go.
Take care.
Okay.
Yuanheng,
your uncle and mother were gone.
Our family was poor.
And now we own a huge debt
for hiring a physician and the funeral.
From now on,
I can’t
feed you anymore.
You are so smart.
I managed to
find you a good job.
You’ll work
in the most glorious place in the world.
Your Majesty,
Madam Xu of Dangyang County came to the palace.
She is at the door,
asking if you have time
to meet with her.
Let her in.
Madam,
please, have a seat.
You love me since I was a kid,
and now I married Xinhe,
you are literally
the closest person to me.
I don’t deserve it.
Your Majesty, you really flatter me.
= Zhao Zhen’s wet nurse, Madam Xu =
Your Majesty,
please have a look.
Things on this list
are all in my house.
I’ve recorded all the gifts
and people who sent them.
In a few months,
I couldn’t count how much I’ve received.
I dare not to decide,
so few days ago I listed everything
and sent the list to the Pavilion of Phoenix
to let Xinhe decide.
Today Officer Ren picked me up to the palace,
and I went to visit Xinhe first.
She said
she dares not to decide either.
Everything depends on you.
The box hasn’t been opened.
Things in it haven’t been touched.
She told me to send it to you,
saying you will decide.
You moved to the palace
to accompany Xinhe.
Officer Ren told me
Her Highness asked him to make arrangement
according to conventions and rules.
It is required by the court,
not because of the relationship.
That is very kind of her.
The Ministry of Internal Service
has four vacant positions.
The Pavilion of Phoenix
asked for some clever servant.
But look at
those idiots!
They are either stupid
or short-sighted.
From tomorrow,
give them two extra hours of class.
Test them every day.
If they can’t pass, don’t give them food.
Keep Liang Yuanheng confined.
If it wasn’t to avoid bringing bad luck
to Madam Miao,
he would’ve been punished
with 50 slashes at his back at least.
I think, we should tell Her Highness
and just send him out of the palace.
= The Hall of Happiness and Tranquility =
= Zhao Yanyu =
= Liaozi =
Your Majesty,
for today’s kitchen, the Imperial Kitchen…
She is so considerate and thoughtful.
She has thought of everything for Xinhe.
She wanted to take good care of her
but not to let anyone think
Xinhe is spoiled for being pregnant.
She knows clearly
officials wanted to
collude with the family with royal baby.
So she told me to be cautious.
Yet I blamed her.
I have my body relying on the nourishment of
the Yin and Yang of the world;
I grew up in a nest built by a loving mother
relying on the trees planted by my master.
Your Majesty,
Fan Xiwen wrote a good article indeed.
He made excellent and impressive metaphors
and sarcasms.
But does he really have to use
this ugly and fat bird with unpleasant sound
to reason?
That bird is the noise at dawn.
Why can’t he use some better-looking birds
in his article?
He used raven to express his feelings,
so his fellows raised ravens
to express their depression
for their unadopted but sincere advice.
Aren’t you worried
ravens from the whole palace
and even the whole capital
hear the news
and fly to the Hall of Peace?
Your hall will be covered
with black ravens.
At every down
they would nag at you at the same time,
So how can a sword be a sharp weapon
if curls once used?
How can a stone be a jade if changes once burned?
I’d rather die to be heard than live voicelessly.
I’d rather die to be heard than live voicelessly”
Your Majesty.
You are more sarcastic than
Sun Fu, Ouyang Xiu and Cai Xiang.
Alright,
I am an old raven
who nags all day long at you.
Then you might as well make a slingshot
and shoot the ugly raven away.
Do you have any wine
you made?
Moyao (name of the wine) still takes a few more days.
But I still have some Yingyu (name of the wine) left.
Today I’ll want some wine from you
to tell you an old thing
that happened in 1027A.D.
Don’t forget to send some food and clean water
to this kid every day.
I’ll try to ask Her Highness
to show him some mercy.
Okay.
I made half way there but then came back.
In the end, I still didn’t see
my birth mother.
The wet nurse said
she felt relieved
hearing Mr. Yan went there,
but sad too,
thinking that if he didn’t come in time,
I could at least have a chance
to see her in my life,
to call her mother.
It’s not.
It’s not because of him.
Actually Mr. Yan
didn’t change my mind.
He just gave me a reason
for being cruel
and unfilial.
She hadn’t told you
a single word
or even showed you
a little bit love,
was she being cruel?
She was not.
It’s because she loved you so much.
If you really
went to the Mausoleum and called her mother,
it would’ve ruined
all the sacrifice she made
for years.
All the willful things I did later
indeed…
In 1034 A.D.,
when you were blamed for
showing grace with public welfare by censors,
you were only in the palace
for less than half a year.
You were only 19 years old,
yet you already understood what an empress means.
Since then,
you’ve been cautious and self-restrained
but never gone out of your way to curry favor.
I don’t deserve it, Your Majesty.
Come here,
Danshu.
This time,
I must give Xinhe
the title
before the baby’s born.
I understand your intention
and your worries.
Censors are worried that she’ll
use my love and the child
to earn more power and bewitch me,
to collude with officials and disturb the court.
But I’m her husband,
and I’m like a brother to her.
I know she’s not that kind of person.
She will believe that
she and our child can rely on me.
Then why does she need to collude with officials?
She trusts not only me,
but also the Empress.
As for those censors,
they perform their duty to give advice.
If their advice
are not taken,
they will come to me.
When they found
what they are worried about doesn’t happen,
they will let it go.
After all,
I am different
from who I was in 1027A.D.,
and you
are not the Empress in 1034A.D.
I’ll come back later.
Okay.
After taking the throne for five years,
if I dare not to insist
something that does not go against morality and laws
for my fear for censors,
what will happen
if I want to
reform military affairs
and cut down redundant officials?
You are right,
I’ve been
shallow-brained.
Thank you, Your Majesty,
for not blaming me for
my shallowness and recklessness,
and explaining to me
all the reasons
and instructing me.
I don’t know why but
I always want to
talk to you about these,
the so-called “instructions”.
Your Majesty,
I shall
devote my entire life
to support you.
Danshu,
be honest with me.
I dare not lie to Your Majesty.
When you heard the news of being the Empress,
do you feel happy
or worried?
After all, the Caos is a noble family,
you should’ve known
what it takes to
support its glamour.
The day when I got the news
is the happiest day
in my life.
You are the perfect candidate for the Empress.
You are always happy
and never reconciled.
Even if you behaved childishly sometimes,
you would correct yourself immediately.
You are the best.
I’ve finished the wine,
time to go back.
Don’t feed the ravens
in the wind tomorrow.
You’re not a raven,
but the phoenix of Song.
You have a tall tree to rest.
You won’t be starving in the sky.
I am not a perfect emperor,
but I won’t let the phoenix
starve in the sky.
You flattered me.
No,
you deserve it.
You, as the Empress,
might be better than me
as the Emperor.
Let me tell you a secret.
All the things I told you today
are some excuses
I used to persuade myself
and you.
I have to give Xinhe this title
just because
I don’t want
my child,
to think his mother
is not loved by his father.
Before he’s born,
his mother served me for years,
who is cautious, tender, and obedient,
yet she was only a Lady of County.
I waited for so many years
for my
first baby.
But what I want for him the most
is not diligence, talents, or dignity,
but
his love to his father.
He won’t blame me
or despise me.
What’s wrong with His Majesty?
I wrote proposals to oppose
the promotion of Madam Miao.
He ignored it
and even commanded me to write the bestowal letter.
Wang Gongchen and Xia Song must be
more than willing to do this job.
Even if it’s not them,
there are
Wang Yaochen and Wen Yanbo
who didn’t say a word about it.
Come on.
Aren’t you waiting for me to say something like
His Majesty wants it immediately
and only gave you half a day,
since Ouyang Yongshu is not here,
you are the only one who can be counted on
with a ready pen.
That’s just your evil thought,
your evil thought!
Even if I am that arrogant,
I don’t need to show it
by writing a bestowal letter in half a day.
But I can’t understand.
Understand what?
His Majesty really wants to
promoted his most beloved Madam Miao.
But he’s worried people would
collude with Family Miao with this.
Writing the bestowal letter
is a perfect opportunity to get close to them.
You
are innocent and aloof,
aren’t you the best candidate?
= Wang Mansion =
My lord, someone from the palace
is waiting for you in the study.
He said he just
sent you something.
Minister Wang.
Any word from His Majesty?
This box is presented by
Madam Miao’s mother
to His Majesty
a few days ago.
His Majesty didn’t open it,
saying
Prime Minister Wang and Prime Minister Lv
are reviewing official performance.
His Majesty said
you could use it as a reference.
Your Highness,
plums are dried.
This wine is called Moyao.
When I was young at home,
my mother would make
Moyao and Yingyu.
The whole family loves them.
His Majesty does, too.
He has emptied your stock
yesterday.
So you need to make more immediately.
Huan,
you have a beautiful face
but one defect.
What is it?
A big mouth.
Your Highness, Mr. Zhang wants to see you.
Let him in.
Your Highness.
Maoze,
I have to seal these two jars
before sunset.
So don’t mind my manners.
What brings you here?
I am here to disturb Your Highness
for a new eunuch.
The Imperial Academy
made five names for a prince.
I’ll let you have a look.
It’s mainly about a princess’s name.
Last time you reviewed many names
but none of them was good enough.
Now there’s a new one,
please have a look.
= Huirou =
Huirou.
“Hui” means kindness,
and “rou” means benevolence.
The Books of Documents says
she is kind, benevolent and humble,
she cares and protects the people.
What a perfect name
for Your Majesty’s first daughter.
Care and protect the people.
She has been laid with duty
before she is born.
That’s her destiny!
I just feel
this kid has been castrated.
If he is sent out of the palace,
there’s no hope for him the entire life.
It’s no different with killing him.
Not avoiding taboo is
indeed a huge mistake in the palace.
Officer Ren’s treatment
is very appropriate.
You didn’t subject him
to torture
concerning it might bring bad luck to Madam Miao.
You’re very thoughtful.
I think
we can lock him in the woodshed first
to let him remember this lesson.
Madam Miao is going to give birth soon.
This kind of great event
will bring amnesty to the palace.
By then Officer Ren
will bring him to me.
I’ll see what I can do.
Yes, Your Highness.
♪ Loved you a gentleman yet got abandoned ♪
♪ Peach blossoms color the city ♪
♪ Spring breeze purified dusty memories ♪
♪ The gate of the vast palace opens ♪
♪ Bid farewell with wine after the glory ends ♪
♪ Outside the city a beautiful world unveils ♪
♪ Long-standing distance doesn’t alienate us ♪
♪ Keep you company behind the gate ♪
♪ Four seasons come and go ♪
♪ We only have each other in this cage ♪
♪ Wish to fly freely in the next life ♪
♪ Willows turn green flowers red ♪
♪ Sing aloud with wine ♪
♪ Hold your hands and go home together ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Life is long yet joy is little ♪