♪ Inside the state a city is built ♪
♪ Where a benevolent emperor resides ♪
♪ Court officials are brave and able ♪
♪ The empress is fair ♪
♪ Princes died too young to ascend the throne ♪
♪ Princesses are spoiled and fragile ♪
♪ Commoners are also the emperor’s children ♪
♪ All are living peacefully ♪
♪ Wish I could live a day for myself ♪
♪ Follow my heart and ethics without distractions ♪
♪ To be a good husband ♪
♪ To be a caring father ♪
♪ We were close when we first met ♪
♪ I hope I can control my desires ♪
♪ To be a worriless emperor and father ♪
♪ Prudence tops all virtues ♪
♪ People build the state ♪
= Held in the Lonely Castle =
♪ May the world be peaceful ♪
= Episode 48 =
When
the Third Princess passed away,
Lady Zhang requested to be demoted
and cut her pay to pray for the Fourth Princess.
Her love to children touches our hearts.
Unfortunately, she loses three daughters
and is still ill in bed.
She serves Your Majesty for ten years
and gives birth to three princesses.
Still, she’s only a Lady.
And she never asks for a promotion.
In danger, she risked her life
to save Your Majesty.
She didn’t protect His Majesty
out of a concubine’s love to His Majesty
but out of loyalty.
Seeing the Emperor in danger,
she, a defenseless woman though,
stood up to the ruffian to protect the Emperor.
She knew it was not in her power
but she also knew she had to stand up.
Her loyalty
is exemplary.
Madam Zhang does have it
to her credit.
You’ve made it clear, Xia Song.
I didn’t realize it.
I thought it was temper tantrum
and blamed her for her stubbornness.
I was up all night.
I’m exhausted.
Let’s call it a day.
The talk will be resumed
when Wang Sheng is arrested.
Is it true that father
is going to replace the Empress
with Madam Zhang?
Princess, please don’t speculate.
His Majesty treats Her Highness
with respect and trust.
It’s just…
It happened so suddenly last night
that the unsolved case
has to be investigated.
And the evidence about the adultery
with Her Highness’s maid is solid.
Only a few officials believe it.
His Majesty doesn’t.
Father is the Emperor.
He can do whatever he likes.
All his subjects wish
to please him,
so they say what he wants to hear.
They condemn Her Highness
and praise Madam Zhang
because father likes Madam Zhang
more than Her Highness,
don’t they?
No.
Princess, it’s not true.
His Majesty…
Father urges me to learn knowledge,
manners
and classical literature.
But he gives all his love to Madam Zhang,
the most domineering
and ill-mannered woman
in the palace.
Huaiji,
I told you before,
except father, Her Highness and mother,
you’re the closest partner to me.
I’m going to ask you a question.
Do not lie to me for father’s sake.
I never lied to you, princess,
and I never will.
Good.
Then answer me.
Does father refuse to marry me
to Cao Ping
because he’s decided
to replace Her Highness
with Madam Zhang?
All I know
is that you’re His Majesty’s favorite.
So…
so the man he chooses
must be the best for you.
Yes.
He doesn’t love Her Highness
and tries all means
to replace her with Madam Zhang.
Obviously, to him, the Caos aren’t the best.
Even if he makes Madam Zhang the Empress,
even if everyone else praises his wisdom,
I won’t
recognize that woman as the Empress
and neither will I address her accordingly.
Let father lock me up
with Her Highness.
Fetch me
the jade comb and the rhino pin
His Majesty gave me a few days ago.
Besides,
a few boxes of the blush I made,
several big pearls
from Cantonese businessmen.
Prepare two sets of gifts.
Send one
to Wang Gongchen’s wife
and the other to Wen Yanbo’s wife,
Mrs. Wen.
Tell them
I’m bored lately
and invite them over to talk
at their earliest convenience.
Yes,
I’ll prepare for it now.
But, madam, you’re not recovered.
I’ve taken the medicines.
I’ll take all the medicines
and the tonics.
I’ll fight for it.
OK.
Lantiao,
tell His Majesty tonight
that you’re pregnant
and you want me
to raise your child
whether it’s a girl or a boy.
I’ll ask His Majesty
to promote you
and I’ll take no more
of your children.
Otherwise,
you’ll end up
like Yuan Cailing.
Although I’m not the Empress,
I’m pretty sure
I can do that.
Madam,
I’m not sure of the pregnancy.
Don’t think that I’m inattentive.
As long as it’s about His Majesty,
I miss no details,
nothing at all.
Your Majesty,
Scholar Wen has arrived.
Be seated.
= Wen Yanbo, courtesy name Kuanfu =
Forgive me, Your Majesty,
what is it that you summon me
for?
You’re the Military Governor of Hebei Province
and are going to leave tomorrow
for Qinghe County to subdue the rebellion.
Here
are a few books for you.
I don’t understand.
Can they help me with the rebellion?
I know
you must have read all the battlefield reports
from Qinghe County,
proposals from local officials
and books on the art of war and formations
to subdue the rebellion as soon as possible.
But,
do you know well
about the rebel leader
and who he is?
The rebel leader, Wang Ze,
is from Zhuozhou.
He moved to Qinghe and herded sheep due to famine.
Later he enlisted in the Xuanyi Army
and was promoted a low-ranking officer.
He believes in Maitreya Sect,
deceives soldiers with heresies,
and instigates rebellion with the forces
from Dezhou and Jinan.
Maitreya Sect?
The Maitreya Sect
originates at the turn of the fifth century.
It advocates killing
and excels in drugs.
The drugs make people
forget their families
and kill indiscriminately.
The sect was destroyed by Yuan Yao of North Wei.
Your Majesty, you believe
knowledge about the cult
is helpful with the rebellion?
Your Majesty, do you have doubt
that last night’s incident is related to the cult?
I heard rumors
that the culprit lost his mind
and made unusual behaviors.
It’s more like that he took
a drug like Powder of Five Minerals.
Or maybe,
last night’s incident
is related to the rebellion in Qinghe County.
I want the rebellion to be subdued
and the culprit of last night’s incident
to be arrested.
But I
give books to you
for the consideration
of not rebellion and the incident only.
I’m thinking...
This man is merely a farmer.
How does he fall
to the cult which instigates killing
in the name of Buddha,
bewitch the others
to kill without mercy
and instigate the rebellion?
I can’t understand, either.
Kill one and you’ll become Level One Bodhisattva.
Such cruel and absurd speeches
spread like a plague
among the people.
Take these.
Be careful.
These are forbidden publications
which are used by the cult to poison mind.
You won’t find any in the Capital.
These are my personal collections.
These filthy publications
can’t be spread out among the people
and bewitch more.
However,
you need to know the origins of the cult
and how it bewitches the people.
We need to know what the cause is
to apply the right remedy to a disease
so that it can be cured for good.
You’re right, Your Majesty.
I’m too simple-minded.
All I can think of is to subdue the rebellion
and kill all rebels in Qinghe County.
Kill all rebels.
Aren’t rebels to be killed
once
the people of Song?
I’m touched and admire
Your Majesty’s love to the people.
I’m ashamed of my shallow views.
For days, I’ve been thinking
how to defeat the rebels.
It never occurs to me
why the once good people
were converted to rebels
and how to prevent the good people
from being turned to rebels.
You’ll leave the palace in a few days, won’t you?
Be very careful lately.
= Ms. Xiu =
Don’t…
Don’t contact with people outside the palace.
I was questioned
by the Bureau of Clothing today
if it belongs to a maid from the Hall of Peace.
There are rumors out there
that the maid is a painter’s lover.
And the painter
is the renowned artist, Cui Bai.
Anyway, be careful.
I don’t believe Ling’er
would engage in conspiracy.
It’ll be dangerous these days.
Be very careful.
Huaiji.
Your Majesty.
Are you still shocked by the incident?
What’s in your mind?
I’m curious
what magic the cult’s publications
you gave to Scholar Wen
have
to make people lose their minds.
When you’re outside,
do you know anyone who cheats people
out of their money with superstitions?
Yes.
My aunt is tightfisted,
but she spends thousands of coppers on rituals
each year
to protect our family business.
My mother
didn’t believe most of superstitions.
But each time someone suggested her
to pray to the Immortal of Letters
for my good scores in examination,
she was generous
and did everything she had been told.
She even made me drink tea made of burned incense.
There was a Granny Li.
She was unable to walk.
Physicians said it couldn’t be cured.
But she listened to a Taoist’s suggestion
that keeping a ghost can…
The reason why these words can bewitch people
is that people hold
obsession, greed
and unrealistic dreams.
It’s common in the people.
Is it not in scholars and officials,
noble ladies,
concubines,
Madam Zhang,
the Empress
or even me?
It’s not only
the Maitreya Sect that bewitches people.
Everything that poisons minds and behaviors
is the Maitreya Sect.
Is that why Your Majesty speak for Ling’er?
She’s just one of the victims.
If everyone can be bewitched,
she isn’t totally evil.
She didn’t engage in conspiracy.
So Your Majesty, you regard her as a poor victim
who should be spared.
Huaiji,
you’re the only person
who knows me.
But the Empress didn’t do anything wrong.
I don’t blame her.
I never did.
I’m just angry
and don’t understand.
She’s supposed to be my soul mate
but why she goes different ways from me each time.
= Kill =
He has to die.
Your Highness,
Wang Sheng died.
Yesterday,
Imperial Guards
found him in the tower
northwest of the city.
But Yang Huaimin ignored
your order to keep him alive
and ordered the guards
to dismember Wang Sheng on the scene.
Now all four culprits are dead.
There’s no way to find the people behind them.
In the end,
only a few chiefs
of the Imperial Security Agency
on duty that night were convicted.
That night,
it was Yang Huaimin who was on duty.
He should have been punished more severely.
But now,
Yang Jingzong and Deng Baoji
are exiled from the Capital.
Yang Huaimin is only demoted
to a servant in the palace.
Your Highness,
it’s so unfair.
Besides, I’m afraid…
That they’ll…
Don’t you say His Majesty will defend me?
What’s to be afraid of?
Qiuhe,
go back and pack up.
Tomorrow morning,
you can go home.
Your Majesty,
I’ve gone through
the proposals
submitted by all the officials.
What do they say?
Right Counselor
and Assistant Administrator, Wen Yanbo,
Zhang Fangping of the Three Ministries,
Deputy Executive of Privy Council, Wu Yu
think the disposition is proper.
But they propose a thorough background
and behavior check on all Imperial Guards
and to cut off those who take drugs,
drink excessively
and conduct ill manners.
Chief Executive of Privy Council, Xia Song proposes
to investigate
if the four are cult members
or collude with rebels in Qinghe County.
Same with Wang Zhi from Remonstrance Bureau,
he agrees with an investigation within the palace
to see if there are…
if there are maids having affairs with guards
or even eunuchs.
If there are,
they should be punished.
And their superiors should be questioned
if they help cover for them.
Deputy Censor, Yu Zhouxun,
Censor, Zhang Bian
and Censor, He Tan
impeach Yang Huaimin.
They believe
that night,
Yang Huaimin was on duty.
But he’s derelict in duty.
The other managers of the Imperial Security Agency
have been exiled.
However, Yang Huaimin can stay in the Capital.
The punishment on him is too lenient.
Everyone believes it’s unfair.
Imperial Guards lost mind due to drugs
and excessive drinking.
They set fire and startled the Emperor.
Those Imperial Guards should be punished.
Five men are exiled.
They deserve it.
= Madam Yu =
But why could Yang Huaimin
who’s supposed to be punished severely
secure a position in the Capital?
It’s said
it was Xia Song
who proposed to His Majesty
that Yang should be questioned
in the palace.
He and Yang Huaimin are close.
I guess he taught him
how to answer the questions
to shirk responsibility.
They’re lenient on those close with Lady Zhang
and strict with the others.
According to my sister-in-law,
though former Deputy Censor, Wang Gongchen
has been promoted to the Three Ministries,
the censor in charge of the questioning
is promoted by him.
His wife and Madam Zhang
are good friends.
He Tan accuses that Yang Huaimin indulged
his subordinates to kill the culprit
in order to destroy evidence
and the witnesses.
He’s suspicious.
Huaiji,
let me ask you.
If we run an investigation,
what are the possible results?
What consequences
will the results lead to?
Don’t pretend you don’t know.
I order you to be honest.
You serve me so long.
If you don’t have your opinions,
then I’m completely wrong about you.
Even if it’s out of the imperial rules,
a lie to your emperor
is a lie.
Without solid proof
that the four guards were under instigation,
now that
they’re all dead,
we can only call
guards in charge of the security
of Your Majesty’s chamber to account.
Given the current punishment,
perhaps Yang Huaimin
deserves more severe punishment.
Go on.
If the four of them
were Maitreya Sect members
and collaborated with rebels in Qinghe County,
then it was a well-planned
conspiracy.
It should be handed to Court of Judicial Review
and the Censorate to question their chiefs,
officials who promoted them
to be guards of the Hall of Politics
and all officials related
to the case.
It might be even related
to ministers.
If in the investigation,
we find
ambiguous evidence
proving Yuan Cailing is related
to the guard’s conspiracy
and she’s been executed by Her Highness,
hence couldn’t authenticate the evidence,
then…
then Her Highness
is unable to prove her innocence
and her integrity will be questioned.
Even Your Majesty trusts Her Highness,
it’s hard to stop others’ judgments.
Your Majesty,
if I’m not too bold,
maybe it’s a trap.
It’s not impossible.
To frame the Empress?
Why?
Who will it be?
You were
with Madam Zhang that day all the time.
Do you think
she was faking it?
Madam Zhang’s anxiety was real.
She almost went mad.
I don’t believe she was faking it.
Yes.
She’s domineering,
wayward
and hostile.
But she never fakes her feelings.
So,
the possible consequence of the investigation
is unrest in the court,
ministers found guilty,
the Empress’s integrity stained
or Madam Zhang being hurt.
They’re like vases that could be broken
due to a few rats.
Or in other words,
if we repel cockroaches on jade vases,
we might not succeed,
but might break the jade vases
that Your Majesty holds dear.
Huaiji,
make me
a cup of tea.
Ping.
Princess.
Ping,
what are you doing here?
= Cao Yi’s Son Cao Ping =
My father and I took deer
and delicacies from mountains to Her Highness.
They have business to talk.
So I’m excused.
As a young man, I dreamed to build a strong nation
and to be diligent in my duty.
I hoped I could uphold virtues,
make friends with decent men
and spend all my life
making the politics clean and just
and the nation peaceful.
However, after all the years,
I realize one thing
that daylight is paired with night,
and flowers and fruits attract insects.
The good and evil
are mixed up.
The emperor is supposed to tell them apart
and safeguard good and remove evil.
But there isn’t
a clear line setting them apart.
The man on a stallion
who brings peace to the people
is only in stories.
Get up.
Don’t be nervous.
It’s not a serious question.
I’m just
having a hard time
and afraid to be seen through
yet couldn’t help
wishing someone could understand.
In the past,
I instructed you
on purpose
that when Zui Xinglai grows up,
there could be a trustworthy,
smart and prudent man
taking care of him
and telling him what’s right and wrong.
See?
However considerate the plan is,
it couldn’t change Heaven’s will.
♪ In drum beats, it’s dawn again ♪
♪ In time, we all grow old ♪
♪Let’s pray for good days ♪
♪ To sing ♪
♪ Proud Fisherman ♪
♪ The river and sky are both vast ♪
♪ No one can be young forever ♪
♪ Don’t be afraid to be drunk and to laugh ♪
♪ As you should know ♪
♪ Sorrow in life never falls short ♪
Princess,
you should go back.
Princess.
Huaiji,
take me back.
I went to Pavilion of Phoenix earlier.
Xiao Ye’er told me you were out,
probably went to His Majesty.
I just came back from His Majesty’s chamber.
I know you weren’t there.
So I think
you may be bored
and come out for a walk.
Do you come
to Pavilion of Phoenix on father’s order
to send snacks
or toys?
I come for you, princess.
Not on father’s order?
You come for me?
I come to you
mainly to tell you
that I think
His Majesty recognizes Her Highness’s importance.
His Majesty respects and trusts
Her Highness all the time.
It’s just others might not see it.
Please don’t let their misunderstanding
misguide your judgment.
OK.
I won’t trust others.
I trust you.
Qiuhe.
Ms. Xiu, is everything all right?
Mr. Zhang asks you to go
to him at the Imperial Office Bureau immediately.
He said a censor named Wang Zhi
reported
that a culprit is related to Her Highness’s maid.
That the conspiracy started in the Hall of Peace.
He strongly proposed His Majesty to look into it.
And he said
rumors point to a maid
of the Hall of Peace
who has affairs with an Imperial Artist
and should be investigated.
If necessary,
torture will be used.
This is a copy of His Majesty’s edict
to depose Empress Guo.
Take it.
Go to the Cabinet and wait outside.
Censor He is debating
with Prime Minister Chen today
on the Imperial Guards.
At dusk,
they’ll come out.
Run over
and pretend to carelessly
drop the edict on the ground and open
so they can see.
If they ask questions,
tell them
Chief Xia
asks you to get it for him.
Will Chen Zhizhong defend Her Highness?
The ministers
don’t want to see an unrest palace
or that the favorite concubine
who colludes with officials
and indulges her families.
I’ll go to the Cabinet now.
Depose the empress?
Why do you hold the edict written ten years ago?
His Majesty is meeting Chief Xia
and Censor Wang
for the last two hours.
Let’s go to Hall of Politics
and meet His Majesty.
Cui Bai is only a painter
who has nothing to do with politics.
= Wang Zhi, courtesy name Zhizhi =
But as far as I know,
he’s close with Ouyang Xiu, Cai Xiang,
Mei Yaochen and Su Shunqin.
It’s possible that they talked about politics
in the name of poems and paintings.
Is it an important matter?
Your Majesty,
Chen Zhizhong, He Tan and Liang Shi
are waiting outside.
They said they have a crucial matter to report.
Since it’s crucial,
let’s discuss together.
I heard
= He Tan, courtesy name Shengcong =
some people intend to defame
the Empress for a maid’s affair.
I think
it aims to stir up the harem
and influence the court.
They should be sentenced to death
for their evil intention.
Censor He,
should we look into the conspiracy?
Now a solid evidence
is that one of the culprits
has an affair with Her Highness’s maid.
Although the maid
has been executed by Her Highness,
should we abort the investigation?
What if there are other maids
in Her Highness’s chamber colluding with officials?
We do need to look into the conspiracy.
But I think
the first to be investigated
is the man on duty
that night, Yang Huaimin.
He was in charge of palace security that night.
And he found nothing wrong.
Therefore, the culprit broke into the palace,
set fire and hurt people.
Then he disobeyed a
direct order which urges him to keep the man alive
and killed the only witness.
Don’t you think
he’s the prime suspect of the conspiracy?
I strongly advise Your Majesty
to hold Yang Huaimin accountable
and investigate if Yang Huaimin
colludes with the culprit.
I propose that Your Majesty
order an investigation on people
close to the deceased maid, Yuan Cailing.
It’s out of your loyalty that you worry
about the palace security
and propose a thorough investigation.
But,
for these years,
the harem has been harmonious
under the Empress’s lead.
All concubines behave accordingly.
All eunuchs and maids perform their duties.
I have no worries about them.
I didn’t sleep well lately.
I’m tired.
Why don’t you go home
and have some rest?
Your Majesty.
What?
The Empress asks for me?
Your Majesty made a promise to me years ago
that I can ask a favor from Your Majesty
as long as it’s not against the laws
or the palace rules,
Your Majesty will do me the favor.
Do you remember, Your Majesty?
I do.
If I’m not too bold,
I’d like to ask Your Majesty to honor your words.
Mr. Zhang.
Yes?
the Prime Minister,
the Chief Executive and Censor He
just left the Hall of Politics.
It’s dark and the palace gates have been closed.
They can’t get out
so they’ll spend the night at Scholar Academy.
They kindly ask you
to sign on the Imperial Office Bureau for them.
They went to the Scholar Academy.
Will the gate be locked?
No.
They’re just staying for the night,
not drawing up edict.
♪ Memory is the breath of deep sleep ♪
♪ It emerges in every crevice ♪
♪ Shallow dreams are like
copper bells under eaves ♪
♪ Woken up when the wind blows ♪
♪ Fate is predetermined ♪
♪ Struggle to break out of it ♪
♪ Who will battle fate with me ♪
♪ Regardless of the ending ♪
♪ Peach branches shake in the spring breeze ♪
♪ Walls sigh, the wind is silent ♪
♪ The boy beside the wall is unaware of it ♪
♪ He plays with the butterfly, gathering honey ♪
♪ Peach blossoms tell a love story ♪
♪ About a couple who lives happily ♪
♪ Unluckily deep love comes to nowhere ♪
♪ All fated,
drawing Double Happiness in autumn ♪
♪ Peach branches shake in the spring breeze ♪
♪ Walls sigh, the wind is silent ♪
♪ The boy beside the wall is unaware of it ♪
♪ He plays with the butterfly gathering honey ♪
♪ Peach blossoms tell a love story ♪
♪ About a couple who lives happily ♪
♪ Unluckily deep love comes to nowhere ♪
♪ All fated,
drawing Double Happiness in autumn ♪