♪ Inside the state a city is built ♪
♪ Where a benevolent emperor resides ♪
♪ Court officials are brave and able ♪
♪ The empress is fair ♪
♪ Princes died too young to ascend the throne ♪
♪ Princesses are spoiled and fragile ♪
♪ Commoners are also the emperor’s children ♪
♪ All are living peacefully ♪
♪ Wish I could live a day for myself ♪
♪ Follow my heart and ethics without distractions ♪
♪ To be a good husband ♪
♪ To be a caring father ♪
♪ We were close when we first met ♪
♪ I hope I can control my desires ♪
♪ To be a worriless emperor and father ♪
♪ Prudence tops all virtues ♪
♪ People build the state ♪
= Held in the Lonely Castle =
♪ May the world be peaceful ♪
= Episode 38 =
The other day,
Fan proposed eight measures for Shaanxi,
including canceling military fields,
drilling wells to bury dead people
and relieving refugees in Shaanxi.
I reviewed them.
Today,
I’d like to discuss about teaching military books.
Scholars only honor passing the imperial exam.
= Fan Zhongyan, courtesy name Xiwen =
So, few people in Directorate of Education
are good at martial arts.
At the border, some soldiers have martial arts
and are familiar with border affairs,
but they haven’t read military books
and don’t know how to be good generals.
I don’t think
we need a separate department for martial arts.
If some scholars enjoy military books
or some border soldiers are smart,
we can pick a few of them
and teach them military books and strategies.
In this case, maybe some of them
will become competent generals.
Not to mention if this measure can be taken,
Fan is at least generous enough
to care for our nation,
without partiality for literature or martial arts.
You should take him as an example.
It’s wise of you, Your Majesty.
I’ve something else to tell you, Your Majesty.
Go ahead.
If you think
some of the measures I’ve proposed
can be taken...
Such measures
haven’t been tried at the border yet.
I thought about them carefully.
But they still couldn’t be perfect
and must be corrected in time.
So, I’d like to go to Shaanxi personally
for inspection and supervision.
I’ll think about it carefully.
Deputy Officer Yang, please kindly
announce the edict.
Get up, Mrs. Xue.
I’m not ordered to come here.
I’m just out for some business
and get you to the palace for Madam Zhang.
She feels bored,
and wants you to talk with her.
Why is there grass and mud on you?
Have you rolled
on the grass?
He pounced on me first.
She was crafty.
I caught her, but she wanted to cheat.
You’re getting more voluble.
Why is here a pimple?
Can it be an insect bite?
A mosquito bite. I feel a bit itchy.
Why don’t you go get me some ointment?
After she was deceased,
I felt my heart broken.
I had wanted to die with her.
But when I woke up this morning,
I saw His Majesty stare at me,
sad,
distressed
and scared.
Just like I was scared
when Chuyue was badly ill.
So, I swore to myself that
I must get better.
I can’t make him as sad as I was.
His Majesty cares for you the most.
You know that.
So, even for his sake,
you must get better soon.
So, today,
I take medicine regularly
and try to have more food.
I even invite you for a talk.
I’m so envious of you.
Your husband remarried you.
But you’re the only wife
he has.
However sad he feels for your sister,
he’s getting nicer to you.
And you have your own children.
My husband is too stubborn.
I’m afraid what he’s doing
will bring him great misfortune.
The proposal from Deputy Censor Wang Gongchen,
says everything about
= Let’s talk about Teng abusing public expenses. =
my wisdom and benevolence.
He pretends to be mad at home, disheveled.
He’s forcing me.
He’s forcing me to punish him
and kill him.
He’s forcing me to be an unworthy man
against ancestral rules.
He’s forcing me to be a fatuous emperor.
Pick it up.
I can’t just kill him.
Do you think he’s not afraid of death?
He just knows I can’t severely punish him.
Trapped in
the moral high ground of benevolence,
I have to watch him make a scene.
Your Majesty.
Manager Zhang Maoze asked to see you.
Get him in.
Zuixinglai was all right this morning.
I watched him eat two stuffed buns
and a dish of pickles
before I went to help Her Highness
with the banquet in a couple of days.
When I came back at dusk,
I found him a bit listless with no appetite.
I coaxed him into having some food.
But he threw up one hour later.
After he lay in bed, he threw up twice again.
I wonder if he has a heatstroke.
So, I want you to check on him.
After I heard of the rumor,
I checked on that
and tracked down to
the letters of collusion for treason.
But as far as I see,
Shi Jie is a mere scholar.
Fu Bi isn’t a powerful official.
They have no adherents, either.
Meanwhile, they’re receiving favor from you.
The rumor goes that
they’re going to force you to abdicate
and support a new emperor.
It makes no sense at all.
We found the letters
Shi Jie wrote to Fu Bi.
We determined it’s
Shi Jie’s handwriting.
But we haven’t found
any arrangements for treason yet.
I can keep investigating on it.
If they really want to do something,
I think we’ll find it out.
I don’t need you
to confirm
if Shi Jie wants to rebel.
Even if he wants,
he isn’t powerful enough.
You want me to check out who started the rumor?
It’s easy to find out, too.
Why do we bother to
find out such an easy truth?
Some royal officials turn out to make a scene.
Some obedient officials turn out to play tricks.
Are they afraid of punishment?
They have the support from ancestral rules,
the nation and the people.
That’s all I care.
They’re not afraid of me at all.
They’re pushing me.
Your Majesty.
Ask the Cabinet to draft a decree.
Fan Zhongyan are insightful to propose
the eight measures for Shaanxi
and they will be very helpful.
He’ll be sent to Shaanxi
for inspection.
Teng Zongliang was slightly punished
when he was demoted for abusing public funds.
Get him demoted again
and banished to Yueyang, Yuezhou.
Then,
let Fu Bi and Shi Jie know that.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I can’t mess up with them.
I...
I don’t understand too much.
= Liang Huaiji =
From the books I read,
I know
wise emperors of dynasties
and ancestors of our nation
have a lot of scruples
and they don’t mess up with officials.
All right.
I coax shrewish officials.
I pretend not to know tricks they make.
I must protect those
who work for me,
whether they’re obedient or not.
Huaiji, you’re wrong.
Not only wise emperors have scruples.
Every emperor who doesn’t want to lose his nation
has scruples in his heart.
It’s late.
Don’t bother to copy them.
I’m going to see Madam Zhang.
Go to Pavilion of Phoenix
and send some toys
to Zuixinglai and Huirou.
Huaiji, listen.
Is there a flying cricket?
Sorry, Your Majesty, I don’t know.
Why do you apologize again?
It doesn’t matter.
Last month in Pavilion of Phoenix,
Zuixinglai saw Huirou’s painting.
He said that was a common cricket.
But Huirou told him
it was a flying cricket.
A bit different from a common cricket.
But it chirps more beautifully.
Zuixinglai wanted
to catch a living flying cricket right away.
But that day,
he failed to recite the poem
and had to copy it for ten times.
He couldn’t go.
So, Your Majesty,
the insect toy you ask me to take to little prince
that can move and chirp...
That’s a flying cricket?
I asked the skilled craftsmen
with Directorate of Astronomy
to make it specially for him.
It moves and chirps.
But don’t tell him
I specially make him
such a valuable thing.
Tell him
I just saw it in the storehouse
and give it to him for fun.
Oh, I see.
You care for little prince
and want to make him happy.
But you must pretend to be very serious
in case he’s spoilt
and can’t rule the nation after growing up.
You’ve worked for me for years.
You’ve learnt
more than what a local official has learnt
after working for two or three years.
But you’ve never
changed your mind.
I’m right about you.
Huaiji.
I’ve told Ren Shouzhong to
get you promoted.
Pick a fine day
and you’ll move to Pavilion of Phoenix,
taking care of Zuixinglai.
What? You don’t like it?
I...
I like it.
I will
take good care of little prince.
I...
I understand.
I know you’re a loyal boy.
That’s why I ask you
to stay with my son.
You shall care for him and defend him.
Sometimes you shall exhort him, too.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Why does he have an even higher temperature
than he did one hour ago?
He isn’t having a heatstroke.
The prince is honorable.
I think
the Head should be asked
to check on him.
I know
I shouldn’t have mentioned the politics.
But I still want to have a try.
All the other ladies
listen to Her Highness.
Only Mrs. Xue gets on well with me.
She has dinner with me
and makes me delicious snacks.
I’ve been feeling depressed lately.
So I ask her to come and stay with me.
If you kill Wang Gongchen,
she would certainly die, too.
Then I’ll lose my only friend.
When has any official been killed?
If you banish him from the Capital
to somewhere barren,
Mrs. Xue can’t
often come to me, either.
Your Majesty, I’m begging you.
Don’t punish Deputy Censor Wang.
Look.
He reported honestly,
for the good of our nation.
Besides,
maybe...
maybe Fan Zhongyan showed partiality.
Ouyang Xiu has been
framing Deputy Censor Wang up.
And Teng Zongliang...
He hasn’t been cleared of
abusing public funds.
The demotion isn’t a serious punishment.
Your Majesty?
Bihan.
You don’t know politics. Don’t talk nonsense.
I’m not talking about politics.
I just want to
plead for Mrs. Xue’s husband.
You want me to practice favoritism?
He will not leave the Capital.
Don’t worry.
You shall no longer talk about politics
or ask for partiality for anyone else.
Do you mean you won’t punish him?
Didn’t I say?
He won’t leave the Capital.
If you feel bored,
feel free to bring Mrs. Xue here.
But you must promise me
to stop worrying
and get healthy.
What’s wrong?
Why are you crying?
I know I’m making things difficult for you.
Unexpectedly,
you didn’t scold me,
but complied with my request.
As you said,
Wang Gongchen is a loyal official.
He won’t leave the Capital, anyway.
But you shall
no longer talk about politics.
You like Mrs. Xue.
Ask her to come and make you happy.
Then you’ll get better soon.
Don’t worry, Your Majesty.
Now I believe that
you truly care for me.
I will get better
and stay with you all my life.
I won’t leave you,
whatever happens.
Sir.
His fever is brought down a little.
And he’s sleeping soundly.
Is he all right?
Madam Miao.
We had a consultation after checking on him.
We think little prince has pathogenic heat.
After taking some medicine to relieve heat,
he’s getting better as expected.
Lusi.
No. No. No.
Madam Miao, little prince is too young
and he’s suddenly ill.
He had a rather high fever just now.
Though he’s getting better,
I’m afraid he’ll get worse at night.
Please give us some bamboo mats.
We’re going to stay overnight,
guarding him.
Go get them.
Get back to sleep.
I’m not hot.
I’ll wait here
until Zuixinglai gets better.
I’m not sleepy. Princess.
I’m not sleepy at all.
Princess.
- Princess. - Huaiji, what brings you here?
Father knows that Zuixinglai is ill?
His Majesty asked me to bring some toys
to you and little prince.
What? the prince is ill?
Nonsense.
= Shi Jie, courtesy name Shoudao =
Nonsense!
I admire His Majesty so much.
How would I ever rebel?
How would I?
Someone is framing me up.
That’s it.
I’ll refute!
Who is framing me up?
Who is he on earth?
= Fu Bi’s Wife Yan Qingsu =
Someone must be trying to
kill you and Mr. Shi.
His Majesty is wise.
He won’t be deceived, will he?
But an emperor is always suspicious.
Will His Majesty
have a grudge against you?
Darling.
Do Mr. Fan and Mr. Han know this?
Shall I
go and discuss with father
for some instructions?
No. I’m going directly to the palace
and meet Her Highness.
Qingsu.
You’re showing His Majesty and other officials
how I can gang up.
In the imperial court,
my good friends are important officials.
At home, my father-in-law is a minister.
My wife often goes to the palace
and gets on well the Empress,
the ruler of the imperial harem.
In this way,
seems like
I’m truly capable of
forcing the Emperor.
What...
What should we do then?
Mr. Fan has defended Teng Zongliang
and saved him.
However, those who are against the reform
hate him more.
Mr. Fan said,
in more than one year since the reform,
half of redundant officials have been fired.
It’s a kind of success.
The war has ceased.
It’s time to build a stable society
and develop agriculture and business.
We’re yet trying to exterminate evil officials
and get rid of corruption.
This action
will certainly bring risks.
These guys
are mortally exaggerating such risks
and try to convince His Majesty.
Darling.
I shouldn’t have interfered
with such an important thing.
Whatever you do,
I’ll just follow you.
But...
you’re framed up for treason.
I only want you
to think of a retreat
for our children.
Tomorrow, I’m going to apply
for leaving the Capital.
It was until now
did I realize
the hatred and objection
resulted from the complete removal
of maladministration.
I don’t want
the nation or the people to suffer, either.
Huirou, look.
What a nice bracelet and pendant!
Aren’t they
what you thought of
when you learnt to draw maids last month?
Your father said you draw the maid
with a wrong specification.
In fact, he kept that in mind,
had them forged
and sent to you.
He didn’t.
According to Huaiji, father said
a senior eunuch found them accidentally
when he was cleaning
the storehouse.
Since your father said so,
let it be.
But what a coincidence!
What you like
and what Zuixinglai likes,
you have them easily
when someone searches the storehouse.
But Zuixinglai is sick.
He just said he missed father.
Why didn’t you ask Huaiji
to tell father
and bring him here?
Your father is busy with business.
Her Highness gave an order
and the head of physicians has come.
Zuixinglai is better.
Besides...
Besides, father is in the Pavilion of Luan.
Huaiji didn’t tell us.
But everyone in the palace knows that.
In recent months,
father has taken the Pavilion of Luan
as his own palace.
Watch your tongue, Huirou.
It’s not
what you should say.
Madam.
Couches and snacks for physicians
are ready.
Huaiji.
Tonight, the head of physicians will stay
with another two physicians.
I’m going there.
Why don’t you stay with Huirou?
Aye.
Don’t go.
You can’t fall asleep.
I’ll go get some soothing incense.
Don’t go, brother.
Princess, you mustn’t call me like that.
Brother.
Why don’t you close your eyes?
I’m not leaving.
If I close my eyes,
I can’t feel you around.
When you close your eyes,
I can still talk with you.
Huaiji, why did you come and work at the palace?
Because my family is poor.
What does poor mean?
It means
we don’t have any money.
But I don’t have much money, either.
Every day,
mother only gives me twelve coppers.
If I lose it in playing the game,
she won’t give me any.
If I win,
she’ll give all my money
to whoever plays with me.
I have no money at last.
I’m also poor, aren’t I?
No, princess.
Being poor means having little to eat or wear.
You may not even have any rice.
You’ll only eat sweet potatoes every day.
But sweet potatoes taste good.
Once I was hungry,
you got me a sweet potato in the kitchen
and that tasted the best.
I’m going to have sweet potatoes every day.
For example,
if you have something,
but others don’t.
And they are in urgent need of it.
They’re poor,
compared with you.
Look.
You have many beautiful clothes.
But your maids don’t have
what you have.
It means
they’re poorer than you.
I kind of understand.
Others have many clothes
and sweet potatoes,
but your family didn’t have
so many clothes
or sweet potatoes for you.
They had to send you here.
Sort of.
I see.
Qiuhe is poorer than me.
Because I have much free time,
but she’s working every day.
She barely has her own time.
Madam Yu is poorer than mother.
Because mother is a senior concubine.
But Madam Yu is inferior.
She has less monthly pay
and fewer festival rewards.
What about
Madam Zhang and Her Highness?
Which one of them is poorer?
Madam Zhang wants to be the Empress.
But she isn’t.
Once she wanted the red umbrella on her sedan
which is used by the Empress,
and also wanted as many guards
as the Empress,
officials scolded her.
But father often
visits Madam Zhang.
Recently, he even goes there every day.
Madam Zhang has lost Yaoyao.
But Her Highness doesn’t have any child yet.
So, Her Highness is poorer.
Get to sleep, princess.
Forget it.
Madam Zhang is very poor, too.
Her daughters died.
Father is poor, too.
Officials don’t let father do
what he wants to do.
I can’t mess up with them.
Huaiji, you’re wrong.
Not only wise emperors have scruples.
Every emperor who doesn’t want to lose his nation
has scruples in his heart.
How is Zuixinglai now?
His fever is gone.
But he gets more listless.
He had porridge this morning, but brought it up.
Your Highness. Madam Miao.
Last night, His Majesty asked Huaiji
to bring Huirou and Zuixinglai
some toys.
I was staying with Zuixinglai
and settling down the physicians.
Huirou was worried, too.
I asked Huaiji to stay with her overnight.
How is His Majesty lately?
He is fine.
But he’s too busy with national affairs.
He reviews proposals and meets officials
until eight o’clock every day.
You always stay with His Majesty
when he reviews proposals.
You don’t need to take care of his living.
But when His Majesty is working,
you should pay more attention
if he’s tired or thirty.
Liaozi and the other are very careful.
If His Majesty keeps working
for two hours,
they’ll try to
bring some tea, snacks and fruit
or have a chat with him.
His Majesty is right about you.
Your Highness. Madam Miao.
I’ve got something to say.
You look much better today.
I think
you’ll recover soon.
Since I thought it through,
I feel much better.
His Majesty cares for me.
I must recover soon,
even for his sake.
That would be nice.
Forget all the unhappy
and sad things.
And we will...
I can’t forget that.
I won’t, either.
My daughter
is my precious treasure.
I won’t let her die for nothing.
The maid who saw Yaoyao have an attack
and ran away,
I will find her,
find out what happened
and I will skin her.
Aunt.
Go tell my uncle,
Wang Gongchen,
and Chief Xia.
Tell them.
If anyone of them
finds that good-for-nothing outside the palace,
I swear
I will try my best
to get him high position and wealth.
Go ask a physician to check on Huirou.
Your Highness.
I had the pimple yesterday.
I guess it was some sort of
insect bite.
It itched.
But it was okay later.
This morning,
when the maid combed my hair,
Huaiji was nervous when he saw it.
You’re a girl.
If a bite isn’t healed,
it’s bad to have a scar.
It’s careful of Huaiji.
Your Highness, you’re experienced.
I guess you’ve realized
it’s not a bite of any common insect,
but the tick.
I’ll ask someone to fetch appliances
from the Imperial Hospital
to get the tick out and kill it.
Off you go.
Fu Bi sounds reasonable.
I also think
Khitan is at daggers drawn with Xixia.
They won’t attack Dai’er people
with Xixia.
If we station troops on the border hastily,
we’ll fall for the trick.
It’s wise of you, Your Majesty.
I quite agree with
the eight measures proposed by Fan.
I thought about it carefully last night.
A lot waits to be done after the end of the war.
We really need to send a capable official there
who is honest, loyal and persistent
with rich experience in
governing the border.
After thinking about it carefully,
I think Fan is the best candidate.
You make sense, Your Majesty.
= Su Shunqin, courtesy name Zimei =
But Minister Fan takes care of
many state affairs.
If he’s suddenly transferred,
I’m afraid state affairs might be affected.
Your Majesty.
I quite agree with Su Shunqin.
There is always an order of priority.
The reform...
The...
Yes, there is always an order of priority.
But for a large nation,
there must be a foundation and a roof.
The peace of the border is the foundation.
If our nation isn’t in peace,
how can we carry on with the reform?
Aye, Your Majesty.
Xiwen.
I won’t let you down, Your Majesty.
In recent months,
disasters happen frequently in Hebei.
A loyal and capable official
should go there for inspection.
Fu Bi, you’ve been to Khitan several times
to defend our nation.
You enjoy a high prestige in border provinces.
Would you like to go?
Aye, Your Majesty.
I’m afraid there’s disturbance in disasters.
The problem shall be solved immediately.
I’d like to go with light luggage
and few attendants
early tomorrow morning.
Has Deputy Censor Wang Gongchen come?
Yes.
= Jia Changchao, courtesy name Ziming =
But he didn’t dare to come in.
He’s waiting outside until being summoned.
Didn’t dare to come in?
He abandoned his uniform
and showed his aspiration with a hunger strike.
What else is he afraid of?
Your Majesty, will...
If he’s properly dressed today,
get him in.
Is she all right
after the tick is pulled out?
Are there still other ticks?
Madam.
Lusi and I checked
all over the princess.
No more ticks are found.
Is it toxic?
The tick sucks blood,
and meanwhile injects toxin into human body.
It was just like the anesthetic.
So, the princess didn’t feel anything.
With the toxin in the body,
people feel differently.
Some might be badly ill.
Some might only ache for days.
Is Zuixinglai all right?
We both rolled on the grass.
Go check carefully
if there are any ticks on Zuixinglai.
Skin behind his ears, on his head
and even the private parts.
Check if there are any ticks on him too.
Aye.
♪ Loved you a gentleman yet got abandoned ♪
♪ Peach blossoms color the city ♪
♪ Spring breeze purified dusty memories ♪
♪ The gate of the vast palace opens ♪
♪ Bid farewell with wine after the glory ends ♪
♪ Outside the city a beautiful world unveils ♪
♪ Long-standing distance doesn’t alienate us ♪
♪ Keep you company behind the gate ♪
♪ Four seasons come and go ♪
♪ We only have each other in this cage ♪
♪ Wish to fly freely in the next life ♪
♪ Willows turn green flowers red ♪
♪ Sing aloud with wine ♪
♪ Hold your hands and go home together ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Be a pair of swallows in the next life ♪
♪ Build the nest and protect the nestlings ♪
♪ The howling wind ♪
♪ Woke me up from the dream ♪
♪ Life is long yet joy is little ♪