2010 ⬇️ 2004, Newlywed Time
This is too strong, so take it out.
This is too hard on your stomach, so take it out.
Everything else is okay.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I've placed the medicine you need in here. So take these.
It's because if your body builds up a tolerance to it, then everything will be bad. Okay?
Honey, you're the only one who takes care of my body like this. You're better than a doctor.
Of course. The doctor is the one who treats you for something that hurts right now.
But, honey, I'm the one who'll be with you for the rest of your life.
Right, right, right?
- Thank you.
- Ah, you don't have to be thankful over this.
- You're a bit cool.
- Cool?
- Yeah.
- You've been anemic these days.
I took out the ones that cause anemia, so be sure to take them.
Are you listening to me?
Okay, I got it.
At some point, we take things for granted because they're shielded by familiarity and comfort.
Hey, take that off.
The wrist area was dirty. Come in quickly and change.
No, I'm lazy. Wearing this twice isn't going to kill anybody.
When others see this, they'll talk badly about you.
I already washed this. Why are you trying to wear that instead? Come in quickly.
But, I'm late.
The generosity of my wife and happiness we're granted...
We lived thinking that's the way things were supposed to be.
Mom, come quickly.
We're late, Mom.
But, the truth that is revealed after losing everything,
No one's existence should be taken for granted.
Episode 10, Nothing should be taken for granted
2005 ⬇︎ 1999 Gangreung
What is this? You woke up early.
You're up now?
I felt like I was wasting time. I couldn't sleep at all.
Do you remember this place?
Well, yeah, a little.
Weren't there fireflies here?
Oh, there were?
You came looking for me yesterday.
You seemed to have gone somewhere yesterday.
Yeah. I was just walking around the neighborhood.
The air is really nice. Whether it's because it's the countryside or the past.
Is this nice?
Yeah, it is.
Then, it's whatever.
What is?
Since you saw them anyway, it's okay. Since it's nice, it's okay.
Cheon Seol, what are you doing?
Oh? I was cleaning things up in the car.
You're meticulous as always. Thanks.
You were tipsy when I saw you yesterday. You didn't cause trouble, did you?
- When did I cause trouble?
- I'm not talking to you.
- Hey, before we leave, make sure you check your belongings to see if anything is damaged.
- What's he saying?
No...
What's this?
Before we leave, let's contact the others and... What's this?
What's with this? Star...
Star01
You guys are pitiful. I'll free you.
One.
Aigoo...
Cheon Seol.
I mean, I don't really know why I did this. I didn't do it on purpose!
What's wrong with you?
Come here!
Hey!!
They'll probably end up dating. They're meant for each other.
Then a girl like Cheon Seol would go to waste.
Hey!
That's true.
Hey. Did you not put a lot of effort into shaving?
Anyway, you're too impatient.
It's not that I didn't shave well. There are no six layer blades here. It's a bad blade.
People who can't do things right always blame the tools. Give me a break, six layer blade...
Jin Joo is caring for me like this.
Jin Joo! I'll shave better next time!
Nam Gil, we'll see you in school.
Get in quickly!
Drive safely. I'll see you in school.
Huh? Okay.
What's this?
We have a lot of baggage. I don't think you can fit in.
What are you saying? That baggage was in the trunk earlier. Hey, I was talking!
Jin Joo, there's a lot of baggage here. So, just comfortably ride in Nam Gil's care. Nam Gil, take good care of her!
Hey, what are you saying? What do you mean there's no room? Ma Jin Joo, just get in quickly. Why isn't there room?
Yeah, Nam Gil will get bored if he goes by himself.
- Keep him company.
- Uh?
What company? Is he a grandpa?
Ma Jin Joo, just get in!
Hey, why'd you take back baggage that was in the trunk?
Yea. Jin Joo could've fit here. The trunk is empty.
Geez, you idiots.
Aw, Cheon Seol. You did great!
She's a total cupid. She's born with it.
Jin Joo has to meet a good person this time and be happy. She's still young.
Right? This time.
Was there someone else in the past?
This place.
There's a lot of fireflies here. Right?
Should we just go now?
We have to drink now. The liquor.
Let's go to drink.
- Thanks.
- Pardon?
Thanks for coming along with me.
No worries... It's not good to drive a long distance alone. You'd fall asleep and get tired.
Thanks to you, I'm going back comfortably.
Uh. Is it clean for me?
Huh? What's clean?
I don't know if I shaved nicely.
Shaving? I'll look.
Yeah, it looks clean.
Really?
So, I did it well.
If you're tired, you can sleep.
If I sleep next to the driver, that's mannerless of me. You'll be sleepy, too.
It's fine.
A huge crowd gathered at Kimpo Airport this afternoon to greet King of Pop, Michael Jackson, who is visiting Korea.
Wow. That amazing person really came here.
I know.
They say it's rare for someone like him to be born once in a century.
The fact that we're living in the same time as him is amazing.
That's amazing?
To me, you're more amazing, Mom.
Aw, our daughter's been choosing to say really nice words lately.
♫  Billie Jean is not my lover. ♫
♫  She's just a girl who claims that I am the one. ♫
Like this.
♬  But the kid is not my son  ♬
Is it like this?
I think it's going to work out.
♬  Billie Jean is not my lover  ♬
- It's like this.
- Wow!!
Like this. Right?
Like this.
It's correct, right?
You're good.
It's not like that.
Then, like this?
Are you riding a bicycle?
You saw, right?
Drink this before you go.
You're not using the blender. That makes it tiring.
Why did you peel all that? So much work.
If you blend all of it in the blender, it'll taste bad.
Besides, you guys don't eat with the skin on saying it's rough.
So, that's why I peeled them.
It's good.
Eun Joo, have this before you go.
No, I don't want to. I'm not hungry.
Drink it. Even if it won't go down.
You need breakfast before you go.
- I said I didn't want to. What's with you?
- Oh, my!
That little...
- Mom, I'll be going, too.
- Okay.
Ma Eun Joo.
Why are you saying that to your unni?
Let's have a talk.
What?
Hey. What, "Ma Eun Joo?"
Are you not going to fix the way you talk to me?  (T/N: You are not supposed to call someone by their name if they're older.)
Okay, Unni.
Yeah. I'm your unni.
What did you want?
Can't you be nicer to Mom?
I'm just worried about you.
What are you saying?
Do you think it's guaranteed that Mom will always be by our side?
There's no guarantee.
What's with you being like an old soul today?
In our lives, the person who will peel tomatoes using their own hands and make juice for us.
And the person who will make sure we have breakfast.
If we don't have Mom, there's no one else like that.
Do you think your husband will do it for you? Your child?
Hey. Are you worried that Mom will die?
In this world, there's nothing that wouldn't be able to happen to us.
Just don't regret it when the time comes.
Unni... what do we do...
Unnie.
Unni.
What's with her today?
Time slip.
Earthquake?
Yes, not the earthquake record, but the forecast.
When there's going to be another earthquake in the Seoul area?
He's calling the weather agency, right?
This isn't Japan. In South Korea, when would there be an earthquake?
Wow... I thought his temper died down quite a bit recently. Maybe he's about to die. He's doing such a strange thing!
You don't know?
Okay.
Why is it that no one is prepared? There's no place on the earth which is safe from earthquakes.
They really won't come to their senses until something actually occurs.
- Where are you going? Class is starting.
- The library.
The library?
I think he's gone crazy.
From Galileo to Terminator, Physics through Star Trek, Time Labyrinth, Nothing is Impossible, The Future
Is time always flowing towards the future?
To time travel you have to bend space and time.
Possible time travel through the wormhole.
According to Stephen Hawking's scientific theory, you can turn the clock and go back into the past...
He expressed it as if you could adjust the time which has already passed.
He said you must bend space and time and go through the wormhole to travel through time.
What is this saying?
From Galileo to Terminator.
Butterfly.
Meow.
Where is it?
What are you eating by yourself?
Huh? Oh. Breakfast.
What about you? Breakfast?
I came here for a cat I know.
But, you're here today.
Oh, it's cat food? For a stray cat?
Yeah. Whether it's lost, or something happened,
it's always moving around and crying. Like someone I know.
Who?
♬  I’m thinking I’m in Love  ♬
Wow, your stomach is giving signs that you want to eat this.
♬  It is very sweet.  ♬
Here. You should have your own food first before caring about the cat's food.
No. I normally don't have breakfast.
♬  I’m fallin’ in love with you  ♬
I can't eat. Just eat this.
A student has to have breakfast. I mean a student who is studying.
It's not that I wanted to eat this for real. I'm eating this to show you my appreciation.
Yes, okay.
You should have it quickly.
♬  Open your closed heart.  ♬
- You're eating it well.
- It's good.
♬  Like that, I keep smiling.  ♬
♬  I'll approach slowly.  ♬
♫ You're not good at falling in love ♫
Are you feeling unwell?
No, I'm fine.
You can go first. Hold on.
What's the matter?
♬  Let me in your mind  ♬
Oh, she'll be suffering for quite a while.
Oh, my. It's not here.
Oh, my.
What do I do?
I'm in trouble.
Thanks.
- I want to go again.
- The ocean.
Grilled clams.
- Shrimp snacks.
- Oh, you.
Why are they not picking up? It's driving me crazy.
I'll have medicine for period cramps.
It works well.
She has a weak stomach. Give me the one with acetaminophen, not ibuprofen.
Hold on.
Thank you. Oh, one second.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
Can you buy me one of those?
Okay.
Sanitary napkins
I'll have this, too.
This, too?
Okay.
Hold on.
This one doesn't have wings. Hold on.
- I'll have this.
- This one?
- Yes.
How much is it? Thank you!
Hey, isn't Choi Ban Do sleeping in the library because he wanted to skip class?
- Choi Ban Do's there.
- What's he doing there?
How did we end up sleeping in a construction site?
I know. I bet we're the first to do that.
Uh, Ma-Ma Jin Joo.
How will I go inside?
What are you doing? You pervert.
This a**hole... is he confused about his sexual identity... is this yours?
Gosh, why'd you suddenly push me like that? It's making me embarrassed.
That's... the one with wings.
What is this? A challenge?
Don't look at me like that. Ma Jin Joo's inside, so give this to her.
What?
That mysterious bastard...
Go Dok Jae. It's so embarrassing.
Does it hurt a lot? Do you want us to buy something for you?
No, it's okay. You guys go eat.
Will you be okay?
Then, you can rest here. We'll come quickly after eating.
Okay. You can eat slowly. I'm okay.
- We'll be going.
- Okay..
Hey, hey.
I knew you'd do this.
How many times do I have to tell you to take medicine with water?
Nagging like an old man.
Nothing compares to your nagging.
Are you okay?
No, it hurts so much.
Lean over.
Hey, it's fine. Someone's going to see.
Does it matter if someone sees? Did you commit a sin?
Should we kiss?
Are you crazy?
It has to be like this for it feel like you're committing a sin.
Anyway, you're such an old man.
Am I the only one? You're an old woman.
I guess your period cramps didn't go away even though you got younger.
Am I not a girl if I got younger?
That's true. It's not good if you keep taking medicine; you'll build a tolerance to it.
This chronic illness won't go away.
♬  Are we the same?  ♬
♬  My hidden heart now  ♬
♬  keeps calling for you.  ♬
- Does it hurt?
- Yeah.
♬  Within time that stopped  ♬
♬  there's me, finding my way towards you.  ♬
♫ At the end of the longing that I cannot hide ♫
♬  Come to me the way you are  ♬
♬  "Our world" found again.  ♬
- Do you not have class?
- It's whatever. Why would I attend class at this age?
♬  Even if I turn back time,  ♬
♬  even if I l live again, it's always you.  ♬
♬  At your side like a destiny which won't be changed, I'll always be by your side  ♬
♬  I'll take care of you.  ♬
Wow!
High schoolers these days are so pretty.
You're pretty, too.
What?
I mean, you got eighteen years younger. You're obviously pretty.
Hey, give me one cigarette.
- Are you not going to be quiet?
- Come quickly. You should carry some yourself.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah.
I want to do my nails.
- Nails?
- Yeah.
Hey, this is awesome. I bought it. A success!
Those young bastards.
Hey, don't do it. It'll cause trouble.
- Let's just go.
- No, if they start doing that now, their lungs will rot.
Kids these days are so scary. You're someone with a family now.
If you just behave without fearing the world, it'll cause a lot of trouble.
If something bad happens to you, I'll be a widow. Remember that.
Hey, a widow? When you talk, you...
Okay, okay. Gosh, those young bastards.
Okay.
Wasn't that weird during the P.E. class?
It's like that every day. I'm the only one who gets caught all the time.
- Hey, take a break.
- You take a break.
Who cares if I have everything there's supposed to be?
I've never used it.
- You're lucky.
- About what, bastard?
You have a girlfriend.
- You bastard.
- What?
Why? Why'd you turn it off?
You just imagined it, right? Bo Reum isn't like that!
What about the item?
Tada!
What is it?
Let's watch it!
Now, it's not a video you see every day.
Singing Contest
Hey, are you ready?
Let's go.
All right...
Is it usually like this?
Aw, you guys are pure like little kids.
What's with you? Acting like you know everything?
I'm not acting. I know it all.
What's this? Have you really not done it yet, even though you have a boyfriend?
Ah, is it like the old-fashioned "waiting until marriage" idea?
Hey, no, it isn't that.
Is Yoon Bo Reum a cultural heritage or something? Protecting her?
I'm going to protect her!
Geez, I couldn't even use it. S***!
Dirty man.
June 1999
June 25
Mom.
Do you want to go to a karaoke place?
Right now? In daytime?
A noraebang place? I want to go!
Noraebang? I'm up for it!
Let's go! Noraebang!
Hey, you need to change.
Dad!
Let's go!
Ballet & B-Boying
What's this?
You know those B-boys I danced with in the streets before?
Yeah. That time when I pushed you to dance with them?
Those B-boys asked around and found me.
They want to perform with me.
Really?
How awesome. This is good.
I'll do ballet the ballet way, but as a hobby, I want to perform with them.
You should come see.
Of course. Of course I'll go.
I helped you with this. You can't forget it later on.
I know.
It's tomorrow.
[Ballet & B-Boying
Hello?
Ban Do, where are you?
Me? I'm going to see Min Seo Yeong's performance. Why?
Agh, Ahn Jae Woo's on a date, too. Go Dok is bored.
Bored, bored, bored!
Ah, that scared me.
Hello! You look like you're going somewhere.
Hello. Yes. Somewhere. Now. I'll be going.
What is this? Why's she following me?
Oh, right. You know Ma Jin Joo, the history major you were with?
Is she okay?
I heard from the other medical students,
but it seemed like Park Hyeon Seok found her and harassed her.
They say he hit her.
Yes! Noraebang!
So there are places that open in daytime.
- Why isn't Jin Joo coming in?
- Yeah, why isn't she?
Tada!
Liquor can't be missing when we're singing.
Oh, drinking during the day. Ma Jin Joo, you're the life of the party today.
A day like today doesn't come by every day.
You, too.
Mom, you should sing first.
What are you saying?
How can I sing in the middle of the day? My voice won't come out. I can't sing.
You should do it.
Honey, you can do it. Let's do a toast!
Here we go.
Cheers!
Han Dae Soo's "Happiness' Land"
♫ Dam da di dam da di dam da di dam ♫
I heard it from other medical students.
That day, he found Ma Jin Joo and harassed her.
They say he hit her.
Park Hyeon Seok!
This punk.
You think I'm truly an idiot for being taken advantage of by a jerk like you?
How dare you touch her! How dare you touch her!
Who?
It's a good thing you didn't make a mistake with Director Park.
That Director Park, does he still make you manage his mistress?
Well, yes.
It hurts!
I didn't do it on purpose.
Are you crazy? Where are you putting your hands?
Where are you putting your hands?
I really like you.
Director Park.
Keep doing this and I'll remove all of your medicine.
I apologize.
Do better.
I apologize!
How dare you...
Hey!
Let go!
How dare you!
I only got to sing once.
You kept giving the mic to Mom.
Goodbye.
Ah, gosh.
- The favor I asked you earlier.
- Oh, yes. Hold on.
Fun Noraebang
Your mother sang so well.
Right?
Fun Noraebang
Throughout life, it's my first time seeing someone crazier than me.
I'm sure there's something he feels guilty about and that's why he let it go.
I was thinking about how quiet you were being, but then you went and caused a huge accident.
Ban Do. He's someone who'll become a doctor later on.
He'll probably save thousands of patients.
How could you beat him up like that?
Whether he saves a thousand patients, or ten thousand patients,
why does it matter to me?
It doesn't matter to me either. I'm just saying.
Uh, did you get home safely yesterday?
Why do you carry around a phone if you're not going to answer it?
You called me yesterday? I didn't see it. Why?
Director Park.
Nevermind, it's nothing.
What about Director Park? Why'd you stop in the middle of talking?
Something came up so I called you.
I shouldn't have expected anything.
What are you saying?
I'm saying you were never there for me when I needed you.
Wow, Michael Jackson's so awesome. The performance was so great!
That's what I'm saying. When will he ever come back to perform again?
Will he come next year?
Is it closed?
Yeah, it is.
What do we do?
Are you not uncomfortable down there?
Yeah, I'm actually made for the floor. Floor physique.
Have you really not done it yet? You have a boyfriend.
Oh, is it the old-fashioned "waiting until marriage" idea?
What's this? He isn't even interested.
♬  Until the East Sea's water dries and Mountain Baekdu wears away, (T/N: Korea's National Anthem)
♬  God protect our land.
What's the matter?
I'm going to buy something really quick.
Where is he going at this time?
No way.
What do I do?
Ah, it's cold.
Oh, did you wake up because of me? Sorry.
Being a cheerleader is good, but you hurt your knees a lot.
Gosh, so cute.
Mom's voice
To my dear mom
What's this?
Grapes.
Am I asking because I don't know?
Why am I in this shape?
For me, why...
Why doesn't anything work out the way I want it to?
There wasn't even one time,
I've never been insincere.
I tried so hard.
Just like 10 years ago today, everything is a mess.
Taxi!
Goodbye!
- Deputy Choi!
- Yes!
Bring medicine and visit my hospital.
Are you being serious?
- I'll be going.
- Thank you!
Salute!
Goodbye!
Yes!
Rock, paper, scissors.
What are you doing?
These little...
Hey, give me a cigarette.
Hey, punk! You bastards.
You, the one who fell over. Come over here.
Come here, it's okay. Come.
Look at him!
Are you okay? Go home quickly.
You bastards learned bad things and harassed a friend.
Whether you drink or smoke, it's your body. So, do whatever you want.
Don't harass a friend.
If he's drunk, he should just go home quietly. What the heck?
What is he?
Hey, honey.
Choi Ban Do, come quickly.
Ban Do, come quickly.
Okay. I'm going now.
Hey, old man. Let's have a talk.
- Hey!
- Stop right there!
Hello?
Get him.
Hello? What's wrong?
What's wrong, honey?
What's wrong? What do I do?
Excuse me. I just want to have a quick talk.
Detective, I have to go right now.
It's a mutual offense. You can't go.
Detective, I have to go now. Please.
Oh, man, seriously. What are you doing? Drag him out.
I really have to leave!
Detective, I have to go!
Detetive, I really have to go.
Let go!
Why are you like this?
Why are you doing this?
Why?
Because of you,
my mom left without seeing my face.
I apologize, Mother-in-law.
I apologize.
I'm sorry...
I tried my darndest to live a good life.
Why am I always sorry...
Like you, I wanted to see Mother-in-law.
I wanted to see Mother-in-law, just like you!
What is he saying?
Mom.
♬  While living,  ♬
Epilogue
The king of pop, Michael Jackson, died today in his home on June 25.
Ten years ago today on June 25, 1999,
he held a concert in Korea.
The attentions of Korean fans are given.
Michael Jackson dies suddenly. Shocking!
When my mom, who was the universe to me, disappeared,
The world was going around so well with other interests.
♬  Leaving me,  ♬
My grief seemed to be buried so unattended and ordinarily like that.
Even to the closest person to me.
Three months after Eun Sook's funeral
♫ In relationships and longing encountering people  ♫
♬  Where does it lead?  ♬
♫ With my small wisdom I can't know ♫
♬  The only thing I know is how to live  ♬
♫ There would be more mistakes and times of distress ♫
♫ We realized that they can't be avoided ♫
- I'm here. Guess what I bought?
♬  If the answer is love, ♬
Tada! I bought steamed pork you like.
- I did good, right?
♬  I'm going to love everything in this world. ♬
Stay where you are. I'll prepare it after I change.
Don't move!
♬  I will meet  ♬
♬  the people who left me.  ♬
♫ The relationships and longing which brushes by other people  ♫
♬  where does it lead?  ♬
♫ I can't know it with my small wisdom ♫
♬  The only thing I know is how to live  ♬
♫ More than that there will be mistakes and times of distress ♫
♫ We realized that they can't be avoided ♫
♬  If the answer is love,  ♬
♬  I will love everything in this world.  ♬
♫ There will be mistakes and times of distress ♫
♫ We realized that they can't be avoided ♫