What could it be?
Seo Jin, shh.
That's right.
- Hey!
- What? Hey, hey, hey. Come quickly and see.
I don't think a woman will come. Kim Jong Min will be stood up.
I think Kim Jong Min will be stood up.
Why did you turn it off?
I told you to play with Seo Jin, and you're watching TV again?
You want to watch the blind date of a celebrity you don't know?
I shudder just by hearing the name of this show! Because of you! You!
If I would have known all this would happen, I could've been living as a prosecutor right now.
You think you are the only one with good memories?
Judges and investigators? Bull. You think studying hard will make anyone a prosecutor?
People who are good at studying usually end up as prosecutors.
Okay. Anyway ...
Look. You shouldn't have seduced me when we first met.
You seduced me first. With your eyes like this.
You kept blinking like that, so I thought you had an eye problem.
Wow, this woman's remembering it wrong.
You had your eyes on me first and made it seem like you would die if I didn't pick you. Truly.
You were like this.
You did that first! Staring at me.
Do you not remember? I chose you because you scared me. Truly.
You seduced me first by doing this with your eyes.
You kept blinking like that!
That is not what happened.
Episode 2: Memories Are Only Remembered When It's Convenient To Do So.
Oppa, you are heading to Professor Hwang's class, right?
I put a lot of effort in to get this from previous students.You should look at it.
If you put in that much effort, you should use it yourself.
Sunbae! This is a newly released one. You should have it.
If it's new, you should have it.
I don't know whose household he comes from but he's basically gleaming.
They raised him well.
I left  that  kid and I went for that loser.
Hello!
Oppa.
You must be going to class.
"You must be going to class."
What then, did he come to play pool?
Are you out of your mind? Or are you suddenly lonely? You want to date?
Why? I said hi because i was happy to see him.
You said hello because you were happy to see him? After you humiliated him yesterday?
What?
Look at him! He's so handsome!
You! Let's date.
He asked her out!
-I don't want to
- Why?
You smell like sweat.
What's wrong with her?
Poor him!
Wow, I can't believe this.
That's impossible. When did I do that?
You did that yesterday!
Wow! Yesterday you hated him and his sweat smell. Today you say hi you're happy to see him?
Wow! You're scary!
OMG! OMG!
Is that why he looked so hurt? Ugh, I don't know!
Why did I say that?
You would know, not me.
I mean, he had just finished playing sports so he would've smelled like sweat. You and your germophobia.
That's right!
Wow, I'm crazy. I'm really crazy. Crazy.
Are you sick?
It's not that kids these days are scary. Kids have  always  been scary.
Aren't you seniors?
No matter what happens, you must never pick a fight.
You must follow what you're supposed to do. The seniors will deal with other seniors!
Aigoo these bastards. At least they know "fair play."
I'm so tired. How long do I have to do this?
I think I'm going to die.
Seniors, when can we stop?
Stop being a wuss. Until the day a woman comes into this room,
you have to remain in this position.
What woman will come in here? That is basically telling us to stay like this forever.
It's a girl!
♫  Will you remember the promise? ♫
Come in! Come in!
♫ I believe. I believe. ♫
♫  Will you recognize my image since I've changed so much? ♫
I'm sorry I'm late!
This psycho
Dok Jae! Oh, right, your hair was like that!
All down!!
How could you say something like that?
Of course he would smell like sweat. He was working out.
How can I lose someone like that.
Aigoo, Ma Jin Joo. Aigoo, Ma Jin Joo.
Hello, Jin Joo!
What were their names? I think one was class rep.
- Hey you, come to the front!
- Yes.
No, it's not. It's her.
Hey!
Cheon Seol!
You're Cheon Seol, right?
What is wrong with you? Are you reuniting with lost family?
The professor came. Sit down.
Oh, right. We used to be really close back then.
But, she left and we stopped talking.
Did I do something wrong to her?
I don't know.
Did she make a mistake this morning? Everyone's been talking.
All these rumors...
Why did she leave without telling us that time?
Regent Heung Seon vs Empress Myeong Seong. Whose policy was best?
You guys prepared your presentations well, right?
Yes.
Wow, can you believe this? I'm in a class in school right now.
Today's topic will be Regent Heung Seon vs Empress Myeong Seong.
They were constantly fighting over different policies and having power struggles.
Even Empress Myeong Seong couldn't avoid conflict with the in-laws. I hate it.
This led to the downfall of Joseon Dynasty. Everyone, shall we make our presentation on our discussion?
So Queen Myeong Seong's supporters opposed Regent Heung Seon's policy of isolation and rejection
of diplomatic relations with other countries which was the main reason our modernization was delayed.
Oh, she's on the wife's side.
Yes, you will experience all this later.
Nice. Next group.
Let's see the next presentation.
Why?
- Hurry go!
- Where?
Who's the next presenter?
You're the presenter of our group. Hurry!
- Me?
- Hurry and go. Make the presentation.
Ma Jin Joo from Group 3?
I...forgot the entire contents of our discussion.
How long was it that you met with your group so that you would forget?
Then, just tell us your opinion. Is it Regent Heung Seon or Empress Myeong Seong?
Uh... I...
I think Go Jong was at fault. (Go Jong was the son of Regent Heung Seon and the husband of Queen Myeong Seong).
Go Jong? Why?
Well, his wife and his father were fighting. King Go Jong should've stepped forward.
The husband should've quickly stepped forward and moved out.
But, this is the palace during the Joseon Dynasty.
Oh, yes. But, anyway, whenever you look at those families, it's always the husband's fault.
The husband should've mediated between them... I mean, how could a wife win against her father-in-law?
Can the wife fit to accommodate for everyone's needs? Is the wife a puzzle to fit everything perfectly?
We?
So you think the dynasty fell because of Go Jong?
Of course not, just something like that..
What a refreshing opinion. I like it.
So, who are the members of Group 3?
F. Lacked an understanding of topic during debate.
What did you do?
Well, how could I remember something from so long ago?
But, the debate was yesterday.
Okay, we'll just go along with the fact that you forgot the debate.
But what? Go Jong?
She asked my opinion. You guys don't know but father-in-laws can be worse that mothers-in-law.
He's so picky, he doesn't eat kimchi that has fish sauce in it.
- Ugh, I thought of him again.
- Who?
There's someone like that. A father-in-law who acts like a mother-in-law.
Give me one.
Fish sauce? Don't you know I only eat kimchi with anchovy sauce?
I'm not eating it! Make it again.
I'm living with a mother-in-law!
Isn't it too harsh?
I thought she wanted my opinion. I can't believe this.
I  can't believe this.
Is this your concept today?
Movie Club
Wow, it's been so long since I saw this film.
Oh this one is here too!
Brad Pitt!
Oh, I remember! Your hairstyle's inspired by Brad Pitt's.
You, young punks. When will I see this again?
You're so cute!
What is this?
Aww, so cute!
Wow, to see how you guys looked again when you were young.
I will kill him!
Hey, I can't believe you did that to a senior.
No. Him.
You! Did you drink during the day? Why would you laugh there?
Do you see my hand shaking? I lost my hand because of you.
Are you that bored with life? Were you trying to make a spectacle?
Aigoo. This Hyung is living something spectacular indeed.
What is that crazy guy saying? Are you not sober?
Okay. Sounds good. I'll explain everything.
Listen to me well, kids. I don't know what's going on right now, either. But what I appear to be is not the whole truth.
I look like Choi Ban Do right now, right? But I'm not the Choi Ban Do that you think you know.
If you're not Ma Jin Joo right now, then who are you?
So, I'm not 20 right now. I suddenly came to the past!
How do I remember something that happened 18 years ago?
You're 38, then?
Ha! With that face?
Well, my face is still the same. When I woke up this morning, I became 20 and it was the year 1999!
Ah, I see. So it's like time traveling. Like that movie  Back to the Future .
That's right.  Back to the Future.  It's exactly that. I knew you were smart.
So what I am like in the future?
You?
Hold on. It won't stop trembling. Massage it.
Hey, how much do you have to work out to have that kind of body?
Be easy, we don't recover at this age.
What is hopeless is your bodies.
Oh!
Do some exercise!...my batting skills are still good, right?
but the director keep saying I lost it
I have to go this time. To the Korean Series.
Cheering Fairy
You'll get healthier. Really healthy.
What about him?
Does he still go around like this?
Hey, his hair will fall out!
- Get a haircut!
- Shut it.
Don't say that. No Dok Jae, do whatever you want with your hair.
Just don't shave it.
What are you saying?
What about me? Do I have a girlfriend?
Is there a girlfriend?
Yes
I got a yacht.
Darling?
Only a girlfriend? No. A wife, too.
I become an aerobics teacher?
Me?
Let's go everyone!
Your husband's in front of you! Hit him hard!
That's it!
Next, kick him! Higher!
One! Two!
Not exactly an aerobics teacher but, something similar to that.
This seems unbelievable.
Well, I don't know what's happening to me, either. Up until yesterday night, that tightwad-
Anyhow, just imagine how surprised I am with this situation.
I can't tell you guys about the pain I experienced before I recover from it.
If you ever think I'm being strange, just remember I'm from the future and be understanding.
Oh. You have injuries, too.
We didn't even know you were like that.
No, don't worry.
What a crazy guy.
She's crazy. She gone completely crazy.
Is she pulling an April Fool's prank again? She's gone crazy from studying too much.
Now he's lying about anything.
Is the time machine in your house?
We should go see it.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
People who are good at studying are the best at creating detailed lies.
Who would believe what I am saying?
Wait for me! I don't know how to get there.
Who would believe me?
Those little bastards. Let's go together!
Hey, I don't know the way!
Excuse me.
♬ From the start it was easier to be alone.  ♬
I kept on watching you earlier. Because you're pretty.
♬ In a time of free choice ♬
Me? Really?
Yes.
If you don't mind me asking, could you give me your number?
Oh, my. What is this?
He thinks I'm pretty!
Uh.. I don't have a phone or pager.
Oh, you don't. Then, what about your home phone?
Home phone? What was it? How could I remember?
I don't really know...
I'm not doing it on purpose. I just don't know.
Then, can you tell me your major and the area you live in?
Oh, my. Excuse me! I have a pager here.
Isn't it that the freshman English major? Did you reject him?
Just give out your number. It's not like you will start dating just because you give it to him.
Pretty girls just...
He really said I was pretty!
If I pass by, he says, "You look pretty today, as well."
He's probably doing that to make you buy something.
Who's pretty? You? Are you on some drug?
No, even when he's with other women, he says it to me.
Because you look the dumbest out of all of them.
No, it's not that. He really did it because I'm pretty!
He was always here somewhere.
♫  Whenever I see you, everything stops.  ♫
♫  I don't even know when it started.  ♫
You're still very pretty today, too.
Oh, thank you.
If you don't mind me asking, can we talk really quick?
Yes.
♬ And I felt that this is fate ♬
A picture book to make the brain a creative playground!
This is an English study book. It's hard to get in Gangnam, as well.
I feel like you're the type of mom to teach her children well.
Today, I'll give you 50% off.
At that kind of price, it's like I'm just giving it to you for free.
Wow this mom's skin is very pretty!
You have such a bright face! Oh, it's so bright and perfect.
This is hard to get in Gangnam. And you are so pretty.
And I think you'll teach your kids well. So, I'll give you 50% off.
But, this mom's skin is so nice!
Oh!
Oh, there were this many pretty women here? I thought it was only you.
Anyway, he's handsome and good at selling. He'll have great success!
Let's go in, Pretty Woman #1.
Guys.
I'm truly pretty, right?
Let's go. You need to be punished.
Hey!
Soda, 300 won
Ahn Jae. Ban Do.
- Thank you!
- Drink this and come back to your senses.
What is that? Nostradamus?
(Signs about Nostradamus' predictions)
Oh, that's right. Now that I'm thinking about it, who would believe this?
Have you decided?
What? Decide what?
July 24th, the last day. What are you going to do?
Hey, don't believe this. It's a lie.
A lie? The planets are lining up and there's going to be an apocalypse.
The planets could collide and we could die. Or a war could break out.
Don't even mention it. The unusual pattern in our climate is because something out there is trying to control us and eliminate some of the human population.
- We could all be wiped out.
- Be quiet! I can't focus.
Hey. You guys stay here.
Where are you going?
Madam.
Ow! It hurts.
Are you crazy? How dare you touch her?
With one punch I think I convinced her.
She seemed dumb so she was easy to seduce.
I think I ended this affair with that punch.
Hey.
You are here.
You bastard, I said you were dead when I met you in college.
You're dead.
A medical student's night occurs only once a year. What a shame.
Right? It's a shame. But, what can I do? I have to study.
Oh! I'm so sorry. I was thinking about something else.
Hey! Look where you're going!
No, it's fine. It's fine. That could happen.
Wow, I'm so sorry. What should I do? Oh, drink this.
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
Gosh, you're so... nice!
Why would I make a big deal? He didn't do it intentionally.
I said he was dead.
It's a bit of a shame he had his glasses on. It would've hit him directly.
Ramen ₩800
Dish with rice, soup, and sides. ₩1500
No way. ₩1500?
It's ₩1500?
It's so cheap!
You could buy a bag of chips with that money!
Hey!
We demand an explanation, Chief Director!
Meal prices increased!
Explain, Chief Director!
Are you eating chips covered in gold? How is this the price of chips?
This is good.
Why aren't you eating?
Oh. You keep eating.
I'm full.
You're full? I'll eat it.
Me too.
It doesn't taste like anything
How is your short rib soup? Let me try.
Since they made it in big amounts for a long time, it tastes better.
If you make it at home, it doesn't taste like this.
Did you starve for weeks? You usually don't eat this.
Why are you eating so fast?
You should try having a child.
What?
A child?
No, no. It's nothing.
Eat up, it is yummy.
Wow, I feel like my stomach's going to explode. I ate well.
You used to say that you didn't feel happy when you were full.
Being full is the good times.
Whether it goes in to your mouth or nose, eating to live while raising a child is sorrowful.
What?
Okay. Our Jin Joo had to change. Good thinking.
Oh. Oh, yeah.
Hey, what should we do after we eat?
Why are you asking like you're a stranger?
Why? What are we doing?
A blind date!
A blind date? The date that I'm thinking of?
What's wrong with you?
Yes!
Why are we crossing paths again? Let's not get involved with each other.
Ugh, Ma Jin Joo. Let's not cross paths.
Why is she here?
What is this? No way...
The first day I met her?
The first day I met this punk?
Let's see how many successful matches are made.
Hey, are their eyebrows supposed to be seagulls?
And, why do all of their lips look bruised?
Did you bring that bomb here?
Did you see their hair? It's like a stoplight. Red, green... What is this?
Yeah, but look at him.
That scared me.
Right, I met Ma Jin Joo at this blind date.
Ugh, why is that day today?
Wait, no. This is good.
I'll just not get involved with her forever.
Why are even my dreams nightmares?
I've been cursed for my whole life because of this day, child.
Let's not get involved.
Don't get involved with me.
You should have it first.
Okay.
Let's not get involved.
Okay, should we introduce ourselves now?
I'm a First Year Civil Engineering major, Eom Won Hee. Not Mother (eomeoni), it's Eom Won Hee.
I'm a First Year Civil Engineering major. I call myself the Kim Won Joon level of handsome. I'm Lee Dae Young.
I'm Go Dok Jae.
Don't call me Dok Jae, but Go Dok.
I'm An Jae Woo.
I like to listen to the radio. And my special talent, well..
I'm trying to decide.
Hey, it's a cockroach!
Where?
That's my friend's special talent. His fast speed.
You mischievous guy.
I just need to not get involved with her.
I'm a civil engineering major, Choi Ban Do.
I'm from Byunsanban-do, so I'm Choi Ban Do.
I am always thankful to my parents for not calling me Byunsan. (Byun = poop)
Done.
You're just poop. A pile of poop.
So, I think we're done with the boys. Let's move on to the girls.
Yeah. Bo Reum, we'll start with you.
How do you know my name?
Huh?
Oh, it says it right there. Yoon Bo Reum.
Yoon Bo Reum.
Oh, Yoon Bo Reum
Oh, that was a close call. It slipped out without me knowing.
Geez, that scared me.
Since we are the same age, let's drop formal language. I am freshman history major Yoon Bo Ruem.
Why would he pick a painful love? You can't, my friend.
I'm a history major, Cheon Seol.
I'm a history major, too. Go Eun Bee.
Hey, there's something in your face. I see a bit of Suzy.
Kang Suzy?
Oh, that's not the Suzy I was talking about. There's a young and pretty Suzy I know.
You guys will know later on in life.
No way.
I'm a history major. Seol Hyeon.
What? (Today, Seol Hyeon is a pretty celebrity)
Seol Hyeon.
I'm a history major. I'm Ma Jin Joo.
You are responsible for the bomb. Take care of the bomb properly ok.
What do you mean by "getting rid of the bomb?" It's not like you are a kid anymore. Just let things happen.
Today's your turn!
My turn?
How do I know which item belongs to the bomb. It's not like their names are written on it.
If I don't know, I can't do it.
Why are you acting like you don't know? Is it your first or second blind date?
Do it correctly.
Why has she been staring at me? It's scary.
No way. Has she...picked me?
Oh that is right, she is the one who flirted so much with me back then.
Isn't this why I ended up this way.
Kiddo, you are scaring oppa.
Suzy... Suzy.
So, who's picking first?
Because of Yoon Bo Reum, my life...
I hate that day so much. I wish I had gone to hell instead.
I pity myself so much.
She ruined my life!
Jae Woo, you're choosing your fate. I'll help you.
Oh, what is this? What the?
Hey, you chose the giraffe!
Oh, Suzy!
It's mine.
What? How is it yours? It's Suzy's!
Even if you like him, you have to follow the rules.
I usually wear 2 different earrings.
So you're saying you use this one?
It's hers.
- What?
- It's hers. Not mine.
These little...
I've heard there are people who wear 2 different earrings.
Be quiet. You don't know how she'll affect your life. Don't choose her.
What are you saying?
Well, would you look at this.
There's still two left. Ban Do, you can go.
Choi Ban Do. You came, too?
So, you rejected me?
Are you saying you want to start a new life?
Ah, what's wrong with her?
You and I cannot meet! Let's not get involved.
I owe you, Ban Do. I'll pay my debt at the next meeting.
He doesn't want to get involved with me, huh?
You traitor!
What? I got rid of the bomb!
Bomb? Is she a bomb to you?
The flying flower pig is a bomb!
You..you. The girl I chose is a bomb! She's the dynamite.
Her personality sucks. She's a shopaholic, has mysophobia, and has anger issues.
She's the perfect bomb!
Anger issues? What's that?
What is that, you bastard?
There's something like that. When you have a bad personality and you get mad whenever.
But... how do you know that?
How do I know? Because I've lived with...
Lived?
I heard it! Everyone knows it except for you.
Get out.
Is that so?
Everyone knows? Then why don't I know?
I have a weird feeling about this...
- Hey. But, still, the Flower Pig!
- Hey!
Let's split up. We'll head out first.
Thanks.
It's nothing.
We'll leave, too.
But, where's Dok Jae and his partner?
Flying flower pig? Hey.
Are you crazy?
Why are you calling me a bomb?
Jae Woo!
Hey. Look at me properly.
I'm going to drink. Follow me.
He rejected me earlier. What is this situation?
I chose her to reject her so we wouldn't get involved with each other.
Are you two not leaving?
Huh? Well...soon
Looking from here, she actually does look pretty.
You should've grown up like this, woman.
This bastard...does he by chance want to be together again?
With me? He's crazy.
Oh, oh, I'm crazy. I must be crazy. This can't be.
Let's end this right here.
Excuse me, Ma Jin Joo.
Looking at you, I see that you have to be studying right now.
Ma Jin Joo, you're good at studying right?
A woman who stays at home with her kid has no charm. What would she do?
You're never full even if you eat.
Then, what? You find a husband who earns money like a gum seller.
Hurrah for that!
Living with you was like being tortured and getting painfully chewed on all over.
So, you shouldn't think of finding a boy here and marrying him.
You should study. Study hard to become a career woman.
It's cool. "Gold Miss." Okay?
What did you say?
I know you're unhappy. I know. I know.
But, you'll understand what I'm saying when you're older.
Anyway. Study hard. You can do it!
Well, I'm done here.
Just in case you might misinterpret what I'm saying...
I am not interested in you at all. I'm giving you a brush off!
What is this?
I...wow.
I'm a hero. How many lives have I saved?
You said you wanted to study. You could be a doctor or prosecutor. Live a life full of variety.
I lived with you because I was me. If it was anyone else, you would've been kicked out.
You don't even know anything.
Min Seo Young?
Do you remember my first love, Min Seo Young, in the past?
I should have seduced her then. I was too shy though.
Even if you did go back to the past, you can't seduce her.
If I do, I'll seduce her. Would I get Ma Jin Joo?
This crazy guy. Did he choose me just to say that?
Torturing my husband? Torturing?
He's saying whatever he wants.
Where is he?
Does he think he came here by himself?
Excuse me..
You're Min Seo Young, right?
Huh?
Is he...
Oh, sorry. Hi.
Do you know me?
Maybe you...
don't?
I don't really know you, but I don't not know you.
Then that means you know me.
What?
♫  It's like I'm dreaming. ♫
♫  If I could turn back time. ♫
♫ When I dream of you... The days where my heart hurts. ♫
♫ When I dream of you, you and I who lost our way. ♫
♫  The warm you, the shining us.  ♫
Wow, Ban Do's amazing.
He went for his first love.
How did he live when he missed Seo Young so much?
♫  I'm praying for... ♫
So, this day gave me a miracle to show me this?
Ma Jin Joo, you lived the wrong way all along.
It's good, then. I got my closure after my divorce.
Seo Jin.
Seo Jin!
It's dangerous. Come here.
That mean bastard.
Please go to Seongbuk-dong, Building Number 31.
♬The golden days ... Sad on the long journey I'm barefoot and young♬
♬ But I'm not stopping there. I'm going and coming Da Da Da Da ♬
♬ Stay with me. Watch me.♬
♬ Someday I'll bing the whole world in front of you. ♬
We're here.
Okay...
Arms down.
Dismissed.
Chairman, we are here.
Don't you know what's embarrassing?
You should leave.
We are not in a relationship to have a talk here.
This is different from what you told me.
I told you to be a part of the student council, but you participated in the ROTC for no reason.
Why? You should just start doing whatever I say not to do.
Why don't you go study History while you are at it?
You should even date, which I've forbidden.<
That's a good idea.
It's Nam Gil!
He's so handsome!
You.
Will you date me?
What is this?
I don't want to.
She's crazy.
- Is she out of her mind.
- What is wrong with her?
Why would she reject him?
Why?
You smell like sweat.
My god.
He's so foolish.
What is she?
In movies, people use time machines to time travel.
If not that, they time travel when they wake up from sleeping.
You're not sleeping?
Yeah. I'm not.
"To my dear mom."
Divorce, time slip, dream?
What is this?
Look at him...
He is my favorite.
Me too, me too.
What?
What? What? What!
watch TV or sleep!
You're putting a lot of pressure on me!
Did I feed her something wrong?
What's wrong with her?
Maybe she's going through puberty late.
Late? Do you not remember?
She put us through so much when it happened during junior high.
She would not be human if she does it again.
That's right. I wonder what is wrong with her.
I will be leaving, Mom.
Mom. Mom.
She is scaring me.
Me too.
Yes.
I can't sleep.
Not sleeping.
What is this?
Why do I look like this?
Yes. Yes.
I'm here.
What happened in 1999.
The real 1999.
[ Epilogue ]
♬ I will meet the people who have left me.
Hey. Why do they have seagulls on their eyebrows?
And, why do they all have bruises on their lips?
Are you the one who planted the dynamite?
she looks like she is going to explode.
There are only two left. Ban Do, it is your turn.
You have to take care of the bomb.
It's your turn.
Make sure-
♫ All I know is how to live ♫
Let's take a picture.
Who knows, someone may end up getting married.
♫ We realized ♫
What the?
♫ that you can't avoid it ♫
♫ Now when the answer is love  ♫
♫ I will love everything in this world ♫
Go Back Couple, Preview.
Give me all this family's money.
I think he's up to something.
You almost had me fooled.
Your acting's as good as Jeon Do Yeon.
Since this is my situation right now, I'm going to enjoy it.
Can you give me your number?
I told you not to flirt with me.
I'm sorry!
I never thought I'd come to a club with you!
- What's the matter?
- If I don't go now, when will I ever?
It's the guy who fell for me!
Director Park?