[English subtitles are available]
[Tiger and Crane]
[Episode 13
Grabbing the Long Token]
Since you saw it,
then
I can't let you leave.
Cat Ghost Bell?
You're the only one
in this world,
who knows my heart.
How did you catch up?
Don't you know I'm a Phantom Weapon Sorcerer?
You have Cat Ghost Bell that helps you leap through space.
Then my Space-splitting Blade
is its nemesis.
Even if you try a thousand times,
it would be futile.
What are you planning?
With your experience,
to be able to fight me once in this life
has already made your life worth it.
Baihua Mountain?
I didn't expect
she had this prepared too.
Fairy.
There will be people here soon.
Today is the full moon.
We can't ruin our plan.
Blood Demon.
After Blood Demon died,
I didn't get rid of it
because I thought
I can still use it in the future.
You are so wise.
You deployed our men
here in advance.
There are so many bee pearls now.
We can definitely win first place.
These idiots
are so stupid.
No matter how strong they are,
who knows howl long
they have to fight for?
This is
the gap between people.
You are wise.
Why are they all flying away?
What's happening?
We scared them away.
We can't scare them away.
I don't have enough bee pearls yet.
What a big bee demon!
So big!
Don't panic.
As sorcerers,
we should work together
and fight the enemy together.
Run!
We'll die if we don't run.
Let's go.
Let's go, Da Changqiang!
Hurry up. Let's go.
Sir.
Get up.
What is this?
Sir.
Over there.
I didn't expect
we could collect enough bee pearls
so quickly.
God is on our side.
Cheng Jinian wanted to stop us
but he wouldn't have thought
we'd find the nest first.
Be careful!
Little thing.
Trying to sneak attack?
That's massive!
Is this also part of the exam?
Could it be if we take down this big one,
we'll can pass?
It's a Thousand-year Bee.
Run!
Hu Zi!
It's too late.
I'll go first.
Hu Zi!
Hu Zi.
Heaven and earth, nothing but my brick.
You've recovered?
You're pretending to be dead?
This is not a good place.
We might hurt others.
We have to lure it away.
Lure it into the cave.
It's stuck.
Heaven and earth, nothing but my brick.
Are you okay?
Yuqian.
Your brick is really effective.
Wang Yuqian,
it's not safe here.
Leave the mountain with me.
There are still so many of them to be saved.
Let's wait a while.
Sir.
Treat our Young Master Cheng as well.
I didn't take a closer look normally.
Turns out Brother Jinian looks like this.
Wang Yuqian.
Can't your brick
cure people?
Cure me too.
It hurts so much.
Xiaoxuan!
Where are Hu Zi and the others?
In order to save us,
they lured the bee demon up the mountain.
Let’s go back to the inn.
Let's go.
Everyone,
to save everyone,
Hu Zi and Xintong
lured the bee demon up the mountain.
I would like to ask
for you to
help them.
Yuqian is right.
Stand united and eliminate demons to save people
is something we sorcerers
should do.
You're right. I'll go too.
Wang Yuqian,
hit me with the brick once.
I'm willing
to save
Xintong
and Hu Zi with everyone.
Since we have to get the Bee Demon Emperor to pay back,
let me give him a hit too.
Hu Zi, let go of it!
You'll die!
Go!
Leave me alone.
Let go! Do you hear me?
Hu Zi!
Fairy.
Should we help them?
It's this moment we are waiting for.
Am I dead?
Where am I?
Who are you?
Hu Zi!
Miaomiao!
Mo Gu.
Mo Gu, I'm here.
Don't move.
I'll detoxify you.
Why are you so careless
and got yourself so severely injured?
Everything was normal.
But this bee demon suddenly appeared.
I fought it for several rounds,
but I was stabbed by its poison needle.
Then...
What about elsewhere?
Are you hurt anywhere else?
I'm much better now, Mo Gu.
How are the examinees?
The bee demon has been eliminated.
The students are safe now.
So Hu Zi is really a demon.
Yesterday at Baihua Mountain,
he showed his real form.
That demonic tail
has to be at least a meter long.
Could that Thousand-year Bee Demon
be lured by him?
It's very likely.
In that case,
we're all in danger.
What if Hu ZI
is really a demon?
As a sorcerer,
we should be irreconcilable with demons,
but Hu Zi
never hurt anyone.
And he saved us this time.
He drove away the bee demon.
In the end, he was the one who killed the bee demon too.
Wasn't it said that
the demoinic tail of Hu Zi
was implanted by someone?
Hu Zi is a righteous man
and treats us well.
Even if he has a demonic tail,
I still take him as my friend.
You're right.
Friends
should trust each other.
Clean the team! Eradicate the demons!
Royal Sorcerers and demons are enemies.
How can we allow demons
to take the Royal Sorcerer Exam?
Isn't that against the rules?
Exactly.
What if he transforms into a demon
and eat us?
Cheng Jinian.
Stop implanting fears here.
Hu Zi is not a demon.
Stop sowing discord between us.
He has demonic tail.
Everyone saw it
at Baihua Mountain.
I'm doing this
for everyone's good.
If he gets out of control and hurts someone one day,
who can take the responsibility?
That's right.
We're going to report to Tiangang Hall
to disqualify him.
Stop arguing.
Greetings, Miss Ximen.
I'm here to announce to everyone
who is qualified
to take the next exam.
Yesterday, when the enemy was in front of us,
some candidates lost their cool.
They didn't care about their friends
and ran away in panic.
What the Three Main Halls look at when recruiting Royal Sorcerers
is unity
to fight the enemy together.
Yesterday, only a few students
did that.
Tiangang Hall has decided,
those who had escaped on their own accord from Baihua Mountain
has been eliminated.
The rest
will go straight to the final round.
Luckily we didn't go down the mountain.
Get ready.
Three days later,
the final exam will begin.
Miss Ximen.
What are you going to do with Hu Zi?
Hu Zi killed the bee demon
and saved all of you.
Is there any problem?
But he...
Mind your own business.
Get ready for the next round.
You're awake, Hu Zi.
Are you all right?
Where is the bee demon?
You killed the bee demon.
Me?
When?
Brat.
You killed the bee demon with Phurba.
You did it.
You can finally
control Phurba.
Looks like our training
is not wasted.
I can control Phurba?
I don't remember.
I only remember
I went to
a very spacious place.
There was also
a big bird with four wings.
What big bird?
It's a big bird.
I think it's a crane.
There are four wings anyway.
That's the Demon Emperor.
Why did he see it?
Xintong.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt badly?
What's wrong with her?
Is she angry?
I don't know.
She was fine just now.
Hu Zi,
let me tell you.
When you were in a coma,
she was so worried about you.
Then how did you tick her off?
I didn't.
You did.
-I didn’t.
-Let me coax her for you.
Ice Cube.
What's going on?
Why was there
such a big bee demon out of nowhere?
What are you Tiangang Hall up to?
We're already investigating.
That's so unreliable.
It's just an exam
and a mess like this occured.
Fortunately, we are lucky.
You should be glad
Phurba saved your life.
Master,
I can really control Phurba now?
Take it easy.
Phurba is very powerful.
Don't use it in the room.
Let me see.
You can't hold it.
It recognizes its owner.
Hu Zi,
take a good rest.
After you recover,
go practice in the training ground.
Okay,
Master.
Eldest Master.
This Phurba...
Phurba
is the magical weapon of Demon Emperor.
But it's also a magic weapon to suppress demon power.
If Hu Zi can
activate the power completely,
then the demonic tail in his body
can be completely eliminated.
Eldest Master,
please take care of them
these few days.
We don't have a clue yet
about the hoard of demons that escaped.
And now, one bee demon
had caused such a fuss.
I have to catch the other demons as soon as possible.
Xiaoxuan.
Just go with a peace of mind.
I'm here after all.
The Demon Emperor reappeared?
Impossible.
It was clearly killed...
500 years ago.
You've been exposed
for what happened at Babao Town.
I stopped the information.
But the people of Disha Hall
will be back soon.
No need to worry.
I have this body as a cover.
Everything
is within plans.
The first stage of Phurba has been activated.
Don't stop the action
on your side either.
I have my own plan.
She's over there.
Xintong.
Why are you eating alone?
Exactly.
How did you offend her?
She left as soon as she saw you.
She left as soon as she saw you too.
How could it be me?
Xintong.
You...
See.
It's you who offended her.
She didn't push me.
She's already like this when I just woke up.
I haven't got the time to mess with her yet.
Did you forget how you used to mess with her?
Did I say something in my sleep?
Did you really forget?
Xintong?
Xintong!
Xin–
Show your moves.
I can't beat you.
If you know, then don't act tough
and bet with your life.
Do you think it's brave?
I bet with my life?
When?
When we were fighting the bee demon,
why did you
take your life lightly?
I don't need you to
use your life
to save my life.
So that's the reason.
It was an emergency that day.
I can't just let you die–
No need
When you kill the blood demon,
it was like this.
When fighting the bee demon,
you're the same too.
Let me tell you.
I won't be grateful for that.
And I won't associate with
an idiot who doesn’t cherish his life.
Xintong.
-Actually–
-Go further away if you want to die.
Xin...
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
I shouldn't have bet with my life.
I promise,
if this happens again,
I'll be the first to run.
Hu Zi, listen carefully.
In this world,
I don't have any
family or friends anymore.
I don't want to others to be subjected to
misfortune because of me.
It's hard to be a Royal Sorcerer.
Today it was a Demon Elder.
Tomorrow it might be the Demon Lord and Demon King.
If you keep
taking your life
lightly,
I would rather not be friends
with you.
Xintong.
I didn’t expect you care so much about me.
Actually,
I too–
Enough.
Who cares about you?
Leave now.
Xintong. Xin–
[Arena]
Such a big setup.
Just a little worse off
than that of Qianyu State
[Arena]
Following the preliminary round at Baihua Mountain,
there are 24 candidates
who entered the final assessment.
Congratulations, everyone.
The final assessment
will be divided into four camps.
The commanders,
Tie Lie,
[Tie Lie
Commander of the Red Camp of Tiangang Hall]
[Miao Yin
Commander of Blue Camp of Tiangang Hall]
Miao Yin,
Qi Yanran,
and Qi Xiaoxuan
will be leading you respectively.
The test takers
will randomly enter
one of the four camps through a drawing lots.
What if you ended up picking up
a team you don't want to join?
What should we do?
He didn't say we can't change it.
We'll try to get
White Camp with Ice Cube.
If we can't get it,
we can just swap for it.
If that doesn't work, we can snatch.
The final assessment's content
is the dragon pillar in front of you.
The commanders
will lead the test takers
to get the position of the commander-in-chief.
The commander-in-chief's Long Token
is at the top of this dragon pillar.
The time limit will be the time of the hourglass.
Each camp
must get the Long Token
within the specified time.
The camp that wins
will have all their candidates
promoted to be a Royal Sorcerer.
The commander of that camp
will be promoted to the commander-in-chief of the four camps.
What’s wrong?
We must help Ice Cube
become commander-in-chief.
Can you swap with me?
No, you can't change.
Move along.
Next!
See you later.
Which camp did you get?
We're in the same camp.
We are rivals.
How's it?
I might have forgotten to wash my hands before I left the house.
I don't want to be in the same team
as that woman.
I'll go change.
Brick!
Is he stupid?
I was kidding.
Who'd be willing to swap?
Brother Xiao.
Can I
change my lot with you?
Why?
Here's the thing.
I know
you're good at martial arts.
You can join any team.
But I...
Hu Zi's too weak,
I have to protect him.
He and Xintong have to team up with me.
You can team up with me.
Well...
It's fine.
I'll ask others.
Wait.
Be careful.
Thank you, Brother Xiao.
He knows nothing. If he go to another camp..
There's really an idiot around?
Someone was willing to swap with you?
Who did you swap with?
Xiao Yunzi.
What's your relationship with him?
He stares at you every day
and cares about you a lot.
It's interesting.
What else could it be?
It's because I have a good character
and admirable.
Wait.
You swapped that strong person
to our enemy's camp.
Oh no.
Uh-oh.
Grandma,
Fulong City has been in various dangers.
Must we proceed with
this competition normally?
By proceeding with it
can we stabilize the world.
If we don't hold it,
we'll alert them instead.
I've arranged my men
to be on extra alert
and keep investigating related clues.
Set your mind on the competition.
Pay more attention to Yanran.
I don't trust her.
New old friends.
We meet again.
I'm your good friend,
Dan Dan.
Blades have no eyes so stop at the right time.
Anyone who oversteps the boundary during the competition
will be disqualified.
A million miles of mountain and river,
flowing straight through the clouds, we meet at Fulong.
Everyone,
the competition begins!
Ice Cube.
Don't worry.
We will definitely
get the commander-in-chief for you.
Be careful.
Let's go.
Go!
Everyone.
Off we go!
How impatient.
Go!
Forget about getting on the dragon pillar.
Da Changqiang?
Bro, I'm sorry!
What are you doing?
After all, we are
enemies.
Hu Zi,
your martial arts have improved a lot.
There are many things you don't know yet.
Who?
Hu...
Hu Zi, Hu Zi!
Don't! Don't!
Don't.
It hurts.
Hu ZI!
We're in different camps. I'm sorry.
Four against one?
Brat.
Hang in there!
Phurba?
It seems that
there's a master hiding
among the youngsters.
Wu Lidan.
I will settle both
our old and new feuds today!
You want to die?
I'm sorry.
Xiao Yunzi?
You used Twin Divination.
Though you'd be twice stronger than normal people,
but the rate that you deplete your spirit essences
is also twice as much.
Wang Yuqian,
With your weak skills,
you think you can defeat Xiao Yunzi?
Dream on!
No.
Xiao,
why do you keep staring at me?
I'll just stare at you.
Fine.
I will stop climbing. How's that?
You climb.
Yan Ling Shan.
Don't think you can defeat me
with Yan Ling Shan.
If you take a step closer,
the poison will move towards your heart for an inch.
I told you
I will take everything
Zhao Sect lost back.
Xintong.
You won!
Xintong!
Are you okay?
It's fine!
I'll save her.
Heaven and earth, nothing but my brick.
Everyone,
I'm sorry.
Brat.
He knows that using the enchantment
and fusing it with the Phurba's strength
will make it more powerful now?
I didn't teach him for nothing.
Why are you suddenly so strong?
This power is several times stronger than before.
I can't hold on anymore.
I quit!
Anyone who still wants to fight him, go on.
I quit.
Hu Zi!
Hurry up.
Cheng Jinian is already up there!
Young Master!
He's quite skilled.
Let's kill him first
before our fight.
Sure!
Seniors,
you're hitting so hard?
Didn't they say
to stop at the right time?
This is not fatal.
Weren't you fighting
pretty hard just now?
Aren't you two teaming up
to bully a kid now?
There's only win or lose on an arena.
It's not that easy
for you to get the Long Token.
Brat!
You hit even harde than I did.
Hu Zi, hurry up!
Do you think
you can win like this?
Today,
I'll make you the target of everyone!
I got the Long Token!
He got it!
Hu Zi,
we won!
Great!
Hu Zi,
we won!
Brat!
Way to go!
We won!
Hu Zi!
I see.
Ice Cube.
Hu Zi!
Don't be afraid.
The pain will end soon.
It's him.
What are you doing?
-Hu Zi
This...
Hu Zi!
What's going on?
Chief Commander,
what's going on?
I didn't expect
to befriend
a bunch of useless people like this.
Qi Xiaoxuan!
Hu Zi has lost his pulse.
What?
This...
How could this happen?
What's wrong with Xiaoxuan?