[English subtitles are available]
[Tiger and Crane]
[Episode 9
Designing a Demon Tracker]
This...
is the problem in your heart.
Do you know where she is?
Can you tell me? I...
How this white tiger is doing?
That white tiger
is being imprisoned.
It's more likely that they are in danger than not.
It's the man in black robe.
Where is he now?
Where is Commander now?
We need to talk to him.
He...
I don't know
if he has the time to see you now.
Just tell me where it is.
Wanchun Pavilion.
Wan...
Wanchun Pavilion?
Right...
[Avoid disaster and ask for blessings]
Did you see
where that old lady went?
What old lady?
There was a fortune teller here.
Forget it.
I'll take you to him.
[Avoid disaster and ask for blessings
Helps you solve your problems]
How is it?
-How is it?
-It really feels good.
That's right.
This book
can help you make a name for yourself
in this environment.
For example, when you first enter,
your eyes must look straight.
You don't like to have fun or drink alcohol.
Don't you feel lonely
in this long night?
Why don't you play a game with me?
I know a little
about chess.
If you win,
I will give you all the clues
of the sorcerers' disappearance.
In your opinion,
what are your odds for this chess game
It's a good set.
But it won't end well.
Black,
may be at a disadvantage,
but can still fight for it.
I wonder
what's the next move?
How would the player
tell the chess piece
what the next move is?
Who is the chess piece?
And who is the player?
The duty of a sorcerer
is to eliminate all demons in the world.
But do you know
what these demons are thinking?
Demons cause chaos in the mortal world
and harm the living.
They are heartless.
Even if they aren't,
they can only have a black heart that is dirty and ugly.
I'm not interested in understanding them.
You underplayed how much
you know about chess.
I have too much free time.
I often spend time playing chess.
Mr. Qi's skills
are more impresive.
Mr. Qi,
don't you want to know
why I have been difficult
to those guests?
Is it just to find the fated person?
I just want to know things
about the case.
There's no need for any other fate
between us.
You're right.
You don't want to hear
nor do you have the time to
listen to things of the past.
Quadruple Ko.
No win nor lose.
Although it's a bad end,
but no one
could play such a wonderful game with me.
Thank you for your advice.
Come again tomorrow night.
I will tell you everything.
As the saying goes, one should be a man of their word.
What you said just now
is breaking your promise, right?
When cheese pieces are stuck in this situation,
I could still survive.
But in life,
when one is stuck with the entanglement of love,
it's difficult to survive it.
I know, Mr. Don't.
If you want to see him,
you have to get through this Mr. Don't first.
Mr. Don't, they have something to do.
Something important.
Can't you just...
Commander.
You're done?
What's going on?
Commander.
Well...
Just say it.
Yes.
We found the corpse of
test taker Shan Cha in the suburbs.
She has been sent to the Siyin Lineage
for an autopsy.
Shan Cha is dead?
Where are we going now?
To the Siyin Lineage.
Bravo! Bravo!
Bravo!
You're really in a good mood.
You came to brothel as soon as you got out of prison.
Arrest the man
by his side.
Yes.
Qi Yanran.
What do you want?
I think your lackeys must've
told you.
One of the Royal Sorcerer test taker died.
Those who were close to them
are a major suspect.
Besides,
he has demonic aura within him.
As for Hu Zi,
I have already explained it
very clearly at the hall.
If you have no other evidence,
this is framing him.
Since you have so much to say,
then take them all to Tiangang Hall
for interrogation.
Let's see who dares to capture him.
Are you protecting a suspect?
I'll take them there.
Let's go.
Commander Yanran.
Your father always praises you.
As expected, like father, like son.
You did well.
I wouldn't dare to steal the credit.
It is still your
witty decision.
Chief Commander,
the suspect and his accomplices
have been brought back from Wanchun Pavilion.
Suspect?
You're being too arbitrary.
Do you have evidence?
Qi Xiaoxuan.
Tell me.
Why did you enter the Ghost Market at night
and protect Hu Zi over and over again?
Chief Commander,
the disappearance of the sorcerers
have been ongoing for months.
Shan Cha's death
is closely related to the disappearance
of the earlier sorcerers too.
I went to the Ghost Market
to find relevant clues.
Royal Sorcerers have never shied away from
associating with people from the Ghost Market.
But you went straight
to go visit brothels there.
Yet you have the cheek to say you're investigating the case as an excuse.
Qi Yanran.
I dare swear upon the Zhao Sect's name
that
we went to the Ghost Market
to investigate the case.
On the other hand,
you kept trying to
to make things difficult for us.
I suspect you're–
You'll be flogged if you shout at the hall.
My throat isn't feeling well.
You work
with this demon,
how can you testify for him?
Ridiculous.
Hu Zi is not a demon.
This matter has already been made public.
Besides, when the case started,
Hu Zi was living in Ruyun Village.
There is no way he could've committed crimes in the capital.
Excuses.
One is a missing person,
and the other is a murder.
How can they be one case?
I heard from the test takers that
before the Shan Cha died,
he went to
this little demon's room.
There is solid evidence.
I don't even want to explain anymore.
No one listens even if I do.
It's useless to say more.
Unlike some villain
with a sharp tongue
who only knows how to speak.
Five days.
Give me five days.
I will catch the murderer
and avenge Shan Cha.
What a bluff.
What if you can't do it in five days?
I'm willing to be imprisoned as punishment..
But this
has nothing to do with them.
Please don't get them involved.
Hu Zi,
can you not be so arrogant?
Chief Commander,
this person likes to talk big
and say things out of anger.
Don't take it to heart.
I'm a man of my word.
A promise is a promise.
Very well.
You can leave now.
I'll give you three days.
If you can't find out the truth in three days,
you'll be sentenced to prison.
Others
will be deprived of the right to take the exam.
As for Qi Xiaoxuan,
he will be removed of the position of a commander.
-I just said it has nothing to do with them.
-Yes, Sir.
Hu Zi.
You dug a hole
for yourself to jump in.
Three days.
Where can we find the murderer?
Shall we just retreat?
I think Brick is right.
Why don't you take this opportunity
to leave Fulong Capital.
How can I retreat?
I've already implicated you.
If I leave, you...
It's okay.
At this point,
we can only find the murderer.
I don't believe
we can't catch the murderer
if we work together.
We didn't find any clues
for the missing sorcerer case.
Finding Shan Cha's corpse
was a mistake made by the murderer.
Let's go to Siyin Lineage
to find out the truth.
[Siyin Lineage]
Miss Shan Cha
is really dead.
The last time I saw her,
she said
she would make me
even tastier desserts next time.
Who would have thought...
The dead is gone.
It's useless to be sad.
We must seek justice
for the deceased.
And make the murderer pay with his blood.
There's no external injury on the Shan Cha's body.
But all her spirit essences
were sucked away.
It's not done by an ordinary person.
To be able to suck dry one's spirit essences,
what kind of sorcery is this?
I've never seen it before.
But to be able to
use such magic,
their level of cultivation
must be at least above Demon Lord.
So they're as strong as Black Wind?
What is it?
Mane.
Judging from the color
and texture of this mane,
it's not an ordinary horse.
You're right.
The analysis makes sense.
Senior.
I went to the Collection Pavillion
to check the demon name list.
This mane came from
a Horse Demon from a hundred years ago.
Its beast form is a horse
with a white body, black tail, and curved nails.
It sounds like a drum.
It's very dangerous.
Senior,
do you know where this Horse Demon lives
and if they have any weaknesses?
Weaknesses?
The Horse Demon likes to eat Monals,
also known as Nine-color Bird.
The feathers of Nine-color Bird
shines like a rainbow under harsh sunlight.
It has the ability to set a curse on Horse Demon.
When the Horse Demon sees it, they won't be able to control themselves
and will surely capture it.
If it's really
this Horse Demon you're talking about,
let's find a Nine-colored Bird
to lure it out
and that should work, no?
Although the nine-color bird
resides in the Fulong Capital,
they are very vigilant.
It's not easy to catch it.
This
is a magic tool to attract birds and beasts.
Why don't you use it
to attract the Nine-colored Bird.
So magical?
Stop.
Who told you to blow it here?
You'll end up not luring birds
but flies.
This can attract flies too?
Give it to me.
Thank you, Senior.
I didn't expect
you'd have such a magic tool.
Yanluo Hall
imprisons various demons.
Some of them feed on birds.
This was found on a
body that was incinerated.
We've been waiting for so long, but there's no bird.
The nine-color bird
often hides in the forest
and won't meet ordinary walking creatures.
What about the whistle?
Is that necessary? You think it's dirty?
If you keep blowing,
the crows will come.
There's no illness on it!
It's coming.
Is this it?
Don't move.
A little more.
Wait.
I told you to wait.
But its head...
Blow it again.
How reckless.
Rash.
Stupid.
I didn't pull it well.
Alright.
The whistle can't be used anymore.
The bird won't come back.
I have an idea.
Look.
So beautiful.
Miss.
It's Mr. Qi and the others.
Miss Mu Dan.
Why are you so excited?
She's not looking for you.
Mr. Qi,
may I have a word with you?
No need.
We have something important to do.
We'll take our leave.
We'll wait for you in front.
Xiaoxuan
really can't read the cues.
He should study
the love novels
I made for him.
He should do some research.
It's useless.
This Ice Cube Face
has ice for his heart.
I hope Miss Mu Dan
can melt him.
Why are you two so talkative?
Let's go.
Let's stop talking.
Miss Mu Dan.
If you have anything to say,
just go ahead.
Mr. Qi,
are you still upset
about last night?
No.
I was rude last night.
Please forgive me.
If there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave.
Are you investigating
the disappearance of the sorcerers?
This has nothing to do with you.
Goodbye.
Mr. Qi.
I've sent people to search for clues
about the disappearance of the sorcerers.
Mr. Qi,
please come to Wanchun Pavilion again tonight.
No need.
We have new clues.
We won't bother you.
Goodbye.
Where did you
find this chicken shed?
Any place with food and drinks
can't escape my nose.
You stole the Phoenix Cake
from my room?
I need to move away from the room next to yours.
Do you think people from Fulong City
are fools?
You're going to fool them with a chicken?
There are a few feathers here.
Just put them in.
Brick.
Dye the chicken
and no one will be able to tell.
I can give it a try.
But I can't guarantee that it won't expose itself.
I've prepared the painting tools for you.
All the best.
What are you doing?
Royal Sorcerers
never steal.
That's too much.
Fine.
This one.
Very good!
Not bad, Brick.
Amazing art skills. It looks the same.
Are you sure
this is the species
as the one we saw in the forest?
Does it look like it?
Resemblance aside,
this chicken is so clumsy.
He doesn't look like a celestial bird at all.
I think you're the ones
who are clumsy.
How many people have seen
the real Nine-colored Bird?
Let's do this for now.
The next step is to see
if we can attract the Horse Demon.
I've been hungry for the whole day.
Mr. Qi,
can we talk while eating?
Yes.
I'm hungry too.
Let's go eat.
Sure.
[Zuihua House]
This is the famous
Zuihua House in the capital?
I heard that the dishes here are excellent.
It's difficult to even get a reservation.
Really?
I'm in for a feast.
Xiaoxuan,
what's your plan?
I've told the boss
of the open-air theatre
to spread the news of the
nine-color bird to the capital.
Tomorrow,
we'll catch the Horse Demon at the theatre.
Will he not show up?
He will.
This is his only weakness.
And the nine-color bird
is known as a lucky bird in the mortal world.
Those who see it will be blessed.
There will be many people who would come forward to see the bird.
We need to prepare in advance.
What are you going to do?
Xintong is in charge of the front door.
She can also dress up as a flower seller.
Report immediately
when there is anyone suspicious.
Flowers!
Wang Yuqian will be in charge of the inside of the theatre.
You will guide the people to their seats.
Report immediately
when you hear Xingtong's signal.
A divine bird has descended from heaven.
Please come in.
Sir.
A divine bird has descended from heaven.
Please come in.
I'm in charge of the capture.
Rise.
Good.
Good!
Look.
Good.
Good!
I've never seen it before.
Yes.
What about me?
You guard the last stage.
You have to make sure he doesn't run way from the back door.
Make him unable to escape even if he has wings.
We only have one chance tomorrow.
Don't let your guard down.
I'm here. Don't worry.
I will definitely...
Mr. Qi, the food is ready.
Serve!
Yes.
Do you have to be this generous?
Mr. Qi is so generous.
I'm don't get to eat such good things even in Qianyu State.
What is this compared to being there?
You made a right choice following us.
Yes.
I'll follow you from now on.
This is the critical move to our success.
No mistakes are allowed.
With this meal,
it's not a problem with even
ten more demons.
Let's eat!
Miss,
a kite is here.
Greetings, Miss.
Did you see anything?
Miss,
You've been waiting for four hours.
The dishes are getting cold.
Do you want me to
warm it up for you?
Take it away.
He won't come.
Yes.
Bravo!
Didn't you say there's a Nine-colored Bird?
Take it out!
Yes.
Who wants to see
these junk.
Exactly.
If there isn't the Nine-colored Divine Bird,
give us back our money!
-Refund! -Refund!
Refund!
The Nine-colored Bird will be here soon.
Don't worry.
Calm down.
Very well!
I
shall present the star of today,
the Nine-colored Divine Bird.
Good!
What a rare sight.
Look.
Have a look.
The divine bird has descended to the world, the country will be prosperous and the people will be at peace.
Everyone,
to be lucky enough to have a look at the divine bird today...
Look! The celestial bird!
You will definitely be blessed
and healthy.
Good.
What are you doing?
You can't touch this.
Bird.
Big bird!
Stay still!
Colorful birds!
Don't move.
Colorful bird.
Can it be him?
He was tricked,
to deliberately cause chaos.
Shut up!
Colorful bird!
No.
This sound...
Listening to this sound...
That's not right.
-Why does it sound like a chicken crow?
-Exactly.
It's not a bird.
This is a scam.
That man!
Where is he?
He ran too fast.
It's definitely a demon.
No one can run faster than me.
What should we do now?
How about
I draw another one?
No.
We wanted to lure them out quietly
but we alerted them.
This plan won't work.
Let's go back to the inn first.
We'll discuss it later.
This demon is really cunning.
He even sent someone
to check it out first.
It will be difficult to use the divine bird
to lure him out again.
Hu Zi,
you were at the very front
when we chased him.
Did you see his face?
He was covering his face.
And he ran so fast.
But I saw his figure clearly.
What is it like?
I don't think he's fat.
All of us
can see that.
At least, that eliminates
some people.
What should we do now?
Didn't we agree
for you to guard the back door.
Why did you go to the stage?
I was eager to catch the demon.
I didn't expect them to...
I...
But I...
Isn't that Sister Mu Dan?
Mr. Qi,
you didn't come last night as promised.
I had something important to do. It was inconvenient for me to visit.
Is that something important
is to have fun with these friends
at Zuihua House?
That's amazing.
She's indeed well-informed.
What brings you here
today?
I heard
you failed in catching the demon at the theatre.
You are so well-informed.
I'm here to tell you
I've received a tip-off.
Most of the missing sorcerers
had their spirit essences
fully sucked up by the demon
and had their body hid.
We already
know about this.
The culprit
is now hiding within
the Royal Sorcerers.
Have you found out about this too?
Is your information accurate?
If it's just groundless accusations,
I wouldn't dare to tell you.
How can I believe
the words of a homeless beggar?
These homeless beggars
that you despise
are my most trusted eyes and ears
in the whole city.
They are like kites
that I set out with a string in hand
to get information
that you can't buy even with a lot of money.
Miss Mu Dan.
I don't mean any despise.
Sorry for bothering you
by visiting so late.
Why did she leave?
Did you piss her off so she left?
What did she say?
People like you
are destined to die alone.
Right?
Yes.
The old single men in my village
Grandpa Yan and Grandpa Guo
were all like this when they got old.
Don't talk nonsense.
Maybe Miss Mu Dan
admires his concentration.
If you two
had any concentration,
this case would have been solved long ago.
She said this Horse Demon
is hidden among the Royal Sorcerers.
Royal Sorcerers?
There are thousands of Royal Sorcerers
in the capital.
How can we investigate in such a short time?
Take a rest.
I'll go to the Tiangang Hall to report.
And see
how we can investigate the Royal Sorcerers.
Is all you know to report?
Why do you report everything?
-When you've reported–
-Stop talking.
We'll wait for him here.
No.
We can't just wait.
It'll be too late after his report.
Let me go meet her again.
What if her news
are more reliable than that of Tiangang Hall's?
That's strange.
That old lady
was here.
Did I...
Enough.
Don't bother.
Fairy,
this person has a unique physique.
His spirit essences could not be touched.
This is the first time
I'm met with this kind of situation.
You shouldn't have captured him.
This kid has the Phurba in his body.
If you want to take his spirit essences,
I'm afraid you can't do it
even if I lent you 50% of my power.
Phurba?
He is the Vessel
that you have been looking for years?
He is the most important part
in the whole plan.
Nothing must go wrong.
You
are not allowed to set him up anymore.
Yes.
I will also find a way
to activate the Phurba in his body
step by step
through the Royal Sorcerer competition.
Go back and tell your master
to finish the collection
of spirit essences as soon as possible.
In that case,
when the time comes,
we can act immediately.
Don't worry.
Since we received your order last month,
we have sped up our collection
and it's almost complete.
You should be careful.
Tiangang Hell is already investigating this.
Don't
ruin the plan because of this.
Yes.
If you are unfocused,
why bother putting yourself in a tight spot?
A day has passed
and we got not a single clue.
After tonight,
there will only be two days left.
The more tricky it is,
the more we can't be anxious about it.
It's late.
I thought I would be the only one
who couldn't sleep at night.
I didn't expect everyone is still up.
Where is Hu Zi?
Is he not in his room?
No.
I just went.
The quilt
was cold.
He's not with you?
I haven't seen him.
He was so anxious.
Did he take action alone?
It's so late.
Could something have happened?
Let's go find him.
Next,
it's time to activate the Phurba.
Fairy.
What should we do specifically?
It takes three stages
to activate the Phurba.
The first step is material stage.
Hu Zi has to use it to kill
a demon above Demon Elder level with it
[Material Stage
The first stage. Hu Zi has to use it to kill a demon above Demon Elder level with it to activate it.]
to activate it.
The second stage is Bodhicitta stage.
[Bodhicitta stage
The second stage. This is not that easy]
[He has to break through the demon obstacle and overcome his inner obsession to activate it.]
This is not that easy
He has to break through the demon obstacle
and overcome his inner obsession
to activate it.
What about the last stage?
I'll keep you in suspense for now.
Do you think
with the talent of Hu Zi,
we can get through
these three stages successfully?
It's not about whether we can,
but we have to.
We found someone like this only after 500 years.
Now the arrow is on the string.
There's no other way.
Fortunately, this kid
is smart
and took Eldest Master as his master.
I will use Eldest Master
to train him faster.
I will choose a full moon night
to help him break through the first stage.
Why does it have to be a full moon night?
That's the time where the Phurba
has the strongest energy.
We've searched all the streets,
but I didn't even see his shadow.
Did he get captured
by the Horse Demon?
What if he was captured?
All he knows is to act on impulse.
If he acts alone now,
isn't he just adding to the trouble for everyone else?
I'd rather that
he's scared
and has escaped the city in the dark.
How is that possible?
Hu Zi wouldn't escape.
I mean...
I was just saying.
Hu Zi.
Why is he here?
How is he?
He's fine.
He's fine?
Well, then...
could he be hurt
in other places?
It seems like
he's not hurt.
He must've gone eating alone.
He's asleep.
The three of us
looked for him all night.
Yet he's here sleeping so soundly.
He's sleeping soundly.
Heaven ground–
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
We've been waiting for you all night.
Yet you're sleeping here?
What happened to you yesterday?
Why were you sleeping in front
of the inn today morning?
I...
I ran into the Horse Demon!
I was about to follow him.
But I was knocked out the moment
I turned into an alley.
I don't remember anything after that.
Why didn't you wait for my news
and took action alone.
Wait for you?
Then three days would have passed.
Did you report yesterday?
How did it go?
We need evidence.
See? I told you.
It would be wasting time on
those close-minded people.
We might as well investigate it ourselves?
I don't think it's right.
You said you met Horse Demon
at the Ghost Market.
Then why
not only did he not hurt you,
but also sent you back
safely.
Right...
Do you think it's because
I was born with divine power.
He's afraid of me.
Let's not talk about this.
There are many test takers here.
It will cause panic.
Yes.
We looked for you all night.
We didn't eat anything all night.
We're starving.
Me too.
Let's go and eat something.
I'm starving.
Hu Zi,
the fish last time was not bad.
The fish is just so-so. The chicken is not bad.
Let's continue today.
Okay.
Sir, would you like a bowl?
What happened last night?
When I went to the Ghost Market last night,
I saw the suspicious person
at the scene of the Nine-colored Bird.
How do you know it's the same person?
It must be him.
I was the closest to him.
I almost caught him.
That back.
It can't be wrong.
Instead of sleeping at night, Hu Zi,
why did you go to the Ghost Market?
You refuse to go
and just wait here for nothing.
I can't wait.
It's said that the Ghost Market is complicated.
There are all kinds of people.
Can't I try my luck?
And then?
He walked into an alley
suspiciously.
I immediately
followed him.
Unfortunately, he was too cunning
and hit me from the back.
When I opened my eyes again.
I was already back at the inn.
After saying so much,
it's as if you didn't say anything.
There's no useful information at all.
You're only making trouble.
How is it useless?
At least I know
he's afraid of me.
He doesn't dare to fight me head-on.
Think about it.
In the end,
he sent me back
safely.
He sent you back safely.
That's the most suspicious thing.
Right?
Yes.
He abducted so many sorcerers.
Why did he send you back?
Need I say that?
He and that demon
are of the same species.
Cheng Jinian.
Why are you here asking for beating again?
I only heard that the demon
captures people and sucks them dry
of their spirit essenses.
I've never heard of them
sending the people back safely.
Tell me.
If you are not related to that demon,
then what?
Yes, I am.
I'll bite you to death now. Come.
Don't take action
in this broad daylight.
This would add another sin to your name for picking a fight.
We don't even need two days.
You can be imprisoned today.
Cheng Jinian.
What do you want?