[English subtitles are available]
[Tiger and Crane]
[Episode 12]
[Baihua Mountain Trial]
Flower in the mirror, moon in the water,
they are all illusions.
I hope one day
you can blossom again.
Young Master.
When did you come back?
This is your first time home
since you returned to the capital.
I came back to get something.
I'll leave soon.
This is...
When you weren't around,
Xiaowu hasn't been in a good mood.
It doesn't eat or drink all day.
The weather is nice today.
So I took it out
for a walk.
I won't do it again.
It's fine.
Put it back.
Yes.
Such a big thing happened in the capital.
You still have the time
to raise flowers and play with birds here?
What are you doing here?
I'm here to tell you
don't think you can be reinstated
after killing the Horse Demon
and everything will be fine for you.
If you didn't kill the Horse Demon
and lost the clue,
the Council of Elders wouldn't have
blamed the Qi family
for not doing our jobs right.
You're a disgrace to the Qi Sect.
Are you done scolding me?
Leave if you are.
I really don't know
what that old lady likes about you.
She supports you to get promoted so much.
Don't worry.
I never thought about
competing with you for anything.
How fake.
You're not competing with me?
But you still took
this body back then.
What?
I got you good?
Let me tell you.
No matter how you disguise yourself,
you can't be him.
You are still that coward
and weak person you used to be.
Don't think that just because that old lady
is supporting you
you can be the commander-in-chief.
As long as I'm here,
don't ever think of that.
Good brothers.
Yan and Qian are good brothers.
Qian.
Save this parrot.
You're better at healing than me.
[Qian, save this parrot. You are better at healing than I am.]
Yan.
Don't worry.
It's fine now.
Good brothers.
Good brothers?
Yan and Qian are good brothers.
Good brothers.
We are good brothers.
Yan and Gan are good brothers.
Good brothers.
We are good brothers.
Good brother.
Hu Zi.
Let go!
Forget it.
Come and take a look.
Hu Zi!
Hu Zi is hitting me!
Get more witnesses
so you can testify at the Tiangang Hall.
Stop arguing!
[Captain of Tiangang Hall Team 11
Ximen Miaomiao]
Did anyone
see my cat?
[Subduing demons to help the world]
Let go!
Pretty girl.
This is the in
for the Royal Sorcerer Exam takers.
What cat are you looking for?
Tell me.
I'll help you find it.
It's a white cat
called Xiaoyao.
Can you help me
look for it together?
[Subduing demons to help the world]
Hurry up.
Find this pretty girl find it.
Hurry up!
Yes.
Search everywhere.
Search carefully.
Okay.
Xiaoyao!
Come out.
[Subduing demons to help the world]
Xiaoyao,
where are you?
Don't move!
Xiaoyao.
Be good.
Here.
Don't run around again.
Thank you, everyone.
By the way,
I'm here to send you a letter.
Tomorrow morning at class time,
the content of the Royal Sorcerer Exam's preliminary round
will be announced at the lecture stage.
Please spread the news
and come on time.
Let's go.
Who is she?
I don't know.
We can go back now.
Don't run around.
I regret it.
I didn't hit Cheng Jinian again.
I...
I'm so useless.
Bear with it.
Prepare for the exam.
If you cause trouble before the exam,
you'll be disqualified.
Also,
there's still a lot of time.
When we become Royal Sorcerers,
right?
There are plenty of opportunities to teach him a lesson.
Oh right.
The exam is coming.
Which hall do you want to enter?
Tiangang wields the sword,
Disha investigates,
and Yanluo supervises.
I'll choose Tiangang Hall.
I will focus on capturing demons.
What about you?
I will follow Hu Zi.
I'll go wherever he goes.
I'm going to Yanluo Hall.
Why Yanluo Hall?
Killing
is quite boring.
I'm not very educated.
This can make up for it.
No.
This is not your style.
This is an administrative role.
After you entered Yanluo Hall,
you will just be collecting the information
of demons over hundreds of years.
It's very boring.
Right?
It's indeed quite boring.
To find Mother's clues,
I can only enter Yanluo Hall.
No matter which hall you choose in the end,
you still have to fight with your martial arts
during the exam.
You still need to practice hard.
Don't slack off.
When we get to the battleground,
we'll meet with our weapons.
Hu Zi.
Shouldn't you choose
a good weapon first?
Silly boy.
The best weapon
is in your body.
I came to you
to ask you for a favor.
Fairy,
go ahead.
It's about Hu Zi.
Hu Zi?
Phurba in his body
can't suppress the demonic tail for a long time.
If he can't control
the power of Phurba,
I'm afraid
he will be devoured by it instead.
To get rid of the demonic tail completely,
he has to activate Phurba.
Thank you for your concern.
Even if you didn't tell me,
I'd have done the same.
I can't let that brat
receive a baby
yet just leave it there.
Leave it to me.
But there's one thing I don't understand.
If we take Phurba
out his body,
how can we suppress the demonic tail?
Don't worry.
What we take out
would just be the shell of Phurba.
Its real body
will still in be Hu Zi's body.
If the shell is away
for too long,
it will force its way to return to its body.
I see.
Thank you, Eldest Master.
Hu Zi has potential.
Maybe
we can see
how amazing Phurba was years ago.
[Yihe Charity]
Search!
Yes!
[Ghost Market]
[Tavern]
Sir,
are you trying to find a living thing in Ghost Market?
I heard that
you have connections.
The Tiangang Hall
has been keeping a close eye.
Money is not a problem.
But
I want
a living thing from the Demon Burning Pagoda.
Are you crazy?
Those demons have a mark burned onto them.
Why do you want them for?
I have my own purpose.
You just need to answer me
if you have them
or not.
No.
I only have some small pig demons.
Their skills are nothing compared to those
in the Demon Burning Pagoda.
You have wide connections.
Have you heard
of a demon appearing
in the Ghost Market?
Since the High-ranking Courtsen Mu DAn
transformed into a demon,
Tiangang Hall searched through
the entire Ghost Market.
Not to mention demons,
even those who committed crimes
were all captured.
See.
Today,
the Royal Sorcerers came checking through
every single shop.
I don't know
what they want to investigate.
It's so strange.
These demons
haven't made any move.
Could something have happened at
Tiangang Hall?
Did a demon escape?
We can't hide it for too long.
We need to find a clue.
[Tavern]
Do you still want the Pig Demon?
[To reach the top of the world]
We've been in the capital
for so long.
We are finally taking the exam.
The three of us
will definitely pass.
That's right.
[Captain of Tiangang Hall Team 12
Mo Guzi]
Nian.
What is he up to?
I don't know.
He's been standing here all morning.
He's probably a test taker.
Everyone can
take the Royal Sorcerer Exam nowadays?
The threshold is too low.
Exactly.
Brick.
Xintong.
Where is Hu Zi?
He didn't come with you?
Didn't he come earlier?
Didn't you see him?
Pretty girl.
He's sick.
Stay away from him.
Why did you hit me?
I,
the captain of Tiangang Hall Team 11,
Ximen Miaomiao,
is your supervisor for the preliminary exam.
Greetings, teacher.
Why is she wearing casual clothes?
She's here for class today.
Not anything else?
You don't believe me?
I do.
I do...
Test takers who have come far and wide,
the preliminary exam of the Royal Sorcerer Exam
will officially begin in three days.
Today, I will explain
the rules of the preliminary exam.
Before we start,
I'll play a game with you first.
If anyone can receive
the bell in my hand,
can have an exception made
and become a Royal Sorcerer straight.
Good!
Great!
Really?
Of course.
I never lie.
This...
So fast?
I didn't see.
There's no chance anymore?
I'm not ready yet.
Why did he get it?
Exactly.
You'd better tell everyone
the rules first.
Congratulations, Mo Gu
for capturing the bell in advance.
Then be my cat
for the day.
Shui.
What's going on?
Who is this person?
I thought he's been strange since just now.
He's albino.
Mo Guzi.
I heard
no one wants to make friends with him.
So I want to ask
what the rules are for the preliminary exam.
I have no choice.
I don't like teaching.
I will just make it simple.
Baihua Mountain.
Form your own teams.
The first team to get a hundred Demon Pearls
from the Bee Demon
will advance directly.
A hundred?
Just a hundred?
That's no problem.
That's too much.
Exactly.
If we want more pearls,
then there should be more people in the team.
Tong.
Team up with me.
With my ability,
let alone a hundred pearls,
even a thousand pearls is a piece of cake.
I won't team up with you.
Go away.
Are you still going to
team up with Hu Zi?
Hasn't he been enough of a burden to you?
Cheng Jinian.
I'm just away for a brief moment
and you're messing around again.
What are you up to now?
Are you sure you won’t team up with me?
Don’t regret it, Tong.
How dare you call her Tong?
The demon is here!
I can also be merciful
and take you in.
But you have to give us the
Demon Pearl in your body too.
Right?
Yes.
That's right.
Sure.
Here.
Let's share it now.
All right.
Looks like everyone is in a good mood.
See you at Baihua Mountain
in three days.
Fairy.
They sent more men
to the Sorcerer's Inn.
It doesn't matter.
The most important thing now
is to activate the first stage of
Phurba in Hu Zi's body.
I've sent the Eldest Master
to enlighten him.
Now,
the three main halls have prohibited demon catching.
This is bad.
Do you know the saying
that goes "black under the light"?
They are in the light.
While we are in the dark.
Now that we know where the light is,
it's instead easier.
[Xizhao Pavilion]
Aren't you going to sleep a little more?
I've slept enough.
What are you braiding?
You're hiding from me.
No.
I want to see it.
I want to see it!
Show me.
Show me!
Annoying.
I won't see it anymore.
I'm not done yet.
I'll show it to you
once I'm done.
Fine.
By the way...
Is it time to go feed
Liang Shan Han and Ye Luo Niang?
Sure.
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
Even the chickens are not up yet
and we got dragged out
for me to learn how to control this.
Hu Zi did work very hard
to control Phurba.
But he lost his focus slightly
and it went back into his tummy,
turning his world upside down.
Eldest Master,
can I change my weapon?
I think I'm quite good at using this.
Do you think
those mere fists of yours
can always come in handy.
Is the Royal Sorcerer Exam
that easy?
Power, strategy, and courage,
these are all important.
What's the use of just fists?
I...
Stop talking.
Eldest Master,
please give us some guidance.
Xintong is wise.
Brat.
Watch and learn.
What's going on?
Don't worry.
Phurba, unlike normal weapons,
can only be controlled by spirit essences.
You need to gather your spirit essences
onto your hands.
Is this Phurba so heavy?
Hu Zi,
hang in there.
I'm hanging in there.
What's the use of just hanging in there.
The strength is not right.
How can you hold it?
I can't anymore.
I really can't anymore.
Eldest Master!
What is this?
Why can't it be picked up nor put down?
Everything is alive.
Unlike ordinary weapons,
Phurba,
essentially,
just like me,
is a magic weapon.
It's just that it's unconscious.
When Phurba was in your hands,
it was like a dehydrated fish
struggling desperately.
With the wrong strength,
how can you hold it?
It's not you holding Phurba.
To be accurate,
it's Phurba holding you.
It held me.
Yi Mei Fairy planted Phurba
into your Dantian.
You have to treat it
as a part of your body.
Use the spirit essences' strength
to match its breathing.
One in each hand.
Before the sun sets,
don't let it touch the ground.
You two too!
What?
Before the sun sets?
The sun j-just
rose.
Think before you do it.
If you can't do it well,
then don't take the Royal Sorcerer Exam!
I...
I'm tired.
I need to go take a rest.
When you can
hold Phurba,
I'll teach you how to control it.
[Peaceful and Smooth Breeze]
Mo Gu.
Do you think Ye Luo Niang lost weight?
A little.
Sometimes,
it's good to be a cat too.
It's carefree.
[Peaceful and Smooth Breeze]
How do you know
they have no worries?
Can't be more than those of humans'.
Mo Gu.
You
are too introverted.
You should come into contact with more people.
People are too noisy.
They
only focus on the surface
and neglect the inside.
Sometimes,
spending too much time with people,
you'd like to be alone more and more.
Some people
are not even as cute as those cats.
Really?
Except you.
This doesn't suit me.
Look at this weather.
I’ll catch a chicken to improve your health.
Xintong.
Don’t worry.
I will definitely
become a Royal Sorcerer with you.
Keep your water bucket stable
before we talk.
You need to use your spirit essences
to hold onto the water bucket
instead of actually lifting it with your strength.
Try it.
It seems to work.
Not too much strength.
You have to stabilize your spirit essences.
Otherwise, it will deplete at a faster rate.
It's too hard.
Master really
left such a difficult task
and went to rest himself.
Eldest Master must have his reason
for this request.
We have to trust him.
Are you really not going to drink?
Go away.
I won’t stop if Xintong doesn't stop.
Xintong’s has practiced the horse stance
since she was a kid.
How can you compete with her?
Go away.
Hey,
it's time
for lunch.
Xintong.
Stop here
and have a rest.
Let's have
the chicken soup I made.
It can replenish your spirit essences.
It's not that easy to replenish spirit essences.
You think you stewed chicken essence?
You still have the mood to joke?
You're trembling so hard.
Enough, enough.
Don't disturb him anymore.
Go and drink elsewhere.
-Practice hard, Hu Zi.
-Xintong.
Xintong, try it.
This water bucket is unlike Phurba.
It won't absorb my spirit essences.
I have to try
using the least amount of spirit essences to hold it
and keep my balance.
Hu Zi.
Are you okay?
You're out of energy already?
Your spirit essence is golden.
It is very special.
I thought
you'd be able to stay till night.
Looks like I overestimated you.
You mean you want to
exhaust his spirit essences?
It's like a mortal warrior
building their muscles.
After being exhausted from weight exercises,
doing some simple exercises
could help them better feel
the presence of the muscles
and the trace of their exercise.
Here.
Drink.
Silly boy.
Take out Phurba
and have a look again.
Even though Phurba
is sucking your spirit essences,
since your spirit essences
have basically run out,
there's only a thin stream going towards it
and it won't block
your meridians.
Take this opportunity
to feel it properly again.
It's said that magic weapons are like its master.
Hu Zi,
you can control Phurba now?
As Master said,
it takes spirit essences
to maintain Phurba.
But if I inject my energy
into it like flowing water
like on normal days,
I will be sucked dry very soon.
Instead,
feeding it mouthful by mouthful like this is better.
Silly boy.
In the battles from now on,
you must focus.
Once you lose your focus,
you won't be able to maintain Phurba.
You need more practice.
From now on,
even when you're sleeping,
you have to be holding onto Phurba
to sleep.
[Fulong State]
What crane?
It's obviously a goose.
Brick.
Yuqian!
You're quick-witted.
You have to be fast too.
Let's begin.
They...
have given up on themselves.
No burn mark.
It's not a demon from the Demon Burning Pagoda.
Are you a Royal Sorcerer?
There are demons!
A few demons appeared
out of nowhere in that cave over there!
It hurts.
Hu Zi.
Hu Zi,
Hu Zi, stop eating,
Hu Zi.
One can only take the exam when they're full.
Master said
it's useful to keep it.
[Sorcerer's Inn]
What's wrong?
Master.
Thank you, master.
After eating these skewers,
don't throw away these sticks.
Why?
For another meal?
It's useful to deal with those bee demons.
Why didn't Eldest Master
send us off?
What if we are
met with danger
during the exam?
What's there to send us for?
You should grow up.
Don't hold us back.
Stop dawdling.
Everyone is there.
Greetings, Miss Miaomiao.
Everyone.
Long time no see.
The mountain behind me
is the famous Baihua Mountain.
There are a bunch of
lovely bee demons.
Before sunset,
collect hundred bee pearls
and hand them over to me
to be qualified
for the next round.
Pay attention to this.
The number of bee pearls is limited.
There is only one entrance and exit
in this mountain.
Don't take the wrong path.
Please ask the assistant, Mo Gu, for the map.
Mo Gu?
More like a poisonous mushroom.
A deadly poisonous one too.
You...
The three of them are late again today.
Wait for me.
The four of you
go take post at each base.
If any of the test takers
are in danger,
send a signal to let me know immediately.
Yes.
What a beautiful bracelet.
Is this what you were making last time?
Is it for me?
It wasn't completed previously,
but now it is.
We'll definitely
be the first to arrive this time.
I don't think it's right.
We will be.
[Xiangnian Shan]
Xiangnian Mountain.
Xiangnian Mountain?
This...
This is the place on the map.
How did we end up at Xiangnian Mountain?
Did you meet anyone
when you took this map?
This...
This was the last map.
Cheng Jinian was there.
Cheng Jinian?
We are done for!
It must be him behind this.
How could you be so careless?
We must get even with him.
But the most urgent thing now
is to find
the right route.
[Xiangnian Shan]
W-what route?
Brick!
[Baihua Mountain]
Who is it?
Why are you rushing in?
We...
[Baihua Mountain]
Are test takers today.
You can't get in anymore.
In order to prevent the bee demons
from coming down and hurting the people.
The formation at the entrance
has already been activated.
You can't get in.
Brother,
we were tricked just now.
Please make an exception.
We will make it quick.
It's not that I don't want to help you,
we don't have the right too.
You can only blame yourselves
for being too late.
No.
We were...
Go back, go back.
Map.
I have an idea.
Here?
There is no formation here
nor the way up the mountain.
This map shows that
this is a way down the mountain.
Xintong.
Is this the idea you're
thinking about?
In spring, many interesting flowers bloom
in  Baihua Mountain.
People come here for fun.
This rope
is probably meant for
people who went up to come down of the mountain with.
But after the bee demons moved in,
it has been deserted for a long time.
Are we really
going to go up the mountain in this way?
I'm not climbing it.
I...
I'm afraid of heights
Loser.
We're already here.
You can't give up.
I'm afraid.
Stop dawdling.
Come here.
Young Master.
Bee Pearl.
How is it going for Hu Zi?
There are no news from Hu Zi.
He must be trapped outside.
But Xiao Yunzi and the others
snatched many bee pearls from us.
Then send more people
to compete with him
and snatch it from him.
I must be the first one
to get a hundred bee pearls.
Go.
Yes, sir.
Brick.
Why aren't you fighting it?
It wasn't easy to get in.
Bee...
Bee hive.
Isn't that perfect?
If we don't enter a tiger den, we can't get the tiger's son.
Why don't we go in
and catch them all?
What do you think?
That's right.
Be careful.
Why...
Why are they all rushing out?
S-So many bee demons.
We can take the chance to go in now.
Let's go.
Say,
what if the bee demons
return?
So stop talking nonsense
and fight them
Xintong.
I’m counting on you.
Be careful.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
No.
This place is too small.
I can't use this spear.
It's okay.
Master has foresight.
Do you really think I was
really just eating skewers?
Fight it with this.
Is this enough?
Shall we go?
You're kidding.
We need a hundred.
How many is this?
How about we go further in?
The nest should be inside.
We have to go further in?
What do you think?
It was a small number of them just now so it was easy to deal with.
What if there are more inside? We'll...
Then hide.
They didn't sting you just now.
Over there.
The hive!
Today
is a good day.
This
is also a good place.
Where do you think
would be the most suitable place?
Looks like we didn't have to break a sweat at all.
No wonder this mountain exit
was abandoned.
The edge of the cliff that is easy to defend and difficult to attack
is the perfect spot for the bee hive.
We are really lucky.
Let's
go back the same way.
Objection.
Let's take the main road.
You don't have to carry me.
He's grown up.
He's mature now.
Let's do it here.
Let's see
his training results.
This is
the Red Pearl replaced last month.
The formation is currently operating well.
There has been no more problems.
You are the first person
to find out the crack on the Red Pearl.
Was there
anything unusual?
Were there any suspecious people
or demons who appeared?
No.
Ordinary people
avoided the legendary sea.
Royal Sorcerers who've visited
will have their names recorded.
The whole defense line is heavily guarded.
If a demon comes here to make trouble,
they are asking to be caught.
All right.
Be more alert.
Don't let your guard down.
Yes.
Report immediately
if there's anything abnormal.
Yes.
Yi Mei Fairy
should be in the capital now.
The demonic energy here
is obviously stronger than the places we've been through.
There was a formation here.
This formation is a forbidden skill.
It is to let demonic energy
to keep injecting into Phurba,
to make its divine power immortal.
What a strong demonic aura.
So many cages.
There should be many demons that have been captured here.
Black Wind Demon Lord
should've been locked up here too.
No wonder we couldn't find
Black Wind
within multiple miles of radios
outside Babao Town.
So she has been locked up in here.
Report this to First Master immediately.
Yes.
Girls of this generation
are so beautiful.
You've even became an examiner.
You have a bright future.
What a pity.
Yi Mei Fairy.
Not only did you kept demons,
you also released the Thousand-year Bee Demon
to disturb the exam.
What are you up to?
Since you saw it,
then...
I can't let you leave.