[English subtitles are available]
[Tiger and Crane]
[Episode 19
Fulong Capital in chaos]
First Master.
This Japanese camellia is Yi Mei's favorite
You even know that?
You really
flatter me.
[Xizhao Pavilion]
Where is Xiaoxuan?
It's a little rude for you to
ask that as soon as you came to my place.
Why did you steal Xuan's
Spirit Mirrow?
I have my own use for it.
500 years ago,
I brought back the first child
in Qi family with twin primordial spirits
from the Dianfeng Valley.
The Spirit Locking Ritual and Spirit Mirror
were both created by me.
Why did you have to involve
the Qi family for your plan?
If you hadn't interfered with
my plan,
it'd have been realized earlier.
Since you refuse to come clean about it,
there's no need for me to be polite anymore.
You betrayed me.
How could I
be manipulated so easily?
In fact, working with Yi Mei
is just a cover.
I just want to take the chance
to get the credit for capturing Yi Mei.
Given our abilities,
it'd be hard to capture Yi Mei.
But with Granny's help,
it'll be different.
By then,
you set an ambush there first.
When she and Yi Mei
are both severely injured in their fight,
you and I will work together
coming after them
to take Yi Mei down.
See.
With the credit of
capturing Yi Mei,
it will be enough
for you to have a sure footing among the Royal Sorcerers.
Aren't you afraid that
something might happen to First Master?
Without such resolution,
how could one be capable of doing big things?
However,
this scene of you two
reconciling
has come way too late.
With your weak skills,
you think you can win?
Although I don't like her,
but I can't stand an undying witch
like you.
First Master, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Go inform the Three Main Halls.
Go!
Wu Lidan,
go quickly! I'll stay here.
Be careful.
This is
to comfort Xing Zhi.
Grandma! Grandma!
Yi Mei...
I hate two-faced
traitors the most.
Accompany your grandma
on her way to her death.
Capture Yi Mei!
Yes. Yes.
Commander-in-Chief.
Commander-in-Chief!
You're hurt. Are you alright?
Where is First Master?
No...
Impossible.
The First Master
has gone through so much in her life.
She would never
leave us like this.
I'll go find her.
Let's go.
Go.
First Master!
How many times have I told you,
you can only change your shifts shifts at 3 p.m. for a break.
[60 years ago]
Who told you to doze off?
These pagodas are protecting
the extremely rare Red Pearls.
The formation is done with magic.
If you don't pay attention and an opening is caused on it,
the Legendary Sea's water will leak in
and everyone will die.
You want me to die,
right?
Leader,
I didn’t mean it.
I have to work two shifts every day.
I have less than four hours
to rest in a day.
I'm really very tired.
So?
Are you blaming me?
Your grace is immeasurable.
Defending the Legendary Sea is
something crucial to the world.
How dare you use your sleep
as an excuse?
If anything goes wrong
while you're dreaming away,
can you take responsibility?
I just didn't give you a gift.
What are you murmuring about?
Just spill it.
Louder!
I said,
it's just because
I don't have money to give you gifts,
that's why you're always against me.
How dare you!
How dare you talk back to your superior?
I can kill you now.
But I pity you
so just I'll deduct three months' salary from you.
Go and stand guard!
What are you looking at? Go on patrol!
Yes.
What world?
Your grace is immeasurable.
These are all lies.
Empty words.
You fell into the Legendary Sea.
You're badly injured.
Don't move.
Have a good rest.
You must be hungry.
There are two buns here.
You can have them.
D-delicious.
You can talk?
This bun is made of mushroom cabbage filling.
My mom is good at it.
If you like it,
I'll ask her to make more next time.
You...
Wh-what mane?
Mane?
Are you asking for my name?
My name is Zhi Xie.
What about you?
Wh-what your mane?
I... I...
My name is Wolf.
Wolf.
Brother Wolf
Brother Wolf.
You said
you swam from across
the legendary sea?
Impossible.
The fire of the Legendary Sea burns both heaven and earth.
Not to mention human,
even a demon,
will be burned to ashes.
It's true.
Then tell me
what's on the end of the Legendary Sea?
There's nothing there.
It's very desperate.
You mean desolate?
Yes, desolate.
Then why are you here?
If my family wasn't poor,
and I have no other choice,
I wouldn't want to be here either.
Then...
do you have any wishes?
To be the best.
I want to be the best.
And no longer be bullied.
I keep getting bullied.
To be the best?
Brother Wolf,
what's going on?
I'm the Wolf Demon King
from the Legendary Sea.
You are a demon?
I can help you become the best.
Folks!
The Legendary Sea's levee is about to break!
Come with me!
The levee is broken!
Run! Run!
You risked your life to inform
12 villages along the way to evacuate,
saving thousands of people.
You have done a great act
of saving the world.
You're a hero in the eyes of the people
and also a role model for the Royal Sorcerers.
From now on,
you can stay in the capital.
Thank you for your promotion.
Brother Wolf.
These
were sent here from the sorcerers
of the Three Main Halls.
Now I'm working in the Yanluo Hall,
the people who wants to suck up to me
have to queue up from Wanchun Pavilion
to the gate of Yanluo Hall.
Congratulations
on becoming the best.
Brother Wolf,
it’s all thanks to you.
You deserve all these.
I mean it.
I'm a man of my word.
I heard
the general at Legendary Sea
has been imprisoned for life by you.
Yes.
Who told him to bully me all the time?
I want him to have a taste of
being bullied.
But he didn't do anything wrong.
When the Legendary Sea was spreading,
he led everyone
to protect the formation.
That's a different matter.
He's paid to do this,
that's his duty.
He shouldn't have bullied me before.
Sir, are you here to buy buns again?
Three taels of mushroom cabbage buns.
We have crab roe and osmanthus stuffing.
Do you want to try something new?
No need.
My friend likes this.
Okay.
Please wait a moment.
I'll make you something fresh.
Have you heard?
A wolf demon
around the capital recently.
It often wandered in the suburbs at midnight,
devouring other demons.
It's so scary.
I know.
People from Disha Hall
are laying am ambush outside the city
waiting to catch that demon.
But
I heard
people who have witnessed it
that its power
is not to be underestimated.
I don't really understand.
Since this wolf demon
feeds on
other demons,
isn't that good?
As long as the people
don't wander around at night,
it will save us Three Main Halls
the trouble.
That won't work.
He's eating monsters outside the capital today.
Tomorrow, he'd eat humans outside the capital.
What should we do then?
By the way,
someone also saw him
near the Yanluo Hall.
Could this Wolf Demon
have anything to do
with Yanluo Hall?
Why do you care so much?
We'll catch him in a few days.
We'll know when we catch him.
Come on, let's drink. Don't just talk.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
I've been in the capital for months.
I've eaten a lot of delicacies.
But this mushroom bun
is still the best.
What's so good about this?
I'm already tired of it.
Maybe it's because I'm nostalgic.
There are nice things about new things too.
For example,
this Shaoxing Wine that has been fermented for 10 years.
Come on, Brother Wolf.
Let me drink a toast to you,
to express my gratitude.
I should be the one thanking you.
If you hadn't saved me that day,
I can't be
sitting here today.
Here, a toast to you.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Good wine.
Don't be in a rush, Brother Wolf.
Since we’ve finished the wine,
there are some things
I have to say.
Go ahead.
I know you poisoned the wine.
Brother Wolf.
Why would I?
I also know
you are meticulous.
To prevent my suspicion,
he must have taken
the antidote in advance.
You'r a demon.
The people of the Tiangang Hall
have already found out about you.
You're wanted all over the capital.
They will suspect
Yanluo Hall soon,
and eventually me too.
So...
You want to kill me?
I can't
lose everything I have now.
I can't go back to the past.
I really can't.
I've been through a lot to come here from the Legendary Sea.
You are the first person I met.
People say humans and demons have different paths.
But you
made me feel that it's not true.
You are a demon.
Demons will hurt people.
But I've never hurt a single person
since I came onto mainland.
I don't believe it.
Demons will never change their innate nature.
You must die.
Only if you die,
can I protect all of this.
When we first met,
I told you
I've been cultivating
for hundreds of years on the Legendary Sea.
So,
this wound and this poison
don't work on me.
I've paid you back.
From now on,
we don't owe each other anything.
You know what?
Compared to this poison wine and these wounds,
what really hurts
is human heart.
We can't find it at all.
Yanluo Hall has been established for hundreds of years.
It collapsed overnight.
Where can we put the demons
we capture in the future?
Just arrest them and execute them on the spot.
Of course.
There are good demons and bad demons.
Demons like Black Wind
should be executed on the spot after their capture.
But if it's
a kind demon,
they probably won't be captured.
Right?
Yes.
Brick.
Does Qianyu State
have Three Main Halls?
Where do you keep your demons?
Good question.
I'll find a chance to ask my father...
My father?
I think Xiao Yunzi would know.
I'll ask him.
It looks like markings
made by tiger claws.
Could it be my mother?
There's a hole there.
They must have escaped from this hole.
What happened?
I don't know.
A bunch of demons appeared out of nowhere
on the streets.
It must be Zhi Xie and the others.
They're coming!
Hurry!
The Royal Sorcerers are here.
He's dead!
That scared me.
This is too scary.
Ice Cube!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
All of this
is your conspiracy?
Yes.
Killing the sorcerer,
taming demons,
and planning for the sorcerers to murder people,
causing people lose confidence
in the Three Main halls,
transferring me away from the capital.
All of this...
has been you!
Yes.
Now,
you're going to attack the Legendary Sea's formation.
Knowing this now
is useless.
Why don't you go back to the city and settle your family?
Master.
Why?
Our fate has ended.
Go ahead.
I don't want to hurt you.
I won't let you put the world
in danger.
Because of fate,
everything is predestined.
The levee at the Legendary Sea's east and south
have already broken.
Royal Sorcerers!
Yes!
Set up the Fulong Phurba Formation!
Ice Cube.
I've been calling your name all the way.
Why didn't you...
It's you.
Where did you hide him?
He's here.
This is the hell
that has trapped me for eight years.
He should also have a taste
of this pain of being swallowed by darkness.
Give it to me.
And get out of his body.
Sure.
From now on,
there will only be
one Xiaoxuan in this world.
Hu Zi!
Hu Zi, run!
It'd be too late if we don't leave now.
Go!
Are you okay?
Run!
Da Changqiang,
come along with me
to lure these demons
to somewhere else.
Three Sisters,
escort the people to leave.
Where are we take them?
The capital is not safe now.
Go to Tiangang Hall!
The Sorcerer Formation is guarding Tiangang Hall.
Okay.
Xintong.
Be careful with Da Changqiang.
Let's go.
Go. Go.
Come with us.
Don't panic.
-Go! Go!
-Get up! Go!
Keep up.
Go!
Ice Cube won't die.
-I have to find him.
-Hu Zi.
Hu Zi, come to your senses!  Hu Zi!
What are you doing?
Your Highness.
Fulong Capital is in chaos.
Come back to Qianyu State with me.
Do you want me to stand by and watch?
I only care about your safety.
It's not only about Fulong State.
What do we do if the demons
go to Qianyu State too?
But we can't save
everyone in the capital
with just the two of us.
Every person we save counts.
Your Highness!
If you want to just stand by and watch,
then go back to Qianyu State by yourself.
I'm going to stay together with Fulong Capital
If you still think of me
as your prince,
I order you to protect the people
and kill the demons immediately!
Run!
Keep up!
Go!
Duo!
Where are you going?
Let go of me!
I'm going to find my child.
You can't go there.
There are demons everywhere over there.
No.
My child is still there.
I need to save her.
Her name is Duo, right?
I'll help you find her.
Da Changqiang, protect her.
Duo.
Go. Go!
Duo. Duo.
Are you Duo?
Come.
Chief Commander,
at this rate,
we won't last long.
We must hold onto
the Legendary Sea's formation at all costs.
The Demon King summoned the demons
and disrupted the formation.
We can't just sit back and do nothing.
Chief Commander!
Let's deal with him.
You are no match for him.
Don't seek your own death.
Chief Commander!
You once said
for a warrior
to on the battlefield
is their greatest honor.
Now,
this is our battlefield.
Listen to my string music that will aid your attack!
Okay!
You will pay
for your mistakes.
Perhaps I will.
But it won't be now.
No!
Tie Lie!
Master...
We can still...
protect together...
Jinian, how long do we have to leave the capital?
Father, we will be there soon.
What are you doing?
Leave quickly...
Don't take it! It's mine! Let go!
-It’s mine.
-Dad, stop picking it up.
Father, stop picking it anymore.
You'll die if you continue to pick it up!
It's mine!
-We can’t get through here.
-What should we do?
Elder Cheng!
What should we do? We can't get out.
Exactly.
What should we do?
Elders,
it’s not a good idea
to stay here.
Sooner or later those demons
will find out about us.
The whole capital has fallen.
-Where can we escape to?
-Yes.
Don't we still have a group of people
guarding Tiangang Hall?
Tiangang Hall?
Hurry!
Hurry up!
Is there still anyone behind?
No.
Have you seen Xintong?
Did anyone see Xintong?
We didn't.
Our team
has been driven away by the demons.
Everyone is dead.
Those demons
are all above the level of Demon Elder.
We can't handle them at all.
Duo...
Listen to me.
Take the people
to go to Tiangang Hall immediately.
With Sorcerers still guarding that place,
it’s safer.
I’m going to find Xintong.
I have to go find Xintong.
Go. Hurry!
Yes.
Go.
Go! Quickly!
Come with us quickly!
Xintong.
Give me the child.
Your arm...
I'm fine.
Let's go to Tiangang Hall.
Let's go!
Search carefully.
Yes.
Over there.
First Master...
Why?
There's no reason.
We're just in different positions.
Why did you become my master
taught me martial arts,
and helped me gain my promotion?
Because
are the most suitable candidate.
You got this bone whip
when I took you to catch demons
for the first time.
I didn't think it'd
become a weapon
against me today.
I won't let you destroy the capital!
Then do your best.
That's more like my disciple.
People trapped demons in
Dianfeng Valley because of their own weakness.
Now their homes have been destroyed,
where can they escape to?
A place like this
is not worth your protection.
Humans are weak,
but the number of people who
dare to fight against their own weaknesses
are countless.
Red Flame?
You're using your final drop of spirit essence
to fight against me!
Have you forgotten?
You taught me this since I was a child.
To not give up
until the last moment.
Yes.
Thank you for teaching me.
You asked me
why I want to protect.
Look at the people behind me.
It's because they are still holding on.
They
are the reason I protect them.
I've returned
your bone whip.
Is it not painful enough?
Stand up!
You looked determined.
In the future,
what kind of person do you want to be?
I want to be the best.
The best?
Many people
want to be the best.
Master.
The best I want to be
is different from theirs.
What's the difference?
I want to be the best who
protects the people and Fulong.
Zilu...
Looks like you haven't been
eaten up by
by the title of a hero.
Master.
Chief Commander and Commander
are dead.
What should we do?
What do you mean?
We have to hang in there!
Brothers.
Chief Commander and the rest
did what they had to do.
The rest will be up to us.
No matter what happens,
we have to hang in there!
Yes!
Xintong.
What’s going on?
They won't let us in.
Chen Jinian
and the bunch of people from the Council of Elders
kicked us out.
No matter what we said,
they refused to let anyone go in.
You should go somewhere else.
What do you mean?
The capital is in chaos.
Among these wounded,
many of them are women, children, and old people.
Where do you want them to hide?
We can't make any mistake
guarding Tiangang Hall.
They can't go in.
This is an order from the higher-ups.
In that case,
we'd have to break in today.
I want to ask
what are you guarding?
What is Tiangang Hall protecting?
The capital is full of demons running amok.
The people have lost their homes.
It's the time they need protection from the Royal Sorcerers
the most.
Yet you turn them away.
Dear guards,
no matter what,
we must let them enter the Tiangang Hall today.
There are still many people
who are being attacked in the capital now.
Even if there's only one person left,
we will still try our best
to save them and bring them here.
We are not guarding the city,
but the people.
If it weren't for this heroine
and these brothers,
we will die in the capital too.
Please let us in.
If there are any consequences,
I will bear them all.
Count me in.
Us too.
And us.
Yes!
Thank you.
Commander-in-Chief.
Weren't you with
with First Master?
What happened here?
Yi Mei...
Yi Mei!