=Such A Good Love=
=Episode 18=
(Autumn 2024, Chongqing)
Sorry for the wait. Here's some ice jelly.
- Thank you.
May we have the menu?
We don't have one.
The owner decides
what's on the menu each day.
The owner seems like
quite the character.
Yes.
Zhou!
Hotpot for three!
Got it! Coming right up!
Your food will be ready soon.
Make yourselves comfortable.
Go ahead.
What?
Order up!
All right. Got it.
Calm down.
I'm heading back now.
I'm hanging up.
What's wrong?
Something came up on set.
I need to handle it.
At least have one bite before you leave.
Just try it.
We waited so long.
You'll regret leaving now.
Ms. Dai...
I can't. I really have to go.
Maybe I'm just not meant
to enjoy the hotpot here.
- But... It'll be quick.
- Hotpot coming through!
The food's here!
You guys enjoy the food.
Here.
Next time.
- Um...
- Don't go!
Order up!
Wait!
Ms. Dai!
Don't go!
Are you all right?
- I'm so sorry...
- It's fine.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I can't believe she left!
If she had just turned her head,
she would've seen him!
Why couldn't she turn around
for just one second?
We were one step away.
And now it's another missed chance.
Try calling her later.
Can you get her to come back?
Are you guys eating or not?
If not, give the table to someone else.
Order up!
Here's your chicken feet.
Thanks.
Enjoy.
How's the taste?
Two bowls of ice jelly on the house!
Rice eels.
- No thanks.
- We don't eat rice eels.
No rice eels?
You can't have hotpot without rice eels.
We don't want it.
- They don't taste good.
- How does someone who loves film that much
end up owning a hotpot restaurant?
All right.
Give it a try.
Enjoy.
Can we get two more dishes?
Here are your ice jellies.
Still not enough for you four?
I prep a limited amount each day.
If you eat more,
there won't be enough for others.
If it's good, come back next time.
- All right.
- All right?
What do you want to add?
This.
This?
Excuse me.
We're happy
you're eating here,
and filming is fine too,
but can you not
post the video online?
Please?
I'm promoting your place!
No need.
We run a small restaurant
and I'm the only one in the kitchen.
I can't handle too many customers.
He does act like a hotpot owner now.
He does.
- It suits him.
- This is just a small restaurant.
I do fine on my own.
Enjoy your meal.
What do you want to watch
during Golden Week?
Anything's fine.
Aren't all the Golden Week movies
funded by Huanteng Films?
All thanks to my boss.
She's one of the top producers
in the country now.
I heard your boss
used to date a director?
He doesn't direct anymore.
He runs a hotpot restaurant now!
Ice jelly coming through!
Really?
Do you think he heard us?
Ice jelly for you.
Thank you.
I'm sure he did.
Juan.
I have something nice for you too.
- Leftover ice jelly ingredients.
- What is it?
- Saved you a piece.
- Watermelon.
Come on. Let's eat.
Enjoy.
Okay.
We finally get to relax.
Smells amazing!
Let me try this.
Try it.
How is it?
It's delicious.
Can I be honest with you?
You're a better cook than a director.
If someone said that to me before,
I would've punched them.
And now?
Now I think you're right.
This is really good!
This is sweet. Try it.
See that?
Only couples eat
from the same watermelon
with the same spoon.
I don't think it's a big deal.
Good friends do that too.
It's not just a couple thing.
You and I wouldn't do it though.
You think that young lady
selling ice jelly
is his wife?
She is the boss.
But I don't think she and Zhou Shui
have anything going on.
My woman's intuition says
they definitely do.
My guy instinct says
they don't.
Want to bet on it?
You're on!
I wonder
if Sansan finished his homework.
He probably did.
Look at the time.
I'm sure he's watching TV now.
Sansan.
Mr. Pan.
You're back.
We're back.
- Sansan.
- Hurry up!
Come here.
- Come here.
- Time to go home.
Okay.
Did he behave?
He was a good boy.
- There's a boy.
- Just leave him with me
whenever you need.
Mr. Pan
- We got some rice eels.
- What's that you got there?
Take them.
Oh, you shouldn't have!
- I can't accept this.
- Just take them.
Take it.
Okay. Thanks.
Thank you.
Thanks, Mr. Pan.
Don't mention it.
Come on, Sansan.
Did you have fun today?
A lot of fun!
Be careful.
I...
I can't believe he already has a son.
They seemed like a happy family.
Let's go.
I'm sweating.
I'm heading home.
See you at three tomorrow.
Got it.
Go on. Don't stay up late.
All right. Get some rest.
Sansan.
Say bye-bye.
Bye-bye!
Sleep early.
- I'm leaving.
- All right.
Get going.
See you tomorrow.
Come on. Let's head inside.
Bye.
Think you could convince Ms. Dai
to come back for hotpot tomorrow?
Although, Ms. Dai has Mr. Zhang now.
Mr. Zhou has a family too.
Maybe we shouldn't let them meet?
What do you think?
Why aren't you saying anything?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Just feeling emo.
Emo?
You? Depressed?
I'll get you a popsicle.
Something sweet will fix it.
How much is this?
Two yuan.
All right.
Welcome to Reverb's livestream!
How are my mama friends doing?
First, I've got some exciting news
to share.
I'm five months and five days pregnant
with my third baby!
Do we have any new mothers?
Isn't that Reverb?
- Comment 1 if you are!
- I think so.
Owner,
she's that popular streamer now, right?
Yes, she's very popular.
She sells mom-and-baby stuff.
Our kid's formula
and stroller
all came from her.
A mom blogger.
Reverb's a mom blogger now?
That wild woman
is now a model housewife.
Look at all those '80s kids.
Zhou Shui with his wife and kid.
Ms. Dai's with Mr. Zhang.
Even Reverb's got a kid.
More than one, even!
Back then they were all about
being wild and free.
Now?
They all turned out traditional.
In their 40s and all settled down.
Is having a family such a bad thing?
Look around. Everyone here's got one.
I don't anymore.
You don't?
What do you mean?
My parents got divorced,
and they sold the house.
I didn't even like
that home much growing up,
but now that it's actually gone,
it kind of hurts.
Now I don't even have
a home to go back to anymore.
Why don't you come home with me?
What do you mean?
My place is just ahead.
My parents can make you poached egg
in fermented glutinous rice soup.
It's sweet.
Eat that and you won't feel sad anymore.
You're introducing me to your parents?
You said you wanted a home, right?
I can give you one.
Stop joking around.
I'm not joking.
What, scared?
Me? Scared?
I'm not scared of anything.
Where's your house? Up ahead?
Yes, just there.
Let's go.
Let's do it.
You think your parents
would accept someone like me?
An unemployed model,
broken family,
older than you?
No problem.
My mom was a Sichuan opera actress,
and she's two years older than my dad.
You said it.
I did.
Then I'm staying with you guys for good.
I'll eat your food,
drink your drinks, live in your house.
I'd never want you to leave.
You're serious about this?
Lead the way.
Let's go.
We're here.
Already?
Yes, this is where I live.
I shouldn't show up empty-handed.
I'll buy some fruits.
It's okay. Don't worry about that.
Oh, look at the time.
Your mother must be sleeping.
Oh, don't worry about it.
My parents stay up late.
They're probably still watching TV.
- Let's go!
You said it.
Where will I sleep?
In my room.
Your room?
What about you?
I'll take the couch.
Let's go.
Come on!
Wait! Wait!
Fine. You win.
What do you mean?
- Are you really taking me in?
- What do you mean I win?
Are you kidding me?
There's a limit to joking!
I'm not joking!
I really like you!
Are you insane?
So all that time we spent meant nothing?
You've got an avoidant personality,
so stop pretending to be a narcissist.
Tong Leyi, don't go!
Go after her!
Your love is doomed!
Your love is running away!
Aren't you heartbroken?
(Summer 2012, Beijing)
Mom! Over here!
My goodness!
Everyone's already left
and now you show up?
Seriously.
I was at work.
I had to ask my boss for time off
to come pick you up.
Haven't seen you in so long.
Did you miss me?
Of course I did!
Why'd you suddenly come here?
Because I missed you.
Can't I come see you?
You can.
Am I not welcome?
Of course you're welcome here.
How long are you planning to stay?
I don't really have much going on,
so probably ten days, maybe two weeks.
That long?
What?
I can't stay that long?
You can.
Where's Zhou Shui?
He's at work.
His future mother-in-law is here
and he didn't come pick me up?
You two had a fight, didn't you?
No, we're just too busy.
We don't even have time to argue.
I'll grab a cab.
Why take a cab? That's expensive!
- But...
- Let's just take the subway.
What's wrong with hailing a cab?
You're so wasteful!
Seriously!
Daji! Over here!
Zhaoyang, what are you doing here?
This is my boss.
When you called me for time off,
I happened to be in Shunyi
meeting someone,
so I figured I'd swing by
since it's on the way.
Mom, this is my boss, Zhaoyang.
- Hello.
- You must be Daji's mother.
Yes, this is my mother.
Nice to meet you.
You look so young.
You're too kind.
Great to see you.
Why are you just standing there?
Get in the car!
- This is too much trouble...
- Come on.
You didn't tell me your boss
was coming to pick us up.
I didn't make myself presentable.
I'm a total mess!
Just get in.
What's he doing here?
He picked us up from the airport.
Zhaoyang, Zhou Shui's here.
Have a seat.
He was doing a reshoot up
at the Great Wall today.
Already started drinking?
Where's your mother?
She went to the bathroom
as soon as she got here.
Oh my goodness!
Mrs. Dai.
Who is this?
- Easy there.
- Be careful.
Be careful.
Sorry. Redo.
And now, presenting Xiaoya!
So you were touching up
your makeup, Mrs. Dai.
I...
Still as bad with words as ever.
Such a young lady must be Daji's sister!
Oh, you flatter me.
Have a seat, Xiaoya.
Just call me Mrs. Dai.
Here.
Mrs. Dai.
For you.
Try this, Xiaoya.
Thank you.
I put the sauce in it just for you.
Thank you so much.
You really didn't have
to go to all this trouble.
And don't call me "boss."
I don't see them as my employees.
They're like younger siblings to me.
Young people need to be held
to high standards.
What they're missing is experience.
We'll work hard, Zhaoyang.
Don't worry. Daji is one of my best.
I've no complaints about her work.
I heard
she just got promoted, right?
That's right.
Yes.
- Just a little step up.
- Planning Director.
She's Zhou Shui's higher-up now.
So...
How's Zhou Shui doing?
I'm currently filming a new ad...
Well, he still has a few "artist quirks"
that he needs to fix.
Your biggest issue is you aim too high
without the foundation.
Not like Daji. She's solid.
I think Zhou Shui's doing pretty well.
Young people
should stay grounded.
The bread will come.
Dreams will come true.
But in the meantime,
try to take some pressure off Daji.
- Stop making her clean up after you.
- He doesn't...
Don't just chase your dreams
without thinking.
Zhou Shui is talented.
He's an artist.
So he never helps you out, huh?
We're not...
We divide things between us.
Um, Mrs. Dai,
let me give you a toast.
Welcome to Beijing.
Look, Zhou Shui.
There are things I must say to you.
I'm not trying to nag.
No. Go ahead.
Mr. Lai's right.
A man needs
to take responsibility.
What's the price per square meter
in Beijing right now?
A bit over 10,000, I think.
The average is almost 30,000 now.
It's only going
to go up.
Exactly.
You'll need to buy a place eventually.
Better sooner than later.
Money sitting in the bank loses value.
Have you talked to your family
about buying a place?
What are your thoughts on this?
Mrs. Dai, I'm not planning on buying
anytime soon.
Two years ago, you came to my house
and swore up and down
that if we gave you two years,
you'd give Daji a home.
It's been two years.
Where's the house? Where's the home?
Mom, I think
renting is fine.
If you don't like a place,
you can always move somewhere else,
right?
If we throw everything we have
into a down payment,
we'd be under a lot of pressure.
That's not a very wise move.
That's what he said, right?
His idea, wasn't it?
I said it.
- You said it?
- That's what I really think.
Really?
You're still as stubborn as ever!
You're not getting any younger,
you know that?
I can't believe you!
Let me be clear.
I don't care where you two choose
to build your careers.
I don't care how far from home you go.
I'm not asking you to take care of me.
When I'm old, I'll go to a nursing home.
But wherever you work,
you should have a home there.
How can this rootless lifestyle
give you any sense of security?
Can you reassure your parents with this?
You two chose Beijing.
You made the choice.
Now, you live with the consequences.
Am I right?
Xiaoya, let's have a drink.
- Cheers.
(Amount due: 1668)
Your bill, sir.
This one's on me.
Oh, that's too kind of you.
It's your first meal here.
It has to be my treat.
Sorry for the trouble, Mr. Lai.
No trouble at all.
Thanks, Zhaoyang.
(Hebei Mobile welcomes you!)
(Have a great day every day!)
"Hebei welcomes you?"
What's that supposed to mean?
Where are we now?
This is Hebei? Are you kidding me?
We already left Beijing!
Hebei and Beijing aren't that different.
How are they even close to the same?
Zhou Shui!
Explain!
What is the meaning of this?
Where do you guys actually live?
You're so annoying.
Didn't you say you lived in Beijing?
We live in Yanjiao.
Just stop here.
We're literally a few steps away.
Are you sure?
I ate too much just now.
Let's walk it off.
Seriously.
Thank you.
This meter is giving me anxiety!
It's about to hit 200 yuan!
We're just a few steps away.
What kind of place do you live in?
Out in the middle of nowhere.
It's not exactly the middle of nowhere.
It's not even inside Beijing.
A lot of people live out here.
They're all like us.
Working in the city.
Right?
Right.
You guys pay 200 for a cab ride home
every time?
We don't often take the cab.
We usually take the bus.
Seriously.
Daji lives this far away with you...
Why are you bringing him into this?
If I'd known this,
I wouldn't have let her come to Beijing!
Jingshu.
Daji.
You know each other?
She's my roommate, Jingshu.
We live together.
This is my mom.
- She just got to Beijing.
- Hello, Mrs. Dai.
Hello.
Why don't we all walk back together?
Sure.
Okay.
Let's go. It's just ahead.
Mrs. Dai, I'll show you the way.
Who was that?
I'll explain later.
That's...
Tell Zhou Shui not to say anything
to Dumbbell.
Here we are.
Welcome home.
Welcome, Mrs. Dai!
- Hello.
- Welcome to Beijing.
Welcome.
We aren't in Beijing anymore.
Close enough.
Yanjiao is basically Beijing.
These are Dumbbell and Jingshu's rooms.
Mrs. Dai,
we're going to tidy up real quick.
Go ahead.
Why are you home so late again?
I had to work overtime.
We should book a hotel
for your mom tomorrow.
She'd never agree to that
if it costs money.
She'd feel it's a waste.
Look.
That's just how she talks.
She's blunt, not exactly tactful.
Don't take it personally.
It's fine.
Sorry you have to deal with this.
It's okay. It's nice here.
You go rest. Get some sleep early.
- Okay.
- We've got an early start tomorrow.
Keep your back supported.
Don't let it get sore.
- Good night.
Oh my gosh!
It's past eight!
Mom!
Why didn't my alarm go off?
What did you do, Mom?
You both looked like
you were sleeping badly last night,
so I turned it off
to let you sleep in a little.
You turned off my alarm?
I have work! I'm going to be late!
You're not helping me!
Zhou Shui!
Zhou Shui! Get up!
Come on! Get up!
It's after eight!
We're going to be late! Get up!
What time is it?
Can you please
stop messing us up?
Daji. Why don't you just stay home
and spend time with your mom?
- I'll call in sick for you.
- Stay home?
Are you kidding?
There's so much going on at work.
All right. What about...
Well, you have to eat some breakfast!
I already made it for you!
Daji!
I even made
your favorite hot dry noodles.
Just have some, okay?
You both have some, okay?
Hurry!
Mom!
We're off!
Hurry up!
We won't be having breakfast.
Breakfast's ready!
I even made steamed buns!
I read it.
What do you think of the script?
This is my fifth revision.
You still haven't fully grasped it.
Your characters
still don't have any soul.
So what does it mean
for a character to have soul?
No one can answer that for you.
You have to figure it out for yourself.
Go back
and finish reading Tolstoy,
read all of Lermontov's poetry,
study every one of Chekhov's
short stories.
Then rewatch
Woody Allen's Manhattan
and Annie Hall twice.
Maybe then it'll click.
Can you just explain it
a little more clearly?
Who am I?
I'm the client.
And what do clients do?
We bring the money.
You do what we say.
You revise how we tell you to revise.
Am I understood?
Yes, you're right.
Then get to it!
I'll revise it just the way you said.
So get moving!
Something wrong with your hands?
Or your brain?
Why are you dragging your feet?
If you don't want this job, refund me!
I'll get someone else to do it!
I don't get it!
I found him the Great Wall!
I went all the way
to Badaling to scout locations!
Still not good enough.
He just has to have an aircraft carrier.
"I want that carrier!"
They asked
for an industrial aircraft carrier.
So of course they expect one.
So what's wrong
with an industrial Great Wall?
This is about your attitude.
You blow up at a client and then?
I have to go smooth things over?
Listen.
- Can't you just be nice for once?
- If you act soft with clients
like this,
- But they're still the client.
- they'll just walk all over you!
So you go off on them
and then I have to clean up?
Can you please stop
making me fix your messes?
Fine. But I never even
thought about these things.
- I'm just really tired, okay?
- I just think people like that...
Mom.
Mrs. Dai.
You're back.
Have you eaten? I'll go reheat the food.
We already ate, Mom.
We ate at the office.
There's fruit too.
I bought fresh fruit today.
We're good.
It's too late for fruits.
We're just talking about work stuff.
Go to sleep.
Zhou Shui, come here!
I know that client is difficult.
But can't you just be
- a little more accommodating?
- He's not just difficult!
He's out of his mind!
Fine, he's out of his mind.
But what do we do about it?
He's still a client.
Don't make me clean up
after your outbursts
every single time, okay?
I know. I don't want you
to fix it for me either.
But I just can't shoot this.
Zhou Shui, I'm exhausted every day.
I've got my own job to do.
He gave me 20,000 yuan
to shoot an aircraft carrier.
How in the world am I supposed
to get an aircraft carrier?
Mom.
Mom, I'm heading out.
You're skipping breakfast again.
What's wrong?
Are you crying?
- What's the matter?
- Quick.
Where's Zhou Shui?
What about him?
Get him to notice me.
He went downstairs.
Downstairs?
He left before I did.
He already left?
- You're kidding me!
- What's wrong?
That boy just walks out
without even telling me!
All that effort for nothing.
Why were you pretending to cry
with eye drops?
What's going on with you?
I just wanted him to see
how much I worry about my daughter.
He's put you through so much
these past two years!
How can
he be so heartless?
Letting you live so far out,
and not even cooking for you!
Mom.
That scene was a bit much.
Too much?
You weren't very convincing.
How was it not convincing?
This time it's for real, okay?
Still over the top.
I disagree. I thought it was good.
I know you worry about us,
but we're honestly doing fine.
I'm your mother. I can tell right away
whether your relationship
is going fine or not.
Let me tell you.
I've eaten more salt
than you've eaten rice.
That much salt?
Are you sure that's good for you?
You!
I know you saw us arguing
yesterday.
But it was just
about work.
It doesn't mean we don't get along.
Don't worry.
You're overthinking things.
And using eye drops to fake cry?
Now you're just milking it.
I'm going to be late for work.
They dock my pay if I'm late.
They do that?
Fine. Get going.
Go to work.
Go on!
Stay home.
See you later.
(Ratings for "Empresses in the Palace")
(continued to climb as it aired.)
(By the finale,)
(it surpassed 2% viewership,)
(topping the boards.)
(Will "Empresses in the Palace")
(go down as an all-time favorite
Qing dynasty drama?)
The food smells amazing, Mrs. Dai!
Try my cooking.
Smells great in here.
Welcome back!
- You cooked.
- Come, come!
Of course!
I made your favorites!
Wow!
Let's eat, Daji.
Fish ball soup,
beer duck,
braised pork knuckle, and mandarin fish.
Thank you, Mrs. Dai.
Try it.
So good!
This fish tastes just like back home.
Amazing!
Zhou Shui.
You should learn how to cook from me
when you have time.
Mrs. Dai, I've been really busy lately.
But if I have time, I...
I've got time! I'll learn from you.
Then Jingshu can have a hot meal
when she comes home.
Zhou Shui,
if you can make her life easier,
you don't even have to cook.
Mrs. Dai.
We live kind of far out.
Right.
If it's far, why not buy a car?
Look at Jingshu.
She has someone to drive her every day,
while Daji has to take the subway.
- Mom...
- Don't you think...
Who's driving Jingshu every day?
What are you talking about?
Who's driving Jingshu around?
My mistake.
You must've seen wrong, Mrs. Dai.
Yes. You got the wrong person.
- That isn't her.
- I...
It couldn't have been me.
I was just saying stuff.
It was a cab, right?
Just eat, Mom.
Maybe.
What did Mrs. Dai mean just now?
Who's getting driven around every day?
She said she was mistaken.
Eat your food.
What are you thinking about?
Seriously?
Has someone been
picking you up and dropping you off?
No, I always take the subway.
Liar.
Why do you think I'm lying?
That time it snowed hard in winter,
you said you took the subway,
but when you got home,
your clothes and shoes were dry.
Jingshu.
(A few months ago)
That car you sold to Mr. Liao
has a rattling sunroof.
A rattling sunroof?
So we're assigning you to be
the after-sales specialist.
Me?
To help
fix the issue.
I don't know how to fix cars.
You don't need to.
So what do I do?
Just sit in Mr. Liao's car each day
and experience the noise.
Just ride along for about 50 kilometers.
Manager,
I've got my own job to do.
I really can't take this on.
Jingshu.
When I hired you,
what did you say to me?
You said you'd work hard
and follow my lead.
Now this is your attitude?
Do you even realize
what level of client Mr. Liao is?
What if he demands a refund?
What if he files a complaint?
You know exactly how much damage
that could do to our dealership.
This favor,
no, this task,
has to be done by you.
If you don't do it right,
not only will you be fired,
I'll lose this job too!
That's 50 kilometers.
Please pull over.
Could you stop the car, please?
Sir.
Don't you know better?
It's late. Take the young lady home.
That's not necessary.
Just drop me off
at the next bus stop.
It's a holiday.
It's not safe
for a young lady to be out this late.
It's really okay.
Pull over.
I'm back.
Didn't think
I'd get home this late today.
You must be starving.
Jingshu.
This job is inhumane.
Who works overtime this late every day?
You must've been
bottling up a lot.
You should just quit tomorrow.
If I quit, what would we live on?
I'll take care of you.
Look what I've got.
Who wants one?
Here. Nobody?
Grab one.
Mr. Liao.
Why are you having boxed lunches?
Mr. Liao, we all eat boxed lunches.
That stuff has no nutrition.
Put the fish maw there. Yes, there.
Hurry up.
Okay. You can go.
Just do it for our dealership.
You're our store's lucky charm now.
Come on!
- Mr. Liao!
- Mr. Liao.
Jingshu.
I had them prepare lobster just for you.
Mr. Liao, I'm allergic to seafood.
Then eat the fish maw.
It's great for women. Keeps you pretty.
No thanks. I'm not hungry.
You...
Gather around!
It's Mr. Liao's treat!
Get moving!
Come on!
Another late night?
Looking at your palm,
you've got a lucky star.
Your fortune looks strong too.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Yes.
He must be a strong guy.
But there's someone
blocking your fortune.
The snow tonight is beautiful.
When we were kids,
we couldn't even go outside
if it snowed this much.
But look at us now,
sitting in a car watching the snow.
Stop the car.
That's 50 kilometers.
Don't wait out here.
Let me send you home.
I'm fine. My bus is coming soon.
Why are you always so polite with me?
How about this?
Let my driver send you home.
I'll wait for the bus.
You don't even know when it's coming.
That's okay.
My grandma used to say
waiting for a bus that won't come
is like waiting
for someone who never will.
I want to feel what that's like too.
Sorry.
The number you dialed
is currently unavailable.
Please try again later.
I think I took a cab that day.
Didn't really walk outside.
So now all taxis
use the same fragrance?
What?
You've had
a certain smell on you lately.
It's the same smell you had on you
that snowy day.
What's going on?
Dumbbell, you have to trust me.
I would never do anything to hurt you.
I'm happy with you.
All I want is to live my life with you.
I don't want anything else.
Please believe me, okay?
Okay.
Shen Jingshu!
Don't get the wrong idea.
Jingshu's just working.
It was the client's request.
We're going home.
Helmet on.
Hold on tight, Jingshu.
Hold on!
Let's go!
We're going home!
Youngsters these days.
(Dramatic Effect, Please Do Not Imitate)
Why are you grinning?
Did you see his face just now?
I did.
He's jealous of us.
He thinks having a little money
makes him all that.
Can he buy true love though?
I'm sorry.
I should've told you.
I'll resign first thing tomorrow.
Don't.
Don't quit.
Stay and do your best.
You can't leave.
Why not?
Because our love is worth
more than his lousy money!
I want him to see
that love isn't something
you can just buy!
Stop being ridiculous.
I will beat him one day!
Is it worth it?
From having nothing to having nothing
To turn back at every crossroads
Is it worth it?
Swearing to become the sea,
not just a river
Is it worth it?
That night,
the wine was finished with just one sip
Do you dare?
When having nothing, I don't frown
Once I decide to start,
I hold your hand tightly
Do you dare?
Even in the coldest winter,
we feel it on the ice
Do you dare?
Striving for an outlet
in reality and love
Only to realize when we drift apart
We mistook that day for forever
Time passes, bidding farewell to youth
Luckily, we have been brave
ever since we met
Perhaps that day means forever
Outrunning time,
leaving the past behind
Is it worth it?
Do you dare?
The love that's worth it, be brave
Later, the ocean drifted far away
Even the waves grew tired
The coldest days once burned
like blazing flames
Perhaps someday,
we will look back on the past
Ideals and vows.
How passionate they were
Once, there was a moment so vivid