=Such A Good Love=
=Episode 14=
(Summer 2024)
- Wait.
- Make way, thank you.
(Summer 2024, Beijing)
I'll help you with your bag.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
It's okay.
Be careful.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Are you giving birth soon?
Next month.
Mr. Chen.
I'm sorry.
I had poor signal on the train.
I went to the court to confirm today.
Your husband's case
has come to a conclusion.
My husband...
The opposing lawyer
has submitted evidence.
It's already been accepted.
The second trial verdict
has also come out.
The final decision is...
It's okay, you can tell me.
I can take it.
It's a death penalty.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Are you listening?
I can hear you, Mr. Chen.
Well...
Can I trouble you with something?
Go ahead.
Can you let him
give our child a name?
Okay, I'll do it.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
Miss.
Thank you.
I heard it.
Is there anything I can help you with?
If it's not too much trouble...
I can tell you my story.
Sure.
Just like that,
we've been in love
for more than ten years.
I always thought
we would be together forever.
I really want to watch
our child grow up with him.
If it weren't for this accident,
we will definitely be together forever.
Tell me.
My husband will come back, right?
Miss, what's wrong?
After listening to your story,
I felt really bad.
It felt like
this
happened to me.
Can you put yourself in my shoes?
Yes.
I felt like
I'm you
when you tell the story.
Why did you reject my script then?
Here's the thing, Yuan.
We submitted
this script to you three times.
It was rejected three times
because you didn't want
to play a pregnant woman.
But I don't think you're like that.
You're someone
who has high expectations for art.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have experienced
this old train so many times.
No offense.
I think
you can win an award with this.
Because you're capable of it.
You...
Miss, what's your name?
I forgot to introduce myself.
Huanteng Films' producer, Dai Daji.
I look forward to working with you,
Yuan.
Ms. Dai, your new assistant has arrived.
Meet her.
Over there.
If there are no issues,
we'll proceed with her onboarding.
Okay, thank you.
Hello.
What's your name?
Tong Leyi.
My name is Dai Daji.
Welcome to the company.
(Summer 2010, Beijing)
My name is Dai Daji.
My name is Zhou Shui.
In August 2010,
I returned to Beijing.
I found the girl I had lost.
I don't know how long
I'll be able to hold on this time
or what the final outcome will be.
But this time we plan to start over,
burn the bridges,
and give it another try.
(Since the beginning of the year,)
(Beijing's rent has risen sharply.)
(To save money,)
(we moved)
(to somewhere further away this time.)
(Yanjiao.)
(Yanjiao)
(People who work in Beijing
call this place a sleeping city.)
(The rent in Yanjiao
is only one-third of that in the city.)
(It's even cheaper
than Chunzhili Residence.)
(In 2010,)
(the average house price in Yanjiao)
(is 7,400 yuan per square meter.)
(Many people who bought houses
in Yanjiao are expecting it)
(to be relocated to Beijing.)
(Chaobai River's bridge
is always packed with people.)
(People in the sleeping city
are struggling to survive.)
(Everyone is looking toward Beijing
with longing.)
(CCTV Tower was going
to be completed that year.)
(Yet we're getting
further and further away from it.)
Zhou Shui.
- You're done?
- Let's eat.
Here.
Let's eat.
Want some beer?
Sure.
Okay.
- Come on.
- We're gathered here for hot pot.
- Hebei welcomes us.
I finished drinking.
- Here.
- It's boiling.
Let me.
Let's eat.
It's almost done.
Almost.
Here, Jingshu.
Be careful, it's hot.
Here.
Take your time.
It's not hot, is it?
(Dumbbell is having adult education
at Sports University.)
(With a degree,)
(he can work as a personal trainer
at a gym.)
(Jingshu works in a store
selling imported cars.)
(The two of them live a happy life.)
(They're now)
(like us in the past.)
There's oil on your mouth.
(Every couple who broke up
and got back together)
(lied to themselves.)
(But I clearly felt)
(we're not the same as before.)
(We're doing poorly in love)
(but excelling in the workplace.)
(We were both successfully
accepted into Shendu Pictures.)
(A new chapter in life has begun.)
Producer of the Year?
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Well...
Zhou Shui.
Lin Ze.
You know him?
Yes.
You know each other.
Well...
He's the champion
of the script competition.
I met him in the subway before.
Shouldn't you call Mr. Lin?
Mr. Lin.
Is your movie coming out soon?
Since you're here,
I want to ask you a question.
Why do you think
Shendu Pictures needs you?
Because I think
I'm the future maestro of Chinese films.
Don't get me wrong.
The next miracle of Chinese film
is standing right in front of you.
How shameless.
No, I always said this.
Well...
Dream chasers need to be bolder.
I like your shamelessness
and confidence.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Mr. Lin.
Well...
Ze.
I just went out for a while.
What are you doing?
No.
I just want to try if your leather chair
is that comfortable.
Have you finished the script?
Hurry up.
Okay, Zhaoyang.
Are you two new here?
Yes.
I'm your department leader.
Director of Web Drama Department,
Lai Zhaoyang.
Don't call me Mr. Lai.
Zhaoyang.
My name is Zhou Shui.
Zhou Shui.
This is Dai Daji.
Hello, Zhaoyang.
You two are now
part of the company.
Show me whatever skills you have.
Give it your best, okay?
Okay.
Come on. Do your best as an intern.
Give me five.
Come on.
Okay.
Do your best. Go.
Hello, I'm Lin Ze.
Hello, I'm Dai Daji.
Why are you here?
Didn't I...
Didn't I win back then?
I won five million yuan,
- but I waited for...
- Hey.
We're in meeting.
I'm sorry.
After three months,
I didn't get a cent.
It hasn't been easy for you either.
You know what?
My dream is to make
the funniest comedy in China.
I've always thought I was funny,
but the people around me don't think so.
It's okay, buddy.
Now that we're in Shendu,
China's best film company,
we're one step closer to making movies.
Aren't we making web dramas?
- So what?
We're in such a good company.
As long as you have film in your mind...
But I have a question.
Why are our lanyards blue?
Everyone's lanyard is black.
Me too.
You too?
Is it because
we're in the creative field?
We're better?
You're so optimistic.
Blue lanyards are for interns.
Black are for full-time ones.
This must be our company's cafeteria.
No way.
This is obviously
our company's garbage corner.
Sorry.
This is our workstation.
Have a seat, you two.
(Web Drama Department)
Zhou Shui, give me that...
Give me the book. Hurry.
No, give me another one.
Yes.
Ze, hurry and take a look at this book.
I can't pretend anymore.
We lost again.
We've been working here for a week.
What on earth have we done?
Yeah.
What on earth do we do every day?
We pretend to be busy every day.
Yang.
Have you edited Entertainment Report's
footage?
I'll finish it today.
Hurry up.
Why do they all look so busy?
Yeah.
It seems like everyone else is busy
except for the three of us.
Do you know
what they call this corner?
What do they call it?
The Ultimate Useless Corner.
(The Ultimate Useless Corner)
(Shendu Pictures)
- Zhaoyang.
Give us some work.
What do you mean?
We're too free.
Didn't you ask us to show our talents?
We have nowhere
to show them.
Yes, Zhaoyang.
Stop. Why are you grabbing my shirt?
You can't just
wait for the company
to assign work to you.
If you want to work,
find it yourself.
(Web Drama Department
Undertakes Video Productions)
Hello.
Do you know that our company
has a Web Drama Department?
Everyone.
This department undertakes
(Accepts All Kinds of Work)
editing and shooting projects.
Yes.
Hello.
Do you need any filming or editing?
I'm the director. He's the screenwriter.
We're professional.
Get to know Web Drama Department.
(We're Professional)
No need.
Help us.
Watch out.
What?
Really smart, huh?
Look.
Web Drama Department.
What stupid have they recruited?
They're not serious at all.
(Editing, Free Editing)
What do we do? There's still no one.
(Keep going!)
Web Drama Department?
Yes.
- Hello.
Hello.
Are you free now?
- Yes.
I'm the head of Video Department.
You can just call me Su Dan.
Our program,
Super Weight Loss King,
needs a promotional video.
I'm a bit short of manpower now.
Can you help me shoot it?
- No problem.
- Come in.
That way.
I'll leave it to you then.
Sure!
It
is a bit
urgent.
You...
Only three of you?
Ze is responsible for the script.
I'm the producer.
Zhou Shui is the director.
This won't work.
Even if it's a small video,
Shendu Pictures
has very high quality standards.
Do you have professional filming?
(Professional Filming)
(Professional Post-Production)
Professional post-production?
We need a professional budget.
Yes.
Here.
What's this?
You need to learn how to save costs.
Go to other departments and ask.
Trick a few people to help you.
Trick?
Invite.
Although the budget is limited,
you guys
still remember to eat breakfast.
Submit the video in three days.
Good luck.
Remember to eat breakfast.
The one with frizzy hair.
I heard
he's our company's editing expert.
Let's recruit him.
Okay.
How are we recruiting him?
I heard that you're the best
video editor in our company.
You're exaggerating.
Buddy.
We've been observing you for a few days.
Why do you keep eating steamed buns?
Do you not communicate with others?
Are you short on money?
If you have any problems, tell us.
At least we can afford
grilled sausages.
You...
You're too kind.
Xiaomao, move over.
We're a team from now on.
Yeah.
We all think
you're a right fit
for Useless Corner.
Why should I join you?
Because we all
- have blue lanyards.
- Have blue lanyards.
Xiaomao.
Welcome, Xiaomao.
Welcome.
Is there anyone in the company
who can film?
Yes.
There's one guy.
He has such handsome bangs.
Action.
Go.
Zhou Shui from Guang'an, Sichuan.
Dai Daji from Ezhou, Hubei.
Lin Ze from Shunde, Guangdong.
Li Xiaomao from Bengbu, Anhui.
Xue Cheng
from Shijiazhuang, Hebei.
- Here.
- Good luck.
Welcome.
Welcome to Useless Corner.
Useless Corner's first film
begins production!
How much budget do we have left?
Grilled sausage cost two yuan each.
We have 40 yuan left.
How can we shoot
with such little money?
Yeah, we still need to find actors.
Who's to say otherwise?
How about
you handle casting the actors
for this?
Yes.
No.
No, do you think actors do it for free?
Beautiful.
Use your connections
at Beautiful.
Find models.
Models.
Yes.
Find a model!
Model?
Beautiful?
It's a small budget.
We bought sausages.
It's lucky to get them here.
Be content.
Forget it.
I'll sponsor a little.
- Gosh, you're rich.
It's for the sake of art.
Photographers don't handle money.
No, well...
Screenwriters
don't handle money either.
I'm an editor.
Director.
Directors can never save money.
Are you saying
I should handle the money?
Our budget will be
in your hands.
- Daji.
Then,
I'm a producer.
I'm a producer!
Good luck.
Are you the producer?
Yes.
Let me make it clear first.
I charge 200 yuan a day.
Pay first, I'll act later.
- Let's just say...
- Meeting.
Shouldn't the producer
handle the bargaining?
Yes.
Me?
Go.
- I'll settle this.
- Go.
Beautiful lady.
Can you do it for 140 yuan?
60 yuan lesser. Give us a discount.
Miss.
Think about it.
What if
you make our film and become popular?
Will you regret
bargaining about this mere 60 yuan
today?
I won't get popular.
Can a potentially popular film
be unable to afford 200 yuan?
Do you think you can become famous?
You can't say that.
Well, I'd like to ask you a question.
How old are you?
60.
What's wrong?
You usually play some extra roles,
right?
At this age,
what else can I play if not extra roles?
Don't you want to be
the leading actress?
Yes, Madam.
Do you know that leading actresses
have to bring funding
to the production?
You don't have to pay.
We'll pay you 140 yuan.
What a good deal.
You won't be taken advantage of.
I also have a little dream.
I...
We also have dreams.
- Dreams.
Dreams.
- Madam.
Be gentle, Madam. Be gentle.
As the sun sets,
the heartbroken soul goes
far away
to the ends of the earth.
(This is my first film as producer.)
(The total budget was only 140 yuan.)
(I could never have imagined
at that time)
(that this 140 yuan)
(turned out to be
the beginning of my career.)
Okay.
Cut! Okay.
Thank you, everyone.
Let's call it a day!
(Fish's Love)
Look.
Executive Producer, Dai Daji.
Producer, Dai Daji.
(Producer, Dai Daji)
This is also Producer Dai Daji.
How did she become a career woman?
Aren't we following a romance drama?
How did it turn into a mystery drama?
Yeah, I also find it strange.
I asked a lot of people these few days.
No one in the company has heard of
the name Zhou Shui.
Not to mention
a director named Zhou Shui.
The Scandalous Couple we watched
won't take place
in another timeline, will it?
Tong Leyi, what are you doing?
Ms. Dai, this is a private call.
Was that Dai Daji?
Are you a hopeless romantic?
No.
I gave you three tasks this morning.
Prepare for the afternoon
production meeting.
Confirm the time and place
for dinner with Mr. Huang and Mr. Wu.
And print out the revised script.
Two hours have passed.
I haven't received any feedback.
All I see is you
calling your boyfriend.
It's not my boyfriend.
I'm telling you, Tong Leyi.
Sweet talk over video call is lame.
You might as well quit
and focus on your relationship.
Why work?
Ms. Dai, do you just assume
a guy and a girl on a video call
must be a couple?
I think you're the one
who's a hopeless romantic.
You want to quit, do you?
- I...
- You can leave now.
No, that's not what I meant.
I've already finished
the tasks you've given me.
Do you have anything else for me?
Find me as soon as you finish your work.
Don't wait for me to find you.
She's gotten so fierce now.
Our film
is considered a success
as long as it gets over 10,000 hits.
How come there are only 3,000 hits
in two hours?
Is it lagging on your end?
It shows 100,000 here.
How much?
100,000.
100,000?
(Hits)
What?
Still rising.
Comments say it's bizarre.
Bizarre?
What does it mean?
Useless people.
Our video is a hit.
How unexpected.
We have such talents in the company.
You guys filmed this?
Producer.
We did it.
(We Became Popular)
Let's go.
I've been in Beijing for years.
It's the first time
I met like-minded friends.
Cheers to like-minded souls!
Let's go home after we finish drinking.
We have work early tomorrow morning.
Daji is right.
We can gather together if we want.
How about I settle the bill first?
Waiter.
Waiter, bill please.
- I'll do it.
- Waiter.
No.
Why you?
I can pack some food back for my dad.
He's still at work.
- Still?
- He's still at work?
He's working overtime.
Where does your dad work?
He's also in Shendu.
What?
Our company is full of young people.
Uncle must be over 50 years old.
- Wait.
Aren't all the bosses older, right?
May I ask
which leader of our company
is your father?
The entrance.
The short stern-looking old man.
The company's
security guard and cleaner, Xue.
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
You scared me.
- I thought...
- Did you give me a chance?
I thought you were an heir.
Yes.
Xue Cheng.
I really envy you.
You have a family member
accompanying you in Beijing.
How nice.
Wait.
I have a family too.
My girlfriend is waiting for me
at the hotel.
You have a girlfriend?
I have a girlfriend too.
And she's coming to pick me up today.
One is like this,
and the other is like this.
Why do they have girlfriends?
Wait.
Ze.
That one.
Over here.
Huang.
My girlfriend is here.
Over here!
I'll take you to meet my new colleagues.
- Well.
- Slow down.
Everyone.
Hello.
Slow down.
This is my girlfriend, Huang.
Hello.
She works as a sales assistant
in the clothing store
next to our company.
Sorry, I'm late.
She's a bit afraid of the dark, so...
I'm not afraid.
You came to accompany Ze
as soon as you got off work.
True love.
- True love.
Now it seems
that these two
are the most pitiful
in our group.
It's not easy
to make it alone in Beijing.
Alone?
I think you two should just make do
with each other.
Yes.
Strive and progress together!
What do you mean?
He's my boyfriend.
She's my girlfriend.
They're a couple?
We're very close.
We commute to work together.
We go to the company together every day.
Aren't you together
because you're going the same way?
You're just taking a ride together.
Then what do you think we are?
You're like...
- Buddies.
Buddies?
Buddies.
I feel a little dizzy.
Zhou Shui.
Why don't we just be buddies?
What do you expect me to say?
Because our current relationship
is just awkward.
Being a couple
is just troublesome.
But being buddies has no burden.
Firstly,
we don't have to worry
about the conflicts we had.
Secondly,
we don't have to worry
about breaking up anymore, right?
Don't worry.
Daji is very loyal.
From now on,
I'll treat you like my younger brother.
Okay?
You know.
I wanted to have an older brother
when I was little.
Isn't that perfect?
You're my brother now.
Brother?
Watch out.
- Dumbbell.
Dumbbell!
You're back.
Why are you here?
What are you doing?
You've grown bigger.
You're annoying.
You always pinch him.
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for Jingshu.
Jingshu?
- Is she not back yet?
- It's 2 AM.
She works overtime.
Don't know when'll she be back.
That late?
That's Jingshu.
- Jingshu!
- Jingshu.
Perfect timing.
Bye.
Bye, see you tomorrow.
Why are you here?
We just got back too.
Dumbbell is waiting for you.
What are you looking at?
Who's that?
Colleague.
Which colleague?
Colleague at work.
- Let's go.
- Come.
- Let's go home.
Your workouts have been effective.
Did you train it today?
I'm alright.
You're like a bullfrog now.
Why did you agree to let him send you?
He's my colleague.
And we split the gas bill, okay?
It's still inappropriate.
It's inappropriate if it's a man.
He's married
and has a three-year-old kid.
How could he go after me?
He's married with a kid.
Yet he let you sit beside him.
What is he after?
You mean I have to sit in the back seat?
Won't I be treating him as a driver?
I don't care.
Even the trunk is forbidden.
Trunk?
You've indeed gone too far.
Dumbbell.
Let me tell you something.
Come.
Come on.
Look at you.
You'll say any trash when you're angry.
The trunk?
How hurtful.
It's normal to be jealous, right?
Men are like that.
You don't have to be so angry.
Look at Dumbbell.
How petty.
He's angry over such a small matter.
Yeah.
Even if he's worried,
what he said was really harsh.
It's like I'm having an affair
whenever I'm with another man.
Don't you know Dumbbell well?
His muscles are well-developed,
but his mind is...
Simple.
Yes.
Yes, I admit it.
I'm a simple-minded person
who speaks without thinking.
She had suffered so much before.
I can't let her get hurt any more.
I must protect her.
Sure.
Tell me how you'll protect her.
I've already thought about it.
I'll save up first.
When I have enough money,
I'll open a training studio.
I'll make money to support her.
When we save enough money,
he can open a private training studio.
Then, I can quit
the car dealership.
I can help him
keep the accounts and collect the money.
Then, we can get married.
And have a child.
Anyway, I'm taking care of her
the whole life.
I'm fine with anything.
I feel like
I could be with Dumbbell forever.
Gosh.
Didn't you just have an argument?
I didn't even need to comfort you.
You two are showing off.
You're upsetting me.
Alright.
I'll go now.
No, wait.
She's still angry.
Haven't you calmed down?
You've even imagined the future.
Having a child, buying a car.
Is this an argument?
You two are showing off.
Back in Chunzhili,
you and Daji showed off to us a lot too.
Did we?
Were we
as close as you are now?
Yes, you two are worse.
Really?
When I think about it,
I suddenly miss the past.
But that was the past.
I miss it so much.
What are you missing?
Haven't you two reconciled?
You know what?
On the way back just now,
I want him to be my brother.
He agreed.
Daji told me today
that we should just be buddies.
Although we're back together,
I keep feeling like
we can never go back
to how things were before.
If that feeling from before is gone,
what's left between us?
How can we maintain our relationship?
Is it time?
90 days, 8 hours, and 43 minutes.
It's time.
Okay.
- Buddy.
Go!
Go in.
It's been three months.
Time to change them.
Our three-month internship is over.
Give us black lanyards.
- Black lanyards!
Okay!
Congratulations.
Next,
you have six months of probation
waiting for you.
These are for your probation.
They're all
blue.
What's the difference?
Take a look.
This is royal blue.
This is navy blue.
It's obvious.
- Kind of obvious.
- It's obvious.
Get out!
Tell me.
What's the difference
between the blue in summer
and the blue in autumn?
The color is a little darker.
I'm leaving, Director Zhou.
Bye.
- See you.
You won't see me tomorrow.
I'm going to quit.
What?
Why are you quitting?
What do you mean?
Xiaomao.
I'm going back to get married.
Get married?
You're getting married young?
I've been working here for so long
but still haven't been made permanent.
My girlfriend's been waiting
for me for years.
She told me
to either get married
or break up.
I love her very much.
We already booked the tickets.
I can't make movies with you anymore.
No!
Where's your girlfriend?
Take us to her.
Dear, listen to me.
It's too early for you
to go to the airport.
Your flight is at 9 PM.
Wait for me, I'll be at the hotel soon.
Right away.
She has packed her luggage.
Mr. Li, welcome home.
No, you're staying here temporarily?
We have always stayed here.
You're staying at a five-star hotel.
Not bad.
It's good to have a staff to clean.
Then why do you keep eating
buns and instant noodles?
A lot of footage to edit.
I don't have time to eat.
Buddy, you're rich.
Why edit footage there?
That's not my money.
It's my dad's money!
Your dad's rich,
so you don't need to work hard!
Do you understand me or not?
If I don't work hard,
I have to go back
to inherit our family's dental clinic!
Mr. Li.
Welcome home.
Li Xiaomao.
Yan.
- Send it to Bengbu, Anhui.
- What?
I brought my colleagues to meet you.
- Hi.
I've met them.
Miss, please stay!
Can you let him stay here?
Yes.
Just break up.
No!
Well... Xiaomao came to Beijing
to make money to support you.
Don't talk nonsense!
She's richer than me.
Can you not get married first?
What do you think?
We've been dating for seven years.
I need to take on the responsibility
that I should bear.
Can you guys get engaged first?
We're already engaged!
Maybe I shouldn't have come to Beijing.
I'm too selfish.
Didn't you bring so many colleagues
to meet me
because you want me
to give you some face?
Okay.
I'll give you face.
I know
you want to stay in Beijing
to make movies.
Right?
Let's...
Break up.
- Okay!
Well...
Break up?
Listen well.
You look pretty handsome today.
Xiaomao.
Let me tell you a secret.
Didn't you say before
that Daji and I
don't look like a couple?
Indeed, we think so too.
Because Daji has broken up
with me half a year ago.
Break up?
She left me and Beijing half a year ago.
I think she couldn't hold on any longer
in the relationship.
But I can't let her go.
Just like how we can't let go of movies.
Why was she willing
to come back with you?
I don't know either.
Yan!
Miss Yan!
I know why you want to leave.
I understand you
because we're the same.
How are we the same?
We both fell in love
with a boy who loves movies.
We broke up before.
The reason
I was willing to come back with him
is because he's different from others.
He has a dream
and loves movies.
He shines!
Miss Yan!
The five of us
became friends
because we have a common dream.
We're going to make movies in Beijing.
Every one of us is indispensable.
I can see that you're the same as us.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have
waited for him in Beijing
for four years.
Li Xiaomao didn't let you down.
We're very close to making movies.
Li Xiaomao is a brave man.
A man with dreams.
People with dreams are worthy of love!
People with dreams shine!
- Stay here!
- Let's make movies together!
Stop talking.
Yan!
I love you!
Please don't leave!
Why did she leave anyway?
It's okay, Xiaomao.
You tried your best, Xiaomao.
What should I do?
Xiaomao.
(Impressing others with dreams)
(sounds like a joke now.)
(But many years later,)
(the me who's been worn down by reality)
(misses that shining era)
(and those shining people even more.)
We can make movies now.
Let's make movies!
Zhou Shui!
I get it now.
I came back to Beijing this time
to help you make movies.
I'm here to help you
realize your movie dream!
Thank you, Daji!
If you don't let me down,
I won't let you down either.
Is it worth it?
From having nothing to having nothing
To turn back at every crossroads
Is it worth it?
Swearing to become the sea,
not just a river
Is it worth it?
That night,
the wine was finished with just one sip
Do you dare?
When having nothing, I don't frown
Once I decide to start,
I hold your hand tightly
Do you dare?
Even in the coldest winter,
we feel it on the ice
Do you dare?
Striving for an outlet
in reality and love
Only to realize when we drift apart
We mistook that day for forever
Time passes, bidding farewell to youth
Luckily, we have been brave
ever since we met
Perhaps that day means forever
Outrunning time,
leaving the past behind
Is it worth it?
Do you dare?
The love that's worth it, be brave
Later, the ocean drifted far away
Even the waves grew tired
The coldest days once burned
like blazing flames
Perhaps someday,
we will look back on the past
Ideals and vows.
How passionate they were
Once, there was a moment so vivid