[Zhao Jiadi S2]
[Director: Jing Xiaoyao]
[Episode 26]
Sweetheart.
Zhao Jiadi.
Who is this?
Li Zhijin is with us.
If you don't want her hurt,
let's meet up.
Be careful
with what you can do
or can't do.
Standing by your side.
Let me introduce you first.
This is...
my mom.
And this is my dad.
This is...
the one I always mention,
Li Zhijin.
Honestly, I've always
wanted you to have dinner
with my family once.
Just one meal together.
Zhijin,
let me take the towel off for you, okay?
Can you not shout?
Untie the rope for me.
I'll feed you.
Tomato scrambled eggs.
No tomatoes.
It's your favorite.
Eat it and I'll untie you.
I'm here. Where is she?
You're dead. No need to tell you.
[Lin: It's done.]
[Boss: Meet at the dock, 2 AM.]
Let me ask you something.
Is Shen Village Port
closer to me,
or to Wei Jinghai?
No idea.
Just give it to me straight.
Thanks.
You love hiding behind others.
Keep climbing.
Bribed a driver to hurt someone.
Ordered your crew to attack.
Kidnapping and smuggling.
Got a group around you,
making them take the heat.
Meanwhile, you just walked away.
If you ever did one thing
fair and square,
maybe I wouldn't look down on you.
You know,
you're in no place to judge me.
Did you call the police?
Yeah, I did.
Zhao Jiadi,
do you know
what I hate most about you?
You're always like this,
acting like you know it all,
pretending to be so righteous.
But honestly, it's all nonsense.
You've planned everything out
just...
for your own gain.
Then you started talking about
what's right
and what's fair.
You're just lucky to be born privileged.
Yeah, you had it easy.
Now you act so above it all,
turning everything down,
like nothing's good enough.
You really disgust me.
I'm not like you.
I never had a choice.
Between people, it isn't all about gain.
There's something else.
Zhao Jiadi.
[Police]
Don't move!
The police.
It's over now.
When we first met, I told you
if we couldn't be friends,
at least we wouldn't be enemies.
Life is all about choices.
You've made yours.
Here is today's update.
In our city's
ongoing crackdown on organized crime,
with detailed planning from the
citywide anti-crime task force,
[Midday News]
the police carried out thorough checks,
and took firm action against
a smuggling group
led by Wei Jinghai.
Seventy-six people were arrested.
Some are charged with smuggling goods,
others with intentional homicide,
and some with intentional injury,
as well as group fighting and more.
It's reported this gang
ran like a company
and hid in Hang City for years.
They made money
through smuggling, laundering,
and other illegal activities.
The impact on society was severe.
Here's the full report.
[Sealed by Hang City Police Department]
[Fei's Restaurant]
Miss, check the bill.
Coming.
Let me see.
Twenty yuan.
That's perfect.
Take care on your way out.
Come back if you like it.
Uncle Bao, I forgot again.
Can you show me one more time?
You forgot again.
Alright, let me show you again.
Watch closely now.
Happiness will come, sooner or later!
I'll show you again tonight at home.
Sound good?
Sounds good.
Tongtong, you're so sweet.
Ready to fly together?
Yes.
Alright, here we go.
Lift me up high!
You want to go up high?
Up you go!
Tongtong's flying now.
You two, be careful.
Don't fall.
Should we keep going?
Tongtong, let's fly to your mom.
Here we go, up we fly.
Watch out, stay safe.
Let's go one more time.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
No problem.
That's fine.
Looks like everything's okay.
Boss.
I heard Jiadi's company
is launching soon.
They said you were invited too.
I turned them down.
You can keep it.
No need, really.
Is there anything else?
That's all.
Ming Gu.
Boss,
I'll give it my all.
Mingjian,
[Zhao Jiadi]
the company license is approved.
If you're interested,
I'd like you to join me.
I want to build a tech-driven team.
Your analytical skills
are way ahead of mine.
Let's work on this together.
We'll make a name for ourselves
in Hang City.
No need to rush your answer.
Take your time to think it over.
[Way and Virtue]
What's in these boxes?
Probably project files.
Peng sent it over.
Sweetheart,
can you check if this looks right?
Looks fine to me.
You really are something.
You turned down Li Group
and Jufeng Capital.
Mr. Huang invested so much in you.
But you still spend so carefully.
The new company isn't ready just yet.
Starting out here works just fine.
Besides,
this is what I call
keeping a low profile.
Alright then, Mr. Zhao.
When you're building your team,
keep me in mind, will you?
I'm pretty talented, you know.
Let me think about it.
Alright.
Send your info to my assistant later,
I'll check it out when I have time.
Zhao Jiadi!
Get up!
Since when did you have an assistant?
Why didn't I know about this?
Ow, that hurts.
Male assistant.
Mr. Zhao.
What do you think of me
as your assistant?
Weren't you coming next week?
I showed up today.
Heard you're starting a business.
I couldn't just sit around.
So I'm here to check in with you.
Come on.
Let me introduce you.
This is my wife,
Li Zhijin.
And this is my good friend,
Wu Dengke.
Hello.
Your wife is really beautiful.
Call her Zhijin.
Zhijin.
Zhijin, can I ask you something?
What made you interested in him?
Why are you always teasing me?
Sweetheart, can you book a restaurant?
Let's have dinner together tonight.
Sure.
Let me help with your luggage.
Come on, let's go, Mrs. Zhao.
- Call her Zhijin.
- Let's go.
That's a big show you put on.
Nanshan Chamber of Commerce
took a big hit.
Fan Longquan passed away so young.
Li Minxian just recovered
from a major illness.
Are you still planning to fight them?
Who's trying to fight them?
This mining site is huge.
Even if I have a big appetite,
eating it all alone
would make me suffer.
You've really changed your tune.
When it comes to business,
partners are important.
That old guy sent an invitation.
He said he wanted to talk.
Then let's just talk.
So where's the meeting spot?
Tang City? He doesn't want to come.
And I don't really want to
go to Hang City.
So we decided to meet halfway.
It's been ages since I saw that guy.
Not sure if he's changed
his temper by now.
When it comes to temper,
yours is even stronger than his.
Have you ever thought about
meeting Baliang?
Why would I bother seeing him?
In the invitation,
he even highlighted
"live-in son-in-law".
Like he thinks he's won or something.
Uncle, let me be honest with you.
About this engagement,
I won't agree to this.
Will you or won't you?
That's not really up to you.
With a dad like you, who'd blame him?
Maybe Baliang
still resents you deep down.
A Zhao family kid
either lives standing tall
or dies kneeling.
If he doesn't struggle a bit
and step outside his comfort zone,
does he really deserve
to be called a man?
About our Go game,
I won.
It's the gambling game you started,
so you'd better remember the rules.
Who says so?
We just met up.
Nothing has been decided.
No one knows who'll win yet.
Watch yourself.
"General Guan Yu lost Jingzhou
due to negligence."
How about this, Uncle,
let's make another bet.
[Reflection]
[Observation, Knowledge,
Sincerity, Reflection]
Next up,
write in semi-cursive script.
Just write down,
"There's no reason
beyond balance.
There's nothing to truly learn
without respect."
This takes real effort.
Can you write in cursive script?
Sure.
Then write down,
"The whole army
wants him to risk his life.
The people want him to value his life.
Without risking his life,
chaos can't be stopped.
If there's no renewal,
chaos is easy to start."
The brush moves smoothly.
Such flamboyant calligraphy.
Beautiful handwriting.
It's making my hands itch to try.
Come on.
Let me give it a shot too.
Alright.
In one's life,
it's all just emptiness.
Some people
chase after fame and gain,
always scheming against each other
just to leave something
in the history.
But what can we really leave behind?
If you're after profit,
think about what's good for all.
If you're after a name,
aim for a legacy that lasts.
In this regard,
I'm not as open-minded as Longquan.
Jiadi,
you're heading to Hai City for talks.
You'll be representing the NCC.
Whatever grudges
there were,
work comes first.
Understood.
Good.
I want to take a break.
Jiadi,
have a seat.
Just now,
something
popped into my mind.
Go on.
But saying it out loud
sounds a bit odd.
You know,
everyone has their own path.
Someday,
when you're a parent,
maybe
you'll see things differently
and understand Zhao Xin more.
Back then,
only you would know
how you really felt inside.
Grandpa,
it's time for your medicine.
Come on, help me escape.
No.
Come on, hurry up.
Why are you
acting like a kid?
Still scared of the medicine's bitter?
I'm already better.
I don't need it anymore.
That's not how it works.
Just have a bite.
That's hot.
Set it down for now.
We did agree on that.
You have to drink it later.
Yeah, I'll drink in a bit.
Grandpa, I wanted to ask you something.
Isn't Jiadi going to Hai City?
I want to go with him.
Why would you go?
Who's watching the company?
It's good to rest sometimes.
Besides, we agreed on this.
I'm just filling in.
You need to
find a new manager.
Why should I look?
Isn't he good?
Come on, don't back out now.
We've got something else to do.
To do what?
My concerns are your concerns.
I want a grandchild.
Grandpa.
Come on.
I'll work hard on that.
Bad boy.
[Hai City]
I'll show myself in.
Alright.
♪The night pauses♪
♪The noisy world falls into silence♪
♪Who lets loneliness tear apart♪
♪The once lost soul♪
♪Waiting for fate to return♪
♪The freedom behind the surge♪
♪Pride suppresses the self♪
♪Desire turns into foam♪
♪The outline in the mirror♪
♪Reminds me of the mistakes
of wasted time♪
♪A thousand truths♪
Please have a seat.
♪Time buries the clues♪
♪That reveal the lies and illusions♪
♪Cruelty awakens the self♪
♪Struggling to begin again♪
♪The shadow hides in biting sadness♪
♪Reason chases the soul's light♪
♪In this confused reality♪
♪Might as well look up♪
♪Through wind and sand,
he narrows his eyes♪
♪The road ahead is rough, each step a fight♪
[The world is vast, yet our paths converge.
Until we meet again to rewrite the rules of the game.]
[See you in Season 3.]
♪Full of passion, he's never changed♪
♪Though they always say
he's a little untamed♪
♪Wind and snow always stay by his side♪
♪They fuel his fire, light his way♪
♪On such a long journey♪
♪The road is muddy,
but he never stumbles♪
♪The stars shine bright above♪
♪Even exhausted, he leaves no regrets♪
♪On such a long journey♪
♪The road is muddy,
but he never stumbles♪
♪The stars shine bright above♪
♪Even exhausted, he leaves no regrets♪
[Exclusive Platform]
[The exclusive network distribution rights belong]
[to Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]