[Zhao Jiadi S2]
[Director: Jing Xiaoyao]
[Episode 15]
[Yunhai Hot Spring Club]
Mr. Liu,
business is business.
What's this for?
Negotiation.
We should all be upfront.
Don't you agree?
No problem.
But since I'm here,
let my friend go back.
You don't need to worry about that.
Those two friends of yours
are taken good care of.
Once we settle things,
you can all leave together.
Just wait here.
Sir, here's your locker key.
The boss is waiting for you inside.
You're Mr. Fan, right?
Before I met Manager Liu last time,
I looked up info on the developer.
You're as impressive
as they say.
Zhao Jiadi,
you scared Liu Xin
just to get to me.
Yes.
I wanted to
give you some advice.
When I traded watermelons
for steel,
you weren't even born yet.
Giving me advice?
I really can't stand schemers.
What do you actually want from me?
Trying to
clear a path for yourself?
Being wealthy isn't
about your bank account,
and status isn't just about your title.
I don't depend on you for anything
and I'm not asking you for money.
Why would I try to block your way?
Zhao, listen up.
Who gave you the nerve
to talk to Mr. Fan like that?
I don't have the nerve.
And I don't need it.
I just speak what I believe is right.
Mr. Fan,
I haven't seen
your commercial district plan,
but I can guess the general idea.
Let me be upfront.
The building where Ms. Fang
runs her noodle shop
isn't right for clothing stores.
It should be for food spots.
For companies to grow, skills matter,
but adapting
to a diverse world does too.
Looking at the trend,
e-commerce is really taking off
and clothing businesses
will feel it first.
The Internet is growing faster
than we imagine.
The new commercial city
is being built.
The focus has to be on dining spots.
Also, on entertainment and services.
Young people think differently now.
Once the subway's done,
the two business areas will connect,
and lots of young folks
will live nearby.
So leading with restaurants
is the real path to growth.
Mr. Fan,
I've said what I wanted to say.
If I crossed a line,
let me offer you a toast.
Take a seat.
Jiadi,
you work in finance, right?
Yeah.
With your skills,
why not head to Hai City?
But you ended up
coming to Hang City.
I came to Hang City to help someone.
And honestly, to help myself too.
So you're saying,
Hang City means a lot to you.
Yeah, it does.
I've heard your advice.
Whether I take it or not,
that's my call.
You make a good point,
but you're not selfless.
To put it bluntly,
you're hoping to save a spot
for your friend who's opening a resto.
Am I right?
I can accept all the conditions
from your friend's store,
without arguing.
But I have one condition.
Go ahead.
I just said it.
I can't stand people who play games.
I hate it when people
try to outsmart me.
I want you out of Hang City tonight.
If you don't,
I can't promise
nothing will happen to you.
Are my friends okay?
That depends on you.
No problem.
Mr. Fan, please make sure
they get home safe.
I'll leave today.
You agreed so easily.
Maybe your goal
isn't that important to you.
That's my business.
I don't owe anyone an explanation.
But Mr. Fan,
I need you to know this.
My friends are my bottom line.
No one gets to touch them.
As for the path,
if it works, I just go for it.
If not, I'll find another way.
There's always a way out.
Alright.
Good.
Loyal, brave, and proud.
I like that.
Boss,
I told you,
he really gets your vibe.
Don't worry.
Ms. Fang and the others
are upstairs getting massages.
I'm looking after them well.
Nothing's going on.
Call everyone down from upstairs.
Let's have a meal together.
Want me to give you a quick rub?
Maybe a back rub.
My acting's as good as yours, right?
It is.
Everyone's in bathrobes now.
I'll change into one too.
Just joining the fun with my people.
Used the wrong word there.
Uncle,
you should try it later too.
That massage was amazing.
You sure had a good time.
You had no idea
how nervous I was down there.
I honestly didn't think much of it.
Mr. Liu explained it well.
I can vouch for that.
This was all my boss's idea.
There's no way I'd think that up.
Mr. Fan.
The kitchen's got limited ingredients.
So I whipped up a few dishes.
Please try them.
This one looks pretty good.
The fish
was soaked in ginger juice, right?
Yeah.
Because cooking wine
takes away the freshness,
and I can't get used to vinegar.
Boss Fan,
you're amazing.
You just tasted it and knew everything.
I begged for ages
to get this secret recipe.
Well, it's not really a secret recipe.
You guys don't know,
my boss's wife cooks at home.
Her cooking
is amazing.
Just the smell
makes my mouth water.
I've been with Mr. Fan for years.
Except for work dinners,
I've never seen him eat out.
No wonder.
Mr. Fan doesn't want to
run a restaurant.
With such great food at home,
nothing outside can compare.
Don't listen to him.
Fang.
Shang Bao.
Let's all have a seat.
Let's eat together, everyone.
Come on, sit.
Good food needs good wine.
Have a little of this.
Thank you.
It's made from pure grains, no headache.
Jiadi,
I caught what you said just now.
You were hinting at me, right?
Am I right?
Don't worry.
I always keep my word.
Fang,
about your resto,
I'll have someone touch base
with you later.
As for us,
we're not moving anymore.
Thank you, Mr. Fan.
Thanks.
Let's toast to you.
Yeah, toast to you.
I'll join you for a toast.
Thank you, Mr. Fan.
Thank you.
Thanks, Fan.
Nobody does it better than my boss.
Eat more. After, we can go soak again.
Later, I'll give you both a massage.
I'll give you two a massage.
Let me give a massage to you two.
Jiadi,
the favor you asked for your friend
can be considered done.
Does that mean
you owe me a favor now?
Of course.
Mr. Fan,
I'm not an expert in business deals,
but finance is my thing.
If you ever need anything,
just let me know.
Actually, I have a project now.
I'm thinking of a joint venture.
I want to
take over
the joint venture's management.
But I'm short on liquidity.
So I want to ask Risheng
for the funding.
Is it a real estate project?
Given Risheng's profile,
we might not do real estate financing.
You'll need to talk to a bank.
No,
it's a mining company.
It's over in Kalpunia.
You can look into it
when you get a chance.
I heard
that the NCC
worked with Risheng years ago.
Boss Fan,
I can't follow all this,
but
I always thought real estate was great.
Skyscrapers and everything.
But just hearing "mining company"
makes me tired.
Come off it.
He's joking.
To this day,
I earn every penny through hard work.
I've always felt
you only get
what you can handle.
But things are different now.
I've got more people on my team.
I have to think about them too.
I can't just
enjoy everything alone,
while the rest work hard for me.
Fan,
good drinks are easy to find,
but true friends are rare.
If you trust me,
let me handle the financing.
No matter how it goes,
I'll give you an answer.
Eat more, okay?
After this, I have to head to the mine.
Try the dish I made.
Here, have some of Fang's fish.
Xu Ziqi,
if you're not upstairs,
I'll deal with you.
Mr. Huang.
[Huang Hu,
Chairman of Honghu Global Group]
And you are?
Hello.
I'm Li Zhijin.
When I was abroad,
I attended one of your talks.
But I'm sure you don't remember.
You're Minxian's granddaughter.
I know, I know.
I just met your grandpa not long ago.
I saw your photo at your place.
He talks about you
all the time.
Miss,
please have a seat.
I didn't plan
to use my grandpa's name.
I didn't except
you two know each other.
My family is originally from Hang City.
I go way back with your grandfather.
We met
long before you were born.
It's just that these years,
I've been living overseas.
So we didn't keep in touch much.
Miss,
what brings you here?
Honestly, my plan was
to pretend we ran into each other
by chance.
See if we could maybe work together.
But now, with my grandpa in the mix,
I can't do it that way.
Your grandpa
wants you back at Li Group.
If that happens,
there's a chance
we could start doing business together.
Mr. Huang.
Are you planning to go back
after this visit?
As people age,
they just want to return home.
My wife
always wished
to go back to where we started.
It was me
who held us back.
I know you run a business.
I can guess why you wanted to see me.
But honestly,
at my age,
money's not
what I care about anymore.
A company is easy to build,
but talents are hard to find.
You...
I came back,
trying to gather
the overseas investors
I have connections with,
to set up a foundation together.
It'll focus on local development.
I get it now.
So what you're looking for
isn't a company like Jufeng,
but someone reliable,
or a trustworthy team,
to help manage the foundation for you.
Exactly.
Mr. Huang, I know just the right person.
Really?
I'm confident about this.
He checks every box you have.
When do you have time?
I'd like you
to meet him.
Sure.
A meeting's not the problem,
but honestly,
there's someone else too.
Ms. Deng.
Is it ready?
Yes.
Here you go.
Alright.
Hope your business booms.
Thanks.
Hey, Mr. Farmer,
didn't you ask me for work before?
I've got something now.
It's a big job.
What is it?
But it might take some time.
Just tell me straight.
When are you free this week?
I'll set it up for you.
He has someone in mind too.
If you're late, you might miss out.
Then maybe just let it go.
You can't force...
Mr. Farmer,
were you genuinely
asking for my help?
Of course.
We have to meet.
Thursday won't work.
I already have plans.
Tomorrow or Friday is fine.
You pick.
He seems busy tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow morning works.
Or let's tentatively set for Friday.
I'll see if I can set it up.
As for my side,
I'll prepare some info for you.
Take it home and read it carefully.
Make sure to read it.
Alright?
Got it.
197-6 Huasheng Road.
Hey.
If you just walk in like that,
I swear I'll start shouting
that Zhao Jiadi abandoned his family,
and left everyone behind.
Miss Pei,
did I do something to upset you?
If I did, just tell me,
and I'll apologize right away.
Wasn't it right here
they hit you last time?
Broker Zhao,
your job today is to keep me company.
Once I'm in a good mood,
I'll tell you
about my investment preferences,
and what I expect,
and all that stuff.
Anyway, your boss said,
"Customers come first."
I need to drop something off.
We're pretty much done here, right?
I'll leave your stuff in the car and go.
No way.
I still haven't bought enough.
Let's try another mall instead.
I want to check out that bracelet.
I'm not like you, all rich and free.
I can't waste my time here.
Maybe find someone else
to hang out with.
Zhao Jiadi,
you came to Hang City
for a reason, right?
You'd better tell me now.
I might even help you plan things.
Otherwise, if something happens to you,
I won't be able to help at all.
Just be straight with me.
What could even happen to me?
So, you're curious now?
Start the car.
Why did you used to
ignore talks about the NCC?
Now you can't stop asking about it.
So in the Li Group,
is the real leader Wei Jinghai,
or Li Minxian?
Honestly, I'm not sure about that.
But Mr. Li
has been out of the spotlight for years.
He only shows up
when it's really important.
I've only seen him once or twice myself.
Wei Jinghai.
What kind of person is he?
Zhao Jiadi,
I don't want to talk about it with you.
As for Mr. Wei,
I haven't met him much.
But I've heard plenty about him.
His relationship
with the Lis is complicated.
He's pretty much Mr. Li's foster son.
How do I describe him...
He always thinks before he speaks,
never leaves any loose ends.
He's pretty mysterious.
Isn't there another heir
to the Li Group?
Chairman Li's granddaughter.
So what's her role in the Li...
Zhao Jiadi,
when you're with me,
don't talk about other girls.
I'm home.
Alright.
Okay, I'm heading out.
I've got so much stuff here.
Are you going to help?
Fine.
Wait a sec.
Don't worry.
Let me pop the front trunk.
I won't bite, relax.
It's open now.
Right here.
Go knock on the door.
There's a nanny inside.
Sit wherever you like.
Where did you run off to, silly girl?
Ms. Cai.
Zhao Jiadi.
Ji Jie.
Yanzhi.
What brings you two here?
We're here to check on you.
You must be Zhao Jiadi.
Yanzhi's mentioned you before.
I'm Ji Jie.
We're all close friends.
Hey there.
Hi, Ji Jie.
Let's just keep it another way.
Hi, Ms. Ji.
Ms. Cai.
Why didn't you tell me
you came to Hang City?
I could've picked you up.
It's fine. I know you're busy.
Have you lost some weight?
You look great, though.
They're all grown adults.
No need for you to pick me up.
Miss Pei is our company's client.
I didn't know you two knew each other.
If I had,
I'd have taken better care of her.
Jiadi.
Where's the lingerie I bought today?
I didn't see it anywhere.
Did you leave it in the car?
Luoshen
has got a bit of a temper.
Don't take it to heart.
Got it.
Oh right, Ms. Cai.
I actually wanted to talk to you.
Should we go somewhere else?
Sure.
No way.
My place is huge.
But there's nowhere for you two to talk?
There's the living room, bedroom, study.
Pick any room you like.
Ji Jie.
Let's head out together.
Leave this house to them.
Let them have a proper talk here.
Ms. Cai.
Did I say something wrong?
She...
She just needs to vent a bit.
Looks like my grandma was right.
The prettier a woman is,
the more complicated it gets.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Are you saying
I'm not pretty enough?
Ms. Cai.
Please, don't be like this.
Come here.
Pei.
Pei Luoshen.
You're not a kid anymore.
Why should I?
Why is she always in the center?
It's always Cai Yanzhi, no matter what.
Why does she get Yang Qingdi?
All those years she had
is more than most get in a lifetime.
I just want that kind of love too.
Every day,
she always looks so cold.
Didn't she already say it?
Yang Qingdi has her whole heart now.
There's no space left for Zhao Jiadi.
So what was she doing just now?
She kept looking at Zhao Jiadi.
What kind of look was that?
Ji Jie, can you be the judge here?
Silly you,
you've never had a tough time.
We've all spoiled you way too much.
All these years,
you've competed
with Yanzhi for everything.
Whatever she likes, you like too.
Luckily, Yanzhi never held it
against you.
Besides,
you're sweet and lovable.
If it were someone else,
you two would've split ages ago.
I knew you were on her side.
Someone said this before.
She doesn't love a specific person.
She's in love with
the idea of love itself.
As long as someone makes her happy,
she'll like whoever that is.
What,
are you getting serious
about Zhao Jiadi?
No way.
He's just some clueless boy,
always getting on my nerves,
no social skills,
no manners,
and always pretending to be proper.
Even after getting beaten up,
he still tries to help others.
Why would I like...
You don't see many like him though.
Right?
I heard Fan Longquan
asked you to help with funding.
Yeah.
I've sorted out the info on Risheng.
If I get anything wrong,
just let me know.
Kalpunia covers 738 square kilometers.
It's rich in mineral resources,
copper, iron, aluminum,
zinc, gold, lead, and nickel,
even diamond and rare earth minerals.
But what they mine the most
is bauxite.
The Nanshan Chamber of Commerce
is located
in the northern part of Kalpunia.
What they produce
is also bauxite.
But Ke's mining district
is in the south.
Over there,
they just found a huge iron ore deposit.
That means
when Jinhai first stepped in,
they weren't competing
with the NCC.
But now,
the area Mr. Fan wants to expand into
just happens to be between both sides.
The resource there
is also iron ore.
On the NCC's side,
they've got workers,
hydropower, transport, stockyard,
and all the facilities they need.
If they switch to iron ore,
they just need to
update their equipment,
and find a mining plant.
Then, they can start anytime.
But it's different for Jinhai.
They have to
start everything from scratch.
Zhao Xin might not even
have finished building yet,
when the NCC is already shipping out.
Same supply.
Same origin.
But Zhao Xin will lose on time.
I heard Jinhai already started
the initial construction work.
And the investment's pretty big.
So, looking at it this way,
there's not much chance to win.
I used to think getting the mine
back for Ke from Jinhai
would take at least fifteen years.
But now, I think there's a shot.
Though
I haven't figured out exactly how,
I'll need to use the NCC.
If I can get shares
in the joint venture,
everything gets way easier.
That's a tough challenge,
not much easier than facing Jinhai.
I know.
But I have to give it a shot.
Will you come clean with Fan Longquan?
Yeah,
but not right now.
Ms. Cai.
I'm not that selfless.
I do care about Ke's situation.
Mr. Fan only sees me
as someone he respects, nothing more.
There's no real bond or trust yet.
I need to help him out first.
He should see
what kind of person I am,
and what I can actually do.
Then I'll come clean with him.
I know the NCC sticks together,
and Li Group is always in the mix.
But for now, there's no real chance
to meet Wei Jinghai.
Still, I think
I should test his attitude.
Actually, I can offer you a chance.
♪The night pauses♪
♪The noisy world falls into silence♪
♪Who lets loneliness tear apart♪
♪The once lost soul♪
♪Waiting for fate to return♪
♪The freedom behind the surge♪
♪Pride suppresses the self♪
♪Desire turns into foam♪
♪The outline in the mirror♪
♪Reminds me of the mistakes
of wasted time♪
♪A thousand truths♪
♪Shatter the shackles of falsehood♪
♪Time buries the clues♪
♪That reveal the lies and illusions♪
♪Cruelty awakens the self♪
♪Struggling to begin again♪
♪The shadow hides in biting sadness♪
♪Reason chases the soul's light♪
♪In this confused reality♪
♪Might as well look up♪
♪Love will cross paths with hate♪
♪Sparking fire♪
♪Speaking with tears and smiles♪
♪That cause and effect♪
♪The stars will shine♪
♪Illuminating the desert of memories♪
[Exclusive Platform]
[The exclusive network distribution rights belong]
[to Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]