ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL
HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
Is this okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
Jiaxu, do you want some hangover soup?
I don't drink alcohol.
I don't need it.
It's late. You should go to bed.
I'll sleep after taking a shower.
Right, Jiaxu.
You need a towel
and other things.
Though your dad's condition is stable,
we must try to avoid repeated infections.
He may be sent to the ICU again
at any time.
JIANG YING: CAN YOU SHOW ME
A PICTURE OF YOU IN A GRADUATION GOWN?
SORRY, THAT IS AN UNREASONABLE REQUEST
WHY AREN'T YOU REPLYING? ARE YOU BUSY?
Why are you still up?
Jiaxu, why are you still awake?
I…
I'm not used to this bed.
I can't sleep.
Then why don't I wake my brother up?
You can sleep on the sofa in his room.
You liked resting on that sofa
during our tutoring sessions, right?
It's fine.
I'll go to sleep soon.
It's late now.
You should go to bed.
Are you upset?
That's not it.
Why would I be?
If you're upset,
you can tell me about it.
You might feel better afterward.
I won't tell anyone about it.
Not even my brother.
It's fine
if you don't want to talk about it.
I can just keep you company for a while.
Let me tell you a secret.
I have
plenty of debtors out there.
Are you in huge debt?
It isn't about money.
Well, I guess it is about money.
How much do you owe?
Is it a huge sum?
How do I put it?
Jiaxu.
Don't panic.
Once I grow up
and start making money,
I'll help you pay it off.
I'm not kidding.
I'm serious.
Sang Zhi.
Actually,
these aren't my debts.
You don't need to help me repay them.
So Sang Zhi,
after you start earning money,
buy some beautiful dresses for yourself.
Was Jiaxu pretending to be tough?
I've never seen him like this before.
Make a lot of money
and help him pay off his debts.
JIAXU
I'm taking a morning flight back to Yihe.
Please tell your parents for me.
Also, you should study hard.
Remember to update me with your grades.
Don't forget the promise
you made to me.
Does she mean the gifts?
CHAPTER SEVEN, PROMISE
THE MOST IMPORTANT LITTLE THINGS
All of you are in 12th Grade now.
Besides the CAP,
you also need to be ready for the NCEE.
This handbook
contains the minimum admission scores
for the nation's top schools
and the corresponding
admission ratio of students
from our school each year.
You can compare your ranking
with this handbook
and make an estimation
of the colleges you can select.
You have to work hard for your future,
move toward your goal,
and enter the university of your dreams.
-This is a critical moment.
-To get into Yihe University,
I think I need to work harder.
FIRST MOCK ASSESSMENT RESULT,
GRADE 3, CLASS 1
TOP 10
Jiaxu, I finally found my dream.
My dream is to get into Yihe University.
YIHE UNIVERSITY
TOP 10
SEND, PROCESSING
JIAXU
MAP TO MY DREAM
NANWU CITY
YIHE CITY
MAP TO MY DREAM
Twelfth place?
Keep up the good work.
Your gift is on the way.
ENERGY CHARGING STATION
YIHE, NANWU, MAP TO MY DREAM
Top ten?
You really did it.
I've ordered your gift.
YIHE CITY
I must work harder
and get closer
to my dream.
Were you rejected again?
Fine, I'll stop talking.
I'll stop breaking your heart.
What did you say?
Duan Jiaxu got himself a girlfriend?
Really?
Isn't that great? He has finally done it.
Do you have a picture of her?
Show me what she looks like.
We can hold a celebration for him.
I'll hang up now. I'm having supper.
Bye.
Sang Yan.
Do you want noodles? I'll get you a bowl.
Does Jiaxu have a girlfriend now?
I guess so.
I just heard it from Qian Fei.
Hey, I got you a bowl.
JIAXU, I HEARD YOU GOT A GIRLFRIEND
It must be fake.
It doesn't sound true.
It's possible that he lied to Sang Yan.
When you find one,
can you show her to me first?
Sure.
I'll show you when I find one.
I'll remember that.
JIAXU
You promised me.
Should I ask him in person?
Hello?
Hello, Sang Zhi?
Why didn't you go to cram school?
Look at the time.
I'm in Yihe.
Where?
Yihe.
Why did you go there?
My online boyfriend told me to come.
You…
Which part of Yihe are you in right now?
The airport.
Stay there.
I'll tell Duan Jiaxu to pick you up.
Listen up.
If you go to see
your so-called online boyfriend,
you'll be in big trouble
when you get back.
Hello, Dad?
Have you found her?
Yes.
Where is she?
Hello?
Zhizhi.
Zhizhi, didn't you promise us
that you would stay away
from that guy online?
Stop it. Just stop.
Zhizhi.
Don't run around in the airport.
Safety first, okay?
It's best to stay in areas
with airport staff and police around.
If someone tries to approach you,
you must go to the police.
Do you understand?
By the way, Sang Yan
will tell Duan Jiaxu to pick you up.
Be nice, okay?
Mom, Jiaxu is calling me.
Okay. Be careful.
Hello?
Where are you?
Exit 18.
Okay.
Sang Zhi!
Jiaxu.
Have you found her?
Didn't you promise me
that you would study hard
and wouldn't make others worry?
Online boyfriend?
Have you forgotten what I told you before?
You're all grown up now, are you?
How dare you travel so far by yourself?
Who is she?
Is she your girlfriend?
You promised to tell me first.
Why didn't you keep your promise?
Say something.
Jiaxu.
Don't speak so harshly to her.
Did he tell you to come?
Have you met him?
He doesn't like me.
He said that I'm too young.
Has he left?
Sang Zhi.
He did the right thing.
You're too young right now.
This isn't right. Got it?
But I will grow up.
Then let's wait until you grow up.
But when I grow up,
he'll fall for someone else.
That's fine.
Sang Zhi, when you grow up,
you will meet someone better.
I guess this lady
is your "someone better."
Sorry.
Sorry for troubling you.
I won't do this again.
You're no trouble.
Wipe your tears.
We were worried about you.
We were scared
that something might happen to you.
But now,
it's good that you realize your mistake.
Wash up in the restroom.
I'll take you out to lunch.
I don't feel like going.
I want to go home.
Even so, you need to eat first.
Give me your ID card.
I'll get a plane ticket for you.
Jiaxu, why don't I take her?
It's fine, miss.
I can go by myself.
I can take care of myself.
Here, get up.
The restroom is over there.
Go and wash your face.
I'll go get lunch with you
after buying your plane ticket.
Go now.
We'll have a nice lunch.
The kiddo is all grown up.
So different from before.
That's how young girls are.
They'll grow up eventually.
Don't be too worried.
Why did you take it off? Put it on.
I don't need it.
Where's the lady?
She's busy and had to leave.
Was I too harsh earlier?
Kids are forgetful indeed.
You're treating me like a stranger
after a few months away.
I'm pretty heartbroken.
How much was the plane ticket?
It didn't cost a lot.
The flight is at 1:10 p.m.
We still have some time.
I'll take you to eat something.
Let's go.
Eat something.
Are you sick?
No, it's just a cold.
I'm fine.
Are you really not eating?
It's a gift for you.
For me?
Can I open it?
So you still remember me.
I love your gift.
Thank you.
I'm going to take this.
I've picked her up.
All right.
Listen to your parents after you get home.
Don't let this affect your studies.
Okay?
You don't need to tell me anymore.
What?
You don't need to tell me anymore
if you get a girlfriend.
Isn't this the bear plushie I got for you?
It's for you.
I wish you
happiness every day.
You must stay happy too.
I'm going now.
Bye.
Go now.
Little demon.
Forget it. I'll spare you this time.
Let's go home.
Mom already told your private tutor
to take the day off.
But I can't help you
if Mom and Dad scold you later.
If so…
How about this?
I'll buy you a crispy taro-crusted duck.
But…
All right now.
It's just heartbreak.
It's not a big deal.
I'll buy you the last several volumes
of the comic you read, okay?
How about this then?
I'll find someone to beat him up, okay?
Not that either?
Good girl. I'm here for you.
I'm here for you.
Don't cry, okay?
It's okay.
You're back.
What's wrong? Are you cold?
Put on something thicker.
Wash up and come to dinner.
Go and get changed first.
It will be fine.
I know you're heartbroken.
But I need to remind you
of the severity of the situation.
Do you know how worried Mom and Dad were?
All right, little demon.
At your age, you should study hard.
Do not get into puppy love.
Besides,
you stole an ID card
to buy a plane ticket.
What if you had encountered a bad guy?
Stop playing dead. Give me a nod.
There was no online boyfriend.
I just wanted to ask him
whether he remembered
our promise.