[English subtitles are available]
Ah.
Oh my god.
I actually moved in and started living with Zhu Xiaoyang.
What was I thinking?
[My Piggy Boss]
[Episode 7]
Come and have breakfast.
The nanny made it.
The nanny makes
breakfast and dinner on weekdays and three meals on weekends.
The recipes are also prepared
using fresh seasonal ingredients under the supervision of professional nutritionists,
taking into account both health and tastefulness.
This is awesome.
It's really great.
Xiaozhu, try this bun.
Why did Shuishui start living here too?
I can't see her spend thousands to live in
a house that's been soaked in water, right?
Thank you for taking me in, Mr. Zhu.
I can never repay your kindness.
How about this?
I'll rent you an apartment.
The company will pay for it.
A one-bedroom apartment.
The company's financial condition has just improved.
It's not good to add unnecessary expenses like this,
right, Mr. Zhu?
You might as well put this money into the electronic firecrackers industrial line
and let me, the product manager, have some work to do.
You are idle indeed.
Exactly.
My tendons are so stiff.
I guess it's because we spend too much time in front of the computer at work.
Is it possible that it's because we're getting old?
That's also one of the reasons.
Mr. Zhu, do you want to join us?
No.
You spend a lot of time in front of your computer too.
Pay attention to the condition of your neck and shoulders.
You're not young anymore.
It's time to start exercising.
I'm only 26. Thank you for your concern.
He's one year older than us.
His bones must be stiffer than ours.
Pretty impressive.
I was in a dance club in college.
That's it?
I can do it too.
Cramp!
What's wrong?
I'm having a butt cramp.
Call an ambulance!
I can't move.
Carry her away.
Ridiculous!
By the way, I forgot to tell you that
the family doctor would be here every weekend.
Mr. Zhu.
I'm afraid I can't live in this room anymore.
I'm not afraid of insects or heights.
I'm not afraid of getting myself dirty or tired.
But I'm afraid of ghosts.
You ran into a ghost in your room?
It kept following me in broad daylight,
but it disappeared whenever I turned around.
That was me.
Why were you following me?
I wanted to ask you
if we should continue our relationship.
We agreed to give it a try.
The relationship was neither real nor fake.
It was a true love's kiss after all.
If we pay too much attention on the goal, that would be too utilitarian.
So...
What do you think of me?
I don't know.
What about you?
Do you really want to date me
or did you simply do it to
solve the problem?
I just feel
happy and relaxed
when I'm with you.
Maybe it's because you know my secret.
Or it's simply because I'm with you.
What about you?
How do you feel
when you're with me?
It feels like
working.
I didn't mean that.
It's just every time I'm with you,
I feel like it's an order from Mrs. Zhu.
Wait.
You mean
you like me?
Since we can't explain it clearly,
we'll know after we give it a try.
So he confessed his love to you?
Kind of.
Did you say yes?
Well, it might not be up to me.
[CEO Office]
Assistant Yang.
What?
What do you mean what?
[CEO Office]
We'll have a meeting in 10 minutes.
Okay, got it.
Why is he still calling you "Assistant"?
It seems you two are even more aloof than before.
But every time he calls me by my full name,
nothing good happens.
He can give you a nickname.
For example, Piggy.
I think this name suits him better.
You're right.
I see.
It's inappropriate to disclose office romance.
Otherwise, it'll be hard to manage.
Really?
It's more exciting to have a secret relationship.
For example, a glance during a meeting,
a kiss in the pantry,
or when you're on a business trip...
Enough. Stop it.
Why did he still turn into a pig?
Was it his problem or mine?
Or was it because of that alien pig?
Yang Xiaozhu.
Yes.
Our only chance to save the company
is this 448 patent investigation hearing.
Go get ready.
We'll go to Huacheng next Monday.
Okay, I'll book the flight and hotel right away.
Mr. Zhu will be flying business class,
and I'll be flying economy class.
Mr. Zhu, we are in the company.
You really can't do this.
Upgrade your ticket to first class too.
You have my special approval.
I don't think it's a good idea
to favor me so blatantly.
We'll be flying across time zones.
Without you by my side,
I'm worried things may go wrong.
There'll be an industry banquet after that.
Remember to bring a gown.
Welcome to take this flight.
Why is it economy class?
Sorry, Mr. Zhu.
I booked the wrong tickets.
Please take your seats.
Do not block the aisle and prevent other passengers from boarding.
How could you make such a stupid mistake?
Everyone in economy class can be seen clearly.
What should I do?
You want me to turn into a pig in public?
How am I supposed to explain that?
You want me to say I'm a magician?
It's all my fault.
Stop yelling.
Do you want everyone on the plane to hear it?
It can't be helped.
And I don't care.
I'm sorry.
Are you really asleep, or pretending to be?
Out of sight, out of mind.
We have plenty of time.
Let's think of a solution.
I'm only a pig. Don't count on me.
Well, I'm a human who even booked wrong flight tickets.
You shouldn't have counted me to book the flight tickets.
Aren't you the assistant to CEO?
Aren't I the CEO?
Mr. Zhu.