[Always My General]
[Episode 16]
[Palace Corridor]
Your Highness,
the wedding ceremony is ready to begin.
Please welcome the Crown Princess in.
All of you may leave now.
Xue Shisan's hand is made for wielding a sword,
with calluses on her palm and purlicues.
Only you would be so naive
to think you could fool me like this.
What are you doing?
This is
a hairpin for your hair.
If you want to kill me, just do it.
I thought we were sisters,
but you're the one who has deceived me the most.
Sister,
let me explain.
Don't call me "sister"!
You don't deserve to be my sister.
Do you think I didn't know what you've been doing?
I've been watching you in secret.
I marked the commander's tally with fluorescent ink.
Your actions have been exposed.
Tell me,
who's pulling the strings behind you?
The Grand General of Southern Yue,
Shang Kefeng.
So you were the first mole
he planted in Northern Zhao?
So our first encounter at Dengying Tower
was part of your scheme.
Is that true or not?
True.
Shang Kefeng kept you around me
just to keep an eye on everything I do.
Is that true or not?
True.
So you made me think we were close sisters
to earn my trust,
only to be ready to take me down at any moment.
Is that true or not?
No!
I genuinely see you as my sister,
and I never intended to harm you.
It's just that we're on opposite sides,
each serving our own masters.
Enough!
Give me the commander's tally,
and all our past grievances will be forgotten.
Alright.
Sister,
Si won't let you down this time.
I'll ask for your forgiveness in the next life.
Pass my command!
Close the palace gates and assemble the guards.
Capture Xue Shisan!
Where do you think you can run?
Your parents' lives
are in my hands now,
and you still dare to betray me?
Don't you even worry about what will happen to them?
Trying to escape?
[Yongming Gate]
[Yaozhou City Gate]
Shisan.
Xu Hanzhi?
When I saw that the bride's figure wasn't you,
I thought,
could this be part of your plan?
Sure enough,
I found you in the back room,
so I just brought you out first.
Where's Si?
Isn't this also your plan?
Oh no,
Si is in danger.
We need to save her.
This maid
attempted to assassinate the new king in the palace,
and has been executed.
Her body will be hung at the city gates for three days
as a warning to others.
[Yongming Gate]
Si.
Shisan.
Si!
I'm going to kill Shang Kefeng!
I'm going to kill him!
If we return now,
we'll definitely die.
The city is swarming with Shang Kefeng's men,
and Si's death will have been for nothing.
But I can't allow her die
and still suffer such humiliation.
Si.
She's my sister.
She's my sister!
[Yongming Gate]
Si.
Are you alright?
Are you hurt?
Sister.
I'm going to reunite with my family.
Where are you going?
Could you please stay?
All this time,
I've always thought of you as my own sister.
I know.
So,
you must take good care of yourself.
Otherwise, I'll worry about you.
Also,
remember that you're a girl too.
So whatever you do,
don't push yourself too hard.
If there's...
a boy you like,
remember to tell me
secretly in your dreams,
and I'll help you out.
Please don't go.
Please don't leave me.
Well, I'm leaving then.
Don't leave me.
Si!
Please don't go!
Did you have a dream?
This was found
in the cloth bag that Si prepared for you.
May this letter serve as my presence.
By the time you read this,
I might already be gone.
We met at Dengying Tower,
but our fate was destined
long before that.
While you were leading the Jet Black Armored Cavalry outside Yaozhou City,
fighting fiercely against the Southern Yue Cavalry,
[Si]
I had already been arranged by Shang Kefeng
to infiltrate Dengying Tower.
Is my name
Si?
I was the first mole Shang Kefeng
Let me try.
planted in Northern Zhao.
Like this.
Before I reached the Northern Border,
I thought I could do anything, no matter the consequences,
as long as it could get my father out of prison,
until I met you.
In others' eyes,
I was nothing but a slave,
a servant, or a pawn.
Only you treated me like family.
Shisan?
I have no regrets...
Why are you called Shisan?
serving you, even in death.
Sister, does it look good?
It looks great.
What is this?
Chicken wings.
No, no.
It's Phoenix.
Right,
it's called Phoenix...
Phoenix Nirvana?
Yes!
Phoenix Nirvana.
Shisan,
it's okay now.
I'll always be here with you.
Shisan.
Your hair...