[Always My General]
[Episode 22]
Shang Kefeng's guards
were originally
expanded from my garrison troops.
But
now the commanders of each battalion
have all been replaced by his trusted men from Southern Yue.
I have already marked
the defensive positions for you.
Although the Xiqiang Wolfguard troops are formidable,
if we want to defeat them,
it will inevitably be a fierce battle.
May Shisan's operation tomorrow
goes smoothly.
Otherwise,
this will be our last time
seeing this palace's
magnificent splendor.
Man proposes,
Heaven disposes.
Your Highness,
Shang Kefeng's men are coming to kill us.
It seems Xue Shisan is leading them.
Was her poison
not completely removed?
If you saw Xue Shisan attack
and still managed to return alive,
it proves she's already gone easy on us.
She's buying us time.
Han Qi.
You take my brother and leave through the back door first.
Ningde and I
will help divert the pursuers for you.
Yes.
Hanzhi,
you can do it.
I'll be waiting for your good news.
Han Qi,
let's go.
Yes.
We meet again.
Vice General Xu,
Back then, you used the Red Flame Scarab to set fire to our camps.
You killed my three younger brothers.
Today,
I'm here to settle the score with you.
One got away.
What a pity.
You almost hit me by mistake.
The body wasn't found.
What makes you say
Xu Hanzhi is dead?
I used
a heavy bow.
Any living creature hit by the arrow
has no chance of survival.
Enough.
Anyway, I
had someone apply poison to the arrowheads in advance.
As long as there's
even a small wound on the body,
he has absolutely no chance of survival.
After tonight,
no one will be able to shake my reign.
Xu Hanzhi.
You must not come to any harm.
Aren't you tired of holding it up like this?
As long as you like it,
I'm willing to hold it forever.
The lanterns here are so beautiful.
♫Climb the city tower and look at the vast land♫
If only time could stop here.
I'm afraid I won't be able to see
♫Yet why sigh by the railing?♫
such beautiful lanterns again.
Why do you say that?
♫From youthful battles to now, hair frosted with gray♫
I'm just saying.
♫Though ruling the world, it's hard to hold her once more♫
Here.
Have a bite.
Is it good?
♫The northern wind chills to the bone♫
Delicious.
♫This night, snow blankets the shoulders♫
Shisan,
no matter what happens,
♫Iron hooves shatter golden armor♫
don't leave me behind.
♫Banners flutter fiercely in the wind♫
Got it.
♫A bright moon reflects spilled blood♫
♫Three decades of relentless battles♫
♫Now no one remains by my side♫
♫What use is reclaiming the land?♫
Let's go ahead and release the blessing lanterns.
♫Unfulfilled and incomplete♫
♫A sudden pipa echoes beyond the city walls♫
♫A vision of you gently plucking the strings♫
-I hope he...
-I hope she...
♫Playing a melody♫
-Lives the rest of his life in peace and happiness.
-Lives the rest of her life in peace and happiness.
♫Until tears run dry and hearts break apart♫
What wish did you make?
If you tell your wish, it won't come true.
But if you don't say it,
how will the other person know?
Then I'll tell you
what my wish is.
♫The northern wind chills to the bone♫
♫This night, snow blankets the shoulders♫
♫Iron hooves shatter golden armor♫
♫Banners flutter fiercely in the wind♫
You're very lucky.
Half an inch more
and the arrow would have pierced your vital point.
This isn't luck.
It's understanding.
This copper coin
was chosen from the first salary I received
after joining the Jet Black Armored Cavalry.
Every captain in the Jet Black Armored Cavalry
chooses a copper coin
and places it over their heart.
This method
was thought up by Shisan
before we deliberately got captured
and entered the military camp
during the battle in Northern Zhao.
What?
To create the illusion of infighting?
To infiltrate the enemy,
implicating each other to gain trust
is unavoidable.
However,
I trust Shisan.
You trust Shisan,
and you should trust me too.
Your Highness,
Shisan has sent a message asking us to start the operation.
Xu Hanzhi.
Han Qi.
You lead the border troops to block the passage,
contain the imperial guards,
and protect the inner palace.
Ningde.
The Eldest Prince.
You lead the local troops and Xiqiang Wolfguard
to directly enter the inner court,
protect the court officials,
and execute the traitors.
I humbly
congratulate Your Majesty on ascending the throne.
May Your Majesty
live forever
and ever,
for countless ages to come!
I, Princess Ningde,
wish Your Majesty
eternal reign
and everlasting prosperity for all people.
Everyone is in position as planned,
except for the Eldest Prince.
However,
the inner court of the royal city is under our control.
There won't be any chaos.
Brother Hanzhi will enter the palace soon.
We only need to delay for a moment.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Should I
address you as
Queen Xue
or General Zhou?
Whatever Your Majesty wishes me to be,
that is what I shall become.
From the Northern Border
to Yaozhou,
from
Dengying Tower
to this throne,
I want to ask you,
where have your scars gone?
The scars have always been in my heart,
but now the scars in my heart are gone,
so the scars on my face have disappeared as well.
Then besides scars, what else is in your heart?
What else is there?
Betrayal,
revenge,
foolishness,
and death.
Am I right?
You're quite familiar with the taste of death, aren't you?
Indeed,
I witnessed with my own eyes from a young age
my parents slain by treasonous guards who betrayed their master and nation.
How could I ever forget the taste of death?
I also witnessed with my own eyes
my brothers-in-arms from the Jet Black Armored Cavalry, who fought alongside me,
their blood spilling in the fortified city.
How could I ever forget the taste of death?
Now, with constant conflicts throughout the land
and people suffering immensely,
how could I ever forget the taste of death?
Everyone is here.
What can you do to me?
I am the king of Northern Zhao.
I am the ruler of three thousand li in the north.
And you...
You are the queen of Northern Zhao.
Southern Yue.
Western Rong.
You betrayed me.
You ruined my carefully planned imperial map.
You fell in love with Xu Hanzhi.
You must die.
I, General Yunhui,
Zhou Chu,
now protect the country and punish
the traitor Shang Kefeng.
Wait!
That's not right.
He is not Shang Kefeng.