[English subtitles are available]
♫I'm fascinated by your every move♫
[Miss Lucky Go!]
[Episode 4]
Zhong Wei, answer this question.
Sir, Zhong Wei has asked for a leave.
Okay.
Zhao Gu, answer this question.
In terms of the transportation problem...
I've heard that Zhong Wei
is seriously ill this time.
He can't even get off the bed.
He even needs two people to help him to go to the toilet.
It's just an allergy.
He's not that seriously ill.
A boy from a rich family like him is delicate.
He could even have a concussion after sneezing.
Chen Miren,
you've become the foe of girls
all over the school who killed their husband this time.
Thank you.
The chain is broken again?
Yes.
It's an old problem.
How did you know?
I know everything about you.
What did you say?
Nothing.
What is this?
Someone gave it to me.
Why don't you open it and read it?
No.
I'm not interested in her.
I won't waste the time.
Well...
There were no books on this seat.
There were also no other signs showing that
someone had occupied this seat.
So, theoretically,
I've found this seat first.
If you want to tell me
you've occupied this seat
for your classmate or girlfriend,
I'm sorry
but I won't give in.
I wanted to tell you that
you dropped something.
Thank you.
Besides, I don't have a girlfriend.
[Administration Management]
[Shi Hou]
You are Shi Hou?
You know me?
You're the top student who ranks first in the graduate school
of the Business Administration Department.
I've read all the five papers you published.
I'm not that excellent.
If you have time,
I would like to ask you something
about the postgraduate entrance examination.
Zhao Gu, you're just a freshman.
I just want to get well prepared.
So, do you have time?
Senior Shi Hou.
That's impossible.
The props for school activities
are all kept here, aren't they?
I found it.
Chen Miren.
I think you're really crazy.
Now that Zhong Wei has deleted the video,
we'll have nothing to do with each other.
Isn't this the result you want?
What's there to be sad about?
Chen Miren!
Huang Xiaoyue, do you want to die?
You don't sleep in the middle of the night,
and you came to the grove instead?
If I had not stayed up till the middle of the night
and come to the grove,
would I have seen you indulge in
your imagination in front of the school hunk's poster
in the middle of the night?
This is the first work in my life
which is shown to the public.
I merely took it back so as to keep it as a memento.
Chen Miren.
I advise you not to overestimate yourself.
For you and me, the shcool punk
and the campus belle
can only be observed from afar and can't be trifled with.
You should learn from me.
Just admire them.
Don't have any indecent thoughts.
Otherwise, you'll be the only one who gets hurt.
So, you came to the grove to wait for Xu Miaomiao?
Huang Xiaoyue, you're a pervert!
You are the pervert!
This is an important workplace for me.
The grove is an important source of gossip.
What do you know?
Do you think if Xu Miaomiao has a date,
she would come to the grove?
You're right.
For a beauty like Xu Miaomiao,
it's a bit inappropriate to go into the grove.
The grove is only suitable for ordinary students,
such as you, me, Bao Jiaguo and...
Zhao Gu!
What a coincidence.
Are they your classmates?
Why didn't you say hello?
We're not quite close.
Wait.
Why did we run away?
I have a conflict with Zhao Gu.
It's too embarrassing to meet her.
Why are you embarrassed?
They should be the ones who feel embarrassed.
When this top student is in love,
she's so wild.
Huang Xiaoyue,
if you dare to tell others
about what happened tonight, which might implicate me,
you'll be doomed.
This is against my professional ethics.
You want to bribe me for such big gossip news?
Give me two boxes of milk.
One box.
So stingy.
Hold it for me.
[Zhengze]
Have you got to the dorm?
Yes.
Thank you for buying me milk tea.
Why did you bring it back?
Well...
It's the first work in my life which is shown to the public.
I've brought it back so as to keep is as a memento.
You might as well sell it on Goofish.
Maybe you can sell it at a good price.
Good idea. I'll post the sales information at once.
I was merely saying it. You take it seriously?
I knew it.
It's my first work, and is very memorable.
I should keep it.
Chen Miren.
You can put it in the dorm,
but can you not put Zhong Wei's face towards me?
I feel uncomfortable.
Miaomiao.
If someone comes to see you every day,
you think he's annoying,
but if he doesn't come to see you,
you would be a little disappointed.
What do you think is the reason?
Are you talking about Huang Xiaoyue?
Of course not.
Almost like that.
It must be because you like him.
Let me tell you.
When I was in high school,
a boy liked me,
and he followed me for three years.
He went wherever I went.
He bought me water, milk tea and snacks.
He even brought me a pillow as I would sleep in class.
What happened later?
Was there a story?
Nothing happened after that.
He wasn't admitted to Hanhai University. I wasn't disappointed, either.
Because I didn't like him.
It's all right that he's gone.
Miaomiao, hearing what you said,
why do I feel that you're a little bad?
It seems I'm a bad girl.
But I can afford to be bad.
I see.
[Interview Notice from Heng Chang]
Miao.
Heng Chang sent me an interview notice.
Really?
Congratulations, future design master.
But it says
I need to bring my own design works.
Do you have one?
No, I don't.
But I must have one.
[Chen Miren]
She really doesn't contact me.
Zhong Wei, the award for the Campus Ambassador has been issued.
Here you are.
You can have it.
Really?
Thank you so much.
To be honest,
I had been the seeded player of the school
table tennis team at elementary, junior and senior high schools.
You know the Golden Radish Cup, right?
I won the first prize for three years in a row.
This is a table tennis bat of Hong San Xi.
It's very precious.
I'm glad you like it.
Zhong Wei, I've made the whole process of how you were chosen
into a photo album, and have sent it to the class chat group.
This is the first group activity of our class.
It is very memorable.
This time, you were chosen,
and it was all thanks to Chen Miren.
I can still be selected without her.
Hello?
Zhong Wei, I have a piece of good news
and a piece of bad news.
Which one do you want to hear first?
Whatever.
The good news is that
the project of Self-heating Companion Cats
has been approved in the company's assessment meeting.
What about the bad news?
The company cut our budget.
They only allowed us to make 20,000 pieces.
20,000 pieces?
For this, it even took me a long time to persuade
your father to agree.
I've contacted the factory.
I'm leaving for Linzhou tomorrow.
I'll make the action figures first.
Then you should go.
You have no idea how stingy your father is.
I've applied for a travel allowance,
but it's not even enough to cover the cost of taking a business car.
Come pick me up at school tomorrow.
I'll go, too.
You'll go, too?
Why are you going?
To shoot a promotional video.
Well...
You always ask others to give you a ride.
Why are you more stingy than your father?
Luo Si, you're back.
Fang Mao's mother is sick.
He can't take care of her alone.
So...
You're such a good girlfriend.
Our dorm wasn't checked, right?
Don't worry. We're here.
Luo Si, you're back.
Yes.
Where is Chen Miren?
She has gone to Linzhou.
Why?
She has gone there to make action figures.
She left early in the morning.
Have you seen the cotton pads on my desk?
Someone is a thief.
Why are you looking at me?
My memory is so bad.
I must have used it.
They're all here.
What are you talking about?
Hello, is that Huateng Processing Factory?
Hello.
I want you to customize and produce a batch of action figures.
How many pieces do you want to make?
100 pieces.
Why did he hang up?
We've arrived at Linzhou Processing Industrial Park.
Move them over there. Yes.
Hurry up.
Hurry up. Move them over there.
Yes. Move faster.
Hello.
Yes.
I want to customize and produce this batch of action figures.
You should ask other factories.
Thank you.
Alright. Hurry up.
Be quick!
Hurry up. Hurry up.
We can produce them.
Really?
The processing fee will be 20 times higher.
Twenty times?
I'm sorry.
Your quantity is too small.
We can't accept your order.
[Linzhou Hongyang Toy Processing Factory]
Your purpose of coming here this time
is to make 20,000 pieces?
Any problem?
No.
But every time when Heng Chang gave an order,
there were at least 500,000 pieces,
or there were more than 10,000,000 pieces at most.
There are only 20,000 pieces this time.
This is not the style of Heng Chang.
It's a limited edition this time.
Limited edition?
Yes, there will be only 20,000 pieces sold in the world.
I understand.
But this time, for the self-heating material,
both its casting and moulding techniques are different.
We have no experience.
You don't need to worry about that.
We've done a technical research.
Just ask our engineers to be cooperative.
To be honest,
recently, Heng Chang
has given us an order
of five million pieces.
We've been very busy lately.
An order of five million pieces.
Whose project? Yu Dawei's?
Yes.
Ye.
I don't think I've introduced the one who sits next to me.
[Business License]
Who is this?
This is
[Business License]
Mr. Zhong Wei, one of the executives in Heng Chang.
He's the only son
of Zhong Changguo, the old Mr. Zhong.
Mr. Qi, why didn't you tell me earlier?
Mr. Zhong.
Hello.
Mr. Ye, to be honest,
actually,
I came up with the idea of companion cats.
My dad thinks it's great.
The series of companion cats
has won the first place
in our company's design contest.
And it got the highest score in history.
My dad also said that
[Business License]
this series of companion cats
would probably become the dark horse
of the next Asia-Pacific Trendy Action Figures Exhibition.
Mr. Ye,
do you think you can produce 20,000 pieces
of this companion cat?
Yes, we can.
Yes, we can. Don't worry.
We can surely produce them.
Okay, Ye.
Take this file
and study it first.
Okay.
We'll come here tomorrow.
Let's go, Mr. Zhong.
Thank you, Mr. Ye.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Bye, Mr. Zhong.
Bye.
Don't worry.
[Linzhou Huapeng Toy Factory Co., Ltd.]
I had to count on you at the critical moment.
I just want to shoot a video on a special subject.
Why am I still responsible for your business negotiation?
At this time,
you still have the mood to shoot a video on a special subject?
The sales volume of the companion cats was not good this time,
so the budget of our team
has been cut by 60%.
Otherwise, they wouldn't have allowed us to make only 20,000 pieces.
How about this?
I'll talk to my dad
and ask him to give you some money.
Really?
You finally figured it out, my brother.
I'll go to Ye now
and ask him to make another 500,000 pieces.
By the way...
What's wrong this time?
It suddenly occurred to me that
my dad hadn't given me the pocket money yet.
I have something to do. I have to go.
Didn't we agree to
eat braised goose together?
It's something you must eat in Linzhou.
Go by yourself.
[Linzhou Qiyuan Processing Factory]
I've made it clear to you.
Your quantity is too small.
We can't accept your order.
Mr. Wang.
Be careful. Be careful.
I've asked all the factories nearby.
You are my last hope.
I've thought about it.
If you can't make 100 pieces, just make 500 pieces.
Be careful.
Hurry up.
1,000 pieces.
I can't add more.
That's all the money I have.
Are you kidding me?
Let me tell you again.
The minimum quantity of an order in our factory is 10,000 pieces.
You should ask others about it.
Mr. Wang.
Maybe my design will become popular in the future.
Then I may ask you to produce one million pieces.
It can help you make money.
Look. Look.
If you keep pestering me,
I'll ask the security guards to come here.
[Only 17 passengers are permitted]
Zhong Wei.
Are you hungry?
Come on. Have some tea.
Be careful. It's hot.
Hello.
Our restaurant is newly opened today.
You can drink the beer for free.
I don't drink.
Go on drinking.
Sir!
Serve the wine.
My restaurant has just been newly opened today.
If you go on drinking, it might go bankrupt.
Don't say something so discouraging.
How can you see a rainbow without experiencing a storm?
In the journey of life,
it's normal to meet some difficulties.
Don't be discouraged.
Okay.
Five more bottles.
Okay, Miss.
Do you know
why I even understand
such a profound principle?
Then I should
start with the winter when I was born.
Fast forward.
So I swore that
I must join Heng Chang,
and become the best
action figure designer in our country and in the world.
Do you know Heng Chang?
Heng Chang is the best
action figure company in the world.
Do you know which is the best action figure
company in the world?
It's...
Heng Chang.
How do you know?
Go ahead.
It's surprising that you don't allow me to join Heng Chang.
If you don't allow me to join Heng Chang,
how can I become a designer?
God, why?
Alright, alright. Stop drinking.
You're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
Zhong Wei.
Take a look.
Is my design that bad?
Why do you forbid me to join Heng Chang?
The style is unique and the details are exquisite.
[Line Drawing]
It's full of strong expressiveness both internally and externally.
I haven't seen such
vivid and inspirational design for a long time.
So you allow me to join Heng Chang?
Just tell me.
Tell me.
Do you allow me to join Heng Chang?
Yes, yes, yes. I allow you to join it.
It's useless to let me join it.
Mr. Wang refused to make 1,000 pieces for me.
Why is it so hard?
Or
is it actually very difficult to realize a dream?
It's difficult to realize a dream.
That's what makes realizing the dream worthwhile.
That makes sense.
Sir, another 20 bottles.
No, sir.
Check, please.
Okay.
Come on.
What's going on?
Chen Miren, we've arrived.
Alright. Time to sleep.
♫I don't need to doubt that I've fallen completely♫
♫I'd imagine it was you while watching short videos♫
♫I talk about you frequently♫
♫It's enough to prove that it's you♫
♫I don't need to doubt that I've fallen completely♫
♫I didn't sleep well, which indicated that there was a problem♫
♫Even if my eyes blur, as long as I think of you♫
Zhong Wei, are you asleep?
I've brought you braised goose.
♫I can rest assured and let my dream continue♫
Zhong Wei.
I'm sleeping.
You're sleeping?
Why did you talk if you were sleeping?
♫You can't feel the heartbeat outside the mobile phone♫
♫I've revised the message again and again, being afraid that it was not good enough♫
♫I'm worried that I'll lose my manners, but I still want to bother you♫
♫This feeling is amazing♫
♫The sun always comes after the rain♫
♫Please believe that there will be a rainbow♫
Chen Miren, get down!
No!
♫A good man won't let the woman he loves♫
♫Get hurt♫
Chen Miren.
Chen Miren, if you don't come down,
I'll let you know
what real injury is after we go back later.
Go back?
Where should I go?
Go home?
♫Go home♫
♫I need...♫
-Good! -Come on!
♫You♫
Sing a song.
Sing one more song.
See you next time.
Don't go.
I love you.
Chen Miren, why are you so heavy?
And your suitcase, too.
What's inside your suitcase? A lead ball?
Zhong Wei.
You're so good.
Now you know I'm good.
Zhong Wei.
What?
Let's go.
I'm here to clean the room.
I'm sorry. I thought you had checked out.
Sorry.
♫We're going to be together forever♫
♫What I like is your smile♫
Sleep a little longer.
♫You shine on my rainy day♫
♫What I like is being hugged by you♫
♫Warm and subtle♫
♫What I like is the corner of your skirt♫
♫All the four seasons are surrounded by spring♫
♫What I like is being needed by you♫
♫Plant a mark♫
[Linzhou Huateng Toy Factory Co., Ltd.]
Actually, I can do it myself.
Mr. Zhong, welcome.
Mr. Wang.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Why are you here again?
Security guards!
Mr. Wang, she's my...
Classmate.
Not only that.
I understand.
Please have a seat.
Mr. Zhong.
I've heard that you came there this time
in order to shoot a video on a special subject.
My fans are very curious
about the production process of this action figure,
so I plan to shoot a video on this subject
so as to introduce it to them.
It's our honor that you've decided to
introduce our company.
I hope that
as a blogger who owns millions of fans,
you can help to promote our company more.
Okay.
Mr. Wang,
There's another favor I want to ask you to do.
Please say it.
My classmate
has a work,
and wants you to produce it.
Last time, I already told her that
the miniumu quantity of an order in our factory is 10,000 pieces.
How about this, Mr. Zhong?
This time, for the sake of you,
I'll make an exception for her and produce 8,000 pieces.
1,000 pieces.
Mr. Zhong, aren't you making things difficult for me?
I won't make things difficult for you.
I'll shoot the video if you can do this.
I won't shoot the video if you can't.
Let's go.
No. Wait.
I'll make 1,000 pieces.
20% off for the cost of processing.
Chen Miren, don't go too far.
Let's go.
Mr. Wang, I'm just kidding.
Just make 1,000 pieces.
With this work,
as an undiscovered talent,
I will finally shine.
If Heng Chang really hires me,
and then I become a famous
designer overnight,
do you think I should still go to school?
If I drop out of college, I won't have a diploma.
If I continue to go to school, Advanced Mathematics is too difficult.
Forget it. I'll quit school.
Chen Miren.
Go to bed early.
You'll have everything in your dreams.
Zhong Wei, don't you trust me?
If I become famous,
don't cry and beg to interview me.
I trust you.
We've been waiting for an hour.
Is there no bus?
Chen Miren, look.
There's a meteor! Make a wish!
Meteor, please bless me to join Heng Chang.
I hope I won't fail the higher mathematics exam,
and Cao won't come to talk to me.
Besides...
Chen Miren.
You're too greedy.
Even the meteor can't carry all your wishes,
and it has run away.
Why didn't you make a wish?
I made a wish a long time ago.
If you make too many wishes, they won't come true.
There's a meteor! Make a wish!
Zhong Wei, what wish did you make?
My wish is that...
No, it won't come true if I tell you.
How narrow-minded.
So, what wish did you make?
My wish was that
I hope we can go to the same university,
major in the same subject,
and be in the same class.
♫The soil is fragrant in the countryside's road♫
♫There's dew on the petals, and a rainbow has formed over it♫
♫We look at each other and smile♫
♫He said he would dance with me with the passage of time♫
Let's go.
Zhong Wei, aren't you going back?
I still have something to do.
You can go back first.
♫We look at each other and smile♫
Tell me when you arrive.
Be careful.
♫He said he would dance with me with the passage of time♫
[Yellow Zone]
♫I felt uneasy at first♫
[No Standing]
♫Then I gradually walked into your heart♫
♫Originally, I was used to avoiding you♫
♫Now I'm holding your hand tightly♫
[No Standing]
Zhong Wei, my wish was that
I hope all Zhong Wei's wishes will come true.
♫It's him♫
♫Who has accepted my unpolished willfulness and sorrow♫
♫Who has brought me sweet spring and flowers♫
♫He's still there when I turn around♫
♫So this is the kindness after he saw through me♫
♫He used his warm hands♫
♫To melt my face which longs for being loved♫
♫I don't need to doubt that I've fallen completely♫