What do you like?
Food-wise.
I don't care much about food.
I just eat to live.
There must be something you like.
What is it?
Kimbap.
The kind I roll at home.
Store-bought's better, isn't it?
Then why'd you ask?
‘Cause I gotta report back.
So,
when you're in a relationship,
what type do you like?
It's been so long since I dated, I forget.
Have you even dated?
I have.
What about you, those rumors
with that actress were fake, right?
No. I'm popular.
Yeah, right, like that's possible.
I am popular.
Oh.
Here's one,
someone honest.
Someone who's there when you're happy,
and there when you're sad.
Does that even exist?
Why wouldn't it?
Just say you're sad when you're sad,
say you miss them when you miss them.
One little line is all it takes.
Guess that one little
line's harder than it sounds.
You haven't tried, right?
Dating.
I said I have.
Fine, fine.
I have!
What are you two doing?
Be quiet. Shh.
You've never dated, huh?