Zhejiang Culture and Arts Development Fund Project
Huzhou City
Literary and Artistic
Excellence Support Project
Gu Xiao, Ruan Qingping, Tang Feixian
Zhang Yanyan, Cheng Jin
Zhang Yanyan, Cheng Jinhui
Dai Jing, Tian Zijiao, Shen Yang
Dai Jing, Tian Zijiao, Shen Yang, Hu Haoxian
Wang Junhao, Yu Yilei, Dong Xingyan
Wang Junhao, Yu Yilei, Dong Xingyan, Ji Yumeng, Tong Xiaohu
Zhu Luning, Zhu Guanlin, Chen Shuang
Qing, this painting is quite good.
This starry sky is so beautiful.
Of course.
My daughter's work.
Look at this painting.
It can rival international masters.
This painting
was completed under
the guidance of my mentor, Zhong Tianshuo.
I would like to
thank him for all his help.
This shattered starry sky
has a particularly unique meaning.
Especially these two white light waves.
Do they have some special significance?
It represents hope.
It's also a kind of
protection that transcends reality.
So many people here.
It's quite lively.
This is an art exhibition.
A female boss has arrived.
Don't tell me we're about to witness some rich family drama.
Sunflower seeds and bottled water for sale in the front row!
Ready for the show!
Ms. Qi, what brings you here?
I'm here to tell Lu Qingqing.
You're suspected of plagiarizing
our contracted artist's work
'Guardian Under the Star Trail.'
This is a court summons
and copyright infringement notice.
That's nonsense!
How could Qingqing possibly plagiarize?
Everyone can see!
This painting was created by my daughter
stroke by stroke.
How could it possibly be plagiarism?
Yes.
Nonsense.
I've never even seen
your 'Guardian Under the Star Trail' painting.
Everything needs evidence.
Qingqing's painting
was created stroke by stroke
with all of us as witnesses.
Yes, exactly.
Right.
I have our company artist's draft here
created six months ago.
Whether it's the color, composition,
or the core elements,
they're highly similar to this piece of junk
in every way.
It's just a coincidence.
My painting
has my own ideas and story.
Everyone,
now you all see it, right?
We're fighting for our home turf,
we can't afford to lose!
What evidence do you have?
This can't be photoshopped, right?
Exactly.
You photoshopped this, didn't you?
Who are you? Who do you think you are?
Do you have any right to speak here?
Who am I?
I'm the unofficial spokesperson for Haizhu Village.
A social media influencer with over a million followers.
Come on, look at the camera.
Qingqing,
we're not afraid of her.
Qi Shuang.
I started creating this painting
seven years ago.
Every stroke was done by me personally.
To improve it,
a month ago,
I asked Mr. Zhong for some guidance.
How could I possibly plagiarize your company's painting?
So you've admitted
that this painting
was created by both of you.
Well, let me tell you.
Our company's contracted artist
is Mr. Zhong Tianshuo.
According to the contract,
anything he participates in creating
or provides guidance for
has its copyright owned by our company.
And before getting our company's authorization,
you used his creative ideas without permission.
This is infringement and plagiarism.
Qingqing.
Mr. Zhong,
what does this mean?
There's a problem with the contract.
Qi Shuang,
you deliberately set me up,
used me.
I didn't use you.
You signed the contract voluntarily.
We have a mutually beneficial relationship.
Qingqing,
I'm sorry.
And also,
do you all know?
This great artist Lu.
I've investigated her.
At her previous company,
she liked to snoop on her colleagues' work.
She hasn't changed this habit.
And also,
she brags everywhere,
claiming to be some art director.
But as far as I know,
at her previous company,
she was just a low-level employee serving tea,
not even an assistant.
This 'art director' title
is just self-proclaimed.
Isn't Qingqing a director in the city?
How could she be just a tea server?
Shut up!
So you're saying
she's been lying to all of us.
Don't talk nonsense.
How could Qingqing lie?
Exactly, how could she lie?
How could she lie? It's impossible.
I didn't.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here with you.
Lu Qingqing.
I suggest you be reasonable.
You can use your land as collateral for compensation.
We can settle this privately.
Otherwise,
just wait for a court summons.
I'll make sure you never
show your face in the art world again.
You can forget about painting for the rest of your life.
I believe in her.
She didn't plagiarize.
Whether she plagiarized or not,
the court will decide.
But right now,
you owe our company 5 million in copyright fees.
5 million.
Where would we get that much money?
You must be joking.
If you don't have the money,
use your land as collateral.
I'm not completely unreasonable.
I'll give you one day
to think it over.
Qingqing.
I'm sorry.
The sketch for that painting
was indeed drawn by me six months ago.
I never thought Qi Shuang would...
Qing.
You really plagiarized?
How could it be plagiarism?
What nonsense are you talking?
All of you, be quiet!
Listen to me.
None of you are allowed to gossip about this.
Plagiarism? No way.
Qingqing, come home with mom.
Get up. Get up. Get up.
Let's go home. Let's go home.
Get up. Make way.
Get up.
Our Qingqing is innocent.
Mom.
It's not a big deal.
When I was working outside,
I saw this kind of thing all the time.
There's nothing your daughter can't handle.
Silly girl.
I've known for a long time
that you're not an artistic director.
How long were you planning to lie to me?
The reason I let you move back home
was hoping you could find peace.
That's why I never called you out.
Then when
did you find out?
One time I missed you,
so I went to the city to see you.
I didn't tell you.
I'll be waiting for you downstairs at your company.
Qingqing.
Working overtime again?
This month's perfect attendance award is definitely yours.
Almost done.
Just need to finish this revision.
The office assistant is about to rise up!
I heard the director praised your edits.
Said they were very inspired.
Keep up the good work.
Maybe after grinding for 10 years,
you could become a director too.
Mom's heart at that moment
felt like it was being carved with a knife.
Hey, Qingqing.
Have you eaten?
Yes, I have.
What did you have?
I'm having dinner with colleagues. It's quite fancy.
How's your daughter doing?
You know very well.
Your daughter would never shortchange herself.
I'm asking you.
Your colleagues...
Are they treating you well?
Yes, they are.
Your daughter is so outstanding.
I have good news.
I've been promoted to senior director.
I got promoted.
Are you happy?
My Qingqing is now a senior director.
When will you come back?
To see me?
Mom.
My colleagues are calling for me.
I have to go now.
Qingqing.
Qing...
Project funded by Zhejiang Cultural and Art Development Foundation
Huzhou City Fine Arts Support Project
Cast
Yu Xichen - Wang Junhao
Lu Qingqing - Yu Yilei
Ding Susu - Ji Yumeng
Zhong Tianshuo - Dong Xingyan
Lu Yujing - Tong Xiaohu
Wang Xiulian - Zhao Wanlushan
Qi Shuang - Ding Yang
A K - Pan Yuanjia
Lin Yue - Wang Tianzhu
Zhu Wanqing - Wang Yanmin
Liang Shouyi - Shi Qiang
Yang Hao - Hu Haoxian
Young Liang Shouyi - Gan Shujie
Young Zhu Wanqing - Guo Li Ruoxi
Opera Actor - Wu Mengyan
Xiao Wang - Li Mubai
Aunt Cui - Zhang Lianfang
Widow Li - Yang Lan Shengjie
Aunt Liu - Liu Yishuo
Zhang Mouren - Zhang Jie
Manager Li - Yang Shu
Li Sanniang - Liu Shiyun
Village Chief - Zhang Jun
Little Qingqing - Xiao Taozi
A Mu - Yang Can
Colleague A
Colleague A - Yang Jinhan
Assistant A - Dong Wenqing
Assistant B - Yang Lu
Hooligan - Jin Junhui
A Chang - Fei Kaizhong
Manager Shan - Li Xuezhi
Xiao Chen - Zhou Liguo
Also Starring
Jia Qingchao, Song Zhizheng, Ma Shuichi, Mu Yan, Zhang Jingxue, Li Yujie
Zhang Xiaomei, Zhao Yiyi, Yang Nianen, Zhao Lechen, Zhao Yichen, Peng Yuze
Shen Bin, Hu Lili, Cheng Manli, Bai Junyang, Zhou Fei, Shen Zhexuan
Bai Xingxing, Li Rongrong, Ye Qichao, Bao Qiang, Ye Wentao, Zhang Qiuyun
Xu Xiang, Wang Hongchen, Liao Yingxi, Shen Long, Qin Weitian, Bao Mingchao
Crew
Executive Producer - Bai Jianhua
Producers: Hu Shuang, Gu Xiao
Hu Shuang, Gu Xiao
Producers:
Executive Producer: Gu Guirong
Production Team
Chief Producers: Gu Xiao, Ruan Qingping, Tang Feixian
Producers: Ruan Qinghua, Zhang Yanyan, Cheng Jinhui
Executive Producers: Wang Tianzhu, Wang Xiaoyu
Production Manager: Chen Qiang
Coordinator: Han Han
On-site Producer: Zhang Yuewei
Logistics Producer: Wang Xiaoyu
External Relations Producers: Zhang Guanglei, Fan Chengwei, Wei Zhidong
Directing Team
Director: Li Liming
Co-Directors: Huang Rongjun, Chen Shuang
Screenwriters: Zhu Luning, Zhu Guanlin, Chen Shuang
Screenwriter Assistant: Cai Yining
Executive Director: Zhang Jie
Script Supervisor: Che Keyan
Behind-the-Scenes: Zong Gangqing
Still Photography: Li Zhenbang
Casting Team
Jisiyuan Casting
Casting Director: Zheng Haoyu
Actors Coordinator: A Zhuang, Yin Ming
Assistant Director for Actors: Han Jian
Photography Team
Directors of Photography: Guo Lei, Bai Jianfeng
Cinematographer: Li Luyao
Photography Assistants: Wang Xin, Cao Fuxin
Camera Operators: Tang Chuan, Ren Zhenghui
Aerial Photography Team
Aerial Photographers: He Lu, Wang Jie, Feng Dong
Liu An
Lighting Team
Lighting Director: Tian Bowen
Lighting Assistants: Tang Jiaqi, Sun Bingguan, Wang Changqiang
Jin Weixiang, Feng Weiquan
Art Department
Art Director: Li Zhiqiang
Artist: Li Zhishuai
Props Manager: Cao Huihui
Props: Li Tongzhu, Wang Limin, Tao Fengyu
Li Yujie, Ning Mingjing
Styling Team
Styling Director: Yang Yang
Costume Designer: Xu Yanfang
Hair and Makeup Artists: Li Wen, Cai Chuanping
On-set Hair and Makeup Lead: Li Jing
On-set Hair and Makeup: Ren Jiale, Lu Mengqi
Makeup Artist: Xiang Sini
Costume Assistants: Cao Hong, Yin Dan
Sound Team
Sound Director: Zhang Dongwei
Sound Recordist: Bian Yun
Transportation Team
Transportation Manager: Xu Lidong
Drivers: Li Yan, Feng Zhaoyang, Zhang Zhilong
Li Yunlong, Liang Dazhang, Wang Kai
Song Zhizheng, Wang Dongwei, Ma Shuichi
Wang Bo, Wang Dongping, Zhang Guanglei
Fan Chengwei  Wei Zhidong
Stage Crew
Stage Managers: Chen Jiayuan, Zhang Haojie, Jia Gaofeng
Jia Qingchao, Chen Fengcheng, Xie Wanlong
Actor Assistants Team
Actor Assistants: Zuo Ling, An Xinran, Jin Junhui
Editing Team
Editing Director: Mei Di
Editor: Cui Yan
DIT: Wang Gang
Post-Production
Beijing Lightning Film and TV Co., Ltd.
Creative Director: Huang Rongjun
Production Coordinator: Yang Hong
Editors: Yi Kejun, Yang Haiyang, Shi Bin
Zhao Yinghua
Colorists: Nie Yaxiong, Ping Yongpei
Graphic Designers: Yang Hong, Xu Zhinuo
Packaging Compositor: Han Jinting
Audio Production
Beijing Lecheng Yisheng Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Audio Director: Ding Liang
Audio Supervisor: Huang Bin
Dialogue Editor: Zhang Changshuai
Motion Effects Editor: Huang Bin
Foley Artist: Meng Dexiao
Music Design
Ding Liang
Music Editor: Li Yanmei
Sound Mixer: Huang Bin
Licensed Music Provider: Quduoduo
Visual Effects Production
Beijing Dingfeng Film and Media Co., Ltd.
VFX Director: Chen Bin
Project Director: Zhang Hongde
VFX Supervisor: Jia Ping
Compositing Supervisor: Zhang Lili
Compositing Team: Zhang Jinglu, Xuan Lei, Gao Tian
Zhang Zhiwei, Wu Hao, Deng Changming
3D Team: Han Leipeng, Yu Chunlong
Opening Theme
"Will You Remember Me"
Performed by Wang Yuzhou (Leto)
Lyrics by Deng Mu
Music by Yang Yuting
Producer: Jin Hua
Arrangement by Shi Songhao
He: Qiao Juncheng
Guitar: Qiao Juncheng
Backing Vocals: Zhou Xian
Recording Engineer: Ming Hanwen (Koppo)
Mixing Engineer: Liu Yanhong
Executive Producer: Han Bing
Production Coordinator: He He
Distributor: Pan Jialin
Planner: Jin Hua
Planning
Promotion: Ji Zhenyu, He He, Shu Shu
Cheng Chen
Production Company: Jike Banyin
OP/SP: Beijing Huashu Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Ending Theme
"Flowers Flying Under the Eaves"
Lyrics by Shi'er Xiong
Music by Qi Xiuyuan
Performed by Wang Yuzhou (Leto)
Producer He He
Arranged by Qiu Muyang
Guitar by Wu Yutao
Vocals by Zhou Xian
Backing Vocals by Zhou Xian
Sound Mixer Liu Yanhong
Mastering by Liu Yanhong
Project Coordinator He He
Producer Pan Haocheng
OP/SP Beijing Huashu Culture Media Co., Ltd & Jike Banyin
Insert Song
"Deep Mountain"
Lyrics by Zhou Ren
Music by Muxia
Performed by Wang Yuzhou (Leto)
Producers Jin Hua, Chen Lin (Len)
Chen Lin (Len)
Arranged by Chen Lin (Len)
Guitar by Wu Yutao
Feng Yini, Qiao Juncheng
Backing Vocals by Feng Yini, Qiao Juncheng
Chorus Design by Wang Daxiang
Coloratura Soprano Wang Hong
Sound Mixer Liu Yanhong
Mastering by Liu Yanhong
Project Coordinator Cheng Guang
Producer Pan Haocheng
OP/SP Beijing Huashu Culture Media Co., Ltd & Jike Banyin
Cooperative Partners
Agricultural Bank of China Limited, Huzhou Branch
Meixin Group Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang Hongying Group Co., Ltd.
Huzhou South Taihu New District Publicity Center
Huzhou Transportation Investment Group Co., Ltd.
Supporting Units
Huzhou Film and Television Artists Association
Huzhou Wang Yipinzhai Brush Shop Co., Ltd.
Huzhou Xiangshun Industry and Trade Co., Ltd.
Huzhou Chengxi Culture and Art Co., Ltd.
Huzhou Herun Automobile Co., Ltd.
Huzhou Guangcheng Leapmotor Center
Guidance Units
Publicity Department of CPC Huzhou Municipal Committee
Huzhou News Media Center
Publicity Department of CPC Anji County Committee, Huzhou
Huzhou South Taihu New District Publicity Center
Special Thanks
People's Government of Tianhuangping Town, Anji County, Huzhou
Yucun Tourism Resort Management Committee, Anji County, Huzhou
Lingfeng Street Office, People's Government of Anji County, Huzhou
People's Government of Shangshu Township, Anji County, Huzhou
Dalu Academy
Xiaoyin Banri Village
Anji Wuwai Hotel
Deep Blue Project · Deep Blue Park
Anji New Year's Day Resort
Dayucun Qinglai Collective Accommodation
Zhejiang Yuxiang Vocational and Technical College
Zhejiang Fenghui Bamboo and Wood Products Co., Ltd.
Anxin Jixian Agricultural Innovation Supermarket (Yucun Store)
Fuyungu Scenic Area
Fuqigu Valley
Meixin Wangneng Environment Co., Ltd.
Meixin Environmental Research Institute
Huzhou National Library Cultural and Creative Center
Huzhou Cultural Tourism Operation Group Co., Ltd.
Huzhou Culture Center
Huzhou Film and Television City
Nanshan South Cultural Creative Park
River of Time·Island Hotel
Zhou's Restaurant (Fisherman's Wharf Branch)
Huzhou Media 711 (Moon Plaza Branch)
Xinyuan Taihu Health City
Xinda Hospital
T Island Fusion Restaurant
Huzhou Caiju Commercial Management Co., Ltd.
China Energy Conservation·Taihu Premier
Huzhou Zhimo Art Training Co., Ltd.
Huzhou Calligraphers Association
Perfect Custom Photography Studio
Huzhou Baining Hotel
Production Units
Zhejiang Huzhou Zuozhou Culture Co., Ltd.
Huzhou Sanrenxing Audio-Visual Culture Co., Ltd.
Co-Production Units
Zhejiang Anji Hemei Yucun Tourism Scenic Area Development Co., Ltd.