(Gokou) I thought so at first
That's the most pleasant isn't it?
(Akari) Women's sex industry Paradise
I'm Fujisaki Akari, who works in-house there.
In addition to requests from users, the shop also includes
There are a variety of jobs available
I'm coming
(Miho Yagira) Come
(Akari) Movies, dramas, and online media.
Various interview requests
Not just the store manager or therapist, but I sometimes talk about it.
There are also users who will help with the interview.
(Door opening and closing sound)
(Door opening and closing sound) (Shop clerk) Welcome
Ah
- (Rabbit) Ah- (Akari) Rabbit...?
- (Rabbit) Akari-san? - (Akari) It's Akari
- (Rabbit) Nice to meet you- (Akari) Nice to meet you
Sorry for keeping you waiting
No no thank you for your cooperation
Oh, it's Tanabe
(Rabbit) Ah
(Tanabe) Thank you very much
please
This is Tanabe, a writer
It's Rabbit
Thank you for your cooperation today
(Rabbit) Please, please today, please
please
(Rabbit) Excuse me
(Akari Tanabe) Thank you
(Shop staff) Thank you for visiting us
(Rabbit) Ah, then please hot tea
(Shop clerk) I'm in a good mood
(Akari Rabbit) Ahhh... hahaha...
Basically, it's not OK, so please ask anything.
(Akari Tanabe) Thank you
Now let me get started
Right away, but first
What made me want to use Jofuu?
What was it?
I've been completely sexless with my husband for 10 years, from the age of 35.
So I asked my husband about how to use it
Did your husband say okay?
- (Rabbit) Reluctantly- (Tanabe) Ah...
My husband is a lawyer
I understand that sexlessness is disadvantageous in divorce lawsuits
Didn't you think it was better than being taken?
-(Rabbit)Hehehe... -(Tanabe) Ah, I see
I think it was great to meet the first therapist
I wonder if he was still around 25 at the time?
that…
I'm a newcomer, but I'll do my best, please
Ahaha
I'm relieved, I'm a new guy too
(2 people) Hehehe...
yes
(Rabbit) Feel the temperature of a man for the first time in 10 years
It's strange though
I remembered that I also had a temperature
(Rabbit) I was worried that I might not be a woman anymore
But I knew that day
I'm still a woman
Anyway, that was nice
Thank you
Thank you very much
I want to know more about Rabbit
The Rabbit's pleasantness
What Rabbit wants to do What Rabbit doesn't want
I want to know anything
Hmm...
So can I extend it?
- (Goku) Aha- (Rabbit)
Of course
Hehe...
(Two laughter)
The day from when you make a reservation at Rabbit to meeting
It's just so fulfilling
Go to beauty salons and nail salons
I'm excited and working hard on maintenance
So, from then on, have you been the same therapist?
Maybe about a year
Ah, have you stopped nominating?
Hmm...
I fell in love with him
It was completely swampy at the time
But in chat
I saw a woman of my generation getting stuck in therapy
I'll write about things that don't happen at all
Do whatever you want, slander therapist or slander
That's terrible
(Rabbit) Then suddenly I was swollen and saw myself.
I've made the distance
From there, he felt like he was the sex consultant.
(Tanabe) Ah
(Mobile phone vibrator sound) How long does it take to say the period?
Sorry, I'm a bit excuse
What's wrong? Manager
picture? Rio cancels at the last minute!?
♪～
～♪
(Yagaraku) Dashing to another child ~
I think you absolutely love it, right?
(Miho) Yutaka, please
(Yutaka) I'll have Rio switch over to you
(Miho) Yes
Take care
What should I do? Maybe it's my fault...
(Ami) Akari-san
(Akari) Huh?
(Ami) What will you do with this?
(Akari) Umm, this is... (vibrator sound on your mobile phone)
Sorry Amy wait a minute
It's Rio
hello
Yeah
Understood, make sure you have that time at the beauty salon.
yeah?
Ah thank you
Of course I'll do my best too
Hehe...
Two new customers
Good tone
Akari-chan
yes
Once the match is over, will the meeting minutes be fine?
Yes I'll do it soon
Akari-chan sorry
Can you buy me some sweets for your customers?
A clever guy
Yes!
(Vibration sound on mobile phone)
Rio...
Lots of phone calls
Yes yes
Yes, finished?
Thank you for your hard work
Do you want to sleep in the office?
I see, it's next night
Eat meals
It's a lot at the end of the month, but let's get through it
Ha... yes
No way...
(Vibration sound on mobile phone)
(Akari) Rio?
Today is the 15th time...
Ah... hm
what up?
(Rio) Acalin
I would like to pick out date spots for reservations for next month.
Ah... That Rio?
It's already night, I'm home
If you don't have to hurry, please send me an email.
It's completely compatible
(Rio) Haa, what?
I said I'd try hard...
It's fine
(No sound) (Akari) Ah...
picture?
Hey... Huh?
(Ringtone)
Are you sniffing from yesterday?
Sorry, I'm sorry
trouble?
It's okay, please continue
And
yes
I want to know more about my sex too
I've started to enjoy traveling
Ah, wandering around means trying out a variety of people, right?
What if you meet a good person?
If you're about to fall apart, leave a distance
I control myself
Because I'm not using it to fall in love
I'm paying to experience sexual pleasure, hehe
It looks like something is fun
(Rabbit) Hahaha, it's fun
So I would recommend traveling to keep it going too far
(Tanabe) I see
- (Rabbit) Ah, write it yes- (Tanabe) Yes
It's a voyage
So look forward to it
Yes Yes Yes Yes
(Cancel sound)
I was a friend of the manager and was saved
For now, I think something has been done
Contact Akari
yes
Ah, the rest is Rio
Rio: Sometimes I get into a weak mental state.
(Tanabe) Oh, Rabbit is
What was the best thing about using Jofuu?
Maybe something you didn't know about your body
What does it mean?
Being teased
I didn't know it felt so good
I also had my ears cum
Nipple orgasms belly orgasms
Ah, my brain is cumming
"Huh? The sexuality of a woman's body"
"Is it so wide and so deep?"
Ah, a series of surprises and discoveries
The most important thing in female sexuality
It's the heart
...It may happen
I'm more pure...
I believe that...
(Rabbit) He should never be able to come out
I love all the women I met in my private life.
Treat with respect
I tried to make it as comfortable as I wanted
He was a master therapist
I changed the way I live
It's a bit dangerous
That's right
Trying to become a therapist
I realized something more important haha
Yeah ha
(Rabbit) Isn't he the most interesting person?
(Akari) It's great, but sometimes it's not funny
Come back without getting any money
They say happily that they have "released sexually again today."
It's so funny Ahahaha
It's not funny, Rabbit
I've gone to get it a few times
There is no boundary between work and personal life
(Rabbit) Ha, that's right
It's the type who has private life just for work.
What is that terrible thought circuit
It's absolutely impossible
Haha...
So, can I ask the two of you at the end?
(Akari) Is it me too?
Yeah
Do women need sex industry?
picture…
(Ringtone)
(Not pronunciation)
(Miho) Haario doesn't come out after all
(The sound of the door closing) (Miho) Haario It's not coming out after all
(Yagaraku) Haa...
(Akari) Thank you for your hard work
(Miho) Thank you for your hard work
Rabbit was the best
That person is a good customer
That's about Rio...
Maybe I've got a little cold
(Miho) You've got a demon phone anyway, right?
Akari isn't bad either
yes…
Please tell me exactly what you're doing this time.
I'm not trying to spoil him, but I guess he's my best friend
I'm also feeling bad for quitting at this time
(Yagara Akari) What?
picture? No, you told the manager, right?
it was
Please wait a minute! Miho-san, are you going to quit?
- (Miho) Yes- (Akari) It's not possible
picture?
Did you think I was working here until I became an old man?
(Akari) Yes
I'm pregnant so I'm getting married and moving
There's a lot of information
I'll order a lot
Miho...
congratulations
thank you
(Akari) Please come once in a while, right?
I don't think it's coming
Haa
Maybe I'll quit too
What do you say!
Miho-chan quit and Ace has not heard from her.
It could be Paradiso's biggest crisis!
that…
If you ask me, "Does a woman need sex industry?"
What would you answer?
What is it? Suddenly
I was asked by the writer during the interview
Miho, what do you think?
picture…
Can I say it honestly?
please
I…
I've never thought about that
It's refreshing and looks like Miho
If it's not decided that it's necessary, there's no work.
If you want to give an answer
Why don't Akari-chan try using Jofuu too?
(Gokou) Women don't need sex industry.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Why is it not necessary?
I am working with the goal of acquiring citizenship for Jofu.
And the men in the world
I want you to deepen your knowledge of women's sexuality
If all men could become like therapists
Inevitably, women's sex industry will no longer be necessary
Hmm, no, wait
This may be when Jofu, who is at a higher level than he is now, will explode...
And as for Gokou-san
Is it necessary? Isn't it necessary?
Things I don't understand about that on "Gokou Channel"
You shouldn't say it, right?
(Door opening and closing sound) Hmm...
(Door opening and closing sound)
(The sound of the door opening and closing) I definitely should say it
I'm definitely going to say it
(Taro) Gokou-san grins while grinning
I was saying something loud
(Yagaraku) It's fine, that guy, leave him alone
Taro - It seems like he's doing well recently
Please
(Taro) Thank you
Starting today, I'm going for a 3 night, 4 days
It's the first long
As per the rules, do you get a proper break or something?
I'm coming
(Yagaraku) Come on, make money!
Leave it to me! Hehehehe
(Door opening and closing sound)
(Akari) So I'll be getting up soon too
Tired
(Miho) Take a good rest
(Akari) Yes
Thank you for your hard work
- (Yagaraku) Ui- (Miho) Thank you for your hard work
Right now
(Hiroki) Welcome home
(Akari) Haa...
(Hiroki) He's dead
The therapist is pounding after cancelling at the 1st time
Maybe he's sick, so I have to listen to him
(Hiroki) Why is Akari so far?
You should also have them take counseling.
No, just in case
Maybe it's my fault, and listening to the story is also my job at home.
Hmm
I like it, I'm dependent on you
picture…
Don't like it?
Because the same thing happened at my previous workplace.
It feels good that Akari is not needed
sorry
Shall we have sex?
- (Hiroki) Where are you going? -(Akari) It's fine
(Hiroki) Wait a minute
Let's quit my job and marry me
picture?
Please marry me
picture? In this flow?
You know, don't you? What's the reply?
I can't think about it now
on second thoughts…
I guess I'm going to go through all the trouble with the guy at the store anyway
teeth? Because it's impossible
So you should marry me
So I can't think about it now
Why?
I'm a full-time employee at a proper company.
That's a sex shop clerk
I don't think I'm going to get a lucky marriage like this
What is the way to say it
no…
Maybe Akari's last chance in life?
You can even quit sex industry, so isn't it okay?
It's fine
break up
teeth?
Slowly... Wait a minute!
no…
If so, give me my proposal back!
It was my first time
My proposal: Where did you go?
Isn't it falling around that?
(Door opening and closing sound) ♪~
♪～
Wow, it's Moeko's first time at home
It's beautiful
(Moeko) Hehe...
So Taro-chan
Let's live together here now
picture?
Ah
I came out despite my own home with great force
What should I do...
If you want to give an answer...
Akari-chan also
Why not try it?
What? Now?
(The sound of birds flapping wings)
(Akari) I work in-house at Jofuu
I want to be kind to the explosion!
(Moeko) Let's live together here from now on
I can't breathe
(Yagaraku) Is it necessary for women to have sex?
Do you understand?