[Watch on www.kisskh.la to support admin]
[The First Night]
Jin?
Jin, it's me, Samuel.
You came late.
The food got cold.
I'm sorry. I tried to get here as soon
as I could after you contacted me.
Didn't you come from home?
You dressed up.
First off, here you go.
Your house is really nice.
I cleaned it up.
- Woo Jin.
- Yes?
Do you mind if I hold your hand?
Why would you ask for such a thing?
Because you might feel uncomfortable.
You can just hold it. It's nothing big.
Here.
From now on, you can just come at me without asking.
I don't want to be rude.
By the way, how are you so good
at saying those things so naturally?
Why? Do you dislike it?
No, I like it. I asked because
I can't really say those things.
Have you always been so bashful, Samuel?
Oh, I'm not bashful.
People said I'm more of the cautious type.
You don't happen to find me
frustrating for being this way, do you?
I love it.
They say you need to meet your opposites.
That would make us perfect for each other.
Yes.
Excuse me, Woo Jin.
Do you mind if I kiss-
[After 3 Years of Marriage]
Gosh, what's wrong with me?
Man, it's not working.
S-Should we call it quits?
What's going on?
Is it because of the hair loss medicine?
Don't try too hard.
Should I quit taking hair loss medicine?
No, your hair's important.
Don't worry about it.
Gosh, it's important, but...
Let's think it's the same as the weather.
There are sunny days, and there are cloudy days.
Thank you.
Can we do it today?
You can just get to it if you want to do it.
I can ask if you're feeling it or not, at the very least.
You start feeling it even if you didn't
while getting to it and sucking each other off.
Really?
In that case,
I'll get to it today, okay?
I'm a little tired today.
I've got the morning shift tomorrow.
Okay.
Let's sleep.
I'm not sleepy right now.
Do you want to sleep first comfortably?
What are you going to do?
I'll be on the computer and
go to bed when I get sleepy.
Okay.
Go to sleep first.
Yes?
What are you doing?
N-Nothing much.
I'm opening the door, okay?
Sure.
How is it?
- You bought lingerie?
- Yes, I bought it.
It's pretty.
Isn't it about time the weather should clear up now?
Yes.
Let's give it some effort.
- Come to the room.
- Okay.
Be honest.
You don't see me as a woman now, do you?
It's really not like that.
You're still cool and sexy.
It's my fault right here.
Your words and your body are too different.
I don't know which one to believe, to be frank.
Wouldn't I be more frustrated than you?
You think you're the only one frustrated?
How frustrated must I have been
to buy and wear something like this?
Don't you know how hard it is
to do something you usually don't do?
It was also hard for me
to knock on your door wearing this.
Do you know how tough it is
when it doesn't get hard anymore?
They said it was because of the medicine.
Can't you be patient and wait for me?
Must you pressure me like that?
How long am I supposed to wait?
Just get a divorce instead!
How can you say that so easily?
That's one thing you can't say.
You like being alone, right?
Be alone all you want.
[Esom / Ahn Jae Hong]
[LTNS]
[LTNS - Episode 6: Long time no sex]
Damn it!
Gosh, you crazy bitch!
Aigoo, seriously.
[On the roof of the Complex 113 front lobby where you live...]
[At 12:30 p.m. on Friday, put 30 million won in cash in a backpack. Leave
it on the roof of the Complex 113 front lobby where you live and go away.]
[At 12:30 p.m. on Friday, put 30 million won in cash in a backpack. Leave it on the roof of the Complex 113 front lobby where you live and go away.]
[Even if you report this to the police, we'll still expose you. Remember, I'm watching your every move at a close distance.]
[D-Day]
A backpack? I haven't seen that one before.
You mean it's the one you saw before.
What?
Where have you been?
Work.
Work? Aren't you off today?
Not that work.
The work we used to do.
Didn't we agree to take a break
from that work for a while?
We did.
Yes.
But a doormat showed up in front of my eyes.
You were doing that work on your own?
Why did you do such tough work alone?
Because I was worried about you.
So who is it this time?
There's this guy.
A taxi driver.
A taxi driver? You extorted money from a taxi driver?
No, from the taxi driver's secret lover.
The driver didn't have much money.
I see. Did his lover have some money?
What does she do?
What else? A f***ing bitch
since she's cheating on her husband.
Right.
There was an interesting thing.
What is it?
She lives in our apartment complex.
Our complex?
Yes.
Surprising, right?
It's our complex?
Her husband is a researcher in Pohang,
so he only comes home every weekend.
She looked pretty good.
But was she very lonely?
Why'd she have an affair with a taxi driver
when she has a competent husband?
What are you trying to do with me right now?
I'm answering your questions honestly.
So, am I the taxi driver...
you're talking about?
Yeah.
Do you have proof?
There's no way anything to call it a proof could exist.
Of course, there is proof.
You two went into her house like it's nothing.
Isn't that an unarguable proof?
This job was way too easy.
I had no need to struggle through it
because she lives right next door,
you f***ing asshole!
You really need help. You should get some psychotherapy.
You stalked me, of all people?
On top of that, you blackmailed an innocent person?
With what right?
You've got it totally wrong this time.
You're in a serious trouble!
You're the one who's in trouble.
Are you curious if there's money in here or not?
I'm curious, too.
I didn't open it yet.
But if there's really money inside, what do we do?
You didn't think to ask me first before doing this shit?
You think I didn't?
But what you'd say was too obvious.
We can just open this together.
Let's see what's inside.
I can guarantee you there's no money in there.
Because we've got nothing going on.
Poor you. You didn't make any money.
You're crazy for money.
Even if it's next door, it still
must've been tough to stalk. Poor you.
Okay.
Let's open it, then.
We've got money.
A whole f***ing lot of money, too.
There's money inside? Shit!
There must be a good reason for the money to be in there.
What did you say to blackmail her for her to give you money?
What else?
I copied and pasted the blackmail message we used every time!
You're...
a demon.
Do you know?
I know.
I earned this money. Don't touch it.
F***!
Shit!
You want to take it all the way, huh?
Fine, let's do it.
Can we go any further from here, huh?
Woo Jin, what right do you have to treat me like this?
How come you're so shameless?
What are you saying? You should be begging-
I saw everything that day!
Two years ago...
the day you ran away from home.
You don't see me as a woman now, do you?
Wouldn't I be more frustrated than you?
You think you're the only one frustrated?
- Can't you be patient and wait for me?
- How long am I supposed to wait?
Just get a divorce instead!
You like being alone, right?
Be alone all you want.
The customer is not answering the phone. After the beep...
[Ms. Woo Jeong Ah]
[07 Kim Sae Ro Mi]
[Mr. Jeon on the Run!]
[Lee Yool Do]
[Dog]
Crazy bitch.
Hey, hey, long time no see.
Hey, are you watching me right now?
Cut the bullshit.
How did you know this oppa came to Seoul, then?
F*** you.
I pressed it by mistake.
Oh, hey, I want to f***.
Come to Grand Suite Room 1069.
Let's have a chat since it's been forever.
The night view is crazy here.
You're still the same, you f***er.
Why would I go there?
Wake up.
Hey, Dom Perignon happens to be here, too.
No matter how crazy I am, I'm not going there.
Because you're a f***ing scum.
I saw the night view, so I'm leaving.
It's going to rain soon.
Stay a bit longer.
I'm going to leave before it rains.
The night view's even better here when it rains.
You know it, too.
What are you looking at?
Aigoo, don't be pretty if you don't like this, you crazy bitch.
I'm ugly right now. I've got no makeup on.
You really don't know yourself.
Your bare face is what kills, bitch.
Don't curse, you crazy asshole.
You're happy to hear my cursing in a long time, right?
Give me a f***ing break.
Get lost, motherf***er.
Gosh, you're so sexy.
There's no girl who can swear flavorfully like you do.
- Moron.
- Yes, I missed your cursing, too.
I know you missed me a lot, too.
You didn't?
As if. A skunk can't quit farting, you know.
I'm a married woman.
Don't even think about touching me.
Yes, you're married, and I'm married, too.
- Fair play.
- I'm different from a f***ing scum like you.
Bullshit.
You're totally the same kind as me.
You can't even lie and just act tough. You're so cute.
My gosh!
Hey, you're honestly crazy sad the world doesn't know how cute you are after you got married, right?
Wait, why are you crying?
Is your marriage life hard?
Hey, marriage life is f***ing hard, to begin with.
Do you now understand what a hard life I'm living now?
You're just a f***ing scum.
Okay, hey, I'm the SOB. Don't cry.
- Okay?
- Don't do it.
Okay, I'm the SOB.
But people easily find solace and cry on SOB's shoulders.
You can also lean on me and cry. It's okay.
Forget it.
- Don't do it.
- No, hold on a minute.
You know I'm really honest, right?
I'm hard right now.
You f***ing lunatic.
- You can get hard in this situation?
- Yes.
- You still want to sleep with me?
Oh, hey, take a look.
- Feel it.
- What's your problem?
Come on, feel it! Right?
F***! Is sex the only thing on your mind?
You horny motherf***er!
You can stop being sexy, then.
Why are you only giving me shit?
Don't misunderstand.
I've got no feelings for you.
F*** me all you want and go,
you terrible bitch.
Yes, I'm a terrible bitch.
And you're a horny f***er.
Yes, I'm the SOB.
I saw everything that day.
I followed you that day because I was worried.
You went into a nice hotel.
In front of that hotel,
I had all kinds of thoughts alone!
"Should I follow her inside?
Wouldn't it be better if I
just pretended not to know?"
You should've just followed in.
You came out after about an hour.
That day,
who were you there with?
I was just there to meet a friend.
You go to a hotel to meet just a friend?
Did you sleep with that friend?
If I tell you honestly, will you do the same?
Sure.
It was just once.
You slept with that friend of yours, huh?
Who was it?
Jung Gi Seok.
Your ex-boyfriend?
But I swear it was just once,
and no feelings were involved.
How can you do it when you don't have any feelings?
How is that possible? Are you a beast?
It was my fault, through and through.
I'm regretting it. I won't give any excuses.
Just give excuses! Why won't you give excuses?
You can give excuses all night,
and it won't be enough!
I'm sorry. It was my bad.
Do you know what you did?
It's your turn now.
You tell me honestly, too.
There's really nothing to tell.
Be honest! I was honest, too!
What do you want to know?
Whether I slept with her or not?
I didn't sleep with her.
That makes no sense.
You went into her house together, but nothing happened?
Yes, nothing happened.
We're...
We?
Oh, it's a "we"?
We're cleaning mates.
We just cleaned together.
Cleaning?
We were both serious about cleaning,
so we helped each other with cleaning. That was it!
We didn't do anything.
Was she in our house, too?
Yes.
You're a total f***ing nutcase!
That woman must've seen my cosmetics,
clothes, and underwear, too, huh?
Did that woman touch my bed?
Tell me.
Since we were helping each other clean...
You're backstabbing me right in the liver.
I didn't tell you intentionally because you'd think like this unnecessarily!
But the only thing we did was cleaning. I swear!
Why did she pay such big money
when all you did was clean?
Are you going to be petty and hide until the end?
What am I hiding? I'm telling you all the facts.
What did you do next door for 30 minutes back then?
Were you doing a midnight clean together?
She said she wasn't feeling well that day,
so I gave her medicine and came out
after she fell asleep. That's all!
Can't I do that much? It's not like we're total strangers.
It's not like we're total strangers.
Who brings medicine and puts the woman next door to sleep?
You loved that woman, huh?
Answer me!
Did you love her?
Yes, I liked her.
Honestly, I needed someone to talk to.
You don't listen to what I say.
But that person had a conversation with me.
After seeing her, I realized how lonely of a person I have been.
Thanks to Min Soo.
You were lonely?
How can you be lonely with all the debt we had?
While you were moping around in depression after
resigning irresponsibly to start a business you failed,
I worked without a break to protect this family.
So, I had no time to be lonely!
Yes, you did all the work to protect this family, right?
And I did f***ing nothing, right?
Do you know how uncomfortable you make a person feel?
Why do you think my dick didn't get hard? Huh?
Try to think a little!
Who'd ever get hard with someone like you who
habitually tries to trample on other people?
Yes, that's why I did it with Jung Gi Seok, too.
No matter how much I shit on him and cursed at him,
Jung Gi Seok still got horny for me.
Yeah, I got horny seeing Min Soo, too.
You're finally telling the truth.
You got horny?
Yes, I got horny.
To adjust to your mood swing
that changes every 10 minutes,
I was always so anxious and nervous.
Whoa, it felt like I was going to get angina with you!
Whoa, but after meeting someone
who's considerate and cares for my feelings,
I got so relaxed that I got horny!
But I still didn't play dirty like you.
Yeah? You were f***ing clean, huh?
Did you ever masturbate thinking about that woman or not?
You must have since you can't answer.
Look how f***ing clean you are.
And how many times did you go
when you did it with Jung Gi Seok?
- Did he even use a condom?
- Enough is enough.
I didn't f***ing pretend to be a tragic protagonist,
soaked in his own f***ing emotions, like you.
You couldn't even f***ing ask me
about it for two years. And now what?
Did he use a condom?
He didn't use a condom!
What the f*** will you do about it?
- That's filthy.
- You're filthier than I am.
You act all nice on the outside but
jerk off imagining someone else's wife.
Your mind must've been over there,
though your body was with me.
- That's deception.
- Deception?
Looks like you don't know what deception means.
Deception is doing it with just anyone
whenever you get horny like you!
You should've just done it once.
I think that'd make more sense for me.
Oh, you didn't get hard next door, either, huh?
That must be why you couldn't do it.
You would've done it a long time ago
if you were able to get hard!
What are you doing?
What is this?
My dick doesn't get hard?
I'll show you. Watch.
- Have you gone mad?
- Yes, I've gone mad.
Gosh, talking to a beast turns you into one.
Going mad was a good thing, huh? Shit.
- Look-
- Are you showing off your dick?
Let go.
Look, I'll make sure to show you my dick getting hard.
You love dicks! Watch-
- Stop it!
- It got hard, didn't it?
- Don't touch me. Don't f***ing touch my body.
- Stop it-
Hey, happy now? Look!
It got hard! Look!
It's f***ing hard. Can I touch it?
It got hard in front of you, too!
I'm a beast now, too!
What's that?
A rock?
Hey, someone threw a rock!
You're showing your worst side.
How can you take this in the midst of all this?
I'm trying to take care of the trouble you caused!
I earned this money! Don't touch it!
This isn't your money! This is Min Soo's money!
It was an adulterous bitch's money, so it's mine!
She didn't cheat, so you need to give it back!
Whose side are you on?
- Let go!
Let go!
Shit!
Don't do it, don't do it.
Don't do it, don't do it, don't do it!
Don't do it, don't do it!
Hey, do you think I don't get angry
because I don't have anger?
Why are you making a good person get angry?
You're great at doing laundry!
You dry them again and fold them!
Am I your dog or something?
You fold them, you fold them!
Do you even know how to fold laundry?
Hit me.
Hit me. Hit me.
Don't do it.
- Hit me.
- Don't do it.
Don't do it!
Don't do it. Hey, hey!
- Let go!
- Stop it!
- Let go.
- Don't come!
Shit!
That son of a bitch!
Hey, where are you going?
Turn on the emergency lights and pull over right now!
I always listened to what you said.
I'm not going to listen to you starting today! F***!
It's so great not to listen!
You better pull over.
Nope, I'm not pulling over.
You'll regret it!
I won't.
Shit.
Move out of the way!
F***!
I'm coming.
Open it.
What?
I opened it, stop! Stop now!
This is mad.
Hey!
Give it.
Shit!
Let go. I'll kick you.
Let go. I'll kick you!
You're mad.
This is money.
It's money, your favorite thing. Come to your senses!
It's so nice to be mad, as you said!
You were already mad! You can't get more mad!
- Let go.
- Please stop!
- Stop!
Stop!
If I can't have it,
no one can have it!
No one can f***ing have it!
[7 Months Later]
It's cleaner than expected for an old house, right?
It's cleaner than I thought, but it's old, as you said.
Well, you can renovate it all over.
I can hook you up with a nice and affordable company.
How were the people who lived here before?
The owners lived here. A newlywed-
A newlywed! A newlywed...
They were such a loving couple, and things
worked out well for them, and they moved.
Maybe this place's energy is great.
Everyone who lived here did very well and moved out.
We'll sign the contract.
Will you, really?
Oh, my, its owner finally showed up.
I'll contact the owners and set up the date right away, then.
Your fate with this house-
You made a really good decision!
Aigoo, my goodness.
Excuse me, did people who used to live here move out?
Must be so!
Because these folks are planning to move in.
- May I ask who you are?
- Don't.
I'm the deliveryman.
- Oh, my...
- Aigoo...
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
The deliveryman! Yes, the delivery.
[Byeoldong Shipping]
Father, you know that house, right?
The one that ordered a stupid amount of bottled water.
- Unit 609?
- Yes, they moved out.
Aigoo, how great. My arms ached every time I passed by that house.
It still makes me mad to think how they caused your arm injury.
Since I'm in a good mood today,
should we go get some jumbo tonkatsu?
Jumbo tonkatsu? Let's go.
All right, yes.
[Byeoldong Shipping]
[Alarm]
There is no way to break up in a cool way.
Breaking up is the ending of the history created by two people.
It's the same thing as exploding a well-built house and
standing alone on the ruins.
It must be built again by yourself.
[Shalom Strawberry Farm]
Aigoo, what a friendly father and son.
Let's come and eat!
Samuel, you're doing the hardest work.
Putting the stickers on.
Aren't you sweating?
- Come out right now and set the table.
- Okay.
[Shalom Strawberry Farm]
Hey.
Why do you sleep in your car when you got Father's house?
It's an eyesore.
It's the trend these days. Don't you know car camping?
Don't you know car camping?
What a stupid trend.
While following the trend, his face might get droopy.
He even smokes these days.
Aigoo, we have a crazy guy in our family
who's learning how to smoke at age 40.
Let him be.
Got it? Stop nagging him.
Father, that's quite upsetting to hear.
Why would I be nagging him? I'm just worried about him.
All of those worries are the same as nagging.
Let him be.
Father, you need to stop leaving him alone.
Neglecting him isn't love.
People these days confuse love with other things.
You're right.
Love isn't the same thing...
- as freedom.
- Yes.
Love is possessing, binding,
- obsession, and stuff like that!
- Right on.
They don't even know better and looking for freedom and other stuff.
That's why they all break up.
Like him.
Hey, you've gone too far.
A divorcé is going to choke while eating.
Let him choke.
What? What is it?
Trying to slack off?
Is he running away?
- Is it really a call?
- Hello.
This is Onnara Real Estate.
We've got buyers offering 620 million won for your place.
It's great, right?
Oh, really?
Yes, you and your wife share the ownership, right?
I think you'll need to come in together.
Hello?
When do we need to come by?
[Onnara Real Estate]
You came early.
Yes, in case there might be traffic.
You came early, too.
I'm going to take a look around.
I see.
We've got some free time. Do you want to have some coffee?
I also have something to tell you.
What is it?
Forget it if you're not comfortable with it.
Did you eat?
Well...
Yes?
I've got a favor to ask.
And the favor is...
I'm going to tell you now, but...
I want you to keep eating.
And don't look at me.
Absolutely don't look up, okay?
Samuel.
Have you been well?
I told you not to look up.
You're still the same.
Listening to what I have to say.
I haven't been doing well.
It was hard.
After the divorce, the only thing we had left
was that house.
It feels weird to hear that the house will be gone, too.
Lately, I'm oddly reminded of when we first bought this house.
We fearlessly took out those loans and
we were so happy we got a place.
I've been thinking a lot
about how we ended up this way
when we had it great in the beginning.
At the end of my thoughts,
I think I really have to let you go now.
Yes, that's what I've come to decide.
In that case,
I realized there was something that I must do.
And I'm going to do that now.
I'm sorry, Samuel.
It's all my fault we ended up this way.
I think you were satisfied to just have me by your side,
but I wanted so many things from you.
Because I took it for granted that you were by my side.
I think...
I ruined you, a kind and smart man.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you for living with me for six years.
I'm going to live a good life from now on.
So, you have a good one, too.
I'm really sorry, too.
[East West Hotel]
Noona.
Could you check me in right away?
I can't.
You checked in too many times this month. So, I can't.
Noona, just once! I really didn't check in that much this month.
What's this?
Twitty. Gosh.
- I made you wait, right?
- Wasn't it cold?
It wasn't cold.
Hello, Noona, I'm back again.
Yes, you are.
And this is for you.
Oh, thank you.
Noona, check-in.
Here you go.
Your lover is so sweet, so you got an upgrade to the suites.
Oh, my gosh! She's so sweet!
What's this? You saw, right?
She's good. She knows what's up.
Noona, I love you.
Thanks to you, I'll have a sweet end of the year with my Twitty.
Enjoy your night, Dear Guests.
Noona.
Merry Christmas.
Twitty.
- Don't call me Twitty.
- Why not?
- It's so pretty.
- Right?
I'm checking out.
Yes, thank you.
Merry Christmas.
I plan to go on a trip for Christmas.
And the trip will take place in my room.
You know, we can travel anywhere.
We think we know everything about our rooms, but I think we're mistaken.
Even in this small room, there are still
[Ms. Woo Jeong Ah]
many places we didn't go to yet.
So still...
Hello?
Hey, Divorcée, it's Christmas. What are you doing?
I'm with my friends.
Shut up, you don't have any friends.
Cut it out and come to my house.
The kids want to blow the candles with Auntie.
Hong Ju, tell Auntie...
Can't you hear? I'm with my friends.
You're serious, right? You're not all miserable alone, are you?
No, I'm hanging up!
- Bye!
- H-Hey, hold on-
Who is it?
Woo Jin.
It's me, Samuel.
You're really...
What are you doing here during the holidays?
What about you? All alone at home during the holidays?
You didn't get a man?
That's what you want to know?
I don't think I've got a duty to tell you such personal things.
You don't anymore.
The strawberries are good.
Yes, it was a good harvest this year.
And your family? Are they all doing well?
Yes, they're all doing well.
Your unni's doing well, too, right?
Yes.
You want some wine?
No, I'm fine.
There's also beer in the fridge.
No, I brought my car.
Okay.
Forget it, let's drink. I'll drink.
I'll drink. Let's have some.
When you were living alone a long time ago,
you had invited me to a studio like this one.
Do you remember?
I remember now.
You were almost like a roommate at my studio back then.
I was.
We were really cute back then.
Yes.
Has anyone come to this place yet?
Why on Earth are you curious about those things?
Well, of course, I'm curious.
You used to be my wife.
You want to know?
I mean, well- Someone did come, huh?
No one's been here.
You should go out and meet people.
Oh, right. You remember the prosecutor we gave up on catching?
- Prosecutor?
- The one with the mold.
Shui Jing Fang* at a Chinese restaurant?
(A Chinese liquor)
- Yes.
He came by earlier with a different woman to have an affair.
I was reminded of you a little.
Gosh, that prosecutor bastard.
Go ahead.
What's with you? Are you drunk?
Right, sorry.
We're divorced.
But we can still have sex.
That's true.
[LTNS]
[Long Time No Sex]