(Suitable for all people to watch)
(No content that involves violence
or needs discretion,)
(and suitable for any age group.)
(Brought to you by Trip.com,
your one-stop travel app.)
(What you want is ALLHAVE,
ALLHAVE have all.)
(This program is brought to you by
main sponsor ALLHAVE.)
(Brought to you by Cremo.)
(Upfeel. Wow with every bite.)
(MVP in every match
with real gaming phone.)
(This program is brought to you
by Infinix HOT 40Pro.)
(Download WeTV and register
to become a member.)
(Then press CHUANG ASIA bar below)
(and click Vote Now
to vote for your favorite trainees.)
(WeTV members
will get the vote eligible every day.)
(You can vote for three trainees each day
with a limit of one trainee per 250 votes only.)
(And purchase WeTV VIP
on CHUANG ASIA page)
(will get 500 votes per trainee daily.)
(Unlock exclusivity, click Send Love
to get unlimited voting privileges)
(or purchase CHUANG ASIA VIP Gift Card
to get extra votes.)
(This round,
members get extra free 50 votes)
(from BUFF VOTE on WeTV.)
(Plus, there's a Surprise Extra Vote
on Debut Day.)
(Stay tuned to CHUANG ASIA social media
and WeTV app for updates.)
(The final round of voting will be started
from March 30th, 2024 at 10:00 PM)
(until April 6th, 2024 during the live streaming
of CHUANG ASIA Debut Night.)
(Last chance!
Come and vote for your favorite trainee.)
(Who's gonna debut
will be solely determined by your vote.)
(THEME SONG performance)
VO: Please welcome CHUANG ASIA Thailand
Grand Debut Night Host, BAM PITIPAT.
(Host: BAM PITIPAT)
HOST: Hello.
HOST: Can I get bigger round of applause
for our lovely trainees once again?
HOST: Wow and a very good evening everyone
HOST: and welcome to CHUANG ASIA
THAILAND Grand Debut Night
HOST: live on WeTV app and One31 channel.
HOST: My name is BAM
HOST: and I am super excited
to be your host for tonight.
HOST: First of all, let me
introduce myself. I'm BAM PITIPAT.
HOST: I'm a host for today.
HOST: Everyone in this studio,
please make some noise.
HOST: That's so good.
HOST: Good evening, everybody.
HOST: My name is BAM and I am your host.
HOST: Oh, super excited to be here.
Firstly,
HOST: I would like to start by thanking
each and every one of you here
HOST: and everyone who is watching us live
HOST: And supporting all the trainees
and voting for them all along.
HOST: Together, we have witnessed the
growth and development and tonight.
HOST: They shine brighter than ever,
all the while creating life long relationships
HOST: and unforgettable memories.
HOST: It is with all your support
and votes from all over Asia.
OST: Better yet, all over the world
that help encourage
HOST: and give hope to these trainees
HOST: to work hard
and strive for their dreams.
HOST: Thank you again.
HOST: It's been an incredible journey.
HOST: And now, ladies and gentlemen,
in this final stage
HOST: is where we will get to witness
the first international girl group of CHUANG ASIA.
HOST: Are you ready?
HOST: All right, let's get things going,
HOST: because the mentors
are ready to meet you all tonight.
HOST: That's right. First up.
HOST: Please join me
in welcoming to the stage.
HOST: Our coproducer and lead mentor,
JACKSON WANG
HOST: and give it up
for Mentor MIKE ANGELO,
HOST: Mentor TEN, Mentor JEFF SATUR,
and Mentor NENE.
HOST: I think you can do better than that.
Give it up for the mentors.
HOST: Hello. What is up, Mentors?
HOST: Hi. Hi. Hi.
HOST: Feel free to say hi to
each and everyone here
HOST: and watching us live
all over the world.
HOST: Starting with you, MR. JACK.
JACKSON: Hi, this is JACKSON WANG,
lead mentor. Nice to meet you guys.
JEFF: Hi guys, this is me, JEFF SATUR,
from CHUANG ASIA.
MIKE: Hello everyone. MIKE ANGELO,
the mentor of CHUANG ASIA.
TEN: Hello, I am TEN.
NENE: Hello, I am NENE.
Host: Truly an exciting night.
Host: I am sure the past few months
have been an emotional ride for you.
Host: And you must
have a lot to share, right?
Host: But if you had to use one word,
and I repeat just one word
Host: to describe how you
feel about the entire season.
Host: What would it be and why?
Host: Let's start with JACKSON.
JACKSON: I think the word that
I'm going to choose is 'born'.
Host: Born?
JACKSON: I think tonight you know
we got 9 trainees.
JACKSON: Nine artists about to be born.
Host: Thank you, JACKSON.
Moving on to the next person.
MIKE: For me, I think it's 'dream'.
MIKE: Because everyone who's here
is here to chase their dream.
HOST: I love it, I love it. JEFF?
JEFF: For me, it feels like...
JEFF: I will choose "summer dream."
HOST: Summer dream?
JEFF: It is the theme song too.
- JEFF: But i mean like...
- HOST: That's two words, bro.
- MIKE: That's two words.
- JEFF: JACKSON.
JEFF: Yeah, but I'm, anyways,
just feel like...
JEFF: everybody gather in the summer
to do the dream
JEFF: and then this time is about to over.
JEFF: And it's like, felt like
just summer dream.
HOST: But it's gonna be the best day
in summer time.
- JEFF: Of course.
- HOST: Of course, thank you.
HOST: TEN?
TEN: I will choose the word 'more'.
TEN: So, every time you like do something
just like try one more time
TEN: So, it might come out better
than the first time.
HOST: I love that. NENE?
NENE: I would choose 'love',
because I think passion, dream, girl,
NENE: everything starts from love.
HOST: Love, all right.
HOST: That pretty much sums up
what this season has been like.
HOST: Thank you for sharing, Mentors.
HOST: Give it up for the mentors.
HOST: And of course, ladies and gentlemen,
HOST: the most nerve-wracking
and anticipated part of the show
HOST: that everyone is waiting for
is the voting results.
HOST: Before we start
tonight's performances,
HOST: I'd like to all the mentors
to announce the current trainee's rank ninth
HOST: in Thailand, Malaysia, North America,
Hong Kong China, Indonesia, Singapore, and Japan.
HOST: This ranking is based on accumulated
votes from March 30th, 10:00 PM
HOST: up to today, April 6th,
7:00 PM Bangkok time.
HOST: Let's start with Nene.
HOST: Please make the
announcement for us, please.
NENE: Yes, the trainee currently
ranked 9th in the WeTV Japan is
NENE: R-JING.
- HOST: JEFF?
- JEFF: Okay.
JEFF: So, the trainee currently ranked 9th
in the WeTV Singapore is.
JEFF: YEAN.
MIKE: The trainee currently ranked 9th
in the WeTV Indonesia is
MIKE: XUEYAO.
- HOST: TEN, you're up next.
- TEN: Okay.
TEN: The trainee currently ranked 9th
in the WeTV North America is
TEN: DIDI.
HOST: All right, next up Producer JACKSON.
HOST: Please announce the trainees who are
currently ranked 9th
HOST: on WeTV in Hong Kong China,
Malaysia, and Thailand.
JACKSON: The trainee currently ranked 9th
in WeTV Hong Kong China is
JACKSON: XUANNING.
JACKSON: The trainee currently ranked 9th
in WeTV Malaysia is
JACKSON: LISSA.
JACKSON: and lastly
JACKSON: The trainee currently ranked 9th
in WeTV Thailand is
JACKSON: EMMA.
HOST: Thank you, Mentors.
HOST: Please remember these results
are only temporary, all right.
HOST: This isn't the final result.
HOST: It is still changing as we speak.
HOST: So, you still have time to vote
for your favorite trainee.
HOST: Anything can happen tonight.
HOST: All 18 of you still have a chance
to reach top nine.
HOST: You know what?
I'll allow all the trainees to, you know,
HOST: give them one last chance
to say anything to the fans.
HOST: One last chance, all right?
HOST: Let's start with rank
number 18, R-JING.
R-JING: Hello, I am R-JING.
R-JING: I'm so happy that
today I have a chance to
R-JING: show my performances
to everyone today.
R-JING: No matter what has happened
in the past,
R-JING: I am very proud of myself.
R-JING: My rank isn't important at all.
R-JING: But today
R-JING: I promise that
I will try my best and be
R-JING: the MVP in everyone's hearts.
R-JING: Thank you.
LISSA: Hello, I'm LISSA.
LISSA: So, this is probably the last time
LISSA: I'll be asking you guys
to vote for me.
LISSA: So I'm always at the last place.
LISSA: Some people said
it's because of luck.
it's because of green.
LISSA: But, I think
it's because of my passion
LISSA: and the power of my fans.
LISSA: I used to
LISSA: I've debuted before,
LISSA: but my group has been disbanded.
LISSA: So, I come back here to pursue
my dream one more time.
LISSA: I really don't care
if I'm the last place, but tonight
LISSA: I'll be the last one
standing up there in one of the top nine.
LISSA: I really want to debut.
LISSA: The last place is also alright.
LISSA: Thank you for your hard work.
LISSA: Could...
LISSA: Could you vote for me?
LISSA: Thank you for your hard work.
LU YUTING: Hello, I'm LU YUTING.
LU YUTING: Hello everyone, I'm LU YUTING.
LU YUTING: I want to be LU YUTING, who is
seen and recognized by everyone.
LU YUTING: If you like me,
LU YUTING: please vote for me.
LU YUTING: Have fun today.
XUANNING: Hello everyone, I am XUANNING.
XUANNING: So, I want to say to those
who like and support me that
XUANNING: we have fought side by side
for so many days.
XUANNING: Today is finally the time for us
to witness the results.
XUANNING: So, I hope you will walk
with me until the end,
XUANNING: to the end.
DUNA: Hello, I'm DUNA.
DUNA: I wanna show you a new side of me.
DUNA: Please vote for me.
DUNA: Please give me a lot of love.
DUNA: Thank you.
PRAEW: Hello.
PRAEW: Hello everyone, I'm PRAEW.
I'm 15 years old.
PRAEW: Everyone knows that I've almost
been dropped out
PRAEW: on so many stages,
PRAEW: but it's because of everyone
who made it
PRAEW: possible for me to be
at this point today.
PRAEW: I really want to thank you.
PRAEW: I really want to debut.
PRAEW: I hope everyone will vote for me.
DIDI: Hello everyone,
my name is OUYANG DIDI.
DIDI: Hello everyone, I am DIDI. Hello.
DIDI: If you guys wanna see,
sing well, dance well, DIDI.
DIDI: Please vote for me.
DID: If you hope me to keep on
singing and dancing on stage.
DIDI: Please vote for me.
DIDI: Thank you, everyone.
DIDI: Thank you.
KRISTA SHIM: Hello.
KRISTA SHIM: Hello, my name is KRISTA.
KRISTA SHIM: Today, KRISTA feels
KRISTA SHIM: the happiest, because
KRISTA gets to do what KRISTA loves,
KRISTA SHIM: which is singing.
And today, KRISTA gets to sing
KRISTA SHIM: for the people
who KRISTA loves.
KRISTA SHIM: So, no matter
what happens today,
KRISTA SHIM: I just want to say that
KRISTA SHIM: I really love you
from the bottom of my heart
KRISTA SHIM: and thank you for
not giving up on me
believing in me.
KRISTA SHIM: So, I'll do my best
for you guys.
KRISTA SHIM: Thank you.
EMMA: Hello everyone, I'm Emma.
EMMA: At the CHUANG Camp,
I have four stages.
EMMA: As the four stages have passed,
EMMA: I want to stand on stages
and shine more and more.
EMMA: I really WANNA debut, I really wanna
shining bright on the stage.
EMMA: So, please vote for me.
EMMA: Please give a lot of votes for EMMA.
XUEYAO: Hello everyone, I'm XUEYAO.
XUEYAO: Please don't forget
supporting me to the end.
XUEYAO: Tonight my dream will come true.
PAILIU: Hello, I'm PAILIU.
PAILIU: PAILIU wants to say that
I'm a person who
PAILIU: just have a chance to be a trainee
for the first time. I may be not the best.
PAILIU: I believe that everyone could see
PAILIU: From my previous stages,
I've tried to improve myself
PAILIU: in my every stages, and
PAILIU: I would like to be an inspiration
PAILIU: to many people who have dreams,
yet aren't brave enough.
PAILIU: Some people may think their dreams
are too far to be real,
PAILIU: but if you don't try it once,
you'll never know if it's really far.
PAILIU: Just be brave to do it, and
PAILIU: I wanna tell you that
PAILIU will do
PAILIU: my best today. And today is
another time for PAILIU
PAILIU: to challenge myself
with a new way.
PAILIU: Everyone, please vote for PAILIU.
PAILIU: Thank you.
YUANKE: Hello, I'm KEKE.
YUANKE: Hello everyone, I am YUANKE.
YUANKE: Thank you guys so much for
YUANKE: your support and companionship
along the way.
YUANKE: Now we are not far
from the destination.
YUANKE: Please keep on cheering for me.
YUANKE: Please give KEKE a lot of love.
YUANKE: Thank you so much.
ILENE: Hello everyone.
ILENE: Hello everyone, I'm ILENE.
ILENE: I wanna say that
many people may want to ask me
ILENE: why I'm so confident.
ILENE: Shout out like cheering
for a boxing match.
ILENE: But, I wanna say that
ILENE: I didn't start off
as a confident person.
ILENE: I've gone through many paths,
ILENE: from actor's path and joining a
survival show, up until
ILENE: being MINDY,
and I really love MINDY.
ILENE: And
ILENE: And I...
ILENE: gets to join
in the CHUANG ASIA program
ILENE: and become one of the top nine,
so I feel like it is
ILENE: very unexpected.
ILENE: And then it made me realize that
ILENE: I love doing shows for everyone.
ILENE: I love dancing, singing,
and performing.
ILENE: So, could you guys make me debut?
ILENE: It's just
ILENE: just one reach away from my debut.
Everyone, would you please vote for me?
ILENE: I want to debut.
ILENE: Could you give votes for me?
ILENE: Could you vote for me?
ILENE: Thank you.
ELYN: Hello everyone, my name is ELYN.
ELYN: ♪It's a lovely day in Bangkok city♪
ELYN: I sang this song
for my audition stage,
ELYN: and I can't believe that
ELYN: I'm standing
at the final Debut Night stage.
ELYN: So, thank you so much to
everyone who supported me.
ELYN: We've come a long way
and let's go further together. Vote
ELYN: for me a lot. Thank you.
ELYN: Please vote for me, thank you.
WANGKE: Hello, my name is WANGKE.
WANGKE: My family, this time I think
we can definitely do it,
WANGKE: so let's hold on.
WANGKE: I feel that I can definitely
do it this time.
WANGKE: I want to debut.
WANGKE: All my friends,
please stay by WANGKE's side
WANGKE: until I debut.
YEAN: Hi. Hello everyone, I am YEAN.
YEAN: Thank you very much
to everyone who voted
YEAN: for me to be here.
YEAN: Today is YEAN's last day
as a trainee,
YEAN: and I hope that
in the next few hours
YEAN: it will be my first day
YEAN: as a girl group member
from CHUANG ASIA.
YEAN: I...
YEAN: I believe that
my performances have shown
YEAN: to everyone that
I am not just the main vocalist.
YEAN: And I feel that
YEAN: I will be able to be
in the debut lineup.
YEAN: And I want to debut
in the top three.
YEAN: So, please vote for me.
YEAN: Please believe in me.
YEAN: Please support me a lot.
YEAN: Thank you guys.
RUAN: Hi, everyone.
RUAN: Hello.
RUAN: Cutie hamster, RUAN.
They told RUAN that I'm already a Thai.
RUAN: Be a Thai,
RUAN: Can I be a Thai?
RUAN: Hello. I'm RUAN.
RUAN: If, I'm Trainee RUAN now,
but if you want to see Idol RUAN,
RUAN: please keep supporting me to the end.
Thank you so much.
QIAO YI YU: Hi guys, I'm QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: Hello, I'm QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: So, today is finally
the big big final.
QIAO YI YU: So, I'm gonna say
my slogan again.
QIAO YI YU: If you guys think I'm handsome,
if you guys love my performance,
QIAO YI YU: please vote for me,
vote for QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: Because I want to debut
as a center.
QIAO YI YU: Thank you guys.
HOST: Thank you all the trainees
HOST: and best of luck
to all of you tonight.
HOST: Go for it.
HOST: Once again ladies and gentlemen,
this is CHUANG ASIA's final stage,
HOST: and your last chance
to support your favorite trainee.
HOST: How do you vote?
HOST: Here is how. Listen carefully.
For all the audience,
HOST: while you enjoy the live,
HOST: don't forget to log into WeTV app,
visit CHUANG ASIA page,
HOST: and vote for your favorite trainees.
HOST: Each user gets 750 votes per day.
HOST: If you purchase the VIP card
through CHUANG ASIA's related activity page.
HOST: You will receive
750 extra free votes. In the app,
HOST: you can also purchase and send love
to your favorite trainees to earn more votes.
HOST: In addition to the regular votes
in the WeTV app, tonight
HOST: we have prepared a surprise for you
with extra votes. During the live today,
HOST: we will give away two rounds of
free votes to all WeTV users.
HOST: First round has just started
and we have added an additional
HOST: 300 free votes in
all WeTV users' accounts.
HOST: So, please log in to WeTV
to check and vote now.
HOST: Please note that any
unused votes accumulated in this round
HOST: will expire with the next round
of votes giveaway starts.
HOST: So, please start voting.
HOST: Now I'm sure you all cannot wait to see
our trainees final performances, right?
HOST: You all are waiting to see
the special shows, right?
HOST: Of course. But before that,
ladies and gentlemen, tonight
HOST: we are joined not only by our mentors,
but also our guest mentors.
HOST: You know them and you love them.
HOST: They're the seniors from CHUANG 2021
who debuted three years ago.
HOST: And tonight they're here
to support our girls
HOST: and witness the birth of the first
international girl group here in Thailand.
HOST: First senior, he is the center
of the debut group in CHUANG 2021.
HOST: He is also an all-round performer
in both singing and dancing.
HOST: He is here with his new song
"CAPTAIN".
HOST: Give it up for LIU YU.
HOST: Let's hear it for Liu Yu.
HOST: Did everyone enjoy it? Wow.
HOST: Amazing.
HOST: Amazing performance
by the 1st Senior. Now,
HOST: on to the 2nd guest mentor
that is here with us tonight.
HOST: Three years ago,
HOST: he created lots of
hit songs in CHUANG 2021,
HOST: and tonight he's singing this
beautiful song called So I Don't Forget,
HOST: Please Welcome MIKA.
MIKA: Hello.
HOST: Let's hear it for MIKA.
HOST: What a beautiful voice.
It's mesmerizing. Such beautiful voice.
HOST: Are two guest mentors enough?
HOST: Are they enough?
HOST: How about one more guest mentor?
HOST: On to the 3rd guest mentor
tonight, ladies and gentlemen.
HOST: He's, wow, one of
the few that has been
HOST: so popular and get to debut as well.
HOST: He's currently a rising
artist with so many fans
HOST: in both China and Thailand.
HOST: Let's hear it for...
HOST: "From the moment you look at me"
by NINE.
(From the moment you look at me)
♪From the moment you look at me♪
♪The isolated island
is lightened by the lighthouse♪
♪The fish swimming in the deep sea♪
♪as if it is on land♪
♪There's no way to go with every breath♪
♪From the moment you walked toward me♪
♪It's like I'm back in the past♪
♪The past is so heavy♪
♪as if an old nostalgic movie♪
♪rerun tonight for the old lovers♪
♪I've made you wait for so long♪
♪like the galaxy running to the universe♪
♪In the darkness, our bond never go away♪
♪It's still tied with our hands♪
♪I've made you wait for so long♪
♪The late evening wind is gentle♪
♪You give me the best life in this world♪
♪Take me to kiss the sky
and the vastness of the sea♪
♪From the moment you walked toward me♪
♪It's like I'm back in the past♪
♪The past is so heavy♪
♪as if an old nostalgic movie♪
♪rerun tonight for the old lovers♪
♪I've made you wait for so long♪
♪like the galaxy running to the universe♪
♪In the darkness, our bond never go away♪
♪It's still tied with our hands♪
♪I've made you wait for so long♪
♪The late evening wind is gentle♪
♪You give me the best life in this world♪
♪Take me to kiss the sky
and the vastness of the sea♪
♪I've made you wait for so long♪
♪like the galaxy running to the universe♪
♪In the darkness, our bond never go away♪
♪It's still tied with our hands♪
♪I've made you wait for so long♪
♪The late evening wind is gentle♪
♪You give me the best life in this world♪
♪Take me to kiss the sky
and the vastness of the sea♪
HOST: Give it up for NINE.
HOST: Come over here, please, NINE.
HOST: And LIU YU, MIKA as well,
please join me over here.
HOST: Yes, the three of you.
HOST: Give it up for the guest mentors.
MIKA: Thank you.
HOST: Amazing performance.
- LIU YU: Thank you, thank you.
- HOST: you all were awesome.
HOST: Say hi to each everyone here
watching us live.
LIU YU: Hello everyone. I am LIU YU.
LIU YU: I'm very happy to be here.
LIU YU: I'm back in the familiar stage
I was three years ago.
LIU YI: And today, there're so many people
witnessing our sisters.
LIU YI: I am very happy
for such an important moment
LIU YU: I'm happy to see everyone again.
HOST: Amazing.
MIKA: Hello everyone, I am MIKA.
MIKA: Hello, my name is MIKA.
NINE: Hello everyone, I am NINE.
NINE: I'm back again.
HOST: How does it feel?
I have to ask the three of you.
HOST: I mean, three years ago
you were trainees
HOST: and now you're on this
very stage as seniors.
MIKA: It's honestly really weird to see
the same stage we saw three years ago,
MIKA: but it's an honor to be back.
MIKA: So thanks everybody.
HOST: Thank you. NINE.
NINE: For me, I'm very happy because
NINE: I was a trainee before.
And coming back here
NINE: is like a reminder
of the old memories and
NINE: most importantly,
I'm back to see the friends and the staff.
Host: Anything you want to say
to the girls, all the 18 trainees?
LIU YU: Fighting.
MIKA: Fighting. You got this.
NINE: Fighting.
HOST: Give it up to the special guest mentors,
LIU YU, MIKA and NINE.
HOST: Thank you, Thank you.
And ladies and gentlemen,
HOST: we'll take a short break
and we'll be right back.
WANG KE: Why is it so tiring?
PAILIU: WANG KE.
ELYN: It's just one trip.
JASMINE: Why do you use so many apps?
PAILIU: Use Trip.com, all-in-one app!
(Trip.com, book a flight, book a hotel)
(Booking together is cheaper)
(There are also tickets)
(So many deals)
(Contact 24hr Thai customer service)
(One-stop travel app)
(Trip.com, your one-stop travel app)
(Choose the right thing)
(Do what you want)
(Enjoy and be yourself)
(Lolane Pixxel, five new colors)
(Brilliant colors show your personality)
HOST: Welcome back everyone and this is
CHUANG ASIA THAILAND Grand debut night.
HOST: Live on WeTV app and channel One31.
HOST: It is time to start
the second part of our stage.
HOST: Throughout the season, we have witnessed
many exciting battles among the trainees.
HOST: For our next performance,
HOST: we will have CHUANG ASIA's
last battle showdown.
HOST: Our trainees have been
divided into two groups of nine
HOST: to perform the song
of their choosing.
HOST: Mentor TEN and NENE.
HOST: Any words of encouragement
before they start the performance?
NENE: Of course, this is an immortal song,
Into the New World by Girls' Generation
NENE: which I also really like.
NENE: Am I spoiling things?
NENE: I want everyone to support
the trainees' dream because
NENE: it's the beginning and
a very important day for them.
NENE: I hope everyone cheer for them.
Host: All right.
Please welcome the first team performing
Host: Into the New World.
YEAN: This is the last performance
in this show.
WANG KE: I need to give it my all.
WANG KE: and shoe the best performance.
RUAN: Since I got here,
I always want to be No.1.
RUAN: I think, in the final,
I want to get that No.1 spot.
RUAN: Hello, I'm RUAN.
R-JING: Hello, I'm R-JING.
LISSA: I am LISSA.
LISSA: MELISSA ANN WONSON.
YUAN KE YUAN KE,
it's almost your birthday.
DIDI: Mom, I love you.
DIDI: Thank you for taking care of me.
KRISTA SHIM: I miss my mom, my dad,
my brother and my dog.
DIDI: I really want to have a dog
that's really mine.
Even though you don't agree, I...
STAFF: Again.
DIDI: Wait a minute.
DIDI: Even though you don't agree,
DIDI: I promise I'll do my best
to take care of it.
DIDI: Now, everyone in Bangkok
is the witness.
DIDI: Everyone, do you hear it?
DIDI: Do you?
YEAN: Hi, YEAN.
YEAN: Thank you for always working hard.
WANG KE: WANG KE, you're the best.
ELYN: The Final performance
is very difficult.
RUAN: This is my second survival show.
RUAN: I thought I wouldn't cry.
RUAN: But up until today,
I've cried a lot.
KRISTA SHIM: I want to give
my best performance for the last show.
R-JING: No matter what happens,
I hope everyone enjoys my last performance.
YUAN KE: I hope
debuting is your 21st birthday gift.
ELYN: ELYN, you did well.
ELYN: I will work harder.
ELYN: I will debut.
YEAN: I don't know
if I will succeed this time,
YEAN: but I'll keep trying.
YEAN: Fighting.
WANG KE: Don't be afraid and keep going.
WANG KE: Keep walking on the big road.
Keep walking on the best road
WANG KE: because this is my new chapter.
LISSA: I've been waiting for this show
for two years.
LISSA: I will debut. Do you hear me?
YUAN KE: I miss you, dad, mom.
YUAN KE: Come celebrate my birthday
with me in Bangkok.
KRISTA SHIM: After, I wanna eat sushi
with R-JING.
R-JING: I wanna eat sushi
with KRISTA so much.
RUAN: I will debut.
RUAN: Thank you for working hard
until today.
ALL: Let's go "Into the New World"
YEAN: We've been through lots of struggles
to reach this point.
YEAN: We've been defeated,
but never given up.
WANG KE: Because we have you guys
and each other. It's our time.
WANG KE: Let's dance "Into the New World"
RUAN: ♪I want to tell you
about this sadness♪
RUAN: ♪even though I have to wait
until it's gone first.♪
YUAN KE: ♪Close your eyes
and feel my heart that's beating for you♪
YUAN KE: ♪ Look into the eyes
that's looking for you♪
DIDI: ♪Don't wait for a miracle♪
DIDI: ♪on this difficult road♪
R-JING: ♪The future
and unforeseeable obstacles won't change♪
R-JING: ♪but we can't give up♪
ELYN: ♪Please protect me with your love♪
ELYN: ♪Save my broken heart♪
LISSA: ♪Just looking at you,
I don't need any words♪
LISSA: ♪as if time stopped♪
WANG KE: ♪I love you.
That's how I feel now♪
WANG KE: ♪It's the end of all the chaos♪
WANG KE: ♪All the sadness in this world♪
WANG KE: ♪Good bye♪
RUAN: ♪In many unknown paths♪
RUAN: ♪I will follow dim light♪
DIDI: ♪We will always ♪
DIDI: ♪be side by side♪
DIDI: ♪Into the New World♪
KRISTA SHIM: ♪The loneliness
in this dark night♪
YEAN: ♪Now, please embrace me♪
YEAN: ♪I want you to know
what's in my heart♪
ALL: ♪I love you. That's how I feel now♪
ALL: ♪It's the end of all the chaos♪
ALL: ♪All the sadness in this world♪
ALL: ♪Good bye♪
WANG KE: ♪Just thinking about you
gives me strength♪
WANG KE: ♪Please stop my tear♪
R-JING: ♪Please♪
ALL: ♪These feelings
will be with me forever♪
ALL: ♪until we meet again♪
HOST: Into the New World by Group 1.
HOST: Absolutely amazing.
HOST: Are they pretty?
HOST: Are they all pretty?
MIKE: Very pretty.
- HOST: Very pretty.
- MIKE: Yes.
- MIKE: Very pretty.
HOST: What an amazing show.
HOST: Let's continue our journey. Up next,
HOST: ladies and gentlemen
for the next performance.
HOST: Mentor MIKE and mentor JEFF.
MIKE: Yes Sir.
HOST: Anything you would like to say
to them before they perform?
HOST: Any words of encouragement?
JEFF: I would say that be
relaxed and enjoy. Everybody here,
JEFF: be here to support you.
JEFF: So, whatever you do, just enjoy it.
JEFF: And this next song.
JEFF: This is going to show you
the speed of life and also the speed of love.
HOST: Love it. MIKE?
MIKE: I want to say no matter
what happens today, I wish
MIKE: you enjoy your stage and keep it
as a memorable moment
MIKE: in your life.
MIKE: And do your best in the next song.
HOST: All right. Now let's give
a big round of applause for Group 2
HOST: with their song Vroom Vroom.
- HOST: Let's go
- ILENE: This
ILENE: is the Final Stage.
QIAO YI YU: I hope in this Final Stage,
QIAO YI YU: I will be able to transfer
my energy yo everyone.
PAILIU: I'll spend the rest of my time
PAILIUJ: trying to do my best.
QIAO YIYU: Dad, mom, now your daughter
QIAO YI YU already got the 1st place
DUNA: I hope my family are healthy
DUNA: and all the seven members of CSR.
Fighting.
ILENE: Everyone, I've made it.
ILENE: I've made it to the Debut Stage.
EMMA: I will...Eh?
EMMA: I...Okay.
EMMA: I will change
from a high school girl
EMMA: to a shining idol on this stage.
PAILIU: Thank myself for being patient
and strong.
PAILIU: And thank all my fans.
LU YUTING: I know
that I'm still not good enough
LU YUTING: and a lot of people
have not seen me yet.
LU YUTING: But I want to tell everyone
LU YUTING: that I can do good both
in dancing and singing.
XUEYAO: ZENG XUEYAO, it's been four years.
You're finally going to debut.
PRAEW: Good job, PRAEW.
PRAEW: Be confident in yourself.
PRAEW: Do your best.
PRAEW: Everyone loves you so much.
XUANNING: Let me be.
XUANNING: I want to shine.
XUANNING: I can't do it anymore.
XUANNING: How can I shout?
XUANNING: I don't want it.
STAFF: Just say anything. Come on.
- XUANNING: I can't.
- STAFF: Don't move
XUANNING: Leave her be.
XUANNING: Just being pretty is fine.
Please let me be.
PAILIU: I just want to say
that I want to debut.
PAILIU: And the last thing that I'll do
in my life is that
PAILIU: I will live as happily as I can
PAILIU: and be more successful.
DUNA: I'll also be fighting.
LU YUTING: I'll go step by step.
LU YUTING: I won't stop here.
EMMA: I want to have my own concert.
XUEYAO: I'll finally be a star.
PRAEW: See you in the Final Stage.
PRAEW: Let's go.
ILENE: Let's go together. I love MINDY.
ILENE: I'll represent the Thai girls
and go as far as I can.
QIAO YI YU: You all have to be healthy.
ALL: VROOM VROOM. We can do it.
ALL: Fighting.
PAILIU: ♪Ah ha♪
PAILIU: ♪Vroom♪
QIAO YIYU: ♪Driving along.
in the night I can't sleep♪
QIAO YIYU: ♪If I don't see you,
I won't go back♪
QIAO YIYU: ♪My heart is on fire,
waiting for you to stop it♪
QIAO YIYU: ♪Ah ah ah ah ah ahhhh♪
XUEYAO: ♪I want to do things with you
until the sun rises♪
XUEYAO: ♪If you can't get up,
just lie down until dawn♪
XUEYAO: ♪It'll be another night
I've been waiting for♪
XUEYAO: ♪Ah ah ah ah ah ahhhh♪
XUEYAO: ♪Driving to meet you tonight
(night night)♪
LU YUTING: ♪No matter how far it is
(go go)♪
LU YUTING: ♪Can you wait for me there?
(Can you?)♪
LU YUTING: ♪I'll see you tonight
baby boy, baby boy.♪
XUANNING: ♪The fire in my heart
light up the way♪
XUANNING: ♪on the long road♪
DUNA: ♪If it's not fast enough,
I don't know what to do♪
DUNA: ♪No one's in front of me♪
PAILIU: ♪If you're real,
we'll meet again.♪
ILENE: ♪But if you're fake,
I'm ready to be hurt♪
ILENE: ♪It's alright.♪
QIAO YI YU: ♪Going to you like♪
QIAO YI YU: ♪Vroom vroom vroom♪
QIAO YI YU: ♪I'll speed over the miles♪
QIAO YI YU: ♪For you to love me.
Coming to you like♪
ILENE: ♪Only you and I know the answer♪
ILENE: ♪We have to meet.
That's the only way out.♪
ILENE: ♪We have to get used to it.
We have to go all the way.♪
ILENE: ♪Ah ah ah ah ah ahhhh♪
PRAEW: ♪ Going like going like
vroom vroom♪
PRAEW: ♪Do you like do you like boom boom♪
PRAEW: ♪I'll be like I'll be like
zoom zoom♪
PRAEW: ♪I'll be yours I'll be yours
toom toom♪
PRAEW: ♪I'll go no matter how far it is.
No matter how cold it is, I'll see you.♪
PRAEW: ♪I don't want to sleep. Wait.
Going to you like vroom baby vroom vroom♪
DUNA: ♪The fire in my heart
light up the way♪
DUNA: ♪on the long road♪
PAILIU: ♪If it's not fast enough,
I don't know what to do♪
PAILIU: ♪No one's in front of me♪
XUEYAO: ♪If you're real,
we'll meet again.♪
DUNA: ♪But if you're fake,
I'm ready to be hurt♪
DUNA: ♪It's alright♪
EMMA: ♪Going to you like♪
EMMA: ♪Vroom vroom vroom♪
EMMA: ♪I'll speed over the miles♪
LU YUTING: ♪Going to you like♪
LU YUTING: ♪Vroom vroom vroom♪
LU YUTING: ♪For you to love me.
EMMA: ♪Going to you like♪
EMMA: ♪Vroom vroom vroom♪
EMMA: ♪I'll speed over the miles♪
QIAO YI YU: ♪Going to you like♪
QIAO YI YU: ♪Vroom vroom vroom♪
QIAO YI YU: ♪For you to love me.
Coming to you like♪
HOST: Give it up for group 2, Vroom Vroom,
HOST: Amazing.
HOST: You're all so handsome.
HOST: This is so fired up.
HOST: I love the reaction
in the studio right now
HOST: The atmosphere now is so fired up.
HOST: and reaction from
the mentors as well.
HOST: They were awesome, right?
HOST: They were killing it.
HOST: Wow. Now the Last Battle Show
is officially over.
HOST: Can I get a big, big round of applause
for the last battle show?
HOST: Once again, please.
HOST: The last battle show
has finally over.
HOST: It's finally over.
HOST: But of course. Ladies and gentlemen,
Trainees still have one more final performance to go.
HOST: And we still have many
more surprises in store for all of you.
HOST: So do not go anywhere, all right?
HOST: Once again,
don't forget to log into WeTV app.
HOST: Visit CHUANG ASIA page
and vote for your favorite trainees. All right.
HOST: Next ladies and gentlemen,
HOST: another exciting performance
is waiting for all of you.
HOST: But once again,
each user gets 750 votes per day.
HOST: If you purchase the VIP card
through CHUANG ASIA's related activity page.
HOST: You will receive
750 extra free votes.
HOST: In the app, you can also purchase
and send love to your favorite trainees.
HOST: And earn more of votes.
HOST: Keep on watching
HOST: and see what surprise voting rules
we have for you.
HOST: Remember, keep on voting.
HOST: Next up, ladies and gentlemen,
we have a special performance for you.
HOST: Get ready to be surprised
by a rising rap star
HOST: who is taking the music world
by storm!
HOST: She's here to perform
her new song, Mirror
HOST: and Hey Hey, give it up for Milli!
♪Put your hands up in the air♪
♪Hands, come on, hands, hands♪
♪Shake ur booty shake ur ass♪
♪Shake, come on, shake, shake♪
♪Mama Apaporn lives in Nakhon Sawan♪
♪But I, Milli, live in Charanthaburi♪
♪Hey, come on, hey, hey♪
♪From now on, I ask you
everybody say 'HEY'♪
♪Hey, come on, hey, hey♪
♪Oh♪
♪Chameleon, Millipede♪
♪Oops, no, it's crocodile-dile-dile♪
♪Who has kaffir limes?
Come exchange limes♪
♪Who has a daughter?
Come exchange a son-in-law♪
♪Boys and girls♪
♪Put your hands up♪
♪Put your hands up high!♪
♪Put your hands up in the air♪
♪Hands, come on, hands, hands♪
♪Come on, hands, hands♪
♪Shake ur booty shake ur ass♪
♪Shake, come on, shake, shake♪
♪Hi Apaporn lives in lives in Nakhon Sawan
But I, Milli, live in Charanthaburi♪
♪Hey, come on, hey, hey Come on, hey, hey♪
♪If anyone hears this, please listen♪
♪Now everybody say 'HEYYY'♪
♪Watch out, Milli, yeah Watch out yo!♪
♪Okay, make a pose, work it work it♪
♪Make a turn at the count of 28,
ooh, you look fabulous♪
♪Looking so damn hot enough
to make the world melted♪
♪Mirror, please tell me
who is the most beautiful one of all♪
♪OK Lips, Hips Neck Fingers♪
♪Lemme Check On the Mirror♪
♪Minnie, what's on your face?♪
♪Ummm Maybe Beauty♪
♪Mirror Mirror Mirror Mirror
Mirror On the Wall♪
♪Who the Freakin Savage Listen Baby♪
♪YES WE ARE♪
♪Mirror Mirror Mirror Mirror
Mirror On the Wall♪
♪Who the Freakin Savage Listen Baby♪
♪YES WE ARE♪
♪YES WE ARE ARE ARE ARE♪
♪YES WE ARE YEAH♪
♪YEAH YES WE ARE♪
♪In the mirror,
I'm wearing multi-brand and multilayer♪
♪Behind me, my crew is waiting
to play multiplayer♪
♪Even though my body's covered up
with Versace's alligator♪
♪My bones are as strong
as the steel of the Terminator♪
♪Have seen myself broke,
stressed out till I had a frown♪
♪But now rising up
at the speed of a NASA's rocket launch♪
♪One more bottle and shout, cheers!♪
♪Started from the Bottom
Now My Whole Team Here♪
♪Seeing all the happiness and sadness♪
♪Seeing all the cleanliness and dirtiness♪
♪Even honesty and swearing♪
♪See the courage and the panic♪
♪Good or bad you know it in your heart♪
♪Seeing everything but the enemy,
how funny♪
♪The only one to win is myself
in the mirror♪
♪Mirror Mirror Mirror Mirror
Mirror On the Wall♪
♪Who the Freakin Savage Listen Baby
(YES WE ARE)♪
♪Mirror Mirror Mirror Mirror
Mirror On the Wall♪
♪Who the Freakin Savage Listen Baby♪
♪YES WE ARE♪
♪YES WE ARE ARE ARE ARE♪
♪YES WE ARE YEAH♪
♪YEAH YES WE ARE♪
♪Hello I'm MILLI♪
♪Changbin, F.Hero Oppa, what should I do?
What should I do? So what?♪
♪My Korean is not so good
but English and Thai I did it great bro♪
♪I knew I'm the best I knew you gonna hate
but the T R U T H♪
♪Oh! Yeah Yeah Yeah♪
♪Rap like sixteen sometimes
Rapping for fun in the house♪
♪One, two, three, four, five
Look at my teeth, say what I need♪
♪Mirror Tell Me This is me, MILLI
Richy with this music♪
♪Coz she kill this beat
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee, okay, bye♪
♪Mirror Mirror Mirror Mirror
Mirror On the Wall♪
♪Who the Freakin Savage Listen Baby♪
♪YES WE ARE (Say what?)♪
♪Mirror Mirror Mirror Mirror
Mirror On the Wall♪
♪Who the Freakin Savage Listen Baby♪
♪YES WE ARE♪
♪YES WE ARE ARE ARE ARE♪
♪YES WE ARE YEAH♪
♪YEAH YES WE ARE♪
HOST: Give it up for Milli!
HOST: Come here, girl!
HOST: Dang! You made the stage on fire!
HOST: How do you breathe?
MILLI: I'm still confused.
MILLI: I, like, no breathe at all.
HOST: No breathing at all?
MILLI: Oh, no.
HOST: That's just the best trick, right?
MILLI: Yeah.
HOST: How does it feel to be here
on this very stage?
MILLI: Wow, I'm surprised
that you guys can sing.
MILLI: For real, for real. Thank you so much that you,
like, sing along with me, rap along with me.
MILLI: Thank you.
HOST: Oh.
HOST: They really enjoy singing and rapping along with you.
MILLI: Yes.
HOST: We'll find out
HOST: who's debuting today!
HOST: Any words of encouragement? As a senior,
would you like to say something to your juniors?
MILLI: Oh, my God.
MILLI: Okay. So it's like
MILLI: Um, today, what is happening
is gonna happen.
MILLI: Whatever's gonna happen, you deserve
MILLI: everything after this.
Good food, good sleep, good
MILLI: Like massage, like Thai massage.
MILLI: You know? You deserve it.
'Cause you do your best and like
MILLI: You're doing a great job.
Keep going. I'm rooting for all of you.
HOST: Beautiful! Milli, everybody!
HOST: Thank you so much.
You're awesome, always.
HOST: Again and we'll take a quick break,
ladies and gentlemen. And we'll be right back.
Super Stay Lumi Matte
(SUPER STAY LUMI MATTE #LuminousFoundation)
Luminous Matte Foundation lasts for up to 30 hours.
(Lasts for up to 30 hours)
Comes with an airy texture.
(Airy Texture Technology)
Flawless, Smooth, and Defined. Perfect every angle.
Luminous Matte Foundation. Flawless in Any Light
Maybelline New York
(MAYBELLINE NEW YORK)
Choose what is right.
Do what you like.
Have fun and be yourself to the fullest.
Five New Colors Lolane Pixxel Hair Color Cream
chosen by JACKIE.
True colors, true self.
(NEW LOOK Lolane Pixxel Hair Color Cream #TrueColorsTrueSelf)
HOST: Welcome back, everybody.
And you are here with us once again!
HOST: CHUANG ASIA THAILAND GRAND DEBUT NIGHT LIVE
on WeTV app and channel One31.
HOST: Wow, truly an exciting day.
HOST: Truly an exciting night.
JACKSON: Truly is.
HOST: Such an exciting night.
HOST: Once again, ladies and gentlemen,
HOST: every minute that clock is ticking,
all of trainees' real-time
HOST: rankings are continuously changing.
HOST: Only top nine trainees
in the ranking will get to debut tonight.
HOST: Let's take a look at the trainees
around the crucial spot.
HOST: The crucial nine spots.
HOST: Who among rank eighth,
ninth, tenth and eleventh
HOST: will make it
into this final debut list.
HOST: JACKSON will reveal the current
rank results
HOST: for rank number eight,
nine, ten and eleven.
HOST: Please note
HOST: that the order of the announcement
did not represent their final rankings
HOST: JACKSON
HOST: Here we go.
JACKSON: Next, I will reveal to everybody
the rankings between number eight and number eleven.
JACKSON: As of today, April 6, 9 PM,
Bangkok time.
JACKSON: The trainees are...
JACKSON: EMMA
JACKSON: DIDI
JACKSON: R-JING
JACKSON: ILENE
JACKSON: So, once again,
I would like to emphasize
JACKSON: that these orders did not
represent the final ranking.
HOST: That's right. Thank you, JACKSON.
HOST: So who will ultimately make it
into Top Nine.
HOST: It depends on all of you.
HOST: I would like to remind everyone that
during our live broadcast, you can log into WeTV app
HOST: and visit CHUANG ASIA page
HOST: and vote for your favorite trainees.
HOST: Each user get 720 votes per day.
HOST: If you purchase a VIP card
through CHUANG ASIA's related activity page.
HOST: You can enjoy 750 extra free votes.
HOST: In the app, you can also purchase
and send love to your favorite trainees to earn more votes.
HOST: In addition, tonight we have prepared
a surprise for you with some extra votes!
HOST: During live today, we're giving two rounds
of free votes to all WeTV users.
HOST: The second round of free vote
giveaways starts now!
HOST: All right! We have added
an additional three hundreds
HOST: free votes in all WeTV user accounts
HOST: Please log into WeTV
and check and vote right now!
HOST: This is a final call for voting.
HOST: The final debut members
are solely determined by your votes.
HOST: So please do not hesitate to vote
for your favorite trainees.
HOST: We have now around less than
thirty minutes remaining
HOST: And we will officially announce
who will get to debut.
HOST: Every single vote counts and could make
a significant difference in the rankings.
HOST: So keep voting
and let's make the dream comes true!
HOST: All right.
Next up is the special unit show.
HOST: All right!
HOST: This special unit show is different
from the battle performance.
HOST: Because all the trainees will have
an equal chance to shine.
HOST: For this last task, all trainees
have been divided into three groups of six.
HOST: And it is now time
HOST: to see how each trainee will present
their charms
HOST: to capture your hearts.
HOST: JACKSON
HOST: Are you ready?
JACKSON: I'm more than ready.
Is everybody ready?
HOST: So let's introduce the first show.
JACKSON: Yes.
HOST: The first show...
JACKSON: will delivered
JACKSON: by RUAN, LU YUTING, YUANKE,
JACKSON: KRISTA, DIDI and WANG KE.
JACKSON: Before the show,
let's have our guest mentor, LIU YU.
JACKSON: Please step up.
Join us on the stage.
LIU YU: Wow, I think 'Say Yes' stage
LIU YU: is very bright and energetic.
LIU YU: I think today,
LIU YU: as a senior who has participated
in CHUANG ASIA before,
LIU YU: I would like to share
my experience.
LIU YU: I would like to share some tips
to my juniors.
LIU YU: The first thing is
to believe in yourself.
LIU YU: You have to say yes to yourself.
LIU YU: The second is to love the stage.
LIU YU: Say yes to the stage.
LIU YU: The most important thing is
to say yes to the people who love you.
LIU YU: I hope they will work hard
LIU YU: and make it to debut.
LIU YU: Keep going!
HOST: Keep going! Thank you, LIU YU.
HOST: For the first song of the Unit Special Show,
our trainees will take you
HOST: to a pink lovey-dovey world,
HOST: with Say Yes!
(RUAN)
MIKE: Congratulations, RUAN.
RUAN: Being the center
of CHUANGE ASIA's theme song,
RUAN: I'm very happy.
RUAN: It's a good new beginning
to challenge myself.
RUAN: Since the AUDITION STAGE,
there have been a lot of unexpected things
RUAN: and a lot of accidents.
RUAN: Many times, I thought
RUAN: God is testing me.
RUAN: If I can overcome it
and debut in the Final
RUAN: to be an idol who's accepted
worldwide,
RUAN: I'd be very happy.
MIKE: This time, your ranking is...
MIKE: 2nd place.
QIAO YI YU: Your new ranking is...
QIAO YI YU: No. 2.
RUAN: I want to be No. 1 in the Final round.
RUAN: Fighting.
(WANG KE)
WANGKE: Actually,
before coming to this show,
WANGKE: I have been through tough times
while trying to improve myself.
WANGKE: My confidence was gone.
ALL: TOP KILLER.
WANGKE: But being here,
I've got a lot of acceptance from everyone.
WANGKE: Mentors,
WANGKE: Trainees,
WANGKE: and all the fans.
WANGKE: They brought back my confidence.
WANGKE: and my inner energy.
WANGKE: Here, I got my first MVP.
WANGKE: I am in Class A for the first time.
WANGKE: Moreover, it's my first time
to be in the Top 9.
RUAN: Your new ranking is three!
WANGKE: Now, it's only one step away
WANGKE: until I reach the highest point.
WANGKE: This time,
I'll make my dream come true.
(DIDI)
DIDI: QUYANG DIDI
DIDI: Do you regret to come to this show?
DIDI: I can say that, for the past 100 days,
DIDI: I don't regret a single day here.
DIDI: I think it's the very right decision
to come here.
DIDI: What I got from here is
I realize that I love singing and dancing.
DIDI: Moreover, I gained more experience
DIDI: learned different cultures
and met good friends, like
DIDI: ELYN, QIAO YI YU.
DIDI: I'm very happy that
people are starting to understand me
DIDI: and like me more.
DIDI: Thank you so much, everyone.
DIDI: It gives me confidence
to improve myself.
DIDI: DIDI, good, good.
DIDI: Yeah!
(KRISTA SHIM)
KRISTA: I am most confident in singing.
KRISTA: Actually, I'm an introverted person.
KRISTA: I'm always in my room alone.
KRISTA: When I have to live
with 70 other people,
KRISTA: I feel like I start to be
more of a social person.
KRISTA: and I feel more extroverted.
KRISTA: and start talking with everyone.
KRISTA: R-JING
KRISTA: I've got a lifelong friend
KRISTA: that I'll never forget
and I fee like
KRISTA: I really really love
KRISTA: like the new friendship
that I made.
R-JING: You're still young.
R-JING: You're just 16.
KRISTA: I've gained more confidence.
KRISTA: I'm confident to say what I think.
KRISTA: I'm confident to dance on the stage.
KRISTA: And I'm confident in myself.
KRISTA: And I think
KRISTA: I'll never ever forget
this experience.
KRISTA: I want to sing more
KRISTA: to everyone.
KRISTA: So, I will work hard.
KRISTA: Thank you guys so much.
(LU YUTING)
LU YUTING: Hello, I'm the cool
and dedicated but stylish girl,
LU YUTING: LU YUTING. I think
the moment that I stood out was
LU YUTING: when the ranking was announced.
JACKSON: LU YUTING
LU YUTING: In every evaluation,
my ranking is high.
LU YUTING: 2nd place
LU YUTING: and 10th place
LU YUTING: and 16th place.
LU YUTING: The ranking keeps decreasing,
LU YUTING: but it's still pretty high.
LU YUTING: I know everyone has doubted me,
LU YUTING: but those experiences
will make me grow.
LU YUTING: This is a way that I can
pursue my dream again.
LU YUTING: If everyone can understand me,
I'd be very happy.
LU YUTING: I'm happy for everyone
to get to know me.
LU YUTING: But if you don't know me yet,
LU YUTING: you can try getting to know me.
YUANKE: In the AUDITION STAGE,
I got Class F. So, I was very sad.
YUANKE: Then, in the theme song,
YUANKE: I worked very hard
as I wanted to move up.
YUANKE: Even if I was disappointed twice,
I never thought about giving up.
YUANKE: So, in the first stage,
I got the MVP.
MIKE: YUANKE!
YUANKE: Thank you.
YUANKE: In Stage 2 and 3,
YUANKE: I maintained my ranking.
YUANKE: I'm more confident.
JEFF: Congratulations,
JEFF: YUANKE!
YUANKE: In the third ranking announcement,
that was the first time I was in the Top 9.
YUANKE: That moment reassured me that
I want to debut.
YUANKE: I don't want to SAY NO. So, today,
YUANKE: SAY YES with me.
♪I'm in front of you, I'm right here♪
♪Tell me with your lips Say yes, say yes♪
♪Without knowing I'm going to you♪
♪I wanna tell you my heart
with the blowing wind Love is true♪
♪Your eyes that only tickled me♪
♪Now makes me smile as if I'm used to it♪
♪My friends keep pushing me
to get closer to you♪
♪And keep telling me to walk to you♪
♪My heels are still heavy♪
♪I just wanna take it off
by the end of the night♪
♪I wish you would hold out your hand♪
♪So I can run to you barefoot♪
♪In my complicated days♪
♪I'm trying to think, each hour Hey♪
♪Now I finally realized♪
♪I will leave everything behind
and only think about you♪
♪Last spring, I saw you by coincidencе♪
♪I hope there will bе no more coincidences♪
♪I want to hold your hand
that used to only pass by♪
♪I want to walk with you,
whatever path we take♪
♪I'm in front of you, I'm right here♪
♪Tell me with your lips Say yes, say yes♪
♪Without knowing I'm going to you♪
♪I wanna tell you my heart
with the blowing wind♪
♪Love is true♪
♪I can go anywhere♪
♪This isn't a lie Yeah, yeah, yeah♪
♪From now on, by my side♪
♪Will be the most comfortable spot
Yeah, yeah, yeah♪
♪Like the sound that comes out of your lips♪
♪I wish you would call out my name
(Only that)♪
♪Even if I fall back and walk♪
♪I wish I would still hear your voice♪
♪I'm in front of you, I'm right here♪
♪Tell me with your lips Say yes, say yes♪
♪Without knowing I'm going to you♪
♪I wanna tell you my heart
with the blowing wind♪
♪Love is true♪
♪The one thing I want♪
♪Is for you to stay by my side♪
♪You smiling at me You listening to me♪
♪That's enough for me too, you♪
♪I'm smiling at you My eyes are telling you♪
♪Answer me like that too Say yes, say yes♪
♪I like it 'cause it's you
I don't care if you make me cry♪
♪Because you're my everything♪
♪Love is true♪
♪I need you♪
♪Baby, words I wanna tell you
Words I couldn't say to you♪
♪Baby baby, baby boy♪
♪Love is true♪
HOST: Well done, trainees.
Incredible performance!
HOST: MIKA
HOST: They are so sweet, aren't they?
MIKA: Yes.
HOST: Everyone, your support is crucial
and determining who will get to debut tonight.
HOST: Please don't wait until the very last minute
to use all your votes, okay?
HOST: Vote now! Vote now!
HOST: The next Special Unit Show
comes with this
HOST: sexy charming love song called
'Be Mine'.
HOST: Trainees who will be performing
this song are
HOST: ELYN, XUANNING, PAILIU,
HOST: R-JING, DUNA and YEAN.
HOST: MIKA
MIKA: Yeah. Yeah.
HOST: You perform this very song?
MIKA: Yes.
HOST: On your debut night?
HOST: How was it?
MIKA: I was really scared,
MIKA: but I'm honestly really excited
to see their version of it.
HOST: You all right?
MIKA: Yeah.
HOST: Any words of encouragement?
MIKA: I just wanted to tell
the contestants if they're listening that
MIKA: it's crazy to finally meet them
in person.
MIKA: I've just been seeing their stages
on my phone
MIKA: and if any of them are scared,
I just wanna say that
MIKA: the amount of talent they have
MIKA: is surpassed what I thought that
they would have.
MIKA: And if they are scared,
they don't have to be.
MIKA: Because the fact that
they made it this far to the show
MIKA: already means something special
that we all love.
MIKA: So what the matter
the outcomes of today,
MIKA: whatever it's good or bad,
MIKA: um, they already proved
how good they are.
MIKA: So just relax and have fun.
MIKA: And enjoy the last night on CHUANG.
HOST: I love that. Thank you, MIKA.
HOST: Now, let's welcome the girls
to the stage with the song, 'Be Mine'.
YEAN: I've been through
a lot of competitions.
YEAN: No one knows me.
YEAN: in the past 14 years.
YEAN: It's been really hard for me.
YEAN: I feel tired and defeated.
I cried every day
YEAN: before coming to this show.
YEAN: And I didn't think I'd stay
until the Final.
YEAN: Before I came to CHUANG,
I was just someone who can sing and dance.
YEAN: But now, I've improved a lot.
YEAN: I've been so far from the first day.
JACKSON: The MVP, YEAN.
JACKSON: The MVP of this group, YEAN.
NENE: The MVP, YEAN.
JACKSON: YEAN, your rank is 8th.
MIKE: And your ranking is 6th.
MIKE: Congratulations, YEAN.
MIKE: You are in the Top 3, No.3.
YEAN: I'm in the Top 3 now.
YEAN: I want to stay in the Top 3
until the end.
YEAN: Let's do our best to debut.
(DUNA)
DUNA: Hello, we're CSR.
DUNA: This is my first time in CHUANG ASIA.
DUNA: Actually, I feel a bit lonely.
DUNA: In the AUDITION STAGE,
DUNA: apart from GEUMHEE,
DUNA: the three of us got Class F.
DUNA: So when we got the song Summer Dream,
DUNA: we worked very hard
because we wanted to move to Class B.
DUNA: When we worked hard,
DUNA: everyone got moved to class B.
DUNA: It made me very proud.
NENE: DUNA
DUNA: There's only one
final performance left.
DUNA: Actually, I didn't think
I'd come this far.
DUNA: Please support me in the Final Stage
performance.
DUNA: I want to thank all the fans
for supporting me.
DUNA: Everyone gives me a lot of support.
DUNA: So, I want to give you a good performance.
(XUANNING)
(GRAND AUDITION)
XUANNING: In the Audition Stage,
XUANNING: I brought the traditional
Chinese dance to the stage.
XUANNING: I'm very proud of it.
MIKE: XUANNING, go to class F.
XUANNING: Maybe I pulled it too hard.
XUEYAO: Go to the hospital.
XUANNING: I don't like to get injected.
XUANNING: For me, this show
XUANNING: is my unlock process.
XUANNING: I'm out of my comfort zone
XUANNING: and learned how to dance
as a girl group.
XUANNING: I think it's very difficult.
JACKSON: The MVP is XUANNING!
XUANNING: To this point,
I've gradually broken my own record.
XUANNING: I feel like it's worth my time.
XUANNING: I hope, in the Final Stage,
XUANNING: I can show a new aspect of me
XUANNING: and show you a stronger TIAN XUANNING.
(ELYN)
ELYN: Hello, everyone. My name is ELYN.
ELYN: I'm a social media influencer.
(GRAND FINAL)
ELYN: Coming to CHUANG ASIA
ELYN: makes me realize that
being an idol is not easy.
MIKE: From Class B to Class F,
MIKE: ELYN
ELYN: It's like everyone's talking
ELYN: about my theme song evaluation.
ELYN: That was the first time I was
downgraded to Class F.
ELYN: It was the first time I felt
ELYN: there's a lot for me to improve.
ELYN: I've been telling myself
in every performance
ELYN: to enjoy the performance.
ELYN: Because this round is very important.
ELYN: I want to keep all my opportunities.
MIKE: Ranking No. 5.
ELYN: Now, I'm ready.
ELYN: I want to debut.
ELYN: And I want to be everyone's idol.
(R-JING)
R-JING: It's like I'm always out of sight.
R-JING: I've never been in Top 9.
MIKE: I'm sorry. You don't get to advance
to the next round.
R-JING: I'm like...
R-JING: Okay, my friends saved me.
KRISTA: R-JING
MENTOR: Congratulations, R-JING.
R-JING: It keeps pushing me.
R-JING: I don't want to disappoint anyone.
R-JING: I feel like I'm a braver person
(FIRST PUBLIC PERFORMANCE)
R-JING: since I got into this show.
(SECOND PUBLIC PERFORMANCE)
R-JING: Now, no matter how bad the situation is,
R-JING: I'm fighting.
JACKSON: The MVP is R-JING.
JACKSON: The MVP of this group, R-JING.
NENE: The MVP, R-JING.
R-JING: Next time, I'll show everyone
R-JING: That I can be the MVP
in everyone's heart
R-JING: not only for the live audience.
R-JING: I don't believe that
because I've been in the lower ranks
R-JING: means that I can't be
in the girl group.
R-JING: On the Debut Night,
anything can happen.
R-JING: I believe that I can debut.
(PAILIU)
(GRAND AUDITION)
PAILIU: All my life, I've been running to any opportunity.
PAILIU: Miss Grand Nakhon Panom.
(GRAND AUDITION)
PAILIU: When I found out about CHUANG ASIA program, I ran towards this opportunity just the same.
JACKSON: No.1. PAILIU.
PAILIU: And when I'm here,
PAILIU: I realize being an idol
PAILIU: is not easy.
NENE: 5th place. Congratulations.
NENE: 8th.
PAILIU: I may have a lot to improve
PAILIU: to prove to everyone that
PAILIU: I deserve to debut.
PAILIU: I keep asking myself
PAILIU: Am I really okay to be here?
PAILIU: In the end, I looked back
PAILIU: and asked why I wanted to be here
in the first day.
(FIRST PUBLIC PERFORMANCE)
PAILIU: Hello, I'm PAILIU.
PAILIU: And I still got the same answer
(GRAND AUDITION)
PAILIU: that I want to try this path.
(FIRST PUBLIC PERFORMANCE)
PAILIU: I want to be an idol.
(SECOND PUBLIC PERFORMANCE)
PAILIU: I want to be successful.
(THIRD PUBLIC PERFORMANCE)
PAILIU: I want to go out of CHUANG ASIA as a debut member..
♪Don't let me wake up,
I want to indulge in the deep sea♪
♪In this black-and-white world,
there's only you that are blooming♪
♪I want you to be mine
you are irreplaceable♪
♪I'll be good or bad for you Live for you
That is true♪
♪I hang all my love in the moonlight♪
♪Only just your whistle
can make the world mute♪
♪Every step you take, I can't resist♪
♪It was engraved in my memory
and was engraved deep in my heart♪
♪I want your love and stop the time♪
♪I want you to be mine. Be my Prince♪
♪My Prince♪
♪Give me your love Be my lover♪
♪Don't let me wake up,
I want to indulge in the deep sea♪
♪In this black-and-white world,
there's only you that are blooming♪
♪I want you to be mine
you are irreplaceable♪
♪I'll be good or bad for you Live for you
That is true♪
♪You will be mine♪
♪I'll be good or bad for you That is true♪
♪Love you Live for you That is true♪
♪No matter how far you go, I'll be there♪
YEAN: ♪We can understand each other
without saying a word♪
YEAN: ♪Some kind of secret code♪
YEAN: ♪Some kind of secret love♪
XUANNING: ♪I want your love
and stop the time♪
XUANNING: ♪Be mine. Be my prince♪
XUANNING: ♪Give me your love. Be my lover♪
DUNA: ♪Don't wake me up.
I want to sink into the bottom of the sea♪
DUNA: ♪In the world of black and white.
With you, it's blooming♪
DUNA: ♪I want you to be mine,
my most special one♪
DUNA: ♪Bad for you. Good for you.
Live for you. That is true♪
DUNA: ♪You will be mine♪
R-JING: ♪Bad for you. Good for you.
That is true♪
R-JING: ♪Love you. Live for you.
PAILIU: ♪The sea stops
and it's stuck in my memory♪
PAILIU: ♪If you want,
I'll change the whole world for you♪
PAILIU: ♪Tonight's the night,
I'll be down for you tonight♪
PAILIU: ♪Down for you tonight.
Let me down for you tonight♪
ELYN: ♪Don't wake me up.
I want to sink into the bottom of the sea♪
YEAN: ♪In the world of black and white.
With you, it's blooming♪
YEAN: ♪I want you to be mine,
my most special one♪
YEAN: ♪Bad for you. Good for you.
That is true♪
ALL: ♪You will be mine♪
HOST: Thank you, Trainees.
What a beautiful show.
HOST: So, so sexy.
HOST: So sexy, right?
NINE: So sexy.
NINE: Very sexy.
HOST: This is your last chance
to cast your votes.
HOST: Ladies and gentlemen, do it now.
HOST: On to the last special unit show
which will be delivered by
HOST: QIAO YI YU, EMMA, ILENE,
HOST: PRAEW, LISSA and XUEYAO.
HOST: Before the show,
let's have our Guest Mentor, NINE,
HOST: Any words of advice?
NINE: Okay.
NINE: I have a lot of things to say
to the audience and to the girls.
NINE: I'll try to be quick.
NINE: QIAO YI YU, I want to tell you.
I know you're in the back of the stage.
NINE: I hope you
NINE: believe in what you believe in.
NINE: To be in this position, I hope
NINE: you can stay in this position.
NINE: I believe you can do it.
NINE: EMMA, I see your strengths.
NINE: I think your dance is outstanding.
NINE: So, today,
you don't have to hesitate.
NINE: Just go for it.
NINE: I believe you can do it.
NINE: Then, who else?
NINE: Who else?
NINE: Oh, ILENE.
ILENE: ILENE, right?
NINE: ILENE, I know you're the youngest.
NINE: But I like your skills
NINE: and your bravery
and I want to say that
NINE: everything will bring you
to the point to want to be.
NINE: And I believe you can do it.
NINE: And PRAEW, I heard that
NINE: you got the MVP of Stage 3.
NINE: So did I.
NINE: You can definitely do it.
Do your best.
NINE: And LISSA,
NINE: because I've known LISSA
for a long time, I want to say
NINE: Fighting, LISSA. I know
you work really hard
NINE: and you try everything
and it will bring you
NINE: to the Final Stage
and the place you want to be.
NINE: I know you can do it.
NINE: Lastly, XUEYAO,
NINE: XUEYAO, do you remember
NINE: if there's a pain,
there'll be a gift.
NINE: I believe that those
who work hard will not be let down.
NINE: So, today, just go for it.
NINE: Fighting. I hope everyone
can help them reach their dreams.
NINE: Today, I hope everyone will help
NINE: make the Trainee's dream come true.
Thank you.
HOST: Thank you, NINE.
HOST: I thought about an overall advice.
You gave it to each of them. How lovely.
HOST: Last special unit is filled
with such great energy.
HOST: Let's welcome our Trainees
to the stage with the song "BEST FRIEND"
PRAEW: I feel like I'm a rocking doll.
PRAEW: Sometimes,
I doubt I'm not good enough
PRAEW: to be here.
PRAEW: I feel like I always fail.
JACKSON: MVP goes to QIAO YI YU.
JACKSON: COCO.
MIKE: This person
will get to save herself.
MIKE: PRAEW.
PRAEW: But after I failed,
PRAEW: I kept trying.
PRAEW: And in the end, the result was...
PRAEW: I got MVP.
NENE: MVP is...
NENE: The MVP of Stage 3...
PRAEW: My goal for the next performance
PRAEW: is to debut as a main dancer
PRAEW: of the debut group.
NENE: Congratulations to her
NENE: I feel like it has to be the right place and time.
Her time was the last time she got MVP.
NENE: And people saw it.
PRAEW: And I want that result
PRAEW: to take me to the debut.
EMMA: To be an idol,
EMMA: for me, is a major
turning point of my life.
EMMA: I feel like when I was in the battle
in the Audition Stage,
EMMA: I didn't know anything
but I won the battle.
EMMA: It made me very happy.
EMMA: Through hard work in Stage 1 and 2,
EMMA: it made me feel that my presence
in front of the camera
EMMA: has improved a lot.
MENTOR: EMMA.
EMMA: In Stage 3, it was the first time
I tried cute concept.
EMMA: My stage presence in front
of the camera
EMMA: has improved dramatically.
EMMA: Before this, I was a high school
student in CHUANG ASIA.
EMMA: Now, I'm a high school student
in a debut position.
EMMA: I have a dream
and I'll make it come true.
XUEYAO: In the opening performance
and theme song, I am both in Class F.
XUEYAO: In the first ranking announcement,
XUEYAO: the results show that I achieved
the same rank in my previous season.
XUEYAO: To me,
XUEYAO: it was very heartbreaking.
XUEYAO: This time, I want to leave behind
the distractions,
XUEYAO: limitations or whatever
XUEYAO: and my self-pressure
XUEYAO: and let everyone know that
XUEYAO: this time, ZENG XUEYAO
will step up her game.
XUANNING: My love, your ranking is 11th.
XUEYAO: It's like, through this path,
I've seen
XUEYAO: how I've changed from a girl
with a white uniform to a grey uniform
XUEYAO: and now I've changed
to the pink one.
XUEYAO: I am the best.
JEFF: Congratulations, XUEYAO.
XUEYAO: The biggest conclusion
XUEYAO: for me is that
XUEYAO: I've grown up
and have more stability.
XUEYAO: Of course, I can't become weak
until the last second.
LISSA: Where there's a will,
there's a way.
LISSA: But 5% out of 100%
LISSA: is your luck.
LISSA: So, I really believe in Fengshui.
LISSA: Joining the CHUANG ASIA program
LISSA: feels like I'm actually pursuing
LISSA: and seizing every opportunity
that comes my way.
LISSA: It will bring me to the dream
that I've dreamed of.
JACKSON: LISSA.
MIKE: There'll only be 26 of you
MIKE: who gets to advance
to the next round.
MIKE: LISSA, 26th.
MIKE: Congratulations.
MIKE: Today is the last elimination.
JEFF: This person loves green.
JEFF: LISSA.
JEFF: For No.17
LISSA: I hope to. I wish I could always be
the lucky girl
LISSA: and I really want to earn it
LISSA: because of me.
LISSA: In the last stage, I have to prove
to everyone
LISSA: that I deserve to be
one of the Top 9
LISSA: to debut.
ILENE: Do you want to go cheer
for a boxing match? You always scream.
ILENE: Fighting.
ILENE: Oh, my God.
ILENEL Fighting.
ILENE: Good job.
ILENE: Joining the CHUANG ASIA program
ILENE: feels like I've been given
an opportunity.
ILENE: It makes me step out
of my comfort zone.
ILENE: Moving from dancing group
to singing group is very difficult.
ILENE: And I practiced very hard.
ILENE: I feel more confident.
ILENE: My hard work from then to now,
ILENE: I think, has increased.
ILENE: I've worked so hard
ILENE: to be in the Top 9.
ILENE: All my hard work
ILENE: has paid off.
MIKE: The last Top 9... ILENE.
NENE: Congratulations, ILENE.
JEFF: Your ranking is
JEFF: No.6
ILENE: I want to show everyone
that this 15-year-old girl
ILENE: from Thailand
ILENE: can be on the Asia level.
QIAO YI YU: My name is QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: Before I came to this show,
QIAO YI YU: I was a nobody
that no one knew.
QIAO YI YU: I was lost and not confident.
QIAO YI YU: Sometimes, I'm not sure
what I'm doing here.
MIKE: B to A, QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: But every performance,
every victory,
QIAO YI YU: has given me more confidence
little by little.
QIAO YI YU: The fire in me
started to light up.
QIAO YI YU: MVP goes to QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: For the first time,
QIAO YI YU: I became an MVP.
QIAO YI YU: I became No.1
QIAO YI YU: and came in the first place.
QIAO YI YU: I've got first place
all the way until now.
QIAO YI YU: I think, from now on,
there're more first places for me to grab.
QIAO YI YU: I'll bring this energy
all the way with me to the victory
QIAO YI YU: and be the center in the end.
HOST: And that was BEST FRIEND.
HOST: Thank you all Trainees
for the outstanding performance.
HOST: Now, I'd like to officially announce
on behalf of the Mentors and the team
HOST: that all Trainees have completed
HOST: all the performances
in CHUANG ASIA 2024.
HOST: That was all the performances
HOST: Thank you, Trainees, wow. Thank you
for your hard work and your determination
HOST: on every stage that you performed.
HOST: Without the persistence,
the resilience and amazing performances,
HOST: we wouldn't have
such a memorable season.
- JACKSON: Definitely.
- HOST: Right?
HOST: And last reminder to our fans,
HOST: your time to vote is about to end.
HOST: This is your last chance
to vote for your favorite Trainees.
HOST: Whether she can debut or not,
it is up to... you.
HOST: That's right.
JACKSON: Yes and in the beginning of 2024,
JACKSON: a group of talented girls
gathered from all over the world
JACKSON: to chase their dreams
right here in Thailand.
JACKSON: With their sweat and effort,
they created their own beautiful summer dreams,
JACKSON: This extraordinary journey
will forever be precious chapter
JACKSON: and the growth and CHUANG ASIA
will always keep
JACKSON: it for you.
HOST: That's right.
Vote is about to close.
HOST: Let's witness
this important moment together.
JACKSON: Yes, we're ready.
- TEN: Yes.
- JEFF: Ready.
- JACKSON: Everybody ready?
- MIKE: Ready.
MIKE: Are you guys ready?
HOST: How about we count down together?
JACKSON: Definitely. Let's go.
MENTORS: Five, four, three, two, one.
HOST: The final voting time is up.
HOST: Thank you all.
Thank you everyone here and watching us
HOST: from across the globe.
HOST: Without you, we wouldn't have
this incredible show.
HOST: So, thank you.
HOST: Now, who will make it
to the debut tonight?
HOST: Please stay tuned.
HOST: Next, I would like to invite
another special guest
HOST: who's been a fan of our show,
HOST: They're coming right up on stage.
HOST: Yes. I gotta say
she's a big big fan.
HOST: The next special guest
HOST: has been a fan of the show.
And she's about to perform on this stage.
HOST: Are you ready?
HOST: Give it up for this song
"Burning for you"
HOST: KT KRATAE.
KRATAE: ♪Bum body body bum bum.
My body's burning for you.♪
KRATAE: ♪Body body♪
KRATAE: ♪Bum body body bum bum.
My body's burning for you.♪
KRATAE: ♪Body body♪
KRATAE: ♪Bum body body bum bum.
My body's burning for you.♪
KRATAE: ♪Body body bum bum♪
KRATAE: ♪Bum body body bum bum.
My body's burning for you.♪
KRATAE: ♪Body body bum bum♪
KRATAE: ♪I like that♪
KRATAE: ♪The way you look at me,
what are you thinking about?♪
KRATAE: ♪I know what you're thinking♪
KRATAE: ♪Ooh I do it to him everytime♪
KRATAE: ♪If you dare, come closer
and I'll say na nah♪
KRATAE: ♪I know you want my body♪
KRATAE: ♪Don't pretend to be a good boy♪
KRATAE: ♪It's easy 'cause all boys
are all the same♪
KRATAE: ♪Try harder. It's my game♪
KRATAE: ♪I know you wanna be mine now♪
KRATAE: ♪If you want it, kneel down♪
KRATAE: ♪Begging and begging me,
what can they do?♪
KRATAE: ♪Do you wanna try
playing with fire?♪
KRATAE: ♪When they say♪
KRATAE: ♪Bum body body bum bum.
My body's burning for you.♪
KRATAE: ♪Body body bum bum♪
KRATAE: ♪When they say♪
KRATAE: ♪Bum body body bum bum.
My body's burning for you.♪
KRATAE: ♪Body body bum bum♪
KRATAE: ♪I like them dumb♪
KRATAE: ♪I like them wasted♪
KRATAE: ♪I think that if they spend
their money, I'll get naked♪
KRATAE: ♪I don't want love♪
KRATAE: ♪I'll make you pay
for all the times my heart's been jaded♪
HOST: KT KRATAE.
HOST: KRATAE, Hello.
- HOST: This way, please.
- KRATAE: Hello.
- KRATAE: Can I go now?
- HOST: Not yet. Let's talk first.
HOST: Wow, the scream in the studio
is phenomenal.
- HOST: This way, please.
- KRATAE: Hello.
HOST: So amazing.
KRATAE: Thank you so much.
HOST: KRATAE, please say hi
to everyone here and who's watching live.
KRATAE: My brain cannot function.
KRATAE: I'm so excited. It's huge.
Hello, everyone.
KRATAE: Today, I'm very happy and honored
KRATAE: to make everyone happy
KRATAE: and entertain
KRATAE: CHUANG ASIA fans.
KRATAE: And I'm very impressed
by the girls. They're so talented.
HOST: I heard you've been
watching the show.
KRATAE: Well, the girls are so talented.
KRATAE: And I'm very excited to show
KRATAE: in front of the Mentors.
KRATAE: It's a very special opportunity.
KRATAE: So, I'm a little excited.
KRATAE: I've created a new show for today.
HOST: It's amazing.
KRATAE: I've never performed
this show anywhere else.
HOST: The stage was on fire.
HOST: Never performed anywhere before?
KRATAE: No.
- HOST: There was a split.
- KRATAE: A little bit.
KRATAE: Just like someone who's almost 40.
HOST: Age is just a number for KT KRATAE.
HOST: That was amazing.
HOST: But this show has a theme song.
HOST: What's the song?
HOST: Summer Dream.
KRATAE: It's like...
HOST: cute.
HOST: Yes, can I have...
HOST: Do you want to see
the KT KRATAE's version?
HOST: How about Summer Dream
KT KRATAE's version.
- KRATAE: Okay.
- HOST: Do you want it?
HOST: Alright. Music.
HOST: KT KRATAE.
KATAE: How does it turn from a cute song
KRATAE: into twerking?
HOST: We need a chair for her now.
HOST: Mentor KRATAE.
- KRATAE: Thank you.
- HOST: That was amazing.
HOST: KRATAE,
HOST: as a senior,
HOST: a senior artist,
HOST: what do you want to say to the girls
who're about to become artists?
KRATAE: Oh,
KRATAE: I don't know what to say.
They're ready to become artists.
HOST: They are ready.
KRATAE: And tonight is a special night.
It's going to change their life.
KRATAE: It's everyone's dream.
KRATAE: I want to support the girls
KRATAE: who follow their dreams like me.
KRATAE: I wish you success
KRATAE: as you wish. I'm rooting for you.
KRATAE: Everyone, please support
the new artists tonight.
HOST: Awesome. Please give
a round of applause to KT KRATAE.
KRATAE: Thank you.
HOST: Thank you.
HOST: Let's move on
to the next special show.
HOST: Next performance is ready as well.
HOST: Her voice is said to be
healing to the soul.
HOST: Her dream also started
on CHUANG Stage.
HOST: Please welcome our beloved Mentor,
with the song "ALL TO MYSELF"
HOST: NENE.
HOST: Thank you, NENE. You're awesome.
HOST: Wow. Her voice really
HOST: healed our soul, right?
HOST: No doubt she's the mentor.
And it's so inspiring that
HOST: not long ago, she's on the stage
as one of the Trainees and now,
HOST: she's back on this very stage
HOST: as one of the Mentors
and such an amazing artist.
HOST: Now, on to the next performance,
HOST: also, another amazing one.
HOST: As you can hear from the crowd,
his voice,
HOST: world class.
HOST: He's ready to deliver
one of his songs
HOST: and that is "GHOST"
HOST: Give it up for JEFF SATUR.
JEFF: ♪When I see you,♪
JEFF: ♪I know immediately
that in your heart,♪
JEFF: ♪there's nothing left.
Then, you said you dreamed of marrying♪
JEFF: ♪Now, in your eyes,
I can only see a goodbye♪
JEFF: ♪It's alright♪
JEFF: ♪I know and I understand.
You've packed♪
JEFF: ♪all the things
and all the feelings♪
JEFF: ♪and all the memories.
You may not need them anymore♪
JEFF: ♪Don't tell me you're leaving♪
JEFF: ♪Don't tell me you're crying♪
JEFF: ♪I'll count to ten. Go hide
and don't every come back♪
JEFF: ♪If it's not you, it's alright♪
JEFF: ♪Don't stay just to wait
for the day to leave♪
JEFF: ♪Wherever you are, I won't find you♪
JEFF: ♪Ah ah won't find you♪
JEFF: ♪If it's not you, it's alright♪
JEFF: ♪I hope you have a life
that you're looking for♪
JEFF: ♪I'll hide all the happiness
of the past♪
JEFF: ♪When I open my eyes,
I hope you're not there♪
JEFF: ♪It's tiring to chase you.
When will it stop?♪
JEFF: ♪I asked myself. You hide, I seek
and you come back♪
JEFF: ♪It's just a delusion♪
JEFF: ♪that's stuck in time.
If you wanna go,♪
JEFF: ♪I'll understand. I'll move on.♪
JEFF: ♪Don't doubt
no matter what you hear,♪
JEFF: ♪keep walking. No matter
how loud it is, it's not me crying♪
JEFF: ♪Don't tell me you're leaving♪
JEFF: ♪Don't tell me you're crying♪
JEFF: ♪I'll count to ten. Go hide
and don't every come back♪
JEFF: ♪If it's not you, it's alright♪
JEFF: ♪Don't stay just to wait
for the day to leave♪
JEFF: ♪Wherever you are, I won't find you♪
JEFF: ♪Ah ah won't find you♪
JEFF: ♪If it's not you, it's alright♪
JEFF: ♪I hope you have a life
that you're looking for♪
JEFF: ♪I'll hide all the happiness
of the past♪
JEFF: ♪When I open my eyes,
I hope you're not there♪
♪ I hope I won't see your face
when I open my eyes ♪
♪ I'll hide my sadness ♪
♪ by saying that's okay ♪
♪ I'll hide you deep down to my heart ♪
♪ no matter how much I've cried.
I won't find you ♪
♪ It's okay if I'm not with you ♪
♪ You don't have to stay to say goodbye ♪
♪ No matter where you are,
I won't find you ♪
♪ Won't find you ♪
♪ It's okay if I'm not with you ♪
♪ I hope you have a life
you're wishing for ♪
♪ I'll conceal all the happiness
from the past ♪
♪ I hope I won't see your face
when I open my eyes ♪
HOST: Jeff Star, everybody!
HOST: You're out of this world.
Mentor, can you join us on stage once again?
HOST: Wow, my man. Awesome.
HOST: Please come.
HOST: Jack also sang alone.
Truly amazing.
HOST: That's why he is a mentor, right?
Mentors.
HOST: Truly an exciting night,
HOST: we're here to watch the very end
of CHUANG AISA.
HOST: And the girls are about to
welcome the moment of glorious summer.
HOST: Mentors, anything you would like
to say to them?
HOST:
I'm sure they're all listening right now.
HOST: Take your time because we're still
gathering the scores and rankings.
JACKSON: I'm sure
they're listing to us right now.
JACKSON: I just wanna say like toniight
JACKSON: It's the beginning for them.
The top nine will be born.
JACKSON: And I think it'll be
the start of our history.
JACKSON: The start of our history
and it's the beginning I hope that
JACKSON: whatever happens down the road,
JACKSON: never forget what's the reason
why you started
JACKSON: to love music.
JACKSON: You know?
To love dancing and singing.
JACKSON: And keep your identity
and find your true color.
JACKSON: That's it.
HOST: Love that. P'Jack, everybody.
HOST: Of course.
HOST: Never forget why you started.
HOST: in the very beginning
and your own identity,
HOST: That's really who you are, right?
HOST: It's a daily reminder.
HOST: Mike.
MIKE: It's been many months
MIKE: since all the trainees
have joined us here
MIKE: and performed on this stage.
I'd like to say that
MIKE: No matter what happens,
MIKE: in this upcoming future,
MIKE: who's going to debut or not
MIKE: just keep fighting.
MIKE: And those who can debut,
MIKE: I'd like to say that
the path you'll walk on,
MIKE: it's not going to be easy
MIKE: but I want you to remember that
the first day you joined us here
MIKE: what's your dream
and what do you want to do to achieve?
MIKE: I want you all to keep fighting
and wish you all good luck.
HOST: Thank you, MIKE.
HOST: TEN, please.
TEN: I'd like to tell all the trainees that
since the first day until now,
TEN: I'm so proud when I saw
you all on the stage. You're growing up
TEN: and making a huge progress.
TEN: I want you all
TEN: to remember that
TEN: Every time you're on the stage,
don't forget to enjoy
TEN: the stage that you're performing,
TEN: because if we don't enjoy,
TEN: the audience won't feel it.
I want you all
TEN: to remember this and...
TEN: Every time you're on the stage,
please give it your all
HOST: Right? Even though
there's some pressure or excitemnt,
HOST: but don't forget
to enjoy every bit of it.
HOST: JEFF, please.
JEFF: I'd like to say that
JEFF: tonight is the debut night,
JEFF: but not only for
those who get to debut
JEFF: as international girl group,
JEFF: but those of you who didn't have
a chance to debut, those of you're here too.
JEFF: I just wanna say that
JEFF: this is also a debut night for you
JEFF: because you're going to go on
and do your things, do you work.
JEFF: Being an artist as you want.
JEFF: You're going to find your stage,
JEFF: and tonight is that night.
JEFF: So, whatever happens,
JEFF: don't say it's because of luck.
JEFF: don't say because of
whatever, whoever.
JEFF: You deserve everything.
JEFF: And I'd say that I'm...
don't forget to thank yourself too.
JEFF: Because you've come this far
because of yourself.
JEFF: And also to the fans here
JEFF: that come to support you that I'm...
JEFF: at their houses too.
Just... I wish you the best in the world.
JEFF: Thank you.
HOST: Thank you JEFF.
HOST: NENE, please.
NENE: Hello, ladies.
NENE: So, tonight is tonight
and the one thing that I want to remind you,
NENE: myself also.
As a friend, as your sister,
NENE: as your mentor, is that
NENE: don't question yourself.
NENE: don't doubt yourself.
NENE: Whether you've made to debut or not,
NENE: even you have a feel like,
"why not me?"
NENE: "why I'm so unlucky?"
NENE: I want to say that
failure paves the path to success.
NENE: And because of the sadness,
NENE: then you know
how the beauty of the happiness is.
NENE: So, believe in yourself
and the world will believe in you.
NENE: Good luck.
HOST: That gives me goosebumps as well.
HOST: Awesome, aewsome.
HOST: Right? It's not easy
to achieve the success and the failure
HOST: is not the opposite thing.
Actually, it's a component.
HOST: No one achieves success without
experiencing failure along the way.
HOST: Right?
HOST: Failure is not
the opposite of success.
HOST: Failure is part of success.
JACKSON: Right.
HOST: You know?
JACKSON: I'm also curious about
what does the guest mentors think.
JACKSON: Cause I guess
it's like life is the first time seeing
JACKSON: all the trainees performance.
JACKSON: So, I really wanna ask MIKA.
JACKSON: What do you think?
What do you have to say to the trainees?
HOST: Okay, thank you so much.
HOST: Thank you, MIKA.
MIKA: I understand your feelings.
MIKA: Because I was standing
on the same spot three years ago.
MIKA: And I know
all of you are probably nervous,
MIKA: you really wanna debut.
MIKA: Your life is about to change
if you do.
MIKA: But honestly,
no matter which direction that goes,
MIKA: I really think
you all should not be worry.
MIKA: You all came here,
came this far to the show.
MIKA: You've made these many fans.
All people support you no matter what happens.
MIKA: they'll continue to support you.
MIKA: And you can keep on trying,
MIKA: you have as many chances
as you want
MIKA: don't worry.
MIKA: I think you guys are all amazing.
MIKA: So, good job.
MIKA: You've made it here.
JACKSON: Thank you.
HOST: Thank you, MIKA.
JACKSON: What about MILLI?
JACKSON: You think
I'm not gna choose you, huh?
JACKSON: Too late. What do you think?
MILLI: Hello.
HOST: This is live.
JACKSON: You have to say to
final trainees.
MILLI: Okay.
MILLI: I think like this is not...
whatever the result will happen,
MILLI: this is not the end of your career.
MILLI: This is your passion, right?
MILLI: Don't turn it to be like,
MILLI: Just only today.
MILLI: You have tomorrow always
and like...
MILLI: I'll always support you.
MILLI: This is your passion,
just do it, going on, keep going with it.
MILLI: Don't give up.
You deserve everything.
MILLI: And whatever
the result is going to happen tomorrow,
MILLI: You promise me
to have a good Thai massage.
JACKSON: Yeah.
MILLI: Please. You deserve that.
JACKSON: It's going to be sponsored by We TV.
MILLI: Please. Sponsored by JACK. Thank you.
JACKSON: Yes.
JACKSON: No!
JACKSON: Okay it's okay.
JACKSON: What about LIU YU?
JACKSON: What do you have to say
to all the final trainess?
LIU YU: Okay, You all can hear me.
LIU YU: We've all came this far,
nothing is important anymore.
LIU YU: But the most important thing is that
you need to think carefully about the next segment of speech.
LIU YU: This part is so important,
do you remember?
LIU YU: And because the results
have been decided,
LIU YU: so, there's no need to worry.
LIU YU: There are many stages
awaiting your performance.
LIU YU: So you must cherish every opportunity
on stage in the future.
LIU YU: After becoming part of this group,
you must unite together.
LIU YU: Because I feel that each member
LIU YU: has put in too much effort
for this group.
LIU YU: So you must work hard
and enjoy every moment on stage. Good luck.
HOST: And what about KATAE?
KATAE: Hello.
KATAE: Well,
KATAE: I'm also those who keeps fighting.
I'll keep fighting unil
KATAE: I'm out of energy.
But I always tell myself that
KATAE: I won't run out of energy
if I haven't tried to make my dream come true.
HOST: Thank you so much.
HOST: NINE.
HOST: Same question.
NINE: Now it's my turn.
NINE: Hello.
NINE: So, I'm going to speak English then.
NINE: Cause when I was on our final stage,
NINE: I was so nervous too
NINE: that I was thinking
what if I can't debut.
NINE: But then I promised myself
always that
NINE: There're so many things
that you actually have to believe in.
NINE: First, you fans.
NINE: Second, the people who love you.
NINE: Third, yourself.
NINE: Like NENE said,
don't ever doubt yourself never.
NINE: And just like MILLI said if today,
NINE: we don't have the results
that we wanted,
NINE: we still have tomorrow.
Like as always.
NINE: So, it's okay
if anything is going to happen.
NINE: Just love yourself a lot more.
And believe that
NINE: we have new opportunity tomorrow.
NINE: Fighting!
HOST: Fighting. Thank you, NINE.
JACKSON: Oh, tonight we have NINE and TEN.
JACKSON: NINE and TEN.
NINE: Big bro, Hi.
JACKSON: Add a Wechat.
TEN: I love that.
HOST: NINE and TEN.
HOST: Any EIGHT in the house?
JACKSON: He is 17.
HOST: Mentors, how do you feel
get to be mentors in this season?
JACKSON: Starting from me?
JACKSON: I feel like it's an honor and...
JACKSON: I'm glad that I can share
what I've been through
JACKSON: since the trainees
to group to the solo.
JACKSON: We're on the same street
but I'm just a little further up.
JACKSON: I'm honored agian
JACKSON: to share all these experiences
and what I've been through.
JACKSON: good and bad with you guys.
JACKSON: And you guys are very talented.
JACKSON: I can't wait for stages
of your performances.
JACKSON: That's my experiece.
HOST: I love that. JACK, thank you.
HOST: JACK. MIKE.
MIKE: I'm so happy to be a mentor
MIKE: for CHUANG ASIA this season.
MIKE: I've met you guys
and witnessed all the progress you've made.
MIKE: I've seen amazing shows
from you guys.
MIKE: I hope that everyone
MIKE: will keep trying and fighting.
I'll always support you.
HOST: Thank you.
HOST: TEN.
TEN: I'm happy to be
TEN: a part of your story
TEN: since the first day to now.
TEN: I'm not sure
how much I've helped you.
TEN: But I'm so happy to be
TEN: a part of your journey.
HOST: JEFF.
JEFF: Yes.
JEFF: Actually, I feel
JEFF: emotional and
JEFF: I'm proud of them.
JEFF: Becoming a mentor
JEFF: is one of my dreams
JEFF: to have a chance
JEFF: to guide them in things like
JEFF: I want new generation kids,
who want to be an artist,
JEFF: know that
JEFF: there're many things,
there's freedom
JEFF: to create art.
JEFF: So, it's my honor to be here.
NENE: I'm so happy to be a mentor
in this show since I've been here so long
NENE: for about 4 years.
NENE: I have a chanceto share many things
NENE: including experiences.
NENE: And I'm also happy
to be a part of those
NENE: who can encourage everyone.
NENE: I'm not the best of all.
NENE: I don't have
all the knowledge in the world.
NENE: But one thing that I always have
is I keep fighting and I always pursue dream.
NENE: I feel like
NENE: that is so important.
NENE: And I want you all
to pursue your dream.
NENE: Because effort can never hurt anyone.
HOST: Thank you mentor
for inspiring words.
HOST: It's almost time
to announce the final results.
HOST: Which nine trainees will get to debut
and start the new journey
HOST: as the first international
girl group of CHUANG ASIA THAILAND.
HOST: We'll be right back.
HOST: Welcome back, everyone.
HOST: You tune in for CHUANG ASIA THAILAND
grand debut night live
HOST: on WeTV app channel on 31
HOST: Our talented trainees
have sucessfully completed their training.
HOST: and are now officially graduated.
HOST: Big applause to yourself.
HOST: Great job.
HOST: And the moment
we've been waiting for have arrived.
HOST: Get ready to witness the birth
HOST: of the new international girl group
as we're about to find out
HOST: the top nine trainees
who will get to debut tonight.
HOST: It's time to unveil the start
HOST: of the first international girl group
journey to start on.
HOST: It's time. Ladies and Gentlemen,
HOST: we'll be reviewing
each rank one by one.
HOST: Starting with announcing
rank number eight.
HOST: and number seven.
HOST: Let's welcome mentor NENE
on the stage.
HOST: to announce the first member
of the debut group.
HOST: NENE.
HOST: The result is in her hand.
HOST: And now I'll announce
rank number eight.
NENE: This person possess a delighful style.
NENE: charm, freshness
and youthful energy.
NENE: She fights her heart in every stage,
NENE: determine for her passion.
NENE: Even though in the third elimination
was not in the Top nine.
NENE: But she said
she's very proud of herself
NENE: for doing such a good job.
NENE: Congratulations.
NENE: She won 48,184,212 votes.
NENE: And she is...
NENE: DIDI.
HOST: Congratulations, DIDI.
HOST: Please make your debut speech.
DID: Hello, everyone. I'm DIDI.
DIDI: I'm so happy to be here.
DIDI: and being able to be
in the debut group.
DIDI: and be with all my friends.
DIDI: Thank you to all the fans for their support,
I'm here because of you guys.
DIDI: And standing here,
DIDI: I also want to thank my family.
DIDI: My mom, sister, and everyone.
My dad is in the back stage.
DIDI: Thank you
for giving me such long legs,
DIDI: Allowing me to face
everything with confidence.
DIDI: And to my cousin over there,
I love you Sharon.
DIDI: And I wanna say something
to my fans. Thank for supporting me.
DIDI: My little sunshine.
DID: Thank you for supporting me.
DIDI: I'm so happy. Thank you so much.
DIDI: And starting from today.
DIDI: Please expect to see
DIDI: Kind, pretty, slim,
DIDI: dance well, sing well. DIDI
DIDI: I just debut! Thank you.
HOST: Congratulations, DIDI!
HOST: Please proceed to your position.
HOST: Ladies and Gentlemen,
the first to debut, DIDI!
HOST: Congratulations once again.
Up next.
HOST: NENE, please.Announce rank number seven.
NENE: And now I'll announce rank number seven.
NENE: she has been....
NENE: stiving to prove herself
NENE: over an extended period of time.
NENE: This girl was one of the bottom class
of the competition.
NENE: And now she successfully
rises to the top nine
NENE: since she has competed in the show.
NENE: Her ability has been proven.
NENE: She's ready to debut in the show
NENE: Congratulations,
NENE: she won 48166903 votes.
NENE: And she is...
NENE: XUEYAO.
HOST: Massive congratulations.
Please have your debut speech.
XUEYAO: Hi, everyone.
I'm number seven. XUEYAO.
XUEYAO: I promise that
XUEYAO: that I'll be
XUEYAO:
XUEYAO: I want to thank
my most important fans,
XUEYAO: Thank you for giving me
infinite love and encouragement
XUEYAO: And countless days and nights
of companionship,
XUEYAO: You're the reason I'm standing here
and to been seen by everyone.
XUEYAO: Thank you to the production team
for providing me with a stage to make my dream comes true.
XUEYAO: Thank you to my company,
thank you to my manager,
XUEYAO: for giving me firm encouragement,
allow me to have the courage.
XUEYAO: So I want to say to
everyone who supports me,
XUEYAO: From now on,
XUEYAO: I will always remember my dream,
XUEYAO: keep on pursuing my dreams,
XUEYAO: I will always be
XUEYAO: the XUEYAO worthy of your love.
XUEYAO: Thank you, love you guys!
HOST: Congratulations, XUEYAO.
HOST: Please proceed to your position.
HOST: In your position.
HOST: There you go.
Rank number seven. XUEYAO.
HOST: We've now announced two ranks.
HOST: Let's continue
to rank number six and number five.
HOST: JEFF, please do the honor.
JEFF: And now I'll announce rank number six.
JEFF: She's an exceptional
JEFF: strong-will person.
JEFF: She travels to pursue her dreams
JEFF: without giving up and to fight..
JEFF: She's the master
of facial expression,
JEFF: paying great attention
to every detail on the stage.
JEFF: She once said that
throughout the past
JEFF: the light never reached her.
JEFF: But today
JEFF: the spotlight has shined on her.
JEFF: Congratulations, she won
JEFF: 49,296,773 votes.
JEFF: And she is...
JEFF: WANGKE.
WANGKE: Everyone, I just debut!
WANGKE: I want to thank everyone
who has always supported me.
WANGKE: Thank everyone
WANGKE: for loving me.
WANGKE: Thank you so much, everyone.
WANGKE: It's like making my dream
of the summer come true.
WANGKE: And I know there will be many more challenges
ahead of me in the future.
WANGKE: But I'm not scared.
WANGKE: But I'm not scared of
whatever will come after that
WANGKE: because I think I have you guys
and I trust myself that
WANGKE: I can do everything,
I can overcome everything.
WANGKE:
WANGKE: Thank you.
HOST: Congratulations, WANGKE.
Please proceed to your position.
HOST: Congratulations.
HOST: JEFF, let's continue with
rank number five.
HOST: And now I'll announce
JEFF: At these there was a controversy
whether she can be an idol.
JEFF: She bravely faced the challenge,
JEFF: and embrace everyone
with her bright smile and hardworking.
JEFF: She's a trainee
who learns Thai very quickly.
JEFF: Even tough she once sang,
JEFF: Why is Thai language so difficult?
JEFF: Congratulations.
JEFF: She won 49,983,314 votes.
JEFF: And she is...
JEFF: ELYN.
ELYN: Hello, everyone.
ELYN: Thank you to my fans
for choosing me to debut.
ELYN: Thank you so much
for showing me love.
ELYN: I want to thank the program team
ELYN: for giving me this stage
to showcase myself.
ELYN: And I want to thank my mom and dad.
ELYN: My mom is over there.
ELYN: Mom, I can do it now.
ELYN: I'll do the best
for the group, for me
ELYN: and for everyone who loves me.
ELYN: And to my Thai fans,
ELYN: I can do it now
ELYN: and Thai language
is not hard at all.
ELYN: Thank you.
HOST: Congratulations, ELYN.
HOST: Please proceed to your position.
HOST: There you go.
Rank number five, ELYN. Eveybody.
HOST: We've now completed
from rank eight to five.
HOST: I'd like to invite mentor MIKE.
HOST: Please announce
rank number four and three.
MIKE: And now I'll be announcing
rank number four.
MIKE: She surprised everyone
with her strong vocal in the beginning.
MIKE: Despite not being
the center of times,
MIKE: she still manages to win every week.
MIKE: She has been rising up her rankings
in the past three eliminations
MIKE: and she wants to say that she wants to
debut in the main vocal position.
MIKE: Congratulations,
MIKE: She won 49,983,314 votes.
MIKE: And she is...
MIKE: YEAN.
YEAN: Hello, everyone.
YEAN: I'm YEAN from Thailand.
YEAN: Thank you all my fans
YEAN: who have been voting for me.
YEAN: Thank you, Mom,
YEAN: for supporting me all along.
YEAN: Thank you, everyone.
YEAN: I've been trying hard for 14 years.
YEAN: I...
YEAN: Today I realized that
there're many people
YEAN: who tried to walk on
the same path with me
YEAN: In this journey,
I won't be alone anymore.
YEAN: Thank you, KS GANG company,
for supporting me.
YEAN: Thank you all my friends
and CHUANG ASIA.
YEAN: Thank you, We TV.
YEAN: Thank you, Barbie gang.
YEAN: Team Panta.
YEAN: Panda, Vita
YEAN: The bread brand that
YEAN: encourages me
to improve my dance skill.
YEAN: Thank you so much, everyone,
for voting me.
YEAN: I'm really happy
to have you guys stay by my side.
YEAN: Today, I just debut!
HOST: Congratulations, YEAN.
HOST: Please proceed to your position.
HOST: Rank number four. YEAN, everybody.
HOST: MIKE, please announce
rank number three.
MIKE: Now I'll be announcing
MIKE: She's the person
who wants to fulfill her childhood dreams.
MIKE: She proves herself in the top nine
throughout the competition.
MIKE: In her stage, three performances,
MIKE: she puts her singing ability
to the limit.
MIKE: She showcased her determination
and passion for excellence.
MIKE: Today, she wants everyone
to remember
MIKE: that she's more of an idol
than the beauty queen.
MIKE: Congratulations.
MIKE: She won 50,093,565 votes.
MIKE: And she is...
MIKE: PAILIU.
PAILIU: Thank you all for the votes.
PAILIU: And...
PAILIU: For today, yes,
I've dreamed since I was little.
PAILIU: And today is something
exceeded my dream.
PAILIU: And I want to tell those
who have dreams.
PAILIU: I want everyone
PAILIU: to follow your dreams
even though we may not be good enough,
PAILIU: but just follow your dream.
PAILIU: Just like when I joined
the Grand competition,
PAILIU: they all said that
I was not born to be the beauty queen,
PAILIU: I was born to do something else.
PAILIU: But in the end, I can prove that
PAILIU: I can be the beauty queen.
And same as this stage.
PAILIU: In just four months,
I may not have enough time
PAILIU: to prove myself
to make you all believe
PAILIU: in myself 100%
but 3 years after my debut,
PAILIU: I'll prove to everyone
PAILIU: see another version of myself
PAILIU: that actually,
PAILIU: I can be an idol too. Thank you.
HOST: Congratulations, PAILIU.
HOST: Please proceed to your positions.
HOST: Ladies and Gentlemen,
PAILIU and rank number three.
HOST: And now it's time to announce
one of the most crucial ranks,
HOST: rank number nine.
HOST: We have with us our Mentor TEN,
HOST: and our producer, KAICHEN LEE,
to announce it.
HOST: TEN.
TEN: Okay, lucky TEN will now announce
the lucky girls.
TEN: Who'll become the luckiest girl.
TEN: in this important moment?
KAICHEN LI: Luck is a way of finding those
who never give up
KAICHEN LI: and those
who always give their best.
KAICHEN LI: And today,
KAICHEN LI: she has showed that
she deserves
KAICHEN LI: more than just a bit of luck.
TEN: Okay.
TEN: And now I'll announce
rank number nine.
TEN: She maybe young
but her talent shines brightly.
TEN: She loves dancing with her heart,
every move she's made,
TEN: on this stage
captivate the audience attention
TEN: She's here with the clear goal
TEN: She wants to bring
her high school spirit
TEN: into her debut.
TEN: Congratulations.
TEN: She won for 47,756,160 votes.
TEN: And she is...
TEN: EMMA.
EMMA: Hello, everyone. I am EMMA.
EMMA: Hello I am EMMA.
EMMA: Actually, I thought
I'm not good enough to debut.
EMMA: But thank you all my fans.
EMMA: Because of you guys,
today I've made a debut.
EMMA: I...
EMMA: I forgot.
EMMA: Thank you so much.
Audience: EMMA.
EMMA: Thank you, it's over.
HOST: EMMA, congratulations.
HOST: Please proceed to your position
HOST: Rank number nine, EMMA, everybody.
HOST: Now we still have
two more important ranks left.
HOST: And after this break,
HOST: we'll announce the most
anticipated ranks.
HOST: Rank number one and number two.
HOST: we'll be right back.
HOST: Welcome back.
HOST: And now you're watching
CHUANG ASIA THAILAND grand debut night.
HOST: Live in WeTV app and channel One 31.
HOST: Now we only have two positions left
for our debut group.
HOST: And we're about to review
for the center position.
HOST: We have with us our co-producer
Lead mentor, JACKSON WANG.
HOST: to announce the final trainees.
HOST: The first and the second place winner
for the debut group.
JACKSON: In my hands are the name of ranks
number one and number two.
JACKSON: And who would they be?
JEFF HAN: So, from over 10,000 applicants,
JEFF HAN: and after months of hardwork,
they've finally proven themself today.
JACKSON: They're...
JACKSON:
In all three rankings announcement,
JACKSON: She has never dropped out
of the Top nine once.
JACKSON: She wins every competition
JACKSON: and adapt herself
to every style of music offered.
JACKSON: She once said
JACKSON: She alway felt like a nobody.
JACKSON: But this time,
she's finally being seen.
JACKSON: And among the trainees,
JACKSON: She's the most handsome
in CHUANG ASIA.
JACKSON: She is...
JACKSON: QIAO YI YU.
JEFF HAN: She's the person
who's extremely hardworking and determined.
JEFF HAN: She's gained a lot of attention
JEFF HAN: with a lot of pressure on her.
JEFF HAN: And this is her second time,
JEFF HAN: participating in the survival show.
JEFF HAN: She's determined to debut.
JEFF HAN: And she is...
JEFF HAN: RUAN.
HOST: Both trainees, please step forward.
HOST: Ladies and Gentlemen,
one of these two young ladies
HOST:
will be the center of the debut group.
HOST: Let's hear it from JACKSON.
JACKSON: The trainees
who ultimately received the center
JACKSON: in CHUANG ASIA THAILAND
JACKSON: has received a total of
JACKSON: 80,796,328 votes.
JACKSON: Congratulations to
JACKSON: QIAO YIYU.
JEFF HAN: Yes.
JEFF HAN: And at the same time,
we also congratulate RUAN.
JEFF HAN: She has received a total of
54,331,403 votes
JEFF HAN: Congratulations, RUAN.
Ranking number two.
JEFF HAN: Ranking No. 2!
HOST: Congratulations.
HOST: RUAN, please give your debut speech.
RUAN: Hi everyone, RUAN.
RUAN: I get to debut!
RUAN: Thank you for believing in me.
RUAN: Believe in me and support me
to the end.
RUAN: I always wanted to debut.
RUAN: I'm very happy that I made it
to debut this time.
RUAN: Please continue to follow me.
RUAN: Today, my mom comes here.
RUAN: I finally made it to debut!
RUAN: Thank you
to everyone who supports me.
RUAN: Thank you CHUANG ASIA and my family.
RUAN: I'll do my best.
Please continue to support me.
HOST: Congratulations, RUAN.
HOST: Please...walk to your position!
HOST: Ladies and gentlemen,
RUAN at rank No. 2!
HOST: And of course,
congratulations to QIAO YI YU.
HOST: Please give your debut speech.
QIAO YI YU: Hello, everyone.
I'm No. 1, QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: Mom and Dad,
are you seeing this?
QIAO YI YU: Your daughter did it!
QIAO YI YU: Thank you to all the fans
who voted for me.
QIAO YI YU: If it weren't for you, I wouldn't be able
to stand here so bravely and confidently.
QIAO YI YU: Thank you to all the Mentors.
QIAO YI YU: Thank you
all the CHUANG girls here
QIAO YI YU: and over here.
You guys are the best!
QIAO YI YU: Thank you to all the staff,
both onstage and offstage.
QIAO YI YU: This journey
has been really difficult.
QIAO YI YU: I just want to say.
QIAO YI YU: My new journey's just started.
QIAO YI YU: I want to make you guys
proud of me.
QIAO YI YU: So,
QIAO YI YU: I'll be a better QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: Thank you, everyone.
HOST: QIAO YI YU,
please walk to your center position.
HOST: There you have it.
Ladies and gentlemen, congratulations to
HOST: all the members of the debut group!
HOST: QIAO YI YU, RUAN, PAILIU, YEAN,
HOST: ELYN, WANG KE, XUEYAO, DIDI and EMMA!
JACKSON: Thank you for all the fans
and audience who were accompanying us
JACKSON: in this amazing journey.
JACKSON: Uh, the first international
girl group of CHUANG ASIA is finally born!
JACKSON: The brand-new journey
is about to begin,
JACKSON: filled with excitement
and endless possibilities.
HOST: Yes! And I'm sure you'll continue
HOST: to support them as they're embarking
on their next chapter.
HOST: All right! JACKSON
JACKSON: It's time to reveal the name
of our debut group.
HOST: Are you ready?
HOST: Let's check it out.
ALL: Hello.
VO: With the support of their fans,
VO: these inspiring young girls
have transformed their Summer Dream
VO: into reality.
VO: They have blended
nine unique inspirations.
VO: And they are ready
VO: to conquer every stage they greet.
VO: The name of CHUANG ASIA's first
VO: international girl group is...
VO: Genles
HOST: Welcome to the very first debut
performance from Genles!
HOST: Genles, everybody! Let's hear it!
HOST: We are thrilled to announce that
Genles's official fanclub will launch on WeTV app
HOST: at the end of April.
HOST: Fans can intensely recieve
HOST: exclusive photos, videos
and update news
HOST: about Genles and can send
direct messages
HOST: to your favorite members.
HOST: Stay tuned for our fanclub
HOST: and once again,
HOST: Congratulations to Genles
for their debut tonight! Whoa!
HOST: Genles embodies the essence
of inspiration,
HOST: magic and dream comes true.
HOST: Transforming the Summer Dream
into reality
HOST: with all your support.
And these inspiring young girls
HOST: have blended
the nine unique inspirations
HOST: as a girl group.
HOST: Get ready to be captivated by them
HOST: and as they conquer
every stage they greet.
HOST: Everyone. Mentors, Guest Mentors
and all of the special guests.
HOST: Please join us on this very stage.
HOST: Let's join Genles. Let's go!
TRANIEE: Genles
TRANIEE: Genles?
HOST: Let's go! Let's go!
HOST: Wow, such a beautiful moment.
HOST: We have finally come to the end.
HOST: This moment that we have been
waiting for
HOST: has finally come.
HOST: We have already revealed
the name of our debut group.
HOST: Genles
HOST: Please stay tuned
for more exclusives.
HOST: Super exclusives.
HOST: Everybody makes some noise
for Genles!
TRANIEE:R-JING
HOST: Can you believe it, guys?
HOST: Our wonderful journey
HOST: for the past four months
has reached its destination.
HOST: Best friend.
That's what friends are for.
HOST: This shows that if you don't give up,
HOST: anything can happen.
JACKSON: Also, at the same time, we would like
to say thank you so much to all the audience.
JACKSON: You know, show them passion
and show them love, support
JACKSON: to the trainees and to Genles.
Thank you, guys. Thank you.
HOST: Thank you. This is apparently not
the end.
HOST: But rather the beginning
of many more beautiful memories
HOST: that we'll create together
in the next chapter of CHUANG ASIA.
HOST: And for now, I'd like to thank
HOST: each and every one on stage.
HOST: Starting off
with our special guests tonight,
HOST: MILLI!
HOST: KATHY KRATAE!
HOST: And of course, we were joined
by our guest mentors, LIU YU!
HOST: Give it up for MIKA!
HOST: Let's cheering for NINE!
HOST: And of course, our Mentors,
MIKE ANGELO!
HOST: Give it up for TEN!
HOST: Put your hands together
for JEFF SATUR!
HOST: Make some noise for NENE!
HOST: And of course, ladies and gentlemen,
HOST: This would not happen
without the Co-Producer
HOST: and the Lead Mentor,
give it up for the one and only
HOST: JACKSON WANG!
HOST: And let's hear it
for all the girls here!
HOST: And from the top of your lungs,
ladies and gentlemen, give it up for
HOST: Genles!
JACKSON: We forgot. We forgot one person.
JACKSON: Ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for
JACKSON: Bam!
HOST: I love you always.
Thank you. Thank you.
HOST: Wow. Thank you once again.
HOST: Well, I'd like to hear
how everyone is feeling.
HOST: QIAO YI YU,
how do you feel right now?
HOST: You're the center.
You're rank No. 1.
QIAO YI YU: Feels like unreal.
HOST: Unreal?
QIAO YI YU: Unreal.
HOST: It's real! Let me tell you!
QIAO YI YU: I'm gonna get used to it.
HOST: It feels like a dream.
But you're not dreaming. Right, everyone?
HOST: This is real. Once again,
give it up for Genles. Everybody!
TRANIEE: Genles
HOST: I can't wait
for all the amazing performances.
HOST: And now, the CHUANG ASIA THAILAND
GRAND DEBUT NIGHT LIVE
HOST: has come to an end.
HOST: Thank you all.
I mean this will not happen
HOST: without each
and every one of you here.
HOST: We've got like six hundred,
seven hundred group of people here.
HOST: The crowd is amazing.
Thanks to all of you.
HOST: And thank you each and every one
who are watching this live from
HOST: so many countries across Asia
and the entire globe.
HOST: Thank you so very much.
Thanks to you!
HOST: Hope to see you again next time!
HOST: Goodbye! Bye bye.
Brought to you by trip.com
Your one-stop travel app
Maybelline New York
Superstay Lumi Matte Foundation
New! Pepsi Zero Sugar Orange
Fizzy with No Limit. Try now!
Five New Colors Lolane Pixxel Hair Color Cream
chosen by JACKIE.
True colors, true self.
The trainee's autograph and unreleased photo
by CHUANG ASIA RISING STAR CARDS at modian.com