(The third stage grouping)
MIKE: Let's be more exciting.
MIKE: Congratulations to the 29 of you
MIKE: for making it to Stage 3.
MIKE: Today, we'll be making
song selection for Stage 3.
MIKE: And for this stage,
there'll be a special arrangement.
MIKE: Each group performance will be
accompanied by a special guest artist.
MIKE: Are you guys excited?
TRAINEES: Yes.
MIKE: We will be having
five songs altogether with five guests.
MIKE: There'll be four songs
that require six members
MIKE: and one song
requires only five members.
NENE: Are you ready to listen to the song?
YUAN KE: Yes.
NENE: Let's start with
the first song for this stage,
NENE: a cute Korean dance song from TWICE.
TRAINEES: Oh, TWICE.
NENE: WHAT IS LOVE?
WANG SHENG XI: WHAT IS LOVE?
NENE: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
LISSA: This song is the song
that impresses me the most, WHAT IS LOVE?
LISSA: It's a mixture
LISSA: of what I haven't done
in the show yet.
MIKE: Next, we have a playful Pop R&amp;B song
TRAINEES: R&amp;G song?
MIKE: called NIGHT RIDE.
ILENE: WIN METAWIN, wow.
LILIANA LI: It has the prop
and everything.
PAILIU: Aw, that's cute.
JAOYING: NIGHT RIDE catches my attention
because it looks like...
JAOYING: there's a little bit
of storytelling and musical.
JAOYING: So, an acting student like me
wants this song.
JAOYING: I feel a little bit
of theater in it.
JEFF: So, we have a sweet love song
straight from CHUANG 2021.
NENE: Okay. It's that song
PUSH NO.5 FOR CUTE INPUT METHOD.
NENE: The song from the last season.
YEAN: I know.
NENE: This is a very cute song.
- PAILIU: JEFF.
- JASMINE: JEFF.
NENE: Next song. We move to the next song.
NENE: This is one of our mentors' songs.
LILIANA LI: I gotta do this song.
ILENE: JEFF.
JASMINE: Aw. Oh.
TRAINEES: I know this song.
PAILIU: I've always thought
PAILIU: if there is a stage
with JEFF's song,
PAILIU: I would definitely go for it.
JEFF: Too sexy.
- YEAN: JEFF, are you gonna dance this?
- ILENE: JEFF, are you gonna dance this?
JEFF: Nope. Nope.
NENE: It's gonna be another guest.
- MIKE: It'll be a guest.
- NENE: Yes.
MIKE: Okay, the last song,
MIKE: also from one of our mentors.
- PRAEW: MIKE.
- YEAN / ILENE: TEN?
MIKE: NIGHTWALKER.
MINGMING: All the five songs
are very good.
MINGMING: I like all of them.
ILENE: DUM DUM or NIGHTWALKER?
MINGMING: I can't choose.
ELYN: I told myself that I want to
try something new.
ELYN: Don't stay in my comfort zone
for too long.
ELYN: I'm going for DUM DUM.
MIKE: Now that everyone
has seen all five songs.
MIKE: Like the last time,
MIKE: the Trainee with the highest ranking
gets to choose first.
MIKE: But for this time,
MIKE: the Top 5 members
MIKE: will automatically become
the center of each song.
TRAINEES: No chance.
MIKE: There'll be no competition or vote
for the center position.
MIKE: But it also means that
MIKE: the Top 5 Trainees cannot be
in the same team.
PAILIU: Oh, cannot be in the same team.
WANG KE: Top 5 cannot be in the same team?
DIDI: Yes.
YEAN: I feel like it's fair
YEAN: because the fans vote for them
to get high ranking.
YEAN: So, they can have the right
to choose the songs
YEAN: and be the center.
R-JING: I feel like this rule
is not fair for anyone.
R-JING: The fairest would be...
R-JING: No.1. That's it.
R-JING: The others don't get to choose.
Only No.1 can choose.
R-JING: Or do I have to be No.1?
R-JING: Even if it's hard, it's worth it.
MIKE: Top 5 Trainees, please step forward.
- MIKE: Ready?
- RUAN: Yes.
MIKE: Let's start with our Top 1,
QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: Of course, I feel a bit good
because a lot of people who saw the demo
QIAO YI YU: told me that
they know which song I'm going to choose.
QIAO YI YU: So, I asked them "Do you
really know it? I might surprise you."
NENE: Oh, I'm surprised.
TRAINEES: I'm shocked.
NENE: I'm so shocked.
PAILIU: I'm surprised
- WANG KE: She likes it.
- PAILIU: Really?
WANG KE: Yeah.
MIKE: We are already so surprised
by your choice.
QIAO YI YU: Because in my Audition Stage
QIAO YI YU: and my first stage,
it was already my comfort zone.
QIAO YI YU: It's handsome. It's cool.
QIAO YI YU: And now it's Stage 3,
QIAO YI YU: I want to
give the audience a surprise.
- MIKE: Good choice, by the way.
- NENE: Okay.
- QIAO YI YU: Thank you.
- MIKE: Good choice.
MIKE: Top 2, RUAN.
- R-JING: They switch.
- MINGMING: They switch.
RUAN: Switch.
RUAN: People normally call me
a cute hamster
RUAN: or something cute.
RUAN: But this time,
I'll show RUAN that's cool,
RUAN: RUAN that's been through a lot
and can do everything.
RUAN: I want to be in the Top 1 with that.
MIKE: Alright. WANG KE.
WANG KE: My song.
WANG KE: I love it.
JEFF: Good choice.
PAILIU: I'm so sad that I don't get it.
ELYN: WANG KE.
ELYN: I think you should have it.
WANG KE: I also like JEFF's song.
MIKE: ELYN, your turn.
ELYN: My choices are
PUSH NO.5 FOR CUTE INPUT METHOD
ELYN: and NIGHT RIDE.
ELYN: Actually, I don't know NIGHT RIDE
ELYN: buy I know
PUSH NO.5 FOR CUTE INPUT METHOD
ELYN: because I've heard of it
when I watched CHUANG.
ELYN: I think this song
ELYN: is very sweet. So, I...
MIKE: Okay. Here we go.
MIKE: PAILIU, you have no choice.
PAILIU: The girls already chose
the other songs. This is the only one left
PAILIU: but I'm not sad
that I get this song
PAILIU: because I think it's my fate
PAILIU: that will make me prove
and challenge myself.
NENE: Next, Top 6 to Top 9,
NENE: you can choose
whichever song you want.
NENE: Please come down
and make your song choice.
MIKE: Starting from YEAN.
YEAN: Actually,
I really wanted to choose DUM DUM.
YEAN: I hesitated for a long time but...
YEAN: But when I thought about it again.
I felt like
YEAN: my mom would hit me.
YEAN: It's too sexy. My mom would hit me.
MIKE: EMMA.
RUAN: Same?
TRAINEES: What?
MIKE: Oh, WHAT IS LOVE?
EMMA: How does it not suit me?
MIKE: Alright. Next, KRISTA.
PAILIU: Finally, someone to help me.
KRISTA: Yeah.
MIKE: ILENE, last one.
JEFF: So, now, as you see,
there're many spots here.
JEFF: But unfortunately,
JEFF: the trainees, you can't choose.
JEFF: All the remaining Trainees
can't choose the song.
JEFF: But you have to wait for the Top 5
to invite you instead.
TRAINEES: Oh, JEFF.
TRAINEES: That's crazy.
- R-JING: Again.
- MINGMING: We can't choose.
R-JING: I never get to choose.
MIKE: We're so sorry, guys.
It's just the rule.
MINGMING: At that point, I and R-JING
turned to each other and said
MINGMING: we don't get to choose again.
MINGMING: and we were blank.
R-JING: I never get to choose.
NENE: Oh, they're begging.
ILENE: I looked at WANG KE
and her face was like...
ILENE: "What can I do? Who should I pick?"
ILENE: I'm worried for her.
RINKA: I can only wait for the others
to pick me
RINKA: which I may to wait until the end
RINKA: and can't choose the song
that I want.
RINKA: I think it's very cruel.
LILIANA LI: PAILIU.
LILIANA LI: PAILIU
PAILIU: Who called me?
TEGAN: I can learn Chinese fast.
TEGAN: PAILIU.
TEGAN: You hear me?
PAILIU: Okay. I hear you.
TEGAN: Okay.
JEFF: So, now it's time for Top 5
to make some choices again.
JEFF: You will now get the privilege
to choose who you want to perform with
JEFF: and invite them to join your team.
JEFF: One by one,
JEFF: you can choose anyone
remaining on the ranking stand.
JEFF: We will start from Top 1 to Top 5.
JEFF: Top 5, are you ready?
QIAO YI YU: Yes.
JEFF: YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: DIDI.
JEFF: RUAN.
JASMINE: RUAN, I want NIGHTWALKER.
JASMINE: I want either DUM DUM
or NIGHTWALKER
JASMINE: because I've never tried
this style.
JASMINE: I gave my signal
to the other groups that I don't want.
RUAN: XUEYAO.
JEFF: WANG KE.
WANG KE: WANG SHENG XI.
ILENE: XIXI.
JEFF: Next, ELYN.
ELYN: JAOYING.
MIKE: PAILIU.
R-JING: I sent my signal to PAILIU.
R-JING: I believed she'd see my eyes.
R-JING: I was like... PAILIU, choose me.
R-JING: My eyes said that.
PAILIU: TEGAN.
MIKE: Congrats, TEGAN.
R-JING: That looks bad.
MIKE: Alright, that's five.
MIKE: Then, back to QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: RINKA.
RUAN: PRAEW.
MIKE: Congratulations.
MIKE: And then...
JEFF: WANG KE.
JEFF: Trainees, stand still.
WANG KE: MINGMING.
ILENE: MING.
YUAN KE: I'm actually a little worried.
YUAN KE: I think I have a lot of pressure
YUAN KE: because I know
YUAN KE: that the song
that I want the most is DUM DUM.
YUAN KE: But I'm afraid
if I don't get chosen,
YUAN KE: I have to go with another song.
YEAN: Look at LISSA, I can see "No."
JEFF: LISSA, don't move your head.
ELYN: ACARE.
MIKE: Congratulations, ACARE.
MIKE: PAILIU.
R-JING: PAILIU, choose me.
R-JING: I believed she heard me.
PAILIU: R-JING.
R-JING: Thank you.
TEGAN: Welcome. Welcome.
KRISTA: Team, team, team.
R-JING: I was so nervous.
MIKE: LILIANA, you look nervous. Why?
What's wrong?
LILIANA LI: It's fine. We can continue.
MIKE: Go back to QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: LISSA.
TRAINEES: Is it full?
RUAN: CAITH.
MINGMING: CAITH.
CAITH: RUAN.
R-JING: LILIANA.
PAILIU: We'll take LILIANA and...
- KRISTA: NINNINT.
- R-JING: And who?
PAILIU: NINNINT.
R-JING: Okay.
MIKE: WANG KE.
WANG KE: Who can sing? You can sing?
- MINGMING: Yes.
- ILENE: She can sing.
WANG KE: Okay.
TRAINEES: Okay.
WANG KE: YUAN KE.
- ELYN: JASMINE?
- YEAN: JASMINE, no.
JEFF: JASMINE, what are you doing?
PAILIU: LILIANA wants to come here.
YEAN: LILIANA wants that song.
ELYN: LILIANA.
TEGAN: No.
LILIANA LI: The song that I didn't
want the most was the song that I got.
LILIANA LI: I didn't choose.
LILIANA LI: My heart dropped.
LILIANA LI: Now, I know how it felt like
for most of the people in ZULU PAKA TAPA HEY.
LILIANA LI: I'm so happy.
JAOYING: Really?
JAOYING: Really happy?
LILIANA LI: You did so well, LILIANA.
MIKE: PAILIU.
PAILIU: NINNINT.
MIKE: Okay.
QIAO YI YU: Does anybody here
give me an eye contact?
DIDI: No one.
TRAINEES: No one.
QIAO YI YU: Okay.
MIKE: QIAO YI YU.
QIAO YI YU: JASMINE.
JASMINE: I didn't want this song at all.
JASMINE: I still don't want it until now.
JASMINE: I'm selling my cuteness again.
JEFF: Okay, RUAN.
JEFF: The last member of your team,
NIGHTWALKER.
RUAN: LU YUTING.
LU YUTING: Okay.
- RUAN: Fighting. Okay?
- TRAINEES: Fighting.
RUAN: Fighting. Okay?
RUAN: Okay?
MIKE: Alright, WANG KE.
XUANNING: I felt disappointed.
XUANNING: I thought I was too bad
or I wasn't good enough.
XUANNING: Or they didn't trust me.
XUANNING: You know? It's those feelings.
WANG KE: XUANNING.
YUAN KE: My love.
MIKE: We still have DUNA, right?
R-JING: Please give DUNA to us.
JAOYING: Just discuss.
PAILIU: You have LILIANA.
R-JING: You already have LILIANA.
- YEAN: Main vocal.
- TEGAN: I told you.
MAMCÙ: Who would be happy
to get picked last?
MAMCÙ: Of course...
MAMCÙ: No matter what,
a person standing on that big place
MAMCÙ: is depressing.
JEFF: There're gonna be MAMCÙ and DUNA.
ELYN: I can choose now?
JEFF: Yeah, you can choose now.
ELYN: DUNA.
- JEFF: Okay.
- LILIANA LI: DUNA.
MIKE: DUNA is gonna be in NIGHT RIDE.
TRAINEES: DUNA.
- JEFF: And of course.
- MIKE: MAMCÙ.
JEFF: You're gonna be with PAILIU.
R-JING: It's fine. It's okay.
R-JING: MAMCÙ, my vocal.
MIKE: Congratulations.
WANG SHENG XI: This song is very good.
TEGAN: You can be a teacher.
TEGAN: Teacher.
KRISTA: We meet every stage.
MAMCÙ: Every stage.
R-JING: It's Chinese.
MIKE: Alright, everyone.
MIKE: Now that we have completed
all the five songs,
MIKE: remember that we'll be having
five special guests performing with you guys.
MIKE: Good luck, guys.
MIKE: And see you guys on Stage 3.
- JEFF: See you.
- NENE: See you.
- TRAINEES: See you.
- JEFF: Good luck.
NENE: Good luck.