(E Ji Ah)
(Kang Ki Young)
(Oh Min Suk)
(Queen of Divorce)
What's wrong with you?
Aren't you sending the flowers away?
I'll just take them.
Noh Yul Seong sent them.
He wants to marry me again.
Who?
Noh Yul Seong?
So?
I'm going to...
go back to his house.
I'll make him go to prison.
Are you going to live as his wife again?
No, I'm going to trick him.
As if I became his wife.
My goodness.
This is too much. You know, right?
Staking everything. If we fail, it's the end.
There's no other way.
There is another way.
I told you we're starting from Na Yu Mi's taxi driver again.
If that were to work,
it should've worked when you were investigating as a prosecutor.
You don't believe in me.
No, I mean...
Professor Seo killed himself right after Na Yu Mi's case started.
So you got fired, and all stopped.
We are trying to reinvestigate, but all the clues are gone.
So,
what can you do in his house?
On the day my mom passed away,
I'm going to find out who was sitting next to her.
If that was Noh Yul Seong,
or if there's another person behind this.
What if you fail?
What's the end of this remarriage?
I don't think about anything impossible.
I only think about something possible.
Noh Yul Seong!
What's going on?
- Stop it now. - Let this go.
Don't mess with Sa Ra.
Let it go. Aren't you letting this go?
Don't worry and leave.
There'll be no such thing as remarriage.
- Mother. - Go back...
and tell her to stop being greedy to take over my house.
You should also...
keep an eye on your son.
So that he doesn't attempt to seduce Sa Ra.
Leave now.
Did you come to our office that day?
I saw you.
On the day Sa Ra's mother passed away.
Is it weird for a lawyer to visit the prosecutor's office?
You're trying to remarry her...
to hide the fact that you met her mom there.
It's impossible not to have a reasonable doubt.
Your imagination is immoral.
Oh, immoral?
I think you're very capable of it.
Wait. Hey.
Why are you so worked up?
Is there any good news that I'm not aware of?
Sa Ra.
Let's sit and talk.
Aren't you leaving?
I'm getting nervous.
Sa Ra,
what do you want to tell me? What brought you here?
Let's do this. Remarriage.
Good.
It is typical of you. You're straightforward.
But why?
Why did you suddenly change your mind?
You treated me like an irredeemable troublemaker.
I decided to only think of Seo Yun.
Will I have Kim Young A on my side?
I'll do my best.
Anyone can do their best.
We're professionals. You should prove it.
Never mind, then.
Let me meet Kim Young A.
Then, I'll trust you.
I'm afraid that if I feel sorry, I will stop doing this.
I'm sorry...
that I can't even apologize.
(Divorce Specialist SOLUTION)
You said you had something to say, but what is this nonsense?
Are you resigning?
No, only for two months.
I need a vacation.
So why?
Are you burnt out?
Actually,
I'm remarrying...
Noh Yul Seong.
- Ms. Kim. - Ms. Kim.
What's gotten into you? Are you sick?
This isn't right.
I'm creating a solution for myself this time.
The solution code is Kim Sa Ra.
Gosh, I disagree.
We should follow the majority decision.
Wait. Where is Lawyer Dong?
Call him first.
I already told him.
How can you do this if you aren't insane?
No pain, no gain.
Everyone says you can't achieve it without going crazy.
That doesn't mean you should go this crazy.
I'm full of dopamine now.
So please support me.
This is not a solution. It's a suicide bomb.
Let me listen first. What's your plan?
It's a grand fraud show for Chayul Law Firm.
First, I need to make Noh Yul Seong to trust me.
He must trust me unequivocally...
so that he won't have any suspicion of me having something up my sleeve.
It's quite surprising.
You managed to make plans with Kim Young A willingly.
Not willingly, but barely.
Did you tell her our situation? What did she say?
Ask her yourself.
She's here.
Ms. Kim!
Thank you for coming.
I need to congratulate you first.
Your remarriage.
Did you hear that I disagreed a lot with her decision?
Did you?
Didn't you know that I dislike you?
I'm ashamed.
But I still came here. That must tell...
how hard I'm working to recruit Sa Ra.
Anyway, let's talk about the Law School Act next time.
We should have a congratulatory party today.
Of course.
Let me fill your glass, ma'am.
Where are they?
On the second floor.
Chairwoman Cha.
Inside, there is...
What are you...
Oh, you're here.
Please say hello. She's my mother.
Hello.
I'm sorry. I came to the wrong room.
I came to earn a favour from Sa Ra.
We'll invite you somewhere nicer next time.
- Please enjoy. - Thank you.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
I enjoyed tonight.
I hope you'll get home safely.
What should we do?
Shall we reserve a hotel and arrange our wedding?
Forget that, and just sign the papers.
(Remarriage Contract)
What's this?
A remarriage contract?
You're cute.
We need to officially register our marriage. Okay.
Kim Sa Ra is responsible for childcare. Okay.
Three million dollars for alimony in case of divorce? This is absurd.
I can't be kicked out empty-handed again.
- One million dollars. - Forget it.
Two million dollars.
But it's under the condition of you...
cooperating in the Chayul Town plan.
Sign it and send it over.
Okay.
I'll get going.
Search and seizure?
Lawyer Dong!
(Search and Seizure Warrant)
Kim Sa Ra, you have been reported...
for violating the Attorney Law Act by handling legal affairs...
and referring a lawyer, despite not being a lawyer.
Let's get started.
- Passing through. - Passing through.
What about Lawyer Dong Gi Jun?
There is suspicion that he shared profits with you.
You know that is subjected to criminal penalties, right?
Let's start from that side.
Is this because you conducted the consultation?
Legal consultation is only allowed when one has a lawyer's license.
Since I always accompanied you, that's okay.
How about the accounting part?
It's clean.
If they issued a search and seizure warrant,
it means the police have something.
What could it be?
So why were you so greedy?
Did you report us to the police?
Do you understand what will happen when you try taking Chayul Law Firm?
Are you blackmailing us?
I heard you two had something, so I thought you would intervene.
But I'm very disappointed, Lawyer Dong.
Please stop.
Stop what you're doing for everyone.
Then, I'll resolve this situation.
Let's clean up.
Gosh. How long has it been since our last date?
I feel butterflies in my stomach, which I find funny.
Stop right now.
Stop what?
Chayul Law Firm is working...
to suspend Lawyer Dong's lawyer's license.
- It's not me. - Convince her.
Or else, there's no remarriage.
Are you trying to cancel our remarriage...
because of Lawyer Dong?
My co-workers in SOLUTION are against our remarriage.
Everyone is trying to convince me to stop,
and honestly, it's exhausting.
There's no need to increase hostility in the midst of this.
I want to restart with support.
You're the only one who can make that possible.
Ms. Kim!
There's a fake account on the seizure list of our office.
What do you mean by fake account?
We never had such a thing.
Someone left it in the office.
I'll search for the CCTV records.
Ms. Kim, you need to see this.
The main board for the CCTV is gone.
They didn't delete the footage, but just took the whole thing?
They know...
that we have someone to recover the deleted data.
Why was the search and seizure only done on the first floor?
Don't you think it's weird?
What are you talking about?
I'm searching the second floor myself.
Wait! Whose permission do you have?
Mine.
Let it go.
Why do spies always leave something behind?
Is it because they're anxious about how they will be used?
We will file charges for trade secret infringement...
and obstruction of business. Be prepared to face legal action.
I salute your capability.
But Yul Seong and you don't match well.
You know that, right?
Were you his girlfriend?
Why? Did the chairwoman say she'd accept you?
Well, it depends on how well I do.
(Cashbook)
Why are you giving me this mission?
If you're not confident, don't.
Could I also have an opportunity if I do well?
Does this mean that?
It depends on what you think.
You're not obsessed...
with Mr. Noh, are you?
You go ahead and be obsessed all you want.
Get out.
Manager Jang was the culprit?
We won't need to worry about the police.
Are you sure you want to go to that house despite all this?
Reconsider one last time.
Don't become...
Noh Yul Seong's wife again.
We've always...
quarrelled over the solution methods.
Right?
Right. Well, if that's the case,
I'll leave SOLUTION.
Won't your husband be bothered if we work together?
Aren't you the one feeling bothered?
You know that, and you're using this as a solution?
I just don't get it.
I won't be able to congratulate you...
or root for you.
I'm off.
Are you really going to be like this?
Where are you going without us?
Ms. Kim.
I can't agree with a solution that hurts and damages...
the client.
Whether it be body, soul,
and even promises. Anything.
I'll see you again.
Lawyer Dong.
As you have asked, we have prepared a separate room.
Thank you, Ms. Lee.
Hello, Chairwoman Cha.
Why is she standing before me?
Who let her in my house?
I told you.
She will be living with us starting today.
What's this?
Mr. Noh sent this to me today.
That is why I moved in.
(Reunion Contract)
(Name: Kim Sa Ra, Name: Noh Yul Seong)
(Name of child: Noh Seo Yun)
(If a divorce occurs due to one's liability,)
(two million dollars must be given as alimony.)
You sign this piece of trash and call yourself a lawyer?
An alimony?
Just think of it as funds for lobbying.
That will make life easier.
I will head to my room.
Wait just a little longer, Mom.
Whenever you miss your mom, dial number one...
and tell her everything you want.
(The Amazing Law Firm, coming soon)
(Taxi driver of the incident)
(Suspicious points from Na Yu Mi's case)
(Taxi Driver's License, Name: Gong Deukgu)
(Congratulations, Amazing Dong Gi Jun)
Gosh, the name is just "amazing."
Oh, you're here.
This is my seat. And you will sit over there.
What? I won't accept you.
I mean, I can't. I can't pay you two.
Ms. Son told us to help you...
while Ms. Kim is on her break.
Oh, Ms. Kim is doing well.
Right.
I see.
You haven't eaten, have you?
(San Francisco)
Seo Yun!
Mom!
My gosh!
- Have you been well, my son? - Yes.
- I missed you so much. - I missed you too.
Am I going home with you now?
You will continue to live with me from now on.
I will make sure to make that happen.
Okay, Mom.
I won't have you at the same table.
It will be hard to set the table twice, Chairwoman Cha.
I will join in.
I'll just have some salad, please.
Mother,
it has been a while since our family has gathered.
Who are you calling a family member?
Why did you come back?
I feel like I'm finally breathing...
because I can be with Seo Yun.
So that's the only reason you came back?
Then you two should share the same room.
Then I will trust you.
Well,
we've already talked about that too.
She said she needed some time, so I agreed with her.
We'll take care of this matter on our own, Chairwoman Cha.
Big Madam and Small Madam.
Come on. Let's get along with each other.
Keep it down for us, Mother.
Seo Yun is with us too.
Bring out some fruit.
- Yes, ma'am. - No.
You bring it out yourself.
Yes, ma'am.
Is this an ancestral rite?
Was this not it?
Are you messing with me?
It has been too long since I've cut any fruit.
But Chairwoman Cha, why did you ask me to do it?
You wanted to be treated like a daughter-in-law.
That's not it. You're doing this on purpose to get a hold on me.
Treat me like a guest.
A daughter-in-law is also a guest that appears once every 100 years.
Are you trying to teach me?
No, I'm not. I'm just asking for your favour.
When you ask a guest to do housework,
I wish you would...
feel at least a little bit sorry.
Gosh. You didn't get hit by the apple?
She must have a bit of a headache...
wondering how to deal with me.
What if she finds you suspicious?
Chairwoman Cha is someone who finds people suspicious all the time.
I must use Noh Yul Seong who has put put his guard down as a shield.
Gosh. I will never be able to do that.
So what's going to happen now?
Next...
The day my mom died,
October 31 of last year.
I have to trace Chayul's trails of that day.
The computer in Chairwoman Cha's study...
is connected to the secretary's office.
It possesses the Chairwoman and CEO's schedule.
(Chayul Law Firm)
(Chayul Intranet)
(Senior Management Schedule)
A1 is Chairwoman Cha's schedule.
A2 is Noh Yul Seong's schedule.
(November, 2023)
(A2 Schedule Content)
(October, 2022)
Mom went to the prosecution at around 2pm.
Let's see.
(Chayul Town Field Investigation)
He wasn't there?
(A1 Schedule)
(November, 2023)
(A1 Schedule Content)
(Assemblyman Kim Suk Woo's Publication Party and Reception)
I wasn't told that you would come back early.
The house hasn't been cleaned yet.
It's fine.
(Turn off computer)
Grandma!
You were home, Seo Yun?
Come with me, Grandma.
Where are we going?
Gosh.
(The Amazing Law Firm)
Dae Gi. Is there something outside?
Do you feel happy?
- Yes. - My goodness.
Ms. Kim went back in just thinking about Seo Yun.
She'll be okay, right?
She's with her best source of strength.
She'll manage to survive.
As of right now, he's the only witness of the Na Yu Mi case, right?
This taxi driver.
Na Yu Mi's case must be solved...
for Sa Ra's mother's case to be solved.
My body is feeling a bit heavy. Shall I do a bit of exercise?
Gosh, Kang Bom. Going undercover again?
(Taxi Driver's License, Name: Gong Deukgu)
My job ends here.
You can do well, right?
Shall I bring back my skills after a while?
I'll be right back.
May I help you?
This credit card was on the ground. Is this yours?
It doesn't seem to be ours.
I see.
It isn't Noh Yul Seong.
- Then? - It's Chairwoman Cha.
No way.
You thought about it, right?
I'll go with two million dollars.
It isn't even a safe place.
I have to have that much as a deposit.
If you call me back to Korea, I will pay you back.
You're going to spend all of it at the racetrack.
I've been keeping the secret about your orders against Na Yu Mi.
Even from CEO Noh Yul Seong.
Of course.
Once that gets revealed, it's prison for you.
There are people tracing this case.
Leave the country before they come without saying a word.
Are you not getting off?
Chairwoman Cha has gone out to play golf.
She will be back after dinner.
Okay.
Someone must be here.
The team leader of transportation from Chayul...
is speaking with the CEO.
At home and not the office?
I believe it to be something urgent.
Do you know who Chayul's team leader of transportation is?
I'll look it up. Give me a moment.
But why?
I need to check something.
Oh, it's this guy.
He was Chairwoman Cha's driver.
You must not know him because he came in after you left.
Thanks.
Hello!
Why do you look so surprised?
Hello.
You know me.
You're CEO Noh's wife.
What brings you here?
Your sneakers.
They feel very familiar.
Oh, these.
CEO Noh wore them and gave them to me as a gift.
I see.
You may leave. I'll see you again.
(Amazing Dong Gi Jun)
My gosh.
We don't have iced Americanos here.
I like coffee sticks too.
Is that so?
How is it here?
I guess.
How are things there?
Somewhat.
Why did you come here? Your husband might have put a tail on you.
I'll just say I came because I missed you.
Tell him that if you get caught.
I want to see the CCTV footage of my mom again.
- It's this guy. - What?
Who is it?
Chayul's team leader of transportation.
He was Chairwoman Cha's driver.
How could you tell? You can't really see his face.
These sneakers. I remember them because they were a limited edition.
Hold on.
This is a photo of him.
They're the same sneakers, aren't they?
Hold on.
Take a look at this.
This is a photo from the house of the taxi driver...
that drove Na Yu Mi.
Why are these there?
Come this way.
Here. Is it this guy?
- Yes. It's him. - His name is Gong Deukgu.
This guy was Na Yu Mi's taxi driver?
And the one with my mom?
(Taxi Driver's License, Name: Gong Deukgu)
Does that mean he's the culprit?
Probably. We spotted Gong Deukgu meeting with Chairwoman Cha.
May I help you?
Give me a moment.
I checked Chairwoman Cha and Noh Yul Seong's schedule...
of that day.
Chairwoman Cha didn't go to the prosecution that day.
What about Noh Yul Seong?
At around 2pm when my mom went to the prosecution,
he was at a field investigation and meeting for Chayul Town.
Hold on. If it's 2pm for Chayul Town...
No. He was at the prosecution at that time.
Noh Yul Seong changed up his schedule.
He followed a separate schedule of his own.
Then let's sort things out.
In both Na Yu Mi and your mother's case,
one person, Gong Deukgu, is involved.
Behind that, there's Noh Yul Seong and Chairwoman Cha.
We do not know how each of them were involved.
Gong Deukgu will know.
If we hear from Gong Deukgu,
we can solve both cases at once.
- Ms. Kim! - You're here!
Have you two made up with each other?
Did we ever get in a fight?
Well, I guess one person got a bit sulky.
Who could that be?
So you're coming back to SOLUTION, right?
I'll need to think about that.
I just thought of a way to get Gong Deukgu to speak up.
If you agree to come back to SOLUTION, I'll tell you.
Hello.
I got curious about something again.
Yes?
Could you tell me where you were on October 31...
last year?
October 31...
Gosh. I can't seem to remember that day.
This man...
Isn't this you in the photo?
I don't think so.
Please take a closer look.
I was quite surprised because you looked so much like him.
That's not me.
I see.
I'm looking for the guy in the picture.
I want to hear about my mother's last moment...
before she died.
I see.
I'm sorry I asked such questions.
Then I'll get going now.
- What did he say? - He said it wasn't him.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
He will probably tell Noh Yul Seong or the chairwoman right away.
Well, that was the intention. That's why I showed him the photo.
Be careful,
both physically and mentally.
She had security footage.
Your wife is suspecting me.
My wife has been investigating her mother's case?
I'm not sure.
Anyway, if you give me two million dollars as I asked,
I'll leave Korea.
Hey.
Do I owe you any money?
I kept my silence this time again.
I kept it a secret to the chairwoman all this time too.
Do you have the brain of a goldfish?
You're the one in the evidence video...
with my late mother-in-law on the day she died.
You know what? The moment you talk,
you'll be admitting your own crime.
Don't you get it?
Just leave.
I'll call you when I'm ready.
That idiot.
Gosh, Kim Sa Ra.
She's been investigating this case behind my back?
You cannot meet with the chairwoman as her schedule won't allow it.
Gosh. Come on.
What brings you here?
Did you already get back together with Ms. Kim?
Are you here to congratulate me?
The police want me to come in for questioning.
The chairwoman told me to do it. She must take responsibility.
Is there proof that she made you do it?
You know what? Next time, date a man...
who tells you that you are enough and is happy with you. Okay?
Know your place. Got it?
Let's get that one.
You're home.
Yes.
Gosh. Really?
Mom. Look at this.
You startled me. Goodness.
There's a guy named Gong Deukgu, working for the company.
The team leader of transportation.
Yes.
Can you take a look at this?
This is the security footage from the prosecutors' office...
on the day of my mom's death.
I didn't know my mom went there.
Really?
But why?
I don't know.
But look at the man next to my mom. Doesn't he look like Mr. Gong?
I'm not sure. I can't really tell.
But how did you get this video?
Lawyer Dong. He asked me if this was my mom.
Gosh. Come on. Are you still in touch with him?
I kept thinking about it, but it didn't make any sense.
So I asked Mr. Gong.
But he said it wasn't him.
Then it wasn't him.
Maybe, you're too sensitive.
Am I?
Come out, and have your meal.
I ran out of sleeping pills in my room. Get some more.
Is something making you anxious?
That's when people usually get insomnia.
How could I sleep?
When I have you in my house.
Right. This is what I heard. If people don't get...
at least 7 hours of sleep starting at the age of 50,
their chances of getting dementia will increase.
You should keep that in mind.
(Lee Jae Hyuk)
- Hello? - We did it.
They passed the law regarding law schools.
- Is the plenary session over? - Yes.
It's been decided that there will be three more law schools.
If we get to build 1 of the 3 schools,
we'll be golden.
Good work. I mean it.
I'll come out. Let's grab a drink.
It was passed.
Good work.
Good work, honey. I mean it.
I told you, didn't I?
She definitely helped us out this time.
Congratulations, ma'am.
Do you honestly believe that your contribution was critical?
Besides, has it been decided that we'll build one of the law schools?
Gosh, Mom. Why do you have to spoil the mood on a day like today?
It's not the time to give each other an attaboy and an attagirl.
I have you to thank, Ms. Kim.
Thank you for your effort.
I didn't do much.
I told you that this would happen anyway.
Right.
Are you casting me for a role in your grand scheme of deception...
you're putting together?
To put it simply, yes.
(The generation-changing Hanjoo Party of the nation)
The law regarding the law schools will get passed anyway.
- Really? - Personally, I'm for it.
But I'm working on it behind the scenes for now.
How come you said you were neutral about the law?
If I didn't say so,
many opportunists would have pestered me.
You know, we have our own scenario too.
SOLUTION isn't the only one with it.
Is it safe to say that I returned the favour?
For helping me keep my children.
You've done more than enough.
But I will take a neutral stance...
when it comes to deciding who gets to build the law schools.
Yes.
My show must come to an end before that decision is due.
So Chayul Law Firm naturally gets eliminated from the list.
Yes. Bye.
Wasn't it obvious?
There was a lot of news coverage on the law school monopoly...
starting a few days ago. The tide had turned.
That's how the law got passed.
Sa Ra had nothing to do with it.
But still. The final selection still remains.
It'll be helpful to have her on our side until then.
Anyway, you're such an idiot.
I told you many times not to trust anyone.
This is why you will never succeed.
Then what about you? Why do you trust Gong Deukgu?
You...
Did you think I didn't know?
- How much of it do you know? - I know everything.
Do you honestly believe that he worked only for you?
You tell me that I'm an idiot and this is why I can't succeed.
Now, you must stop telling me that.
You don't have the right to tell me that.
- Where are you going? - To meet with my investors.
Today is a good day...
although you totally ruined it.
That jerk, Gong Deukgu.
He drank a lot as today is a good day.
I'll take it from here. You can leave now.
Okay.
Gosh.
(9 unread messages)
(Calls)
(Mr. Kim from M Hotel, Secretary Baek)
(Secretary Baek)
(Get-together with board directors, next Tuesday at 7pm)
(Garbage disposal, next Monday at 8pm, Sinyeong-ro 24-Gil)
(Kim Sa Ra)
Yes, it's me.
I need you to get ready next Monday.
Is it what you expected? Is there something happening?
That's probably D-Day.
Okay.
I mean... How were you able to predict this?
There's only so much Noh Yul Seong and his mother...
can possibly do once they find out that...
we are on to them.
I guess moving in there paid off.
Do you see it now?
Yes, I do.
- I'll see you that day. - Okay.
Right. Continue to be careful.
Okay.
Over there.
Let's follow him.
We'll reach the destination in ten minutes.
Then let's do it at the next traffic light.
Okay.
Hold on tight.
Gosh. What was that?
Were you even looking ahead?
How could you get your eyes off the road?
Are you all right?
Hold on. Let me check on your back. Oh, no.
- Gosh. Look at your wrists. - Oh, no.
- Let me check on your wrists. - Goodness.
Gosh. You're going to be okay.
You were going to Sinyeong-ro 24-Gil, correct?
Mr. Gong Deukgu?
Who are you guys?
Untie me right now!
Let's go.
- What are you doing? - Gosh. Wait.
"Who are we?"
Keep walking.
We just saved your life.
(I've arrived.)
(Stay in the car.)
(Don't let anyone see you.)
Watch it for yourself.
I told you, didn't I? We just saved your life.
Hey. How did you guys know...
What are you doing here, Ms. Kim?
Do you still not understand who's behind this?
Noh Yul Seong.
Why did you do that to my mother?
Your mother's death had nothing to do with me.
You took my mother!
That's because...
I was told to do that.
You were told to do that? By whom?
That day...
Let Secretary Baek take care of the car.
There's an old lady,
dressed in a purple jacket in front of the desk.
Yes. There. Go to the desk already.
I took Mr. Noh's car to the office as backup.
- Ma'am. - Then he gave me an order.
The prosecutor will be coming down shortly.
- Please wait. - Okay. Thank you.
Excuse me. Are you here to see Prosecutor Dong Gi Jun?
- Yes. - You can follow me.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Gosh. Ms. Kim.
Afterwards,
I was told to get out of the car in the middle of the road.
By whom?
Mr. Noh Yul Seong.
That's all I know.
I don't know what happened after that.
Then what about Na Yu Mi's case?
You were behind it, right?
Who made you do it?
Chairwoman Cha?
Can I...
smoke a cigarette?
Are you all right?
Noh Yul Seong was behind it.
Hey!
- Hey! Stop it! - Mr. Gong.
No.
(Queen of Divorce)
We must change the target.
We must corner them into the abyss of mistrust.
So they end up revealing each other's crime.
- What we need to do is... - To make them turn on each other.
Then at least take some weapons with you...
because we're at war now.
Do you still smell like food?
Did you know that we wear the same perfume?
You should focus on trying to get the stink off your son instead.
You were the one who tried to kill Mr. Gong...
and gave out the order to bring Sa Ra's mother-in-law.
I wanted to ask you that.
Two million dollars were wired to Gong Deukgu.
As money laundering was suspected, they're pursuing a certain law firm.
Gong Deukgu was your driver, Mother.
All right. Don't fight now. Why don't you go together?
I wonder which one of you the police have come to arrest.