It's going online soon.
Can’t you even think of an attractive slogan?
Mr. Jiang, you've denied all of these.
Lin Mochen, let's see how long you can be proud of.
When will this date end?
Hey.
What kind of boys do girls like?
It must be you.
Handsome and rich.
Who told you to make an objective statement?
Answer my question.
No.
Why do you want to ask this today?
Are you trapped in love?
Can you answer the question?
Ah.
Who is it?
Dong Wei Wei.
How is that possible?
Oh.
Yes.
You're double-faced.
Do you like her?
Humph.
Dong Wei Wei.
How is that possible?
[Laughing]
There's no reason for love.
Humph.
What you just said
this red rose.
Yes.
It's too vulgar.
It's tacky, but it's useful.
If we have more,
The sky is full of stars.
Is this pretty?
The meaning of stars is that I'm willing to be an extra.
It means to protect the one you love silently.
It's very romantic.
Why should I be an extra?
Is that the point?
Just listen to me.
Joon-sung.
Hey.
Do you know what stars symbolize?
Yes.
Ah.
Did the stars save your life?
It's tacky, okay?
I shouldn't have listened to him.
You're willing to be an extra.
Don't be so emotional.
What kind of flower do you like?
Himawari.
It's sunny.
It's also very romantic.
Okay, I got it.
Why did you suddenly give me flowers today?
I followed you and had a crush on you.
Why didn't you give me a ride before?
I'm in a good mood today.
You're not in the circulation, are you?
No one else will change
You're the only one who's changing.
You helped me out yesterday.
Miss.
I don't seem to understand what you're talking about.
Every time I meet him,
time will restart for no reason.
No, I have to find out.
That's not right.
Lin Mochen used to follow me.
How can I find him?
I know who you're looking for.
Follow me.
Why should I trust you?
You don't trust me? Do you trust these men?
Then send me to get a skirt first.
Why did you bring me here?
Do you think
a little mental problem recently?
It's not my problem.
This world is the problem.
Do you think the world is repeating every day?
You're just too nervous.
Relax and enjoy life.
No, no, no.
I don't want to enjoy it anymore.
This time is different.
I've prepared a few great handsome guys for you.
Don't.
I'm going to throw up.
That's it.
Lin Mochen.
Oh.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Are you stained?
I'm fine.
I'm really fine.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Take off your clothes.
What?
Do you need my help?
Hey.
What are you doing?
Don't be nervous.
I've prepared something better for you.
No.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I...
Hey.
Open the door!
Darn it.
Where did this woman
took Dong Wei Wei?
Why are you here?
I'm worried about her too.
Can't I?
Guys,
I hid Dong Wei Wei.
In these rooms,
Whoever finds it first will get it.
There must be more than 100 rooms here.
It depends on your fate.
What do you want?
I advise you to hurry up.
Be careful
she'll fall in love with someone else.
You deserve that she doesn't like you.
What were you doing earlier?
Hey, where is the surveillance room?
The negative floor.
Hey.
Whose prank is this?
But he's really fast.
Have you seen these two ladies?
Which room are they in?
We can't tell you this.
Please.
This is really important to me.
Sorry, we have rules here.
Please.
Pretty lady.
I swear I'm not a bad person.
Please help me.
Sister.
Please.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hello bro
Hey.
Excuse me.
Do you have the CCTV from half an hour ago?
I'm sorry.
The CCTV has been broken for a long time.
No.
This is a serious violation.
Are you looking for someone?
Ask the receptionist.
I...
I can do this.
Oh.
Wei Wei.
Sorry.
It's the wrong way.
Lin Mochen.
Isn't the door locked?
How did you get in?
Oh, well...
There's no one else here
The door is broken.
Who else could it be?
Well...
What about that woman?
I don't know.
Okay, I'll see if you're safe.
I'm leaving.
Hey.
Where are you going?
The door is broken.
No.
Why is the door broken?
No, brother.
I told you three times that the door is broken.
Come here. I have something to ask you.
Come here.
What on earth
Wow.
Lin Mochen.
Look at the fireworks.
Look.
Actors.
Dong Wei Wei, Sun Qianling.
Lin Mochen Yao Rui
Jiang, Yu, Zhang Yiqian.
Jack Wang Chang Kai
Special actor.
[Flower shop guy, Hwang, Kim]
[Doctor in Cardiology, Yoo Ji-kyung]
Designer Lin Zhiwei
The bride Fei.
Lam. What a coincidence.
Chef Jerry.
Handsome guy, Luo Rong.
A handsome passerby, Liu Zihang.
Fireman Zou Jianbo.
Assistant Luo Xiang.
Yoyo, Peng Weifeng.
Boss, Yi Ming.
Hotel receptionist Fang Se-mi
Player A, Jiang, Yu.
Weird. Thief. Zheng Tony.
Li Dynasty, the waterer.
Motorbike boy, Li Jun Xiong.
Planner Lin Haitao
Shameless man Liang Xubiao
Liu Zihang.
Liu Jiafeng.
Xue Yu Lu, Ah Teng.
Liu, Jia, Wang Xiao Hui.
Shao Limin, Chen Ju Mei.
Seong Bin-hee.
[Staff Form]
Product Zhang Jisi.
Jiang Haocheng.
Director Zhang Xinbing.
Xu Yafei.
Photographer He Xiaofeng
Lighting instructor Sun Junyang
art instructor, Party An Bang.
Producer Zhao Yi.
Producer Director Ding Ye
Executive director Lin Haitao
Actor consultant Wan Xin
Yiming.
Outer producer Ding Ye
Drama Photo Liang Sun Zhi
Fan Ge.
Photographer group.
Photographer Li Tianci
Photographer assistant, Li Ziya.
and the pilot, Zhang Fuyong.
Lighting team.
Lighting Master Sun Junzheng.
Lighting assistant, Wu Yanjiang.
Song Mingjie.
Costume team.
styling instructor, Chen Suxian.
comb, make-up, Zhu Wenxi.
Costume assistant Guo Xiaotian.
Makeup assistant Duan Juanping.
Art team.
Artist Chen Chuwen
Chen Zongchang, the prop team leader.
Tool Yang Daxian
The recording team.
Recording instructor, Li Ka Ren.
Voice assistant Huang Sheng Juan.
Action team.
Zhang Xinbing.
Li Jun Xiong.
Master Yi Yinghua
The venue team.
Mr. Liang Xu.
Lee Hui.
Driver team.
Driver Zhao Shichang
Xiao Xianping.
Information Co., Ltd.
Editor Chen Hui
Li Peifu.
Editing assistant, Liang Wei Chao.
Special effects team.
Special effects director, Qin Shao wins.
Voice guidance Xia Yingxiang.
Xia Yingxiang, a mixed recorder.
Theme song, Kan.
Singing Guan Fen.
Arrangement: Xia Yingxiang.
The ending song "If I Once Again".
Singing Huang Haoming.
Ming Xie.
Dongguan Flowers Video MCN live streaming base.
Product unit.