[English subtitles are available.]
[Crossroad Bistro]
Who are you?
My name is Peng Man.
I knew you would
have a baby sooner or later.
Dai Xiaoyu.
Shame on you!
I will slap you.
I am a forty-two-year-old man.
At this age,
if I want to have another child,
first,
I won't have enough energy.
Second and foremost,
Ivy may not be able to accept this.
If so,
it will make our family
extremely complicated.
Ivy. Ivy!
All you think about is your daughter.
Have you considered me?
I didn't say we should never have children.
It's in my body right now.
I have the right to decide its life and death.
That is my child too.
I also have the right.
No, you don't.
I don't accept a man
who keeps saying that he loves me
but asks me to get rid of his child.
Don't follow me.
I will kill myself if you follow me!
Can I
ask you a favor?
My dad and my mom
always urge me to find a girlfriend.
If I can't find one,
can you...
Can I?
Hello.
Table for two?
Yes.
Miss.
Are you Feng Xi?
Yes, I am.
And you are...
We are Zhao Henan's parents.
Look.
It's hard for you to run this restaurant.
In the next few days,
your dad and I will go to your place
and cook you some of his special dishes.
You can relax a bit.
Great.
[Ep22]
Dinner's ready.
Come, let's eat.
What about a drink?
Sure.
I'm so happy today.
OK.
One for you, dad?
Henan.
Don't fill your dad's glass.
Don't let him drink.
He has high blood pressure.
Just one glass is fine.
I have to wash my hands.
This way?
Yeah.
Mrs. Zhao.
You can use the brown towel.
That's Henan's.
OK.
During our trip,
you guys have done a lot,
especially Feng Xi,
who kept us company the whole time.
Thank you for taking days off.
It's okay, Mrs. Zhao.
It's no big deal.
I want to
make a toast
to our big family!
Yeah.
Cheers.
Feng Xi.
Slow it down.
I know. I know.
Here.
Try this.
Thank you.
How's it?
So good.
I'm so glad you like it.
What do you think?
You fried it twice.
Yeah. Twice.
I usually fry it three times.
Just two times are fine.
For the second time,
heat the oil a bit longer.
Our first two times
are your first.
In this way,
the meat is tenderer.
You've become a better chef than me.
Dad, cheers.
OK. Cheers.
Feng Xi.
Do your parents
know about you and Henan?
Yes.
What do they say?
They
think he's a good guy.
If so,
how about we
meet your parents someday?
Sure.
But they have not retired yet.
They may not have much free time.
We have plenty of free time.
We retired already.
Plus,
we should visit your parents anyway.
Right?
Mom.
Could you
give Feng Xi a break on this?
We are not in a hurry.
Why should you?
Of course, I'm in a hurry.
How can I not be?
Both of you are over thirty.
Your dad and I are getting old.
We'll be older in a few years.
How can we take care of your kids for you then?
What?
Kids?
Mr. Zhao.
Cheers.
These are all very delicious.
Thanks.
She's just like that.
Always talking a lot.
Even more
when she drinks.
There is literally no one
who knows my mom better than you, dad.
Mom.
Cheers.
Your mom only tells the truth.
I'm leaving for shooting tomorrow.
It'll be over a month.
Play with me.
Be a good girl.
Wait a sec.
I have been waiting for two hours.
I'll go to bed.
Go ahead.
Han...
Han.
You are so handsome.
Stop that, Han.
No...
Fell asleep?
Hmm.
What?
Is your work done?
Let me ask you something.
Shoot.
Who is Han?
Han?
Han is...
Well.
I don't know.
What Han?
If you don't know him,
why did you say his name?
I did?
No way.
I don't know Han.
What are you talking about?
Wait. Wait.
Let's make it clear.
Who is Han?
I don't know him.
I don't know him well.
What?
You just said you didn't know him.
Now you don't know him well?
Who the hell is Han?
I just can't
keep secrets, can I?
OK, I'll tell you.
You can't get mad.
Han...
He is some guy I just met.
Single, cute,
and kind of rich.
What?
Let me finish.
When I first met him,
I felt that
the smell of him
really appealed to me.
So I asked him.
I said,
Han, what do you do for a living?
Guess what he said.
How should I know?
He said he's from Shanxi Province.
His family owns a big factory,
producing vinegar only.
So I said,
what a coincidence!
My boyfriend loves vinegar.
Then he said,
Miss,
now you are Han's friend.
No matter when,
say my name, and you'll get vinegar.
That's it.
Are you kidding me?
Are you playing with me?
Huh?
You asked for it.
I said I don't know him.
You had to ask.
You are bad.
Tell me.
Did you get jealous?
I smelt something sour.
So strong.
Eat my fart.
That's not funny.
Eat fart?
You'd better eat it yourself.
I'll pass.
You are so bad.
I was busy.
You had to make me stop.
You are bad.
You could have spent the whole time
chatting with me rather than being jealous.
OK. OK.
I'll play with you.
That's more like it.
What do you want to play?
I'm thirsty.
Pour me a glass of water, please.
OK. OK.
It's my sister.
Hello?
I'm at Yu Songyang's house now.
What happened?
Where are you right now?
OK.
I got it.
Wait for me.
I'll be right back.
OK. Bye.
My sister had a huge fight with Peng Pai.
I have to go home now.
Is she okay?
Not so good.
Crying so hard.
Do you want me to go with you?
It's okay.
You still have work to do.
Sweetheart.
I will go to Huairou tomorrow.
Be good.
Huairou is not far.
I'll visit you when I'm done.
Hmm.
OK, I should go.
Call me if you need anything.
OK.
Be careful.
OK. Bye.
Sorry, the number you have dialed is busy.
Please try again later.
Sorry, the subscriber you have dialed is power off.
Sorry,
the subscriber you have dialed is power off.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Is Dai Xiaoyu here?
No.
OK.
What about Bao Xue?
Is she here?
No, she's not here, either.
Is there anything you need?
No.
Thank you.
Well,
Henan's father
has been in the kitchen for his whole life.
But when he watches TV,
still, food shows.
He loves what he does.
Mrs. Zhao.
Where do you want to go tomorrow?
I heard from our old classmates
that there is a temple
called Hongluo Temple in Beijing, right?
Yeah.
Do you want to go?
Sure.
Then let's go there.
I heard that it's a great place
to pray for a good marriage.
I'll burn some incense and pray for you.
Sure.
Wherever you want to go.
Great.
Hmm.
Enough of TV.
Let's go back to the hotel.
It'll be over in a few minutes.
Turn it off now.
They need to go to bed.
I'll go get Henan.
No need.
We can go by ourselves.
Don't bother.
Let him sleep.
OK.
I'll get you a cab.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Goodbye.
Go home and rest.
Go.
Bye-bye.
You're awake.
How did I fall asleep?
I found that
showing them around
is more tiring than cooking in the kitchen.
Your parents went back to the hotel.
Thank you for these days.
You are a good actress.
My dad and my mom
really believe you are my girlfriend.
Your parents
and you are all very kind.
When I was with them these days,
sometimes I forgot
that I am just pretending.
OK.
Good night.
I should go.
Hmm.
Bye.
Can you see the lights here from outside?
Of course, yes.
Then turn off the light.
He will definitely come here to find me.
I don't want to see him.
Sis.
I don't think this is a long-term solution.
If he comes over today and sees a dark room,
he'll probably come here again tomorrow.
If you are really
determined this time,
you should talk to him face to face.
When I heard
what he said to me today,
I felt like another word with him
would be a total insult to me.
How could I talk to him?
I can't.
I want to stay here for tonight.
I left home in a hurry,
so I didn't bring anything.
I will find a hotel tomorrow.
Why hotel?
What's wrong with my place?
No.
He will definitely come here to find me.
But you didn't bring anything with you.
Not even clothes to change.
What should you do?
I can wear yours.
When you finish shooting,
you can go to his place
and get all my stuff for me.
OK.
You have cried your eyes out.
Now,
you should take some rest.
Bao Xue.
Bao Xue?
Xiaoyu?
Xiaoyu.
He's gone.
Why am I so unlucky?
There, there.
Stop overthinking.
I think you are right.
Your child. Your decision.
If you really want to have it,
I will raise the baby with you.
Yuanyuan fell asleep.
She just finished the course on Banma AI KE.
You know what?
Our girl likes it.
Look at this study report.
All three stars.
Our daughter used to
study only under watch.
Now she learns on her own initiative.
How nice!
If a kid can study
without parents' supervision,
that'll be the best.
I want to tell you something.
Sure.
Starting tomorrow, I want to go to Crossroad Bistro
and help You Shanshan for a few days.
Is her restaurant
understaffed?
Feng Xi has to take days off.
You Shanshan needs to
watch the store herself for a few days.
I'm thinking that
I'm kind of free.
Go ahead.
Will you pick up the children?
Sure.
Who else?
Du Shijun.
I think something is wrong with you.
What's wrong with me?
Usually,
you must have tones of questions.
Why did you agree so fast today?
You...
In the past, I didn't support your work.
So you were unhappy.
Now I support you, but you think I'm weird.
Who is weird, really?
It's unnatural.
Your reaction is strange.
Recently,
you come home early,
you cook,
and you even put Yuanyuan to bed just now.
Be honest with me,
did you do something bad
behind my back again?
You are quite observant.
I did do one thing.
What thing?
Through my hard work,
the department I am in charge of
shifted.
It used to be the evaluation department,
and now it is the audit.
Why?
Since that incident happened,
I have been thinking for a long time.
I think I should
respect your ideas and choices.
I shouldn't always say
that I'm the breadwinner
and keep you in the house.
When we had that trip,
you said that
we need to change.
Can't agree more.
We must change.
And I think, not just us.
Everyone needs to change as well.
And it should start with me.
You should have your time,
your space,
and your own circle of friends.
Now that I'm in the audit department.
There will be less entertainment than before.
Things that can be discussed in the office
don't have to be taken to the dinner table.
In this way,
I can take care of my family more.
If you get busy someday,
this house won't be messed up.
Right?
Did I hear you right?
I was just kidding.
Well,
I mean it.
In the future,
I will pick up the kids most of the time.
You can do your own thing.
If you have nothing to do, you can just
stay at home and write
or cook.
If sometimes I have entertainment,
I will tell you in advance.
OK?
Is it perfect?
Hmm.
After hearing what you said,
I almost want to thank Wei Lan for this.
What?
You thank her?
This is what I realized by myself
after I was vindicated, OK?
Don't thank her!
Do the policemen have to thank the criminals
for catching them?
Your analogy
is quite accurate.
Of course.
I'm in the audit department now.
I have to be accurate.
Now,
can we not talk about her?
OK.
Never.
I'll be mad if I hear her name again.
If I weren't your husband,
I would be mad at you.
I'll go brush my teeth.
OK.
Today is my first morning meeting with everyone.
Well...
Uh...
What do you guys usually talk about
in the morning meetings?
All right. All right.
Let me introduce someone to you.
This is my friend Si Meng.
For the next few days,
she will help us in the restaurant.
Good morning.
Thank you for your hard work.
Without further ado,
what you did
when Feng Xi was here,
now keep doing it.
Hello.
Sis.
What are you doing?
I'm having breakfast.
Did you sleep well last night?
No.
I'll go back to sleep later.
Are you there yet?
About that,
I found out that the crew arranged
a double room for me this time.
Come after you finish your breakfast.
Is it okay for me to go?
I can say you are my assistant.
Is that appropriate?
Sure.
If you're here,
I can take care of you.
I'll worry
if you stay alone.
Be a good girl.
Come right after breakfast.
OK.
Send me your location. Is it far?
No.
It's only one and a half hours by taxi.
Okay, I'll leave in a while.
Great.
OK.
See you later.
Bye.
Excuse me?
Yeah?
Are you sleepy?
I'm okay.
Not sleepy.
If you are sleepy,
I can take another cab.
I'm fine.
Copy that.
Thanks.
I've got good news.
I don't have to shoot today!
Sis, where are you?
Hello?
Are you a friend of the phone's owner?
You are?
Excuse me! Sorry!
Excuse me!
My sister had a car accident.
Can I take this cab?
Thank you.
Chaoyang Hospital, please.
Uncle.
I am Xue.
Hello?
Shut up and listen to me.
My sister had a car accident just now.
She's in the ER.
I'm telling you, Peng.
If anything happens to my sister,
I'll kill you!
Please,
can you drive faster?
Hello.
I'm done...
What happened?
My sister had a car accident.
Bao Xue!
How is she?
Still in the operating room.
She'll be fine.
Doctor.
Doctor, how is she?
Are you Dai Xiaoyu's kin?
I am.
I am her cousin.
Her parents are on the way here.
You can tell me everything.
The patient's wound is not very large.
But the glass cuts are too deep.
Plus, she is two months pregnant.
The external squeeze
caused her inner wall to rupture.
There is also trauma on the outer wall,
which is causing extensive bleeding.
The uterus must be removed now.
We need your signature.
OK?
Doctor, please.
Is there any other way?
I can understand your feelings.
But now,
there is really no other way.
The patient's bleeding hasn't stopped yet.
Can you make a decision?
The patient really can't wait.
Please decide quickly.
OK?
I'll sign.
Also, I need to tell you that
now the blood bank in our hospital is running short.
It'll be best if her immediate family members
can make blood transfusion.
When will her immediate family members arrive?
Her parents are coming from Hangzhou.
They will arrive in the evening.
What should I do?
If we transfer blood from other hospitals,
I'm afraid the time...
Doctor,
My blood type is the same as hers.
Take mine.
What is your relationship with the patient?
Friends.
Take a blood compatibility test.
If your blood groups are compatible,
we can do it, OK?
Yes.
Prepare him chocolate or something.
OK.
Thanks.
Don't worry.
Thank you, Liu.
She will be fine.
Please,
I'm begging you.
Please ask the doctor to come up with another way.
Aunt.
She keeps bleeding now.
If I don't sign, it will be too late for her.
Don't blame me.
Xue.
Sign the form now.
Her life matters the most.
Xue.
We'll be there in a while.
OK.
She is only 30 years old.
How can she face the fact?
Liu Liangzhou.
Who is Liu Liangzhou?
I am.
Come. Please check this.
Is your name Liu Liangzhou?
Yes.
Can you confirm that you have type O blood?
You want to make
a voluntary blood donation to Dai Xiaoyu, right?
Yes.
OK, come with me.
OK.
[Operation]
The baby is gone.
Not just the baby,
so is her uterus.
Now your daughter can have a dad of her own.
Can you stop talking?
Please?
I didn't want this to happen.
Shut up!
How is she, doctor?
The patient is out of danger.
Now she is transferred to ICU.
Can we see her now?
Not yet.
She's bled so much
that she has to be observed in the ICU for a few hours.
If there is no more problem,
she can be transferred to the surgical ward.
You can see her then.
Thank you.
Also, she has to be admitted for a few days.
You should prepare some things
for her hospitalization.
Of course.
No problem.
I'll buy the stuff.
I'll go.
Let him do it.
And,
thank you.
Liu.
Thank you.
Don't say that.
You don't need to say that to me.
You saved my sister's life.
She is also my friend.
Don't cry.
Sit down.
Excuse me, nurse.
Where is Dai Xiaoyu?
C15.
Okay, thank you.
Thanks.
Uncle, aunt.
Xue.
Hello.
I'm Peng Pai.
How is she now?
She just fell asleep.
You can go in.
OK.
You. Go away.
Xue.
How did that happen?
Aunt.
I can't explain to you
the whole thing clearly right now.
When she wakes up,
I'll tell you everything then, okay?
What did the doctor say?
How is Xiaoyu?
The doctor said
she is out of danger now.
She just woke up for a while,
and now she is asleep again.
Sit here.
There was a young man out there.
Who is he?
He is a friend of ours.
Before you came,
he donated blood to her.
Xiaoyu.
Mr. Dai.
What's your name?
My name is Liu Liangzhou.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Xiaoyu.
You're awake.
Xiaoyu?
Sis.
Don't move now.
You can't move now.
Mom.
Dad.
Xiaoyu, don't get too excited.
Dad is here.
When you were in the OR,
it was Liu who gave you his blood.
Dai.
Get out.
I'll be near the door.
Call me if you need anything.
Get out.
Thank you.
I will go home now
and come again tomorrow.
Don't show up in front of us anymore.
I know you hate me.
But it has happened.
You hating me can't solve any problem.
What I can do now
is to try my best to make it up to her.
I will
book a hotel room for her parents to stay.
I have booked one.
And,
You don't have to
feel stressed about this.
We don't need you to make it up to us.
You
just go back and live your life.
I can tell you this explicitly.
Peng Pai.
Your relationship with my sister
is absolutely over.
Everything she has been through today
is caused by you.
You and she
are never, ever getting back together.
Xue.
I don't want to argue with you.
Can you calm down?
If Xiaoyu
could calm down today,
she wouldn't have had such a big accident.
I won't make excuses.
But I'm telling you
I care about Xiaoyu.
I love her very much.
I will take care of her
no matter what happens to her.
Cut it out!
Listen,
what you're saying now
sounds like farting to me.
OK?
I'm calm enough now.
If I calm down more, I'll freeze.
I suggest you leave now.
If my uncle finds out
why this happened,
he will definitely kill you.
Fuck off.
I'll come tomorrow.
Fuck off!
What?
You should go in there and stay with them.
I'll buy you something to eat.
Thanks, Liu.
Go in there.
Xiaoyu.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Xiaoyu.
I don't blame you.
How can I blame you?
Don't say sorry.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
Xiaoyu.
I'm the one who's sorry.