Someone called me
and claimed Jay was her man.
This is my man's room.
I don't have any feelings for you.
Fine! We're over.
Why would someone do this to another?
If they broke up,
then who was that?
We're just having fun together.
I found someone...
who could make me feel better!
If you want to know me, have fun trying.
♫Happy birthday to you♫
♫Happy birthday, happy birthday♫
♫Happy birthday to Blue♫
Happy birthday.
Wishing you lots of happiness.
Hello.
- Hi, Him.
- Yes?
Are you free?
I want to give you your shirt back.
[Him: Nitikorn Pankram]
[Nail: Atagorn Sonyot]
[Chao: Supanut Sudjinda]
[Phai: Atthaporn Uengthaweesab]
[Techin: Nattawat Nopphakornnattakrit]
[Piece: Panuwat Somnam]
[Dream: Panya Mcshane]
[Chaochom: Panisara Prinyarux]
[Pae: Suchanon Chueluecha]
[Yihwa: Areeya Pholphutrakul]
[Somsom: Aissaree Tharakoolphipat]
[Phaploy: Punnisa Sirisang]
[Ployli: Mayura Ekrungruangkul]
[Jay: Kooppong Chumnanyong]
You don't have to.
But let me come see you, please?
No, you can't.
I'll go to you instead.
What about you coming over
and watching a movie with me?
Do you really mean it, or...
If you want to watch a movie with me,
I'm happy to do so.
However,
if you want to do other things...
Anyway, I'm giving you your shirt back.
I don't want it anymore.
- Then, what do you want?
- Nail.
I'll go now.
I'll come to you.
- Him.
- Yes?
If it's not fun with you, I'll leave.
It's my job...
to make you stay.
I'll see you there.
I miss you so bad, Nail.
Why would you miss me?
We're not together.
Should we?
You said we'd watch a movie.
Did I?
Well...
What kind of movies do you like to watch?
I don't know.
Romantic movies were my favorites,
but...I'm not into them anymore.
Why is that?
I just got dumped.
How could I believe in love?
Well, maybe...
If you watch one with me,
you might believe in it again.
It depends on...
what you have in exchange.
Anything...you wish.
You're treating me so well.
Is there anything you want from me?
If I ask you for something,
will you give it to me?
If I can, yes.
He won't pick up.
What the fuck is wrong with him?
Maybe he's not coming.
Let him be.
I think he wants some time alone.
But it's Blue's birthday.
Why can't he make it?
It's what Blue wanted.
He might be with his mom.
You guys can make it,
but why can't he?
Isn't he with someone else?
We're here...
because you asked us to, Te.
Fine.
Isn't it good that
Him is going out with someone new?
Who is that?
Do you know him, Chao?
I don't.
I was just about to tease him
so that he could move on and be happy.
Where are you going?
Te!
Where the fuck is he going?
What's with him?
The audacity of you, Chao...
Let me start over with you tonight, Nail.
I'll make you feel like it's our first time.
Sure.
I'll make you forget everything.
I thought you were some kind of ghost.
If you saw a ghost,
then you're also a ghost.
You're messing with me?
Isn't it you who started it?
Isn't it you who always mess with me?
What did I do?
I saw that 1,000-Baht note with you.
I found it first!
- Is it yours?
- No.
But I found it first, so it's mine.
If it's not yours,
give it to the landlord and let her find the owner.
You can't simply claim it.
Are you nuts?
How can you prove it's someone else's?
You're trying to claim it, huh?
Don't blame me for what you're trying to do.
Think about it.
If you lost your money, how would you feel?
Hey!
Give it to me. I found it first!
No!
I'll tell the landlord myself.
I don't trust you.
Give it to me!
I found it!
- It's mine!
- Go away.
- Let go!
- Give it to me!
It's mine!
Give it to me!
Let go!
Jeez!
I'll go now.
It wastes my time talking to you.
Why are you following me?
What a narcissist you are.
Hi, ma'am.
What ma'am? Shut it.
I meant to say "girl."
Can I pay in installments this month?
I haven't gotten paid yet,
so I'd like to pay in installments as usual.
Honey, isn't this too little?
A thousand?
Once I get paid,
I'll pay it as soon as possible.
Please.
Fine, then.
Someone found a banknote
in the hall last month,
but no one has claimed it yet.
I'll use it to cover your rent.
A 1000-Baht note from last month?
Right.
I haven't found the owner, though.
Think of it as if the owner's
helping you pay your rent.
Also, I know that you always keep your word
and never not pay your rent.
Thank you so much.
Once I get paid, I'll pay it for sure.
- Thank you.
- Sure, don't worry about it.
Thank you.
Hey, Nail.
It's been a while.
Hi, Phai.
Are you going to work?
Yeah. You?
That's a nice shirt.
Whose shirt is that?
I just got here.
I'll change my clothes
and go to the college.
Then, let's meet up and have a meal later?
I was about to say the same thing.
By the way, when are you free?
Let's have a meal together.
I'm fine with anything. You can decide.
Okay.
I want to talk about getting tattoos, too.
What? You want some now?
Aren't you afraid of needles now?
I am, but I want to overcome it.
I think it's best to...be yourself.
Thank you so much, Phai.
Whenever I talk to you,
it helps me feel better.
You don't need to thank me.
You're like my brother.
You really don't need to.
I do.
I really do have to thank you.
Last semester, without you,
my project wouldn't have succeeded.
Don't mention it.
It was just an interview.
Nail, I have to go now.
Kao's calling me.
- See you.
- See you!
- Get there safely.
- Okay.
Where were you on Blue's birthday?
Why weren't you there?
Guys, Van wants us to perform at the club tonight.
All members of the usual band
are having the runs.
At what time?
You have your report to finish.
An hour.
Wait. Two...
Just in case.
Speaking of the report, I'm sick of it.
You won't do anything, huh?
Are you guys...
...okay?
If you're okay, then I am.
I'm okay with that, too.
Alright, meet me at my room at 6 P.M.
Finish our report first,
then we'll leave at 7 P.M.
Yes, sir! Let's go.
Okay?
We need to talk.
Are you enjoying it?
What's with you?
I already told you.
I don't want you to be happy.
Hey, Te.
What the fuck are you trying to do, Him?
Did you forget about that?
Stop it.
Don't ever mention it again.
Don't ever think you'll get to live a happy life.
You'll have to suffer like I do.
Stop!
Game on!
Let me see.
Whoa, hey!
Hi! What's your name?
I'm Phaploy.
Hello. I'm Ployli.
I'm Somsom, and this is Yihwa.
What? Som, why did you say that for me?
Well, is this your faculty?
You don't look familiar.
No, it's not my faculty.
Then, why are you here?
Are you searching for your love, aka me?
That's too much, girl!
That's not it.
I'm here to take Nail for a meal.
That's even more than too much.
Do you know Nail?
- Nail's taken him.
- What should we do?
He's here!
Nail's here. Please excuse me.
Look at him!
Have you been waiting for me long, Him?
Not at all.
Hey, are you guys having a meal together?
Right! Nail's about to have a meal with us.
So, can we just go together, or...
- Right?
- Yeah!
- You should come with us.
- Let's have a meal together.
Girls!
Don't be too obvious.
Come and have a lunch with me.
Isn't that too much, girl?
Come here. Go.
Let's have some lunch.
- No!
- Come on.
Come on!
- I want to go with them!
- Stop it!
We can go together.
Why are you smiling?
It's because someone's being possessive.
You're cute.
Why would I be possessive of you?
We're not together.
Fine.
You're not being possessive, then,
Can you come to Flower Club with me tonight?
Why?
I'm performing tonight,
so I want you to come.
Will you?
Sure.
I'll take you home first,
then we'll go to the club later.
- Is that alright?
- Yeah.
Hi.
What's your name?
Can I have your contact?
Staring like that...
Wanna be mine?
I guess you didn't like that.
Then...
Do you have anything to carry home with?
Because I can be one.
Do you have no one to talk to, huh?
Of course not.
That's why I wanted to talk to you.
Sure. Give me your phone.
Here.
[It's none of your business]
Jeez! I won't let you go next time!
Hi! We're Stay Four.
We hope you'll enjoy our show.
Who is your crush right now?
No matter who it is...
just tell them.
Don't play the fool.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you. You can call us anytime.
Yeah. Thanks a lot.
Without you guys, I'd be in trouble.
- You should buy us some drinks, then.
- Sure!
Anything you want. Enjoy the night.
It's on me.
Van, I'll be right back.
What's with you?
What? Why are you making that face?
I'm sick of this.
What is it?
He's not the left one,
or the middle one,
but he's the right one.
Shit...
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Pretty people are always mean.
Who is it?
Whatever. Leave it.
Where did Te and Him go?
I don't know.
Him said he'd leave early,
so Te followed him.
Who were you looking at?
"Pretty people are always mean," right?
I don't want to leave you yet.
Can I still be with you?
Some breaks would be nice.
Anyway, you looked cool performing on stage.
And did you like it?
You're always flirting with me.
It might change your mind.
Let's change the topic.
Anyway, when did you learn to play bass?
Since high school.
Really? That's cool.
Does that mean...
lots of people have tried to flirt with you?
No, I was taken.
What? Why did you stop?
Keep going.
It's getting dark.
You should get some rest.
Or...
do you want me to stay?
No, you should leave.
I want some rest now.
Can I pick you up tomorrow?
Let me think about it first.
Then, once I reach home,
can I call you?
Mm.
I'll go now.
Okay.
- Bye-bye.
- Goodnight.
- You're so fucking heavy.
- Keep walking.
- The driver's been here for ages.
- You're talking too much.
- Text me when you're home. See you, Kao.
I carried your ass and said nothing, damn.
Why don't you open the door?
Easy, man.
You can go now, sir.
Wait, you won't come with me?
Are you okay? Are you drunk?
I'm not drunk.
I said I wouldn't let you go
if I met you again.
Can I have your contact?
Stop saying your cheesy pick-up lines.
If you don't like them,
I can do other things.
Are you sure you want it?
I am sure I want it.
[Mom: Don't forget to keep up with
your doctor's appointments]
[Okay]
[Te: Who did you leave with, Him?]
- Hello?
- Hello.
Have you gone to bed?
Not yet.
So, you can talk to me
before going to bed, right?
Yeah. Sure.
I'll tell you when I'm sleepy.
Okay. Tell me if you are.
Mm.
Come in.
Tonight, can I...
If you want me, come and follow me.
Tonight, can I feel you?
Be gentle. That's all I want.
As you wish.
Can you...turn your camera on?
Sure.
Do you realize how adorable you are?
What adorable?
Are you on a balcony?
That's right.
It's got great views.
Right?
Should we try...having fun here later?
You're good at mentioning it.
I'll take that as a compliment.
I'm asking for your permission, then.
Nail, I don't want to be someone
you're just having fun with.
- Can we change our relationship...
- I think...
...it's better that we are like this.
You know, we're just having fun together.
I'm sleepy.
Okay. I understand you.
Don't worry about it. Goodnight.
[Nail: I don't want to lead anyone on]
[Nail: Please understand me]
[Blue: I miss you]
You've never said you missed me.
We're together, aren't we?
Why don't you have time for me?
Blue,
you know I'm busy with my family matters.
Why don't you understand me?
You always say that.
Do I not matter to you at all?
You're my best friend, Te.
This is Nail.
Nail?
We're friends.
Is this how you wanted to start over?
What are you doing?
Making you realize.
You know what? You're my type.
Stay away from him. He's mine.