(They enter into an unknown world.)
Into the unknown world.
- I can really feel it.
- It's really the Amazon now.
We're entering the jungle now.
Look at this.
- Achiote.
- Achiote?
(They find a unique fruit
as soon as they enter.)
- Add.
- Is that good?
(Is it safe to eat?)
No. It's for putting on your face.
- On your face?
- I see.
Si Eon. This is that thing
that Yamulu put on.
(Kian84, This is the thing that Yamulu
from Amazon's Waura tribe put on.)
Everyone. Take a look at this.
It almost has the color of paint.
I thought it would be
a mosquito repellent,
but it wasn't something like that.
It's just for makeup.
Indian community.
Thank you.
You too?
(Me too.)
No mosquito?
- Not for mosquitoes.
- Amazon style.
(Amazon style)
- Isn't this that thing?
- You too?
You.
This is...
I am...
a Korean painter.
Artist.
Korean movie star.
Sure. Korean artist.
(Sure.)
They seem to think we're lying.
(They seem to think we're lying.)
Why did you interpret it in that way?
They had almost no reaction.
It felt like they thought
we were saying useless things.
I'll make you look cooler.
Shouldn't it not go in my eyes?
It's not an artificial chemical.
(Not my problem.)
(They don't hold back
when investing in improving their looks.)
(Satisfied)
I'll put it on like this.
- Wait here.
- Yes.
Nice.
The more I put on, the more I want.
A little bit more like this.
(Putting on more and more)
(Nice.)
Some on my lips too.
- He's really putting on a lot.
- Gosh.
It fits you. It's nice.
It looks like we put on gochujang.
(The gochujang brothers from Korea)
- Here.
- What is this?
- Fishing for piranhas.
- I see.
- It's a completely handmade fishing pole.
- Interesting.
I think we can put down our bags.
Okay. Go.
(Let's go fishing.)
They're going fishing finally.
I really like this.
I wonder what it'll be like
to fish in the Amazon.
You know when fishermen catch a big fish?
That's not something you come by
often in life.
If I can do something like that,
it'll be like winning the lottery.
It'll be like a dream.
I'm very excited.
(I'm very excited
for fishing in the Amazon.)
Salvatore!
(They take off while dreaming
of becoming Amazon's big fish king.)
(Excited)
(They anchor down at the fishing spot.)
(The bait is chicken gizzards?)
- Is this the bait?
- Yes.
They usually use worms for fish bait.
These are piranhas. They have teeth.
They said they could smell blood.
(Piranha, Meaning "fish with teeth")
(A carnivorous fresh-water fish
that responds to blood)
Oh, those teeth.
I'll add one here.
(Put on some bloody bait,)
We should start together.
(and they're ready to fish.)
I've never seen someone
fish for piranhas before.
(Interesting)
(First, Eric, the fishing tour guide,
gives a demonstration.)
- What is that?
(He makes a unique sound
to lure the piranhas.)
- They have to call them.
- I see.
They don't run away instead?
(They do as they were taught.)
(Splashing)
(They swish around
until their arms are about to fall off.)
(He's so focused.)
(Biting down)
Why aren't they biting?
(Why aren't they biting?)
(Gosh.)
In movies,
I always see piranhas attack people...
- when they're playing in the water.
- That's true.
I feel like I hear something.
(The piranhas people normally see)
(So peaceful)
(I'm here.)
(I'm here too.)
(No answer)
(They didn't expect fishing would be
lacking in interactions this much.)
(Pouting)
Fishing is all about waiting.
(So peaceful.)
That river was so peaceful.
It was so quiet.
Do they actually bite?
They seem to have realized
that we are fishing.
This isn't easy.
(Will they have to give up
on becoming Amazon's big fish king?)
(Flinch)
They're biting.
(They're biting!)
They're here.
Bite it. Just do it.
Fishing is my only hobby.
I'm excited about fishing in the Amazon.
(This is it!)
(Excited)
Gosh.
(He got nothing.)
I should wait a little bit more
before I pull.
(Glancing over)
- Give me some space.
- What?
- Move just a little.
- Okay.
(He moves right away
after the news of the fish biting.)
(While they were all
waiting for a bite...)
I got one.
- Oh, my.
- Oh, he got something.
- Oh, my!
I got one.
A red piranha.
(A red piranha)
Yes.
A piranha?
The stomach is red.
- Those teeth are scary.
- Gosh.
This is a red piranha.
He's really good at fishing.
(Turning around)
Why do you keep switching directions?
I started to feel a bit competitive.
- Let's concentrate.
- Oh, my!
- Oh, my.
- That side is better.
(Will Si Eon become
Amazon's big fish king?)
(No!)
Pull it up.
(It goes back in the water.)
- Oh, no!
- What a loss.
How sad.
- Gosh.
It fell in? That's a relief.
I need to catch at least one.
(After seeing Si Eon almost catch one,
Kian84 feels rushed.)
Maybe the smell of blood
has almost gone away.
I really want to catch one,
even if I have to make my hand bleed.
You need to at least get one to bite.
How infuriating.
(His anger explodes...)
(from Si Eon provoking him.)
I just kept doing that.
That's not going to work, Kian84.
What?
Be smooth.
(Irritated)
(As Si Eon was provoking Kian84...)
(Flying up)
(Eric catches one too?)
I saw one.
- Eric is kind of weak.
- He is.
I thought he'd be really good at fishing.
Eric.
(He's similar to us.)
(They just keep waiting for a bite.)
(Glancing over)
(Glancing over again)
Oh, baby.
(The piranha that the tour guide caught)
(He suddenly moves
to the inside of the boat.)
This...
Living? Go?
With the smaller ones,
they're supposed to be
from an underwater palace.
So we should let them live.
You have such a warm heart.
Sure. Go ahead.
Okay.
Oh, I got it.
I'm sorry.
(The piranha goes back
into the Amazon River.)
What? He's weird!
You didn't catch it. Someone else did.
Why are you letting it go?
That's true.
- That's true.
- That's true. He didn't catch it.
- It's fine if he caught it.
- Exactly.
He could have a family at home.
Gosh.
Si Eon. Do you know
how cutely the piranha flapped its tail...
while swimming away when I let it go?
I really don't understand you.
Finish.
- You're finished?
- Yes.
(They finish with no fish left.)
We'll change the system.
Okay. Let's go.
(The second course
of their Amazon fishing tour)
(Look over there.)
- They're using nets, I see.
- Yes. They're throwing in nets.
- Net fishing.
- I see.
(They exchange their fishing poles
for nets.)
Are they catching it just like that?
Yes.
(Will they be able to achieve their dreams
of coming back with a full boat?)
We must be riding in that.
Oh, a small boat.
Yes.
(A small size)
(Rocking side to side)
This looks even more dangerous.
(Just getting on is difficult.)
It sinks a little with the three of us on.
(Oh, my.)
(They could fall into the Amazon River
full of piranhas.)
Balance.
(Look at this.)
This is nice.
(So good)
(Their fishing tour has become
a little bit more analogue.)
How often does someone get a chance
to fish a boat like that on the Amazon?
- Exactly.
- That's why I'm jealous.
(They find a place where piranhas
might be hiding and anchor down.)
(Glancing over)
(Orlando was trying to balance,)
(but he falls into the river.)
- What happened?
- Oh, my.
(He falls into the river.)
Isn't that a bit dangerous?
Seriously. Can you just go in like that?
Won't piranhas attack if you swim in here?
- No attack.
- No attack?
Why? Why don't they attack?
(Piranhas only bite if you have a wound.)
(He dives in with ease
as if he came to play in the water.)
(Staring)
(He follows him into the Amazon River.)
- He has no fear.
- True.
I see. Is he trying to unravel the net?
That's it.
Oh, I see.
(Kian84 has naturally settled in.)
He's unraveling the net.
(He has totally become a local.)
(Good job.)
Gosh. That's how long they make it.
(They stand on the boat
and keep unraveling,)
(and soon, they have a net
that's crossing the giant Amazon River.)
So they put the net
all the way across like that?
They block it off completely.
- Now that...
- Oh, my!
(A surprising size)
(They put all of their strength together
to pull the net.)
(Jumping)
Their jumps are so cool.
(The Amazon has such lively views.)
- Oh, my.
- That's so cool!
Look over here, Kian84.
This is what peace is.
(The Amazon family became one
through fishing.)
I had so much fun.
I like how fishing makes me feel.
More so than catching the fish
and eating it,
it gives me a feeling of exaltation,
what with the nice air and all.
Fishing and riding in a boat.
It's not something you can do every day.
(A unique experience
you can't have anywhere else)
I'm really grateful for it.
- It's so cute how they jump.
- Seriously.
- Oh, my.
- Piranha.
(Piranhas caught in the net)
Four piranhas.
What if one of them is the one you let go?
- That could be.
- Didn't you think about that?
Then that one's just unlucky, honestly.
Yes. It was meant to die.
(Net fishing is over.)
I want to swim.
Do you want to ride the boat?
I'm going to swim.
(He kept talking about swimming
since the first day he got to Peru.)
(No swimming pool?)
(There's no swimming pool.)
(He kept trying to swim
even while fishing.)
(Finally,)
(his wish comes true.)
I think this is so cool.
He just bravely tries everything.
He must not have any regrets.
(A man who does things
just because he was born)
Gosh. Look at that. Look at that sunset.
This place is so beautiful.
You're such a free spirit, Kian84.
I almost swam across the river
at some point.
It was like a dream.
Will I have an experience like this again
in life? That's how it felt.
When the sun was setting,
(A double thumbs up
from feeling deeply moved)
Look. Who in Korea...
has rowed across the Amazon...
during a sunset?
I loved it.
(An unforgettable day on the Amazon River)
Is it deep?
I feel like I'm going to die.
- Stay next to me.
- Okay.
- Si Eon.
- What?
(He's already tired.)
Hurry.
- I'm tired.
- I can't go that way anymore.
It was a lot farther than I thought.
- Si Eon's so helpful.
- Hey. Be careful.
Hey. You can't hang on to that.
Hey. Don't hang on to that. Hey!
What is that?
- Did you hit him with the oar?
- Just stay still.
I was almost about to drown
because my endurance is bad.
How can you tell me not to hang on?
(So upset,
How can you tell me not to hang on?)
(He barely held on to his life
despite Si Eon stopping him.)
(Swaying side to side)
Hey.
Stay still.
Please stay still.
Let go. You shouldn't do that.
(He was stopped from boarding the boat,
so he just lies down.)
(An Amazon waterbed)
(Grabbing the boat)
There are no alligators in here, right?
No, there aren't.
If there are alligators, we're in trouble.
- Go faster. Alligators might come.
- Gosh!
I'm not worried about piranhas,
but I'm worried about alligators.
- I'm going!
- Go!
(Hurrying)
We're almost there.
(The fishing tour ends
somewhere in between romance and reality.)
(Completely exhausted)
(The two brothers are tired
from the intense fun in the water.)
My house is close by.
Come change your clothes and eat with us.
- Okay. We go with you?
- Yes. To my house.
Is going to Eric's house part of the tour?
The tour ended after net fishing.
I think he offered to let us wash up...
and eat at his house
because Kian84's clothes were wet.
- How kind.
- Really.
- He invited you guys over.
- It's over there.
- I see.
- Okay. Thank you.
(They carried their things together.)
Okay.
There's some heat
coming from my feet and shoes.
(They follow Eric.)
(After a few steps...)
- Is this your house?
- Yes. It's my house.
(Eric's house is right next to the river.
Welcome.)
- Excuse me.
- The stairs are very steep.
They build their houses
high up from the ground.
- During rainy season, the water comes up.
- I see.
(The house is built high up
as water levels rise during rainy season.)
This is my daughter.
- Hello.
- This is my grandmother.
- This is my mother.
- Hello.
- This is my youngest daughter.
- Baby? Is this your baby?
- Yes.
- Is this your wife?
- This is my wife, Esposa.
- Wife?
- Wife.
- Hello.
- What a big family.
You can put your stuff over here.
- Okay.
- Yes. Right over there.
Okay. Thank you.
You can wash up first,
- then you can change your clothes.
- Okay.
- Is it okay?
- Yes.
- Nice.
- Shower time.
Shower.
Kitchen.
(An open shower right next to the house)
I don't have pants.
You know how this works.
He assimilates easily anywhere.
(Splashing)
- My goodness.
- He just...
- He looks like he's at home.
- It's like he's at home.
That's practically your home.
(Si Eon came to Kian84's house shirtless.)
What happened to your body?
It looks like he drank a lot.
Splash some water on my back.
(Screaming)
(It's very cold.)
Is it good?
(Groaning)
Look. The front of your body.
(Splashing)
(One more time)
(Once again)
It's refreshing.
(Very satisfied)
What's more fascinating is,
we just swam in the Amazon river.
That water was from the river too.
(The water they used to wash up
was from the river as well.)
- What's that?
- They're all connected.
- That's why I...
- If that's the case, why...
Why did you shower?
Do you filter the water...
or use the river water as it is?
When you put the water in there,
the impurities sink.
- And you only use the water on top.
- Yes, the water on top.
(Rummaging)
I brought a towel.
(He dries himself.)
(He checks his handsome face
in the mirror.)
Kian84, don't you need to dry yourself?
It's okay.
(Wearing his clothes just like that)
His clothes...
(At a loss for words)
(Right, he is Kian84 after all.)
It was here. This must be our dinner.
(The dinner is getting prepared
in one corner of the kitchen.)
You get to eat Peruvian home-cooked food.
(They come for the fishing tour
and get to eat Peruvian food too.)
(Place vegetables...)
(on the piranhas they caught)
(Roll them with a banana leaf...)
(and place them on the fire.)
What's that? Alligator?
- It looks like fish.
- That's the one.
Pirarucu.
- Pirarucu?
- I see, pirarucu.
- Luxurious fish.
- Pirarucu?
- Yes.
Do they normally eat this?
They shared what they bought
for themselves.
- Hello.
(Shy)
(Hold on.)
Wife.
- Mother.
Mother.
(She is Eric's...)
- Sister.
Sister.
Oh, Father?
- Orlando.
- Father.
- Your father is Orlando?
- That's right.
- I only found out then.
Me too.
- Hello.
(My name is Orlando,)
(Eric's father.)
(He explained
when they met in the afternoon.)
(When they met Eric,)
(they thought
he was just a fishing tour guide.)
(That's true too.)
(We speak pretty good English, don't we?)
(We're pretty cool right now.)
(Embarrassed)
- Father.
- Captain.
- Hello.
- He's good at English.
- He is.
Is your father American?
- Your father...
- From the jungle.
Father, you look like
a Hollywood movie star.
Yes.
He didn't react much.
I am from Piura, in the north of Peru.
- Buran?
- Piura.
- Beach.
- Beach?
Yes. Mancora Beach.
- Beach.
- It's by the sea.
(They don't know what else to say.)
What is this?
If you have any questions,
feel free to ask.
We'll translate for you.
We couldn't hold a conversation,
so they translated for us.
Yes.
They didn't expect us to be that terrible.
I see.
Have any outsiders been here before?
Normally, they tour the Amazon
for a few days.
(They normally camp in the jungle.)
They rarely have people sleeping over
at their place.
They hunt and stuff.
I have a small group...
for expeditions.
And they go to different places.
Because of COVID-19,
they took a big blow as well.
Tourists didn't come.
It's been a while since they had tourists,
so I think they were being considerate.
I see.
(The dinner gets ready
with warm consideration.)
(Take out the rice wrapped
in banana leaves.)
That's their most common food.
They cook it with Banana leaves.
It's steamed rice.
Piranha.
(Grilled piranha they caught just now)
(Add deep-fried pirarucu.)
It looks good.
(A meal of the Amazon is completed.)
- Father, you first.
- Yes, Father.
- Grandmother.
Grandmother.
(Thank you.)
(From Grandmother to the baby,)
(everyone has dinner together.)
Thank you.
(Taking a bite)
(He picks up the whole piranha.)
(Taking a big bite)
You released a lot of them just now
saying you pitied them.
Exactly.
He looks as if he'd eat down to the bones.
Piranha tastes good.
Si Eon, try this.
Mine doesn't have much meat.
It doesn't have meat.
(Rummaging through for a long time)
(Little bit)
(He sure is a city man who eats a little.)
(He changes to pirarucu.)
- This is good.
- It's good.
Pirarucu...
Normally, fish meat crumples easily.
This is bouncy like pork.
It's chewy.
(Shaking)
What's that white stuff?
What's that?
Salad.
- This is salad.
- Salad.
- Palm.
- Palm tree stem?
- Take this.
- Thank you.
It's like noodles.
And you add sauce onto it.
- Like salad.
- Yes. That's salad.
I wonder what that tastes like.
You really eat it as if it's noodles.
It's really soft.
I thought it would feel like the bark
of a tree.
(Slurping)
That was good.
Keep eating this.
- Si Eon is almost...
- What's that?
What's that on his hair?
It's a moth.
I didn't know.
You've become a local.
You need more rice? Here.
(No and yes)
(The Amazon-customized prodigy
eats everything well.)
(Satisfied)
Look at that.
Yes?
Is that liquor? Makgeolli?
Whiskey?
- Whiskey? No whiskey?
- No.
It's our typical food.
It's a drink.
- Drink.
- Alcohol?
- No.
It's a traditional drink
we drink often in Peru.
It's called masato.
- Masato.
(Masato is
a Peruvian traditional drink...)
- Yuca.
(made by boiling yuca,
a common root vegetable in South America.)
- It looks like makgeolli.
- Yes.
If you leave it long enough,
it becomes like makgeolli.
I see.
I saw this in a documentary.
- Really?
- I saw this on "National Geographic."
Thank you.
(Drinking)
It tastes like yogurt.
Thank you.
(He pours it full and takes a sip.)
It brings back memories.
It tastes like yogurt mixed with coconut.
That was delicious.
The bug is still on my hair.
It's living on your hair.
(It has become one with him already.)
You know,
it's been a very long time
since I was invited to a family's meal.
I always eat alone.
My relatives' house is in Yeoju.
But that house is...
a very old-fashioned house. So...
It was a house with a furnace.
The kitchen was made of dirt too.
So things felt similar to me.
It reminded me a lot of when I was young.
(The meal reminded him of his childhood.)
- Have another dish.
- I already did.
You know Korean idols?
(He randomly starts looking
for similarities.)
BTS?
Yes, BTS.
You know BTS?
Si Eon,
aren't you close with one of the members?
He has a lot of Korean superstar friends.
Many of them.
(He means Si Eon is close with idols.)
Idol.
Do you know Korean...
- BLACKPINK?
- Yes.
BLACKPINK, BTS.
(Oh, right!)
Jennie is my friend.
What?
- What do you mean?
- Are you talking about MINO?
Really.
Last time, I did a video call with Jennie.
(When he camped with MINO,)
Who is it? What's happening?
(he had an honorable video call
with Jennie.)
(I'll root for you. I'm your big fan.)
She's already a friend to me.
(Even after then...)
(My phone friend)
(His love as a fan was revealed
in South America.)
I'm sorry.
How many times did you say that?
(He was so proud of himself for it.)
- She doesn't believe it.
- She didn't believe it.
We are, together, we...
You treated us.
(Treated?)
So I want to draw a picture for them
as a present.
Good, thank you.
I had nothing else to do for them.
That was nice.
Are you going to draw the family?
It will be too tough
to draw all the family members.
Should I draw Father...
or Grandmother?
- Grandmother?
Should I draw one
for the daughter as well?
(He already made up his mind.)
You...
Drawing present...
I'll draw you.
- Me? Yes.
- You?
- Okay.
- Draw her.
(He passes him a notebook they use
at home.)
Thank you very much.
(With a special model)
In a way, she is Generation MZ...
of Peru.
She's Generation MZ of Peru.
You wanted to draw Generation MZ of Peru.
- When I see youths like her,
- Generation MZ of the Amazon.
I want to root for them...
because they will have
to enter the real world soon.
Look here.
She might feel awkward
if she looks into my eyes.
(She stares as she is instructed.)
Oh, gosh.
- Are you okay?
- Okay.
(Fidgeting)
(Blinking)
Why are you so nervous?
I'm shy.
(Sighing)
(He tries again.)
(Clenching his eyes shut)
- I can't draw.
- Why?
I feel awkward whenever our eyes meet.
He's so shy about it.
The daughter is so nonchalant.
I'm shy.
Very difficult face.
Beautiful.
Because you're beautiful,
it's difficult.
Please translate.
It's hard to draw her
because she's pretty.
He says it's hard to draw you
because you're pretty.
(Grinning)
She likes it.
(Laughing)
I'm sorry.
(It's fun to watch.)
So I'm sorry.
(Shy)
Gosh, her throat must feel dry too.
Are you done eating?
- Yes, thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
- Draw quickly.
- I'm shy.
Let me collect myself first.
I'm not in my right mind
because I just ate.
(He'll draw next time
after collecting himself.)
Who is she?
- She's Mother.
- She's Mother?
(She is Eric's mother?)
She's not.
She's not. Mother's over there.
You're right.
Does Father have two wives?
Their culture is different from ours.
(What is she doing?)
This is masato.
Masato.
That day was the day for making masato.
They drink it all the time like water.
- They drink masato like that?
- Yes, they need to drink all the time.
These are a cleanly-washed mortar...
and yuca, washed and boiled once.
Yuca.
When you boil it,
the texture becomes like potato.
You boil it once before crushing it.
Come to think of it, you boil rice once
before making makgeolli as well.
You need to boil it to ferment it.
- If you don't, it won't ferment.
- You're right, for fermentation...
(The process is rather similar.)
I'll do it.
- He'll do it.
- It must be hard.
This is pretty tough.
(Scraping)
(She puts it into her mouth.)
Is that how you eat it?
It's like...
She's eating a lot.
- She must be hungry.
- She must've been starving.
- Why is she eating?
- She keeps eating.
(She munches...)
(then spits it out.)
(Spitting it out)
She...
Really?
(They're at a loss for words.)
(Shocked)
(Innocent)
No way.
That's how they ferment it.
No.
Yes. I watched this...
on "National Geographic."
(You really spit it?)
Yes.
Really?
The city man is shocked.
She's really keeping it in her mouth.
Of course.
She ferments it in her mouth first.
That's what we drank?
(Masato they drank 10 minutes ago)
They drank a lot.
It tastes like yogurt.
That's what we drank?
(The secret to the taste is revealed.)
That's right.
It's rude to do that.
(Chewing)
(Spitting)
You chew it to ferment the drink.
That's right.
Yes, that's the wisdom of life for them.
(The wisdom of life
that was passed down to them)
This requires a lot of work.
(Still, it's too hard for me
to accept it.)
Your reaction is so funny.
I didn't expect her
to spit out what she was chewing.
Masato... Gosh.
It's a culture shock, honestly.
I liked it.
It's worth trying once.
(The fermenting factory operates nonstop.)
If you keep it without chewing it,
it will rot.
Instead, we brush our teeth cleanly
before chewing.
(The city man has a hard time adjusting
to the cultural difference.)
(Devastated)
(Laughing)
That's rude, Si Eon.
What does that make Mother?
Keep quiet.
She's not Mother.
Mother is over there.
Then she must be the aunt.
She's their aunt.
- Aunt.
- I told you she was their aunt.
(Auntie that lives next to Eric's house)
What's more fascinating is...
that she's the only one who can make it
in that town.
(She is the only one
who can make masato in this town.)
(Instead of mother's touch,
it's Auntie's mouth.)
What's with "Auntie's mouth?"
Do you have to eat all of this?
(Eating)
- All?
We ferment a fully-chewed dough.
To chew all of that...
Imagine how hard it is for her.
(Mix sugar to the dough and ferment it,
and it's done.)
Right, they add sugar in it.
(After that...)
(Staring intensely)
(The memory of masato will remain...)
(as an intense one.)
(Sighing)
(The strong impression lingers.)
It must be so hard for Auntie.
Look at her sweating.
(Sweating buckets)
We need to be thankful when drinking this.
(After watching her make it
with a lot of effort,)
(he works up the courage
and takes another sip.)
Drinking after knowing this...
It is a bit tough.
(It's a bit tough to eat it
now that I know how it's made.)
All right. Let's bring out the masato
we brought and give it out.
There's masato?
I saw the producer spitting
something out earlier from upstairs.
- I saw him constantly chewing something.
- Right.
I don't think he's an expert.
If you want to try it, call us.
- We'll go and chew it for you.
- Really?
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the food.
- Sure.
(They're checking the remaining budget.)
Hey, do you want me to tell you
tomorrow's schedule again?
Wait. Did you actually plan our trip?
I only planned one thing for now.
What did you plan?
I planned on riding a motorcycle.
- I wanted to do that abroad.
- Okay.
We have to make two transfers.
(He looked up plane tickets at home.)
We can rent motorcycles there.
(Si Eon planned this activity himself.)
(Riding a motorcycle in Cusco)
Going on a motorcycle tour
while traveling overseas...
was my biggest wish...
just like Kian84 wanted
to come to the Amazon.
(Si Eon enjoyed driving motorcycles
only in Korea.)
I used to drive that back in the day.
(Will he be able to fulfill his wish
of riding a motorcycle abroad?)
Si Eon only thought about
riding the motorcycle. Seriously.
- That's the only thing I wanted to do.
- Right.
- That was the most important goal.
- Just that.
- And it was my dream.
- Right.
Anyway, when we get up in the morning,
we'll go back to the airport.
The same airport we landed at.
Then we'll take the plane
to go to Cusco from Lima?
Yes.
We'll arrive in Cusco tomorrow.
- We'll get our lodging there.
- Okay.
- We'll take a day to regroup ourselves.
We really need to rest up.
Or we could cause accidents the next day.
I'll be fine.
- That was around 8 p.m.
- I see.
I have a T-shirt.
So let me know if you need it.
Okay.
It's pretty late.
Why don't you sleep here tonight?
Really? Can we?
Yes. You can sleep here.
- But there's nothing we can do for them.
- Of course.
(Pondering)
Okay?
(Their stuff is at the lodging
where he extended his stay.)
Okay?
- One minute.
- Thank you.
That's... Si Eon. What was his name?
- Eric.
- Eric?
(He turns on Kian TV
after pondering for a moment.)
Everyone, we're in the Amazon now.
We were just going to fish
and swim for a bit.
But he said he would let us crash
at his house for one night.
So we'll sleep here tonight.
His family is here.
So we'll try to stay out of their hair.
I hope we can have a good time
before going back.
Sleeping over there
wasn't part of the tour.
Right. They have their own privacy too.
- Right. They're so kind.
- Yes.
- I feel awful staying here, though.
- Gosh.
Should we do something for them
for letting us sleep here tonight?
Yes. Shouldn't we help them or something?
- You must have felt bad.
- Is there anything we can do for them?
(They will be returning the kindness
tomorrow morning.)
- Did you help them with the chores?
- Gosh.
- My legs. Gosh.
- You should.
(An Amazon way of paying for the lodging)
Then yesterday,
I shouldn't have extended my stay
at the lodging.
- Hammocks. Yes?
- Thank you.
- I'll set them up for you.
Since there aren't any beds,
they will sleep on the hammocks.
Hammocks?
Hammocks. I see.
Gosh. This is a great experience.
But I've never slept on hammocks before.
(Hang both ends of the hammocks
on the ceiling.)
(And then it's done.)
(Amazed)
What's the name of this?
Hammocks.
How many times do we have to tell you?
- Hamburgers?
- Let me lie down here.
- Hammocks.
(Trying out the hammock
for the first time)
Hammocks.
(Surprised)
- Good?
- I've seen that.
Good. It was really comfortable.
I'm serious.
- And this is so spacious.
- Right. It stretched a lot.
- Is it comfortable?
- It's so comfortable.
It's comfortable,
but I still need to get used to it.
(The younger one lies down
just like the older one.)
(Feeling uncomfortable)
Are we supposed to sleep like this?
It's sort of bending a lot for you, right?
- Right. I see.
- Then move up a bit.
I should move up.
- I just heard it rip.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- Wait. This...
(Wriggling)
Like this.
By the way, I've never slept
in a hammock like this before.
Hey, let me know
if you need a pillow. I have that too.
But Si Eon,
my body is at a 90-degree angle.
- This...
- You need to move that up.
I already moved up. Wait.
- You mean I should raise the hammock?
- Yes.
You need to raise it and spread it out.
- Okay.
- Like mine.
I should raise it later.
(It's not easy to sleep in a hammock.)
Gosh. This is so comfortable.
- It was so comfortable.
- It's more comfortable than I thought.
We should get an early start tomorrow.
We should leave early.
First of all, as for tomorrow,
we'll be moving around a lot,
but let's rest up once we arrive.
Okay.
That way, we can drive the motorcycle.
Let's go to sleep. Good job today.
- Goodnight.
Gosh. I got to sleep properly
after three nights.
I bet you slept so well then.
(Meanwhile, many stars have embroidered
the sky in the Amazon.)
(Snoring)
(The two of them are sleeping soundly
while snoring away.)
(The sky slowly brightens.)
(The sea of clouds springs up magically.)
(Busy movements of nature
signal the start of a day.)
(There's a rainbow in the sky.)
(And the kids are already up.)
(It's a bright morning in the Amazon.)
(They're still sleeping
at 90-degree angles.)
(Opening)
(Flinching)
(He gets up with a stiff body.)
- Hi.
- Hello.
(Groaning)
(He escapes the hammock
with some difficulty.)
(Squirming)
Oddly, it got cold during the night.
(Peeking)
Kian84, let's get up.
What? I'm up.
(Wiggling)
I should brush my teeth.
My breath stinks.
(I slept so well.)
I should brush my teeth.
- Si Eon.
- Yes?
- We only have one, right?
- Yes.
- Can I get the toothpaste?
- Okay.
(Smelling)
(Rubbing)
(The socks pass the test
and are worn again.)
(He borrows the toothpaste...)
(and puts it in his mouth.)
(Spreading)
(He's done
once he rinses it with the water.)
Oh, my gosh.
Hello.
(He films in the morning
after washing up.)
We slept in the owner's room for a night.
There weren't a lot of bugs in here.
There weren't any bugs.
It was comfortable to sleep here.
But the problem is...
the rooster.
Was it you?
It wasn't dawn.
This crazy rooster kept crying all night.
(The problematic night)
(Cock-a-doodle-doo)
- It kept crying when we were sleeping.
- Gosh.
(The rooster didn't rest
when it was pitch-dark outside.)
Gosh. That crazy rooster.
"Crazy rooster."
(Getting up)
(He couldn't hold it back anymore
and got up to inspect it.)
(Rattling)
The rooster crossed the line
it shouldn't have.
Roosters don't cry late at night.
It just cried when it wanted to.
Right.
I went out to make it quiet.
But the dogs...
They snarled at me.
(Snarling)
I saw two pairs of eyes gleam at night.
I was scared, so I came up.
Then the rooster cried again.
(Cock-a-doodle-doo)
I kept waking up and falling asleep.
That's how I slept.
(Boohoo.)
- Which one was it?
- That rooster.
- I can shove sticky rice in your...
- Hey.
- Which one was it?
- I think it was this one.
Seriously. Consider yourself lucky.
Gosh. I couldn't sleep
because of that rooster.
(They are chasing away the rooster.)
(Eric is doing a house chore.)
(They start their day
as they retrieve the net.)
We spread out a small net last night.
- In the morning? Now?
- Yes.
They're alive.
(Freshly caught fish)
He must have caught them now.
A sardine.
Good, right?
How do you ask him if he needs any help?
Don't ask me.
(We should do something in return.)
(Surprised at the sight of the machete)
- A machete?
- Yes.
Colombia.
(I see. This is a machete.)
Do you want to come to the farm?
Sure.
Let's help them with the morning chore.
(They head out to Eric's farm together.)
(In this vibrant rainforest
of the Amazon River...)
How beautiful.
(Nature is preserved in Eric's farm.)
This is so beautiful.
Amazing.
(Surprised)
(A bicycle?)
She's on her way to school. To study.
- School?
- Yes. School.
- Yes.
- I see.
- School.
- She was a student.
- Gosh. She was going to Eric's farm?
- No.
- There's a school?
- There's a school.
- I see.
She was riding the bicycle to school.
That was around 6 a.m.
(She went to school at 6 a.m.)
Gosh. I went to my relative's house
in the countryside...
when I was in elementary school.
My cousin used to go to school
on a trail like this.
He took this kind of trail to school?
It was unpaved back then.
It reminded me of the Amazon in a way.
No, Kian84. Things weren't
this underdeveloped when we were young.
- But my relative's house...
- Were there trees like that?
No, listen.
When I went to my relative's house,
it was like this.
The bus ran every four hours.
I went to school while walking
on the grass with morning dew.
(What's he talking about?)
It's shocking that
you don't seem to understand this.
I'm sorry, but I'm a city man.
Right. That's surprising.
(He looks around the Amazon
with this city man.)
Bananas.
Kian84, isn't this cotton?
It really is cotton.
(Eric demonstrates
how to use the machete.)
Gosh. This is sharper than the trimmer.
My back hurt more.
(They start to cut down the grass
with Eric.)
(Clean)
- In one swing.
- That's a trimmer.
This is no joke.
(He pulls something out
after cutting the grass.)
That's the root.
(The root of the yuca is revealed.)
(Shaking)
That's yuca.
- They are root plants.
- Not to damage the roots.
(Not to lose out to him,
Kian84 shows amazing power.)
(They carry the crops on their shoulders.)
- Okay, let's go home.
- Okay.
We're doing a lot of cardio this morning
on an empty stomach.
(They return home with yuca.)
- We bring yuca for masato.
- Wait.
This is so long.
(He groans as he's exhausted.)
We should have gotten more.
(Dirty)
(To chase away the heat,
he pours a bucket of water on him.)
(Dirty)
(Rubbing)
This is cool.
(He has a sip of water
after digging out the yuca.)
Gosh. It was so tough to harvest the yuca.
That's not a one-man's job.
(Sprawling out)
(His socks have turned dark.)
Gosh. Living in the Amazon isn't easy.
(Packing)
Gosh. I don't have shorts in this big bag.
I'll cut out your pants with the machete.
- Kian84.
- Yes?
I'm sorry. I don't want to live like you.
Then buy a pair.
(They started off the trip
very differently.)
(As they chat in the room...)
(Sizzling)
(They are busy in the kitchen
cooking breakfast.)
(Chopping)
We'll have breakfast.
- If you want some, come with me.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Hello.
- Okay. We have...
- Yes.
fried eggs.
- Yes. That's an American breakfast.
- American breakfast.
- The city man must like that.
- Coffee.
- We have butter and bread too.
- Okay.
And bananas.
(It would be a shame
to leave out the bananas.)
Okay. Dig in.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
We woke up and helped them at the farm.
- And they cooked breakfast for us.
- One, two...
It's universal all over the world
that people have three meals a day.
All right. I'll eat my breakfast now.
Eat a lot.
(This city man is happy to see food
he's familiar with.)
Sometimes,
they served hamburgers in the military.
I used to spread jam like this
on my burgers.
- Like this?
- Yes.
Like this. And that's it.
(The military-style burger in the Amazon)
- That looks good.
- It was good.
(The food in the Amazon
was shocking to this city man.)
(Hesitant)
(Picking at his food)
(Si Eon had a hard time
eating the local meals.)
It's been a while
since you enjoyed your food.
- That was my first meal.
- I'm glad.
(Munching)
Hey, this is slightly refreshing.
- It's good.
- You know?
(The family is happy
to see him enjoy his food.)
It was really tasty.
I'm glad.
- I loved it.
- It was an American-style breakfast.
Right. I was wondering
if they cooked that for us.
- But that's their typical breakfast.
- That's their breakfast.
- That's their typical breakfast.
- That's what they eat for breakfast.
(Enjoying the meal)
(Chuckling)
(Why are they laughing?)
(A cup of masato)
- I'm good.
- Me too.
- I'm okay.
- Okay.
- No, thanks.
Okay.
No. Do you want some more of this?
Why?
(He laughs it off to turn it down.)
- He was the only one who cracked up.
- Why?
(Let me know if you want more.)
But we harvested a lot this morning.
Masato is their staple here.
I had fun yesterday.
We fished,
screamed, and shook the canoe.
It was so fun.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Thank you.
You guys became close
after spending only one day.
Eric. You...
Machete.
- An ax.
- That's "ax" in English.
- He said that in Korean.
- "Ax?"
- Yes.
You were bad at fishing.
(We weren't lucky that day.)
I started to crack jokes.
Tell him we should go fishing again. Go.
(I can catch fish this time.)
Go.
- Thank you.
Picture.
Father. Picture together?
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Outside.
Go.
(As Eric's family doesn't have
a family picture,)
(Si Eon wants to take their family picture
with his instant camera.)
Be careful.
House in the back.
House in the back?
- House.
(Stand in line here.)
- Okay.
- Should they stand there?
- So I get their house in the picture.
- Okay.
- Right.
- It was an instant camera.
Hey, do you want to be in the photo too?
I should be.
Don't ruin their family picture.
- Let's take one for the family first.
- What?
Okay.
One, two...
(Clicking)
- Okay.
- Stay.
- Okay. Come on.
- Kian84, get in the picture.
- Let me join you.
- That was for us.
Right.
(Kian84 walks over
to take a picture with the family.)
- You stood right next to her.
- One, two...
- The spots...
- But you didn't draw her.
three.
(He met them in the Amazon by accident.)
- That's a great picture.
- That's a good picture.
(But the family gave them
an unforgettable memory.)
(Thanks for the family photo,
Uncle Si Eon.)
- I'm glad you brought that.
- Yes.
- I'm so glad.
I had an instant camera
and a film camera too.
You were fully prepared.
- Thank you.
(They took pictures with the family.)
I'll give it to you.
Can you draw me?
Okay.
She wants me to draw her.
I promised last night.
Okay?
(He confidently grabbed his pen to draw.)
(Tell her...)
(that it's hard to draw her
because she's pretty.)
(The portrait drawing class
was postponed.)
- She must have looked forward to it.
- Right.
Okay.
(Artist Kian84 grabs a log.)
I'm nervous.
You sit here.
Okay.
What's that? A spoon?
I didn't have a drawing board.
So I used that instead.
(He sits down right in front of her.)
(Flapping his lips)
Okay. You look there.
(He gives it another try to draw Sharon.)
(Drawing)
(He only has a piece of paper
and a pencil.)
(But he's fully focused.)
(Last night,
they went out to pick off bananas.)
There are a lot of snakes at night.
So be careful when you walk.
- She told you to be careful.
- Okay.
In Korea... Snakes...
Me... Young...
- Country...
- "Mi Young?"
- Or Young Mi?
- He said names. Mi Young and Young Mi.
"I lived in the countryside
when I was young."
- I see. When you were young.
- I see.
Gosh. That long sentence
turned into two words?
Yes, it did.
(They weren't able to communicate...)
Right here.
(But they formed a friendship
while picking off the bananas at night.)
Gosh. I bet you won
like 200 brownie points with Sharon.
(He draws Sharon's face with care.)
(As a model,
she concentrates on her posture.)
(Scratching)
(They keep...)
(scratching themselves.)
(They scratch themselves everywhere
while facing each other.)
(Is it taking too long?)
Just one minute.
It must be difficult
because of the mosquitoes.
Yes.
This will make the mosquitoes stay away.
(Flapping)
You should fan her.
(Volunteering for the model)
Hang in there for a while, Solar.
Usually, it's difficult.
- Her name is Sharon.
- Sharon.
I'm sorry, Sharon.
- He called her Solar.
- Solar is a MAMAMOO member.
Right.
Because of the flies
that suck blood from you,
my skin stung so much.
I still did the best I could.
That's when I got all the bug bites.
His legs got bitten all over.
- Oh, no.
- The camera director went...
to the hospital because of the sandflies.
- What?
- Because he got bitten so much?
- He got bitten a lot.
- Who is he?
He's a city boy.
You mean the director
who's wearing a sweater vest?
(While struggling against sandflies,)
(he tries his best to draw well.)
(He doesn't straighten up even once.)
To...
- Sharon.
How is it spelled? Sharon.
Here.
Here you go.
(Staring)
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
(Thank you.)
Do you like it?
Yes, it's very pretty.
Thank you.
- She must be moved.
- Seriously.
He made a drawing of me.
It looked really nice,
so I will keep it.
I did it suddenly in the middle of a meal.
I used a pen on a small notebook,
so I couldn't draw well.
Today, the paper was bigger.
I used a pencil, so it was much better.
(He feels proud of it.)
(You seem especially nice to Sharon.)
No.
I feel like her older cousin.
I hope that she'll meet a kind man
in Iquitos.
Sharon.
(All of a sudden)
Meet a good man,
and don't get your heart broken.
(Drawing that he made
from the heart of her older cousin)
"The heart of her older cousin?"
(After some drawing
in the peaceful Amazon)
(Exclaiming)
I only used a toothbrush
from this heavy backpack.
(Silence)
Let's go.
Kian84. Do you want to stay longer?
- You look quite sad to leave.
- No.
- We should go.
- Are you okay?
(Trudging)
Time passes by too fast.
I know.
(As intense as it was,
the time passed by fast.)
Thank you for coming.
- Thank you.
- Hope to see you again.
Feel free to come next time
like it was your home.
Come to Korea.
The whole family. Come to Korea.
Of course.
(Kian84 stays quiet.)
He seems sad.
It was sad to leave after one night.
They probably grew on you.
- Of course.
- It was a bit sad.
- He gets attached easily.
- He does.
No.
(Kian84 stays quiet.)
Follow my Instagram.
- Instagram.
Do you have a pen?
Give him a pen.
Here you go.
Instagram?
You shouldn't write on your hand.
Write on hers.
(It was almost worse than not writing.)
On your hand.
- Your ID.
- My ID?
- Can I write in Korean?
- No.
That's...
I'm sorry.
(Trying not to laugh)
- K-I-A.
- A.
- I don't think this is it.
- A-N.
It's Kim Hee Min.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Write on her other hand.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Write on here.
I'll write here.
(After a long attempt)
Okay, this is my Instagram.
- Please follow.
- Okay.
(He forgot to write the number.)
Oh, my.
Did you become friends with her
on Instagram?
When we arrived in the city,
she hadn't contacted me.
That's unfortunate.
- Bye.
(It's time to leave.)
I don't feel good about leaving...
after just one day.
It feels touching like visiting relatives.
I don't get to see my relatives often.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Eric.
(The family members wave their hands.)
- Bye.
She keeps holding the drawing.
I didn't want to come to the Amazon,
but when would I get to go deep
into the Amazon again...
and share a meal and talk with the locals?
We did a lot including axing...
and fishing on a boat.
You don't get a chance to do this.
It was great.
I expected sensibility to dry out
as you get old,
but it hasn't completely dried out in me.
You have something pure in you.
- Now...
- There's something humid.
Humid?
(He means that it hasn't dried out.)
What do you mean by humid?
Are you heading to the airport?
When we get to the airport,
we'll head to Lima.
- Lima?
- Thank you.
(There's no overland route
to the exterior.)
(They head to the airport to fly.)
- Do you want some ice cream?
- Ice cream?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Ice cream.
What's this?
Is this like the Baskin Robbins of Peru?
(Small happiness found on the street)
Iquitos.
(Iquitos Airport)
(On the front yard of the airport,)
(the running fanatic starts to run.)
- Why is he running?
- I wonder.
We have a lot of waiting time.
I didn't get to work out today.
(But still...)
It's about 28C right now.
(Actually, it's 34C.)
I think it's about 28C.
(He runs in the tropical heat wave.)
I feel bad about making
the camera directors turn on...
their cameras.
Please take a break.
(After running, they flew
for an hour and 45 minutes.)
(They arrived at Lima Airport.)
Everyone, from Lima Airport,
we'll go to the south to a place
called Cusco.
After a layover here,
I'll film again when we get to Cusco.
Kian84.
Aren't you tired?
No, I'm completely awake.
(Laughing)
Where are you taking me?
- We'll be going to Cusco.
- Yes.
It's about 3,000m above sea level.
That information is important.
You have to take this.
You'll get altitude sickness.
- Take one pill.
- Right.
I'll take care of you
if you get altitude sickness.
- Okay.
- Take it.
I hope they won't suffer.
I think medicine is necessary to pack.
- Right.
- It's a must.
I died without it.
How long is the flight?
- It's an hour and a half.
- An hour and a half?
I should hurry.
For our lodging,
I have to make a reservation now
with the owner.
The lodging?
- Is the owner Korean?
- Yes.
That's good.
(Making a real-time reservation
of the lodging at the airport )
- He's dependable.
- Yes.
Si Eon.
(You can count on me, Kian84.)
If I didn't reserve it,
we would have slept on the street.
It's convenient when
your traveling buddy likes to plan.
Right.
Suddenly, they're calling people
going to Cusco.
The camera got lowered all of a sudden.
- The screen...
- It means that he's in a hurry.
(They arrive in Cusco
after flying an hour and a half.)
Hello, Kian84 TV viewers.
We finally arrived...
- We arrived in Cusco.
Symptoms of altitude sickness should
appear...
starting from now.
How do you feel?
My ears are slightly muffled
now that I got off the airplane.
The route from here
to Uyuni Salt Flat will continue...
to get higher.
Do you get...
altitude sickness
when you go to a place...
- of a high altitude?
- Yes.
How high should the altitude be
to get altitude sickness?
Do Yeon will explain.
I mean...
- Jang Do Yeon.
- Yes?
When you reach a place with an altitude
over 2,000m to 3,000m,
you get altitude sickness
as you run out of oxygen...
and feel uncomfortable.
Some of the symptoms are headaches,
nausea,
vomiting, hypothermia,
and difficulty in breathing.
Mount Baekdu has an altitude of 2,700m.
I heard that Cusco has...
an altitude of 3,000 to 3,500m.
You know well.
When you take a plane up there...
- I asked that question.
- Me too.
There's a control of air pressure
on the plane.
- A control?
- If that breaks,
everyone will pass out.
There has been an accident...
- because everyone passed out.
- It broke.
Gosh.
Tell them about Pani Bottle.
By the way, where is Pani Bottle?
- He is...
- Is he the one who's filming you?
He's traveling.
I really want to meet him.
Kian84, you should put on something thick.
You'll be cold.
Everyone is wearing a padded jacket.
It's not cold at all right now.
You put it on.
For me, this isn't cold.
(Real men wear short-sleeved T-shirts
no matter the temperature.)
I should put it on.
- I'm sorry.
- He's putting it on right away.
- He is.
- It was cold.
My love, corduroy.
(He puts on a jacket
that fits him perfectly.)
I've had this jacket for a long time.
Is this altitude sickness?
It's hard to breathe.
That's altitude sickness.
This is...
- It feels like...
- It's because of the backpack.
Even if I breathe deeply,
it doesn't feel completely refreshing.
In this case,
we should inhale through the nose
and exhale through the mouth.
(Inhaling)
- Really?
- Yes.
Is it effective?
It's definitely effective.
Taxi?
Yes, taxi.
Where are you going, my friend?
He's catching a taxi.
Please go to Calle Recoleta.
I knew it.
- He's prepared.
- He's all prepared.
Okay. Did you see that?
- How long will it take?
- Ten minutes.
- Twenty minutes?
- Okay.
- Ten?
- Okay, thank you very much.
- Ten minutes.
(They load the taxi with their luggage.)
Thank you very much.
Get in.
Si Eon, I couldn't breathe
because my bag was too heavy.
I thought so.
- That's a relief.
- My bag got heavier...
because I packed a lot.
Wait, where's the meter?
Right.
Taxi, meter?
- Meter?
- Price.
- That's the Korean pronunciation.
Price. How much is it?
It's 30 soles.
- Twenty?
- No, 30.
Thirty soles? Okay.
- Okay.
- Okay?
We paid 20 soles for a tuk-tuk ride.
Thirty soles sounds about right.
(They figured out the taxi price in Peru.)
(The streets at night appear unfamiliar
in the new city.)
Si Eon, look at the view outside.
It looks different from Iquitos.
It's completely different.
(The view of Cusco has a different charm
from Iquitos.)
(Cusco, the last capital city
of the Inca Empire)
Look at the view at night.
I really want to visit there.
(An altitude of 3,399m)
It looks amazing.
This is one of the hot places.
I really want to go there.
It looks completely different.
(Blended with its ancient history)
(A cultural heritage where traces
of two civilizations exist)
- Thank you.
(Very tired)
(Current location, they must
get to an alley from the avenue.)
Let's go.
Isn't it this house?
We have to look at the location.
Looking at the image will be confusing.
They built it recently. Take a look.
This is it.
Did they repaint it?
(The exterior looks too clean.)
- What?
- It's not this way.
- This isn't it.
- It's that one.
- This is it.
- Yes, let's go up. This way.
(They found something.)
It's not it.
Si Eon, what's the name of the lodging?
Comma Cusco.
(They look for the lodging again.)
It's a little frustrating.
(He doesn't know how to read the map.)
Si Eon, can I look at the map?
I'll take a look.
You shouldn't just look at the image.
Google Maps doesn't show the destination.
(Those with a bad sense of direction can't
tell where the destination is.)
Hold on.
It's like this.
- It's this way.
- Thank you.
(He's thankful for everything.)
- Is it that way?
- Si Eon, I think I can find it.
(Following)
(Kian84 - He doesn't plan,)
(but he's good at reading the map.)
(Si Eon - He has plans,)
(but he can't read the map.)
This is it.
It's this way.
(Their relationship is
definitely symbiotic.)
- This is it.
- It's unfamiliar to see him...
lead the way with the map.
I found it.
It's Korean. It's the only Korean place.
Let's take a photo here.
- Let's take a photo in front of "Comma."
- Okay.
I can't capture the sign.
"Comma" doesn't show.
- It doesn't matter.
- Let's go in first.
- Hello.
- There's ramyeon.
You're the first Koreans we met in Peru.
I'm glad to meet you.
Seriously.
This place is...
run by sisters.
Are three of you sisters?
- Yes, we're sisters.
- Really?
Would you like to check in?
Who made the reservation?
Please come this way.
That's amazing.
It's not easy for sisters to run
a lodging abroad.
Usually, the check-in is at 2 p.m.,
but since you came late,
you can check in right away.
If you leave us your laundry,
it takes about half a day.
If you give us your shoes...
Yes, we have to wash everything.
Si Eon, what's important is,
how many nights will we spend here?
For now, I reserved two days,
tonight and tomorrow night.
- Tomorrow night too?
- Yes.
- Are we sharing a room?
Could you separate us?
- Separate?
- He wants a separate room.
- Can we get a separate room?
- Really?
- Then...
- Do what you'd like.
One of you can sleep in the bathroom.
- Send him to the bathroom.
- Come on.
We will go upstairs...
and bring down our laundry.
- We have to eat dinner too.
- Okay.
Si Eon, we should pay first.
The dormitory is 15 dollars per night.
For two people and two nights,
the total is 60 dollars.
- Sixty dollars.
- Yes.
- That's nice.
- How much is a bottle of soju?
It's 30 soles.
Isn't it more expensive than lodging?
It costs about 10,000 won
when you're abroad.
Can we get soju and ramyeon?
I'll buy them for you. Wait. Go upstairs.
- Take a look at the room first.
- First...
- Wait.
- Okay.
I was talking to the dog.
It's been only two days
since you arrived in Peru,
- but you crave soju and ramyeon already.
- Right.
- It felt like it had been two months.
- In the Amazon...
It had been only one day,
but I was happy to see it.
- Ramyeon after a shower.
- Yes.
- I was happy to see it.
- Ramyeon is the best.
- You make some ramyeon.
- I was really looking forward to it.
Go slowly.
We're at a high altitude,
so you should climb up slowly.
- That way, you won't feel sick.
- At a high altitude,
isn't it dangerous...
- if you run out breath?
- Yes.
You feel a bit dizzy.
Is it because my bag is heavy?
Gosh.
- I don't think I can go up farther.
- I see.
Do you feel sick...
- even inside?
- I felt sick since that moment.
It feels different.
- Welcome.
- It looks nice.
- It looks really nice.
- Put down your bags.
- Wait a minute.
- Go ahead and sit down.
(Dizzy)
- He looks completely pale.
- Oh, no. He looks sick.
My ears are so muffled.
- The oxygen...
- Like on top of a mountain.
Right.
This is the room that you will use.
It's a four-person dormitory,
but no one is using it right now.
You can share this bunk bed.
- Like this?
- Yes.
Here are the lockers.
You can keep your backpacks here.
He lost weight in an instant.
- His face is getting worse.
- Oh, no.
It was really difficult.
You'll find small pots here...
to make simple meals like ramyeon.
I can't see clearly.
- Isn't this it?
- Yes.
You might get the chills at night.
I keep seeing her afterimage as she moves.
Hot water.
- Is that how it appears?
- Yes.
- Seriously.
- If it gets cold?
- You can keep it in your arms.
- Just use the sleeping bag.
- Thank you.
- That's all.
We'll bring down our laundry.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Kian84, I feel a bit dizzy.
(Dizzy)
Will you be able to wash up?
You can wash up, right?
- Will you wash me?
- Shall I?
I'm afraid that you'll pass out.
Can you put the shoes by the entrance?
These?
Gosh.
(With the fragrance
from the Amazon sealed inside)
Did the owner bring...
It's strange. I feel like I'm tipsy.
Right.
When you drink a lot,
you get a hangover the next day.
It feels similar to that.
You saved money on alcohol.
- That's a good way to think about it.
- You don't have to drink.
The power of positivity.
That's too positive.
There's one positive side.
- I'll take a shower.
- Go ahead.
Gosh, I feel strange.
I hope that he'll get better.
- Do you feel refreshed?
- Yes.
(Tired)
(His mouth might tear.)
I feel really refreshed.
(Scratching)
I should take a shower.
I'll go and wash up.
(Kian84 goes to take a shower.)
(Si Eon brings out the laundry.)
That startled me.
Slowly.
This is tiring.
(Struggling)
Yes?
(You can't help but laugh
when you see him.)
You take good care of your skin.
- I can take that.
- Yes.
We'll have it done tomorrow.
You can give it to us.
(He takes something to the kitchen.)
What is he taking?
Is he going to cook?
- It was a special day.
- Really?
- That's why.
- Are you preparing for it?
Today is Kian84's birthday.
(Goodness.)
Oh, dear.
What a good friend he is.
I prepared Gijang seaweed
for his birthday.
Gijang seaweed and dried pollack.
- I got the best quality.
- I brought it from Korea.
Really?
It must've been heavy to carry it around.
(Can you get me some beef for soup?)
(Yes. We'll try.)
(A little bit of soy sauce too.)
(We have soy sauce.)
My goodness, Si Eon.
- That's what I did.
- Oh, my. Si Eon.
(He quickly prepares ingredients
while Kian84 is taking a shower.)
I already practiced at home.
I won't try to be funny.
I'll make delicious seaweed soup for him.
- You haven't seen it yet, then.
- No. I didn't know he was cooking.
(He stir-fries seaweed in perilla oil.)
It's a lot of beef.
(He'll stir-fry beef too.)
You should cut it.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
(Flustered)
(Oh, dear.)
I haven't cut meat.
(He starts cutting the meat with a knife.)
(I'm a little worried.)
He's quite fast.
Yes.
(The masked man...)
(gives his full attention to the seaweed.)
(Cutting)
Dried pollack seaweed soup.
It must be good.
I won't try to be funny.
I'll just be serious.
(Looking around)
(He gets some water in a bowl
and comes back to the pot.)
How touching this is.
It wasn't even in Korea.
He made it for you overseas.
(He cuts meat at the same time!)
(His practice is paying off.)
(Flowing)
(Floundering)
(Lost)
I spilled some water.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
That's okay.
(Laughing)
It's all right.
(He was a little clumsy,
but he continues cooking.)
(Will his seaweed soup be okay?)
The key to making good seaweed soup is
to simmer it.
(Laughing)
It sounds like I'm adding poison.
It's almost done.
(Kian84 came out of the shower.)
I'm hungry.
He's going down.
No way.
Do you have instant rice?
No, we don't.
(Will his surprise party be ruined
like this?)
(He's just roaming around
after taking a shower.)
I'm hungry.
He's going down.
No way.
Do you have instant rice?
No, we don't.
It sold out.
- You don't have rice.
- No.
Kian84 would love ramyeon too.
(As he's in a rush,
he buys 2 packages of ramyeon instead.)
He said he wanted to have ramyeon.
(The seaweed soup is now boiling.)
(Is it cooked well?)
Why isn't the water for ramyeon
boiling yet?
It's at a high altitude,
so water doesn't boil easily.
- I can imagine.
- Right.
- It's not easy.
- The heat is low.
(Sighing)
I'll just add it.
(The water hasn't boiled,
but he adds noodles to it.)
What was Kian84 doing in the meantime?
- He was sleeping.
- Me?
Were you sleeping?
I didn't even think about eating.
I was just resting after a shower.
He was tired.
I was scared to go down.
- Once I go down,
- It's not easy to come back up.
- It's so hard.
- It's like I should be prepared...
to come up about ten floors.
You had to cook
while suffering from altitude sickness.
It must've been hard.
(It was rough.)
(Gosh.)
- Kian84.
- Yes, Si Eon.
(He came all the way up to take Kian84.)
Let's have some soju.
- What?
- Did you bring it?
- I was going to drink downstairs.
- Really?
- Shall we go down?
- We can come up.
- Okay.
- He's going to surprise him.
How sweet.
I was nervous
that he might not want to go down.
It's not easy to go up
once you're downstairs.
Look how tired they are.
It was so tiring.
(Soju bottles are here.)
- I also made ramyeon.
- Oh, my.
That's good.
Gosh. The smell. It smells so good.
Do we have kimchi?
- No. Don't come.
- Just sit down.
Okay.
- He listened.
- Is it Korean style?
(The seaweed soup
will finally be revealed.)
Kian84.
- What is it?
- Happy birthday.
- Yes!
- Seaweed soup.
- Thank you.
- I made it.
- Seriously.
- Hey.
Try it.
I brought the ingredients from Korea.
It's so touching.
(Moved)
Goodness.
Thank you, Si Eon.
You didn't have to.
Thank you for the soup.
- Kian84.
- Yes?
It's too late, but happy birthday.
Okay. Thank you.
(Laughing)
How should I react to this?
All right.
I'll take it as a birthday wish
for next year.
(A birthday wish by accident)
I'm tearing up.
(Proud)
- Thank you.
- Try the seaweed soup.
You really didn't have to do this.
Thank you so much.
(He takes a sip of the soup.)
(Slurping)
Just say it's good.
(Is he enjoying it?)
(He also serves ramyeon quickly.)
How is it?
- The taste is...
- It's not good?
- It's the thought that counts.
- They said it was good.
It tastes healthy.
I added dried pollack and shrimp.
- I bought the shrimp on Ganghwa Island.
- Oh, my.
- Really?
- He got the best ingredients.
I thought you'd drink, so I added shrimp.
Let me sing "Happy Birthday."
(Happy birthday to you)
(Happy birthday, Dear Hee Min)
Here's a birthday gift.
Si Eon!
I criticized you a lot
in the interview earlier.
- It's a designer brand.
- I feel bad now.
It's a wallet.
- It's a high-end wallet.
- Yes.
I actually got a birthday gift for him.
- I bought a wallet.
- A wallet?
His wallet is worn out.
(He knew Kian84 had an old wallet.)
My gosh.
(He's just thankful that Si Eon
remembered a small thing about him.)
He can be quite sweet.
(He nags Kian84 as soon as he sees him.)
(They always bicker.)
(He's grumpy on the outside.)
He doesn't really cook,
but he's been carrying it
in his heavy backpack.
(Si Eon brought his bag
all the way from Korea.)
(It's over 20kg.)
(Sunblock)
(Padded jackets)
(Sleeping bags)
He nags him because he cares for him.
Right. Of course.
You do that
when you care about the person.
When you made Kian84 seaweed soup,
how did you like his reaction?
As you already know,
he's not really good at showing gratitude.
He's shy.
I think I've never seen him
being that thankful before.
Honestly, I thought he'd complain...
and say he didn't like seaweed soup
or something.
If he did that there,
he wouldn't be a decent person.
- Right.
- Your expectations were so low.
I'm not that horrible.
- Right.
- I'm not evil.
He'd be a jerk
if he complained in the alpine region.
I could see how touched he was.
I felt so good.
I was so proud.
It was worth preparing for the surprise.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you, Si Eon.
(Si Eon gives him a drink
to celebrate his birthday.)
We're here...
in Feru to celebrate your...
Is it with a P?
- Peru.
- We celebrate it in Peru.
- Go, Inca.
- Inca.
(Cheers.)
(Drinking up)
It was so good.
Kian84, it also has beef.
Oh, my.
Seriously, Si Eon.
Do you know you get sweeter every time?
He's grumpy and also sweet.
Why do you become nicer?
When you get old, you become mellow.
I can't eat the ramyeon
because of the seaweed soup.
(He loves the seaweed soup.)
It's good.
- Right?
- Yes.
It would've been better
if I had boiled a little longer.
I love seaweed soup.
(How is the ramyeon?)
It must be so good.
- Gosh.
- I wish I was there with them.
It's driving me crazy.
(Si Eon inhales his food
as if he's been starving.)
It looks so good.
It must be delicious.
(I'm hungry.)
(They're only licking their lips.)
(Well...)
You're all hungry, aren't you?
Yes, I'm a little hungry.
- Me too.
- I knew you would, so I brought this.
You brought something for us?
Aren't you hungry?
- Yes.
Here.
- It's not that much.
- Is it...
- All right.
- It's a famous brand.
Yes. It's well-known.
I like basic porridge.
- Red bean porridge.
- It's red bean porridge.
Dongji is right around the corner.
Well, it's a holiday.
We eat red bean porridge on Dongji.
- Right.
- Is it a holiday?
It is not.
On Dongji, we eat red bean porridge...
to remove bad luck and bring happiness.
- You know a lot about it.
- How considerate Kian84 is.
He's indeed thoughtful.
I know.
- Thank you for the food.
- It's good.
- It's tasty. It has rice cake balls too.
The portion is big too.
- It's delicious.
- It is?
Everyone, since we had
porridge for Dongji,
let's be happy next year.
- Thank you.
- Go away, bad luck!
- Full of happiness.
(They had been missing
Korean spicy foods.)
It's so good.
I feel like we're back in Korea.
- This seaweed soup...
- Isn't it good?
I like it better than the ramyeon.
(They're getting even closer tonight.)
(They started traveling in Cusco
in a good mood without any plans.)
(But that mood didn't last long.)
(Don't do it.
Take a picture of this first.)
(Si Eon, can we drop by
the cathedral later?)
(Hold on.)
(They start to disagree
with each other...)
(little by little.)
(How about we make a fire...)
(and sleep on the street once?)
I'm a little worried
about the staff, though.
(So you want to sleep outside.)
(- Whether it's a tent...
- But we don't have a tent.)
(You build a fire and sleep.)
(Kian84, we can't sleep like that.)
(They begin to hurt
each other's feelings.)
(You shock me
whenever you say things like that.)
(Don't say that again.)
(I don't deserve to hear that from you.)
(To be honest,
I felt a little frustrated at the time.)
(He doesn't seem to have a plan either.)
(Thinking about it makes me mad again.)
(He knew he wouldn't do it
and it wouldn't work.)
(Why does he even suggest it?)
(I couldn't really talk to him anymore.)
(I thought we might stop
being friends at this rate.)
(Kian84, let's stop.)
(It might have been a hint.)
(How they felt
when they almost ruined their friendship)
(To save the guys' friendship,)
(Pani Bottle is here.)
(As they don't speak foreign languages,)
(he'll be their translator.)
(He's so cool.)
(He also eases the tension
between the two...)
(as the life of the party.)
(If you mess with them,)
(I, Chihuahua, won't stay still.)
(Look forward to Pani Bottle's role.)
(Adventure by Accident)