Xiao Ying.
Where should I put the towel?
You...
Miss.
This is the men's bathroom.
I'm sorry.
I went the wrong way.
Don't do this again.
Miss.
Slow down.
Don't fall again.
No.
This...
Who is this lady?
has such a hobby?
She's the eldest daughter of the Su family.
Su Nian Qing.
Your future sister-in-law.
You know her?
No.
I'd like to see
what she is up to.
Tell her
If you want the necklace, come to the New World Nightclub.
Nightclub?
Why did you ask me out here?
Miss, this way.
Miss, what would you like to drink?
A glass of water, please.
Okay
Young Master
It's not good if Eldest Young Master knows about this.
As long as I want it,
must be mine.
No matter who it is,
Isn't this Miss Su?
I asked you out so many times but you didn't come out.
You pretended to be serious.
Why did you come here alone today?
I rejected you
because I hate you.
I'd like to see
how long
stop pretending?
Stop pretending.
Don't be shameless.
My woman!
How dare you touch her!
Young Master.
You...
Get lost!
Are you okay?
I thought
come today.
Sir, your wine.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have asked you to come here.
Where's my necklace?
Go ahead.
Are you here
for this necklace
or for me?
For you.
The necklace in your hand
So pretty.
It's from my mother.
Of course.
I'm not talking about the necklace.
Don't go. I can still drink.
Be careful.
I feel dizzy.
Miss Su.
Wake up.
Don't go.
Be careful.
Where is your address?
I'll call a taxi to send you home.
Don't go.
Where is her bedroom?
This way.
Go make her hangover soup.
I'll be right there.
We have plenty of time.
Miss, you're awake.
Am I seeing it right?
The man who sent you back is the second young master of the Huo family.
He is Huo Hanjin.
That's why I'm willing to act with him.
But Miss,
you're marrying Huo Qixuan,
not Huo Hanjin.
So what?
The business world of Yun City is like a chess game.
Huo Qixuan is just a pawn of the Huo family.
Huo Hanjin is the last player.
If I join hands with him,
to take over Yuncheng Spinning Factory.
When Huo Hanjin returned to the Huo family,
He took over half of the Huo family's business in just two years.
He's very scheming.
He's very cunning.
He's no ordinary person.
I gave him a gift.
If he catches it,
he will be rich.
What if I can't?
then
is the price for him bullying me.
Stop!
Sorry, Young Master
Master
Bastard!
How dare you!
How dare you seduce your sister-in-law?
The Yaheng Party
Weiyu Committee.
Yin Peng.
Xue Ke Yang Wei.
Cheng Peng Qingxue Keyang.
Mingxin Cong, Xiaohao.