It's thirty percent higher than the market price. Okay.
Nian Nian.
Young Master Huo
is not as professional as you said.
Let’s think of another way
Young Master Shen
You’re asking for food
to separate personal and personal
or to control the Su family?
You...
Huo Hanjin!
You know we need these machines.
to save the Su family.
Why are you making things difficult for us?
Are those machines that important?
Do you know
how many shares
in secret these years?
If my brother hadn’t
protect Su’s assets in this way,
I'm afraid the Su family
by your Huo family.
One more thing.
The Huo family has been coveting our assets.
So I transferred some of my assets
to my personal account.
Don't worry.
I didn't take a penny of the money.
I was going to tell you later.
But I’m worried that Huo Hanjin
will make use of this.
Don't worry.
He won't.
Nian Nian.
Don't be fooled by him again.
I sent someone to find Huang Ying.
She looked crazy.
But she said
the one who killed Huo Zhenhua
is Huo Hanjin.
Nian Nian.
Do you really know him?
I knew you would slander me.
I don't think you did it for Nian Nian.
You just want the machines.
Shen Renran.
I'm the chairman of the Huo family now.
The secrets between you and my father...
I can find out
if I touch my finger.
As the president,
because you killed your father.
What did you say?
I said you killed your brother and father. You don't admit it.
Brother.
You're a scumbag.
Shen Renran.
Nian Nian.
Huo Hanjin!
I won't let you off!
Brother.
Let's go.
Here.
Nian Nian.
I'm telling the truth.
You can't go with him.
I hope you
consider our cooperation seriously.
Brother.
Nian Nian.
Why are you here?
About the machines,
about the machines.
You haven't recovered yet.
About the machine,
I'll think of another way.
Have you eaten?
I'll get you something to eat.
Have a seat.
Okay.
This is my diary.
Su Nian Qing.
Where are you?
Please tell me.
who killed my father.
Shen Renran?
or Huo Hanjin?
Why can't I find the truth
but never find the truth?
Did you
found the truth?
They told me the murderer who killed my father was drowned.
I don't believe it.
But why does Huo Hanjin
stop me from investigating?
But I won't give up.
The yarn factory has been in trouble lately.
The return of the goods hasn’t come yet.
Huo Hanjin helped me find funds everywhere.
Luckily, I have him.
We quarreled again today.
Huo Hanjin never did it for me.
He wanted to help the Huo family take over the Su family.
Then why did he stop me from investigating?
Could my father's death
related to the Huo family?
After we got married,
Huo Hanjin is no longer the man he used to be.
There are only quarrels and suspicion between us.
So from the beginning,
we were destined to be a tragedy.
Huo Hanjin bought raw crow.
He killed my father.
Impossible.
Absolutely impossible.
It's not true.
Nian Nian.
You...
remember anything?
How could it be true?
Yes.
I've been investigating for so long.
I didn't expect that
the murderer was Huo Hanjin.
He's not that kind of person.
Did Nian Nian forget how he treated you?
And the car that hit you
the car that hit you was his.
But why did he do that?
For the benefit.
He wanted to kill my father before controlling you.
Now he refused to help us get the machines.
just in case our Su family
threaten their status again.
Before this,
I didn't return the diary to you
because I didn't want you to remember the pain in the past.
Now that you've seen it,
don’t be deceived by Huo Hanjin.
It's all my fault.
I made you live with a murderer
with a murderer?
That's right.
We can't let Nian Nian
live next to a murderer.
Nian Nian.
It's too dangerous here.
Come with me.
Isn't it dangerous to be with you?
Are you
Are you suspecting me?
Huo Hanjin.
Do you think I'm not here?
No matter what happens today,
I'll take Nian Nian away.
Nian Nian.
Why do you trust him so much?
Because he's my brother.
I've lived with him for ten years.
Huo Hanjin.
It's useless to say anything.
You killed my father.
I'll let you pay with your life!
No!
Nian Nian.
What are you doing?
Leave.
Why won't you let me kill him?
Brother.
You can’t be accused of murder.
So he can't die in the Su family.
Miss Su.
As I ordered last time,
I’ve bought
I've copied all the drugs
I copied them all.
Have you
have you seen the drug on this list?
Yes.
It's a raw crow. It's very poisonous. It's very poisonous. It's good. It's good. It's good.
is extremely poisonous.
A slight mistake could lead to death.
I paid extra attention to the plagiarism.
Could it be a mistake?
No way.
This is a special medicine.
I'll keep an eye on it.
It can't be wrong.
Did anyone else
came to look for this list?
Looking for the order from a year ago?
Miss Su,
you are the first one.
Thank you.
The Yaheng Party
Weiyu Committee.
Yin Peng.
Xue Ke Yang Wei.
Cheng Peng Qingxue Keyang.
Mingxin Cong, Xiaohao.