What you said before
is it true?
When your father was shot,
the murderer disappeared.
A month later,
we found several bodies by the river.
The case was closed
he closed the case
that the murderer was drowned.
Do you remember?
the real murderer didn't die?
Someone was trying to cover up the truth.
That's right.
The murderer left Yun City successfully.
and changed his appearance.
No one knows where he is.
But I
I found the person behind the murderer.
You don't want to tell me.
Let's read it.
Do you want to know?
As long as you follow me,
I'll tell you.
Huo Qixuan.
Why are you here?
I warned you.
If you ever think of Nian Nian again,
I won't forgive you.
Why are you holding me?
Beat him!
Hit him!
Nian Nian!
Nian Nian.
Brother.
don't mind him.
Enough.
For Nian Nian's sake,
I'll spare you today.
Let's go.
Take care of yourself first.
Take care of yourself.
Nian Nian.
Stay away from him.
Young Master
You're awake
Erhu
I'm just in a coma.
I'm not dead.
Why are you wearing mourning?
Young Master
He...
What did he do this time?
He's dead.
What did you say?
You followed me.
I can not only help you find out who killed your father,
but also make you Mrs Huo.
Why are you still obsessed with that illegitimate child?
You are obsessed with me.
because I’m Huo Hanjin’s woman.
right?
What?
You don't want to?
I want you.
I just want him to experience
how it feels
how it feels to lose your wife.
I also know
you know business.
and the yarn factory.
I want you to help me
what Huo Hanjin took away from me.
and take back my position in the Huo family.
Sure.
Let's make a deal.
Tell me.
Who is the murderer?
Are you okay?
Tell me.
who killed my father.
Huo...
Huo Hanjin!
You...
Qi Xuan.
I'm your mother. I'm your mother.
Although I'm not your mother,
we are mother and son after all.
Why are you leaving?
Master.
We have found out his whereabouts.
The last person he saw was...
Tell me.
It's Second Young Madam.
What Second Young Mistress?
Su Nian Qing
is no longer a member of our Huo family.
She killed Qi Xuan.
The day my brother died.
Su Nian Qing
I did see him.
It's Su Nian Qing indeed.
She doesn't
the Huo family at all.
Tell everyone in the Chamber of Commerce
no matter what he does,
from now on,
all cooperation with the Su family
with the Su family.
Yes.
Su Nian Qing.
You can't stay.
Let me go.
If Su Nian Qing kills my brother,
I'll kill her myself.
Master.
I'm afraid that Young Master
for Su Nian Qing.
Haven't you always wanted to join the management of the ship station?
They need someone reliable.
to
this matter.
Yes.
Father.
Hanjin.
You're the only son of the Huo family now.
Don't let me down.
Okay.
Master.
Let's go.
You can leave now.
Hanjin!
Hanjin.
The one who has been blocking us
is Su Nian Qing.
If Young Master could kill her,
it's not your turn to teach me what to do.
You...
As long as you can kill Su Nian Qing,
I can help you get more than the Wheel Bureau,
and everything about the Huo family.
Who are you to decide
Who are you to decide?
Nian Nian.
Why didn't you tell me
Why didn't you tell me?
Don't go anywhere now.
Stay at home.
I've sent someone to investigate the murderer.
I will clear your name.
Brother.
I didn't kill Huo Qixuan.
You don't have to say anything.
Of course I trust you.
Young Master!
Bad news.
Nian Nian.
Have a good rest.
Don't go anywhere.
I will find a way to prove your innocence.
I don't know what happened.
From top to bottom,
from top to bottom.
When Nian Nian was suspected,
when Nian Nian was suspected.
I'm afraid the Huo family is behind this.
Young Master.
You have to find a way.
How's the investigation going?
The murderer who killed Huo Qixuan
is now in the abandoned flour factory in the west of the city.
Thank you.
[I'll prove my innocence.] Okay.
But I will prove my innocence.
The Yaheng Party
Weiyu Committee.
Yin Peng.
Cheng Peng Qingxue, Ke Yangwei.
Peng...
Cheng, Peng Qingxue, Keyang.
Mingxin is smart.