This drama deals with the sensitive topic of euthanasia
and may be disturbing for some viewers.
Mom.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Forgive me, Mom.
The patient was brought
to the emergency room this morning.
His condition seems to have stabilized
a bit now.
Thank you.
Are you Ye-na?
Yes.
Where did you go yesterday?
I went to see Mom.
Is she okay?
Same as always.
Except this time, a lot of weeds
had grown.
Everything was a mess.
Why does Mom keep making us feel bad
even after she's gone?
I miss Mom too.
Ye-na,
is it okay if I...
go to Mom first?
Our mother...
hasn't she been alone for too long?
She must be so lonely.
I'll go to her.
Let's make sure
you do your part too.
You can stay here.
Stay here for a long time.
A long, long time.
Then come join us,
okay?
I'm sorry,
I didn't know you wanted this so much.
I didn't know how hard you were trying.
Then just do what you want.
Go to Mom,
and take good care of her for me.
Understood?
I'll talk to Dr. Woo.
Thank you.
We received a consultation request.
We don't have medication right now,
so we can't accept it.
But the patient is very anxious...
Who's the client?
My brother.
MARY KILLS PEOPLE
(National Forensic Institute)
Although the body
was found in the lake,
There's no water in the lungs.
It appears the body was moved
after death.
EPISODE 8
As you can see, the victim was shot.
Cause of death was exsanguination
from a gunshot wound to the head.
In addition,
traces of gunpowder and gas were found.
It appears the shot was fired at close range.
Speculation is that he suffered cardiac arrest
before the car sank into the lake.
Did the autopsy confirm the type of weapon?
The weapon appears to be...
A homemade gun.
All those things are things I really like.
All those things are things
that I really, really like.
As soon as I feel a little better, I want to eat.
But lately, I can't even taste them.
I wanted to shove all this in my mouth.
To feel the meat juices running down.
Chewing the meat.
If I'd known it would be like this,
I would've eaten more when I was healthy.
It's a shame.
I love all those things too.
Your taste in food
is exactly the same as mine.
But...
What motivated you to make me
such a generous offer?
I heard the medicine is not only hard to get,
but also quite difficult to handle.
You're my godfather.
Wasn't it you who gave my brother and me so much help?
I heard your trip to Switzerland was canceled.
It really broke my heart.
So I asked around.
But I didn't expect
to get the medicine so easily.
First, let's confirm
if it guarantees a painless death.
We can discuss the terms later.
How are we going to confirm that?
Do you have any friends...?
Who'd volunteer to die as a guinea pig?
Then, in the presence of my lawyer,
administer the medicine.
After he confirms my peaceful death,
the agreement will be fulfilled by my lawyer.
And the amount will be given to you,
on my behalf.
How much are you asking for this?
Now, in front of CEO Jin...
In a situation like this...
How much can you offer?
Any amount you want.
If you want my money, it's yours.
If you want my building, it's yours.
Make your decision.
Anyway, I'm already a dying man.
In fact, there's nothing left for me to hold onto.
All I want
is to die without pain.
That's enough for me.
- You're here.
- Was the trial good?
Just a moment.
Here's Dr. Woo.
Thank you for coming.
Well, I'm sorry,
but we don't have the medication right now,
so I don't know when it can be administered.
Ah, okay.
Ye-na has already agreed as well,
and the doctor promised to do it.
I just have to wait a little longer and this pain will end.
Thinking like that makes me feel better.
Until then, Mr. Geon-soo...
If there's anything you want to do, do it.
Then...
while you're looking for the medication,
can I travel with Ye-na?
You want to travel?
Yes.
I want to go to Gangwon-do to see the sea.
It might be difficult to get there, is that okay for you?
Ye-na, you're a skilled nurse. You'll take good care of him.
Before we go, let's visit Father Yang's hospital.
I'll prepare everything we need.
Okay.
Thank you.
- My little So-song looks so cute today.
- So-song, So-song.
- Are you going to have fun?
- Yes.
- Hello.
- Goodbye.
So-song, is there anything you want to do today?
Or any place you want to visit, just tell me.
And I will grant your wish.
To that place.
That... place?
Okay, let's go to that place.
Don't worry about things here.
Have a great trip with your brother.
I feel bad that you're so busy and I'm leaving alone like this.
I'll work even harder when I get back.
You're already doing so much for us.
We're very grateful to you.
We'll take care of everything here.
Enjoy your time with your brother
and come back happy.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
Come with me to the medical supply store later.
The patients are running out of bandages and medicine.
It completely slipped my mind.
I'm as happy as if I'd seen the Lord himself.
I need to go in and check
what supplies we need.
Then we'll be off.
Go ahead and take the basket
and check the items.
Okay, take care.
(Charity Hospital)
Here it is.
I'll contact you
as soon as I have the medication.
If Mr. Geon-soo's condition worsens,
or if you have any concerns,
please don't hesitate to call me.
Yes, thank you.
We're leaving.
- Take care.
- Goodbye.
Is this where you wanted to come, So-song?
Yes.
So-song,
as soon as we sell everything,
we'll go home.
(Original Golden Fish Bread)
- Hello.
- Two, please.
Two, right?
Enjoy.
Did you come to get the blanket, So-song?
Yes.
So you were waiting here
until Mom finished selling everything?
Come on.
Shall we take the blanket?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(Original Golden Fish Bread)
Wow, you look so pretty.
Let's go.
Isn't the girl's mother working?
She left her here and hasn't come to pick her up
in a long time.
If she stays here,
I'm going to have to throw the cart away.
Besides, she still owes me money.
Well, some things happened...
I'll cover the costs.
It's 50,000 won a month, right?
It's 100,000 won a month.
The price went up.
It went up quite a bit.
Well, okay.
Please watch the cart for now.
- Okay.
- Yes.
So-song, play hide-and-seek
with your uncle for a bit.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Watch your head.
Sir,
could you take her to the place I mentioned?
Sure, no problem.
So-song, you go first.
You really are a troublemaker, huh?
Makes me want to slap you.
Let's go.
Why didn't you bring the little one?
Wouldn't it be better to have her close?
There's a patient who needs to see Woo So-jeong.
She promised me before...
That to get the medicine, she'll do anything.
And I already gave her a dose.
What was the little girl's name?
She... her name is So-song.
Yes, whether it's So-song or whoever...
Do you think her mother's death was simple?
Woo So-jeong has gone crazy,
saying she wants to choose her own patients.
But that's ridiculous.
If she rejects my orders again, no,
if she dares to defy my orders again,
I won't be able to do anything more for her.
So, if you want to save your friend,
what do you think you should do?
Convince her, bring her here.
Yes, I...
No, no, wait.
Sir.
I can try to do that.
You?
Who are you trying to fool?
Are you a doctor, by any chance?
I'm discussing an important matter with the chairman.
Continue.
Right, um...
Euthanasia...
I was the one who started this business first.
After my medical license was revoked.
When my hands were shaking so much
that I couldn't do plastic surgery anymore,
that's when I started doing this.
I can do that.
Can you really?
- Are you sure?
- I am.
But I need your help to get the police off my back.
I may not be like Woo So-jeong,
but nothing will be detected in the autopsy.
But you just need to hold back the police.
Knock, knock, knock. Hey.
Little cheater.
Are you enjoying the sea?
Yes, it's nice.
Where do you want to go now?
What else do you want to do?
There's something special I really want to do.
What is it?
We're going to visit Dad.
I miss him.
You wanted to come all the way to Gangwon-do just to see him?
Dad's in a nursing home near here.
I know he's hiding from loan sharks.
He's been living there since last year.
We barely made it all the way here.
Do you really need to see him?
I just want to resolve everything I feel guilty about,
so I can leave in peace.
I know you're upset,
but come with me.
After all, it's the last chance, right?
From over there to here.
There, there.
Take them all.
That one, that one.
This one and that one, too.
Bring the leather shoes.
Pack all the leather shoes on the right.
Take that Thom Browne.
This is the doctor who will help him.
He used to be an excellent plastic surgeon.
Now he's a good Samaritan.
Like a gentle assassin.
His task is very simple:
Make sure Representative Jin rests in peace without pain.
He's also a patient who meets Dr. Woo's and your requirements.
Set the date as soon as the property
transfer documents are ready.
Understood, sir.
I will deliver the documents only after
confirming Mr. Jin's peaceful departure.
If he dies in pain, the contract is canceled.
If he dies in agony,
the contract is canceled.
If he screams in pain during the process,
or even frowns after death,
the payment will definitely not be made.
And, of course, we won't be able to guarantee your safety.
Don't worry. I absolutely won't tolerate...
that happening.
Now you've decided to stay at the door, scaring my family?
Did you forget that I can report you for harassment?
We found Kim Si-hyun's body.
The prime suspect is missing.
Are there no more leads to find the criminal?
Is this what you wanted?
You only came to me
Because you shouldn't have any leads.
I want to find who killed Kim Si-hyun
because you could be the next target.
Can the police say that to such
an important suspect?
Do you want me to confess out of fear?
The children could be in danger, too.
And I'm not here to investigate anything.
How about...
if we go home?
Let's go see Dad.
I had to pay the bills
for the nursing home,
so I saw him occasionally.
I didn't want to take you there
and make you uncomfortable,
that's why I was against it.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
They saw that the owner of Kim's car fled.
It's time to close this case.
Don't pretend you're working hard.
I know you contacted Interpol on purpose
to make a scene.
I'm going to close the case soon.
Where are my things?
I'll give them back to you as soon
as the case is closed.
I'm very busy.
I don't have time to waste.
Hey!
Bring me my things immediately.
I need them for tonight.
How much?
Detective Bu checked the scene.
If it's a large amount,
it could be difficult.
Besides, much of the evidence
has already been processed.
I had to work hard
to keep the subordinates quiet.
Very little is left.
You can use a similar powder to mask it,
just put the real substance
on top.
Anyway, the evidence analysis is already done.
It won't need additional confirmation.
If you don't solve this,
we'll not only lose our jobs.
We're all going to die.
Okay.
We're being led
by a gang of criminals...
We need to find
a solution quickly.
At this rate,
we'll soon be in danger too.
How are you?
Hey, you finally decided to come.
I've been here for so long,
and you only visit now.
Ye-na must have told you I was here.
I didn't tell him.
He's sick. I didn't want to worry him.
Always exaggerating...
Your brother's always saying he's sick.
He really is sick.
Seriously sick.
Why are you yelling?
You brat!
Did you come here to cause trouble?
I just need some money.
Why don't you take care of this yourself?
I'm not sick, I'm just hiding from loan sharks.
You damn ingrate.
Ye-na...
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm not healthy enough to earn money,
and I also get help from Ye-na.
So I don't have money to help you.
I'm sorry.
Dad...
What is it?
I'm about to die.
Since you were a kid, the doctors said you wouldn't live long,
but you've lived until now.
So stop talking nonsense!
I'm really going to die soon.
I probably won't make it past this month.
That's why I came to see you.
Dad...
I...
I don't hate you.
You shouldn't.
After their mother passed away,
I raised you two alone. I endured so much suffering.
Thanks to me, you grew up and became adults,
so you can't be ungrateful.
I think you're very pathetic, Dad.
What?
I have a wish.
It's my last wish before I die.
You must promise me one thing.
What is it?
Please apologize...
to Ye-na.
What?
Are you asking me to apologize to this girl?
Yes.
I don't hate you.
And you don't have to apologize to me,
but you must apologize to Ye-na.
Our Ye-na will have to live alone from now on.
She needs to forgive her father.
Only then will she be able to live with that strength.
Holding a grudge against someone
won't give her a good life.
So...
for Ye-na's sake,
even if everything's okay now,
please, apologize.
You two are crazy.
It's been a while since you've visited,
and you come empty-handed.
And now you're saying...?
- You little...!
- What's wrong?
Is he going to hit us again?
You brat!
Dad.
What are you looking at?
Oh, I'm sorry about yesterday.
I felt like someone was following me.
So I sent So-song home first.
Who was following you? Is it the chairman?
No, it was just my imagination.
Did something happen? Where's Ye-na?
We need to help her brother.
Ye-na agreed too.
Really?
For Geon-soo, it's very lucky somehow, isn't it?
But the problem is that we don't have pentobarbital.
Is there any way to get it?
Let me try.
I have a feeling I can get it.
You're not...
going to ask Mr. Koo, are you?
We have to hide this matter
about Geon-soo from Mr. Koo.
If he finds out, he'll charge Geon-soo a huge fee.
He'll make absurd demands again.
When can you get the medication?
Geon-soo's condition isn't good.
It should be within one or two weeks.
When I have the exact date,
I'll contact you immediately.
(Unknown number)
So-jeong, I'm getting a call.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
- Hello.
- Ah, hello.
Mr. Koo asked me to call you.
It'll be this Saturday.
Where should I go?
I'll send you the address.
Prepare well.
I'm sorry.
I probably made things complicated for you, didn't I?
Don't worry about it.
- Bro...
- Yeah.
Last time, Dad said
that the people who truly love me are my family.
It's not about blood ties.
So, look...
Gather those you really want to see and who deeply love you.
People who are like family to you,
and let's have a party.
Your band can perform.
And we can enjoy delicious food. It'll be great, right?
How about having a funeral before dying?
Sure, a living funeral sounds good.
I heard they also do this ceremony abroad. Let's do it.
I'll take care of the preparations.
Sounds good, right?
Yeah.
Don't worry about me.
I'm going to live well.
Even without Dad's apology.
I've always had such a wonderful brother,
how could I not live well?
So don't worry about me.
Yeah, you'll definitely be okay.
And now...
- Time to hug Ye-na!
- Don't even think about it.
- How absurd.
- How clingy.
Are you planning to have a funeral and a show
on the day of his death?
Yes.
I know there might be a lot of trouble that day because of the people.
But I really want to do this for my brother.
He can't see his friends often because of his illness.
I want him to say goodbye and see everyone one last time.
Most of them are musicians.
They can gather to sing and perform on stage.
It'll be more like a celebration.
Everyone having fun and ending everything in a happy way.
We have plenty of time.
With proper preparation, everything should go well.
I hope you and your friends have fun.
When it's time to go, we'll help you.
We should receive the medication by then.
I'll bring the medication at 7 p.m. on Saturday.
Thank you.
I'm going to book a place nearby,
prepare some food, and the stage.
Let's have a joyful celebration together.
Since it's a farewell celebration,
we could prepare a spicy beef stew.
What do you think? It'll be great, right?
Spicy beef stew sounds a little sad,
but whatever you want to eat, I'll help you make it.
Don't worry about the preparations.
Geon-soo, you should focus on preparing for your presentation.
Thanks.
(Announcement)
(Rock band 'Rounders' performance)
I don't want to cry today.
I'll do my best to make sure my brother leaves happy.
Okay.
Kyung, take off your hat.
Don't take it off.
- Your friend is here.
- Who is it?
Hey, here comes the artist.
You guys come here.
If it wasn't a funeral,
you wouldn't even have come, would you?
Why do you say that?
Today we'll have a band performance.
Let's have fun.
Just enjoy.
Great, I'm going to replace the condolence money with this.
I drew your portrait.
It looks just like you.
You finally captured my beauty.
It's good to see you while I'm still alive.
Yes, it really is.
Is this Jin-suk?
Are you Jin-suk?
Hey, how long has it been since we last met?
I brought a guitar too.
Are you going to sing for me?
Yes, I'm going to sing your favorite song.
Great, we're going to perform too.
Not just us. If any of you want to sing,
feel free to come up on stage.
I'm definitely hoping to hear several songs today, okay?
Awesome.
- Thanks, guys.
- See you later. You can sit anywhere.
- Okay.
- Go on, go on.
Having a funeral before dying is wonderful.
Before departing,
being able to meet the people you miss,
and sharing a delicious meal together is amazing.
Everyone will be very grateful to see you one last time.
Yes.
After I'm gone, the kind of funeral where people gather to cry,
won't be as good compared to this.
Here, for you.
Your spicy beef stew.
Eating spicy beef stew at my own funeral...
Only I would think of that, right?
- Eat slowly.
- Yes.
- How is it?
- Very salty.
Is it really salty?
It seems like it needs more water.
That's how I imagine the end should be.
It seems kind of pointless...
having to say goodbye to your loved ones...
in the midst of pain, losing consciousness from painkillers.
You're right.
Everyone has their own way of saying goodbye...
And dying in a hospital seems a bit miserable.
But I can't do that now.
It's too dangerous.
That crazy guy...
He could be watching us somewhere.
I know.
I don't want to get involved with that guy either.
Ye-na.
Your father is here.
Why is he here?
I needed to talk to you both.
I heard Geon-soo is dying, that he's about to pass away.
So, as your father,
I have to tell you... one last thing.
I'm sorry.
Back then,
I was also in a difficult situation.
I had to raise you alone.
It was exhausting.
Anyway, I'll leave it at that.
I'm sorry.
You should apologize to Ye-na.
I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, Dad. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Dad.
Wow.
That's a nice pile of money.
Wow, you're being a very good daughter.
Thank you.
Be careful.
The loan sharks might still be looking for him.
I'll take care of that myself.
But...
Is Geon-soo really going to die?
Yes.
Gosh, he's so young.
Who did he get his weakness from?
Please, go away.
By the way...
Ye-na.
I shouldn't be saying this, but after taking your money...
I'm sorry.
You once told me,
that what we should do
is let our loved ones
go without worries.
♪ Untouchable clouds ♪
♪ Unheard things ♪
♪ Imprisoned darkness ♪
♪ What is unseen ♪
♪ What is felt, but not touched ♪
♪ I'll set off to find you ♪
♪ Under the fragmented moonlight ♪
♪ If she could brightly light me up ♪
♪ Whenever, always ♪
♪ I'll light a light for you ♪
I'll go get the medicine.
- Be careful.
- Yes.
I'm on the street...
Tell me the location, I'll go right now.
Don't get nervous.
I'm going to use this opportunity to pay off the debt
that So-jeong owes Lee Yun-hee.
As soon as I'm done, I'll leave immediately.
I left in the middle of an event. If I don't get back quickly, it'll raise suspicion.
Starting today, we must act decisively.
And you know, right?
If this person suffers even a little bit, you, immediately...
Don't make any mistakes.
(Contracting party personal information: Jin Yeom-soo)
(Registered under the name: Jin Yeom-soo)
(Registered owner: Gwang Asset Operations)
It can't be.
We personally verified it and brought it here.
How could it disappear?
I also thought it should be here,
so I asked the Narcotics Department.
Of the seven kilos confiscated,
the pentobarbital has been missing from the start.
Why wasn't it there?
What are you talking about? We confirmed those vials.
Seven kilos?
At first glance, there was a huge pile.
How could it only be seven kilos?
Two people were caught at customs.
What they were hiding was seven kilos.
But if what was transported by truck
was also recorded as seven kilos,
it just doesn't make sense.
Someone from the inside must've taken it.
They definitely took it from a blind spot.
Or it was taken during a security break.
Unbelievable.
The investigation isn't even over,
and they already took it?
Are they brave or crazy?
Probably both.
I don't know who it is,
but there must be supervision, right?
Should we report this to the captain?
No.
It's not yet clear who's involved in this.
The stuff taken from here must've been sold on the market.
We need to find them through known drug dealers.
Let's track them down later.
Even if I shove everything in my mouth like a madman,
I still can't taste anything.
I don't know if it's the illness or the medication,
but everything tastes bitter.
Did you say goodbye to your family already?
At this point,
my wife is probably arguing with my mother
about who gets the biggest share of the inheritance.
They don't know I'm dying.
No one's going to be heartbroken over me.
You can do it without worrying.
Woo So-jeong's vehicle location has been confirmed.
Where?
They say it's on the outskirts of Ocheon.
It's an area with many houses and hotels.
Send me the location.
Yes.
What the hell.
I'm contacting her family immediately.
I'm leaving now.
Wait.
That's just the beginning. You'll have to follow my instructions.
And don't do useless things.
Choi Dae-hyun,
keep a cool head, okay?
Sure.
Fix everything.
Mr. Jin,
you should leave in peace,
and carrying all this would be too heavy.
And now,
here's today's main act
who's also the lead vocalist of 'Rounders.'
Our beloved
Choi Geon-soo, please come up on stage and sing.
Thank you all for waiting for me.
Yes.
Today...
I'm truly grateful for everyone's company.
The song I'm about to sing
is one that I adore.
And as our final farewell,
I think it's very fitting.
Today...
I feel so blessed by everyone's presence.
I hope everyone can be happy.
I hope that all of us,
in the distant future,
can be in a wonderful place
and meet again.
I'm just gonna take this off.
Okay, okay.
That feels good.
♪ No matter how hard I try to forget ♪
♪ I can't forget that face ♪
♪ No matter how hard I try to erase ♪
♪ I can't erase that name ♪
Sing with the oxygen.
Ye-na,
let's sing together.
♪ In the sad silhouette when I turn around ♪
♪ I can still feel you holding back tears ♪
♪ If we meet again in the distant future ♪
♪ I must say that I loved you ♪
♪ Sometimes loneliness strikes ♪
♪ Sometimes regret invades ♪
♪ And one day, as time passes ♪
♪ I can't help but cry alone ♪
Geon-soo...
♪ I refuse to say goodbye ♪
♪ That's why you sob in my arms ♪
♪ Deeply kept inside me ♪
♪ What remains are the words I always wanted to tell you ♪
♪ Those words... ♪
- Geon-soo.
- Yes?
We
will meet again.
Later on?
Of course.
Much later.
In a very, very, very, very distant future.
Okay?
I'll see you there then.
Thank you.
♪ In my sad departing silhouette ♪
♪ I can still feel you crying ♪
Someone said that
people are always
preparing for winter,
preparing for death,
because you know winter will always come.
As for me,
being able to make this decision
is my true happiness.
♪ I can still feel your cries ♪
Thank you, brother.
Thanks to you,
I got Dad's apology.
Now I need to try hard and live well.
Ye-na,
you must live well.
I'm so sleepy.
So sleepy.
Brother.
Geon-soo.
♪ In the distant future,
if we meet again ♪
♪ I must say... I must say that I loved you ♪
These are the patient's final messages.
(Epilogue)
Everyone's recording them,
so just say whatever you want.
Recording.
Choi Ye-na,
What?
I'll record alone.
Why?
I can be more relaxed alone.
I'm shy, just go already.
But I can't leave you alone.
Come on, hurry.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Quick, quick.
- I'm going to play, I'm going to play.
- I'm going to watch you record.
Go further away.
Choi Ye-na.
Well...
I'm really going to say
that I don't know what to say.
You...
were born on the same day as me,
at the same time.
My twin.
That's why...
since we were little...
even before I said it out loud,
you already knew what I was thinking.
You know it now too, right?
Right?
Ye-na.
Me, your brother...
I haven't been well since I was a kid.
I haven't done much for you. I'm sorry.
Please, forgive me.
You are...
my everything in the world.
Ye-na,
as always,
you must be strong
and live confidently.
I'll be in heaven with Mom,
watching over you.
Okay?
I love you.
Thank you,
my other half,
Choi Ye-na.
Thanks to Kim Kwang-sik, Heo Jeong-do
and Kang Ki-doong for their special appearances.
MARY KILLS PEOPLE
I'd like to give you some advice.
This time, I can offer you more money.
Please, let me die. I beg you.
Please, release me from this pain.
Why are you doing this?
If you want to kill someone, just kill me.
I don't know how I could kill you.
You're too good to die.
I want to talk to the police.
Do you know Jin Yeom-soo?
Where were you when Jin Yeom-soo died?
Choi Dae-hyun, you told him, didn't you?
Things turned out this way
because you chose to deceive me.