♪The gentle breeze leaves no trace♪
♪It stirs the old times♪
♪Love is gained and lost♪
♪Only then does it become unforgettable♪
♪The bamboo leaves
are rustling and falling♪
♪Fate is delayed and scattered♪
♪Only lingering hatred remains♪
♪Echoing♪
♪Old dreams are like illusions♪
♪Alas, the world is too indifferent♪
♪If there were no obsession♪
♪I wouldn't be thinking of someone♪
♪If it's destined to be alone♪
♪Like a snowstorm♪
♪When love and hate dissolve♪
♪Only a long gaze remains♪
♪A drop of tear♪
♪Falls, burning my heart♪
♪We loved without regret♪
=My Destined Consort=
=Episode 16=
Mr. Chu,
I've picked a gift for you.
Thank you for healing my scar.
I've put it here for you.
You travel far and wide
for the people of the world.
I hope
this small water pouch
can provide you with some comfort
during your long journeys.
Qilan.
Here, try this.
It's prepared for you.
If you like sour food,
it means it's a boy.
Eat more.
It's delicious.
It's a boy.
Come on. Eat up.
Here, try this.
Try this.
Qilan.
Eat more fruit.
The braised pork is
Master Jingxiu's favorite.
Let him eat it.
It's just braised pork.
Danling,
the way you're speaking now
is becoming more inappropriate.
Sorry for speaking out of turn.
It's okay.
Lady Lan,
the antiabortifacient is ready.
Qilan, drink it while it's hot.
Be careful not to burn yourself.
Master Jingxiu, you eat too.
No rush.
Try this.
My son will surely like this,
just like me.
What's wrong?
- What's wrong?
- What's wrong, Qilan?
My belly...
Your belly?
Qilan.
- I didn't.
- My belly...
Call the physician!
Yes.
Qilan...
How is it?
How is the baby?
Lady Wang,
Master Jingxiu,
I'm afraid
Lady Lan
had a miscarriage.
- What?
What?
Consort Danling...
Consort Danling, why harm me?
What are you saying?
How could I harm you?
I was fine.
Why did I lose the child after taking
your antiabortifacient?
Yes.
Qilan drank your medicine
and had a miscarriage.
What exactly happened?
Master Jingxiu,
I'm innocent.
How could I be foolish enough
to poison her in front of everyone?
Shen Qilan,
I've treated you with so much care.
Why repay me with hatred
and frame me like this?
That's not true, Lady Wang.
Consort Danling
has always disliked Lady Lan.
Not long ago,
she made Lady Lan kneel
until she fainted,
claiming it was the rule.
Outrageous!
You have no place to speak here.
Master Jingxiu,
Mother,
she's twisting the truth.
Don't believe her.
I'm not twisting the truth.
Lady Wang, if you don't believe me,
you can ask the other servants
in the mansion.
I...
Qilan.
- I've always been careful.
- Qilan.
I've been careful with my food.
Consort Danling
brought the antiabortifacient to me.
Mother,
you have to stand up for me.
Please believe me.
Don't walk into others' traps.
In that case,
bring the private physician here.
Whether you've poisoned her
will be clear then.
Yes.
My child...
(Master Jingxiu's Mansion)
Jingxiu, don't worry.
This physician is the one
who normally treats your father.
I've invited him today
to find out
who wanted my grandson's life.
Lady Wang,
Master Jingming,
someone altered the formula
for Lady Lan's antiabortifacient,
turning it into an antiabortifacient,
causing Qilan to miscarry.
You've always been in charge
of Qilan's antiabortifacient.
The physician has said so.
What can you say in your defense?
Mother,
are you suspecting me?
It's not me.
Master Jingxiu, believe me.
How could I
harm your child?
Master Jingxiu...
Fine.
Then explain to us
what happened.
- I...
- It was me.
Lady Wang, Young Master,
- You have no place to speak here!
Speak!
I had increased
the dosage of the antiabortifacient.
But I only wanted
to make the baby stronger
so I added more.
I checked the dosage with a physician.
Nothing should've gone wrong.
It must be Shen Qilan.
She must've eaten something bad
and framed me with the miscarriage.
I see.
Lady Lan's pulse
tells me she's weak.
With that dosage,
she'd surely have a miscarriage.
What more do you have to say?
You poisonous woman!
This is the Prefect's eldest grandson!
Mother,
I meant well.
I could never harm
Master Jingxiu's child!
Let the physician leave.
Lady Wang,
Master Jingxiu,
this
is of great importance.
I dare not hide anything.
I will report it truthfully
to the Prefect.
Master Jingxiu, Lady Wang,
I beg you.
Please be fair to Lady Lan.
These days,
Consort Danling has been
making things hard for her.
She had to review the ledgers
late at night
and would be punished
even for the slightest mistake.
I didn't.
- She had to kneel on the abacus.
- I didn't.
As a maid, even I couldn't handle it.
Lady Lan was even pregnant.
- And this antiabortifacient.
- I didn't.
Consort Danling
must've plotted
to cause this miscarriage.
Is this true?
Mother,
please don't believe her nonsense.
Shen Qilan begged me.
She asked me to teach her
how to manage the household
so I agreed.
I never expected her
to twist my intentions,
accusing me of targeting her.
She's overestimated herself.
She's a concubine's daughter
from a humble family.
So what if she has a child?
Even without a child,
I'm still the general's lineal daughter
and Master Jingxiu's wife.
Why should I bother to plot against her?
I think what happened today
is part of her plan to play the victim
and frame me.
Are you saying
she used her child to frame me?
What kind of mother
would risk her child's life?
Mother,
you don't understand.
Women of low birth
like her
often pretend to be subservient.
She's known since she was young
that she had to suffer
to get something better.
My child...
Qilan...
Qilan, I'm here.
My child...
Master Jingxiu.
Master Jingxiu,
I just dreamed about our child.
He looked adorable,
just like you.
Our child
was so smart.
He could call us at a young age.
I also dreamed...
I dreamed that our child
loved his grandparents.
When the Prefect held him,
he grabbed the Prefect's beard
and made the Prefect laugh.
The Prefect said
he was the eldest grandson,
his eldest grandson.
Qilan, we will have more children.
I didn't see him grow up.
I didn't see him study or practice
martial arts with you.
I didn't even let him help me
solve your problems.
Now, Master Jingxiu,
I've never even heard him
call me Mother.
Qilan...
Master Jingxiu,
I really don't know
how this happened.
Even if there was a mistake,
it was unintentional.
Please forgive me, Master Jingxiu.
Stop defending yourself.
If it weren't for your jealousy
over Qilan's pregnancy
and your dirty tricks,
how could I lose my grandson?
Even if your father
knows about this,
he can't defend you.
Jingxiu,
you can't forgive her.
Qilan,
rest well.
How could it be unintentional?
Today,
I'll strip you of your position
as my consort.
In three days,
you will be sent to the ancestral tomb
to reflect on your mistakes.
Master Jingxiu,
you're abandoning me?
I'm your wife,
yet you want to abandon me for her?
What about our bond
over the years?
Master Jingxiu,
it wasn't me!
I didn't do it!
Jingxiu,
I didn't mean that.
This is too serious.
You need to discuss it with your father.
Mother,
I've made my decision.
This concerns the heirs of our family.
If the physician tells Father,
he will never forgive
such a vile woman.
Mother,
if I'm lax in managing
the household and indecisive,
how will Father view me?
How will I manage Dongzhou
in the future?
I've made up my mind.
No need to discuss this further.
(Prefect's Mansion)
My Lord, sorry for my crime.
What crime have you committed?
My Lord,
sorry for bad parenting.
I just found out
that Danling has made
such a grievous mistake.
It's because I spoiled her
too much.
I've been too busy
with military affairs
to spend time with her,
so I wanted to make up for it,
but in the end,
I've spoiled her this way.
However,
I know
my daughter well.
Though she's a little spoiled,
she doesn't harbor
any malicious intentions.
She grew up under your watch.
I hope you can be lenient
with her.
I've been lenient with her twice,
so she made this huge mistake.
How about
I ask a strict nanny
to discipline her?
Once she's well-disciplined,
I will return her
to Master Jingxiu
and let her give you
a healthy grandson.
If you think that's not enough,
then please strip her
of her position
as Master Jingxiu's consort
and send her back to me.
I guarantee she will never
step out of my mansion again.
No need.
This time, we can't let her off.
Let her go to the ancestral tomb
to reflect on her mistakes.
She
is my only daughter.
I've served Dongzhou in battle
for half a lifetime.
Please spare Danling's life.
General Wang,
this is my eldest grandson!
Master Jingxiu, why are you here?
Is it not enough to strip me
of my position?
Are you here to vent your anger for her?
Danling,
I never intended to abandon you.
We've been married for years.
You know how I have treated you.
I've always thought
of our marriage bond.
For all these years,
whatever trouble you've caused,
I've thought it was
because I spoiled you.
You didn't bear a child
in the last five years,
and I didn't allow anyone
to speak ill of it.
But this time,
you've gone too far.
Master Jingxiu,
I...
Don't you understand how important
this child is to me?
It's the Prefect's eldest grandson.
How could you be so inconsiderate?
Master Jingxiu,
sorry about this.
Please give me another chance,
okay?
If Father didn't know about this,
I could help you cover it up,
but since he knows,
what can I do?
Master Jingxiu,
the bond we share
is much more important
than an unborn child.
We grew up together.
I married you soon after I came of age.
For all these years,
I've been with you.
We shared...
Danling,
do we have any bond between us?
What...
What?
It's true we grew up together,
but have you ever loved me?
The man you've always wanted
to marry is Jingming.
Because of my identity
as the lineal eldest son
and Golden Guards,
you changed your mind
back then
and plotted to spend a night with me.
One more drink.
Danling, you can really drink.
Jingxiu,
let me pour wine for you.
To Jingxiu.
May all things go
as you wish.
Thank you, Danling.
Afterwards, you framed
Shen Jiangli with this.
No...
Do you really think I don't know it?
You wanted to become
the most respected woman in Dongzhou,
while I just wanted
to use your family.
We were just using each other.
No, it's not like that.
I admit
I used some tricks,
but
I love you.
I also know,
Master Jingxiu,
that you love me too.
You've caused me so much trouble.
For your family, I've endured it all.
But you laid hands on my child.
Master Jingxiu,
I can give you a child too.
I can do it.
Don't think about it.
Jingxiu.
- Mother.
- Please sit.
Why call me here?
Jingxiu,
Wang Danling will be abandoned,
but your mansion needs
to be taken care of.
What if someone causes trouble
in the absence of a consort?
Don't worry, Mother.
After Qilan recovers,
I want her to take charge temporarily.
She needs to learn
how to manage the house.
What do you mean by that?
Are you planning
to make her your consort?
Qilan has been in the mansion
for a while.
If she can manage the household,
I won't bother looking for a new one.
- Jingxiu.
- Mother.
Qilan just lost her child
and is heartbroken.
Let her do something
to distract herself.
She can temporarily take charge,
but you absolutely can't
let her be your consort.
I will find you someone worthy
of your noble status.
Don't worry about this.
Mother,
let's discuss this later.
I have to work,
so I will take my leave for now.
Jingxiu.
This child...
Dingxiang,
go and find some
portraits of noble ladies
at a marriageable age.
My Lady,
Master Jingxiu said to let Lady Lan...
What do you know?
Shen Qilan is just
a concubine's daughter.
It's already her good fortune
to be Jingxiu's concubine.
She can never
be Jingxiu's consort.
I'm afraid
if she's in charge for too long,
she might have other ideas.
Fuling.
How is she?
She just fell asleep.
Bring some bright flowers.
These are withered.
How can they help cheer her up?
Hurry up.
Yes.
Qilan.
Take it slow.
Greetings, Master Jingxiu.
Qilan,
I've given instructions.
Once your health is better,
you'll be in charge of the household.
From now on, you're in charge
of this family.
I haven't done this before.
I'm afraid I won't do it well.
No worries. You can learn over time.
Thank you, Master Jingxiu.
But it's pitiful for my child.
This is my first child,
but he never even had the chance
to see the world.
We'll have another one.
I have no other wishes.
I just want to have a peaceful
and happy family with you.
Please believe me.
I'll get better,
and I'll definitely
bear a child for you soon.
Sure.
I'll wait for you.
My Lady!
Bad news!
Greetings, Master Jingming.
I didn't know you were also here.
Why so panic?
I heard from the servants
in Master Jingxiu's Mansion
that Lady Lan had a miscarriage.
It's said that Consort Danling
repeatedly bullied Lady Lan,
which weakened her body.
With some medicine,
Lady Lan miscarried.
I see.
This shouldn't be spread
within the mansion.
You may leave now.
Yes.
I'll take my leave.
I'll go see her.
Do you want me to accompany you?
No need. I can go myself.
Then be careful.
Shen Qilan just married Master Jingxiu,
and Wang Danling is furious now.
Be careful with what you do,
and protect yourself.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Consort Jiangli.
I...
It's fine. Go back to work.
Yes.
Jiangli, you're here.
Jiangli.
Please sit.
Fuling, prepare tea.
No need.
I just came to see how you're doing.
Let me check your pulse.
Master Jingxiu
has asked the Prefect's physician
to examine me.
You don't have to do this.
I'm your sister.
I think it's better if I check it.
Thank you, Jiangli.
But I don't want Master Jingxiu
to misunderstand that I don't trust him,
so I hope you'll forgive me.
I'm just glad you're alright.
Jiangli,
this is
the Lantian jade bracelet
from Master Jingxiu.
This jade is rare and valuable,
and it perfectly matches
your noble demeanor.
Please allow me
to give this to you.
You should
keep it for yourself.
The inner chambers are eerie.
One slight mistake
might make you fall into hell
like Wang Danling.
This bracelet
will help protect you from evil.
You're right.
We can't harbor malicious intent
like her,
but people have many helpless moments.
Sometimes, it's just
to protect themselves.
Jiangli, do you agree?
It's never wrong
to consider yourself first.
But people live only once.
Some things can be done,
but some things can't.
We must stick to our bottom line.
I'll follow your advice.
I don't have any advice for you.
Where is Wang Danling now?
She's under house arrest in her room.
Are you going to see her?
We've had many entanglements for years.
Now that she's leaving,
I should go see her.
Rest well.
No need to see me off.
Jiangli, take care.
What are you here for?
I came to see you.
Are you here to laugh at me?
Let me tell you.
I'm doing just fine.
Stop playing tough now.
Still dreaming about becoming
the Prefect's wife?
Who are you to laugh at me?
Even if I'm not a consort anymore,
I'm still the general's only daughter.
I'm not you.
You marrying Master Jingming
can even be considered rarely lucky.
Do you think your marriage
can make you my equal?
You don't deserve it!
Someone as insignificant as me
could still become your thorn
in the side
and the target of your schemes
again and again.
I don't even know
whether I should feel sad
or proud.
I don't even know what I did
to offend you.
It was you who chose
to marry Master Jingxiu,
but to achieve your goals,
you plotted against me.
I hadn't even sought revenge on you,
yet you made things hard for me
because I married Master Jingming.
Don't you think you're too overbearing?
Overbearing?
You should know this.
Even if it's something I have discarded,
you have no right to pick it up.
Even picking it up is a crime.
Your arrogance and pompousness
are truly vile.
You look like a tiger,
baring your fangs and claws,
but you have nothing to back you up.
Stop showing off here.
I don't need you to teach me a lesson.
Do you know?
Qilan is actually not pregnant.
What did you say?
I just went to see her,
and I discovered something.
Consort Jiangli.
I...
It's fine. Go back to work.
Yes.
She used medicine
to create a false pregnancy.
Then she used medicine
to fake a miscarriage.
As for the blood,
she must've calculated the timing
and waited for her period to come
before blaming it on you.
I knew it.
I had consulted with the physician
about the dosage,
and the child would've been fine.
You go.
Go tell Master Jingxiu
so he will know I was wronged.
You go.
You go tell Master Jingxiu.
It's too late now.
She's destroyed the evidence.
I knew it.
You two were in cahoots
to make a fool of me.
I knew you wouldn't be so kind
to visit me.
Wait and see.
If my father knows about this,
he will surely plead with the Prefect.
In just a few days, I'll be out of here.
By then,
I won't let you get away with it.
You probably don't know
that General Wang went to the Prefect,
but the Prefect didn't change his mind.
What did you say?
I don't believe it.
My father holds a lot of weight
with the Prefect.
With his military merits,
the Prefect has to consider his opinion.
Wang Danling,
you've been treating everyone
like pawns in your game.
Do you really think you're a player?
Good and evil will be repaid.
Take care of yourself.
Shen Jiangli!
Come back here! Don't leave!
Explain yourself!
It's impossible!
Fuling, pour me a cup of tea.
Fuling.
Pour me a cup of tea.
Alright.
My Lady, sorry.
When I sent
the clothes out earlier,
I ran into Consort Jiangli.
She saw those clothes.
If...
If she associates those clothes
with something
and discovers our secret...
- It's fine.
- I...
Get up.
Even if she didn't see those clothes,
she'd still find out about it.
I did this
to protect myself.
I never intended to harm anyone.
Wang Danling went too far,
so I had to resort to this.
It's fine now.
From now on,
we can live peacefully.
Jiangli is wise.
She won't interfere with matters
that don't concern her.
By the way, My Lady,
your mother just sent a letter
and said she'd come over later.
Help me change my clothes.
(Master Jingxiu's Mansion)
Why are you here?
It's getting cold,
so I brought you a coat.
What's happened?
I'm just a bit sentimental.
Wang Danling,
as the general's lineal daughter,
favored by all,
grew up in the Prefect's Mansion,
studying with the Prefect's sons,
yet she's trapped
in the inner chambers,
scheming and plotting,
hurting others and herself.
She wants too much,
and in the end, she's trapped
by her desires and obsessions.
But this endless struggle
really changes people.
I went to see Qilan today,
and she's changed a lot too.
I hope she can learn from this
and not repeat Wang Danling's mistakes.
No matter what the situation is,
the path is one's own choice.
I hope that those who feel helpless
can hold on to their true selves.
Let's go.
(Governance and Protection)
By the Prefect's order,
the guilty woman, Wang Danling,
has plotted against Lady Shen Qilan,
and her as the consort is revoked.
She is to be sent to the ancestral tomb.
(Authority)
I invited you here today
to express my feelings.
I love Master Jingxiu
for who he is,
not for his status or wealth,
and I won't be your enemy.
I will always respect you and love you.
I will never be a threat to you.
♪Nowhere to send letters;
no news ever comes♪
♪The night fades away♪
My lineal daughter
should be the most respected woman
in Dongzhou.
I'll give you a grand wedding
and always stay by your side,
shielding you from suffering.
Once Master Jingxiu has Golden Guards
and becomes the Young Prefect,
you will be the most respected woman
in Dongzhou
after the Prefect steps down.
That most respected position
must be mine.
♪Gradually disappear on the horizon♪
♪There's only an incense stick of time
between us♪
♪Will you remember me♪
I lost.
In the end, I lost.
My Lady, Ms. Zou is here.
Mother.
- Sit.
- Qilan.
Qilan, are you feeling better?
I pity my grandson.
Wang Danling is truly heartless.
Mother,
I'm fine.
Wang Danling has gone
to the ancestral tomb,
and Master Jingxiu has let me
manage the household.
Really?
What a blessing.
However,
this miscarriage
must've harmed your body.
You must take good care of yourself,
so you can conceive again.
Mother,
actually...
What?
You...
Don't worry, Mother.
No one knows about this.
I can endure
Wang Danling's abuse,
but she shouldn't have humiliated you.
On my wedding night,
she humiliated you for no reason.
Good child.
It's my fault
for letting you suffer this.
Mother,
now, Master Jingxiu loves me
and trusts me.
We'll have many good days to come.
What's wrong?
- What's wrong?
- Qilan,
I'm afraid
there won't be a future for me.
What happened, Mother?
I heard that your elder sister
found the servants who used
to serve her mother
and said she'd investigate
her mother's death.
Didn't her mother die of illness?
Why investigate?
Actually,
there have been rumors
at home for years
that her mother didn't die of illness.
Mother, what do you know?
Let her investigate.
But...
Mother,
we needn't worry.
You didn't do this.
We have nothing to fear.
Actually,
back then, to protect us,
I also used some methods.
I'm just afraid
they might use it to frame me
during the investigation.
Mother,
tell me the truth.
♪The sound of the flute lingers,
making the night more tender♪
♪Stealing a bit of the starry sky,
making the encounter romantic♪
♪The lights fade; the story isn't over♪
♪Let's continue our fate♪
♪A cup of wine
to honor courage and love's trials♪
♪For you, I'd dare to travel,
however long the journey is♪
♪The world's many twists
end in separation♪
♪I can't bear to watch♪
♪This mortal world is full of hardships♪
♪Alas, this fate is full of misfortune♪
♪But I refuse to accept♪
♪That regret is
the only natural outcome♪
♪So, I cross mountains and rivers♪
♪Just to keep you by my side♪
♪The joys and sorrows,
the partings and reunions♪
♪How profound♪
♪Whether it's to part or reunite
is not up to me♪
♪I can't escape fate's pull♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither;
there are always results♪
♪Leaving me no choice♪
♪So, I cross mountains and rivers♪
♪Just to keep you by my side♪
♪The joys and sorrows,
the partings and reunions♪
♪How profound♪
♪Whether it's to part or reunite
is not up to me♪
♪I can't escape fate's pull♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither;
there are always results♪
♪Leaving me no choice♪