My Little Princess
Episode 4
Yuzu.
Sister.
Madam.
Yushu.
Sister.
Madam.
What's wrong with me?
You fainted.
Do you feel anything wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just a little tired.
Say it again.
What happened just now?
I came in with my sister just now.
Then she cried.
She fainted right after that.
If you dare to play tricks,
I'll kill you.
Chongming,
it's not about her.
I was gambling and I was blind.
I was a little hurt.
Go back.
You're back.
How is it?
Is it beautiful?
What are you doing?
I saw that the house was cold.
My sister has also grown up recently.
I decorated it with Aojue.
It's a celebration.
So many seafood.
I haven't seen it.
Did you make all of this?
Most of it is made by me.
Aojue brought the ingredients.
Where is Aojue?
I'm back.
Madam.
Happy birthday.
Please have some cake.
You got it wrong.
Today is not my sister's birthday.
My sister's birthday is in January.
I've seen it.
No.
Your sister's birthday is the fifth day of Yin Li's birth.
I almost forgot.
To hide my identity,
I changed Yin Li's birthday to Yang Li's.
It's been so many years.
How did you know?
Aojue found out.
You're not a fake model.
You're really a big guy.
You're really funny.
Okay.
I'll take the flowers.
Thank you for celebrating my birthday.
Let's have some cake first.
Thank you, Li Li.
As long as you're happy.
Please sit down.
High-class heart.
Despicable.
So many seafood.
I haven't eaten it yet.
Let me taste your cooking.
Where did you get these?
These are the relatives of the villagers.
Your relatives are the ones who are in charge of the fish and shrimp.
Is this a joke?
What a cold joke.
You...
Make a wish first.
Then cut the cake.
Happy birthday to you.
Your Majesty.
Madam.
Chong Ming.
What's up?
Madam.
I'm not ready today.
This is a special gift from our clan.
It's a birthday gift for you.
Thank you, Chong Ming.
Madam.
You should rest early.
Okay.
Sister.
Ming Tai.
I didn't have time to prepare for the sneak attack.
These are the flowers I prepared for you.
Happy birthday.
Wild lily.
It's my favorite flower.
I used to visit my family when I was a kid.
Sister, don't worry.
Next time, I will give you a precious birthday gift.
No need. I like this very much.
Then you rest first.
I'm going back.
You haven't slept yet?
What's up?
Nothing.
Thank you for today.
I haven't had a birthday like this for a long time.
I'm very happy.
Is the little box in your hand
a gift for me?
I'm sorry.
I picked it up on the way.
What do you want to try?
What is it?
I don't know.
You see for yourself.
Give it to me.
It's so beautiful.
You...
I like it.
Help me put it on.
I'm sorry.
Aju.
God of War.
Go to see God of War first.
Don't worry.
He won't die.
It's you.
You have a heart attack.
If you didn't lie,
you would go to see your ancestors now.
Aju.
Say it.
I'm listening.
Aju.
What?
How is sister?
I just checked her blood pressure.
I checked her body.
I can't find anything.
There are dragon beads in her body.
In theory,
it won't be controlled by magic.
But just now I saw her eyes.
It seems to be controlled again.
What should we do?
Dragon beads in her body.
So there will be no life danger.
We'll see later.
That's all.
Where is Aju?
How is Aju?
She's not hurt.
I'll go see her.
Go.
I think the wound...
Her heart vein was hurt by her own evil spirit.
Fortunately, the angle was a little bit wrong.
Otherwise,
it's hard to save even a god.
I gave her the blood of Shanyun.
Now she's recovering faster.
I checked the situation of Shanyun.
There is no strange thing.
Did anything strange happen
when you went out?
Madam fainted in the old house of the Shans yesterday.
But she woke up soon.
She didn't check any abnormalities.
There are dragon beads in Shanyun's body.
Magic can't control her.
In this world,
is there anything except magic
that can control the spirit of human?
Have you heard of Wudu?
Wudu?
In ancient times,
dragon's surname is Ying.
The dragon is not the only dragon.
Dragon's seed is left everywhere.
The queen of dragon clan thought the dragon king didn't love herself.
In order to save the dragon king's heart,
she went to the big house of Miao River
and asked for a kind of medicine.
After the dragon king took the medicine,
he killed the queen.
Since then, the dragon clan has a special Wudu.
Zhan Xiang.
Go.
Nansheng, get out.
No. I want to wake up my sister.
I want to check her body.
It's inconvenient for you to be here.
Get out.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Don't be afraid.
I'm dizzy.
If you're dizzy, go upstairs.
Why are you here?
Will something happen to my sister?
If something happens to you,
Shan Yun Shu will not be in trouble.
Stop it.
You're so annoying.
No.
What happened last night?
You were injured.
My sister was poisoned.
You should make it clear.
I went to give her a gift yesterday.
Then there was an accident.
Give a gift?
Why didn't anything happen when I gave her a gift?
How could I know?
You're so bad luck.
Since my sister met you,
she has never been better.
What did you say?
Who is bad luck?
You...
Let me tell you.
I'm listener.
We were kissing yesterday.
Don't talk rubbish!
My sister will never fall in love with you.
She doesn't like you at all.
If you don't believe me,
ask her when she wakes up.
How is she?
As I know,
it's the poison-free
Crescent Thread.
It should be
put into food.
Someone would come
to poison the house
without any reason.
Crescent Thread?
Crescent Thread is a poison.
It won't harm
the body of the poisoned person,
but it will affect
the mind of the poisoned person.
The more you love someone,
the more you want to kill someone.
As long as you're moved,
you'll be killed.
You can only kill
the person you love
to ease the pain.
Poison is a life-long evil.
Only the one who forgets the love will be saved.
But most of the poisoned people
will die from the torture
of the one they love.
Even if they don't die,
their spirit will be divided into two.
Life is not like death.
You're too much.
Why are you laughing?
She loves me.
You...
Sister.
Wake up, sister.
What's going on?
It seems to be Meng Ye.
The
What's wrong with me?
Sister, you're awake.
You're poisoned.
It's Crescent Thread.
I used magic
to suppress it for the time being.
It won't kill you immediately.
Is he okay?
He's hurt his heart.
But he's recovered quickly after drinking your blood.
He's probably having fun
somewhere.
Having fun?
The poison of Crescent Thread
will only kill the one he loves.
Now he knows
that he's the one you love.
He has forgotten
that you killed him.
What's wrong?
When I think of his happy face,
I feel like I want to kill him.
Me too.
You can kill him for me.
But after your sister and Zhang Mingkai
heard me explain the effect of Crescent Thread,
they seemed to be a little different.
I...
Crescent Thread is poisonous,
but it can prove
who cares about it the most.
I care about my sister the most.
How could it be?
I'm not asleep yet.
I just passed by the toilet.
Did I wake you up?
No.
I'm waiting for your apology.
Your wound...
It hurts.
But I can't die.
What about you?
I'm fine.
I'll go back if I'm fine.
You're so perfunctory.
I almost died today.
But you're not dead yet.
And I can't control it.
Am I poisoned?
You know the principle of that poison, right?
I just woke up.
I don't know the principle of Crescent Thread.
What's wrong?
I didn't say it's Crescent Thread.
What do you mean?
I can't see you,
but I can feel your emotions.
What's wrong with me?
Are you going to hurt me
or like me?
Or you want to like me?
Aojue, listen to me.
I'm a married woman.
I like Brother Zhenxuan.
You can't think nonsense.
And you can't tell others.
Or I'll tear your mouth apart.
You tore my heart apart.
I don't care.
Are you really Aojue?
How can you say such disgusting words?
I'm not.
Then you can throw up.
But I still want to say
I didn't ask you to forget him.
He sacrificed his life for you.
It's good that you know.
But
I've sacrificed my life for you several times.
If my flesh and blood were all dead,
would you cry in my grave
because of indigestion?
Good people don't live long.
You can't live for a thousand years.
You're still alive.
I'm leaving.
I don't want to hit you.
He likes me.
Admit it.
I like you.
From Auzom.
What did he say?
What else can he say?
He doesn't admit that he likes me.
I'm not talking about this.
I'm talking about the poison.
The Crescent Thread is a dragon-type special poison.
And it's already out of the realm.
The Black Robe can get the poison
that only dragon-type people have.
It seems that
you may know it.
I actually have a feeling that I know who it is.
Who?
Do you know that I stole the dragon-type
to save my brother?
I don't know.
He was poisoned by the Crescent Thread.
My father cut off the bond between Ao Feng and his mother.
He poisoned him with the food I sent him.
He killed his own mother with his own hands.
Your brother died of such a poison.
In theory, this poison
should have been out of the realm.
How can the Black Robe get it?
Although I have repeatedly overturned my guess,
the most likely one is my brother,
Ao Feng.
I'm afraid that I can't prove it.
Thank you.