[Strange Chronicles of Tang]
[Episode 11]
Home, sweet home.
This chicken soup Xijun made
really has the taste
of Nanzhou Prefecture's family tradition.
I'm full.
Xijun,
you should eat too.
I won't have any appetite
unless I see you getting better.
With you taking such good care of me,
it'd be strange if I don't get better.
It was your miraculous medicine
that helped you recover so quickly.
Fei.
How about a drink?
I'll...
hold off on drinking for now.
When my wound heals,
I'll drink to my heart's content.
So you've learned to value your life.
Those two assassins were truly vicious.
Fei,
why were they targeting you?
Wasn't it because of you?
They're disciples of Silent Ember,
named...
Wu Zhu and Chi Zhen—
two bird names.
If they wanted revenge,
why didn't they come for me directly?
You don't understand.
Silent Ember is known for his cunning.
The first rule he teaches his disciples is
if you can't win, run.
With your reputation
in martial skills,
you think they'd dare to come after you?
That's strange.
Then why did they suddenly
fight me so desperately
when I went to save you?
And they were saying something like,
"the ritual has begun,"
"so it can't be stopped."
Fei,
what ritual were they talking about?
The wind was strong in the forest.
Who knows what they were saying?
You must have misheard.
In the Ascension Forest,
I also encountered these two assassins.
I stumbled upon them,
but Fei was taken captive.
That's not right.
If they wanted revenge for Silent Ember,
Lu Lingfeng
should've been their first target,
and I should've been the second.
How could they...
Why is my chest hurting again?
I heard Yingtao say
they went somewhere yesterday
that was very interesting.
Everyone can pour out their troubles there
and find some relief.
Whatever troubles are in your heart,
once spoken, they will pass.
Since we're free tonight,
why don't we
try that game too?
That sounds good.
I didn't get a chance
to pour out my troubles yesterday.
My heart has been heavy all this time.
How about this?
The four of us
take turns.
I'll go first.
I'm from the Su family
of Wugong in Guanxi,
a collateral branch.
My family had no vast fortune,
only a few thatched huts.
When I was 8,
my father died in an accident
at the government office.
The cause was never determined.
My mother made and sold shoes,
enduring every hardship
to raise me.
I studied for 10 long years
and eventually
passed the imperial examination.
On the night the results were posted,
I looked up at the sky
and asked myself
where my ambitions lay.
With the stars as my witness,
my ambition was never high office,
but criminal investigation.
So I apprenticed myself to a great master
and learned the art of detection.
However,
for various reasons,
I have been drifting in official circles,
rising one moment and falling the next,
for more than ten years now.
People often say
I'm shrewd,
but who knows the resentment in my heart?
After investigating cases
for over a decade,
my own father's death
remains unsolved.
How painful.
Yingtao is both strong and gentle.
I hope to share my life with her.
Yet,
I'm caught in a vortex,
surrounded by turbulent currents,
living on the edge of danger every day,
with death always near.
How could I...
I can't bring myself to push her away,
yet keeping her close risks
dragging her down with me.
Trapped between letting go and holding on,
my heart is full of worry.
As for the Tang Empire,
which weighs most on my heart,
I can never let it go.
I...
Have I said too much?
Xijun,
it's... it's your turn.
Don't look at me,
or I'll feel embarrassed.
Lu Lingfeng,
especially you.
Look away.
I was born into a noble family
and raised in official circles.
That's nothing special.
In Chang'an,
women of my background
are countless.
People say women leave no mark in history.
Those recorded are only empresses
or princesses.
Though unworthy,
I decided to defy fate,
so I trained in painting from a young age
and finally mastered it,
able to capture all things in the world.
I want to leave traces of my life
through painting.
Painting is my passion,
and through it
I met the one I love.
I originally intended
to speak of my sorrows,
but after thinking it through,
I realized I have no sorrows to tell.
Or rather,
compared to your troubles,
my small troubles
hardly matter.
So I'll just share a thought with you.
Life passes
like a fleeting shadow.
There's no need
to keep pain and sorrows bottled up.
Instead, with true friends,
you can open your heart
and speak your mind.
I believe
that if you do this,
good fortune will follow.
No matter how harsh the past,
the road ahead will be smooth.
My turn.
I'll tell a story
about a princess, an assassin,
and a child.
[Great Virtue Can Carry the World]
Later,
the child came to the capital.
The former Empress was gone.
Of those who killed his father,
only the princess remained.
And she
was also the very woman who gave him life,
his mother by blood.
Fei,
it's your turn.
Master Fei,
though you're optimistic and cheerful,
you must have something
you want to share too.
Fei,
you haven't fallen asleep, have you?
What's there to share?
If you want to interrogate me, then do it.
I've got nothing to say.
If you're going to torture me,
make it brutal.
Send me straight to my mentor.
If you still see me
as a friend,
please do me a favor
and bury my remains
outside the Medicine King Hall.
Master Fei.
Shut up!
You little girl.
You're in on this with them,
plotting against me.
I know,
I
have been in Chang'an for decades
and still don't even have
a house of my own.
I can only lodge at your Pei's Mansion.
What?
Are you kicking me out?
Fine, I'll leave.
Fei!
If you don't want to talk,
no one's forcing you,
and no one's kicking you out.
That's right.
You're not young anymore,
and you're badly injured,
so why keep
losing your temper?
Look how you've frightened Xijun.
We were wrong.
Just rest well.
If there are things
you don't want to talk about, then don't.
If you don't want
to bring up the past,
then we won't mention it again.
Alright?
Come on.
Though he didn't say anything,
it was as good as an admission.
[Great Virtue Can Carry the World]
Fei heals the sick,
benefiting the people.
We've all seen it
with our own eyes over the years.
As for his past,
let it remain a mystery.
He's been mysterious
from the start.
I'm not trying to dig up old matters.
It's just that lately,
the Crimson Pact assassins
have been appearing frequently.
I'm worried
something big might happen in Chang'an.
That's why I wanted to get
some information from him.
The three female assassins
who imprisoned Xie You
were probably minions.
They have long lost contact
with the Crimson Pact.
Their exposure this time
must be coincidental.
[Great Virtue Can Carry the World]
As for Wu Zhu and Chi Zhen,
I actually find it interesting that they
keep showing up in Ascension Forest.
How so?
The other day, Fei said that
minions
are assassins in the Crimson Pact,
but not really assassins.
They can recruit their own subordinates,
but have only one direct handler.
If they lose contact
with their  handler,
they become expendable.
There are cases where a master
trains a disciple as a minion.
If Wu Zhu and Chi Zhen
are such minions,
then their master, Silent Ember,
must be their handler.
So...
Ascension Forest
is their meeting point?
That place is dark and frightening.
People are wary of it.
Isn't it perfect
for a meeting point?
When punishing so-called traitors,
they also chose Ascension Forest.
Therefore,
the Crimson Pact's headquarters
must be nearby.
Perhaps...
it's in Xiuzhen District.
Back then, when my master, Master Di,
was investigating the Crimson Pact,
[Great Virtue Can Carry the World]
he came all the way
from Divine Capital to Chang'an.
He also suspected
it was in Xiuzhen District,
but never found solid evidence.
What is it?
I'd like you
to visit Xiuzhen District again
and draw a map for me.
That's easy.
I'll go tomorrow.
[Chicken Master of Tang]
[Relief-from-Woes]
If there's anyone special,
it would be her.
She came to us on her own.
And the gold coin she gave
was quite unusual.
Gold coin?
Where is it?
Put it away.
This gold coin
was specially made when His Majesty
was invested as Crown Prince.
I've received such a reward before,
so I remember that mark clearly.
Although I've never received
such a reward,
I can still tell
that gold coin is special.
This mere Relief-from-Woes Shop
actually has something to do
with His Majesty.
Truly unexpected.