[Strange Chronicles of Tang]
[Episode 21]
So, you're the son of Grand Tutor Guo.
Do you know how to play polo?
No, I don't.
That's quite a pity.
Though I can't play polo,
I've excelled at painting since childhood.
I'd be honored...
to paint a polo match for Your Highness.
That's actually a good idea.
When the rain stops,
I'll call them
to play polo with me.
I'd like to see
how well you can paint.
My painting...
will surely be passed down
through the ages.
You're so arrogant.
Do you think you're as good as Gu Kaizhi?
Gu Kaizhi was merely
peerless in painting, unmatched in talent,
and utterly obsessed.
I'm more versed in the classics
than he was.
I can recite
the "Spring and Autumn Annals" backward.
Does Your Highness doubt
that within 10 years...
my fame will surpass his?
That crazed scholar?
I remember now.
He was the son
of the great Confucian Master Guo Yu.
Yes.
It was Guo Sigong
who presented a folding screen
to the Palace Secretariat,
10 years
after Emperor Xiaojing's death.
And upon that screen
was the painting
"The Lament of the Imperial Scandal."
Liu,
every time you come to see me,
you stare at that screen in a daze.
Could it be
that you and Guo Sigong
have some connection?
Liu!
Take off your disguise!
Liu Zigui.
Why did you do this?
Did you kill all those people
in the painting?
They deserved to die.
Every single one of them deserved death!
[United in Virtue and Learning]
It was a spring many years ago.
At that time,
the great Confucian Master Guo Yu
was teaching Emperor Xiaojing
the "Spring and Autumn Annals."
[Guo Yu, Eastern Palace Official]
Your Highness the Crown Prince.
Your Highness.
If Your Highness finds the passage
in the Spring and Autumn Annals
about Shangchen murdering his father,
the emperor, too cruel
and unbearable to hear,
then starting tomorrow,
I will teach Your Highness
the "Book of Rites" instead.
Your Highness?
Why isn't he dead yet?
Wasn't the strychnine
supposed to have killed him already?
I can hit him in the temple
with a polo mallet!
[Zhu Ling]
To put him out of his misery.
What do you think?
You can't be the only one to strike him.
[Wei Yan]
If we're doing this,
everyone present
must take part.
You're afraid
that otherwise,
[Tutu Wenzhen]
someone might leak the truth
in the future?
Aren't we just acting on orders?
[Bo Cui]
What is there to fear?
Fear that the one who gave the orders
[Zheng Zhong]
might change their mind later.
Wei Yan's idea is good.
Let's go with that.
Xi,
you must strike as well.
Me too?
[Xi]
Otherwise,
you'll eat the rest of the flatbread
and follow His Highness in death!
No, no.
I'll do it.
Hurry up then. You go first!
You're talking nonsense!
Guo Yu was fabricating stories!
He was lying!
Sheriff Wei,
there's no need to be so agitated.
The one fabricating stories
is probably not Guo Yu.
Let him finish what he has to say.
My grandfather
witnessed it with his own eyes.
He told everything to my father.
And less than a year after
Emperor Xiaojing's death,
he died of depression.
And my father,
because of Emperor Xiaojing's death,
lost his promising career.
Before he died,
he told me the secret
of "The Lament of the Imperial Scandal"
and instructed me
to avenge Emperor Xiaojing!
I, Guo Zigui,
[Liu Zigui, Ma Meng's Classmate]
then sneaked into Chang'an with my mother,
[Guo Zigui, Ma Meng's Classmate]
waiting for an opportunity.
Until Ma Meng...
rose from a mere
Hanzhou Judicial Advisor
to become Deputy Director
of the Palace Secretariat!
He's now a fourth-rank official.
I both admired him
and felt a bit jealous.
But more importantly,
I saw an opportunity for revenge!
I sent Gulou Pastry
to those people while disguised as him—
who would refuse it?
This must be His Majesty's kindness.
Grand General,
do you need me to spell it out?
In that case,
many thanks to Secretariat Ma.
The Ghost Market Magistrate Feng
also recalled something:
Crown Prince Hong held his teacher Guo Yu
in the highest regard.
The Crown Prince once
bestowed upon him the golden polo mallet
granted by Emperor Gaozong himself.
What you're carrying now
is that very item, isn't it?
Yes!
And so what?
I had planned to force
strychnine poison down Wei Yan's throat.
Then, using the same method they used
to murder Emperor Xiaojing,
I'd deal with him
just like the others!
Secretariat Ma...
Why?
Who are you, really?
The golden mallet bestowed by His Majesty
didn't get to taste Tutu Wenzhen's blood.
Though that old eunuch is dead,
this still leaves me
like Duke Xiang of Song—defeated at Hong,
filled only with regret.
Stop desecrating
the "Spring and Autumn Annals" here!
Do you know
who delivered the screen
painted with
"The Lament of the Imperial Scandal"
to the Palace Secretariat?
It was me,
Tutu Wenzhen.
You're still alive?
This old life of mine
isn't worth saving.
What's truly regrettable is
that back then,
I helped your father
deliver the screen
to the Palace Secretariat,
yet it still didn't cure his madness.
What did you say?
Attendant Tutu,
you were my father's good friend.
Please help me.
It's not that I'm unwilling to help.
But everyone knows you're ill,
and I don't know
how best to help you.
I have just completed a new painting
of Emperor Xiaojing playing polo,
also titled
"The Lament of the Imperial Scandal."
It's exquisite.
Attendant Tutu, I only ask
that you help me
send it to the Palace Secretariat.
I believe
once His Majesty sees it,
he will surely be impressed by my talent.
Then,
there will be hope for my official career.
Fine.
For your father's sake,
I will help you.
According to
the Ministry of Personnel's records,
the court
no longer employed Guo Sigong
because he suffered from
severe delusions.
Especially after Guo Yu's death,
his condition worsened significantly.
Therefore,
Guo Yu's so-called eyewitness account
of Crown Prince Hong's murder
must be Guo Sigong's delusion.
Impossible!
I know!
Many street storytellers
often fabricate tales
about Crown Prince Hong's death,
bewitching the common people.
In their wild inventions,
Empress Wu Zetian becomes
the mastermind behind it all.
Some even dare
to slander Emperor Gaozong himself.
And we, the former officials
of the Eastern Palace,
become accomplices.
Do you know
that after His Highness died,
Emperor Gaozong and Empress Wu Zetian
were extremely grief-stricken?
Otherwise,
why would they posthumously bestow
upon him the title Emperor Xiaojing
and have him buried with
the rites of an emperor
in the imperial mausoleum?
I heard Emperor Gaozong say
with my own ears
that Crown Prince Hong's death
was a loss to the nation
and that the empire lost a wise ruler
and a polo champion!
When Emperor Gaozong said this,
he was in tears.
This old man
still remembers it vividly to this day!
Impossible!
Impossible.
You will never convince me!
My father was the most
excellent man in this world!
If Crown Prince Hong hadn't
been murdered by you,
he could have at least become chancellor!
And I,
Guo Zigui,
wouldn't be like I am now—
skilled in both civil and military arts,
full of talent
yet unrecognized by anyone!
Wei Yan,
Tutu Wenzhen,
you are the murderers.
By Emperor Xiaojing's edict,
I hereby take your lives!
This was bestowed by His Majesty.
This was the treasure
granted to our Guo family
by Emperor Xiaojing himself!
I'll kill you!
No!
Stop!
Sheriff Wei.
It seems that Guo Zigui
also suffers from madness.
Although he has confessed his crimes,
this case
involves many high-ranking court officials
and still requires a joint trial
by the Three Judicial Offices!
There is no need
for a joint trial for such a madman!
[The Lament of the Imperial Scandal]
His Majesty has ordered
the Palace Secretariat
to destroy this screen.
I heard.
Xijun thinks
it's a great pity.
In terms of artistry alone,
this painting is on par with
Gu Kaizhi's work.
It would indeed be a shame to destroy it.
Fortunately,
Her Highness the Princess learned of this
and sent someone to request the screen.
What does Her Highness want it for?
Her Highness said
she wishes to gaze upon the painting
to ease her longing for her elder brother.
When Emperor Xiaojing passed away,
Her Highness was only 10 years old.
It's said they had
a very close sibling relationship.
Whether this is an excuse or not,
at least
this treasured painting has been spared.
I just wonder
if this painting will survive
for thousands of years.
Who knows what will happen
thousands of years from now?
[The Lament of the Imperial Scandal]
[Benign Governance with Ease]
Your Majesty.
Yin,
is today's gastrodia powder ready?
I heard Your Majesty
was furious over
"The Lament of the Imperial Scandal" case.
This worried me
to the point of distraction,
and I forgot to prepare it.
This servant deserves death.
This servant will go make it right away.
No hurry.
Do you know...
I dreamed about you last night?
Your Majesty, please don't tease me.
[Benign Governance with Ease]
However,
it wasn't in this lifetime.
No matter which lifetime,
I'm happy just to be
by Your Majesty's side.
I dreamed of a thousand years from now.
I was no longer the Emperor,
but merely...
a clerk in a general store.
A clerk?
Then what of this servant?
[Benign Governance with Ease]
You were not an ordinary person
but a goddess who could
travel between heaven and earth at will.