Oh, Miss Earl.
Miss Earl, Miss Earl.
Miss Earl.
Why are you sleeping here?
I've been looking for you all over the palace.
I must be tired.
I've been very busy lately.
Is there something wrong?
Um... Your Highness and Your Lady have called
regarding an important matter.
Alright.
But let me go take a shower first. I'll call them back later.
Oh, what about Kanthir?
He made a call since early morning,
telling that he'd come here a little late today.
I think he had an amazing time last night.
Don't forget to eat breakfast before going to work.
I don't want to have a skinny boyfriend with a big head.
This crazy boy.
When did I become your boyfriend?
I ate it.
What a bad cooking skill.
But thanks.
Come home soon.
Do you still love it even it sucks?
I don't know.
I just know that I miss you.
What?
I got to work.
I'll see you after work tonight.
Okay.
Hello, Father.
Is there something important?
It's Kong's parents.
They asked me since you've been engaged for a long time.
I'm not ready. It's not the time yet.
Don't let it go on too long.
It's not easy to find a good guy like Kong.
He loves you sincerely.
I don't think I will be able to love Kong like a lover in this life.
When you live together, you'll fall in love with each other eventually.
Your mother and I have high expectations of you.
Don't let me down.
Dear Grandfather,
today I made some Kanom Pra Pai for you.
They say that Kanom Pra Pai is an auspicious dessert.
Eating it makes love strong and lasting.
But why is my love life
always filled with sadness?
Hello, Fierce?
What?
What did you say?
In front of the palace?
Am I really that untrustworthy?
That's why your maid is standing over me like this.
Ta is always like this.
This palace doesn't receive many guests. They probably aren't used to it yet.
Then...
I guess I'll have to come here more often.
So she'll get used to it.
Do you have free time? You said you were busy with work.
For someone special,
I always find time.
Ta, today I bought grilled fish for you.
But you have to be careful.
There are a lot of cat burglars around here.
Don't worry, Miss Milinth.
I will keep my eyes on them.
Good.
Prey, I have a lot to tell you.
Really, Madam.
I don't like the way this new friend of Ms. Prey looked at her.
She seems like a total flirt.
So you called to tell Tian.
Because I'm worried about Miss Prey.
No matter how much you scold me, I will accept it.
That's good. We have to take special care of her during this time
until she gets stronger.
Madam.
Is this Miss Fierce the one who made Miss Prey cry?
What I'm worried about is that she's not the one that Prey is waiting for.
I didn't know that you had a guest today.
I thought I would discuss with you about the Thai dessert competition.
Are you holding it?
Great, I was just looking for something to do.
I'm going to ask you to join.
Importantly, Tian is also a major sponsor of this event.
Then I would like to join in too.
If you join,
then I would like to be your co-sponsor.
I hope you don't mind, Milinth.
Sure.
Okay, then can you go to celebrate with me, Prey?
She's probably not convenient now
because I got a lot of works to discuss with her today.
You can leave first.
So let's consult with Ms. Sinee about what kind of desserts we're going to make.
Okay? / Yes.
Let's go.
Thank you so much. / Let's go.
This is going to be fun.
Miss Earl.
Miss Earl, Miss Earl.
What's up?
Sign the document.
Here.
Earl.
Are you having a personal problem?
Is it that easy to see through?
Yes.
If you let me guess, it must be about your rushing marriage, right?
You should be a fortune teller instead of a secretary.
And what if it were you?
Will you choose your happiness or rightness?
If it were me, I would choose rightness if it was about work.
But if it was about love, I would choose my happiness.
That's true.
Even something as simple as this, I can't figure it out.
Until almost everything went wrong.
Earl.
No one never made a mistake.
But if we know where we went wrong,
we will know more about how to fix it.
It's been two months now, Great-Grandmother.
I haven't got in touch with Earl at all.
I think…
Earl is probably not the reincarnation of you.
Because if so, she wouldn't be so mean to me.
I'm stupid.
Prey.
What are you mumbling to yourself about?
Let's go.
It's almost time for the competition.
I haven't prepared anything yet.
Don't worry.
Ms. Sinee and Ta have already put them in the car for you.
That's great.
Let's go.
Prey.
This event,
Earl is a judge.
Are you okay with that?
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Let's go. / Go.
You organized the event very stylishly.
Thank you very much for coming to the event
and helping to report the news.
Yes, do you have a schedule for when the next event will be held?
Oh, it should be early in the year.
Sorry, it should be early next year. Please come again.
Sure. / Anyway, excuse me for now.
Thank you.
Oh, Miss Earl is here.
Let's take their photo in one frame.
Can I take a photo of you two together?
Yes.
This camera, please.
Thank you very much.
Hello, Earl.
Kong isn't coming with you today?
We're not close enough
to talk about personal stuff.
Today we may not be close, but who knows in the future.
The two of us have many things in common.
We are friends with Tian
and also...we like the same person.
This should be enough for us to become close.
Miss Athithan, what are some of the delicious dessert menus you have in this final round?
We have Bulan Dan Mek, Chor Phaka Krong and Saneh Jaan.
Good luck. / Thank you.
And what about you, Jamjan? The other team has Bulan Dan Mek,
Saneh Jaan and Chor Phaka Krong.
What menus will you bring out?
We're preparing Chor Muang, Intanin, and Sum Pun Nee.
Good luck. / Thank you. / Over there, please.
Hello, where are you?
I'm standing here waiting.
There's a Benz parking right in front of you.
Here.
You should know the time and place. Next time, don't leave your things at my house.
I just want to see your face.
You've seen my face all night, why do you want more?
Huh? What did you say?
I can't hear it very well.
Come closer to tell me.
I want to say
Don't forget stuff at my house again.
I am working now.
Hey.
I have the motivation to work now.
See you tonight.
Mines are Bulan Dan Mek, Saneh Jaan and Chor Phaka Krong.
For me, there are Sum Pun Nee, Chor Muang and Intanin.
Both contestant, please come to the front of the stage.
The winner of this Thai dessert competition is…
Miss Athithan Utsanakhorn, the creator of Pray for Love.
Prey, congrats.
Good job.
Congratulations, Prey.
Congratulations.
You are the best.
I want to try your desserts too.
Could you take care of the stuff for me?
Okay, I'll take of it.
Prey.
Let me give you a little reminder.
If you want the truth,
you must tell him everything that's on your mind.
Do you understand?
Okay, thank you.
Earl, Earl.
Earl.
Aren't you going to congratulate me?
Congrats.
Do you know?
Why did I make the Pray of Love dessert?
I don't know.
And I don't want to know either.
This dessert
represents my love.
Bulan Dan Mek
is like a young woman who has never been in love.
Even though she is bright and cheerful,
she is surrounded by clouds.
And then one day she found sweet love.
Filled with the allure just like Saneh Jaan.
In the end, whether my love
will be as sweet as Chor Phaka Krong
or will become only a snack
is up to you now.
I can't give you any answers.
Earl.
If we cut out Utsanakhorn,
I'm just a girl
begging for your love.
Why don't you look back at me?
All these times,
Was it all my fault that I thought this way?
Can you look me in the eyes
and tell me
that you never loved me?
Calm down and listen to me carefully.
I never loved you.
Excuse me.
Prey.
Do you want to tell me?
No.
You never cares about me at all.
I feel hurt too.
Now you're acting like
the person who hurt you.
That's not true.
I'm not that kind of person.
I'm not mean like…
Really?
Prove it.
How do I prove it?
If you're not that cruel,
tonight
you go on a date with me.
Do you dare to prove it?
I…
You're so cruel.
You've rejected me countless times.
Okay, I'll ask for permission from Thian first.
I already told Tian.
Let's have dinner tonight.
I told Tian already.
Don't worry.
You guys did a great job today.
I'll see you at the office.
Could you look over there? There's a little trash.
Okay.
Thank you.
Today's event went well.
Good job. / Milinth.
Milinth.
Yes? / Have you seen Prey?
I've been looking for her for a long time and I can't find her.
I let Kanthir help for the search.
Wait a minute. Prey isn't with you?
No, Prey followed Earl out
and now she's missing.
Here.
Why aren't you answering the phone?
Kanthir.
Have you found her yet?
No.
But most importantly, Miss Fierce has also disappeared.
Huh? / Fierce?
They must have left together.
And…
And where is Earl?
What happened?
Prey left with Fierce.
I tried to contact her, but it seems like her phone is turned off.
I don't know where that snake is taking her.
Wait.
Prey's bag has an AirTag to prevent it from getting lost.
It also connects to my phone.
Here it is.
Did you find it?
Wait a minute, this is a bar near Lat Phrao.
A bar?
That means Tian's friend
definitely has bad intention towards her.
I'm going to report it to the police.
Please calm down.
If you go and report it, it might become news
and it won't have a good effect on Prey.
Then what should I do?
Should I stand still and not be bothered like you?
To be honest,
the culprit is you,
who put my niece in danger.
Calm down, Sinee.
Please trust me.
I will bring Prey back safely.
Thir, tell Tian to meet at the bar.
Milinth, come with me. / Yes, yes.
Let's go.
Calm down.
What would you like to drink?
I don't really like drinking wine.
It's bitter.
Really?
But sometimes…
To forget someone,
alcohol is also a good helper
that makes you forget your suffering.
Wow.
You drank it all in one go.
This is not good at all.
You'll get drunk fast.
Excuse me.
I'd like two of these whiskeys, please.
Are you just drinking it straight?
An eye for an eye, right?
I saw that you were drunk.
Drink this now so that you can sober up when Tian picks you up home.
See? It's much better.
It's a pity
that a beautiful girl like you is single.
If I were Earn, I definitely wouldn't let you go.
Can you please not mention that person?
Then
tonight,
it's just the two of us, right?
Excuse me, I would like one Virgin and On The Rocks.
You're so good.
Knowing what to order.
Hey, I'm in a hotel industry.
This is very basic.
Prey.
How dare you slap me?
This is a blessing not to kill you.
You… evil wicked. You trash.
You worthless trash.
Can you hold her a bit?
I'll take care of this witch myself.
I just found out that Tian has a jellyfish as her girlfriend.
You looks innocent,
but in reality, you're full of poison.
But it's better than you.
At first you seemed friendly.
But you're clearly a snake.
If you dare, go ahead.
But I can assure you that
your business will surely be ruined.
Tian, Prey definitely can't go home in this condition.
Thir, take Prey and Earl to the Sittalrat Palace.
Let me deal with this evil friend first.
All the companies I have shares in at Crawford,
I want to cancel all contracts.
If you are not satisfied, sue me.
I give you Prey. Please take good care of my sister.
Kassakorn.
Let's go. / Move.
You gave Prey to Earl,
but you stop me?
Yes.
Why?
Because my sister loves her.
And Earl never used low-level methods to win like you.
But Earl doesn't love Prey.
I'm the one who loves Prey.
This is not called love.
Have you ever thought about
what would happen if she were yours against her will?
If you really love my sister,
Then don't use such low methods.
And every project
that Methakorn has done with Crawford,
I will cancel them all.
Tian, I'm your friend.
Friend?
Not anymore
Today, you sleep at Sittalrat Palace first.
I'll give you a ride to your palace tomorrow morning.
What's the matter?
Your body is warm and fragrant.
That's why I don't want to stop hugging you.
If you don't let go of me now,
you can't let go of me for the rest of your life, my dear.
Since the first time we met,
I can't let go of you anymore.
I'm ready to fly with you everywhere,
every place,
with the wind of love.
Hello, Tian.
Hello, Ms. Sinee.
Tonight, Prey will sleep at my friend's house.
She will be back home tomorrow.
Please tell Grandpa about this.
Okay, I will inform the Prince.
Thanks a lot.
Yes, goodnight.
Is that Tian?
Yes.
She asked me to tell you that
Prey will be sleeping at her friend's house. She will be returning tomorrow.
Tian's friend that is called Earl?
Yes.
Earl?
Kassakorn,
daughter of M.R. Sasimonthon
Sittalrat,
right?
Grandma,
I'm Ahatsakorn, your grandson.
I…
I'm well aware that the two families have had a great deal of conflict.
But what should I do?
I just want this whole thing to end.
Grandma,
please take care
of my granddaughter Prey.
I hope that what you wish for
will come true.
What happened?
Your dear sister has disappeared somewhere.
You mean Wee?
There is no way.
I'm very worried about Wee, my son.
She'll be okay, Mother.
We found her. We found her.
We have found Lady Wee, Your Majesty.
Wee, where is she?
Oh, why are you delaying? Hurry up and tell me.
She passed away in the canal at the end of the palace
along with Miss Kwan, Sir.
My dear Wee.
Mother.
Please calm down.
What's wrong, Your Highness?
I feel…
a little uneasy.
Is this about Lady Piangrawee?
Last night, the lady didn't take me away.
She has never broken a promise even once.
The lady did not come even though she knew
that my lady would have a wedding ceremony this morning.
This might be her answer.
My daughter is so pretty.
You are becoming one with Panudejrangsee.
In the future,
you will know how much I have done for you.
Alright, once you're all dressed up,
hurry up and go to the ceremony, or we won't make it in time
for His Highness's visit.
Kaew.
What's the matter, Your Highness?
The water pouring ceremony is unlikely to be completed,
but the royal holy water should be considered complete.
How could my daughter's wedding be so miserable?
Your Highness, don't let this go.
It is necessary, Your Highness,
that we cannot hold this auspicious event.
Why?
Is my daughter not worthy?
It has nothing to do with her.
Now all the relatives have gathered at Utsanakhorn Palace.
Why are they going there? Did someone die?
Yes, there is.
And Utsanakhorn blamed it on us.
Who died? Who did it?
What did they do?
M.J. Piangrawee's boat
capsized, leading to her death at the end of Utsanakhorn Palace last night.
Lady. / Daughter.
Your Highness, this way, please.
Relax, slowly.
My dear. / Mother.
Your Highness.
Calm down.
Take it easy.
You'll be fine.
Calm down, calm down.
Mother.
Do you already know about this?
What do you mean?
You're accusing me now.
Piangrawee is my fiancé.
Suddenly she died on my sister's wedding day.
And this.
How did your subordinate Boon
have a bag of money stamped with the seal of Sittalrat Palace?
How will you answer me?
I didn't think things would escalate this far.
I didn't want anyone to die.
So you let Boon sink Wee's boat last night?
I knew it.
The low class people…
They must have done something low.
M.J. Utsanee.
Are you behind my daughter's death?
Why？
How could you think of hurting Wee like this?
We will soon be related.
Your Highness.
Please let us arrest you and send you to the authorities.
Please take it easy.
Why？
Why do we have to be calm?
Your mother didn't even think about the consequence.
Come with me to the police now.
What are you doing?
Ratchanon.
This is Sittalrat Palace.
You don't have evidence
Fine.
If the law can't do anything,
I will depend on karma instead.
I, Princess Utsanee Utsanakhorn,
the wife of Your Highness,
will curse you from now on.
You will never be happy.
No heir, the royal family will end here.
There will be no male heirs
from now on.
Because
the bloodline is mixed with that of the lower class.
And all of Utsanakhorn's descendants
will hold a grudge
against Sittalrat in every life.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I'm not.
What kind of good kid is lying since early morning?
I'm not lying. The tears just flowed on their own.
That's what they call crying.
I'm just sad.
What are you sad about?
What happened last night.
I don't deserve it.
Don't be like this, my love.
I was so happy last night.
Don't you feel the same way with me?
I love you.
But what we did was wrong.
Because you already has a fiancé.
No one owns me.
Your fiancé does.
Just because we're engaged
doesn't mean I love him.
But he still has the right.
Should I break off the engagement for you?
I prepared some Sum Pun Nee and hot tea for you.
You have some to refresh your body.
After I'm done eating, I'll drive you to the palace.
Since we're dating now, can I go inside your house?
You can drop me off at the front of the palace like usual.
I don't want you to waste your time.
Not at all.
Today I want to drop you off inside.
Let's do it next time.
You rejected me like this, are you afraid that people will see us?
Anyway, you're not good at lying.
Then drop me off inside the palace.
You forgot your phone.
Thank you.
You come back at this hour?
Who gave you a ride?
I think it's familiar face.
Tian's friend. We just met at the mall, so she came to drop me off.
When your father was young,
I raised him much more strictly than this.
But with you,
I think I'm too kind.
So you dare to lie to me so blatantly.
I didn't lie to you.
I didn't say that you lied about what happened earlier.
But you got a friend who is many years older than you?
I told you it's Tian's friend.
But you didn't tell me that she was from Sittalrat.
Do you have any other excuses?
No.
From now on, you are not allowed to leave the palace for 2 weeks.
I'm going to confiscate your mobile phone too.
Sir, being grounded is fine,
but confiscating her phone, I think…
Yes.
It's okay.
I will do as Grandpa said.
Prey.
Here's my phone.