THE NAMES OF PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, AND
BACKGROUNDS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
EPISODE 10
Time, please.
It's now 3:12 p.m.
I'll remove the heart.
A ghost doctor?
Mr. Han Yihan was the ghost doctor
who operated on the VIPs of Banseokwon
in Gu Hyunseong's place?
I am sure.
Director Gu Hyunseong
left for the US five years ago
and worked hard to develop surgery robots
because Dr. Han left Banseok.
What about
how he said he'd operate on me?
He was going to leave it
to another doctor.
A new ghost doctor to replace Han Yihan.
If what you just said is true,
I cannot condone this.
That ungrateful man must pay
for making an attempt to deceive me.
Then why don't you meet him
to confirm this?
Mr. Han Yihan?
You should meet him
as a doctor, not a lawyer.
The best cardiac surgeon in Korea,
Dr. Han Yihan.
I heard the story.
That you are
the best cardiac surgeon in Korea
who stood in for Director Gu Hyunseong.
Is this true?
Please give me an answer.
Have you been operating
on the hearts of Banseokwon's VIPs
in Gu Hyunseong's place?
That's correct.
I'm the doctor
who operated in Gu Hyunseong's place.
I'm his ghost doctor, Han Yihan.
It's nice to meet you.
Can you be
in charge of my heart?
I'll take charge of your heart.
I'll remove the heart.
It's now 3:35 p.m.
NEW-HOPE LAW OFFICE
NEW-HOPE MEDICINE CLINIC
How is he?
He'll need other examinations,
but his ventricular septum is thick,
and the pressure difference is very high.
He'll need surgery.
You can sit up.
By any chance,
have you ever received heart surgery?
You can tell him, Dad.
He can keep a secret.
All right.
You exposed your disgraceful past,
so I must be honest with you.
Yes, I've received
heart transplant surgery.
When did you receive it?
This is probably the fifth year.
-Five years.
-Why? Is there a problem?
No, it's for the procedure.
Thank you for sharing it with me.
Thank you. Yihan, I owe you a lot.
You saved me, then you'll save my dad.
I can't guarantee that I'll save him.
I can't find out
the result of the surgery beforehand.
It didn't feel too real until now,
but you seem like a real doctor
after what you did today.
Be honest.
Are you operating on my dad
as a part of your revenge
against Chairman Gu Jingi?
It doesn't matter
if this is my revenge or not.
We know Gu Hyunseong
can't operate on him anyway.
You're right. Nothing will change.
But who knows?
We can become much closer.
Should we become
even closer than this?
Do you think I said that
because I wanted to date you?
We both can benefit from this.
I don't want the situation
to get the best of me anymore.
In order to prevent that,
I must first create the situation I want.
-Do you feel all right, Dad?
-Yes, I'm fine.
Let's keep our meeting
under the table for a while.
And the condition of my heart.
Of course.
Thank you
for referring me to a trustworthy friend.
You should thank Ms. Lim.
She plays a huge part
in my favor upon you.
All right. I'll stay in touch.
How close are you to Jayden?
You don't have to worry.
It's unlike my relationship
with Hyunseong.
Gu Hyunseong.
If he really had a ghost doctor,
then we must call off the engagement.
Then will you set me up with another guy
who'll be helpful for your career?
From now on, I'll choose everything
regarding work and men.
And it won't be to help you
but only for myself.
What do you think you're doing?
We said it was a top-secret
that he operated in Gu Hyunseong's place.
I'm sorry.
I needed to show what I had
in order to bring a big shot
like Lim Taemoon to our side.
Then you should've told us first.
Were we the only ones
bound by confidentiality?
I thought it'd be a surprise.
Weren't you and Dr. Han
trying to get closer to Lim Taemoon?
What are you doing?
Did you put a tail on us?
No, it wasn't you.
I put a tail on Mr. Lim.
Tens of trillions of won are at stake
in this project.
Of course, we put a tail
on key persons in concern
in order to keep the risks down.
I'm not sure why you two are after him,
but feel free to make use
of my wealth and influence.
We seek different things,
but our goal is the same,
to destroy Gu Jingi.
What do you get
once Lim Taemoon becomes the president?
Every business I begin
in this country will be smoothly conducted
thanks to the highest authority
who's very close to Honours Hand.
It sounds like you want to make
the president of a country as you wish.
Please do understand.
It's my job as a lobbyist
to assist a politician
and help him take the power
as someone in favor of our side.
If that's what you're after,
why did you choose Lim Taemoon?
Yoon Miseon has a higher approval rating.
It doesn't really show
if you jump on the bandwagon.
In order to become the kingmaker,
you must bet on the underdog.
On top of that, unlike Assemblywoman Yoon,
whose power is mostly domestic,
there are many things I can do
for an ambassador like him.
Then what if Lim Taemoon is
someone who should never be the president?
What do you mean by that?
Five years ago,
my brother was hospitalized
after his heart surgery in Banseokwon,
but Gu Jingi took his heart.
He took the heart?
What do you mean?
SURGICAL TIMER, CURRENT TIME,
ANESTHESIA TIMER
Hold the suture in place.
Yes, sir.
Cut. Time.
It has been 5 hours and 15 minutes.
Time to speed up.
I know that!
I would be done by now
if I had V-Rock here.
Let me finish.
Sir, please give me your order.
I'll be your hand.
-Change spots with me.
-Yes, sir.
Suture the aorta first.
Yes, sir.
This kid is a monster too.
There's a high possibility
that Lim Taemoon received the heart
that Chairman Gu Jingi stole
from a patient.
Do you have any evidence?
Through his exam today,
I confirmed that he received
a heart transplant surgery five years ago.
Once I operate on Lim Taemoon,
I'll be able to disclose the rest.
I know it's tough to believe.
But if you'll side with Lim Taemoon
and benefit from that,
you need to be notified of such a risk.
I don't care which one of the VIPs
got my brother's heart.
I'll make sure they pay
just as Gu Jingi will.
Don't worry.
I know I should accept
high risk for a high return,
but I don't plan on
turning a murder accomplice
into the president.
If everything you said proves to be true,
instead of siding with Lim Taemoon,
I'll side with you and fight to the end.
Thank you for telling me.
It feels like we've become closer.
I'll immediately share the information
I find out in the future.
Man, today's operation was just perfect.
So smooth.
You punk. I remember
how you never listened to me.
You should've done this sooner.
Life is great for you now, isn't it?
Keep your eyes on the patient.
His condition can worsen quickly
even after good surgery.
Yes, sir.
Keep it up, okay?
GIL SOYEON, PATIENT
Hello?
Dr. Choi Yosub?
I'd like to meet you.
Why did you want to see me?
Have you not received the thyroplasty yet?
I couldn't.
I wanted to get the surgery
as soon as the trial was over.
But I couldn't go into the operating room.
The memories of that day came back to me.
I want you to do it.
-Sorry?
-If you come
and operate on me
at Dr. Han Yihan's hospital,
I think I'll be able to bear through.
I don't think I can do that.
Why?
Thyroplasty must be
operated by an ENT specialist.
Yihan and I are both cardiac surgeons,
so we have no experience in this.
Then can you at least come into the OR?
I don't trust any other doctor.
You and Mr. Han are
the only doctors I can trust right now.
-I missed you.
-Me too.
You've been busy with a drama,
so we haven't met for two months.
Then let's stay together all day today.
You can't go anywhere. You're mine.
I'll begin the foot massage.
What do you want to eat?
I don't know.
There's a good pasta place around here.
What's wrong? Is something going on?
I'm sorry, sir.
We brought the wrong oil.
We'll get the right ones now.
Sure.
Are you insane?
How dare you take money
in exchange for our VIP's privacy?
I'm sorry. I must have gone crazy.
They just asked me to take any video
that'll prove their love scandal--
Do you call that an excuse?
Your resignation won't be the end of this.
Expect to hear from our legal team
that we filed a lawsuit against you.
-Excuse me, Chief Yoo.
-What?
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but thankfully, it was just an attempt.
Why don't we just let it go quietly?
This is a sensitive period.
We shouldn't draw any attention.
Turn in your resignation to HR right now.
What's the reason--
Make up something! Go do it right now!
Yes, ma'am.
Am I having bad luck?
I already had enough to deal with.
Cho Darom.
How long have you been with us?
Three months, ma'am.
Why do you think our members pay
many times the fee compared to other shops
just to come here?
Because we give good massages?
No, it's their trust.
They trust that what happens in here
never gets out.
I'll remember that.
Anyway, you've done
something very important today.
-Thanks.
-I'm just doing my job.
I just followed your guidance,
because you told us that
confidentiality is the key
here at Banseokwon.
Hey.
Do you want to do special work with me?
This is…
Assemblywoman Yoon Miseon.
She's the top VVIP of Banseokwon.
You'll be my assistant starting tomorrow.
Remember everything to a T.
And about our security…
I won't have to elaborate, right?
"Yang Sunae, her daughter,
is staying long-term in the VIP ward?"
Thank you for giving me this opportunity.
I'll do my best
with my heart and utmost effort.
I met the chief prosecutor today.
He got furious and demanded
I change Nam Hyukchul's prosecutor.
It took a lot of effort to stop him
from reappointing you.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry.
And that's all?
I'll take my hands off
Nam Hyukchul's trial.
And thank you for letting me stay here.
Forget it. I should protect my teammates.
Right, what about Assemblywoman Yoon?
Will you restart that case?
No, I shouldn't make an issue
during the election season.
There's no new suspicion either.
Good. I'm glad you made that decision.
Don't mind them and stay low for a while.
Yes, I'll do that.
SENIOR PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE
Prosecutor Geum, was he harsh on you?
I'd rather have him yell at me.
Then I'd feel much more at ease.
Sorry?
What's your plan after work today?
Do you have any plans?
No, I don't.
You must feel upset.
So? Should we grab a drink?
Let's grab a drink next time,
but please give me some time.
There are some people you should meet.
People we should meet?
Let me introduce them to you.
You already know Mr. Han Yihan.
Cho Darom, our investigator who was
a former entertainment reporter.
And he's Kang Daewoong, a former nurse
at Banseok University Medical Center.
I'm the nurse and the chief clerk.
Yes, right. The nurse and the chief clerk.
This is Mr. Park
of Medical Crime Department,
and next to him is
Mr. Jung Heekyung, an investigator.
Nice to meet you. My name is Park Bongsik.
Bbongsik?
His name is Bbongsik?
No, not Bbongsik.
It's Bongsik. Park Bongsik.
I see. I'm so sorry.
Prosecutor Geum, he comes off as rude
from the first time. May I leave now?
We're sorry. He's a half-wit
who doesn't know when to socialize.
I'll teach him a good lesson from now on.
It's fine. People make mistakes.
Mr. Park also makes slips of the tongue.
Hey, I didn't say I was fine.
Why do you get to say that it's fine?
-It's fine, right?
-You punk.
All right, we can socialize next time.
Why don't we talk about work first?
Let's go upstairs.
Assemblywoman Yoon Miseon.
The first, the youngest,
and the longest-running female newscaster
at a major TV station.
A five-term assemblywoman of Daehan Party.
The day we took Nam Junhwan
from Banseokwon,
she's the VVIP who made them turn off
the security cameras at Banseokwon.
Her chief aide, Kwon Yoonseok.
He's her right-hand man.
He's been working for her
for 15 years since her first term.
Five years ago when I investigated
an illegal political fund case,
he refused to comply with the subpoena
and tried to commit suicide.
And I got him to Banseok University
Medical Center in an ambulance.
I remember him.
The patient with a knife
lodged in the chest.
We did the surgery together.
That's right.
Back then, I didn't have time to think
about work because of my brother.
But he got discharged
five months after the surgery.
And the investigation fizzled out too.
Five months.
He didn't have to stay that long.
I remember his post-ops being fairly good.
Well, he was probably stalling,
so the investigation would end.
A lot of people use that method.
YOON MISEON WILL PULL IT OFF
At the National Assembly session
the year after that,
a bill to register Banseokwon
as a non-medical institution
via a back-door listing was passed.
Assemblywoman Yoon led it.
Gosh. I can smell something rotting
from a mile away.
But why is she always
visiting Banseokwon at late night?
Getting a massage isn't a crime.
Maybe, she did more than
getting a massage.
Did she get some special procedure done?
I think I can answer that.
Seokyeong, it's my turn now.
Gosh. How pretty.
What? She looks familiar.
Is she a celebrity?
Yang Sunae. She was born in 1996
and is the only daughter
of Assemblywoman Yoon.
Wasn't she famous for being pretty?
You all know
Assemblywoman Yoon is divorced, right?
She changed prejudices about divorce
and rebranded herself as a career woman
with her daughter's help.
She raised her daughter
to be an intelligent, beautiful,
and well-behaved girl
without any help from her husband.
It definitely gave her a good reputation.
She used her family to promote herself
by giving out press releases herself.
I see. That's why.
But what does that have to do
with her sneaking into Banseokwon?
But her precious daughter
received emergency surgery
and has been staying
at Banseokwon for three months.
When you look at her registered guardian,
it's Doh Jinwoo.
Not the assemblywoman.
Doh Jinwoo? Who's that?
Beats me.
Anyway, seeing how he registered
as her guardian when she was admitted,
he must be close to her.
But there's
Banseok University Medical Center.
And there's a regional ER too.
Why did she get the emergency surgery
at Banseokwon?
It's just like Seokju's case
from five years ago.
Emergency surgery for a VIP at Banseokwon.
It had to be kept a secret.
Who could that be at this hour?
Doh Jinwoo.
YANG SUNAE, PATIENT
DOH JINWOO, GUARDIAN
NEW-HOPE LAW OFFICE
NEW-HOPE MEDICINE CLINIC
Yihan. It's Dr. Choi.
Seriously. How dare he show his face here
after betraying us like that?
-I'll go see him.
-Okay.
Yihan. I have a favor to ask you.
Soyeon is
having a hard time
because of the trauma from the surgery.
The thought of going into an OR
makes her hyperventilate
and gives her nightmares.
She can't trust other doctors
and is scared.
So she wants to have it done
at your clinic.
She said she would be able to trust us
and handle the surgery if we performed it.
I understand that, but the thyroplasty
should be done
by an experienced ENT specialist.
Right. But…
just being in the OR with her
will help her.
What she needs right now
is a doctor she can trust like us.
"Us"? You have no shame.
You betrayed us big time to save yourself.
Now, you want to do this
to stop feeling guilty?
Yihan, don't do it.
Do you think we're some pushovers?
Daewoong.
-Let's do it together.
-Yihan!
Soyeon dealt with her trauma
from medical malpractice,
trusted us, and stayed with us.
So we should help her to the end.
I mean, that's…
That's true.
Thank you, Yihan. And…
I'm sorry.
Daewoong, I'm sorry.
You got hurt because of me.
Well, it's not about the injury.
Hyunseong 's mother,
Jang Jungok… The Head of the US office
will return to Korea soon.
If Chairman Gu Jingi becomes
the Minister of Health and Welfare,
he will need someone
to take over his position.
And if Gu Hyunseong becomes
the director of the hospital too,
Banseok will be
one of those typical family businesses.
And they probably think of you,
the R and D Center's director,
as their family already.
Family.
My father had always been the shackles
I wanted to break free from.
So I studied medical engineering.
But I'm still in his shadow.
If you marry Gu Hyunseong,
what will your father get in return?
What do you mean?
An arranged marriage
is high-level politics.
It will never go through unless
both parties gain something in return.
Gu Jingi will gain a lot
from having your father as his in-law.
But what about your father?
What will he gain from this marriage?
To him, not losing something
is more important than gaining something.
If you're thinking about investing in
the presidential candidate as a lobbyist,
you ought to be more careful.
My father comes with a lot of strengths
as well as weaknesses.
How was your flight?
Good. Let's go to the hospital right away.
Yes, ma'am.
BANSEOK FOUNDATION
2022 EXTRAORDINARY BOARD MEETING ITEMS
CHAIRMAN GU JINGI'S DISMISSAL OF
THE TITLES DUE TO NOMINATION OF MINISTER
Has it been five years
since you came back?
Yes. It's already been five years.
You're such a workaholic.
You must be enjoying your youth.
But you're not even dating.
You never leave the hospital.
If I didn't ask you,
you wouldn't have come back, right?
You're a newly appointed director
at Banseok Foundation, after all.
And this is an important moment too.
This is more than I deserve.
Once you become the chairwoman,
I plan to go back right away.
Who can stop you?
I can leave the office in your hands
because I know you will do a fine job.
So you know, right?
When I'm in Korea as the chairwoman,
you're the acting head
of the US office. Okay?
Next, I will move on
to the highlight of today's auction.
Nineteen whisky masters
made this over 72 hours.
Only three bottles were produced
in the entire world.
It's 65-year-old single malt whisky.
It was aged in a carefully selected
sherry oak cask.
This is considered
the best product of Macury.
A bottle of this was sold
for 1.45 billion won
at an auction in Hong Kong last week
and became the highest-priced
single bottle of whisky
throughout auctions in Asia.
We'll begin the bidding
at one billion won.
And we'll raise it by 50 million won.
Let us begin.
One billion won.
Thank you. Anyone for 1.05 billion won?
That's 1.05 billion won. Thank you.
1.1 billion won.
We have a bidder. 1.15 billion won?
Yes, we have another bidder.
How about 1.2 billion won?
We're at 1.2 billion won.
Anyone for 1.25 billion won?
Okay. 1.25 billion won.
How about 1.3 billion won?
Yes. We're at 1.3 billion won now.
How about 1.35 billion won?
Okay. The highest bid now
is 1.35 billion won.
Anyone for 1.4 billion won?
I call 1.5 billion won.
All right. We're at 1.5 billion won.
We have the highest bid in Asia,
1.5 billion won.
Does anyone want to take it
for 1.55 billion won?
If there's no one, I will wrap up.
Yes. The gentleman in the back
bid 1.55 billion won.
That's amazing. 1.55 billion won.
The highest bid is 1.55 billion won.
All right. We will have to raise it
to 1.6 billion won now.
Will you bid 1.6 billion won?
-Yes, he bid 1.6 billion won.
-What?
Yes. 1.65 billion won.
He bid 1.65 billion won right away.
You must bid 1.7 billion won
to take this bottle.
He's thinking now. 1.7 billion won…
-I call 1.7 billion won.
-Okay. He bid 1.7 billion won.
I see. The gentleman in the back
bid 1.75 billion won.
The highest bid now is 1.75 billion won.
You must bid 1.8 billion won
to take this bottle.
What about 1.8 billion? Anyone?
Go for it.
He bid 1.8 billion won, everyone.
Would you like to make
the highest bid, 1.85 billion won?
Will you bid?
Let's end this.
Two billion won.
He just bid two billion won!
We just received an incredible bid,
two billion won!
How about 2.05 billion won?
Will you bid 2.05 billion won?
All right. Unless there's another bidder,
I'll wrap it up at two billion won.
Two billion won.
Sold!
The 65-year-old single malt whisky
from Macury
was sold to Number 29 at two billion won.
Congratulations.
Darn it.
Who the heck was that? He spent
two billion won on a bottle of whisky.
I was going to show off
in front of the foundation directors.
Exactly.
I bet everyone is looking forward to this.
Even if they got their entire savings,
it wouldn't be enough to buy that.
Hey.
It was a nice bidding war.
I had fun thanks to you.
Bidding war?
He was basically showing off his money.
Are you here to gloat?
Please take it. This is yours.
What is this? Are you making fun of us?
It's a present…
for the new chairman
of Banseok Foundation.
Well…
YOON MISEON WILL PULL IT OFF
CERTIFICATE OF APPRECIATION
YOON MISEON
ASSEMBLYWOMAN YOON MISEON
It will sting a bit.
I increased the ratio
for umbilical cord blood,
so your skin will glow
during the presidential debate.
This is the stem cell cream.
Your touches are always pleasant,
Chief Yoo.
Is that her? Your new assistant?
Yes. Say hello to her.
It's an honor to meet you.
My name is Cho Darom.
I'll be assisting Chief Yoo from now on.
I still have a lot to learn,
but I will do my best.
You're polite, unlike girls at your age.
How old are you?
I'm 30 years old.
Thirty.
You're about the same age as my daughter.
Come on in.
There's something I must report.
Go ahead. It's fine.
Yes, ma'am. The order
you gave out for your daughter.
It will be executed today.
Okay. Tell them not to make any mistakes.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll let you handle the rest.
Just let me get some quality sleep
for three hours.
I've been having a hard time
falling asleep these days.
Yes, ma'am.
GLUCOSE
-Are you sure this is the place?
-Yes.
The address on Yang Sunae's hospital file
says it's Unit 607 of this building.
Doesn't it look a bit shabby
for an assemblywoman's daughter?
Look around the neighborhood.
I'll go upstairs.
Okay.
Darn it.
Mr. Doh Jinwoo?
Who are you? Move out of my way.
Move.
Daewoong,
come to the entrance of the apartment.
Gosh, that darn weasel.
You're dead meat. Come here.
Come here, you punk!
Hey, why don't we just walk down
if you don't mind?
Or should I make you crawl on all fours?
Come here.
Come here, you punk.
Hey!
Hold on.
Come on.
Yihan!
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Mr. Doh Jinwoo.
You know Ms. Yang Sunae, right?
Let's talk for a moment.
I'm not with them. I'm an attorney.
I want to ask you about Ms. Yang Sunae.
Don't give me that nonsense.
Sunae and I
won't let people like you
take advantage of us anymore.
-You…
-Doctor.
It's been a while.
No. Should I call you a lawyer now?
Easy.
Let's not cross the line.
If we start crossing the line,
people will get hurt. You see?
Just like before.
I'm not sure about that.
I think the table has turned today.
What's this?
Gosh.
Yihan, he's the bad guy. Right?
I didn't mess up, right?
No.
So you lost him?
I'm sorry.
ASSEMBLYWOMAN YOON MISEON
Yoonseok.
You were nothing but a mere driver.
Do you know why I made you the chief aide?
Because you were loyal.
There are a lot of smart
and competent people.
But you're the only one
who would die for me.
That's why I'm giving you one more chance.
Do whatever it takes
to make sure he never sees
Sunae ever again.
-Got it?
-Yes, ma'am.
Okay. You can go.
ASSEMBLYWOMAN YOON MISEON
There's something I must discuss.
I'll go to Banseokwon tonight.
Okay.
Honey.
The meal is ready.
Shall I tell them to wait?
No. I am coming.
I am sorry for making you wait
when you haven't come back in a while.
It's okay.
Let's eat.
We can take our time with conversations.
Okay. Let's eat.
Okay.
NEW-HOPE LAW OFFICE
NEW-HOPE MEDICINE CLINIC
Boyfriend?
You and the goddess…
I mean, you and Sunae are dating?
-How?
-Is there something wrong with it?
There isn't anything wrong with it,
but the two of you are very different.
I apologize.
This punk has no sensitivity whatsoever.
Apologize to him right now.
Okay.
I understand.
Sunae is way out of my league.
Well… I am sorry.
You practically flew
between buildings earlier.
You looked so cool.
What is it called? Parkour?
-Freerunning.
-I see.
It's something similar.
In any case, would you explain
what happened earlier?
Why did they try to kidnap you?
Assemblywoman Yoon Miseon sent them
to keep me quiet.
Sunae you know isn't real.
Assemblywoman Yoon made that image,
but Sunae
hated it.
Tell me.
What happened between
Assemblywoman Yoon and her daughter?
In fifth grade,
she had her first surgery.
She is beautiful
because she takes after you,
but her protruding ears ruin her looks.
-Is it possible to fix them?
-Yes, it is.
Ears stop growing
in the early teenage years.
But since ears have a lot of nerves,
the surgery will be painful.
She could suffer a lot
if she gets the surgery at a young age.
It's okay. Please fix them.
Mom.
To be a better person,
you need to erase one fault at a time.
I will help you
so that you can be more perfect.
Okay?
Your nutrition and exercises
have been taken care of perfectly.
Why aren't you growing any taller?
Your legs are short and ugly too.
Who do you take after?
After she became an adult, she was forced
to get limb-lengthening surgery.
But Assemblywoman Yoon
is well-known to love her daughter.
It's a lie.
It isn't love, but abuse.
Sunae never wanted that life.
It was Yoon Miseon,
that woman's greed.
It was too painful to see Sunae suffer,
so I went to Assemblywoman Yoon
and asked her to set Sunae free.
I said I would tell the media outlets
about her abuse otherwise.
You punk.
-She became extremely angry,
-Let go of me!
but she accepted my terms.
That was when the two of you…
Yes.
We lived together.
Our place was old and cramped.
There were many inconveniences,
but we were happy
to be together.
But…
Sunae! What's wrong?
Sunae.
Sunae, it's okay.
She needed surgery for the aftereffect
of limb-lengthening surgery,
so I had no choice
but to contact Assemblywoman Yoon.
She got admitted to Banseokwon
and received surgery.
As far as we know,
Sunae hasn't left Banseokwon
for over three months.
I don't know what Sunae's condition is.
After she entered Banseokwon,
Assemblywoman Yoon kept me away.
I am worried sick.
I want to know if the surgery went well.
I want to know if she is alive.
I plan to resign
before the board of directors
brings it up.
It's a position I have to give up anyway.
It shouldn't look like I am being ousted.
I agree.
There is no reason
to let them set the pace.
Both positions should be vacant
until the hearing.
Once you become the minister,
the directors will yield naturally.
No.
I will appoint the hospital director
before I resign.
My son.
You can do well, right?
Father.
Honey.
I believe Hyunseong will do well,
but wouldn't it look bad if you appoint
him before your resignation?
If I say it's the last appointment
before my resignation,
it will be justified.
He will soon be the head of a family.
We need to help him.
Okay. Do what you want.
You dote on your son more than I do.
-You must do well.
-Okay.
The aromas are nice.
This liquor is on another level.
Director Jang Jungtae,
let me pour you a glass.
Okay. Thank you.
Goodness.
I don't know
if I can receive this precious gift.
Please don't be pressured.
Even if it weren't for you,
it would have ended up in your hands.
It must have taken a lot of effort
to get this liquor.
I don't know
if we should be drinking by ourselves.
Three bottles have been made.
Since one bottle is here,
someone must have
the other two.
Could it be
the same liquor?
Did you win it
at the Hong Kong auction as well?
I was lucky.
I acquired two bottles of nice liquor
before a meeting with important people.
Please share this
with the directors of Banseok Foundation.
Please tell them that it's my small gift.
A small gift?
I don't know how rich you are,
but excessive modesty
comes off as arrogance.
I apologize if you felt that way.
I simply meant that this is nothing
compared to the wealth
the directors and I will enjoy together
in the future.
Together? What do you mean?
Let's talk more as we drink.
The night is still young.
Let me see you, my son.
-You can do well, right?
-Of course.
Okay.
My wife doesn't know what happened, right?
-No, sir.
-I am always grateful for you.
I was five years ago and I am now.
May I ask you a question?
That day,
Geum Seokju's heart
was damaged beyond saving.
But it wasn't due to emergency phlebotomy.
Okay.
It was the heart
of a dilated cardiomyopathy patient,
but there was
no cardiac tamponade.
"A clear cause of death
minimizes the damage to the hospital,
so change the results of the autopsy
to a cardiac tamponade
due to the pulmonary artery rupture.
Medical malpractice isn't punished,
so Dr. Han won't be harmed."
I trusted your words
and changed the autopsy results.
Was that the only reason?
Was there another reason--
Did you truly believe my words
-when you fabricated the results?
-Pardon?
You could have refused,
but you followed without a complaint.
Now that it seems to be a bigger issue,
you say that you trusted my words.
What is it?
Are you scared now that Han Yihan is back
and Park Kitae is dead?
Did you realize that your action was
more immoral than you initially thought?
You aren't feeling guilty. You are simply
afraid.
You don't want
your wrongdoing to be revealed.
No, it's not like…
If…
you are certain
that you won't be punished,
your flimsy sense of guilt…
will disappear without a trace
like snow in spring.
No, I…
I promise you
that you will never be punished.
So you don't need to be afraid.
Understood?
Are you done already?
You haven't gone on a date in a while.
Forget about a date. I am tired.
The flight was long.
What are you going to do?
Do you want to stay the night?
She is leaving.
Yes.
I will get going now.
-Get some rest.
-Yes, sir.
Why is she so busy? Is she tired?
I should retreat to my room
and get some rest. How about you?
Assemblywoman Yoon is at Banseokwon,
so I have to drop by.
Does she think she is your superior?
She visits all the time.
-Get some rest.
-Okay.
My goodness.
Foolish girl.
I raised you like a princess.
You had every reason to be happy.
Why did you break my heart?
Don't worry now, my daughter.
I won't let you go.
I will have your mean heart fixed too
as I did with your body.
Doh Jinwoo.
He is the punk
who fooled and destroyed my daughter.
Mr. Han Yihan hid him.
Hid him? How…
That's what I want to ask you.
How did he find out?
From the day she received surgery,
my daughter hasn't left Banseokwon.
I apologize for inconveniencing you.
I don't need your apology.
How will you take responsibility?
From the start,
he threatened me
with the nonsense of abuse.
So I wanted to shut his mouth.
But that lawyer will ruin everything.
Why don't we postpone the time
she wakes up?
Postpone the time? What do you mean?
As you know, she is in the final stage
of idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis.
Even if she wakes up,
she won't be able to do normal activities.
Had Sunae stayed by my side,
her disease
wouldn't have progressed so much.
It's a shame.
She worsened her condition
by leaving her disease untreated.
If she gains consciousness
and insists on leaving the hospital
in order to stay by his side,
her life will be in danger.
What should I do then?
Let's inject her with a concoction
that won't hurt her body
in order to keep her
in suspended animation
and look for lungs
that can be transplanted.
It will also give you time
to retrieve Doh Jinwoo from Han Yihan.
So we will use drugs
to keep Sunae asleep.
For now, that's the most certain way
to protect your daughter.
You shouldn't endanger the life
of your precious daughter
because of that classless man.
I have a son too.
You can't always see
eye to eye with your child.
So what can you do
other than help your child find
the right path?
That's a parent's responsibility.
We'll keep in contact more often
from now on.
Okay. I am in your care.
-Let's get going.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Are you okay?
-What kind of a lunatic…
Please stay in the car. I will check.
We meet again, Chairman Gu Jingi.
What brings you here at this hour?
The guardian of your patient
sued the hospital for negligence and
a violation of the Medical Service Act.
Pardon? What do you mean?
It's nice to meet you.
I am Prosecutor Geum Seokyeong
of Medical Crime Department in Seoul
Central District Prosecutors' Office.
Banseok has been sued
for a Medical Service Act violation
regarding your daughter, Yang Sunae.
May I ask a few questions?
I apologize, Assemblywoman Yoon.
There must be a misunderstanding.
Ms. Yang Sunae is recovering
without a problem at the hospital.
That's correct.
As her guardian, I entrusted the hospital
with her treatment.
So stop interfering and go back.
I won't put up with more rudeness.
No. I can't do that.
You are no longer Yang Sunae's guardian.
What nonsense…
I am her family,
not you.
What? What nonsense are you spouting?
Check for yourself.
MARRIAGE CERTIFICATE
DOH JINWOO, YANG SUNAE
Marriage certificate?
You are the director of a hospital,
so you would know
whether a parent or a spouse
has a say in decision-making
for an unconscious patient.
What nonsense is this?
Marriage? My daughter?
Sunae couldn't have gotten married
without my permission.
You have
no right to be Sunae's family.
Right?
I am her mom. What right do I need?
Sunae is mine. You are the one
who ruined my daughter's life.
If it weren't for you…
He didn't ruin her life.
-Excuse me?
-Sunae's life isn't ruined.
She will get back up again
and live her own life from now on.
I doubted it,
but you really intended
to have both in your hands.
You must be very concerned
about making your daughter fall
into a critical condition.
I am Doh Jinwoo's attorney, Han Yihan.
We will move Ms. Yang Sunae
to New-Hope Medicine Clinic.
Even if it's a guardian's request,
transferring a critical patient
at such late hours is against our policy.
We must think about the patient's safety.
If you care so much about patients,
why did you move Nam Junhwan here
right after surgery?
You even used violence.
Lead us to Yang Sunae
right now.
What do you want me to do?
Wait. It could cause the patient to die.
Are you aware of this?
Chairman Gu, what is he talking about?
Lung transplant is the only way.
The person
who can donate lungs the fastest
is her family.
Please donate lungs to Sunae with me.
Michael and I will attend
the board meeting as investors.
We must stop Gu Hyunseong
from becoming the director.
I will assist you properly tomorrow.
Let's decide by vote.
Before we do that,
I would like to say a few words.
Did you wait for me?
I thought you would need a lawyer.
There is one thing I didn't tell you.
Translated by Won-hyang Son