YoYo English Channel YouTube
Subbers Alina, Sophia, Sophia
The Legend of Princess Miaoshan
Episode 16
Mrs.Chen, you are so elegant.
Where is your Mr.Chen?
He let you come here?
Let me introduce to you.
This is Mrs.Chen of Mr.Mirui.
Isn't Mr.Chen's girlfriend the actress Su Peipei?
I haven't seen her before.
What's wrong with the actress? You don't know men.
What is a man?
The wedding banquet is their specialty.
As long as it's a man, he will definitely cheat.
No way.
Miaomiao, if you don't want Mr.Chen,
remember to tell me that I want you.
I can give you what he can give you.
Who are you?
I'll go take a look.
What is wrong with him?
What is this? Don't be mad at him.
This place is not gonna happen again.
I bought the car.
I walked away with a foot on the door.
It was so cool.
He left me alone in the parking lot.
Did he get his conscience eaten by a dog?
Mr. Chen, calm down.
Calm down.
You broke the house.
Are you kidding me?
How could I break the house?
Let me calculate the bill for you.
Your mother slapped you.
Secretary Lin slapped you.
Su Peipei slapped Secretary Lin.
Secretary Lin slapped Su Peipei.
Su Peipei slapped Su Peipei.
Stop calculating.
What are you doing?
Look.
Secretary Lin slapped Su Peipei.
He must have given the most love.
What nonsense are you talking about?
It's raining.
Let's go this way.
Chen Zixing.
Why are you still here?
What's going on?
What are you doing?
This...
What's going on?
I told you.
You'll meet ghosts if you walk on the street.
You have to be careful.
But, sister.
He just finished drinking.
He's so dizzy.
Will he die?
Let's go and have a look.
Are you okay?
Are you dead?
Lin Miaomiao.
What are you doing?
Did you slap me?
What are you talking about?
Are you crazy?
I saw someone
taking this suit and slapping you.
I just came to see if you're okay.
You slapped me.
It's not me.
Don't move.
What are you doing?
I'm not.
Don't be angry.
I'll take care of you.
Hello?
Ceng Siyu.
Miss Lin.
Your wife is in my hands now.
What wife?
I'll give you ten minutes.
Come here, auntie.
Or I'll propose to her.
You decide.
Mr. Ceng.
What's going on?
Let's go.
Chang Jingxin was beaten by someone.
Miao thought she was dead
and went to watch the fun.
But Chang Jingxin caught her
and said that Miao was the one who beat her.
She's dead.
What fun is there?
She's back.
Who did Mr. Chang offend?
He hit his own foot with a rock.
He was too coincidental today.
I have to suspect that he was the one who beat me.
I didn't beat you.
So why did you call me here?
Mr. Ceng.
We've known each other for so many years.
You know me.
I'm not unreasonable.
Admit that she's your wife.
I'll let you off the hook.
What do you think?
I was the one who beat you.
You said it?
Yes.
Okay.
Yu Yang, call the police.
He beat her and caught her.
Mr. Chang.
Miao didn't dare to beat you.
She said that to piss me off.
If she goes in,
my mom will kill me.
Admit that she's your wife?
I'm here.
Say something.
Right?
Yes.
I admit that she's my wife.
Good.
Very good.
Who is this?
Stop talking.
I can't answer.
You admit that she's your wife.
What about Miss Su?
Her father?
Fan?
Fan.
It's hard to tell.
It's not easy to...
It's not hard.
It's simple.
This is Yu Yang.
This is Yu Yang's girlfriend.
Simple, right?
Look.
We all make sense.
It's late.
The news is everywhere.
Just tell us.
Miss Su.
What is yours?
Ex-girlfriend.
Ex-girlfriend?
Girlfriend is girlfriend.
Fiancé is fiancé.
Third is third.
What is ex-girlfriend?
Mrs. Zeng.
You're so rude.
She's looking for Third behind you.
Sun Siyuan.
You bastard.
Sorry.
Since you're Miss Zeng's wife.
I trust you.
I didn't hit you.
Let's go.
I'm shocked.
I need to rest.
Can you think before you act?
I didn't hit you.
What's wrong with me?
I know what you're like.
You're still pretending.
Why are you yelling in the hallway?
Besides,
I asked you to come here today.
I'm sorry for everything.
I'm sorry.
I'm not involved in your business.
I am.
Okay.
Now I'm the
bitch who steals other's boyfriend.
Are you satisfied?
How could there be
a heartless bastard like you in this world?
Bastard.
Yes.
I'm a bastard.
Okay, stop it.
Go find someone.
I've already said goodbye to her.
Just go.
Bastard.
Why did you kill him?
Because...
YoYo English Channel YouTube