The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 18
Taoism Grandmaster
The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 18
Taoism Grandmaster
The time of death should be between 9 and 11 this morning.
The broken neck should be the cause of death.
It looks like it was cut off by a human.
And there are some footprints left on the ground next to it.
These steps are not even.
The first few steps are similar.
But there is a slight increase here.
It should be a slight pause and then a correction.
One could be the murderer's injury.
Another could be the health of the body.
Judging from this footstep,
the murderer's height should be around 1.75 meters.
The weight is about 70 kg.
And the pattern on the foot is worn out.
The murderer should be between 35 and 40 years old.
Zhao Zhi, if Guonong says that the car belongs to him,
I think it was a car accident when Yang Dong escaped from the car.
But we haven't found any other witnesses yet.
Does anyone in the village know him?
No. They all said they haven't seen him.
He should have appeared here by accident.
Accident?
Zhao Zhi.
Let me have a look.
There is a print here.
Do you think Yang Dong's death spot is special?
Let's change the angle.
What is special about Yang Dong?
Why did he choose to park his car there?
Judging from the traces of the rubbed floor,
the speed has reached its limit.
Why did he run away when no one knew him?
And the mud on the floor comes from the river.
Why did he go to the river with the murderer?
Wu Shouwei said that Liu Kui was looking for Yang Dong's hideout.
Could it be around here?
Liu Kui?
Did Yang Dong's phone data recover?
Lin Chen said it would take about an hour.
I'll go urge him.
I have to go to Liu Kui's transportation company.
Now?
Yes.
We don't know them well.
We don't know the relationship between Liu Kui and Yang Dong.
We don't know what Liu Kui is trying to steal.
We can't solve the case.
Zhao Zhi, I'll go with you.
Go where?
Stay at home.
Don't call me Zhao Zhi.
I'm still your master.
Liu Kui's Hideout
Master, I'm here.
You...
Who are you?
I'm a landlady.
I'm here to find my relatives.
I've been asking for a long time and I don't know.
I just want to ask.
I'm here to find my relatives.
Come in.
Sure.
Thank you.
You don't know?
I've asked for a long time.
We're all locals.
How come you don't know anything?
You're here to find people?
You've found the right person.
I've been here for a lifetime.
How can you not recognize me?
You've found the right person.
That's great.
Hurry up.
This is my relative.
Look.
Do you recognize me?
This...
What?
Isn't this our boss,
Kui?
Liu Kui.
Kui is your boss?
You're so smart.
Kui is your boss.
You're a family.
Look at me.
Come.
Nothing good.
A little wine.
Come.
A family.
I'm happy.
Come.
Master.
Where can I find Kui?
Where can you find him?
I want to find him.
I haven't paid for a long time.
He's gone.
He ran away.
This...
What was this place used for?
Did you see it?
These stones in the yard.
Do you know what they're for?
What for?
For the field and the sea.
That's a big business.
Big business.
It's amazing.
Amazing.
Have you seen anyone
around Kui?
Do you remember anyone?
I remember when the business was good,
I brought a little girl back.
Little girl?
Yes.
She just got out of the hospital at the age of 20.
She's beautiful.
Thank you.
Girlfriend.
How can such a young girl
be Kui's girlfriend?
Kui, Kui.
Amazing.
It's very intimate.
The boss has money.
Yes.
Kui's girlfriend.
I'm the police.
I'm investigating the various luxury night clubs
such as the Beauty Palace.
The crime scene is that
there are 47 girls in the black room
and the night club is occupied by the bad place.
Who is it?
I'm the police.
I'm investigating the high-pressure situation
and I'm determined to eradicate social exclusion.
Brother Wuchong, why are you here?
Rui Rui.
I just passed by your house.
So I bought this flower.
I forgot.
The boss said
you can't take it.
Well,
I saw her for a few days
and she didn't come to school.
Is she sick?
She's not at home.
If you see her,
remember to tell her
that I'm looking for her.
Don't worry. I'll tell her.
And...
Rui Rui.
Who is it?
Who else?
Your favorite senior,
Brother Wuchong.
You're not going to school?
No.
Okay.
I'll sign for you.
I love you.
Brother Wuchong left?
What?
Are you jealous?
Yes.
Hani ran away from someone.
Did I say something wrong?
Don't move.
When did you learn to explode?
You've been gone for almost two years.
You know
a lot about me.
You regret taking me in?
Listen.
Don't pretend to be pitiful.
I'm back.
Are you leaving?
Liu Kui is a social brother.
He must have a lot of girlfriends.
Didn't you check it before?
Liu Kui has no relatives or friends in Tai Ning.
I don't know where this girlfriend is.
We can only track her down to the Qingmen District.
Then the number will be turned off.
Are you sure this number is Liu Kui?
Hello?
Do you remember Dai Qian's husband
has a foreign trade company?
Zhao Zhi, the owner's name is Dai Qian.
He's married.
Her husband is the boss of a foreign trade company.
His name is Chen Zhengwei.
It seems to be called Yang.
Foreign trade company.
It looks familiar.
But I really don't know his name.
His name is Liu Kui.
Four years ago,
we held a logistics meeting.
All of you bosses have participated.
He's here too.
A logistics meeting.
Here, it's hot.
Thank you.
Four years ago...
I remember now.
He seems to be doing
some mining business.
There's also a business outside the city.
Yes, he's doing mining.
What did you talk about that day?
And who are there with you?
Mr. Qian,
we businessmen
are doing this kind of activity
to make money and make a name for ourselves.
There's nothing else.
It's okay, don't worry.
Let's think about it.
Anything is fine.
Anything can be said.
Anything is fine?
Anything.
Is it convenient?
Convenient.
You know.
It's convenient.
Next, let's welcome
the chairman of the Yiyang Commercial Trade
Mr. Chen Zhengwei to come up to the stage.
Everyone,
I'm very happy to have everyone
come to our...
What are you doing here?
Don't look at me.
Picking vegetables.
Where's the stuff?
I'll go get it now.
Do you know where it is?
Which school?
You're an adult now?
I'll go get the tools first.
Wait a minute.
Do you know the rules?
You're too confused.
Don't touch me.
This...
Who are you?
The future of a common good.
Good.
It hurts.
Let's go.
It's okay.
Do you remember
what the girl's name was?
The girl...
I don't know.
How about this?
Go ask the supervisor.
It's more intuitive.
Okay?
My clothes are all wet.
Slow down.
Are you cold?
No.
Lanlan,
you've really gotten back together with Liu Kun.
I'm hungry.
But you were so sad
when you broke up.
Now you're forgiving him so quickly.
This is the first time
I've ever seen you like this.
Although it's not the first time,
I believe
that Liu Kun is a good man.
Send me home.
I'm not a little boy.
I don't have time to spend time with you.
I know.
You might not be able to see me often.
Is this what you want?
Yes.
But why did he suddenly come back to you?
And the wounds on his body.
Did you ask him
what happened?
Shui Rui,
I know you're worried about me.
Yes.
He's much older than me.
And we have a lot of secrets.
But I really don't care about these.
I just want to be with him.
Why?
I don't know either.
But
when you really fall in love with someone,
I will understand.
It's love.
I'm sorry.