Episode 1
Qiqi.
What is this?
Sugar.
Wrong.
What your father gave you is sugar.
What others gave you is poison.
All the things you like are possible to be dangerous to you.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Good boy.
Is this dangerous?
Yes.
What is dangerous?
This is what my father used to blow your hair.
Only I can blow it, others can't.
Okay.
Thank you.
Let's go home.
Do you still remember?
Yes.
The Child of the Year
Episode 1
This child is yours.
Did you see it?
In 2005,
the children I brought
were all sent to Hongwu.
Hongwu
There is a man named Shan Chong.
Mr. Han.
What are you talking about?
He likes to have a girl.
The mountain of mountains.
It's a long way.
If I were you,
I wouldn't look for it.
If I didn't look for it,
I would have lost it.
Look.
The Child of the Year
All the children and women
were found by you.
No more talk.
Except for the crime of selling the population,
and the fact that you took part in the crime,
I'll tell you right away.
Liu Keying's car was sent by the woman.
I asked her to blow it.
The child was sent to Hongwu.
It's so scary.
What are you doing?
Look, what are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
Then,
my mother said she was the one who did it.
I told you something.
How did you know it was a bomb?
I...
My brother...
was the one who blew it.
He blew it.
What?
Then,
they were completely separated.
Liu Keying
was the one who told me to let him go to the prison.
He also had a grudge.
I
had a problem.
Don't move!
Put your weapon down!
Liu Keying.
Calm down!
Luo Haixiao and Zhang Guiping
are all the cars you used to drive.
Right?
That's right.
Mom!
This is your work desk.
Be careful.
Okay, okay.
Let's go.
Don't be afraid.
Go, go, go.
Okay.
Zhang Guiping!
I'm here!
You wanted them to kill each other.
You took away all the gold.
Right?
They all have to die.
Do you understand?
What kind of a person
loves you and your family?
Do you understand?
You've been with Zhang Guiping since you were a kid.
He's the most emotional for you.
You're like them.
Do you hate him?
What do you hate?
Do you hate me?
What are you laughing at?
You're a double-edged sword.
You don't know Zhang Guiping's taste.
I'm a genius.
A genius.
Is this the child you raised?
Are you satisfied?
I'm telling you, Zhang Guiping!
I won't give up.
All my parents won't give up!
Bye-bye.
You're here.
I'm here.
I'm here to see you.
Why?
Bye-bye.
That's the one you just told me.
I'm here.
Stop!
Be careful.
Zhao Zhi is in the car.
Go and call him.
Zhao Zhi.
Thank you.
I'm going.
Let's go.
Lin Shen, don't forget your water.
Yes, yes.
Put it here.
Let's go to the meeting room.
Yes.
I'll go.
Don't let the girl move.
You can go.
Wait for me upstairs.
Okay.
Wait for me.
Let's go, Qi Yu.
The red mushroom is falling off.
He's guilty.
I know.
I have to go.
You go alone?
Yes.
The special forces have disbanded.
You have a new mission.
I'll do it myself.
Okay.
No need to mention it.
I promise to follow the instructions.
I'll go.
Okay.
No need to mention it.
I promise to follow the instructions.
How are you?
Have you made your wish come true?
Do you feel like a hero?
Okay, Zhao Zhi.
You're still laughing at me?
Xin He.
I don't know
how to call it a hero.
But I know that
all we can do is continue.
Don't listen.
We are the last line.
Okay.
I promise.
Do your best
and keep your promise.
Take care.
Xiaogua looks like you.
She does not.
It's funny.
I do not think so.
The other smile.
We can take more.
More?
Old brother,
how are you feeling now?
I feel cool.
Then smile more.
Master, these years...
I've never blamed you.
Never.
I will find Qiqi.
Trust me.
People say you are going to leave the village
and leave the village.
We will miss your smile.
Your eyes are brighter than the sun and the moon.
So, in our hearts,
come and sit beside me.
Don't leave this place.
Thank you.
The night flowers are like a steam.
Let people panic.
In the wind, loneliness opens.
When the fog is gone, it's time to leave.
I change my clothes.
I stop here.
I'm satisfied.
I'm still a different kind of person.
I walk in theæ¯ of the cheek to continue the endless journey.
Never give me parting to be free or separated from you.
No, that counts