Timing and Subtitles by the 🎶 Sing for a dream 🎤 Team @ viki
Have you figured out what's missing?
Find it.
Find it right now!
Ki Joon!
Is it that student?
I'll talk to him.
Ki Joon...
Did you by any chance...
come to school last night?
I was with him.
I was in the club room with him yesterday.
I was at school, too.
M-Me too.
If what they say is true, we need to investigate these students.
They're trying to protect their friend.
Stay put, all of you.
The officer needs to check something just with Ki Joon.
I said I was with him, Ms. Song.
Jung Young Joo.
Let's go.
Oh, no. What has happened?
Oh, no.
What is he going to do?
You came through this door and then went to the director's office, right?
Ki Joon,
you need to tell me the truth so I can help you.
I'm Director Gu.
I looked through everything carefully. Nothing was stolen.
The drawer was only damaged,
but our security guard is so dedicated to his job
that he called the police first.
But we should still look into the forced entry.
Yes, of course. Certainly...
But what happened at school must be resolved within the school.
If the police investigate the school over a damaged drawer,
I think my heart would ache too much as an educator.
Gosh.
- I understand, but—
- So...
Officer...
Please don't take our student's issues to the station.
I beg you.
You're Supervisor Lee Kang Hoon, correct?
Yes. Who are you?
You mightn't remember me. We met once before.
I'm the news reporter from the bribery incident.
Ko Byun Ho from KBD.
I heard about some interesting events, so I came by.
I never thought we'd meet again like this.
So you were fired because of bribery,
and now you're an unfairly dismissed teacher.
Wow. That's interesting.
I'd really like to report on this.
You should just go.
Really?
He will just be scolded?
Yes.
That's a surprise.
That's not like the Director Gu we know.
Could she be taking him to her office to punish him in secret?
How can anyone punish students these days?
"Gong Ki Joon. You must be in shock from this morning."
"Would you like some chocolate milk?" That's what she will say.
That gives me the chills.
Whatever it is, it's a mistake, right?
Ki Joon's okay, right?
Of course. It's just a misunderstanding.
Hey, Kang Seo Young.
Starting tomorrow, I can't come to school.
I'll be at training camp for the auditions.
I know. Good luck.
If I make it to the final round,
you won't see me for three months.
Three months is short.
Fighting.
Even if I'm eliminated in the preliminary round,
I'm still there for two weeks.
Oh...
Three months from now is next year.
So won't I see you until next year?
That's right.
Today is the last day we will see each other.
I'm going back to an apprenticeship.
What?
- Congratulations!
- That's great.
When do you get paid?
You'll buy us jjolmyeon, right? And pork katsu?
Of course.
- I'm so happy for her.
- Ji Won.
I think Ki Joon's issue is resolved.
What?
Look at you go from zombie to brightening up when hearing Ki Joon's name.
I'm hurt.
That's not it.
But what do you mean by resolved? How do you know?
I overheard it in the office.
I think he's talking to Director Gu now.
"Director Gu"?
It looks like Director Gu will say a few gentle words and leave it at that.
Oh. Really?
Hey, look at this.
It really wasn't me.
I never came into this room.
After being caught on the CCTV,
how can you be so shameless?
Yes, I was on CCTV,
but I didn't do this.
There's no video of me in here.
Then why were you at school in the middle of the night?
Jung Young Joo!
See... you can't answer me.
Bring me the notebook now.
I don't know about any "notebook."
Why would I take it?
Because Lee Kang Hoon made you?
Every morning, you make a scene at the gates about returning Mr. Lee to his position.
Is blackmailing me the only method that occurred to you?
Did you think this kind of blackmail would work on me?
"Blackmail"?
You children don't know what's right and wrong.
If teachers seem even a little bit nice, you trust everything they say.
I understand.
The teacher who uses students is at fault.
How could anyone blame innocent students like you?
So...
Ki Joon...
Will you give back what you took?
I really don't know.
Don't you know how to knock?
It's not Ki Joon.
What are you talking about?
How do you know that?
Because I was with him.
I'm his witness.
You were with him?
Are you an accomplice?
You won your brother's trial thanks to Lee Kang Hoon.
Did you want to repay his kindness?
We didn't come into this room.
I don't want to hear anything more.
Choose one of these two options.
Either give me back the notebook, or
face a Guidance Committee meeting.
Ah... of course... such a meeting means you'll both be expelled.
We never did anything to be expelled for.
No?
Jung Young Joo,
you were supposed to be expelled, but I overlooked it.
And there's video of your forced entry.
Do you think you can take classes at my school after stealing so shamelessly?
"Stealing"?
What nonsense—
We didn't do anything.
Don't get worked up.
I'll only wait until lunchtime.
Bring me the notebook.
That's enough time, isn't it?
Come out.
Let's go.
Don't expect me to let this slide.
When your parents come in,
you can state your position in front of the Guidance Committee.
Tell your story properly, then.
I don't have any parents.
You must have some kind of guardian.
There's no one.
Then, find proof that you guys didn't do it.
I should have been more careful.
If I hadn't been caught by the CCTV,
this wouldn't have happened.
I'm sorry.
I'm the reason you're in this mess.
So think before you act.
Even in taekwondo, you only knew how to attack. You called it "your tactic."
Sorry.
To be fair... honestly...
If I found a way to get Mr. Lee back,
I would have done something too.
But I wouldn't have done it alone, like you.
Don't you have any friends?
What were you doing on your own?
Hey. What about you?
You were talking like you're all alone in this world.
What? No adults?
My mom would be sad if she heard that.
You have Ji Won's parents, too.
Jung Young Joo...
Yes, Ms. Song?
Okay.
What happened?
I have to go see Ms. Song. I'll tell you after that.
Are you also going?
Yes.
Hey. Why are you going?
She only asked for me.
The director said I'd be expelled too.
So I'm coming with you.
"Expelled"?
What's going on?
Expelled for what?
What made you go there at night that's got you wrongly accused?
Why did you try to get in there?
We wanted the board-meetings log.
The board's record of meetings? Why would you need that?
We heard that the board rejected Mr. Lee's dismissal.
If we could just find the meeting's log,
Mr. Lee could come back.
Still, it's not right for you to try to get it for yourselves.
I'm sorry.
What's the notebook that Director Gu is asking for?
Is it the log of meetings that you're talking about?
We don't know about that.
Okay, I see.
Go back to class for now.
Okay.
This isn't what you said when you had the officer leave.
I was trying to be considerate, so the students don't get a criminal record,
but they are lying so shamelessly.
There's no proof that they stole it.
How can you say that after seeing the CCTV video?
As you saw,
they weren't seen stealing anything.
Threatening to expel them is going too far.
"Too far"?
Ms. Song Chae Rin,
who am I?
I think you tend to forget sometimes.
I'm the Director of Nulji High.
How dare a regular teacher like you argue with me?
Director Gu said that we stole the notebook to blackmail her.
That means it contains something to blackmail her with.
Seeing that she sent the police away
and tried to resolve this on her own in secret,
doesn't that mean something is seriously illegal?
I think that's why she wants the book back as soon as possible.
She will call the Guidance Committee if it isn't back by lunchtime.
How can you return it when you didn't take it?
She's overreacting and being pushy.
Could there be a way for us to prove we didn't take it?
She said she'll expel you as soon as tomorrow.
How could we prove it by then?
Geez. I actually wish we had the notebook.
She couldn't do anything if we just exposed her.
I know.
Then...
that's what we should do.
Hey!
Where are you guys going?
Come back here!
Gong Ki Joon!
Jung Young Joo!
Call their guardians.
The Guidance Committee meeting will take place tomorrow at five o'clock.
By tonight, even, I'll forgive them if they act sensibly
and show remorse. Tell their guardians to bring them in.
But...
there will be a problem if the committee meeting is held like this.
Who would be so arrogant as to cause an issue?
What I mean is...
We need to allow time for the committee to carefully consider the disciplinary action
as well as for students to explain themselves—
Are you trying to lecture me?
No.
So should we expose all of Director Gu's corruption to the public?
Yes.
Even without the notebook,
we can expose her with the things we've experienced.
I recorded all the times she tampered with students' records.
And all the internal school competitions are rigged.
As for Jin Sung University's competition,
I'm certain she manipulated it by bribing the university president.
But is this possible without definite proof?
They are bound to be exposed if they're fully investigated.
We can shake Director Gu just by suggesting suspicion.
It's a good idea,
but how do we expose her?
The Anti-Corruption and Civil Rights Commission of Cheongwadae?
(TN: South Korea's presidential residence)
I'm pretty familiar with that bulletin board.
We will need 200,000 votes to get a response.
But things like "Corruption in education" and "Our school is weird" posts are so common that—
Bam!
It won't get noticed.
How do we get 200,000 votes when the Guidance Committee meets so soon?
It's hard. It's practically impossible.
My Ji Won knows best about the bulletin boards.
What about the news?
"News"?
Do you know any reporters?
Oh. We could just go to a broadcasting company,
grab a reporter who feels right, and ask for an article to be written?
I approve.
You wouldn't really do that, would you?
It's a bit weird, right?
The person who wrote your article.
Hey, right.
Let's call him right now.
I don't know his number.
Geez.
You're no help.
Hey, you—
You smile brightly like that yet you say this to me?
- You—
- Oh, right!
Vice-President Jo Jae Min would know.
Call him right now.
Hold on.
Please...
The line is currently busy. After the beep...
He's not answering.
Of course. He's the vice-president, after all.
He's busy. He won't answer if people like us—
Hi, Mr. Jo.
Yes, hello.
- Yes, yes.
- He took our call.
- I'm heading out now.
- Bye.
I'm off.
I've told all the Guidance Committee members, so you should call the parents.
I gave him details over the phone.
I said you are great guys.
I personally asked him to take good care of it,
so he'll write a great article.
Tell him all the unfair things you experienced at school.
I told him to make lots of time for it.
I understand.
Thank you, Mr. Jo.
Okay.
Are you Nulji High students?
It's good to meet you. I'm reporter Choi Hyun Gyu.
Hello.
I said not to bring those things home.
I'm sorry.
These needed approvals rather urgently.
Here you go.
Here.
Being a teacher is a very tiring job.
I'm worn out after school ends. I don't even want to move a finger.
Oh, I see.
Still, I respect you
for doing something so worthwhile.
Don't respect me and do your job, okay?
It feels like I'm the only one in this company.
I apologize.
Hello? What is it?
So you want to meet?
Right now?
Ah, so that was when you found out who I am!
Wow...
You even prepared this.
Wow!
You're more cunning than I realized.
Yes?
I'm pretty meticulous.
I just don't let it show.
So...
Why did you do something so irrational? What if I refused?
The fact that Director Gu is the biggest problem at our school,
Mr. Shin,
you know that better than anyone.
And Mr. Shin, I thought Director Gu would be your biggest hindrance.
So I made up my mind to help you.
That is why I was so irrational...
Sir.
I suddenly don't know how to address you.
Just do as before. Sudden change is awkward.
That's right. Aigoo.
But don't get too comfortable.
Yes, sir.
So...
someone who's been a teacher all his life broke into
Director Gu's office in the middle of the night,
smashed a drawer open and stole her notebook for this reason?
Well, there's no need to describe it in such detail like that.
Sure.
You've always worked hard at the bottom and were about to suffer more.
I can understand why you'd be mad.
That's all good.
I was also having a hard time because
I couldn't do anything to Aunt because of Dad.
Having such perfect evidence makes my life easy.
Well then, our Director.
Goodness.
What would you like?
You're being so blatant—
You're very straightforward.
I've actually been thinking...
I think I should continue down the path of an educator.
So what if I take charge of this school,
and do a good job running it for you, Mr. Shin?
I see.
So do you want to be the director?
Well... yes...
Then do that.
Sorry?
Let's push Aunt to the side, and you can take her place.
Do you mean it?
Oh, one thing, though.
You know I hate commotion, right?
Of course. Of course!
My nickname used to be "library" because I was so quiet.
Wow. This is amazing.
This is enough to get into the top three items of Haerang News' social pages.
I'll give it my best.
Really?
Thank you so much.
If it becomes an article, will Director Gu be unable to do whatever she wants?
Definitely. She will have to be investigated by the Ministry of Education.
And once the meeting's record or the notebook is confiscated, everything will be revealed.
What about reinstating
the unfairly dismissed teacher?
I'm not sure,
but I think it could be possible.
There's a high chance.
Good job.
Aigoo, they're so simple-minded.
Those innocent children think that by having evidence, you can win anything.
Those "innocent children" are braver than I am.
Why bother, though?
They'll be kicked out like...
No way.
They can't kick students out so easily, right?
They didn't have a hard time kicking you and Mr. Kim out.
What are we going to do about those guys?
That was so good.
It was.
The ramen tastes better after a fruitful day.
What?
Are you laughing?
Aren't you going to your academy job today?
No, I'm not.
I told the director I was busy here, and she gave me today off.
What?
Mom knows we are here?
Yes.
She asked if you and I were close, and she seemed really happy.
Wow.
It's a free-pass when I hang out with a smart friend.
Who is it? Answer it.
Yes, Mr. Lee?
You guys are so reckless.
If you have information like the meeting-log, you should tell me.
Why would you go and look for that?
And I heard you guys left school without permission today.
Geez. What were you thinking, leaving like that?
We just worked on some things.
You'll be surprised when you find out.
Sorry?
No, I'm still at Ki Joon's.
Yes, we're all together.
Ah!
Mr. Lee wants to talk to you.
- Me?
- Yes.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
The signs?
Of course, I'm going to make them. I am. I'll make them.
Sorry?
Okay.
Got it.
All right.
What did he say?
He said there are only signs about unfair dismissal,
so we should make one to say that it's wrong to expel you two.
Geez.
What in the world!
Of course, right? Why should we be expelled?
So let's clear this and make signs.
Don't play and you lose. Rock, paper, scissors.
- Rock, paper, scissors.
Oh, you two.
- He was late.
- Come on, rock, paper...
It's kind of surprising.
What? What is?
What is?
You don't like fighting.
But watching you fight for our carpentry teacher,
I can feel how sincere you are.
Mr. Lee is the one who made me realize I have a talent for carpentry.
I thought I wasn't good at anything.
I've come to like carpentry more thanks to Mr. Lee.
You must really like carpentry now.
Wow, Mr. Lee helped Gong Ki Joon learn to like doing something.
That's a lot to thank him for.
Hey, it's not just Mr. Lee.
There's also my grandpa... and you.
That's why I like it.
Really?
So can I tell Ji Won what you said?
Just Mr. Lee, grandpa and me?
Don't be childish.
That's not what I meant.
Ji Won is, man...
She's on a different level.
- "Different" how?
- Stop it. Stop it!
Is this funny to you?
Hurry up and help me find it.
"Director Gu..."
Hey, Dad.
Hot chocolate?
Oh, no. I'll come and get it.
I'm on the top floor. Okay.
You're going to trip. Why are you in such a hurry?
If my dad comes here,
we will be trapped with his dad-jokes for two hours.
I'm going downstairs.
Ki Joon...
What?
You have a call.
Hi.
Mom.
It's nothing.
I ate.
I'm good at cooking so don't worry about me.
I'm just doing carpentry and working.
Yes.
What?
What do you mean so suddenly?
Come to you?
Do you mean Canada?
Why would you say that...
I don't know.
I'll think about it.
So, Ki Joon's mom is in Canada.
Yes. Ki Joon's maternal relatives are all there.
They run a taekwondo studio.
I knew she called him every now and then,
but it feels a bit different this time.
I think she called to tell Ki Joon to join her.
That would make sense.
If he went there, he wouldn't have to worry about income.
He wouldn't be lonely, either.
I think it's a good thing for Ki Joon.
Let's go.
I can take the cups downstairs and wash them there.
Pardon?
I'm just washing them while I'm at it.
Mom told me to join her.
She's worried since you're alone.
There are a lot of students at Uncle's taekwondo studio,
so I guess taekwondo is really popular there.
She said I could help coach and go to college there.
It feels weird.
In what way?
I don't know.
It must be because it's so sudden.
After a good night's sleep, tomorrow
you might wake up and feel excited and look forward to it.
Do you think so?
I do.
♫  I want to know your thoughts because I can't read them  ♫
♫  I get nervous sometimes because I like you  ♫
♫  I want to see the swaying waves  ♫
♫  I want to see you more on my way there  ♫
Mom told me to join her.
♫  Another day  ♫
♫  Passes by again  ♫
♫  During that time, my heart isn't my own  ♫
Come to you?
Do you mean Canada?
Why would you say that...
Once you get a good night's sleep, tomorrow
you might feel excited and look forward to it.
♫  And it makes me happy  ♫
♫  Then, in the next moment, I ache  ♫
Eun Bi, you'll be there as our company's representative,
so don't get intimidated
and always stand out in the center. Don't back down.
Got it?
And cameras are everywhere there,
so don't let your guard down.
- Mr. Lee!
- Hello.
You're here.
Wow!
The signs really stand out.
But...
I was nervous that you'd all get into trouble again for leaving school without permission.
But I'm glad you're all here without trouble.
I think we did cause trouble.
What? A-Again?
Actually,
we asked a reporter at Haerang News to expose Director Gu's corruption, but it hasn't been published yet.
What? You met a reporter? You guys?
He said the article would posted this morning, so we're still waiting.
But it's not posted yet.
Once an article appears, the whole school and all the media will know.
That will cause commotion.
Wow, you guys really are brave at problem-solving.
The article has to come out soon to stop today's committee meeting.
I think it's too delayed.
We have to stop the Guidance Committee meeting.
This is your school. Why would they do this to you?
Director Gu called it her school.
"Her school"?
Wow. She's seriously a dangerous person.
Something is not right.
Let's try calling Reporter Choi.
Okay.
I was arguing for it all morning,
but I'm afraid it won't be published.
I'm in charge of travel and leisure usually,
so I don't have much power.
I'm sorry.
Go inside.
It's upsetting.
Don't stand here. Go to class.
We're sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- No, don't worry about it.
Go on.
Mr. Lee, don't you know any reporters?
If you hadn't stopped it, Press Director,
I would've been like a sitting duck.
My gosh...
I'm always indebted to you.
I was reviewing the articles submitted this morning,
and something felt off.
I looked, and he had written an unbelievably provocative article about you.
Geez, it was so offensive to me.
I always remember that 50% of my education business is all your doing.
Oh, right. Isn't it about time to renew your golf club membership?
Right?
I'll tell my husband to renew it and send you a new one. Yes, yes.
All right, talk to you later.
I overheard at the office that there will be a Guidance Committee meeting today.
Really?
Oh, no.
We tried to stop it, but it didn't work.
Maybe they should just have a proper police investigation.
How can a guidance committee meeting take place so hastily?
Just wait and see.
The committee will make the right decision.
The students protesting at the gate are right.
This is definitely a private-school foundation tyranny.
"Tyranny"?
How can a teacher at a private-school foundation say that?
Mom. You can't get too worked up.
Don't worry about me.
I'm just going to tell her to lay out the truth.
How dare she treat our children like thieves?
We know Young Joo and Ki Joon would never do such a thing.
- How dare she—
- No, Mom.
Calm down. We have to fight this calmly.
All right.
Let's go.
Guidance Committee to that end, please.
Now we're just waiting for the principal and the director.
Yes.
You should go in.
Teaching Director, look here.
Geez.
What in the...
Director Gu.
I think you should look at this.
So you were appointed to the position and then dismissed by Director Gu,
but you were dismissed unfairly?
Yes.
I heard that the board rejected the dismissal,
but Director Gu went ahead anyway.
- Right?
- Yes, that's right.
If firing a teacher is this easy, what about the students?
She's currently holding a Guidance Committee meeting to expel students without any evidence.
That's right. There's no evidence.
I see.
Oh, and you're currently attending Nulji High?
Yes. I'm in the 11th grade.
I'm Director Gu's niece.
That's right.
Are you okay with saying that?
Yes.
Ms. Song Chae Rin.
For now, show them out.
Isn't the committee meeting about to start?
For now, I think the meeting is canceled.
What do you mean?
Do you mean our boys' charges are lifted?
Well...
Director Gu.
Say something.
I'm very proud of what we did.
Nulji High, fighting!
- Fighting!
- Fighting, fighting.
- Fighting fighting.
- Fighting.
For Mr. Lee's reinstatement!
Cheers!
I thought we just did it once.
Why are you copying your dad?
You don't know anything. You have to do these kinds of things.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
So...
Mr. Lee and Lee Jae Hee are a completely unexpected duo.
Yes. Jae Hee's really interesting.
Her family must be in a mess right now.
I'm worried for Jae Hee.
It's out.
Wow. So much!
- Looks so good.
- Isn't this expensive?
No. Don't worry and eat up.
So...
why are you two buying?
You got into trouble because Young Joo went to school at night.
I see...
Right.
Yes. I was going to pay for all of it, but Seo Young offered to help.
I see...
So, Seo Young is buying because of Young Joo.
And because of Young Joo, Seo Young–
Anyway, Seo Young and Young Joo, thanks for the food.
It looks amazing. Let's eat.
What?
What is it?
Wow!
Hey. It's so good!
- It's good?
- It is.
Why aren't you leaving?
We have to hurry and clean up here.
This is not fair.
Why do they believe Jae Hee's naive words?
And they believe the words of Lee Kang Hoon who was fired?
The investigation results haven't come out yet.
This is unfair dismissal.
It's unfair dismissal for now. But this would change the story.
Did Gong Ki Joon go to you?
Gong Ki Joon?
Oh, the 11th grade...
Why doubt him so recklessly?
You're not fit to be an educator, Aunt.
It wasn't Gong Ki Joon?
Aigoo. You're not fit to be an educator.
You're no good at reading people.
Don't trust the people closest to you.
The teaching director–
Bingo.
You've caused too much commotion, Aunt.
Hurry up and pack.
Ah, those twins.
Now I understand everything.
Hey, no one could win against the director's niece and nephew.
- Right?
- I know.
But your grade  and rank would stay the same.
You little...
- Mine stay the same, too.
- I know.
I hope Jae Hee isn't scolded.
Yes. After all, she did a good thing.
Jae Hee's nice, but what's wrong with Lee Jae Hyeok?
Jae Hyeok?
- Jae Hyeok is nice too.
- What are you saying?
- The two of them do seem alike.
-
His personality totally sucks.
So if Director Gu is fired, our school will get better, right?
I wonder what kind of person the new director will be.
We'll find out at the public hearing tomorrow.
"Public hearing"? What public hearing so suddenly?
Oh, what did they say again?
The head of the Foundation will announce a plan to improve our school or something.
I heard a lot of the school's parent leaders and local residents are coming.
There will be a lot of reporters too.
I'm class president, so I have to attend.
Oh, I see. I hope the head of the Foundation is a good person.
I hope he listens to people and changes the school.
Even if it doesn't change like that,
I just hope he can stop sending us to bad companies to raise employment rates.
- Yes.
- True.
I hope he can add pink to our school uniform.
Seriously, I just hope he can make the school pork katsu bigger.
Enough. We're discussing the improvement for our school, guys.
Hey, this will be the biggest improvement.
- Bigger katsu means improvement.
- No.
Test, test.
I wonder what kind of person the director is.
Geez, what fuss is this?
The head of the Foundation isn't here yet.
It looks like it.
What the heck? He has everyone gathered here.
So what plan is he going to suggest?
We'll find out soon.
The public hearing will begin shortly.
Everyone, please be seated.
Why isn't the principal here?
I didn't invite him since he would just cause a scene.
Now, we shall begin the public hearing for a better future for
Nulji Science and Technology High School.
Firstly, I know all of you must be busy.
Thank you so much for coming.
Several big and small changes regarding the operation of our school have taken place recently.
But as they say, happiness and misfortune are always shifting.
I believe this is only a winter-like phase
that we must pass through for beautiful flowers to bloom.
I'd like to introduce you to the person guiding us through this time.
He is the son of CEO Shin Eul Seop,
the founder of our Nulji Science and Technology High School.
He is temporarily leading the school as the head of the Foundation
until we find a new director.
Mr. Shin Cheol Min, please come up to the podium.
Mr. Shin?
- Oh my.
- What's going on?
First, I feel deeply responsible for causing an unfortunate incident.
I realized this was the limit of our Foundation,
and I felt a deep sense of regret.
I made this decision after suffering many sleepless nights.
If we cannot provide a proper education, we must close the school.
- What?
- Close it?
What does he mean?
- What?
- Closing the school?
I have a question!
What do you mean exactly by "close the school"?
- It's just as I said.
- What?
Getting rid of the school?
Nulji Science and Technology High School will be shut down.
What?
What's he saying?
Timing and Subtitles by the 🎶 Sing for a dream 🎤 Team @ viki
♫  Dream on, dream on, dream on  ♫
♫  My heart keeps thinking of you. I can't even understand myself  ♫
The ultimate boss? Who?
Are you playing around?
The school is closing. What nonsense.
Whatever you want.
Even if the school shuts down, you must push through with your goal.
I thought it was because I felt grateful you.
Can I speak first?
What's going on? Were you eliminated already?
Ki Joon!
I've reserved your plane ticket already.
Have you made your decision?
What about Ji Won?
I thought about it,
and I think it would be better if you go with your mom.
♫  It sparkles again  ♫