Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Hurry.
Hey.
Ji Won.
Oh?
What is it?
Hey, Jin Ji Won, I told you not to walk around at night—
Oh...
Well, I know this might look weird, but...
What's going on?
What are you doing here?
Young Joo, there's a reason for this...
I had something... to say to you.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
I'll get going.
What was that?
What's going on?
Young Joo carried this here for me.
Gosh. Why did you have to come out at that moment?
If you were going to bring this home, you should have told me.
I don't know.
I really don't know what to do.
Move.
What?
Oh, okay.
Gosh.
Oh, no.
Geez.
Oh, no, what do we do? What do we do?
Aigoo.
I got it.
Geez, it's so heavy.
How did Jung Young Joo carry this here?
We put it on his motorbike.
Right.
It's comfortable and nice.
Sit down. It's yours.
Hey.
How is this mine? We made it together.
Indeed, it's ours...
so why would you make a fuss out of carrying it here alone
and cause this mess?
How should I explain this to Young Joo?
What do you mean how?
Just tell him the truth.
Is that okay with you?
Are you from Nulji High?
Yes, is that a problem?
No, not at all.
Where you go to school doesn't matter for this part-time job.
So do you want to do this work while taking lessons at the after-school academy?
Are you preparing for college?
Yes.
I see.
But our classes mostly prepare for the CSAT.
(TN: College Scholastic Ability Test)
Since you're from Nulji High, aren't you preparing for a specialized field?
Then isn't it better to prioritize your school grades instead?
There's a college I want to go to,
but I think it's difficult to get in there with school grades.
Is that so?
Nonetheless, how marvelous.
In terms of lessons, you can take them whenever you like as long as it doesn’t affect your work,
since you'll be assisting the teachers anyway.
And the person working at the time can hand over the rest of the work to you.
Okay. Thank you. I'll work hard.
And...
you're coming here straight after school, right?
Yes.
We don't necessarily have a uniform for the part-time job, but...
Oh, I'll come to work in regular clothes.
Could you?
I'm sorry.
Since you'll be taking lessons with others,
there's no need to stir up stories about
why a specialized-school student takes lessons.
Yes, I understand.
It's all right.
Study hard today, okay?
See you at home.
You forgot to take your food.
- See you.
- Bye.
See you later.
You were shocked yesterday, right?
Yes. A little bit.
So the thing is, Ki Joon lives on the second floor of our house.
Ki Joon's actually...
No. That's okay.
As you said, I'm sure there is a reason.
There's no need to explain it. I'm not all that curious.
Oh!
Okay.
Then what...
Oh, right. What was it that you wanted to say?
Oh, well...
After the carpentry competition, I received an offer from someone.
- What?
- I'm not that interested,
but I wondered if maybe you would be.
That was why I went back yesterday, to ask you that.
What is it?
Can we talk for a minute?
I'm not a bad person, so don't be scared.
See?
I proved my identity, so what I'm about to say is real.
We're gathering high school students at our company.
To put it grandly,
we're fostering future carpenters and contributing to the world.
That's what we're trying to do.
But to put it simply,
we want to spend less and improve the company’s image.
Something like that.
What does that have to do with me?
Well, well...
You're hasty, just like me.
All right.
Look.
It's like a social project using carpentry.
We're gathering ten teams of high-schoolers from across Korea
who will contribute to their hometown through carpentry.
We'll be providing a small payment.
And depending on the activity’s result, we may award you.
You'd get a special benefit if you apply to our company.
Whether students want to work at our company is not important right now.
Well, so...
Why are you telling me this?
I’m bad at running the company, but I'm crazy about carpentry.
I noticed earlier that you have a rare talent.
Let's work together.
Since I picked you, I'll make sure to support your team.
So with that said...
Your number, please.
So did you give him your number?
No.
Come on. Wait a second.
Wow!
It's real.
It sounds amazing.
I thought you would say that.
If you want to do it, I could do it with you...
Yes! Let's do it, let's do it.
But I'm not good at putting a team together.
So are you asking me to take the responsibility?
Something like that.
That's my main talent.
Sounds good.
A company-sponsored project?
That's good. It sounds like a great opportunity.
Are you sure you're not interested?
Oh, does this not help you in getting into college?
I started a part-time job at a college prep academy downtown.
I'll work there, take lessons and study.
I see.
I guess you'll be busy.
I'm going to go this way starting today.
The academy I work at is this way too.
I see.
Good.
We don't have to go around anymore.
It must've been taxing for you all along.
I'm just saying that.
I'm joking. Don't take it seriously.
Bye. See you tomorrow.
Where are you going?
This is my family's diner.
I see.
If you're hungry, you can eat here before you go.
That's okay. Maybe another time.
See you.
Okay.
Baro Furniture?
Isn't that a famous place?
Is it?
I guess I've heard of it before.
Wow, so is my son going to work there now?
It's not like that...
Maybe it could work out well.
Of course, my Young Joo would do well.
You got an award at a competition,
and you learned a lot from your dad.
Mom.
Here we go again with "My son is best."
Oh, right. We had a group order earlier.
A hundred-twenty rows of gimbap on Monday.
Monday?
You should have told them we can't. It's the day of the trial.
Why should I?
I can go by myself. I'll have the lawyer with me.
But still...
I'll go with you.
I'll go.
Don't worry.
From now on,
just deliver what you're told to
and relay exactly what you hear.
I think that should be easy enough.
Why so serious? It's unlike you.
What are you looking at?
Here.
Thank you.
I'm just watching the students.
They're cute when you see them from far away.
They're not so cute up close.
They look nasty when you look at them too long.
Aigoo.
It isn't easy to manage them, is it?
Don't mind it too much, whatever they do.
They don't know anything.
They seem pretty complicated too.
Why... did you recommend me for this school?
Well, I didn't really have a reason.
A position opened up in the Architectural Design department,
and I thought of you. That's all.
When you recommended me, did the school say anything?
The school loved it.
You were awarded at a competition, and you have a solid resume.
Not like that.
I told you before.
Things didn't end well with my previous job.
Does the school know about that?
I'm not sure.
They couldn't know that far.
There was no reason for me to tell them either.
Aigoo. It's complicated.
Being a teacher is hard.
It's admirable of you; to get a project like this from outside the school.
I just discussed details with Baro Furniture.
I also submitted an official report to the school.
I asked for a teacher to direct the process, so do your best.
- We will. Thank you.
- Thank you.
He's here now.
The project is related to carpentry, so I asked Mr. Lee Kang Hoon.
Please change the teacher in charge.
Young Joo.
Hey. What are you doing?
Sit down for now.
I need to know why you're acting like this.
I thought a teacher who recognized hard work would be in charge.
What does that mean?
Did something happen with Mr. Lee Kang Hoon?
It must have been uncomfortable for you.
Sorry.
What is it?
You saw what happened at the competition last time.
If he's in charge, it'll happen again.
Do you think there's a connection between the twins winning and the carpentry teacher?
I don't want to see him hurting and ruining someone who is trying to do their best again.
Hey.
Come on.
It might be unrelated to the teacher.
We are all his students. There's no way.
Does he even think of us as his students?
You should have told me if something like that had happened.
What's the point of telling you about it?
The result already turned out to be that way.
I tried to put myself between them to keep the students from getting hurt.
It didn't work at all.
I thought it was weird that Director Gu
went to the competition site.
My gosh. What is wrong with this d*mn school?
What is wrong with this damn company? This isn't right.
- I heard that one before.
- What?
Are you worried about the students?
No, I'm busy looking after myself.
The school has to be a fence for the students,
but it feels like it's driving them to a corner.
It's good to think about them,
but you're not getting ahead of yourself again, are you?
Never mind me. I'm not interested.
Never mind them. I only care about getting my monthly salary
and getting off work on time.
You should worry about yourself. Don't get on their nerves anymore by saying proper things.
I'll talk it over with Young Joo.
Do whatever you want.
Not being charge of them would be better for me anyway.
Hi, Kang Seo Young's boyfriend.
Oh. Hey.
I'll eat with you since I'm a loner. I can sit here, right?
You're already sitting.
Shouldn't you eat with your friend?
Should I sit somewhere else?
No, no. I'm really comfortable right now.
Don't worry about me.
Just eat. Pretend she's not here.
Okay.
Are you going to eat with her?
She thinks we stole her award.
She'll look down on you if you go there.
We did steal it from her.
Are you insane?
Don't you have any friends?
Why do you keep following me?
That's it for today's lesson.
I put up the notice about the Baro Furniture project on the group chat,
so anyone who wants to participate, tell Young Joo.
That's it.
Thank you.
Wow, new guy.
Are you... the team leader?
Yes. The vice president of Baro Furniture asked him himself.
He saw Young Joo's carpentry skills.
- Wow.
- Daebak.
So if the team wins,
the whole team gets a benefit when applying to their company?
Yes.
Hey. Young Joo's the leader.
Why are you answering for him?
I got the offer,
but Ji Won will be taking the lead.
Whoever leads, I'll take part.
Hey. You guys should do it, too. It's a great opportunity.
No. It's hard enough preparing to earn certificates.
I have to ask my mom.
I'll add my name for now.
Okay. What about you, Min Seo?
Maybe I should do it before I start my apprenticeship again.
Sounds good. So, me, Young Joo, Jong Bok, Tae Ri, Min Seo...
We're short exactly one person.
I'll do it, too.
We got everyone.
Gong Ki Joon.
We can't accept you.
Why not?
It's not like there's a standard.
Carpentry is fun, right?
But you'll give this up too once it gets boring, no?
Young Joo, Gong Ki Joon isn't that bad.
Yes, Gong Ki Joon does well once he puts his mind to it.
Indeed. Ki Joon does well when he tries.
I don't think they know.
How shameless and selfish you are.
What?
You only care about yourself.
Whatever happens to your friend.
You do something if it's fun, but give up once it gets boring.
Enough.
We can talk about this later.
Talk about what later?
I don't have anything else to say to you.
I won't work with a jerk like you.
You have a lot of enemies.
What do you have against Gong Ki Joon?
It's just that... seeing that jerk's face makes me angry.
Gong Ki Joon doesn't seem to feel the same way.
You hate him, but he likes you?
It's not like that.
He's just... not important to me.
Insisting won't get you anywhere.
So...
Should I pretend I didn't hear that?
Hear what?
That volume level sounds like you need to eat something right now.
What are you talking about? I'm not hungry.
Geez. Insisting won't get you anywhere.
If you have time, you should eat before you go.
- Hyung.
- Hey.
Oh... It's my brother.
Hello.
Hi. Are you Young Joo's classmate?
Yes.
- Where's Mom?
- She went upstairs for a bit.
What do you want to eat?
I'll have tonkatsu.
Wait here a minute.
Hello.
- Hi, Ji Won, you're here.
- Yes.
A lot of Young Joo's friends are coming by today.
Seo Young.
Hey.
Why are you here?
Oh? I'm just dropping by.
Is it really okay if I sit with you?
If you guys are on a date, I can sit in the corner.
It's not like that. Don't worry about it.
Here we are.
I took a while with the jjolmyeon, didn't I?
Eat up, Ji Won.
Wow! This is way more than usual.
It's nothing for Young Joo's girlfriend.
- What?
- I—
He cared so much for the chocolate that you gave him.
I asked him for one, but he refused to give me any.
Mom, seriously.
That's not true.
Are you dating in secret?
Oh, no. You have your friend here.
Did I say the wrong thing?
Ahjumma, it's really not me.
It's...
It's me.
I'm Young Joo's girlfriend.
Really?
Thank you for the food.
I'll drop by often with Young Joo.
I have to go. I have work.
Okay.
- Goodbye.
- All right.
Good... bye.
Wow. That's Seo Young for you.
She's so straightforward.
I guess.
I guess you didn't tell your family that you had a girlfriend.
Well...
So Seo Young and I...
Never mind.
What was it that you wanted to say?
Oh. It's...
It's about Gong Ki Joon.
The offer from Baro Furniture, can Ki Joon do it with us?
We need one more person anyway,
and Ki Joon became pretty serious about his field of study while preparing for the competition last time.
Is that it?
The thing that you had to come all the way here to say?
What? Well, I was just here to eat anyway, so...
Sorry, but I can't work with him.
You should go.
Hey.
Did you finish fixing it?
Yes.
I stopped it from squeaking, but this part.
I can't do anything about this gap.
The joint isn't properly connected.
Still, other than that,
everything else is well made.
We could have gotten an award if we had only worked on the joint properly.
Still, it hasn't been long since you started. Your skills have improved a lot.
Of course, I'm your grandson.
It's just that I didn't work hard enough, but once I put my mind to it,
I learn quickly.
Aigoo, aigoo. You're bluffing.
Geez.
So...
should I get serious about carpentry like Jin Ji Won?
Are you talking about me?
Ji Won. Teach Ki Joon well.
He seems to be enjoying it.
Well. Would it really work?
How could you catch up to an excellent apprentice
who learned under Grandpa since kindergarten years?
Talent triumphs over time.
Come on.
What?
- Are you laughing at me?
- Yes.
I don't know about talent, but you do have some sense.
So about that new project. It starts soon, right?
Yes. It would be nice if you could do it with us.
I mean, you should do something so your carpentry skill can improve quickly.
I meant it would be good for you.
That's true.
What is it? Are you doing something again?
You can do it, too, Ki Joon.
Someone's stopping me from doing it.
Can you tell him off for me, Grandpa?
What jerk would do such a thing?
Bring him here this instant. I'll take his leg and—
Like this?
So we learned about the elements of traditional Korean architecture.
Here's the performance assessment assignment.
Quiet.
First, visit one of these traditional architectural sites—
Quiet!
You youths.
Go to one of these sites and take pictures based on what you learned in class.
Write a report and do a presentation on it.
Ms. Kim? Which of them is the closest?
They're all similar distances.
Location B is a little further away, but you'll have a lot to write about.
Why are there two locations for B?
You might as well visit both if you're making your way further away.
The two buildings have distinctly different styles.
It's worth 30 points so don't even think about getting something off of the internet.
- All right.
- That's it.
Goodbye.
Hey, guys. Let's do B.
I'm bored of hanoks.
(TN: a hanok is a traditional Korean house)
Let's just go to nearby A and look around quickly, then hang out at a pretty cafe.
There's a seriously good restaurant near C.
Wow, seriously? That sounds great.
- Can't wait to go.
- Hey, Team Leader.
- To which one are you going to go to?
- What?
You're the team leader for the Baro Furniture project.
Do you want to go to the hanok with us?
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm not sure...
Come with us.
You get to know each other and do homework together if you go with the team.
You're supposed to hang out with the team.
To bond, you know?
Okay, I'll think about it.
Min Seo. Let's go to B.
Let's go to B.
It's too far.
- Please.
- It's far.
Please.
- Please?
- It's too far.
Did you decide where to go for the performance assessment assignment?
No.
It might be better to go where many won't go.
Jung Young Joo.
I want to do it, too.
The new project club.
You?
I did as you asked. Do me a favor, too.
This is not up to me.
I know I'm indebted to you,
but if you join us, wouldn't the same thing as the last competition happen again?
I know Director Gu and the carpentry teacher made you twins first place behind our backs.
Mr. Lee Kang Hoon wasn't a part of it.
- What?
- He actually got on Mr. Lee Han Soo's bad side
because of the last competition.
What do you mean? Tell me in detail.
The judge was the carpentry teacher's sunbae
so the school ordered him to buy out the judges,
but he didn't do as he was told.
So that's why Director Gu stepped forward herself.
- Your aunt.
- Sorry.
You almost fooled me.
You and Director Gu. You're all the same.
Why do you want to join a club again?
Director Gu really didn't make you do it?
She didn't. Really. I just volunteered because I really want to.
Do you like carpentry that much?
I mean...
I do like carpentry,
but more than that, I want to try hanging out with friends.
Look, Eun Bi. She just uploaded a few cover dances on YouTube
and got a ton of calls from entertainment companies.
I don't know anymore.
Now that the ones who defended me are gone,
I have no energy.
I was completely fooled by you and Kang Seo Young's teamwork.
Come on, don't be like that.
You were moved and told me I was suave.
What the heck. I said we should just go.
Hey! You're Jung Dae Hye's boyfriend, right?
Sorry? Who are you...
He is. You're a funny one.
Can you really live well on your own?
What— what do you mean?
Never mind.
You make a perfectly sane girl drop out of school in 12th grade.
You look happy with your new girlfriend.
- Drop out?
- That's enough. Let's go.
It's embarrassing.
You. You shouldn't live like that.
Let's go.
Eun Bi, sorry. One second.
H-Hey, excuse me!
Did Da Hye noona drop out?
Are you saying you didn't know?
I really didn't know.
I haven't seen her since winter break.
You're more shameless than I thought.
Da Hye was even grounded.
What?
Wh-Why?
How are we supposed to know? Shouldn't you know that?
- Wow. He's trash.
- Really...
Did you have a girlfriend?
Yes.
I met her last year.
I was dumped over winter break.
Why?
I don't know.
It was going well,
and then suddenly, she started ignoring my texts.
Even to this day.
I see...
It must have been hard for you.
Yes...
What? No, not at all.
It's already in the past. Nothing hard about it.
Well, was she your first girlfriend?
- Y-Yes.
- What about afterward?
I was single.
Then what about now?
What?
I'm not sure.
Perhaps it's still a work in progress.
Are you already leaving, Ji Won?
Yes, It's further away, so I have to leave early.
Ki Joon, it's a school project. Aren't you going?
I said I would go today, too, but I'm going somewhere close with my friends.
Is that so?
Ji Won, you should have chosen somewhere closer.
I really wanted to go to this place.
Where is the tape measure?
Are you okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
Let's see.
Aigoo, you should go to the hospital.
- Honey!
- Don't tell Mom.
Oh. Okay.
Ki Joon, we'll be back. Don't tell her mom.
Let's go.
Aigoo. You should have been careful.
I know. I'm going.
Eat something if you're hungry. Don't tell me.
Seriously.
What's fine about this?
What's nothing?
You went to the ER this morning with your finger sliced open, and it's nothing?
We only went to the ER because no other place was open, it's not that serious.
It's not serious, but she had five stitches?
Sorry, Mom. But I have to go.
Where are you going with your finger like that?
I have a performance assessment assignment. I have to go see traditional wooden architecture.
Do you still talk about carpentry after being injured because of it?
You hurt and cut yourself all the time.
I said I'd be careful.
How many years has it been since you said that?
If you keep hurting yourself like this, it means your body's not getting used to it.
That means you have no talent.
Mom.
What?
You didn't win the competition this time either.
You should know when to quit.
Why do you hold onto what's not right for you and suffer?
Honey, calm down. You'll get anemia again.
You said I could work hard on what I love even if I'm not talented.
Why are you going back on your words now?
You...
- That was so long ago—
- And who said I'm not talented?
I am talented.
Be careful, okay?
She's talking back to me.
- What is this?
- You hurt yourself looking for this, right?
You forgot to take it.
I can do without measuring tape.
Are you here to bring me this?
Yes.
We're leaving.
What are you doing? Aren't you getting off?
I'm going to sleep. Don't wake me up.
Wow, it's big.
Yes.
It's much larger than I thought it would be.
It says it was an upper-class house.
These people were rich.
I'll take over here. You do the Mu Sung School building later.
Whatever works.
But when are we eating?
I haven't been on a bus in a while, and I'm really tired, hungry—
So why did you follow me?
I'm regretting it.
I'm proud of you, so I'll buy lunch.
As you should.
Of course, you should buy lunch.
Fine, come on.
I am coming.
What did you do all these years not growing up?
You look like an elementary school student from far away.
Hey.
I'm of average height.
Unbelievable.
Hey, look at this. Looks good, right?
Nice.
Let's eat.
Are we going now?
Are we not eating?
Careful.
You be careful.
Hey.
You said you'd buy lunch.
Is this what you meant?
The weird thing is,
whenever I see something nice or go somewhere nice,
I always crave ramen and gimbap.
Do you know that feeling?
Wanting to eat the most mundane thing at the most beautiful place.
So romantic.
Wow.
That's a grand story, considering it's an excuse
just to save money.
It's true.
I'll buy you an expensive dessert at the terminal.
You ate it well.
True.
Hey, hey. Hold this.
Sorry. Sorry
Sorry, sorry.
Hey, Young Joo.
Where are you?
I'm working on the performance assessment assignment.
I see. You're already there.
Yes. It's quite nice here. You should visit.
Okay.
I will.
Why did you call?
I just thought we could go together.
Did you want to come here, too?
You should have said so. It would have been nice to come together.
No, no. It's okay.
It might be dangerous all by yourself, so get on the bus before it gets too late.
It's okay. Ki Joon's here with me.
What?
Is it Seo Young or Ji Won?
What are you doing?
Were you standing there?
Geez. Whoever it is, you should have mentioned it sooner.
Come out, let's eat.
This is a completely different vibe.
- I'm glad we went to both, right?
- Yes.
So is a "seowon" like a school?
It's something similar.
Did you come here without even knowing what it is?
This place looks nice.
Are we allowed to go in?
Of course not! He's hilarious.
Watch where you're going.
♫  Even though I try to think of something else  ♫
♫  My brain won't listen to me  ♫
♫  Your every little thing  ♫
♫  I like all of them, what can I do?  ♫
♫  Because your smiles every day are a little bit different  ♫
♫  Every day is a joy  ♫
♫  When I happen to pass by you  ♫
♫  My heart beats loudly  ♫
♫  What do I do with my heart that keeps liking you?  ♫
♫  What do I do when I can't hide it?  ♫
♫  They say that's how it all begins  ♫
♫  Hesitating, not knowing what to do  ♫
Goodbye.
Is she awake?
Is he still asleep?
Geez, I think we're here.
Gosh, what do I do?
Keep calm.
And...
I just have to get up naturally, right?
Hey, aren't you getting off?
So Director...
I hope you can get through to my child.
I prepared him to go to a science high school since elementary school,
and now he wants to go to a specialized school.
Gosh. It's so shocking.
I see.
Children are constantly changing their minds at this age.
He will regret not listening to his mother once he does manual labor making a living,
while being mistreated
and being overworked.
But it's not always like that these days.
Specialized technical jobs earn more money
and societal perception has changed now.
And many students go to college from specialized high schools too...
- Director.
- Yes?
You speak too lightly since it's someone else's business.
Oh, no! That's not what I meant.
Anyway, please convince my child.
Of course, I will.
Goodbye.
Gosh, the biases that people have...
They don't go away easily.
Don't your parents worry about you working over the weekend?
No, it's okay.
All right. Don't work too hard.
I'll go downstairs for a moment.
All right.
You better work hard. Don't inconvenience others this time.
I said I threw the flowerpot.
So why did you throw the flowerpot then?
What are you talking about out of the blue?
I was just curious.
Why did you throw it?
Why are you asking me that?
Oh, sorry. It wasn't you.
Who was it again?
What are you trying to do?
Hey. Did you see my phone?
I don't know.
Didn't you take it to the restroom?
I didn't.
Wow. It's tiring, right?
Yes.
So tiring.
Oh. So.
Good work today.
Rest up.
Okay.
Go inside.
Was it not Jae Hee?
So Kang Seo Young told her to say that,
but Kang Seo Young didn't throw it?
Indeed.
I could have found out more.
Geez. So close.
But it's obvious.
The people that Kang Seo Young would go out of her way to protect.
There are only two.
Who are they?
First, it's a girl named Go Eun Bi.
It can't be her.
She was in the classroom then.
- A flowerpot.
- What is it?
What's that? Daebak.
What's going on? What is that?
So there's only one person left.
Kang Seo Young's boyfriend.
I'm 90 percent sure.
Does Kang Seo Young have a boyfriend?
What is his name?
Jung Young Joo. A new guy in my class.
Jung Young Joo?
The document prepared by the plaintiff
seems to repeat the same content from last time.
What is the reason you wish to push back the date to plead?
Yes, a long time has passed since the date of the incident,
so there are some difficulties gathering evidence.
If you could push back the date once more,
we shall gather and submit additional evidence
that the accused is responsible for the accident.
We shall push back the date for additional evidence.
And if you cannot gather evidence until the next date,
we shall conclude the plead.
That will be all.
For now, we earned some time.
But we have to gather testimony or evidence as much as we can during that time.
I think you should ask Supervisor Lee Kang Hoon again from last time.
That will be tough.
He's working at a school affiliated with Sang Rim.
I couldn't ask that of him.
Then we're at a disadvantage.
Should I contact him myself?
It was a Nulji High uniform for sure.
What was his name? Did you see his name tag?
Noona, I did well today, right?
His name.
Don't speak nonsense and tell me his name.
Jung Young Joo.
Jung Young Joo?
Jung Young Joo. A new guy in my class.
Yes.
Yes, of course.
All right.
Two, three. Two!
Darn.
Oh, Team Leader.
You're super late.
He already told Ms. Song.
I heard you might not come. You're early.
Yes. It ended faster than I thought.
What was it?
Is Jung Young Joo in this class?
Jung Young Joo.
Come sit.
That's what beggars do.
I heard you were transferred here.
Are you adjusting to school well?
Yes.
I'm glad.
How is our school?
The teachers are great. We have great facilities.
It's quite nice, right?
Yes.
The view from here is great too.
Especially the view from the rooftop.
Have you been to the rooftop?
It's already time for class. Go on ahead.
Oh, right.
I have something to give back to you.
This is yours, isn't it?
♫  Dream on, dream on, dream on  ♫
♫  My heart keeps thinking of you  ♫
♫  I can't even understand myself  ♫
♫  I'm always curious about you  ♫
♫  Whenever I run into you  ♫
Why did she point out Young Joo right away?
Expel him.
So this person named Gu Byeong Chul knows Jung Young Joo?
He won't let it go.
Are you keep going to be like that? Let it go.
Not Mr. Lee. It'll put him in a difficult position.
Could I ask for your help?
Did you change your mind?
He said he tried to get it back for you.
I came here because I knew you would come.
You're always avoiding me.
You can't run from here.
♫  Tell me what you wanna be  ♫