It's…
Didn't you say
you wanted to live independently?
- You're yelling now?
- Trai!
Hey, stop!
Money!
If Trai never liked your business
and loves his freedom so much,
why don't you just let him go?
He's my son. He has to come back here.
But I'm not as good
at making money as Pakbung.
How could she think about money
with every breath?
You're only good at making money.
Why don't you try getting a man?
Your mom didn't die here, right?
And no kids died here either, did they?
You wanna meet them?
100 for each clear glass.
500 for each wine glass.
Break it and you pay.
Stingy.
Dad?
Let's get it started.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Having fun?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Where were we?
Does saying sorry fix anything?
We were having fun,
and now, it's all ruined.
Sorry. I'm sorry, miss.
Niuniu, what happened?
Oh, no.
Petch, I didn't mean to.
Her friend was dancing and bumped into me.
Are you blaming my friend?
Ms. Mika.
I sincerely apologize.
My staff wasn't careful enough.
How about I take the dress to be cleaned?
No need. It's dirty.
I'm not going to wear it anymore.
That's good. Yeah.
Mrs. Mookmanee, it looks like
Ms. Mika is having a problem.
Children's problems should be handled
by the children themselves.
My mother taught me that
if someone does something to you,
you return it.
It splashed on you too, right?
Yeah. I'm soaked.
What a very entertaining performance.
Today is a special day,
Ms. Mika's birthday.
May I invite everyone
to raise a glass
and toast our lovely birthday girl.
All together, cheers!
You lowlife. How dare someone like you
wish me happy birthday?
Someone at your level
doesn't even deserve to look at me.
That's right.
- Yeah.
- Right?
Mr. Rachen, let's drink.
- Yes.
- Sure.
I've always wanted to try this wine
that costs tens of thousands per bottle.
So this is how it tastes.
It's delicious.
Thank you.
You ruined my birthday cake.
It's your fault!
Hey. What are you doing?
- Please, don't do this.
- Let her go.
Hey. Hey.
You wanna eat expensive things that much?
Fine. I'll donate some to you.
Eat it. What are you staring at?
Ms. Mika,
I apologize.
Please have mercy.
Please don't take this any further.
I didn't start it. You all did.
And you spilled wine on my dress.
You were drunk
and not watching where you stepped,
then you blamed my friend.
Pakbung, stop.
You fell into your own cake.
You lost face, so you took it out
on someone you could push around.
Go ahead and film it. Film everything
and share it.
Let everyone see how Ms. Mika
bullies and oppresses poor people.
Go ahead. Bully me!
- You!
- Mika.
Don't make this a big issue.
I taught you that if someone
doesn't consent, don't force them.
There are many other ways
to make someone pay.
Call the lawyer.
- Yes, ma'am.
- What?
The event was ruined
due to staff negligence.
I will sue for damages.
Mrs. Mookmanee, please. I beg you.
Please don't do that. Please don't sue me.
I have no money.
My daughter's birthday was ruined.
Her feelings were hurt.
I can't let this go
unless you make
my daughter feel satisfied.
If Mika is okay, I'll drop it.
If I eat it, this will end, right?
Maybe.
Try it and see if I change my mind.
Eat it.
Happy birthday, Ms. Mika.
How dare you ruin Ms. Mika's birthday?
Dad?
What are you doing here?
Get out. Leave this place right now. Go.
Did you cut the power?
Yes.
Why?
To help you.
Why did you turn off the lights?
Why did you pull me out?
Wait, Pakbung. Calm down.
Get yourself together.
If you go back in, it will only get worse.
Ms. Mika won't let this go,
let alone Mrs. Mookmanee.
She has power and connections.
If you fight back, it will escalate.
They're worse than you think.
I saw my father.
The father
I've wanted to see for ten years,
I wanted him to come back to me,
to be with me and Kanah.
He was there. He protected that girl.
He slapped me.
Uh, Mrs. Mook. Mrs. Mook.
I'm sorry. When I saw that girl come in
and ruin Ms. Mika's birthday,
I couldn't take it. I lost control
and had to teach that kid a lesson.
That girl called you Dad.
Why would I be her dad, Mrs. Mook?
I'm single. I've never been married.
I've never had a child.
I've never loved anyone but you.
Yongyut, if you want to stay with me,
don't do anything I haven't ordered.
I'm sorry.
If you want to leave the past behind,
cut it off completely.
If I find out that you went in there
to protect your daughter,
it's over for both of you.
Did you find him?
It has to be him. Try searching again.
Search everywhere.
Why did Trai come here?
And he was in a server uniform.
Or did he come to see Dad?
A friend of my friend who has met Mr. Trai
said he saw him
at Ms. Mika's birthday party.
Prarop and I have checked.
This clip is the clearest one.
I captured it and adjusted the color.
It really is Mr. Trai.
Bring him back no matter what.
- Yes, sir.
- Bung!
- Bung, how are you?
Are you okay?
Did you get hurt? Huh?
Niuniu told me everything. Petch is
really upset, so she's staying with him.
Too bad I wasn't there. Otherwise,
I would have smashed a wine bottle
on that spoiled girl's face
and rubbed her head into the cake.
I'd take off my shoes
and slap her in the face with them.
She'd be finished.
Brutal but agreed.
- Did Niuniu tell you who I ran into?
- Who?
What? Are you keeping secrets?
If you're hiding things from me,
you could die anytime.
I'm not dead yet.
I can still pay your tuition.
Then try dying. I will dig you up myself.
You already look like
you crawled out of a grave.
How about this?
We hire Noy and the guys to deal
with that spoiled girl and her mother.
Are you crazy?
Why risk ourselves for people like that?
They can look down on us,
but we do not have to sink to their level.
Then black magic.
Conjure buffalo hide into their guts.
Are you crazy, Samlee?
I know you're angry. I am too.
But there has to be another way.
Yes. There has to be another way.
But maybe Pakbung should shower first.
Right. Go shower.
I'd like an antibiotic cream
that reduces inflammation
but doesn't leave scars.
My friend…
My friend fell
and has a small scrape on her hand.
Sure.
Anyway, have you called your friend yet?
My friend? Pakbung?
Oh? Someone came
looking for you the other day.
I already told Pakbung
and gave her his business card.
He said there would be
a reward for information,
so I told Pakbung to try contacting him.
Mr. Trai! Mr. Trai!
Prarop?
I am sorry, Mr. Trai.
Easy, Mr. Trai…
Hey, Mr. Trai!
- Wait, Mr. Trai!
- Let go, Lee, Rop!
Let me go!
Please hold on.
Mr. Tritot wants to see you.
I don't want to see him. I don't.
Let go!
Block the way.
Mr. Trai, please see Mr. Tritot.
I'm begging you.
Please calm down. Calm down.
Calm down…
Even if you run,
Mr. Tritot will find you anyway.
Wait. Did Pakbung tell you where I was?
I already paid the caretaker fee.
Don't worry.
Huh? Caretaker fee?
- Yes…
- How much?
100,000?
Yeah.
When I was leaving for school,
someone asked about Trai.
Excuse me, do you know this person?
That's Trai.
Do you know him?
- I don't know him.
- Wait, wait.
- Please calm down.
- Wait.
He's my younger brother.
He ran away after fighting with Dad.
If you know where he is, please tell us.
But I didn't tell them Trai was here.
They asked for my account number,
so I sent the QR code, just in case.
They really transferred the money
and said it was a caretaker fee.
Hey. Is Mr. Trai that rich?
Just a few days of service
for 100,000.
It's "only" 100,000.
Pakbung, wait for me. Hey.
Wait for me. Wait.
- Mr. Trai.
Pakbung would never take only 100,000.
You hurt her, didn't you?
- No, we didn't.
- No.
Fists, sticks, or guns, huh?
Mr. Trai, we are not thugs.
But you chopped the back of my neck?
It still hurts.
- No, Mr. Trai. We…
- We really did pay them.
There was no assault, for sure.
She said 300,000.
How could she take only one?
If you were going to sell our friendship,
you should've asked more than this.
I can pay more.
If you think 100,000
is too little for your value,
I can arrange it.
Keep your money to buy something else.
When something has value,
you pay to get it.
If you're counting on freebies like usual,
you'll probably only get a bite or two.
Or you’ve never gotten even a bite?
If you want what I have,
if you want what I get,
then get as rich as I am,
have as much power as I do.
Don't act like a pathetic loser.
The moment anything happens,
you run and cry.
And just like that,
everything gets taken from your life.
Mom.
Have you greeted your son yet?
Haven't seen each other
in a long time, right?
You must have missed each other so much.
We're all here today. Father,
mother, and son.
What a perfect family.
You married Darin
to punish me, didn't you?
I sent you abroad for three years,
and you were still stubborn, asking
for Darin all the time. Are you insane?
Because I made her suffer.
I caused it,
so I have to take responsibility.
Responsibility for what?
Do you know the victim was a doctor?
People cursed you all over the country.
You weren't driving.
Why did you take the blame?
It was because of me, Dad. It was my car.
I forced Darin to drink.
But you were not the one driving.
And someone that drunk
shouldn't be driving.
Are you going to trade your whole life,
your future, for one woman?
And you call that love? Stupid.
Any feeling that drags you down
is not love.
It's stupidity, obsession, foolishness.
Idiot!
Then what was actually
behind everything you did to me?
Good intentions? Or love?
A love that only forces
and controls me all the time?
A love that is ready to kill me
the moment I disobey you?
Good. Someone like you needs
to get hurt sometimes,
so you will stop being stupid.
So you really do want to kill me.
You're so naive.
Someone as naive as you
will never keep up with Darin's game.
This world is brutal, Trai.
There is no place for the weak.
That is why I taught you, handled you,
so you would be stronger
and stand higher
where no one could drag you down.
Remember this. I will never
allow anyone to destroy you.
Did you ever ask me even once
if I wanted that?
Stop forcing your love on me.
I'm going to die because of it.
Don't go up yet.
Mr. Tritot is talking to his son.
You rushed here because you heard
Trai is back, didn't you?
Please wait.
Father and son need to talk in private.
Outsiders should not interfere.
If you're angry
because your lovers kicked you out,
then go scream in the bathroom.
Don't take it out on me.
It's annoying.
- Let's go, Mr. Trai.
- Mr. Trai.
- Let's go.
- Mr. Trai, come with us.
- Please don't, Mr. Trai.
- Please don't. Come with us.
- Mr. Trai.
- Put him in the room.
Guard the door and don't let him come out.
Let him calm down in there.
- You cannot force me.
- Why not?
- Take him.
- Hey. What's wrong with you again?
Here. Your favorite son is here.
Rachen obeys everything you say.
Let him do it for me.
The inheritance, the business, all of it.
Let him do it.
You want it so badly? Then take it.
I will transfer
my status as his son to you.
Trai, you are my only son,
and that will never change.
But I don't want to be that.
What kind of parenting is this?
You treat me like a dog.
If you could put a collar on me,
you would have done it.
I don't want a father like you.
Stop forcing me. Stop hurting me!
- I'm telling you, stop hurting me!
- Trai!
- I barely have a life now.
- Go.
- Take him.
- Deal with him.
Take him.
Take him!
- Mr. Trai, let's go.
- Let's get to your room.
- Please, Mr. Trai.
- No.
- Enough, please.
- Let me go.
Please, Mr. Trai.
Let's go inside.
Dad, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Dad.
Calm down.
Wow. This is Mr. Trai's house?
Damn.
Now I know why you said
it was only 100,000.
He wouldn't give me money that easily.
Something must have happened.
Hey, Pakbung!
- What's the matter?
- I'm here to see Mr. Trai.
I'm his friend.
You? A friend of Mr. Trai?
I don't think so.
Hey. Why are you looking down on us?
Go live.
Fine. Let's do it.
Everyone, help us out.
I'm here with a friend,
and we're coming to see a friend
at a friend's house, and this guy
is insulting us.
Hey.
Give it back.
- Give it back!
- You can't film here.
Let go!
Where are you going?
Hey! Pakbung!
Help, everyone. He's using force.
- He's assaulting us.
- Give it to me.
- Stop.
Stop.
Why use violence? You can talk nicely.
Are you okay?
I remember you,
from Ms. Mika's birthday party.
That was you, right?
I'm here to see Mr. Trai.
You're Trai's friend?
Yes. Mr. Trai stayed
at Pakbung's place for several days.
Trai is inside. I'll take you in myself.
You can't.
Mr. Trai won't allow any guests.
When are you going
to stop causing problems, Trai?
Isn't it you
who has problem with me, huh?!
Dad loves you. He cares about you.
Try being a good son for once.
What kind of love is that?!
He stole my girlfriend, and now,
he's locking me up like a prisoner.
He sacrificed for you. For you!
So you'd finally open your eyes.
You want a cheap woman
like Darin as your wife?
If you’re so much like Dad,
why weren’t you born his real son?
Why don't you die then?!
So Dad will have only me.
You want to kill me that badly?
Go on. Do it.
If I'm gone, you get everything,
money, Dad's love.
You've been waiting for a chance
to kill me this whole time.
Come on. Come on, Bro. Go ahead.
Do it. Kill me!
I want you dead.
I want you dead!
But if you die, Dad will suffer even more.
You can't die yet, Trai.
Mr. Trai said you wouldn't be satisfied
with only 100,000 baht.
Sign here.
"The recipient is prohibited
from contacting Mr. Trai
Bowornmongkolphong through any channel."
"The recipient's prohibited from involving
themselves in any way with Mr. Trai…"
This is like a drama. A messy romance
with a mafia prince or something.
Did Mr. Trai tell you
to write this contract?
Yes.
And he told you to bring me this check?
Correct.
Please. I'm just poor, not stupid.
That kind of person
would never give me money.
He wouldn't give me even one baht.
So what did you do to him? Kidnap him?
Detain him?
Or did you kill him?
You talk exactly like him.
What kind of people do you think we are?
If Mr. Trai is fine,
then let him come talk to me.
You lived with him for a few days,
and you think you know him well?
And how long have you been with him?
You still don't know what he's like?
I want the money so bad.
If you're giving it, then give it.
But I'm not gonna sign this contract.
And tell the person
who ordered you here this.
If you want me to stop getting involved
with Mr. Trai, then pay more.
Pakbung.
100,000 is already a lot.
I'd take 10,000 and be done.
You're leaving me again?
Who left who?
Trai.
As far as I remember,
you left me to marry my father.
Trai, can you listen to me first?
I'm listening. Go ahead.
Your father forced me. I had no choice.
Don't tell me you had no choice.
You did. You just didn't choose it.
The other path was poor and hard,
so you sold your dignity,
sold yourself.
Three years.
Three years, Trai.
You never cared about me at all.
If that day, you hadn't run off abroad…
No.
If that night, you hadn't made me drink,
would my life have ended up like this?
Drink it! Drink it! Drink it!
Bottoms up. Bottoms up.
- Are you leaving?
- Alright, get home safe.
- We haven't finished it yet.
- Get home safe.
- Let's go.
Trai, I'll drive.
Let's go.
It's because of you
that I ended up like this.
Because you were weak.
You never protected me.
The day I got sued, the day I got fired,
the day I had no job, no money,
where were you?!
Where were you?!
You're not me. You'll never understand.
You would never understand.
And what if you had
the chance to choose again?
That other path you said didn't exist,
it's right here.
Come with me. Leave everything.
Leave the past behind and start over.
Will you go with me?
But all I have is what you see.
Just me and my heart, none of Dad's money.
So you're thinking of having an affair
with your own father's wife?
This is my house.
If I could be a little worse,
I'd have gone around and used
the same woman as you already.
But too bad.
This is a house, not a brothel.
And I'm not like you.
- Trai!
- Don't worry.
I'm not going to mess with your woman.
But if your woman comes after me first,
then that's on her.
Call it karma catching up with you.
Look at how confident you are, Trai.
Is Trai misunderstanding something?
Tell him, sweetheart.
Mr. Trai.
Ms. Darin doesn't want your help.
Let me go.
Your mother still isn't well,
is she, Darin?
Let go of me. Let go!
If you still want money from me,
then stop throwing yourself to my son.
How is Petch doing?
The doctor already pumped his stomach.
They have to monitor him,
but Petch still hasn't woken up yet.
A letter from Mrs. Mookmanee's lawyer.
They're suing us
for 20 million baht in damages.
20 million baht?
This is obviously harassment.
Petch was so stressed out.
He downed a whole pack of sleeping pills.
Good thing Samlee and I saw it,
so we called an ambulance.
- Good afternoon.
Good afternoon.
You didn't have to come in person.
I was going to bring the documents to you.
I just wanted to see how my company…
I mean, the company
I hold shares in, operates.
And will Mika get bored, having to
sit here listening to adults talk numbers?
If I were bored, I wouldn't have come.
I came because there's
something interesting here.
Mom wanted me to come see for myself
whether I like it or not.
So far, I'm okay with it, Mom.
Mr. Rachen, do you have time?
I want Mika to learn how things work here.
Of course.
I'll take good care of Ms. Mika.
You don't have to worry.
Mr. Rachen looks good. He seems like
a great match for our Ms. Mika.
I mean your Ms. Mika.
I like that he's capable.
A son of a mistress being ambitious
enough to come this far is impressive.
But if Mika doesn't like him,
I won't force her.
Ms. Mika is really lucky
to have a mother who loves her
and who is kind like you.
Please wait here for a moment.
I'll go get the car.
Mrs. Mookmanee.
You're suing Petch
for 20 million baht in damages.
Petch overdosed on sleeping pills.
He's in the hospital right now.
Are you just going to stand there?
Uh, right.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I was arrogant and cocky,
so you and your daughter got upset.
If you're angry at me, then come after me.
Demand whatever you want from me.
But please withdraw
the lawsuit against Petch.
Everything has a price.
Even if you can't afford it,
that's not my problem.
I'm sorry I was born poor,
with no money, no way to compare to you.
And I was stupid and reckless enough
to get in your way.
But you're rich. You have everything.
You have power.
Can't you show us a little mercy?
Mrs. Mookmanee, cornering us like this
is the same as killing us alive.
So you're recording this.
She's not recording. It's live.
There are over a thousand viewers.
If your banking partners see this,
it'll be bad.
Only a thousand people?
I know a thousand people
can't do anything to you.
But there has to be someone
among them who hates you.
You think doing this
is smart?
I just want you
to withdraw the lawsuit against Petch.
Loyal but stupid.
People like you have ruined
so many bosses already, you know.
I'm not…
You're picking a fight with my mom?
- Ms. Mika.
- Let go.
- Mika.
Come here. Come here.
Let go of me.
Go.
Pakbung.
PARKING AREA
Put this on it, so it won't swell up.
It doesn't hurt as much
as when you slapped me that day.
Come on, Pakbung.
Can't you see?
What I did that day was to help you.
Help? By pretending you didn't know me?
Acting like you didn't recognize
your own kid?
I had to.
I'm working for Mrs. Mookmanee now.
She's my boss. I don't want trouble.
How much is she paying you?
- Why are you asking?
- How much?
Hey, Pakbung. I don't have much either.
I'm living paycheck to paycheck too.
I'm asking
because I want to know how much money
it took to buy fatherhood from you.
Tens of thousands? Hundreds of thousands?
If it's less than that, that's disgusting.
Dumping your kids for a few thousand.
Okay, Pakbung. It's my fault.
I didn't dare go to you
and your brother because of this.
I'm not a good man.
I can't provide for a family.
You can hate me all you want.
But don't waste your tears
on trash like me anymore.
Just live our own lives.
I'll go now. Okay. Goodbye.
That only worked on me
when I was in eighth grade.
You're still a little kid--
Enough. Stop acting.
You can go be with whoever you want,
wherever you want. I don't care anymore.
But you still have to take responsibility
for the debt you created.
What are you gonna do?
I won't do anything. But Mr. Song might.
What the heck is this?
Being poor isn't enough.
My dad even ditched me too.
In this life or the next,
don't ever let me see you again.
Mika.
- Come here.
- Hey.
Let me go.
You're trying to ruin my mom's reputation?
What do you want?
What? Hey.
That's my phone.
You punks. Let me go!
You bastard. I said let me go.
I'm going to use the media
to bring all of you down!
Hey, you know what makes us different?
I have friends with power, not cowards
who cry all the time or swallow pills
to kill themselves like your friend.
And I have a mother who backs me up,
who cleans up every problem for me.
You know what it all starts with?
Money.
Hey, don't move.
I'm gonna use the media to…
Get up.
Come here.
Mr. Trai.
Watch out!
Let's go.
Let's go. Get up.
Run.
- My phone.
- Let her go.
Does it hurt?
How did you know Mrs. Mookmanee
was at my dad's company?
That brat posted it on Instagram.
So you went in alone
without thinking it through?
Pakbung, don't do that again.
Don't confront
Mrs. Mookmanee head-on like that.
How could I just do nothing?
Petch almost died.
And then they came after me too.
My phone.
My phone… They recorded me.
I'll use it as evidence,
post it, expose all of them.
Mika took it.
She's rich, and she still steals my phone?
It cost over 10,000.
Don't think having a clip
means you can take them down.
Like your livestream earlier today.
Mrs. Mookmanee's legal team
already handled it.
How can she be that untouchable?
It's not much. She owns shares
in both major and minor media outlets.
She's got friends who own mobile networks.
And she has connections with the CEO
of the app you livestreamed on earlier.
Damn it!
That's exactly what you looked like
trying to fight Mrs. Mookmanee.
You almost broke your leg,
but the table leg barely moved.
There has to be a way. Right now,
we need to calm down and think together.
We?
I didn't tell anyone you were here.
I knew it.
100,000 or 200,000 can't buy you.
If it was 400,000 or 500,000,
I might consider it.
Take that.
You didn't run back home
on your own, did you?
You think I left you?
Maybe you got bored playing poor.
It was probably at Mika's birthday party.
Lee and Prarop must've figured out
where I was. That's how they found me.
I saved your life once.
Today, you saved mine.
We're even.
From now on, it's just friendship.
Heart for heart. Nothing owed.
Deal.
But the 100,000 you gave me,
consider it a gift then.
A gift, my ass.
Hey.
You're still greedy. Come here.
Be gentle.
You're so tough, huh?
Get up.
Go ahead.
- Trai?
- What the hell?!
I've got work this afternoon.
Look after Petch for me.
Yeah, of course.
Petch has helped me a lot.
Back when I didn't have a job,
he was the one who gave me jobs.
I'm just scared that if he finds out
all his gigs got canceled…
He can't find out.
How long can we keep it hidden?
That woman won't let us go.
She sued us, and on top of that,
she got all of Petch's work canceled too.
So we really can't fight them at all?
Revenge is for people with power.
Then we need power first
if we want to fight them, right?
But before you get power,
you need money first.
When's the next doctor's appointment?
Next week, Boss.
Pakbung!
You! Stop.
No! Don't get ahead of me!
Our speed isn't the same.
Don't go before me.
Where do you think you're going?
You won't get away.
- You…
- Boss.
What?
- Why am I so screwed?
- Hey.
Hey, hey.
Heaven really doesn't favor the guilty.
In the end, we met here.
Where are you going?
What happened?
Are you hurt?
I am. It hurts a lot.
- Could you drop me off just up ahead?
- Yes.
Did it hit her?
No, no. It didn't.
Where are you taking
my beloved little sister?
You. Hey.
You can drop me off here. Thank you.
You're still hurt, aren't you?
You!
I'll take you home.
You're Mr. Trai's brother.
- That's all you remember?
- You're on Mrs. Mookmanee's side.
Are you going to kill me?
They're your father's creditors, right?
Mrs. Mookmanee sent you
to dig into me, didn't she?
One should be responsible
for the debts they create.
Why don't you just tell them
where your father is?
So you want to know about my dad?
Actually, you still worry
about your father, don't you?
Yes, the numbers might drop
next year. But let's see
whether they still haven't gone up yet,
- or if it's stuck at a 2.3% return.
- Dad.
What is this flight ticket?
It's the original plan.
You'll go train with Mr. Jim.
- No, it's not.
- It's not my plan. It never was.
Don't you dare chop me again.
No, Mr. Trai. I'm just escorting you out.
Just a moment. Hey, get out.
Can't you see I'm working?
We need to talk, Dad.
Mr. Tritot is having a meeting
with investors right now.
Get out. Can't you see I'm working?
- Yes.
- I'm not flying anywhere.
You can't force me.
Yes. That's right.
Trai!
Go after him.
Yes, sir.
- To my mother's house.
- Yes, ma'am.
Trai.
If you're not getting out, shut the door.
Mr. Trai! Where is he?
- He's in the car.
- Mr. Trai!
Mr. Trai. Hey, Mr. Trai!
Mr. Trai.
So you've lived around here
your whole life?
No. I used to live in Heaven.
I was an angel.
You're still funny as always.
What do you want?
You really don't remember me?
Don't follow me! Get out of the way!
You! Where are you running to?!
I'll kill you!
Pakbung, Noy's getting crazy again.
- Help me. Take him!
- You're dead!
Pakbung.
Pakbung!
You ungrateful son.
You're more shameless than I thought.
I hate you, Dad.
You fought with your dad again?
This will probably be the last time.
He finally set me free.
Now they have matching phone cases?
What do you want from me?
Why are you being this stupid?
My head hurts, not my leg.
Why are you holding me?
Can't I take care of you for once?
The other day, you were kicking me out.
Today, you're happy I'm here?
How can someone change overnight, Dad?
Mr. Trai!
You think I sent someone to kill you?
That makes sense, doesn't it?
And where did you hide the evidence?
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon