- Do you want to try dating me, Mr. Trai?
- Huh?
You asked Mr. Trai to be your boyfriend?!
Yeah.
I'm giving you my body.
Then I'll be your gift too.
I want her to hurt.
It'd be even better if she just died.
Rachen!
Please take care of Rachen for me, okay?
You're Mr. Trai's girlfriend.
How could he tell you
to care for another man?
You two are not
just friends anymore, are you?
If Mr. Trai
really steps aside for Mr. Rachen…
I've got someone to take care of me.
- Here I am. I'm here.
- Pakbung?
Trai told me he won't take
anything from me anymore.
That probably includes you.
But I'm not anyone else. I'm…
You're what?
One day, you'll get hurt, like I did.
I've prepared a warm bath for you already.
It's okay.
You sure you can bathe by yourself?
And if I can't, will you help me?
There'd be an extra charge.
150,000 to bathe you.
500,000 for me to go into the tub.
That's more like the Pakbung I know.
When you came in,
you looked really irritated.
I am irritated.
But I have to separate
work from personal matters.
Very good. I like this version of you.
Focused on money, cheerful,
being yourself,
not tying your happiness
or suffering to anyone.
Right.
Tying it only to money is already good.
Thank you.
Rachen, are you…
Pakbung. You bitch.
- Mika.
- Hey.
Mika, Mika, let go.
Let go!
- Mika.
- So you came
all the way here to seduce him?
Mika, let her go.
I said let go.
You said you were badly injured.
How could you even sleep with her?
Your mind's always in the gutter.
No one stoops as low as you do.
You come in and start insulting people.
Are you crazy?
You psycho! That hurts!
- Hey!
- You hurt me too.
Wanna see whose scalp is tougher?
Huh?!
You wanna try me?
I've got hands and feet too, you know!
Pakbung, stop!
- You crazy bitch!
- Pakbung! Darin, help stop them. Now.
I can't. I'm scared.
Then go get Trai. Hurry.
Trai, hurry!
Hey, Pakbung.
- Stop!
- Pakbung, stop.
- Let go!
- Stop!
- Stop, Pakbung.
- You're ganging up?
You're ganging up on me? I'll tell my mom.
You're good at running to your mom.
You suck at fighting
but are great at running to mommy?
I said stop!
She started it!
Pakbung, I said stop!
Mika, there's nothing
between me and Pakbung.
She's just here to care for me
as an employee.
‪Rachen, why?
‪Why are you protecting her again?
- You've already slept with her, right?
- Mika.
Listen to me. Calm down and listen to me!
I'm the one who asked Pakbung
to take care of Rachen myself.
There's nothing to be jealous about.
And Rachen would never
cross the line with Pakbung
because Pakbung is my girlfriend.
And if you have a problem with Pakbung,
then you have a problem with me too.
- And what are you gonna do about it?
- Wanna try me?
Wait. Where are you going?
You're really going
to let Pakbung go home alone?
She just had a fight with Mika.
Her mother won't let this go.
I already had Prarop
take her home and keep watch over her.
Prarop alone isn't enough.
I'm going myself.
You're not fully recovered, are you?
So you're more worried about my feelings
than your own girlfriend's?
Pakbung already told me she's dating you.
But you didn't tell me
because you were afraid
of hurting my feelings.
You're willing to sacrifice for me,
but you don't care about Pakbung at all?
I…
You can't take care of Pakbung,
just like you couldn't take care of Dad.
You can't take care of anyone, Trai.
So, step aside. I'll handle it myself.
I never intended
to let go of Pakbung for you.
Didn't you tell me you wouldn't take
anything from me ever again?
Have you forgotten?
I haven't.
But I'm not taking anything,
because Pakbung was never yours.
Go rest until you're better.
About my relationship,
I'll take care of it myself.
What a shame I wasn't there yesterday.
I could've helped you pull
that rich girl's hair.
So what did Mr. Trai say?
Nothing. He just had
Mr. Prarop take me home.
We didn't even talk.
You got beaten up like that,
and he didn't even comfort you?
Comfort me? He only scolded me more,
like I was the one who started it.
He's probably worried about you.
But of all people,
you had to get into it with Mika.
You know how scary her mother is, right?
After this,
Mrs. Mookmanee
definitely won't let you off easy.
I'm screwed. What have I done?
Ugh, realizing it now is too late.
Hey, don't be scared.
She probably
won't send someone to kill us…
I guess.
Oh, my.
Weapons? Weapons.
Oh, what's that sound?
- Hey, take it.
- Okay.
Take it.
Yeah.
Go.
What?!
What is this?
Are you rehearsing for a performance?
Shooting content?
What content?
These are weapons for self-defense.
Yeah.
We're afraid Mrs. Mookmanee
might send someone to hurt Pakbung.
No way. I stayed on watch all night.
No suspicious people at all.
Why are you here?
To clear things up.
- Wait. She's not saying okay yet.
- Okay.
I want to talk to Mr. Trai alone.
Do you want to talk first, or should I?
You came here, so you start.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for yelling at you
when you fought with Mika.
I'm sorry for being hesitant
about our status in front of Darin.
And I'm sorry for making it look like
I was handing you over to Rachen.
I'm truly sorry about the last part.
I cared too much about Rachen's feelings,
and I forgot about yours.
Can you forgive me?
10 baht's worth of gold
and I'll stop being mad at you.
Pakbung.
Can you be serious for once?
I don't want to be serious.
Being serious hurts.
Pakbung…
Yesterday, I didn't like myself.
I couldn't control anything,
like my emotions depended on what you did.
I felt awful.
Even if I'm not mad at you anymore today,
if being with you makes me
dislike myself again,
then I think we should reconsider
our relationship status.
See? I told you.
I don't want to be serious.
Pakbung.
Thank you for being honest with me.
I understand you better now.
I won't make you feel bad again.
Give me a chance, Pakbung.
POINT-COLLECTING CARD
A point-collecting card?
Yes.
Whenever I do something good for you,
or you make me happy,
I'll put one of these stickers
in this box.
When it reaches ten stars,
there's a grand prize,
whatever you want to ask for.
Anything at all?
And if I make you angry
or you make me sad,
then we put one of these,
an angry-faced sticker.
You already made me upset.
But I'm not counting this time.
But if there's a next time,
I'll keep adding them
until it reaches ten, and then…
Don't you dare say we'll break up.
You'll have to pay me as your apology.
Fine.
Then I'll pay you with…
my heart.
What am I, some ghoul?
Keep your heart.
I want money.
Money. Money. Money. And money.
Got it?
- Money?
- Yes.
Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Why are you carrying me?
You want money?
Then I'll pay you with… my body.
Hey.
Hey! Get off me.
You want me to put
an angry-face sticker or what?
I want a star sticker from you more.
Thank you for understanding me.
It's not like I wanted
to break up with you.
How could I?
I still haven't gotten a single baht.
Pakbung…
It's true.
So money is all you care about, huh?
Money, huh?
- Pakbung, huh?
- Hey.
- Huh?
- You wanna fight?
- You only care about money?
- No.
That's not it.
Should we invite monks
to perform a big merit-making ceremony?
Something bad always happens here.
It's totally déjà vu.
How many times will we have
to clean this place up before we can open?
Ugh, you're not even old yet.
Stop complaining.
I'm not complaining. I'm just saying.
Yes?
I didn't call you.
Come help lift this table.
You complain too much.
You can't lift it alone?
Mr. Trai.
Yes?
Whose phone is this?
That's Rachen's.
How many phones does Mr. Rachen have?
Just this one.
But when he was in the hospital, he said
it was broken, so I bought him a new one.
I couldn't contact Mr. Rachen all night,
so I tracked his phone signal.
If Mr. Rachen only has one phone,
which is this one,
then how could he say that day
that he tracked Mr. Rachen's phone
and found him at the hospital?
Wait. Who are you talking about?
Rut.
Mr. Rachen, you're feeling better now?
I tried to visit you so many times,
but Mr. Trai wouldn't let me in.
I'm better now.
Were there any updates while I was away?
I investigated the stock
buying and selling like you asked.
I found a list of suspects.
I'm still digging into
whether it connects to Mrs. Mookmanee.
Is that why you got shot?
It's possible.
The police are investigating.
The police still
haven't identified the shooter?
How long have you been
working for me, Rut?
Next month will be three years.
Three years already?
Time flies.
We're together almost every day,
yet I don't know anything about you.
If you're free tonight,
let's go out to eat.
I want to get to know you better.
What do you need me for, Mrs. Mookmanee?
I remember you are Rachen's secretary.
I didn't care…
until I found out you were more than that.
I'm not sure what you mean.
Even if you destroyed the safe house
you were hiding in,
my people still tracked you down.
Doing everything alone all this time…
you're pretty skilled.
I have work to do.
If there's nothing else, please excuse me.
I want to support you, Rut.
Someone as capable as you
could go much further with a sponsor.
You want to hire me?
Name your price.
Money is not a big deal for me.
Thank you for the offer,
but you've misunderstood.
I'm not doing this for money.
Not for money?
So you're suspicious of me too, Trai?
Pakbung picked a fight with me.
She crossed the line again.
You said you'd help me.
You haven't done anything at all.
I called you, and you didn't even pick up.
If you're not actually going to help,
don't come offering yourself.
Hey! Stop rambling already!
You…
I'm sorry.
I've been under a lot of stress lately.
Ever since Mr. Rachen got shot,
everything's been chaotic.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry as well
for taking it out on you.
As for Pakbung,
I'm going to deal with her for you.
I just haven't found the right timing yet.
But if you help me,
it might make things easier.
How?
They're holding the event
at two branches at the same time.
- Yes.
- For the Bangna branch,
they only want staff,
so I'll send Niuniu and Samlee there.
For the Bang Yai branch,
they need an event organizer
and someone to run the cue,
so I was thinking I'd go with Pakbung.
So we have to split up, Petch?
Mr. Trai hired us to stay with Pakbung
all the time, you know.
I understand that.
But honestly,
my schedule's been light lately,
so when this job came in,
I had to take it.
If it weren't so last-minute,
I wouldn't bother you guys at all.
Bother us? Come on.
Don't forget.
I'm your company's partner too.
Your work is basically my money.
Of course, I'll do it.
You might not know this,
but your secretary
forged all
of his job application documents.
No one seems to be living at that address.
So I checked his educational background
with the university.
No one named Rut
graduated in the year he claimed.
As for his past employers,
they admitted they were hired
to lie for him.
From what I suspected, the culprit
must be extremely skilled in IT.
But I didn't think he'd be good enough to
fake records and identities this cleanly.
So you think Rut is the culprit.
Even if he doesn't have a scar on his
wrist, he's the most suspicious one now.
That day, I only saw the attacker's eyes,
so I wasn't sure.
Yesterday,
I tried inviting Rut out to talk,
but he didn't show up.
That's when I started to think it's him.
Do you know where Rut is right now?
Thanks.
You really think you can protect her?
WE DIDN'T FINISH IT LAST TIME.
GOT THE GUTS TO FACE ME YOURSELF?
OR ARE YOU ONLY GOOD AT HIDING
UNDER YOUR MOM'S SKIRT?
Pakbung.
IF YOU'RE THAT TOUGH, COME MEET ME.
You're challenging me?
We're here.
Are you sure this is the place, Petch?
This isn't a closed restaurant,
it's just an abandoned hotel.
Uh… but this is where the pin shows.
Let me call the client again.
Sorry, the number you have dialed
cannot be reached at this time.
I can't get through.
I think this isn't the place.
We should leave.
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go.
Pakbung.
Ms. Mika?
Hey!
So you lured me here just to slap me?
You're still not done?
Yeah, I'm not done. You were the one
who texted and challenged me.
How dare you?
You rotten pakbung.
- Stop, please.
- Hey.
- Petch, take Pakbung and run!
- Pakbung, go.
- Let go of me!
- Let's go.
- Pakbung!
Hurry up.
Pakbung, watch out!
Pakbung!
Pakbung! Follow her!
Come on.
Pakbung, where are you? Pakbung!
Pakbung!
Mr. Rut?
Mr. Rachen asked me
to come take care of you.
This way, please.
My car is parked just up ahead.
Pakbung, what's wrong?
My stomach hurts, Petch.
Oh, what should we do?
Want me to carry you on my back?
I can just pick you up. Come on.
Mr. Rut.
My stomach hurts. I really can't walk.
Can you go get the car
and pick us up here?
Stop bullshitting, Pakbung.
Why would you talk like that?
Petch!
Hey. Pakbung…
- Pakbung.
- Petch!
Petch, hang in there.
Hello. Someone's been shot.
Mr. Trai, Prarop's calling.
Pakbung…
What?
Pakbung.
Mr. Trai.
You shot Petch.
What do you want? Why did you shoot him?!
He was in the way.
Mr. Rachen would never order
something like this.
Mrs. Mookmanee hired you, didn't she?
Do you think everyone in this world
is money-hungry like you, Pakbung?!
Then what do you want?
You've been trying
to kill Mr. Trai all along.
Mika said I sent her those messages,
but I didn't send anything!
That was you, wasn't it?!
You planned everything, didn't you?
Don't tell me you kidnapped me
to use me as bait
and lure Trai here.
Wow, so damn smart.
Too bad
you figured it out a little too late.
What did Mr. Trai ever do to you?
Figure it out yourself.
Think, think, think.
He hurt you, didn't he?
That's why you hate him this much.
Stop asking so many damn questions!
You're annoying the hell out of me!
I don't want to die. I'm scared.
Poor you…
There, there.
Don't be scared.
Mr. Trai will come save you.
He'll come save you.
You already called him?
Not yet. Why rush it?
Let him suffer,
search for you for a day or two.
Then I'll call him. Sounds good?
Good?
Does that sound good? Sounds good?
You psychopath.
This is nothing compared to what Trai
and Tritot did to me. Remember that.
You're cunning. I shouldn't let you live.
Damn it!
Pakbung!
You just love sticking your nose
where it doesn't belong.
If you'd stayed out of it,
you wouldn't have to die.
But you had to get involved with Trai.
You were in my way.
Even if you die, I can still use
your corpse to lure Trai here.
Right?
Hey!
Mr. Trai.
I've set your phone
to share your location with mine.
And here.
I saved my number
as your emergency contact.
If anything happens, press this button.
Your phone will immediately
send an SOS message to me.
My stomach hurts, Petch.
Oh, what should we do?
Want me to carry you on my back?
It's him. He's the attacker.
He's going to kill you!
I know. I know.
I'm here now. I'm here to help.
Don't be scared, Pakbung.
Lee!
Come here!
Pakbung.
What do you want? What did I ever do?
Why did you kill my father?
You're the one who killed my parents.
What the hell are you talking about?
When did I ever kill them?
When you got drunk and drove, Trai.
Don't you remember?
My dad was the scapegoat
who went to jail for you.
You're Uncle Rat's son?
Don't. Don't.
Don't!
No.
If you hate me or are angry at me,
then take it out on me alone!
Don't play hero.
All of you are going to die.
Lee and Pakbung have nothing
to do with this. Let them go.
Why?
You can't stand seeing the people you love
get hurt?!
And what about me?!
I had to watch the people I loved die!
How do you think I felt?!
My mom died because of your money.
When my dad found out,
he wasted away in prison and died.
You people are selfish to the core.
Whoever lives or dies, you never care.
It's still hot, Son. Here.
Thank you, Dad.
And this too.
- Your favorite shrimp paste dip.
- Thank you, Mom.
You two should eat too.
You keep serving me everything.
Eat a lot. Exams are coming up.
You'll need energy to study.
Yes, Mom.
I'll save a big meal
for the day you graduate.
You're gonna be so hungry.
It won't be long.
Our Rut is smart.
I couldn't afford
to send you to a good school,
but you worked hard
and earned a scholarship yourself.
If all I can do is pick the meat
off the fish for you, why wouldn't I?
Then I'll graduate quickly and find a job,
so you both can finally live comfortably.
My parents weren't rich,
but they never let me suffer.
When I was with them, I was so happy.
But then my dad got a new job,
driving for your father.
The pay was higher.
It looked like life would get better,
but it didn't!
Rut, your dad's calling.
Yes, Dad?
Go to bed first, Rut. Don't wait for me.
Tonight, I don't think I can come home.
But Dad, you said you'd eat with me
on my graduation day.
I want to celebrate with you,
but what can I do?
Mr. Tritot is still working.
If the boss isn't done,
how can I go home first?
I have to go now, Son.
On an important day my dad had waited for,
he couldn't come because of your father.
Your father worked him morning to night.
Why?!
Why do you think just because you're rich
that you're above everyone else?
You're just rich.
You think you can order anyone to die
or go to prison for you? Bastard!
You know, my family was my only happiness.
And you,
you and your father took that from me.
Who gave you the right?! Who gave you
the right to destroy my happiness?
Rut, it's my fault. I admit it, all of it.
Just let everyone go.
No! Don't show your face now.
It's too late.
I don't want anything from you.
But I'll make you understand that
even if I'm not rich or have money
like you, I can still destroy your life.
I'm going to kill everyone you love.
Don't, Rut. No. Don't. Rut.
Don't! Don't, Rut!
Don't!
Pakbung.
Someone's injured here.
Why did you kill my father, you bastard?!
Why did you kill my father?!
You piece of shit!
You scum! Why did you do that?!
Why, Rut?! Why did you do that?!
Why did you kill my father?
You bastard! Let go of me!
Please calm down.
- Please calm down.
- Let go!
Let go!
Please don't blame yourself, Mr. Trai.
Everything is all my fault.
How could I be so stupid?
He was right by my side all along,
and I never once suspected him.
You're okay, right?
I thought the attacker
was someone who hated Be Rich
or Dad's business.
But all of this was because of me.
Uncle Rat worked for Dad for years,
but we never really knew his family.
Just like Rut.
He worked for me for so long,
yet I never really knew him either.
If anyone is to blame, it's all of us.
Aren't you going to blame me at all?
I'm the reason…
that Dad died.
You're already falling apart
just by blaming yourself, right?
When you're better, then I'll blame you.
Go take care of Pakbung.
She's waiting for you.
Please wait here for a moment.
Okay.
Don't you want to stay overnight
for observation?
I'm really not that badly hurt.
The nurse said I can rest at home.
‪Sit down.
How are Petch and Mr. Lee?
Petch lost a lot of blood,
but we got him to the hospital in time.
He's safe now. As for Lee,
the bullet missed any critical organs.
A few days of rest and he'll be fine.
Prarop, please look after Lee for me.
Of course.
I'm sorry, Pakbung.
You got hurt because of me again.
You weren't the one who hurt me.
- Let it be!
Here.
Om.
Bad luck, be gone.
Spirit, come back. Spirit, come home.
May all your suffering and sorrow be gone.
He's going to get worse
because of your ritual.
Don't jinx it!
These are star gooseberry leaves
and soap pods.
Tradition says they ward off evil spirits.
And this is holy water from nine temples.
Honestly, he's supposed to bathe in it.
Yeah, and you should too.
Come on.
What if it infects the wound?
Right. Good point.
Then, let's do a fake sprinkle for now.
Om…
Let it be!
Don't make me laugh.
My stitches will split.
Does it still hurt?
On and off.
Don't make that face.
I'm actually glad we survived.
Let's say we paid off some bad karma.
From now on,
only good things should come our way.
In that case,
you should buy lottery tickets this draw.
You'll win for sure.
Yeah.
Yeah…
Does that mean you have lucky numbers?
No.
It's just that earlier today,
the police came to question me.
They asked
who contacted me
about the job at the restaurant.
Wasn't it Mr. Rut?
But the caller was a woman.
Her name was… Rujee.
When the police
traced the number,
they said no such person existed.
Rujee…
Rut… Oh?
Those names are similar.
Could they be siblings?
Or could it have been Ms. Mika's voice?
No.
The voice sounded older.
Then who was that?
Mom, how was I supposed to know
that Rut was the son of that driver?
Oh, he was planning to kill Trai too.
How would I know? I shouldn't have called
to tell you this at all.
I already said I didn't know.
I don't know, I don't know,
I don't know anything.
Use this new SIM
to call and hire Pakbung for the job.
I…
I'll tell you exactly what to say.
Trust me.
No one will know it was you.
RUT
DELETE
MOVE TO TRASH
Darin.
Did you know Rut's been arrested?
Rut? Your secretary? Arrested for what?
How close are you to Rut?
I only know him as your secretary.
But you called him more often than I did.
And only your number is in his phone.
He was hitting on me. But I wasn't
interested. I just felt sorry for him.
Felt sorry?
So you called
and tricked Petch into that job?
Tricked? What are you talking about?
Then you should know Petch was shot.
Luckily, Petch regained consciousness.
Otherwise,
you'd be charged as an accomplice
to attempted murder.
What nonsense are you spewing?
Accomplice to attempted murder?
I told you I don't know anything.
Mr. Rachen,
are you and Pakbung
here to pick a fight with me?
Why do you hate me so much?
Why are you accusing me like this?
I've had enough!
Darin.
We don't have any solid evidence
that Ms. Darin
worked with Rut.
Do you think Trai won't believe us?
Pakbung,
Trai's not stupid.
Come on.
Pakbung, what's wrong?
Does it hurt?
It's swollen. Does Trai know about this?
He already took me to the hospital.
Pakbung,
that's not what I asked.
I asked whether Trai knows
your ankle is injured too.
Just the cuts and bruises
on my face and body
already make him feel terrible.
If he knew about my leg too,
he'd never stop blaming himself.
Pakbung,
you care about Trai so much
that you don't care about yourself?
If Mr. Trai's upset, I'm upset too.
So please do this for me.
Don't tell Mr. Trai about this.
So Rut was arrested?
What a shame.
I thought he'd be more capable than that.
Please don't come in yet.
- Trai.
- You can't come in yet.
I won't waste time with pleasantries.
Where's your daughter?
This is a summons.
It's for Miss Khemika ChairatIttanawong.
We'll need to ask her
to come give a statement at the station.
On what charge, exactly?
Here.
You rotten pakbung.
- Stop, please.
- Hey.
Please stop.
It's just kids fighting.
Why blow it up into something so serious?
It's not just a fight.
Miss Khemika may also be connected
to an attempted murder case.
Attempted murder?
Wow, really? Are you genuinely shocked
or just pretending?
You usually know everything,
but this time, you didn't know
what your daughter did?
Do you think
something this small can touch me?
Watch yourself.
Oh, of course.
But don't waste your threats on me.
Use your time and energy
to deal
with your precious daughter instead…
if you even can.
Mom.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
You wanna party with me, right?
Party! Party! Let's dance.
- Dance, dance.
- Mika. Mika.
Get a grip.
What trouble did you cause?
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want to tell you.
I wanted to slap her.
Slap her till she's dead.
Do you understand, Mom?
- Take Mika home.
- I'm not going.
- Hey, I said I'm not going!
- Come on, miss.
- I said no.
- Go, Mika.
Let go!
DUANGKHAE RUEANGWICHAN
RAT RUEANGWICHAN
It took me a long time to come
and apologize to you, Uncle.
But I'm sorry for everything
that happened to your family.
I'm sorry.
Take it.
Yeah.
Don't zone out, handsome guy.
I'm hungry.
Feed me, please.
What're you staring at? Toss it.
Toss it again, please.
I'm waiting.
That's not me. That's my friend.
Wait, so which one is you then?
That one.
Throw it this way. Come on.
Ah, toss it.
Delicious!
More, more, more.
What did you season it with? Wait.
Here.
Put your regret,
your sadness, your pain, into this.
Okay, now throw it.
Throw it. Throw it far, far away.
Throw your bitterness
into the water.
Don't hold onto it.
What if it gets moldy?
Your hand's gonna rot, you know.
Throw it.
If I throw it, will I really feel better?
No idea.
But at least…
we'll be full.
Throw it. What are you waiting for?
Throw it already.
Like that. Look.
Far away! Go!
Toss it up to the sky,
let it fall into the water. Yummy.
More, more, more.
You're done feeding the fish.
Don't forget to feed the human too.
What do you want to eat?
- BBQ.
Hey.
You're crazy. You read my mind.
Then should we go now?
I'll use the bathroom for a sec.
Wait here.
- Alright?
- Yes, sir!
I'll wait right here.
I put ointment on,
but the swelling still won't go down.
Pakbung, let's go.
Wow. That was fast.
Didn't want you waiting too long.
- Did you wash your hands?
- Not yet.
Hey? Oh?
Kidding. I washed them.
Why isn't she back yet?
Pakbung.
Weren't you with Trai?
Why are you back alone?
Where is Trai?
I told him myself
he didn't need to walk me home.
I bought something for you.
Let me see your ankle.
Mr. Rachen?
It's really swollen.
Rachen, what are you doing?
Mr. Trai…
You forgot the food you bought for Kanah.
Thank you.
Why are you here? What's up?
Didn't I tell you to take care of her?
- I am taking care of her.
- You sure?
Mr. Trai took great care of me.
He took me to make merit, we ate,
full of blessings, full of food.
So, who's protecting who here, exactly?
Wait, you're here
to catch me doing something wrong?
Let me ask you something.
You're with Pakbung,
but where's your mind?
What are you talking about?
You can't stop thinking about Rut.
You're obsessed with the past, and you
forget to care for the person beside you.
You didn't take care of Pakbung at all.
That's enough. Mr. Rachen.
Mr. Trai, I'll walk you to the car.
One second, Pakbung.
- Pakbung.
Are you okay?
Come on.
You're out of chances now, Trai.
Get out of my house!
Get out!
Can I come back and live here?
I'll give you a lump sum,
enough for you to get back on your feet.
But you have to move out of my house.
If you're going to stab me in the back,
do it cleanly.
Don't let me catch you.
But if we let this go,
Mrs. Mookmanee will gain even more power.
If you all still let Mr. Trai
remain the majority shareholder,
I will withdraw all my shares myself.
You're still money hungry as always.
I care about money,
and you only care about yourself.
We have nothing left to talk about.
I want Trai to trust me,
for us.
He's a murderer,
but I can't do anything to him.
It's really Rut.
How did he get out of prison?
I'm gonna kill you, Rut!
Let go!
I'll consider you one of Tritot's sons
and your life's going to be ruined too.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon