[Insider]
[All people, places, organizations, and incidents
appearing in this series are entirely fictional.]
Are you going to scream if I take that off of you?
Please take Jin Soo Mi as far as possible and let her go.
And you?
The guy who picked us out while we were tailing Kim Yo Han.
I caught him while sniffing around Seongju Prison, as you said.
Attorney Koo Bon Chul.
He visits his client once a week.
There's an inmate named Do Won Bong.
Do you know him?
A long time ago...
But still, Yo Han...
A person shouldn't fight with a bear.
Kim Yo Han was going to get at Do Won Bong.
Even if it's only during hibernation...
Do you know anything?
He was going to attack the Dosan-ro White Bear.
But...
the fact that Kim Yo Han got released on time
means Kim Yo Han is working under Do Won Bong now.
Then does that mean Yoon Byung Wook is running into trouble with Do Won Bong?
A chief prosecutor is...
connected to a loan shark rotting in jail?
So you're a prosecutor?
Won Bong.
I heard you have a brain tumor.
Yes.
You're a better actor than I thought.
I heard you requested the suspension of execution.
You can request that at any time.
But why now?
Because I'm in much physical pain.
Not because of The Skin Nation?
You got a job for our Yo Han.
Is he Attorney Koo Bon Chul's intern or something?
When you go down to Daejeon soon,
it will have nothing to do with you, Chief Prosecutor.
What's going on between you
and Chief Prosecutor Yoon Byung Wook?
Why don't you ask him yourself if you're so curious?
They're on the same boat.
Do Won Bong is on the same side with Yoon Byung Wook.
Why?
Suspension of execution.
He's trying to come out of prison and take Chairman Yang's position.
And not for The Skin Nation
but he seems to be going for the Goldman Casino seat.
Bring me a baseball pitching machine.
Jin Soo Mi.
I'm not a bad guy.
I'll let you go. I will, but...
let me ask you something I'm curious about.
At the Goldman Casino,
how much do they make a year laundering money?
Turn on the machine.
Quiet.
[Died during Shin Dal Soo murder investigation]
[Kim Yo Han's grandmother, dies near Paldang Bridge]
[Did he kill Shin Dal Soo?]
Send me to a hospital.
Something's wrong with my leg.
I don't feel anything since earlier.
Since when?
I have no personal vendetta against you.
I just got my money
and I'm doing my job.
Not that.
How long have you been sick?
Did you get any sleep?
Will you stay?
Should I leave?
Well, it doesn't matter.
Then I'll watch.
It's not my revenge, but
it's finally starting.
Fess up.
What?
That you killed my grandma.
I was also behind bars when your grandma passed away.
Chairman Do told you to do it.
Did Do Won Bong say that to you?
Why would he say that...
We can have a three-way confrontation then.
Min Ho recorded it. Woo Min Ho.
You remember Woo Min Ho, right?
You know. The kid you kidnapped with Woo Sang Ki.
Who?
No!
That's not true at all!
Come on! I'm serious!
It's true.
I saw your call history
and you've been in contact with Hong Jae Sun a lot.
In front of the Seoul Northern District Prosecutor's Office.
Geez, this is nuts!
Geez, it wouldn't feel so unfair if I actually did that.
Well, actually...
Actually, that day...
That's what I'm saying!
But you know...
I did promise a sunbae in my organization...
So, you'll leave that supermarket just like that?
If she dies, it becomes yours.
Prosecutor Hong said that your grandma's supermarket will be
worth top dollars due to redevelopment.
He did mention I should scare her and take the supermarket away from her.
But then I saw your grandma there that day.
Then she suddenly disappeared!
The person who kidnapped my dad and me...
It's the one who killed your grandmother.
So...
just fess up, Sun Oh.
If you keep your mouth shut like that, you could really lose that leg.
Not only your legs...
I'll send you to the hospital if you spill everything.
I promise.
On Min Ho's social media account,
it's recorded in detail how you killed my grandma.
Woo Min Ho...
I remember him now.
But...
he died, though.
There's no witness now...
and there are only a few posts that the kid uploaded.
And what about this video clip?
What can you prove with this?
Stop it, you a**hole.
- Do you know who killed Kwon Dae Il?
- You.
Mok Jin Hyung killed him.
And that Lee Tae Gwang's USB you were desperately seeking in prison.
Do you know what's in it?
But the bulls***.
You'd better cut the bulls*** and untie me.
If I die, you'd never get to find out anything
and die by Do Won Bong or Yoon Byung Wook's hands.
I said just fess up to everything!
You'll never kill me!
Lately, for small brain tumors,
they don't have to open up your head, and are treatable by gamma-knife radiosurgery.
But since your condition is graver than that,
they'll open up your head and for about four to five hours,
they'll perform microsurgery. So, that will be...
the official statement by the specialist.
Since your blood pressure is normal
and you're very healthy,
you'll just get anesthesia and sleep for four to five hours tomorrow
and just leave. That's how I've arranged things.
Sounds good.
No news from Jang Sun Oh?
I think the battery has worn out now.*
(Meaning Jang Sun Oh's time is up)
Did he get caught?
Should I check on newly arrived unidentified corpses throughout hospitals?
Don't make a fuss. Just look for a new guy.
He's reached his limits on his usefulness.
We'll have lots to do going forward.
Don't be short on workers.
It's Kim Yo Han.
How about the money?
I secured the Goldman slush funds.
Chairman?
Yes. Good work.
It's all thanks to you, Chairman. But...
I finished work just now.
May I visit you at the hospital tomorrow?
Yeah, yes, yes, yes.
Yo Han...
Yes, Chairman?
I think I'll live 50 more years, all thanks to you.
Enduring is the true power.
Thanks for breathing life into me, who was dying away.
I'll see you tomorrow, sir.
Okay, okay.
Thank you...
Thank you.
And next is...
Chairman Do?
Look for two people.
Pardon?
Find one more person to work for us.
We should get rid of Kim Yo Han now, too.
The Skin Nation stocks that doubled as soon as it went public successfully on the 18th
is stabilizing in its value faster than expected.
Regarding this matter, the insiders
[Hello, Dosan Holdings: Account Balance 300 billion won]
are talking about selling the unofficial holdings by the biggest shareholder Chairman Yang Joon...
Where is Attorney Koo?
I believe he's still wrapping things up at the Seongju Prison.
The share structures show that Goldman Company owns 32%, Taepyeong Plaza owns 12%...
People at Seocho-dong...
must be desperately waiting for us.
So that we can gift them with what we promised,
pay off the balance.
Now, you can put the name Dosan Holdings there.
I got it.
Mr. Do Won Bong!
You fasted yesterday, right?
You didn't smoke, either, right?
Of course not. I've been waiting for this day for so long.
You'll soon enter the operating room.
So, don't be nervous. Just lie down and relax.
Yo Han...
After I get out of surgery,
it will be our world.
Let's have a big party, okay?
Yes.
All right...
[7 a.m.]
[3 p.m.]
The Skin Nation's stock share structure was announced.
Chairman Yang Joon of The Skin Nation owns 36%,
YH Holdings owns 26%, and
Malay Investments owns 14%,
[The Skin Nation's share value expected to hit 260 billion won]
and miscellaneous corporations make up 11%.
A total of 83% of majority shareholders
[The Skin Nation's Share Structure]
and the remaining 17% of minority shareholders make up the company ownership.
- How come Dosan Holdings isn't listed?
- A total of 83% of majority shareholders and...
- Chairman, are you okay?
- the remaining 17% of minority shareholders
make up the company ownership.
How about the balance?
I paid off the balance.
Oh, it won't be Dosan Holdings.
It will be called YH Holdings,
Malay Investments and...
miscellaneous corporations. I paid all the balance under those names.
YH Holdings?
I imitated what I had learned from you, Chairman.
YH Holdings...
I'm not good at naming things.
So I used my initials.
[Account transfer]
[Transferring funds / Transfer completed]
[Caythy Bank: Transferred to Kim Yo Han, 150 billion won]
[Caythy Bank: Kim Yo Han, Transferring to various accounts]
[All accounts under Kim Yo Han]
[Kim Yo Han]
Now, you can pay the balance on The Skin Nation under your corporate name.
Start buying.
500 million won.
Why did you do all this?
I'm out of prison now.
And all I learned there was how to run a gambling house.
So I think...
I could run a casino pretty well.
I thought I had crossed the bridge, but it looks like I'm still on the bridge.
Hey...
you have no inkling of what you've just done, huh?
You just told the elders at Sinseon-dong a big f*** you!
Attorney Koo is going to take care of all that for me.
Attorney Koo?
Oh, Attorney Koo...
will start working with me now.
Chairman,
Sinseon-dong wanted me to deliver a message to you.
What?
"You're...
fired from Sinseon-dong."
[Four hours ago]
Attorney Koo filled me in on the details.
I'll lead you inside.
You're returning to us what you stole
and asking us to pay extra for other options as well?
I believe you have it wrong.
What?
Manager Yang is the one who couldn't protect and manage that money
and I...
went through hell to get that money back to you.
So, what is it you want?
I heard that the Goldman Casino manager position goes to the most suitable person.
And?
Triad of Macau* was running the chairman election using the Goldman slush funds
(Macau mafia)
and they're stumped now that the money disappeared.
But if they find out Sinseon-dong's Go-to man got that money back,
you'll be able to get the votes from Macau as well.
I did not come here only to ask for Manager Yang's position.
If you would install me as the new Go-to man for Sinseon-dong,
I'll do...
my utmost best for you elders for the rest of my life.
The priority for Goldman slush funds is to support the Triad of Macau election. I mean...
that is such an absurd situation.
If I become the new Goldman Casino manager,
I'll prioritize investing...
into Sinseon-dong businesses.
Why do you seek to work for us?
I also...
want to hold the sword handle of the law.
I'll hold the sword handle of the law
and the f***ers who messed up my life this way...
Yoon Byung Wook, Yang Hwa,
Yang Joon,
Hong Sang Wook, Hong Jae Sun,
Mok Jin Hyung, and even Do Won Bong...
I will...
slaughter all these f***ers.
If all of you would allow me to get a hold of that handle,
I don't need...
I don't need anything else.
Th-that manager position...
It might look like it's sugar-coated on the outside, but
it's like food that's poisoned.
Those Seocho-dong morons you have to deal with...
They're not human. Those scumbags...
Those scumbags are the only ones who make money in all this.
With your head, they're no match for you.
You can't handle them!
More than anything, I will...
I'll never let you get to that position-
So...
what will you do then?
Chairman, you didn't get released. You got a suspension of execution.
You have to return to prison when you regain your health.
Isn't that it?
Mr. Do Won Bong, how do you feel?
Keep talking.
Looking perfectly healthy.
I'll give you some more painkillers.
Thank you.
You'll feel fine very soon.
Your visitors' hours are usually 6 p.m. to 8 p.m.
But one guardian can continue to stay with you.
Oh, come in!
Your nephew will be staying with you tonight.
So, don't worry and get some sleep.
Now, your life is...
up to my arithmetic.
But still, you've managed to come out.
Get plenty of rest.
If you need anything,
just tell the nephew.
Then, will you be personally taking care of finishing up Chairman Do?
He's lived a long time, and it's about time karma got to him.
He'll be taken care of naturally.
How about you, Yo Han?
Is Yang Hwa next for you?
Yang Hwa...
Yup.
Which hospital is Jang Sun Oh at?
Are you going to go?
No.
I'll just go over to CEO Oh's place.
Be careful.
You now know that your body doesn't belong to you, right?
I won't bring harm to Sinseon-dong.
Don't be shocked.
I didn't come here to kill you.
I'm sorry for causing concern all this time.
Do Won Bong has been fired by Sinseon-dong as of today. I'll leave him here.
Sinseon-dong's Go-to man has been changed to Kim Yo Han.
So, we have to get rid of Chairman Do today.
But I felt a little uneasy about you, Jang Sun Oh.
What about me?
[14 years ago]
- Geez!
- I got it.
You'll adopt the kid, Director Yang?
But that moron of a father
is asking a lot for the cost of the kid.
You're going to pay him?
What if I get rid of him, and the kid finds out later?
What?
You can't tell him he died, man.
You have to say that his dad abandoned him.
A person has to be lonely to look for someone to rely on.
Let's go.
Why?
No!
So that the kid will come with me.
A person...
has to be lonely to look for someone to rely on.
You know that Chairman Yang is looking for you, right?
You're not feeling well and also running out of time.
I'll step away for a moment.
This.
I took one from the hospital earlier just in case you might need it.
Why!
I said I'd share all the profits with you once I become the casino manager!
You don't have to live as Sinseon-dong's dog.
I said I'll help you, so you can lead a new life. So, why?
Once a dog, always a dog.
You know that people don't change.
You tried to have Jo Hae Do kill me.
You had lost Woo Sang Ki but pretended you hadn't and sent over Kim Yo Han.
What were you going to do after you got rid of me and took over the casino?
After that, were you going to drive out Sinseon-dong elders out of Goldman?
And after that...
you didn't want to become a manager again, but
become a Deep Pocket like them, didn't you?
That can't happen.
Dosan-ro White Bear played all the tricks,
but...
Kim Yo Han took all the money.
You go.
I'll go to Oh Soo Yeon and Kim Yo Han.
What are you talking about?
That woman must be with Kim Yo Han.
Our Chairman Yang, are you sure you won't make any mistakes?
Don't worry.
I'll bring her back alive.
Whether you kill her or not, you do what you want after that.
You don't have to listen to Attorney Koo.
H-he's mistaken about everything.
Right...
You said you were a casino manager at one point, right?
I guess Yang Joon and Yang Hwa...
had listened to you at one point.
Do you remember when we recruited Yo Han hyung?
Okay, 500.
Before I get older,
I decided to get rid of the two, Yang Joon and Yang Hwa.
Call.
Chairman Do, who doesn't know how to give up. What happened to you?
What do you want me to do?
A man named Woo Sang Ki
will enter the country soon.
So I kidnapped Woo Sang Ki and his son like that
and Yo Han came into the prison.
I heard Chief Prosecutor Yoon asked to get rid of that kid.
The kid was investigating him and got caught.
He's just a Judicial Institute Trainee...
Is that kid holding something over his head?
He was looking for the video that Lee Tae Gwang had filmed.
Lee Tae Gwang?
Oh, that Chairman Yang's underling you messed up?
What kind of video is it?
Hey, Tae Gwang.
Yes?
Go and exchange more money.
Well, how much?
Just enough.
Okay. Got it.
Well, Yang Joon alone gambled abroad.
But they got caught together, but Lee Tae Gwang only went to prison.
So I'm sure he felt it was unfair and got pissed off.
Then...
make that Kim Yo Han...
become one of us.
Excuse me?
But how?
A person is bound to look for someone to rely on when he's lonely.
I heard he has one family member left. So get rid of that person.
And only one person for him to rely on.
Prosecutor Mok Jin Hyung of Seoul Northern District Prosecutor's Office.
Make a video that makes him look like the killer
and send it to the detective in charge of the case.
Must you take it that far?
Just like you and me, we have to make him
rely on nothing else but taking revenge.
You said a person looks for someone to rely on when he's lonely.
I thought adults all thought that way.
But the reason I wanted to kill Yang Joon isn't because
of my father. But my father...
I don't remember much about him anymore.
But to let it go makes me feel like such an idiot.
That's why I stabbed Yang Joon behind his back.
But that a**hole... He cut off part of my body.
So I was going to take revenge...
That's how I've lived.
But you...
why does it seem like it's only natural that I kill you?
Sun Oh... this is...
Even in arithmetic, there is an order to it.
My problem was my big mouth...
but Yang Joon is actually the one who knifed you and your father.
Why not settle the score with Yang Joon first
and settle the rest with me...
No.
Because someone like you exists, there's also someone like Yang Joon.
I'm...
I'm already past 70 years old.
How many more years would I have to live?
They said not to look down on old people.
People who have lived decades
are all strong...
and cruel.
I'm cruel?
Do you know how cruel this world is?
Do you know how crappy this world and the laws are?
[Oh Soo Yeon's address]
I got Oh Soo Yeon's house address.
Seoul Sangui-gu, World Park-ro 79.
Perimese, Royal 63rd floor.
Wow...
It's worth living a long life.
Chairman Yang...
Forgive me.
Looks like excessive bleeding.
Sun Oh,
I knew you'd die before me.
[Hyung]
The call is not going through. You'll be connected to the voicemail.
There is no one who is pure in this world
and no one who is completely tainted.
You have to launder people and use them.
Work on them again and-
Anyway, this old man is always trying to dance to a tune.*
(Meaning he never misses a beat)
Send the dead guy over to the incinerator
and as for this old man with a big mouth...
- Put him in the trunk.
- Yes, sir!
Chairman Yang!
What's going on?
Who are you guys-
Hey, erase everything starting from an hour ago.
Security.
We received a complaint.
How do you do?
Mr. Yang Hwa.
You're under arrest for the attempted murder of Jo Hae Do.
Please call my attorney.
Let go! What are you doing?
Let's go!
[Hong Jae Sun]
Thanks for letting me use the house.
He caught him.
Oh, my goodness...
I can't believe he actually arrested Yang Hwa!
The reason you couldn't readily attack Yoon Byung Wook
is because of Yang Hwa who was behind Yoon Byung Wook, right?
If you compare it to cards, Yang Hwa is an ace
of spade.
His mere existence is dangerous.
The raw violence, shall I say?
He's so raw that I can't easily read his next move.
If we don't hold him down like this,
we can't do anything.
And...
once we cut off these shackles,
it's finally Yoon Byung Wook's turn.
It's because of your medication, right?
Excuse my expression,
but we're housemates, after all.
I noticed that...
you take lithium.
After I was rescued from the red-light district,
I was diagnosed with bipolar disorder.
But my brain slows down when I'm on medication.
I don't take it if I feel the urgency to stop.
But you don't have to worry.
What are you going to do with Jang Sun Oh?
Will you leave it to the law to punish him?
Yes.
You haven't gotten his confession yet.
Wouldn't it be difficult?
- It will be difficult.
- Then why do you hesitate?
It's dangerous.
I also...
promised myself a hundred, a thousand times that...
if I ever found my grandmother's killer,
I'd kill him with my own hands.
As I hit the prison walls with my bare hands.
And even when I got so close to killing Jang Sun Oh,
that promise didn't change.
But...
from Jang Sun Oh...
No!
I saw myself.
And...
I also saw you...
in Jang Sun Oh.
If the law would've changed the world!
If the law would've changed the world,
we would've never even met.
- I know that.
- And?
I know that, but...
Please give me more time.
- Take it.
- The beginning of casino money laundering
starts with cash, exchanging currency,
settlement office, then safe.
The settlement office.
Here's the safe.
Move.
Did you do it, Attorney Koo?
I should clean the house since a new tenant is moving in.
Attorney Koo, Jang Sun Oh was...
someone I desperately needed.
Yo Han, you're now Sinseon-dong's Go-to man.
Go-to man... What that means is that...
you're not really out of prison even though you've been released.
Even though you're all dressed up,
you're forever an inmate.
Forget all your personal feelings or hopes for revenge.
In Sinseon-dong,
there are no penalty points or solitary confinement.
Do you remember when we recruited Yo Han hyung?
You said this.
"Before I get older, I decided to
get rid of the two brothers, Yang Joon and Yang Hwa."
[An inmate disappeared from a hospital in Seoul yesterday afternoon, right before his surgery]
Around 4 p.m. yesterday, in a hospital in Seoul,
Do, in his 70s, who was hospitalized for surgery, went missing.
[An inmate disappeared from a hospital in Seoul yesterday afternoon, right before his surgery]
Considering the CCTVs in the hospital were damaged, the police
believes that Do either ran away...
[A man in his 70s hospitalized due to suspension of execution goes missing]
Send the dead guy over to the incinerator
and as for this old man with a big mouth...
Put him in the trunk.
F***!
I'd like to meet the Chief Prosecutor.
Our deputy chief is busy sitting in meetings.
She's here. Your boss.
You're Annie, right?
Hello, Prosecutor.
We're meeting for the first time, right?
[Prosecutor Hong Jae Sun]
I'll be outside.
Please call me when you're done talking to him.
Thank you.
Having handcuffs around your wrists...
It's been around 20 years, right?
But you've really had a long run at it if it's been 20 years.
What is it you want to say to me?
Well...
They told me to fire you.
The money that was in the Labuan Bank...
They all know it's been stolen.
If Seocho-dong can help us a little,
we can restore everything in 24 hours.
Of course. I'm sure.
I'm sure you feel that way.
I get that.
But...
people in Macau...
are extremely upset about it.
Macau...
Is there really no other way?
[A cloud server link]
Please upload all the data you have
for managing the account right here.
Did you already find my successor?
Move it! S***!
This! F***!
This is wrong...
That's not up to you to decide, Chairman Yang.
How about my hyung?
If you're that concerned about your hyungnim,
hurry up and move out.
[kcgold88]
Open your eyes wide and look at the screen.
So, Chairman Do is still missing?
Yes.
He broke away from his restricted area without reporting first.
So I heard the officers in charge are looking for him.
We may not apply the crime of escape, but
we can definitely redetain him.
And did Annie say that firmly?
That Kim Yo Han replaces Manager Yang?
Yes. And...
she told me to detain Manager Yang until she tells us to.
We have less than 30 hours out of 48 hours.
What should we do?
Gosh, s***...
The Corruption Investigation Agency has been giving me a headache as is...
Why?
Did Attorney General say something again?
The nominee to lead Corruption Investigation Agency
is the key player at the Ministry of Justice, Kim Jung Gyu.
Kim Jung Gyu, the 24th class of Judicial Institute.
That's tough.
I hear he's already recruiting prosecutors for the Corruption Investigation Agency.
The AG tells me to manage the people under me well.
That's why I'm at the Central District Prosecutors' Office
and you're at the Supreme Prosecutor's Office.
That Kim Yo Han. I'm sure he has ill feelings toward us, right?
They say people working in a warehouse are generous.
Managing our subordinates all takes money.
Of all days, Kim Yo Han happens to settle there.
Geez, the timing is so...
Aigoo...
Hey!
Let go of me! Please!
I've been waiting for you.
I'm Kim Yo Han.
Based on the opinions of the Deep Pockets gathered,
Kim Yo Han, you've garnered more than half of the yes votes.
I install you as the new manager for our Goldman Casino.
I don't know how long it's been since Macau and Sinseon-dong have come to an agreement.
But...
aside from Sinseon-dong and Macau,
there are Deep Pockets who own a third of the shares.
Elders who are outside of the Sinseon-dong.
If you focus on only taking care of Macau and Sinseon-dong
and forget about us,
they say they'll kill you.
As you wish.
[Goldman Casino Manager Kim Yo Han]
♫ You got me wrong ♫
[Insider]
♫ Wrong, who is driving the wheel of fate? ♫
♫ I cannot stop even though my entire body will breaks ♫
♫ Wrong, we will now break you down ♫
♫ Wrong, wrong, wrong, hey ♫
Looking at same thing outside the window all your life...
That's why we're stagnant.
I'll punish Yoon Byung Wook according to the law as well.
You'll expose everything as an insider?
Even if you die, I'll go on my way, Yo Han.
You must normalize this place for you to live, Manager.
- Let's just go.
- What are you doing?
As long as you've got the Goldman Casino manager position,
you've inherited all of Do Won Bong's debt.
I'm thinking of exposing Sinseon-dong next.
To fight against those heavy weights, shouldn't we have something more firm?
Byung Wook, we're running out of time now.
The thing you're doing right now. Did Kim Yo Han instigate it?
I think I'll abandon Kim Yo Han.
I think I'll become that Sinseon-dong Go-to woman.
♫ Who is driving the wheel of fate?