[Insider]
On June 8, in the first episode of "Insider",
we apologize for causing concern to the Buddhist community and viewers by describing the shrine where Buddha,
a symbol of Buddhism, was enshrined as a gambling hall,
and broadcasting a scene where a person posing as a monk illegally gambles.
The temple shrines and characters that were the background of the scene are fictional creations
and revealed that we have no intention of destroying a particular religion.
We will pay more attention during the production process so that there is no inconvenience in viewing in the future.
Once again, we apologize to the viewers.
(All people, places, organizations, and incidents
appearing in this series are entirely fictional.)
The trump card has a total of four pictures.
It has a total of 52 cards.
And those 52 cards can create for the first 2 cards a variety of
169 different hands.
After receiving a hand of the first 2 cards,
you have to know how your cards are stacked up against the other hands.
Raise.
A pair of Aces is considered the top rank cards.
A pair of aces is considered the best hand in all the games, but
how about a 10-double?
How do you think a 10-double would rank?
Ace one pair, K one pair, Q one pair, J one pair.
Isn't that a fifth-place hand?
In Hold'em, a 10-double is lower than a pair of A and K.
So, starting now, from 1st to 169th,
I will recite it for you.
A-all in one time?
Why? Do you want me to do it in parts?
No, go ahead.
W-wait...
(He chants the hands in the rhythm of Buddhist chant)
Do you know how to calculate a winning percentage?
Imagine I have a 7 and an 8.
The received hand has a 7 and an 8.
And the middle is lined up with a 5, 6, and an A.
If a 4 or 9 comes up, it's a straight.
Is this worth a match?
There's a total of four 4's.
And four of 9's.
And there are 8 cards that can create a 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 or 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
You have only a few out of the 8 cards.
You can say that your opponent has beat you in this game.
If you subtract those 5 from the total of 52 cards, and out of the remaining 47,
if eight cards belong to me...
Eight out of 47 cards...
The probability of getting one of eight cards on the next turn is 17%.
If going all the way to the river, then it's twice that at 34%.
In Hold'em, the position...
Your position is very important in this game.
[Dealer]
[Small Blind]
[Button / Big Blind]
Those who have to bet from the start like this
[Early-Late positions / Hijack / Cut-off]
have no choice but to inevitably expose themselves
[Under the Gun]
to others by how they bet.
Call.
Those who bet later
can plan their moves according to how the others made their bets.
So it's very advantageous.
Even though they may have the same hands,
they can have a different result.
I see...
I think I'll be leaving shortly.
I lost a sense of time.
Although it may not be exact.
By any chance,
are you Lee Tae Gwang?
Are you asleep?
Sir...
Hey, 2345.
I called out to the one in the next room, but there was no response.
He went back to his room last night.
- What?
- You need to come out, too, 2345.
Your 20 days are over.
What's with you?
Please give me one more chance.
I can even pay for the game myself with the detention money I received.
The money you lost before, I will get it back
including interest.
And I will go up to the 1st league
and I will surely complete
what you asked of me.
Fold.
This, I can do.
Raise.
Call and raise.
I guess he's got a pretty good hand.
Let's check the flop.
Call.
Flop.
Check.
He's got a mediocre hand also.
If he's got even one Jack, he would've bet instead of checking.
But he raised even before seeing the first three cards.
He may not have a J, but he might have at least a pair.
Turn.
I got a J, 4, two pair.
Let's find out what he's got.
Raise.
Call.
River.
It's impossible to make a flush with five diamonds.
No straight, either.
Let's bet aggressively and see how he reacts.
Raise a carton.
- What a man!
- He's the bomb.
Okay! Call.
All in.
That's right! Right on!
- Amazing!
- Look at that.
Look at that.
All right. Are you for real or are you bluffing?
What's certain is that you think I'm a pushover.
You're looking at me as someone beneath you.
You are bluffing.
Call.
Another raise.
He's raising again?
I'm getting chills. The chills...
What's this?
(Qs-Js over As-5s)
Wow, what the heck?
Hey, what are you doing?
- If you've lost it all, get up.
- One second.
Wait!
D*** it!
W-wait...
Okay.
All of you should go to sleep.
It's time to start taking care of your physical condition.
Gil Sang,
do you know what movie they are planning to show?
Yes, well, I'm not sure what it's about, but
it's two and a half hours long.
That's enough.
If you miss this day, he'll be getting out soon.
- There's no next year.
- Yes, Hyungnim.
[The 18th]
Two.
Four.
Six.
Eight.
Each pack is 50, so it's 400 altogether.
This should be more than enough to cover the last three weeks' missed payment plus interest.
You freak, you think this is money?
That's why...
I'm including extra for labor.
Wow, I'm dumbfounded.
You guys were also after my house instead of money.
Don't I just have to pay the price that matches the money I owe?
We do have a debtor-creditor relationship, but
we are in jail.
For a person to leave as a cripple.
It's not strange at all.
What is it?
Paying for damages.
Hey!
Back off. Back off!
How dare you puny gamblers act like gangsters?
We can beat them 500,000 won worth, right?
I don't think this is enough, though...
Bite down, or you'll lose your teeth.
Does no prison staff want to take you to the break room yet?*
(It means going up to the next league)
No, not yet.
Then it will take some time to see Jang Sun Oh's face.
As for these flowers,
you have to keep looking at them, touch them.
That's how the friendship blossoms.
You'll have to go to the outpatient today.
- Outpatient?
- Yeah.
That guy is pretty much at the infirmary all the time.
So, go and smell some antiseptic
and make some friends before coming back here.
Gil Sang will help you.
Come on!
Let go! Let go of me!
If your hand is injured, it'll affect you holding the cards at night.
But if we stab your stomach with the hoe or shovel,
we have to worry about you getting tetanus.
So, unfortunately, your ankle will need to be twisted in an unusual way.
- What?
- But it's going to hurt a lot.
Let me go. Hold on. Hold on, hold on!
Must you do this?
If your injury is not convincing, then Jang Sun Oh will cause you more pain.
Can you- can you do it on one try?
Yeah.
S***...
Do what you want to do.
I didn't want to do this, but...
Here, bite down on this.
You can scream out as loud as you want.
Hey, scream as much as you want!
I'm going.
That guy is pretty much at the infirmary all the time.
Who's there?
Who are you?
I'm hungry. Give me some bread.
[Dementia]
Give me some bread.
Give me some bread, I said!
[Neuropsychiatry]
[3883]
[Actor Training]
What are you doing?
Sang 1, Room 8. It's Yangbang!*
(Whatever card comes before or after the card, it makes a Straight.)
He was going through your room.
My room?
Why?
Please accept me into the 1st league.
I came in here with a gambling debt from the den.
That's why I need money.
I see...
Is that right?
What the...
Well, since you came this far, let's go for a massage.*
(A one-on-one gamble)
If you win, I'll consider your request.
Hey, did you fix the generator?
All right. Your hand?
Watch, this is level 1.
This is level 2.
Dean, Dean!*
(Seon Oh's nickname, since slang for prison is "school")
And we'll go for level 9.
The one who guesses his card first wins.
And the game money is
the truth.
If you get caught lying, this will drop into the bucket.
You'll be wearing a diaper for the rest of your life.
So, make sure to guess correctly what's on your forehead
or only tell the truth.
If I win, you'll put me in the upper league.
- Song Doo Cheol sent you, right?
- No.
- 5 of hearts.
- What did that old man say?
- I told you it's nothing like that.
- Ace of spade.
10 of hearts.
How are you going to pay back for damages to Mr. Jo's gambling house?
Did Song Doo Cheol tell you he'll cover your debt?
Ace of hearts.
If you move up to the front and stay by my side...
He must've instructed you to cut my head off while I sleep, huh?
You just fell for your own lies, didn't you?
Stop right there.
You're holding the lie right now.
When people lie, there are certain habits people display.
It's a physical reaction that shows up, like locking and loading right before lying.
But with you, that comes out of your hand.
Why did you come here?
Shut it off!
2345! 2345!
It was an electrocution. He needs a complete physical exam.
It's fine as long as he's awake. Come out now.
Geez, he needs to change his clothes, too.
I said no.
He may look fine on the outside, but he could come down with septicemia.
This is a special VIP visit.
The VIP has been waiting for him for an hour in the Sinseon-dong.*
(It means a new building, but it has a deeper connotation here)
Sinseon-dong?
What are you doing? Hurry up and get up.
Get up.
Get up. Come on.
That way.
2345.
Change into this.
Hurry up and get changed.
You'll have to go to the outpatient today.
- Song Doo Cheol sent you, right?
- No.
Did Song Doo Cheol tell you he'll cover your debt?
Then I'll take care of Hae Do for you.
You're holding the lie right now.
This is the lawyer consulting room.
You're going over there. To Sinseon-dong.
Hurry on over there.
One gangster, two gangsters...
one prosecutor, two prosecutors...
one avenger...
two avengers.
Six percent bank account is full...
flop and 36 families of victims, Corruption Investigation Agency, Tokarev.
Turn and Seongju Prison
and river, river, river...
As long as I get the river, the small blind will die.
And the big blind...
If you waited a bit, you could've gotten off at Seocho-dong.
Why are you trying to ruin it all?
It's been a while.
Hello, Yo Han.
We'll see each other soon.
Well, it can't be because of the clothes.
You seem so different in such a short amount of time.
Who are you?
What do you know about my grandmother's incident?
If you want to hear my answer, you go first.
Why did you call the cops that day?
The cops are on their way.
Do you want a ride to the bottom of the mountain?
You knew the cops were coming that night also.
No. I'll stay a little longer.
For what reason did you turn that mountain upside down?
Chairman Yang?
Welcome, Hyungnim.
It's good to see you, Mr. Jo.
Chairman Yang.
The Skin-nation.
It's nice here.
- Hello, Chairman Yang.
- Hey, Soo Yeon!
- How have you been?
- I've been well, of course.
Why are you standing in line? Looks so cheesy.
He had been indicted a few times for gambling abroad but was released.
Why did you keep checking up on Chairman Yang?
According to the tabloid rumors,
Hong Sang Wook of the Supreme Prosecutors' Office is said to be behind it.
Did you also know that your colleague Hong Jae Sun's father
Chief Prosecutor Hong Sang Wook of the Central Investigation Division is behind him?
Does Mr. Jo still have a strangle on you?
I asked who you were.
[Oh Su Yeon]
I will become whatever you wish, Yo Han.
Raccoon is missing.*
(Code for "Missing target")
Looking around.
Gosh, it's ticklish.
I'll just be your pushover.
I'll go to the Ladies' Room before I go.
I'll see you next week at the Palace.
Okay, I'll see you next week.
Yeah.
5735. This one?
I pressed it.
Is that it then?
What about the camera?
Do you see it?
Yes?
[Warden's Office]
I brought in 2345.
Have a seat over there.
I understand you were about to graduate from the Judicial Research and Training Institute.
That's pretty intense.
So, you're playing...
cards in here again?
No, no.
Don't worry. I'm not leading you with questions.
Hold'em is not gambling. It's a sport. A recreation.
Like a game of Go or Gomoku.
I think a recreation like that could be enjoyed
like that in here in our free time.
I think the human rights of prisoners are important.
But you shouldn't become addicted to it.
Then that would become a problem for all of us.
So who was the visitor earlier?
No.
It's rare for the Department of Justice to directly request a change of venue,
unless it's by the higher-ups in Sinseon-dong over here.
Who was that VIP visitor?
If you return to your room like this, what will you tell Song Doo Cheol?
In order to maintain a gambling den here, you have to be extremely careful.
You have to be aware of everything that happens here.
That's the reason why I'm asking you.
So you can relax and just tell me.
Who was it?
Who was the Department of Justice VIP who came to visit you?
- May I?
- Sure.
At the gambling house, when I was outside,
she had faced some trouble there.
And I helped her with it.
A little bit.
Is that right?
So, that's what happened.
So that's who that was...
Gosh, really.
Here. Have another one.
What do I need to do if I want to move up to the 1st league?
Actually, I hear you keep winning in 3rd league.
But the proper order is for you to be verified in 2nd league before moving up.
But let's see...
You are on good terms with Jang Sun Oh.
That concerns me a little bit.
Unless you can defeat Jang Sun Oh yourself.
That's right.
Then he has no reason to stand against you.
Yes, that's it!
Did you meet with him?
Yes.
How did you meet him?
Pardon?
Even if you went into the infirmary,
I don't think he'd just be anywhere.
I went to look for him in his solitary cell.
Did he open the door for you?
Actually, he was just coming out of the room.
And nobody was there to bother you?
No, I wasn't in any more danger, thanks to you.
All right.
When did they ask you to come in for a checkup?
They told me to come once a week to get medicine.
Good job.
Here he comes, Hyungnim.
Since you keep winning lately, even the warden wants to talk to you.
Mr. Hwang, in the Occupational Training, even got a new car.
Unless you can defeat Jang Sun Oh yourself.
Then he has no reason to stand against you.
- I mean, look at you.
- Jang Sun Oh...
- You have to win now.
- I have to beat Jang Sun Oh...
- Geez, the gambling is so...
- But how?
- But it doesn't seem...
- So, do you want me to teach you?
What if he is...
- Lee Tae Gwang?
- 2345.
How much is it to make a phone call?
- Fifty won, isn't it?
- Not the landline.
Your cell phone.
That's not allowed.
Yes, that's a violation.
Would a cost of a car be enough?
Here.
Enjoy your phone call.
Hello?
This is Kim Yo Han.
Whose cell phone is this?
What you said earlier about helping me, you still mean it?
What do you need?
I need some money.
And Lee Tae-
5735. This one?
Yeah, I pressed it.
Is that it then?
I don't know his name.
But when I was in solitary confinement, he was in the room next to mine.
I'm looking for him.
Let me talk to the owner of this cell phone.
It's not Lee Tae Gwang.
Is your name...
Just...
call me Professor.
So, starting now, from 1st to 169th, I will recite it for you.
I heard you've been looking for me so desperately.
He's the one.
The one who was in the room next to you.
Why did you help me?
You needed my help then.
And back then,
this...
I was better than you.
This gambling thing needs more than just a theory.
You need to have guts.
So, why did you look for me?
It must've cost you some money to get help from the prison staff.
Lee Tae Gwang.
Where can I find him?
Lee Tae Gwang...
Lee Tae Gwang?
He's in the infirmary now.
You can't go back there now.
Then can you set up a meeting with him outside the infirmary?
- That's going to be tough.
- I'll give you a commission.
Money is not the problem.
It's the Dean that's the problem. You know?
Jang Sun Oh.
I'm done.
Fold.
Raise.
When will you get to 2nd league?
It won't be long.
In business,
you have to go full force when you've got the momentum.
Look at this.
Once the flow stops, I can't start another game the way I want to play it.
I'll fix it.
I heard you're dilly-dallying at the gambling den lately.
Are Mr. Jo's guys still bothering you?
No, sir.
It's not like you have any family to worry about outside.
You just have to shape up.
Yes, I'll stay focused.
You are not alone anymore.
Gil Sang?
What! What is this?
It's because we are out of time.
- Time?
- Yeah, something like that.
You'll find out soon enough.
Hyungnim, the fertilizer storage room is locked.
Hey, let's do it there.
Wait!
No! No!
It's hard to hurt yourself the first time, but the second time is...
- Put the tape on him.
- No, don't!
Don't!
I'm sorry. This greenhouse is not soundproof.
Hey, stop acting like amateurs. Hold him tight!
I'm sorry, Hyungnim.
I'll get it done in one blow.
Okay...
What the hell are you doing?
Our newbie was messing around, so we just wanted to scare him a bit.
You call this just scaring him? Looks like you're about to kill him!
Everyone who was holding down 2345, stand over there. Do it now!
2345, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Get up.
Careful.
I should take you all in. D*** it!
Let's go. You're fine now.
Excuse me...
Why did you help me again?
For a person to help another person,
should there be a reason?
- What about Lee Tae Gwang-
- Geez, I said I can't.
I didn't help you, so I can arrange a meeting with Lee Tae Gwang.
Actually,
there's a way to move up without Jang Sun Oh's permission.
You know...
You can get on the Warden's good side.
If Jang Sun Oh objects...
Not if your sponsor is more powerful than him.
In the 2nd league,
you know that the prison staff members sponsor the game fee
and take a cut of the winnings, right?
So, if you keep winning in 2nd league and move on upward,
the sponsor keeps getting a cut of the winnings.
So, it's important for the sponsor for his player
to play in the 1st league.
In other words,
as long as the player is skillful
and if the sponsor is powerful enough,
you can definitely move on upward.
Which sponsor is powerful?
In ranking order, after the warden,
it's the security manager.
I hear the security manager is a house manager.
And that security manager is
a hoobae from my hometown.
If you want, I can make the introduction, but...
But?
The commission you mentioned before.
How about 40% of your winnings?
My stomach is full, but why am I still hungry?
Hunger pang like that isn't good for you.
Food is dangerous
but money doesn't make you fat.
I also have a debt to repay.
How about taking just 30%?
All the players I select give me 60%.
Same for all.
How about increasing it little by little?
You are the one who came looking for me.
No?
I'll get you the 60.
If you lose, you lose your own money.
If you win,
then it's mine.
I understand.
Lunch's on me.
Check, please.
Hey.
[2nd League]
Call.
All in.
I'm out.
- Fold.
Where is the confidence you showed while playing Seotda*?
(Type of game played with Hwatu)
How does it feel to be robbed blind?
Maybe because I was beaten silly.
I'm craving some meat. It's driving me crazy.
How about you, monk? You can't eat tripe, can you?
Aigoo. Didn't you know that I'm a fake monk?
I go crazy for tripe.
Is that right?
If we have to afford your share of meat, monk, we must have it out with him.
Hey, dealer, why are you holding up the hand?
Wow, what's going on here?
All the enemies are gathered around one table.
Take a rest.
It's okay if I watch, right?
I just want to know how good you guys are.
Okay?
You're holding the lie right now.
By the way, Yangbang...
My body still smells like it's burnt.
All right...
What are you doing? Blind, come on.
How about you go first, ahjussi? Action!
Call.
Two 10s.
Raise 80.
I see you.
Call.
Call...
Flop.
I'm going all in.
Fold.
- Fold.
Here you go. Aigoo.
All for me.
- Congratulations.
- Gosh, thank you.
There.
Flop.
Geez, my ear hurts!
If you keep doing that, I'll cut off your wrist.
I don't think I'm the one who should lose a wrist.
Oh, got some education already?
Also, do you know how to cheat?
I should know it well.
In a scam, several people group together to cheat against one.
They do it by exchanging silent signs amongst each other.
I use the color of chips.
Colors?
The quickest thing your eye catches are colors.
White chip is a diamond...
Green chip is a clover
blue chip is a spade
and red chip is a heart.
If you use your right thumb, index, and middle finger to push the chip, then it's K.
But if you do the same with your left hand, then Q.
If you use both hands to round up the chips and push forward, then J.
Q spade.
If you use your index and middle finger to push the chips in a V shape, then it's an ace.
Ace of hearts.
Was it you all along, Jang Sun Oh?
Faking you by making noise with the chips
they're communicating through hand gestures holding the chips and the colors.
Raise.
I see you.
Call it.
Call.
Q spade and ace of hearts.
Did Jang Sun Oh just signal me the monk's hand?
Or...
Why did Jang Sun Oh help me from the adjacent room?
What does he get by helping me?
But when you fake out another fake...
The real sign is...
communicating through the amount of the exchanging bets.
1010.
10 in a turn?
Is this a scam?
Call.
Okay, call.
Turn.
Fold.
Here I go.
Raise.
Call. 60.
I'm going all in.
Call.
Okay, all in from both sides.
I'll open the cards then.
Monk, you first.
Relieve my suffering and return to Buddha...*
(Buddhist chant)
Relieve my suffering and return to Buddha.
You, too, Yangbang. Open your cards.
There's still one more river.
If there's an ace from the river, it'll turn the table.
Then river!
Hold!
As for the river, I'll open it.
Okay, monk.
River.
To cross a river you can't return from.
To survive through this on the back of Jang Sun Oh...
or get killed tonight by getting hit by Jang Sun Oh.
I don't see it... no side...
Please...
No side!
It's an ace!
[Insider]
Why me?
Isn't having an ego a luxury for you right now?
Are you staking me out?
Kill him.
When I get out of here,
I'll take over the gambling scene in Korea.
In the world of scamming, finding one you can trust is a priority.
I'll give you what you want if it's worth my life.
I have a plan.
You have nothing to lose in a deal like this.
He'll reinvestigate if that's the card I hold.
I heard you're moving up to Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office.
What did that cost you?
Was it erasing me out of the system?
Did you forget I'm the only one who can get you out of here?
You are not a Judicial Institute trainee anymore.
You're a criminal.
Seongju Prison.
Take it over.
Timing and subtitles offered by The Payback Team @Viki.com