Listen,
I have an idea.
Look at this.
It not only solves the food problem,
but also,
I can even
make this village
develop rapidly.
What do you mean?
You gave me the inspiration.
This crayfish...
the flavor now has a soul.
So,
you are
its spokesperson.
Spokesperson?
And then,
we'll turn it into
a brand
and promote it.
First,
we'll use the Wei Kingdom as a base.
What we need to do
is seize the pain points of the people's tastes,
then form an industrial closed loop,
and empower the industry.
Then, in all directions—north, south, east, west—
radiate it outwards,
push it nationwide,
and unify the commercial landscape.
We also need to give this brand
a louder name.
Think about it.
This is our Wei Kingdom's silt-clearing divine object.
Spicy is the most popular flavor.
Let's just call it
Wei Shen Ma.
How about that?
Although I don't understand,
it sounds very impressive.
I wish you success.
But what good is success?
Our two countries
are bound to go to war.
Look at them.
Back then, to escape the war,
they came here
and built this Shangri-La.
Now,
it seems they can't escape it.
I don't want to fight.
Who wants to fight?
But this kind of thing,
is it something a Princess like you
and a Strategist like me can decide?
How about this?
Let's write down the story of this place.
I'll write to my father.
You write to the Lord.
Maybe
it can stop the war.
Just like you said,
who wants to fight?
I think that works.
Eat up.
It's getting cold.
The Daye Kingdom Princess Consort has arrived!
I,
Princess Consort of Daye Kingdom,
Ao Tian,
have come this time
to do only three things.
One,
take back the Princess.
Two,
loot the commoners.
Three,
Reconnaissance behind enemy lines.
This third thing
is a military secret of my Daye Kingdom.
So,
this time,
I'll mainly talk about the first two.
Hand it over.
Delicious.
Peel one for me.
It's okay, it's okay.
Unruly peasants.
Becoming unruly peasants at such a young age.
Crying just because I snatched a shrimp today?
How will he cope when I burn his house down later?
This guy won't...
Strategist.
Let's observe the situation first.
Calm down, calm down.
Princess.
Who brought you here?
Him.
Reward him.
Get lost.
I said go back.
I'm talking about you.
Princess.
How about
we go back?
The Lord has prepared the wedding banquet.
I...
Strategist.
Calm down, calm down.
Who said I want to go back?
I like it here.
What a coincidence.
I like it here too.
Although my troops
got lost in the heavy fog,
but it's fine.
We'll do some looting,
and take back everything we like.
Fighting is forbidden in this village.
But this time I support you.
Just this once.
Why are you hitting me?
I... I...
What did I do wrong?
What's wrong with looting the commoners?
You guys be the judge.
Aren't commoners born
just to be looted by us?
What did I, Ao Tian, do wrong?
Mr. Long, don't be angry.
My surname isn't Long.
I'm just called Ao Tian.
Alright.
Mr. Long Ao Tian.
Our village's ancestral motto
is to take pleasure in helping others.
You want to loot the commoners,
that can be discussed.
However,
you have to tell us your difficulties,
so we can explore the options.
I don't have any difficulties.
No difficulties?
Why not make one up on the spot?
Otherwise, we can't really let you loot.
You are mocking me.
Absolutely no such intention.
If my words just now made you uncomfortable,
I apologize to you.
I'm sorry, Mr. Long.
My surname isn't Long.
Doesn't your village forbid fighting?
I didn't see anything.
With He Qi standing next to him,
he looks much more pleasing to the eye.
General Wei Long of the Wei Kingdom.
Princess Consort of the Daye Kingdom.
What advice do you have for me?
Wei Long, right?
I'll remember you.
Just you wait.
My Daye Kingdom's army will arrive soon.
When that time comes,
I'll behead you first.
Get some rest, Mr. Long.
I'll say it again, my surname isn't Long!
My surname isn't Long!
What are we going to do?
What do you mean, what to do?
Between the two of us, civil and martial,
can't we handle him?
You saw it too.
His intelligence has returned to a primitive state.
For a moment,
I don't know how to deal with him.
Just target his weakness.
But the problem is,
he is entirely made of weaknesses.
I don't know which to choose.
Hurry up and choose.
Or you'll lose your wife.
Right.
I'll go ask Yu Tong.
What time do you think it is?
Asking Yu Tong now?
Her husband is here.
Will she still stand by your side?
The Strategist...
always loses when it comes to women.
Where are you going?
To cook.
Didn't we just finish eating?
Brother,
you said the wrong thing.
You said the wrong thing again.
Which part?
"Or you'll lose your wife."
"Find Yu Tong."
Which one was it exactly?
What should I do?
It must be that one.
Talk too much and you'll slip up.
Yu Tong.
Come home with me.
Although you...
have been cold to me the past few days,
you never actually left.
Based on that alone,
I don't believe
that you aren't moved at all.
From the day you risked your life to save me,
I was indeed moved.
Born into an imperial family,
my father and brother
have always treated me as a pawn.
You are the first person
who truly cares if I live or die.
So at that time, I was thinking,
if we could stay together forever,
how wonderful that would be.
Then let's stay together forever.
Won't you come home with me?
If Father gets angry,
war will break out at the border again.
The people will suffer.
As the Strategist of the Wei Kingdom,
can you bear that?
What kind of bullshit Strategist am I
if I can't even keep the woman I love?