This...
Is this shrimp actually roasted?
It tastes so bad.
And you still want people to help?
That's right.
When roasting things,
you have to sprinkle seasoning.
How is it?
Does it have the feeling of midsummer?
Passionate and unrestrained.
It certainly feels like leftovers.
You can't keep them when it's hot.
It's the Summer of Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter.
Midsummer.
Midsummer, Midsummer.
Then just dump it.
If it's leftovers, just dump it.
Is it really that bad?
I'll go research it some more.
Mr. Yuwen.
You should instead research
how to catch the Strange Shrimp.
The lotus roots in the pond,
the fish,
the rice in the paddy fields,
have all been eaten by them.
Every household in the village
is running out of food.
Village Chief.
I just want to figure out
a tastier recipe for this Strange Shrimp.
That way, the villagers
will spontaneously go catch shrimp.
Then take them home to eat.
Wouldn't that solve everything?
Eat that?
We would rather starve to death.
Forget it.
Mr. Yuwen.
You all should just leave.
You have done your best.
It's fine if we starve to death.
Lately, I...
keep dreaming of my mother.
She tells me
not to cause trouble for others.
Starving to death...
is actually no big deal.
Village Chief.
Strategist.
Do you have no heart?
Hurry up and think of a solution.
A fine Strategist ignoring the Art of War,
and studying recipes instead.
Everyone!
Have a taste.
It must be delicious this time.
Well...
I just promised a villager
to help with some farm work.
I'm heading out.
I...
want to go...
watch ants by the roadside.
I want to join Miss Aqin to watch ants.
The folks are starving to death,
and you're in the mood to watch ants?
I just want to watch ants.
It tastes terrible.
Miss Aqin.
Let me massage your shoulders.
No need.
Let me massage your legs.
Miss Aqin, Miss Aqin.
What exactly do you want?
Is there anything you need?
I need you to stay away from me.
Excuse me
What are you doing?
You have no sense of timing at all
That's it
This feeling is right
Pain
She is in pain
But I need to be in more pain than her
What does that mean?
Pain is the source of all inspiration
Like music
Dance
Poetry
The inspiration for many art forms
All comes from pain
I'm in more pain than you now, aren't I?
Cooking Little Dragon Shrimp is the same
Just now when I saw Yu Tong
Sorrow welled up from within
In my heart
There was a trace of pain
The inspiration is about to come out
But
Just like a spark
It vanished in an instant
Why don't you just vanish?
Long
I beg you
I want pain
I want a lot of pain
I'm about to have an epiphany
Pain, right?
Fine
Don't cry later
Do we have to be this real?
You asked for it
Does it hurt?
How is it?
Painful
But it's still missing a little something
The inspiration is almost here
Does it hurt?
Why did you stop suddenly?
My inspiration was just about to...
Yu Tong
He...
He begged me for ages to do this
Don't explain
No
He said he needed this
You're making it worse
Why don't you do it?
Yu Tong
Help me first
Disgusting
No
Help me undo this
I'll give you...
No
You guys have to help me undo this
Let me tell you
This inspiration all comes from pain
You... you're in pain
Just...
That's the flavor
Lemongrass
You must taste this
Are you willing
to eat another one?
I am willing
Come on, have a taste.
It smells so good.
So good.
It's really nice.
I'll have one, I'll have one.
Give me one.
Let me taste it.
Give me the one on the ground.
Give me one.
You've already eaten two.
It's so delicious.
It smells so good.
It really makes Brother Yuwen's...
...days of research worthwhile.
It solved the village's food shortage crisis.
It was you who gave me the inspiration...
...to make this thing so delicious.
Say, what should...
...we call this thing?
I don't know.
What do you want to call it?
Then we'll call it that.
Look at it.
Doesn't it look like a dragon?
I think it looks more like a shrimp.
Shrimps are so ugly.
Dragons are cool.
Then let's...
...take a word from each of us...
...and call it...
Dragon Shrimp.
Sounds quite imposing.
But it's not cute.
Let's add the word "Little".
Okay.
Then let's call it...
Dragon Shrimp Little.
Sounds like there's too little meat.
Little Dragon Shrimp.
That works.
Little Dragon Shrimp works.
Little Dragon Shrimp sounds cute.