It's all your fault.
I knew I'd get the blame again.
Enough.
I'll go check if the ground at the west end was touched.
Is that even necessary?
Brother, it's such a long way.
Why do you insist on making this trip?
Look.
The ground at the west end hasn't been touched.
Of course it hasn't been touched.
Because the jar we talked about...
...was buried at the east end of the village!
It's all your fault!
You couldn't even explain the rules clearly.
Sir.
I'll go ask Xiao Hua for help.
Go ahead.
Wait.
Did you tell Xiao Hua...
...that the jar is buried at the east end...
...or the west end?
No need to mention burying the jar anymore.
It doesn't matter anyway.
No way.
We're going to argue again.
Have you been waiting long?
No.
This is what I ran all over the mountain...
...to brew for you: Hundred-Flower Snakegrass Brew.
Taste it, quick.
How is it?
Tastes like a sleeping mat.
It's delicious.
Thank you, Brother Wei Qiao.
As long as you like it.
Um...
Actually, I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
What?
There's a spy?
The Village Chief knows the way out.
Spread this news as fast as possible.
It will force them to make a move sooner.
So exciting!
I promise to complete the mission.
My dad knows the way out. Keep it down!
My dad knows the way out!
You're back.
Let's eat.
So many dishes.
Smells so good.
You've all worked hard.
Have some tea.
Not at all, not at all.
Just in time, I'm thirsty. Thanks.
What special occasion is it today?
To have cooked so many good dishes?
Haven't you heard?
The Village Chief knows a secret passage.
We might be able to leave soon.
However...
some people...
...will have to part ways with everyone.
True.
After all, some people have to go back to report back.
You...
Alright, alright.
Stop arguing, stop arguing.
Just eat your food.
Yu Tong...
You actually...
Don't move.
Don't hurt them.
Brother Yuwen.
I'm sorry.
We each serve our own master, that's all.
I won't hurt you all.
Now that it's come to this...
I just want to ask you one thing.
Did you really...
...never love me?
I have to say...
...what are you thinking, kid?
This is the Third Princess of my Daye Kingdom.
You, a lowly Wei Kingdom Strategist...
...dare to be so impudent?
Congratulations, Princess.
The great undertaking is almost complete.
Dig up the jar.
Then let's leave immediately.
Let's go.
Princess
There's no Jar here either
We were tricked after all
Brother
Do we keep digging?
You like digging?
Go dig yourself
Dig, dig
What kind of acting was that?
After I fell, you should have waited a bit before falling
What was my acting?
At least I had a process
You didn't even have a process
You just fell straight down
I thought you dropped dead
Who dropped dead?
You're the one who dropped dead
Your whole family dropped dead
Just in time, I'm thirsty
Thanks
I knew this method would force out the spy
I didn't expect it to really be her
Strategist
Look at the situation
And you're asking if she loves you?
Seriously
Enough
Tell me
That look in her eyes when she left
Was she reluctant to leave?
Strategist, have some dignity, will you?
She is a spy from the Daye Kingdom
Exactly
This has nothing to do with feelings
So, in this scheme...
Was I included too?
No
Then why didn't you tell me?
There was knockout drug in the tea
If I hadn't been on guard...
I would have fallen for it long ago
Isn't your martial arts skill so high?
You'd surely know
Right?
But you still should have told me
Stop arguing
Please, stop arguing
Argue, argue
Let them argue
Argue harder
If that's not enough, use knives
Stab, stab, come on
Stab right here
Save me from this misery
Now I'm the only single one
Strategist
You still have a chance
That there's a way out...
That news was fake
Maybe they'll come back in a bit
Then I'll go welcome her
Come back, come back
Bad news, bad news
What's wrong, Xiao Hua?
My dad said there really is a way out
Yesterday He Qi asked him to drink
He got drunk
And seems to have told He Qi
Yu Tong
Wait for me here
Don't go anywhere
Okay
Chase, chase, chase
Back again?
Is it because of me?
Cut the crap
Where is the Jar?
Please tell her
The Jar is right in my heart
If she wants it, come and get it
Shameless
Princess
Tell him
I only want the Jar
Tell her
Taking the Jar will also take my heart
Tell him
Saying that only makes me sick
Tell her
Even disgust comes from the heart
If you take it, take it all
Tell him
Without the Jar, I'm not leaving
Tell her
I'm very happy she can stay
I like you. I hate you
Never seen anyone so disgusting
Yeah
This guy has no dignity left
Did you find the Jar?
No.
However,
Your Highness,
even without the Jar,
we can still go back and report.
Then I'll storm back with a thousand Elite troops.
We'll leave no stone unturned,
and we'll surely find the Jar.
Do you take them for fools?
If we leave, they won't stay put.
Well,
do you...
take us for fools?
Anyone with eyes
can see at a glance
that you're not staying for the Jar.
You're just after that lousy Strategist guarding it.
What nonsense are you talking?
I've already told you,
it's just to get the Jar.
There is no other reason.
I mean what I say.
You said it.
How are you talking to me?
Fine, then.
You... you get some rest.