[The Night is Still Young]
[Episode 18]
Come on, make way.
Move aside. Move aside.
Let us through.
Now that my plans have been exposed,
I'm afraid I can't stay in Ye City any longer.
But before I leave,
I must see Weiyang one last time.
Kid?
Okay.
[Beauty House]
Weiyang?
I knew you would come.
Weiyang.
I know
it may be a bit late to say this now,
but I still want to say goodbye properly
to you before I leave.
Actually,
I've liked you for a long time.
From the moment we first met,
your radiant presence made you stand out among thousands,
and I was immediately drawn to you.
And now, after our many interactions,
my admiration for you has only grown deeper.
It's just a pity...
pity that I misjudged people,
falling into his trap.
But don't worry.
When I return to Xuannan,
I will surely rise again.
What a touching confession.
How come it's you?
Feng Xuanyi,
not only are you poor at judging people,
but your eyesight isn't very good either.
You...
But I didn't expect
you to like Weiyang too.
Looks like you and I
do have something in common after all.
On my turf,
where do you think you can run to?
Ye Mingxuan, don't get so smug.
Your vicious ambition
will be exposed to the world sooner or later.
Save your breath.
Arrest him
and let him rise again... from prison.
Weiyang.
Uncle,
could it be that you're also here
to arrest the wanted criminal Feng Xuanyi?
I am here.
No one can take him away.
Uncle, could it be that you want to rebel together with Feng Xuanyi?
[Order]
Father,
I previously put myself at risk
by pretending to ally with Feng Xuanyi.
Only then did I find
evidence of Feng Xuanyi's intention to rebel.
The fireworks explosion at the previous palace banquet
and the deaths of Vice General Wang and General Shangguan
were all orchestrated by him behind the scenes.
Father, please judge wisely.
It was all done by him?
Yes,
he did all of it.
If I remember correctly,
Fifth Prince,
you previously wanted to put Feng Xuanyi to death.
Uncle, you've misunderstood.
I didn't want to kill Feng Xuanyi.
I only wanted to capture him.
What about moving the counterfeit money?
That was to obtain evidence of his rebellion.
What about General Shangguan's death?
Poor General Shangguan.
It was because he discovered Feng Xuanyi's vicious ambition
that he was killed by him.
What a silver tongue.
But according to my investigation,
your alliance with Feng Xuanyi was not fake—
it was a real partnership.
This is the secret correspondence of their conspiracy.
It even has the Fifth Prince's personal seal on it.
This is the secret letter exchanged between the Fifth Prince and me.
Your Majesty,
the reason the Fifth Prince threw Feng Xuanyi under the bus
was to sacrifice a pawn to protect himself.
Please investigate thoroughly, Your Majesty.
Do you have anything else to say?
[Given time, you and I will surely achieve great things together] [Mingxuan of Great Ye]
What else do you have to say?
Father, please let me explain.
These are all fake.
The reason I put myself at risk
and pretended to cooperate with him
was that I had already seen through his plan.
This is the treasonous alliance agreement
that I obtained from King Xuannan.
It has not only King Xuannan's signature
but also the handwritten signatures of other kings from different lineages.
This proves
they have long harbored treasonous intentions,
aiming to break free from the court's control
and carve out their own kingdoms.
These traitors all deserve to die!
Father, please calm your anger.
This matter
must not be decided hastily.
What?
What good strategy do you have?
I believe
that kings from different lineages have always been
a hidden danger throughout history,
but they can only be gradually weakened,
not forcibly removed.
Otherwise, it will surely lead to widespread rebellion,
plunging the people into chaos.
Instead, Father, you could issue an edict
under the pretext of study tours,
ordering these kings to send their eldest sons to the capital
as hostages.
This move will surely make them hesitate to rebel,
fearing for their sons' safety.
Your Majesty.
Come on.
My brother has been so mighty and commanding for many years,
stabilizing the borders
and achieving great military achievements.
There is already nothing left to bestow upon him.
If I'm still alive,
I can still keep him in check.
But if I were to pass away,
I really can't think of
any of my sons
who could stand up to him.
Your Majesty,
please don't say that.
You are in the prime of your life.
You have been serving me for all these years.
There's no need for empty flattery.
I know my own health condition.
Your Majesty.
What I'm worried about
is all about King Yan.
But I didn't expect
Mingxuan...
to rise so unexpectedly.
Do you think the Fifth Prince is
not as simple as he seems
but rather ruthless
and would stop at nothing?
I don't know,
and I don't even dare to speculate.
When the older brother dies and the younger brother inherits,
this often brings calamity.
A weak ruler and a strong minister
can also lead to power slipping away.
For an emperor,
it's better to have sons who are wolves rather than sheep.
And morality is something that binds the saint,
not emperors.
Your Majesty, you're wise.
I have learned much from you.
Since Mingxuan has the ability
to challenge King Yan,
I will give him this opportunity.
I'd like to see
if this son of mine, who resembles me the most,
can truly protect my empire.
Go and draft the decree.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Queen.
How did it go?
Ye Mingxuan discovered that Feng Xuanyi
intended to collude with other kings
from different lineages to rebel.
The Emperor was furious
and issued an order to revoke Feng Xuanyi's hereditary fief,
and he would soon be exiled.
At the same time, the Emperor particularly commended Ye Mingxuan
for his meritorious service in protecting the country
and decided to crown him as the Crown Prince.
What?
[Imperial Edict]
By the grace of Heaven, the Emperor decrees:
The Fifth Prince, Ye Mingxuan, is gentle, diligent,
humble, and intelligent.
He benefits the court and has rendered great service to the country.
He shall be immediately appointed as the Crown Prince,
to receive the heavenly mandate and succeed to the throne.
This decree is hereby issued to inform the world.
Thus, it is commanded.
Uncle,
I never thought there would be a day...
when I would wear these dragon-patterned robes.
Save your complacency for
when you truly sit on the throne.
Uncle, your character is strong and unyielding,
but you're always pressing others too hard.
Aren't you afraid that being too aggressive
might make you an easy target?
Nephew, your methods are devious and scheming.
You might inevitably fall victim to your own schemes
and lose everything.
Uncle, you worry too much.
If one doesn't seize what heaven offers, they'll be blamed.
If one doesn't take action at the right moment,
they'll suffer the consequences.
Born into the royal family, not fighting for benefits
is the path to destruction.
Look at me now.
Aren't I about to ascend the throne?
Until the very end, nothing is certain.
The future is still unknown.
You have only 10 minutes.
Weiyang.
Weiyang, why are you here?
How are you?
They didn't torture you, did they?
They wouldn't dare, even if they had the courage.
I knew that you cared about me.
When you wanted to see me yesterday,
did you have something important to tell me?
I have something important...
I...
I seem to have forgotten.
It's not on me.
Wait until I get out.
I'll give it to you when I'm out.
Is it a clue? Where did you put it?
No,
it's just...
something unimportant.
I thought
you would escape from Great Ye.
It's all my fault
for misjudging him.
I know
this wasn't entirely your fault.
You were also deceived.
So,
if you have any evidence to prove your innocence,
you must give it to me.
I'll do what I can to reduce your punishment.
If I had any,
I wouldn't be facing exile.
Don't worry. It's alright.
Once I leave Ye City,
I'll be like a dragon entering the ocean.
I'll definitely make a comeback.
If Ye Beichen dares to bully you,
I'll rescue you,
even if I have to tear down his mansion.
Think again.
Are there any important clues
that you may have overlooked?
Weiyang.
Why did you come here so suddenly
without notifying me in advance?
Weiyang.
Ye Mingxuan!
Let her go, Ye Mingxuan!
Let go of me.
If you dare harm her,
you'll pay for it when I get out!
Let go of me.
Ye Mingxuan!
Your Highness.
Get lost!
Weiyang.
What exactly are you looking for?
Feng Xuanyi raised his own army, killed important officials,
and planned to rebel.
Everyone can see it clearly.
Why do you choose to turn a blind eye?
The court can be deceived,
and the people can be fooled,
but my eyes won't be mistaken.
Weiyang.
I know you've been misled by Ye Beichen,
which is why you misunderstand me.
But now, I've become the Crown Prince.
As long as you return to my side,
I'll definitely make you see the truth.
You don't need to say anymore, Ye Mingxuan.
No matter how persuasive you are,
I will never trust your words again.
You won't trust my words,
yet you trust Ye Beichen's?
At least he's more upright and honest than you.
So, you're going to abandon me...
and marry him?
But I forgot to tell you, Weiyang.
I've already petitioned Father Emperor on your behalf.
The Crown Prince has just been appointed,
and the entire nation shares in the joy.
It might be a conflict if the kings are getting married at this time.
Your wedding has been postponed.
So what?
Even if it were postponed for ten years,
I would still marry him.
I won't let anyone take you away from me.
What are you doing, Ye Mingxuan?
Are you crazy?
Let go of me.
I am the Crown Prince.
So what if you're the Crown Prince?
If you dare to disrespect my fiancée again,
I'll make you understand what despair truly means.
Ye Beichen!
Sooner or later, I'll tear you to pieces
and scatter your ashes to the wind!
I never thought that this Ye Mingxuan,
after becoming the Crown Prince, would become even more despicable
and more unscrupulous.
That's his true nature.
What a pity.
I didn't manage to get any clues from him.
It doesn't matter.
Even if he makes Feng Xuanyi take the fall,
his true nature won't change.
Sooner or later, he'll sink his claws
into the imperial court.
We just need to wait and see.
As for you,
next time, before acting impulsively,
could you discuss it with me first?
If Chu Mo hadn't reported in time...
I was wrong this time.
But you've got my back, don't you?
Aren't you supposed to escort Feng Xuanyi
out of the capital tomorrow?
How do you have time to see me?
I've noticed you've been agitated and restless lately,
with rising internal heat,
so I specifically brought an ice pack
to relieve your toothache.
Ye Mingxuan has now turned the tables and become the Crown Prince.
Wanting to arrest him and bring him to justice
seems even more distant now
and increasingly difficult.
Just thinking about it
keeps me awake with anger night after night.
Don't rush things.
I'm here.
Come on.
Feeling better?
Ye Beichen is personally escorting His Highness out of the city,
with Eagle Guards keeping strict watch along the way.
Tell me,
how are we going to rescue His Highness?
That's not difficult.
Your Highness?
Your Highness, do you have a way
to rescue our King?
I am close friends with King Xuannan.
How could I possibly stand by and do nothing?
Thank you, Your Highness.
King Yan is powerful
and has framed King Xuannan in dire straits.
Although I am the Crown Prince,
I have no troops at my command.
It's truly difficult for me to contend with him.
Be assured, Your Highness.
As long as you can rescue our King,
we, the Xuannan Army, will remember your kindness
and will surely repay your favor
by following your leadership, Your Highness.
That's excellent.
I have a plan in mind.