[The Night is Still Young]
[Episode 27]
[Taiji Hall]
♫The wind stirs the war flames, and the rain-soaked fur returns with the geese♫
♫In the capital, the pace of carriages and horses is slow♫
♫Several lifetimes of devotion, yet this bond remains unresolved♫
♫Entangled in grudges, love hangs by a thread♫
♫Unable to part with the eyes♫
♫I point to the moon, questioning beneath it, before the city tower♫
♫She's in red♫
♫With angry eyes, a word severs grudges♫
[Taiji Hall]
♫A sword in the heart, a farewell waves over the land♫
♫This life has slipped away, the next life will be complete♫
♫A heart of purest jade♫
♫In the dim night, searching for her, past a thousand sails♫
♫Watching the snow fall, year after year♫
♫The song is not over, making a promise to grow old together♫
♫The night is still young, I will not betray the people♫
♫Nor will I betray her♫
♫This empty city is so regrettable without you♫
♫Even if the skies fall♫
♫Covering my eyes♫
♫In the next life, no more separations♫
Your Majesty.
I've assigned more men
to strictly guard the gates of Ye City,
checking every one coming in and out.
We will definitely capture Ye Mingxuan and his accomplices.
Only ten days left.
Your Majesty.
Chu Mo,
you've been with me for so long.
You should know what I care about the most.
No matter what,
within ten days,
we must eliminate the threat of Ye Mingxuan
completely.
Yes, Your Majesty.
By the way,
how is the situation with
those princes?
I've sent people to investigate the princes
thoroughly.
The Fourth Prince's mental condition is congenital,
and even Hua Tuo reborn
would struggle to cure it.
The Sixth Prince, though talented,
is indulging in pleasure-seeking.
As for the Seventh Prince,
despite his young age,
he has the best character.
His writings are brilliant,
and his horsemanship and archery skills are among the best.
This Seventh Prince is not bad.
By the way,
you need to continue to
secretly observe those court ministers.
The regent ministers are crucial.
Yes.
My lady.
It's alright.
My lady,
the Imperial Affairs Department takes care of this specifically.
Why bother yourself?
The secret recipe for making soft armor by the Shangguan's army
is a unique formula,
even unknown to the Imperial Affairs Department.
There's no need to rush.
It's been cold for so many days.
Today, there are finally some sunshine.
Why don't we go for a walk?
Yeah,
the coldest winter is about to pass.
Counting the days,
it's only ten days left.
Why are you in the mood for painting today?
I won't show you.
Look over there.
You painted epiphyllum?
An unfinished painting
is not for others to appreciate.
Then I've come at just the right time.
We can paint together.
Capturing both form and spirit.
That's great.
However beautiful this epiphyllum is,
its beauty lasts only for a moment.
But as long as it has bloomed freely,
why care about how long it lasts?
That's true.
As long as we're happy in the moment we have,
that's enough.
Don't you think so?
As long as when we think of the epiphyllum,
we recall its most beautiful form,
that's all that matters.
Your Majesty!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What brings you all here?
Your Majesty,
although the traitor Ye Mingxuan has been wanted,
his remnants are still lurking in the palace.
If they are not completely eradicated,
the poison of these remnants cannot be eliminated,
posing a great threat.
Ye Mingxuan's accomplices in the palace
have long been eliminated.
What remnants are you talking about?
Your Majesty,
the woman who almost became Ye Mingxuan's Crown Princess
is now accompanying you.
They never got married,
so there is no such Crown Princess!
Although they weren't married,
it was widely known.
Your Majesty, keeping Shangguan Weiyang by your side
is not only against propriety
but also dangerous for you!
Shangguan Weiyang
was bestowed upon me as a consort by the late emperor!
But you were not married at the time.
This matter needs no further discussion.
All of you should focus on your own duties.
My private affairs need no more concern.
Your Majesty,
this memorial is jointly submitted by all the senior officials.
The traitors plotted against Your Majesty,
nearly causing turmoil in the court and country.
For the sake of the Great Ye and
for the safety of the people,
we implore Your Majesty to banish the remnants from the palace
and never allow them to set foot in Ye City again.
We implore Your Majesty to prioritize the welfare of the state!
Please, Your Majesty, prioritize the welfare of the state.
What if I refuse?
We are all dedicated to the court
and to Your Majesty.
Please consider this carefully, Your Majesty!
Please consider this carefully, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
Thinking about it,
the foreign ministers coming to congratulate the new emperor
should be arriving soon.
My lady, what's wrong?
I heard that
Lord Zhang and the others plan
to keep kneeling in the Imperial Garden.
But don't worry,
His Majesty has already sent Chu Mo to handle it.
I'm not worried.
His Majesty won't harm these senior officials.
When the time comes,
I will also give them an explanation.
Then why do you still look so worried?
There are many state affairs.
The burden on his shoulders is too heavy.
Yet I can't do anything for him.
I think
as long as His Majesty sees you,
he'll surely be happy.
His birthday is coming soon.
I should do something for him.
Your Majesty,
Miss Shangguan said she's waiting for you in the flower forest.
♫Reciting a verse, dreaming of a scene of♫
♫Similar pasts♫
♫In the end, it is like passing clouds, all in vain♫
♫Looking up and seeing the moonlight♫
♫Just like in a past life♫
♫This moment's wish is to be together♫
♫In this life, once more♫
♫To experience this rise and fall♫
♫Just to be with you until the end of life♫
♫Can I be spared from the fate♫
♫Of being forgotten by each other?♫
♫Holding a solitary lamp♫
♫To part ways with that old acquaintance♫
♫This life is lonely, the road stretches endlessly♫
Weiyang.
Your Majesty.
This is the mansion,
♫Parting ways, free as water and clouds♫
not the palace.
♫The south wind fulfills the wish; the dream fades away♫
You can just call me by my name.
It's not proper.
♫Under the Three-Life Stone, I felt the sorrow of the pear blossoms♫
Although I am the emperor of the state,
♫A glance back, and still, deep love remains♫
I am just Ye Beichen to you.
♫Memories linger, refusing to fade quietly♫
Alright.
Ye Beichen.
♫Time flies, and the love, hate, joy, sorrow♫
The flower forest is especially beautiful today.
♫Partings and reunions come alive on the page♫
Did you arrange it all by yourself?
Everything has been rearranged.
♫A wish from the past life, fulfilled in this life♫
♫The world is eternal, and longing lasts long♫
I really appreciate it.
For you,
♫Turn that unwillingness into meaning♫
and for today.
it's worth it.
♫Turn regret into sorrow♫
What's special about today?
♫Time slowly tells the stories of the past♫
Come.
Why have you prepared so many river lanterns?
Have you forgotten?
Today is your birthday.
You're so busy dealing with state affairs now,
sleeping at midnight and waking at dawn,
working hard day and night.
You've even forgotten your own birthday.
It's not a big deal anyway.
But you remembered it for me.
♫In this life, once more♫
♫To experience this rise and fall♫
Your matters are important to me.
♫Just to be with you until the end of life♫
♫Can I be spared from the fate♫
♫Of being forgotten by each other?♫
Hurry,
make a wish to the river lantern.
It's said that on one's birthday,
wishes made to river lanterns are most likely to come true.
♫Holding a solitary lamp♫
♫To part ways with that old acquaintance♫
♫This life is lonely, the road stretches endlessly♫
Can a river lantern really grant wishes?
♫Parting ways, free as water and clouds♫
♫The south wind fulfills the wish; the dream fades away♫
♫Under the Three-Life Stone, I felt the sorrow of the pear blossoms♫
♫A glance back, and still, deep love remains♫
Lantern,
♫Memories linger, refusing to fade quietly♫
I dare not ask for completeness.
I only hope that in the days when I'm gone,
♫Time flies, and the love, hate, joy, sorrow♫
he can protect the people
♫Partings and reunions come alive on the page♫
and bring blessings to the world,
and then,
♫A wish from the past life, fulfilled in this life♫
forget about me.
♫The world is eternal, and longing lasts long♫
Don't let him be trapped in a future without me.
♫Turn that unwillingness into meaning♫
He deserves a better life.
♫Turn regret into sorrow♫
♫Time slowly tells the stories of the past♫
Weiyang.
Thank you.
♫Time flies, and the love, hate, joy, sorrow♫
What wish did you make?
♫Partings and reunions come alive on the page♫
♫A wish from the past life, fulfilled in this life♫
♫The world is eternal, and longing lasts long♫
♫Turn that unwillingness into meaning♫
Lantern,
♫Turn regret into sorrow♫
I've never believed in deities,
♫Time slowly tells the stories of the past♫
but now I hope
there really are deities in this world
that can tell me how to achieve completeness,
not failing the people
or my beloved one.
I'm willing to burn all the incense in the world.
Greetings, Your Majes—
I've said before,
you don't need to bow to me.
The military tally of the Shangguan's army?
My father once said
that the military tally must be
handed over to someone trustworthy.
Now that you've ascended the throne,
it's time to hand over the military tally.
I have a way to lure Ye Mingxuan out.
What's your plan?
He is now like a homeless dog,
with no more power to rely on.
His only hope now
is the military tally.
I understand.
[Tomb of Shangguan Ting, General of Loyalty and Valor]
Although Ye Mingxuan is in hiding,
he must have sent people to watch in secret.
As long as the military tally of Shangguan's army
shows even the slightest trace,
Ye Mingxuan will show up.
[Tomb of Shangguan Ting, General of Loyalty and Valor]
Father,
Ye Mingxuan's crimes have all been exposed.
Now his power
has been completely eradicated.
The one who now rules over the Great Ye
is Ye Beichen.
Father,
I haven't forgotten your teachings.
Only if Ye Beichen
can truly live up to the title of a wise and capable ruler,
will I hand over the military tally to him.
[Tomb of Shangguan Ting, General of Loyalty and Valor]
Let's go.
Hiding things in your own father's tombstone,
intentionally disturbing his peace after death.
[Tomb of Shangguan Ting, General of Loyalty and Valor]
Pick up the item.
Yes.
My hands!
[Tomb of Shangguan Ting, General of Loyalty and Valor]
So it was a trap.
Ye Mingxuan, you can't escape now.
Get him!