[The Night is Still Young]
[Episode 14]
I survived.
You should fulfill your promise now.
I truly didn't misjudge you.
Refine blood with poison and feed the gu with blood.
perhaps
you can really contain the King of Gu.
What should we do next?
This is the result of my countless efforts,
the most extraordinary poison in the world,
the king of all Gu,
the Life and Death Gu.
You use the Death Gu,
and she uses the Life Gu.
As long as you both serve as vessels,
the Death Gu can drive the Life Gu
and bring the dead back to life.
One life, one death.
I wonder what choices
you will make in the next life.
Lanterns year after year,
favorable weather for all of us.
Today is the Lantern Festival
of the year of Jiayou.
Weiyang.
♫Reciting a verse, dreaming of a scene of♫
♫Similar pasts♫
♫In the end, it is like passing clouds, all in vain♫
♫Looking up and seeing the moonlight♫
♫Just like in a past life♫
♫This moment's wish is to be together♫
♫In this life, once more♫
♫To experience this rise and fall♫
♫Just to be with you until the end of life♫
♫Can I be spared from the fate♫
♫Of being forgotten by each other?♫
Could it really be you who saved me?
How is it possible?
How could this be?
The arrowhead with a Weiyang flower.
Why?
Even if I wanted to kill you,
you still saved me. Why?
Why?
Why do you do so much for me?
Your Highness.
Weiyang,
in the end, you still
chose to leave.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, a message from the palace states
that His Majesty has learned about General Shangguan's matter.
I'm afraid His Majesty will soon send someone
to summon you to the palace for questioning.
Have you seen the Queen?
I have not seen her, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
You should first appease the palace envoy.
Try to buy as much time as possible.
I'll deal with it after I find Weiyang.
Your Highness, this matter is urgent.
If not handled properly, I'm afraid it might...
Go.
Yes, Your Highness.
Brother Beichen?
Brother Beichen.
You shielded Shangguan Weiyang from the explosion.
How could you not consider your own safety?
This matter doesn't concern you.
How can it not concern me?
Brother Beichen,
you are my only family.
If anything happens to you,
do you know how heartbroken I would be?
Shangguan Weiyang has caused you to be hurt so many times,
each time worse than the last.
Brother Beichen,
you can't be with her anymore.
Brother Beichen.
Even if you don't want to hear it now,
I have to say it.
I am the one who can truly help you,
the one who can protect you.
What can you help me with?
Your situation is delicate now.
You're viewed with suspicion by His Majesty
and isolated by the court officials.
Now, with the Shangguan family incident,
even the common people
have doubts about you.
It can be said you're surrounded by enemies on all sides.
Even if the whole world is against me, so what?
I know, Brother Beichen,
you don't want chaos in the world
or the people to suffer.
I can help you clear your name
and prove your innocence.
Help me?
Yes.
I can do anything for you, Brother Beichen,
as long as you leave Shangguan Weiyang
and be with me from now on.
Wishful thinking!
Brother Beichen,
why are you so stubborn?
Did Ye Mingxuan really kill my father,
destroy my Shangguan family,
and try to take my life?
Did Ye Beichen really try to save me,
even at the cost of his own life?
Those things I saw—
were they dreams
or things that really happened?
Is all of this true or false?
Weiyang,
I know there are many misunderstandings between us.
Disturbing General Shangguan's body
was truly unavoidable.
Because I believe
there must be something suspicious about General Shangguan's death.
I must investigate thoroughly.
Weiyang,
I'm sorry.
I neglected your feelings.
Please trust me.
Give me some more time,
and I will definitely uncover the truth!
How long?
Seven days, is that alright?
Please, Uncle.
His Majesty requests your presence.
Father,
King Yan, Ye Beichen, disregards the law.
Not only did he kill General Shangguan,
but he also held Weiyang captive.
To destroy evidence,
he even went so far as to desecrate General Shangguan's body.
His ambition is treacherous, his intentions punishable.
I advise
to strip him of his military power and imprison him.
Is what Mingxuan says true?
The reason I disturbed General Shangguan's body
was actually to investigate the case.
Was it really to investigate
or to destroy evidence?
Uncle, you know best in your heart.
Your Majesty, I have something to say.
Speak.
There are indeed many suspicious points about my father's death.
To avoid being exploited by those with ulterior motives,
I, Weiyang,
am willing to give King Yan a chance to uncover the truth.
Weiyang, you...
You may have misunderstood.
King Yan did not imprison me,
nor did I personally witness
him killing my father.
But we were all there at the scene.
Before General Shangguan died,
he called out for Ye Beichen.
It's also possible
that my father wanted Ye Beichen
to uncover the truth for him
and clear his name.
[Mourning]
[Tomb of Shangguan Ting, General of Loyalty and Valor]
When I was little, my father was busy with military affairs.
I was afraid of the dark,
so every time he went out,
he would prepare a gift
and hide it in a corner of the courtyard.
[Tomb of Shangguan Ting, General of Loyalty and Valor]
He told me
that as long as I found it, he would come back.
So, I searched
and searched.
Every time I found it,
Father would always return on time.
He never broke his promise.
But this time,
no matter how many clues Father left,
whether I find the real culprit or not,
he won't be coming back.
Don't worry,
I'll make sure the real culprit pays for this in blood.
I can trust your words for now,
but I also want to search for the real culprit with you.
Alright.
Try this.
Your Highness, please have a taste.
His Highness personally cooked this for you.
You said there's something suspicious about my father's death.
Have you found any clues?
When I first saw General Shangguan
at the villa,
I suspected
that he was being controlled by something.
So I snuck into the general's mansion
to examine the body.
Sure enough,
I found a Gu worm
in your father's Danzhong acupoint,
but I didn't know what kind it was.
Brother Beichen?
Brother Beichen,
although you didn't agree to my proposal,
your business is my business.
Look.
[Compendium of All Poisons]
There are rumors that General Shangguan's death was suspicious.
So, I looked into the Compendium of All Poisons my father left behind.
It seems it might be of some use to you.
You can take a look at it.
Brother Beichen,
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to introduce it to you.
I'll go back and study the Compendium of All Poisons first.
Change your clothes later
and come find me.
Okay.
I appreciate your help with the Compendium of All Poisons.
Brother Beichen.
Take a look at this.
It records many types of Gu worms.
Is there anything similar to the one found in my father's body?
Ghost Gu.
Completely black,
cold-loving and bloodthirsty,
emitting black mist,
able to control a person's nerves
as if they were possessed by a ghost,
making them act against their own will.
I think this is the one.
♫Reciting a verse, dreaming of a scene of♫
♫Similar pasts♫
♫In the end, it is like passing clouds, all in vain♫
♫Looking up and seeing the moonlight♫
♫Just like in a past life♫
♫This moment's wish is to be together♫
♫In this life, once more♫
♫To experience this rise and fall♫
♫Just to be with you until the end of life♫
♫Can I be spared from the fate♫
♫Of being forgotten by each other?♫
♫Holding a solitary lamp♫
♫To part ways with that old acquaintance♫
♫This life is lonely, the road stretches endlessly♫
♫Parting ways, free as water and clouds♫
♫The south wind fulfills the wish; the dream fades away♫
♫Under the Three-Life Stone, I felt the sorrow of the pear blossoms♫
♫A glance back, and still, deep love remains♫
♫Memories linger, refusing to fade quietly♫
♫Time flies, and the love, hate, joy, sorrow♫
♫Partings and reunions come alive on the page♫
♫A wish from the past life, fulfilled in this life♫
♫The world is eternal, and longing lasts long♫
♫Turn that unwillingness into meaning♫
♫Turn regret into sorrow♫
♫Time slowly tells the stories of the past♫
♫Under the Three-Life Stone, I felt the sorrow of the pear blossoms♫
♫A glance back, and still, deep love remains♫
♫Memories linger, refusing to fade quietly♫
♫A wish from the past life, fulfilled in this life♫
♫The world is eternal, and longing lasts long♫
♫Turn that unwillingness into meaning♫
♫Turn regret into sorrow♫
♫Time slowly tells the stories of the past♫