[The Night is Still Young]
[Episode 15]
♫In this life, once more♫
♫To experience this rise and fall♫
♫Just to be with you until the end of life♫
♫Can I be spared from the fate♫
♫Of being forgotten by each other?♫
♫Holding a solitary lamp♫
♫To part ways with that old acquaintance♫
♫This life is lonely, the road stretches endlessly♫
♫Parting ways, free as water and clouds♫
♫The south wind fulfills the wish; the dream fades away♫
♫Under the Three-Life Stone, I felt the sorrow of the pear blossoms♫
♫A glance back, and still, deep love remains♫
♫Memories linger, refusing to fade quietly♫
♫Time flies, and the love, hate, joy, sorrow♫
♫Partings and reunions come alive on the page♫
Weiyang.
Weiyang, wake up.
Hand over the swapped Gu worm.
I swapped the Ghost Gu with Love Gu.
But Brother Beichen,
don't you understand
my true feelings for you?
Using such a lowly trick like Love Gu,
you dare to speak of true feelings?
Brother Beichen,
I was wrong.
There's no place for you in the King Yan's mansion anymore.
Brother Beichen,
have you forgotten the promise you made to my father?
It's only out of respect for Master
that I'm sparing your life.
This is the last courtesy I'm extending to you.
You may leave.
Father,
I want to eat your cherry pancakes.
If my daughter wants to eat,
I'll go make them for you right now.
Try this,
it's a new product from the Divine Pastry Shop.
Alright,
my pleasure.
[City Defense Requirement]
[To General Shangguan]
General Shangguan!
General Shangguan.
Copper ash.
All the counterfeit coins have been moved.
The counterfeit coin case is under intense scrutiny now.
Feng Xuanyi has been arrested.
General Shangguan is dead.
Ye Beichen is also investigating the case.
The current situation is very unfavorable for us.
We must clear out this place immediately.
Yes.
No one
can leave here alive.
Watch out!
Ye Beichen!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I didn't expect that by cleaning out, they meant
sealing the cave entrance
to conceal all the evidence.
Using any means necessary
is their way of doing things.
What should we do now?
We won't be buried here forever, will we?
Don't worry,
we'll definitely find a way out.
♫Lend me a moment of joy, with dreams of fantasy♫
♫Lend me half the warmth, to heal a lifetime♫
♫Lifting a cold lamp, illuminating the city♫
Oh, right,
I haven't asked you yet.
♫Who waits in the fleeting years♫
Why did you come here?
♫Refusing to budge an inch♫
I investigated
General Shangguan's villa
♫Hate that we can't meet♫
and found mining soil and copper ash.
♫Lend me a setting sun, to fall on a lonely city♫
I followed the secret letter my father left me
and finally found this place.
♫Lend me the silent wind, to accompany me for a while♫
But
we still couldn't catch the culprit.
♫Frost on my heart, as cold as bone-eating ice♫
You must have
♫Chasing memories of years gone by♫
an answer in your heart, right?
♫Geese pass, leaving only regrets and cries♫
Ye Mingxuan's vicious ambition
♫Our love was a mutual mistake♫
is already obvious now.
♫I sigh half my life, unable to leave the fog♫
If it was really Ye Mingxuan who killed my father,
I will kill him.
♫Lighting another stick of sandalwood♫
But now
they have moved the counterfeit coins.
♫Burning the bitterness of parting♫
Isn't it even more difficult
♫Looking back, life is but a dream♫
to find evidence?
♫Leaving only love and hate to return to the dust♫
Don't worry,
even in the darkest situation,
there's always a path
that leads to light.
Let's go
and find the way.
Take it easy.
Be careful.
Again?
They say things don't happen more than three times.
Are you ever going to stop?
I saw the moon is particularly beautiful tonight.
We'd like to invite you to enjoy
the moon with us.
Enjoy the moon?
There's no need for such a big fuss.
I see your true intentions are elsewhere.
Fine.
I'll be straightforward then.
When did you
start colluding with Ye Mingxuan?
I... I'm in your mansion every day.
If I were to collude with anyone, it would be you.
Even now, you still dare to be defiant.
Don't, don't, don't,
Ye Beichen, let me out quickly.
I am the mighty King Xuannan of Yunnan.
Isn't what you're doing too undignified for me?
Dignified?
Being Ye Mingxuan's lackey is dignified?
I'll ask you one last time.
What promise did he make to you?
Don't forget,
you came to my mansion to recover from illness,
not as a guest.
I can send you to the imperial prison anytime.
There are 100 ways to make you talk in there.
If you want to know the answer,
let Weiyang come to my room.
I'll tell her everything.
You're really not afraid of death, are you?
She is Queen Yan.
What qualifications do you have to talk to her?
Whether I have the qualifications or not
is not up to you.
Never mind.
There must be evidence of his collusion with Ye Mingxuan.
Let me talk to him.
Weiyang,
I knew you would save me.
Just like last time when I was in danger,
you did the same thing,
risking everything to save me.
Feng Xuanyi,
since you know I've done you a favor,
but how have you repaid me?
You secretly colluded with Ye Mingxuan
and killed my father.
Heaven and Earth be my witness.
Weiyang,
you must believe me.
Even if I die,
I would never harm you.
I just want to know the whole truth.
If you want to know the answer,
you must answer me three questions.
Go ahead.
First question,
what do you usually like to do?
You've been building up to this for so long,
just to ask this?
This is very important to me.
I practice archery daily.
Occasionally, I brew tea and make incense.
Second question,
Weiyang,
what kind of person do you like?
I'll only know when I meet them.
Well, Feng Xuanyi,
what are you really trying to do?
I just want to ask if I have a chance
to win your love.
No.
I understand.
Actually, many emotions in this world
are unrequited.
But I believe that
with my personal charm,
one day,
you will be mine.
Now it's time for you to fulfill your promise.
Actually, you guessed right.
Ye Mingxuan did want to build a great cause with me.
He promised me
that if I helped him seize the throne,
he would grant me a kingdom of my own.
That day,
General Shangguan discovered the secret of the mine.
Xuanyi, you're here.
Come and see how this batch of goods is.
Can it be circulated?
General Shangguan tried to persuade him to turn back,
but
he was blinded by power and profit.
It was really Ye Mingxuan
who killed my father.
He asked me to destroy the evidence,
and then ruthlessly killed General Shangguan,
and framed Ye Beichen for it.
Weiyang.
After being reborn once,
not only did I fail to change the fate of the Shangguan family,
but I actually accelerated my father's death.
It's all my fault.
I misjudged Ye Mingxuan.
I failed to uncover his true face earlier.
I failed to protect my father.
Weiyang.
You're awake.
You've been with me all along?
I want to show you something.
What is this?
This is the Gu that was swapped by Huan Yan.
Ye Mingxuan used it to control my father
and then framed you.
Ye Mingxuan has finally shown his true colors.
But soon,
I will make him tell the truth
and avenge your father.
Fifth Prince, please remain calm.
There are fallen rocks blocking the road ahead.
Let me clear the path.
Where are you?
Is anyone there?
Ye Mingxuan.
General Shangguan?
A life for a life.
It was Ye Beichen who killed you.
If you want revenge, you should go to him!
Ye Mingxuan.
How dare you deceive me?
The one who killed me is you,
not Ye Beichen.
You're already dead.
Does it matter
who killed you?
You counterfeited cpins, embezzled weapons,
and colluded with feudal lords to rebel.
Every one of your doings deserves death.
How dare you still argue?
So what if it was me?
If you hadn't insisted on reporting to Father,
I wouldn't have thought of killing you!
Only by blowing up your body,
would the Gu worm not be exposed.
Blame yourself for being too loyal
and failing to see the situation clearly!
Huan Yan.
It's time for your Ghost Gu to show its power.
Don't let me down.
Repeat after me,
Ye Beichen is the one who killed me.
Ye Beichen has no grudge against you.
Why would you frame him
for your evil deeds?
Ye Beichen,
he dared to compete with me for the throne
and took away my Weiyang.
He deserves to die!
You approached Weiyang
for the military power of the Shangguan family.
Nonsense!
My feelings for Weiyang...
Ye Beichen?
Watch out!
Weiyang!