[The Night is Still Young]
[Episode 19]
My lady!
What's the matter? Why are you in such a hurry?
Someone claiming to be a messenger from the Xuannan Army
delivered a confidential letter,
and requested that you open and read it personally.
You only need to exploit Ye Beichen's weakness
to lure him away.
[King Yan's Mansion]
Even if he refuses to let go,
we can still buy time.
Your Highness.
Chu Mo, I need to go to the Town God's Temple.
You take the team and continue forward.
Yes.
You come with me.
And I will lead another team
to intercept the prisoner on the official road.
Your Highness,
you truly are prescient.
As long as we frame the Xuannan Army's mutiny
and Feng Xuanyi's death
as a mutual destruction with the Eagle Guards,
both sides will fight to the death.
When the Xuannan Army revolts,
and court disputes arise again,
that will be my true moment of power.
Your Highness is wise.
How dare you
kidnap my Queen?
You're asking for death!
Your Highness,
I'm not afraid to die.
The Queen Yan will be buried with us anyway.
Come on!
Used by thieves, utterly foolish.
If you were my subordinate,
I would have already cut off your head
and hung it outside the tent.
Take a good look.
This is His Highness's handwriting.
Ye Mingxuan has just become the Crown Prince
and urgently needs military power.
But Jun Yang is leading troops outside
and is cut off from information.
He only knows that I'm cooperating with Ye Mingxuan
but doesn't know I've been harmed by him.
I'm worried Ye Mingxuan will deceive them.
If the Xuannan Army is used by him,
it will surely lead to endless troubles.
You can give this blood letter to Jun Yang
to eliminate future troubles.
[The one who harmed me is Ye Mingxuan.]
Ye Mingxuan actually betrayed His Highness
and played us for fools!
You've been used as pawns.
The time you bought is enough
for Ye Mingxuan to step on your brothers' bodies
and assassinate Feng Xuanyi.
Let's go!
Hurry.
I guessed Ye Mingxuan wouldn't let me leave easily
and would kill me.
But I didn't expect
you to protect me.
If you die,
the Xuannan Army will rebel,
and the court will be in turmoil.
Tonight, you'll leave with the Eagle Guards through the small path.
Your Highness, it's Ye Mingxuan's death squad.
It's indeed him.
What a Crown Prince.
I will always remember your great
kindness to the Xuannan Army.
[Tomb of Shangguan Ting, General of Loyalty and Valor]
Now that we've cut off Ye Mingxuan's connection with the Xuannan Army.
It's like cutting off one of his arms.
Ye Mingxuan has played all his cards.
[Tomb of Shangguan Ting, General of Loyalty and Valor]
He's at the end of his rope.
But we must also prevent him from desperate counterattacks.
When our great revenge is achieved,
I suppose we
and everything around us
will gradually get better, right?
Of course.
There will surely be peace and prosperity throughout the state.
[Tomb of Shangguan Ting, General of Loyalty and Valor]
♫The wind stirs the war flames, and the rain-soaked fur returns with the geese♫
♫In the capital, the pace of carriages and horses is slow♫
♫Several lifetimes of devotion, yet this bond remains unresolved♫
♫Entangled in grudges, love hangs by a thread♫
♫Unable to part with the eyes♫
♫I point to the moon, questioning beneath it, before the city tower♫
♫She's in red♫
Your Highness.
♫With angry eyes, a word severs grudges♫
The King Gu's backlash is becoming more frequent.
Your body...
♫A sword in the heart, a farewell waves over the land♫
My time is running out.
♫This life has slipped away, the next life will be complete♫
The most urgent matter now
is to eliminate Ye Mingxuan.
♫A heart of purest jade♫
♫In the dim night, searching for her, past a thousand sails♫
What about Her Highness?
Since we've chosen to take this step,
♫Watching the snow fall, year after year♫
we can't back down now.
♫The song is not over, making a promise to grow old together♫
If we leave enough beautiful memories,
♫The night is still young, I will not betray the people♫
she won't be
♫Nor will I betray her♫
so regretful when I'm gone in the future.
♫This empty city is so regrettable without you♫
Your Highness.
♫Even if the skies fall♫
♫Covering my eyes♫
♫In the next life, no more separations♫
♫With angry eyes, a word severs grudges♫
♫A sword in the heart, a farewell waves over the land♫
Pray for blessings and good fortune; holy water to ward off disasters.
♫This life has slipped away, the next life will be complete♫
I never thought the usually cold-hearted King Yan
would have a side that enjoys festivities with the common people.
♫A heart of purest jade♫
♫In the dim night, searching for her, past a thousand sails♫
♫Watching the snow fall, year after year♫
♫The song is not over, making a promise to grow old together♫
♫The night is still young, I will not betray the people♫
♫Nor will I betray her♫
♫This empty city is so regrettable without you♫
♫Even if the skies fall♫
♫Covering my eyes♫
♫In the next life, no more separations♫
♫The night is still young, I will not betray the people♫
♫Nor will I betray her♫
♫This empty city is so regrettable without you♫
♫Even if the skies fall♫
♫Covering my eyes♫
♫In the next life, no more separations♫
This is how I remember you.
Galloping on horseback,
full of vigor and spirit,
bending the bow with an arrow falls in the setting sun.
I didn't expect
you would remember
so many moments so clearly.
Of course.
These are our memories.
Yeah,
beautiful memories
should be mentioned often
and carved into time,
so that they will be enduring
and never forgotten.
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
I have urgent matters to report.
I'll be right back.
Your Highness,
this is the location of
Ye Mingxuan's troop garrison found by the Eagle Guards.
Garrisoning troops requires money.
I suppose he gained a lot from the last
counterfeit coin case.
As for military equipment,
he has lost the supply from the Xuannan Army.
He can only borrow from the imperial armory,
using inferior goods as substitutes.
Have you found out
when they're transporting the equipment?
It's tonight, Your Highness.
Good.
We need to catch them red-handed to convict them.
This time,
I will not let him escape.
Order the Eagle Guards to lie in wait on the official road.
I will lead the troops to surround and eliminate them.
As you command.
Weiyang.
I have urgent military matters to attend to.
It's a pity...
It's alright.
Duty comes first.
These paintings can be drawn anytime.
Wait for me to return.
Your Highness, they're here.
Don't move! Surrender your weapons and you won't be killed!
Your Highness,
the people and military equipment
are all here.
Something's not right.
So many military equipments
can't be escorted by just a few people.
Ye Beichen?
♫Who inquires amidst the dim lights♫
♫These stars that fill the sky♫
♫The fate of love and hate, separation and union♫
♫Blame the depth of our love♫
♫Meeting you feels like encountering an old friend♫
♫As if in a past life, passing by the door♫
♫The past is hard to keep, attachment leaves no trace♫
♫How can I join you in this life♫
♫If the soul doesn't cross, if the person doesn't return♫
♫Could you lend me the rise and fall of the next life♫
♫If fate protects us♫
Ye Beichen!
♫In the midst of heavy snow♫
♫Eternal love through the ages♫
♫If love does not fail♫
Ye Beichen!
♫In the depths of blooming flowers♫
♫Accompany you to the twilight years♫
No.
♫If one life and one death are our destiny♫
Ye Beichen!
No!
♫Who inquires amidst the dim lights♫
♫These stars that fill the sky♫
Ye Beichen!
♫The fate of love and hate, separation and union♫
No!
♫Blame the depth of our love♫
Ye Beichen!
Wake up!
♫Meeting you feels like encountering an old friend♫
♫As if in a past life, passing by the door♫
No!
My lady!
Something terrible has happened!
News has come from the Eagle Guards
that His Highness has fallen into an ambush.
What exactly happened?
Your Highness,
last night, His Highness discovered
the Crown Prince's secret troop garrison.
He led the Eagle Guards
to intercept their military equipment transportation,
but they fell into a trap.
Whether they will survive is uncertain.
Where did this happen?
Take me there quickly.
Yes.
Search.
Keep searching.
As long as there's no body,
it's a good sign.
We can't give up even the slightest hope.
Yes, Your Highness.
Let's go!
-Yes!
This is...
My lady.
Could His Highness have been captured?
They disappeared because of Ye Mingxuan's
secret troop garrison.
There must be
a register of provisions
and a list of soldiers.
Such important things,
he must have hidden them himself.
Mingxuan.
[Past Life]
Weiyang.
As long as we find the ledger,
even if Ye Beichen has truly been captured by Ye Mingxuan,
we'll have leverage.
[Ledger]
Weiyang?