Can't take Li Zhian to Taimiao
Why
If she finds a flaw
What to do if our plan is exposed
How smart can this be for those who believe in love between men and women
Besides, she's a blind man
Even if she sees it
Just say that my father asked me to find it
If you can't find it, you'll torture it
She loves me so much
Hearing this
She will definitely tell the whereabouts of Long Yu.
But what if she doesn't believe it
Why are you feeling sorry for her?
Stay with each other day and night
You're really moved by that blind man
What's the joke Chen Lang is
The Seventh Prince is a lump of wood
Even a woman like me has never been moved
How could he fall in love with that blind man Li Zhian
Too
The Seventh Prince is really worried about Li Zhian
What's the charm of this blind man?
Just because she is born innocent than me
Is it nobler than me
That afternoon
Go to Taimiao as planned
Oro Oro
Oro
What are you doing
Don't prepare for the Taimiao
The protection of the family is meaningless
I will definitely overturn the murderer's plan
Let his true face be made public
Only this
Only then can he understand the pain of survivors
See how she is
Go and have a look
Princess
Why is it so hot
I heard that I was hit by a ghost in the Taimiao a few days ago
Frightened
Have been sick for many days
She used to be able to lead troops to fight
I'm afraid I can't live now
Ai Butler Duan let her die by herself
Let's go quickly and don't worry
Go quickly
Let's go
Being hit by a ghost in Taimiao
What's the matter for me
The emperor's brothers are here to seek medicine
Seventh brother really enjoys it
The last special five stone slab
This is finished
Not the emperor
What I want to ask for is
Sada-san
Just because my brother has frequent nightmares recently
I
I think the Seventh Prince is very refreshing
The amber shavings in this horror
It's a drug to treat horror and loss of mind
Now in this house
Have this disease
Need medicine
I'm afraid it's only that blind man
Li Zhian
Seventh brother cares about her so much
I also came to ask for medicine for her
Could it be that I like her
I don't
You two are matching
A sick man
A star of destruction
otherwise
I'll give her to you
She's a blind man anyway
Can't tell who is who
Brother, don't joke with me
Li Zhian has not yet revealed the whereabouts of the Dragon Jade Treasure
She can't die
Let me give you medicine
only
Clean Yurou's feet
Chenlang, you are so bad
Painting plum blossoms
The Seventh Prince
You're a good person
You boiled the medicine for your third sister-in-law
Thanks
You're all soaked
This medicine is not wet
This is for you
I'll go back now
The third prince suddenly wants to take you to Taimiao
The servants are not prepared
It's time to take a shower
I'll prepare now
He was just a temporary idea
You don't have to be nervous
Just prepare it simply
yes
This taste
Princess, are you okay
Princess, I brought you a bottle of medicine
It will be better if you wipe it on your hands
Who are you
Why should I give me medicine
I'm just a little maid
I have to leave quickly
Otherwise, it will be discovered
It's the fragrance of wintersweet
It turns out that she was the one who gave me medicine to treat the injury.
It's a plum blossom
You are injured in Huamei
Come here soon
All the servants broke the cup with clumsy
Stop ignoring the cup
Don't underestimate this wound
If it is infected with dirty
Become a carbuncle
But it's troublesome
Princess, I
I have medicine in the box of dowry
Remember to wipe it yourself when you go back
Princess, you are so good at painting plums
It's time to be nice to you
Painting plum blossoms
You probably am in the prince's house
The only person who can trust
Are you willing to do something for me
Of course I am the princess's concubine
Be loyal to you
My maid will do it now
This is the medicine you gave
I've been paying attention to it all the time
No one sees it
Please help me prepare for going to Taimiao
Oh, right
Princess, I just heard the maid in the mansion talk
It seems that the water from Taimiao is gone
You don't have to go
Taimiao Water
Um
I remember that Taimiao was not burned
Isn't my ecstasy useless
Damn I wanted to use this medicine
The gang of people pretending to be gods and ghosts
What's going on
Who did it