It's exposed if you dodge
Only
Zhian
who
It's me, it's me
Who is it
It's me
Husband
I just wanted to go out for a walk
I got lost as a result
My hands My hands hurt so much
I know I know
I'll take you to heal
This Li Zhian is sneaking first
Even if you die, you deserve it
There are also problems with these peace signs
I don't know why the seventh prince trusted her
Husband
I'm afraid of pain
Be gentle
good
You can't see
In the future, Huamei must be with you
I don't want to see you hurt again
good
What did your husband do just now
Why are you so alert
As soon as I got closer
There was a powerful weapon flying out of it
Oh, just deal with some official duties
The guards are too nervous
So that's it
My husband is so concerned about the people
It's also a blessing for the people
But my husband is busy until late every day
Pay attention to your body
good
Zhian
I'm dealing with official business today
I want to discuss something with you
Maybe there will be new ideas
Husband just say it
As long as Zhian can help
I must know everything
An old man's wife and daughter were killed in the north
He endured humiliation
From the murderer's house to the accountant, he worked as a coolie to the accountant.
He lived a ten-year terrifying life like this
Later he finally found out
Evidence of the murderer reselling military rations
It just puzzles me
He obviously has a chance to get close to the murderer
Why not choose to take revenge directly
Zhian
if
If your family is killed
You'll choose to take revenge directly
Blood debt and blood compensation
Or endure humiliation
If it were me
I won't seek revenge on the murderer, either
Wouldn't that be with the murderer's life be exchanged for another life
The protection of the family is meaningless
I will definitely overturn the murderer's plan
Let his true face be made public
Only this
Only then can he understand the pain of survivors
I will also seek justice for my entire Li family.
certainly
There is a man who distinguishes right from wrong like a husband
I will definitely give my wife, daughter, and old man a fair
What's wrong with him
It seems like Wushi San is addicted to medicine
Zhian asked someone to take a bath
Painting plum blossoms
The royal children insist on touching the harming thing
So unloved
It's also his own fault
Zhian
Husband, call me
My husband feels uncomfortable again
fine
I'm already done
That's good
By time
The Western Imperial Envoy is coming soon
I wonder what Zhu Huaijin would do with those letters
Will he go to the court to expose Zhu Huaichen
Manager Duan
I heard last night that the princess was injured
Check it out today
It's very good
I'm worried about Butler Duan
My husband took care of him carefully last night
I'm fine, of course
The prince's concubine just entered the mansion
Don't understand the rules
You will be injured if you go around
Today I will tell the princess
In the Prince's Mansion
Be polite during the day
You are not allowed to walk around at night
Butler Duan is so majestic
Pay attention to rules so much
It's really not like the rumor
Make shameful means of becoming the top
It was really pretending last night
You can see clearly
So what
That's just
Just some fun with my husband
Instead of beating my husband
Why not pay attention to the Seventh Prince
What are you doing with Prince Qi
Of course it's for you
Maybe you can still win a title
you
Why don't you talk anymore
Could it be that the Seventh Prince has rejected you
Of course not
I was in a quagmire before
It was the seventh prince who saved me
I remember
It was clearly Duan Yurou who Zhu Huaichen rescued in the brothel
How did it become Zhu Huaijin
You guys are going to take the princess to change clothes quickly
In the afternoon, the third prince will take the prince's concubine to the Taimiao to pray for blessings
Have you heard it
yes
It turns out that Zhu Huaijin saved Duan Yurou in this life
That's why she was driven by him
So what changes will happen to this trip to Taimiao