[iQIYI Present]
♫Spirits in between heaven and earth are scattered♫
♫Spirits in between heaven and earth are scattered while snow blossoming♫
♫Thousand years of time is immortal like amber♫
♫I'm still obsessed♫
♫Twilight is falling into chaos♫
♫Twilight is falling into chaos and past life is hard to let go♫
♫Tears are falling, my love♫
♫Tears are falling, my love is deep like see♫
♫Fate rises and falls♫
♫Fate rises and falls, my heart is sealed♫
♫Love and hate are pouring down♫
♫ Love and hate are pouring down following me♫
♫Lonely safeguarding, going faraway, roaring in anger♫
♫Lonely safeguarding, going faraway, roaring in anger, but never let go♫
♫It's me♫
♫It's me staring at you♫
♫ It's me lighting you up♫
♫It's me♫
♫It's me running towards you♫
♫It's me merging into you♫
♫It's me♫
[Thousand Years For You]
[Episode 11]
Master.
What kind of person is Lu Yan?
No, to be precise.
What kind of monster is he?
Scarier than spirit-hunter?
You two...
Don't you know his legend yet?
The General Yan
is more terrifying than spirit-hunter.
Thousand times more terrifying.
It is said that
three thousand years ago.
The spirit clan and human race
had a war that lasted for decades.
It caused the world to be devastated and bleeding.
At that time,
a young general was newly appointed in ancient Shu.
He alone
put an end to the war between the spirit clan and human race.
Thus,
the future generation of spirit clan
called him
General Yan.
Wait…
In that case,
Lu Yan was a human being.
[Commentary Cigarettes]
No.
To be precise,
he should be half human and half spirit clan.
Legend has it that
General Yan
fell in love with our Spirit Clan Saintess.
Then he was hunted by the spirit clan
and was seriously injured.
In order to save him, the Spirit Clan Saintess
gave him her energy core.
After receiving the energy core from Spirit Clan Saintess,
General Yan's power increased dramatically.
He then became half human and half spirit clan.
Low-born spirit clansmen like us,
we dare not disobey him.
So he really has an old lover.
[Commentary Cigarettes]
What happened to that Saintess?
That energy core
is the source of energy for our spirit clan.
Without the energy core,
her power was greatly reduced.
In the end,
the original body of the Golden Crow was wounded.
Its spirit also dissipated.
However,
recently there are gossips that
three thousand years ago,
General Yan wanted to reunite the spirit of Spirit Clan Saintess.
So he took
one of the remaining spiritual feathers of Spirit Clan Saintess
and placed it in Qingquan Mountain.
He also sealed himself there.
He nourished the spiritual feather with energy core every day.
Day and night, he tormented.
He only hoped that Saintess can reincarnate.
If this comes true,
then our Spirit Clan Saintess
will reappear in the world.
I reckon that
she should be in
someplace around Qingquan Mountain.
Golden crow.
Sacred bird.
Do you remember when you were three or four years old?
You had an illness.
Yes.
You told me.
My father caught a bird from the mountain.
It was from the spirit clan and I ate it.
As a result, I was cured.
Could it be that bird? 20 years ago,
when Senior Master came from Qingquan Mountain
and brought it back
for you to eat in soup.
[Weile Cigarettes]
Master, don't be like this.
Senior Master said,
he just caught a sacred bird in Qingquan Mountain
and took it back for you to eat.
It may not be the Saintess.
Think about it.
Don't deceive yourself.
A sacred bird that can bring dead people back to life.
How can there be so many of them?
It's not a pheasant.
I finally know why he wanted to kill me before.
It turns out
that because I ate his old lover.
Well…
Why
did he send us money along the way?
I got it.
He's deliberately using money as bait.
He wants us to relax our vigilance toward him.
Mr. Zhao.
Help me kill a fish.
Okay.
When the concubine was enjoying the fish,
it took her jewel ring.
She is afraid that we are not good at knife skills,
which may cut the ring.
So she asked me to bring the fish to you.
Use a quick knife to help take out the ring.
Okay, give it to me.
Slowly.
After we let our guard down,
he'll cut me like a fish.
He'll cut my belly open.
And then dig out the sacred bird.
Master.
It's been 20 years. It has been digested.
What do you have left?
Well.
That's a scared bird.
You may not digest it all.
Then Lu Yan is too tough, right?
[No. 3 Room]
And glutinous rice cake.
This is our specialty.
Every room has them.
Try some, girl.
By the way, Dahai.
Do you have glutinous rice cake in your room?
What glutinous rice cake?
At Laifu Inn.
Do you have any glutinous rice cake?
No.
Sure enough.
No wonder that I feel the taste of glutinous rice cake
exactly the same as the one in Qingquan Town.
Lu Yan is coming with us.
He's doing it on purpose.
Let us stay in the free room.
Go to Laifu Inn.
What is this?
Inviting you into the tile.
Into a jar.
Yes, that's what it means.
This Lu Yan is too evil.
Dahai.
If it is true that according to
what that little spirit clan said just now.
Then are we no match for him?
We can't beat him.
Then…
Well, Dahai...
Get Gu Beixi and let's go.
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
Let's get out of here, quickly.
To ward off evil spirits.
Come and buy some wormwood.
Wormwood. Wormwood.
To ward off evil spirits.
Do you want to buy some wormwood?
Let's go.
Master. Master.
Well...
Why do I think the vendor is fooling us?
Does it work with this thing?
Better to take it than not.
Where is Gu Beixi?
I went to get him. No one was in the room.
I left a note.
I said let's meet outside the city.
Okay, I'll go look for him first.
Don't go looking for him.
Gu Beixi has power here.
He will be fine.
Besides, he's not the one that Lu Yan is targeting.
The most important thing now is that
you should get out of here.
I'll come back to meet him later.
Okay, let's find our horses first.
Go, go, go, go.
Where are the horses?
What happened to them?
Horse care. Our horses have been taken away.
[Xin]
Lu Yan.
Don't blame me for your unkindness.
Dahai, do you know how to drive a carriage?
Well, sometimes I can.
You can do it.
I can do it.
Go.
-Make way.
-Make way. Make way.
Make way. Make way. Make way.
Make way. Make way.
[Chengyu Firm supplies new foreign fabrics]
[No. 3 Room]
So many sneaky things that you did along the way.
Sneaking around and following us here.
What the hell do you want?
What does it have to do with you?
It has nothing to do with me.
If you dare to hurt Dengdeng.
If you hurt Dengdeng even a little bit,
I'll kill you.
Kill?
With this?
I know you have some skills.
You're not afraid of guns.
But besides a gun,
I also have a cannon.
I have explosives.
I also have my life.
Lu Yan.
Listen to me carefully.
If you dare to hurt Yu Dengdeng even a little bit.
Even if you are a lion, a tiger, or a python.
You met me.
I may die,
but I will still kill you little by little.
If you don't believe me, just try.
It’s my business with Yu Dengdeng.
None of your business.
Don't be so arrogant.
I'll find a way to deal with you.
Let’s wait and see.
Sir,
why are you talking to him so much?
After all,
his heart for Yu Dengdeng is true.
But we're not bad either.
We've made so many arrangements along the way.
Even the carriage that she drives away
was left there on purpose.
But she still doesn't appreciate it.
In my opinion,
we keep protecting her secretly.
It's not a good idea.
Let's tell her the truth.
Take her with us to find
the second half of the Millennium Memorial.
We can't rush this moment.
The question of whether she is Yun Xi or not.
We're not sure yet.
If you rashly tell her what happened 3,000 years ago,
I'm afraid she won't believe it.
Nor would she let her guard down.
Sir, they're out of town.
[Qianhe Town]
How dare you drive their carriage?
It's a loss if you don't take advantage of it.
That's right, and...
Well...
He, he, he...
Without the carriage,
he can't catch up with us, can he?
Does that monster still need to ride and drive?
I think we'd better leave quickly.
Hurry up and get to Yingdu.
At this rate,
we won't make it to Yingdu tonight.
There's Fanhua Town ahead.
Why don't we stay overnight?
Hey, kid, what are you doing?
Miss, you're so pretty.
Could you give me something to eat?
I haven't eaten in days.
-Hey kid.
-Give him two buns.
You're so young,
but you're so sweet.
She is beautiful and kind-hearted.
But I am also not bad.
It's going to be dark soon.
Tell me,
where do you live?
I live in…
Thief.
When I made a living wandering from place to place,
you were not even born yet.
Let me teach you a lesson.
Don't be so rude.
Just a kid.
Just... just let him go away?
Just leave it?
Stop.
It’s you again.
I caught you stealing again, didn't I?
No, no, no.
I won't dare. I won't dare.
Go away. Next time I catch you,
-I'll hand you over to the police.
-Stop!
You let him go?
He's just an unwanted kid in the mountains.
He grew up by stealing.
It's pathetic.
If you haven't lost anything,
just forgive him this time.
Is your money missing?
The weight hasn't changed. I don't think the money is missing.
Kids don't learn well.
I should teach him a lesson.
Forget it.
Since you've got the money back,
let's forget it.
It's getting late.
Let's hurry back to Fanhua Town.
You won't be able to return to Fanhua Town in such a short time.
Did you just come from the trail?
The forest is about to fog up.
You can't go on the small roads.
The main road will take you a long way around.
Not to mention this dense forest.
In the evening, the fog will be thick.
If you are not familiar with the road,
it is easy to get lost in the dense forest.
Besides, in the mountains,
there are also some wild animals or something else.
It's very scary.
Master.
Watch out.
Master, where is the thief?
He ran away, but the money is back.
Okay.
Well, let's go.
Let's find a place to rest for a while. I'm exhausted.
Are you looking for a place to stay?
Why don't you go to my hotel?
It's five kilometers ahead.
You can rest for the night.
Tomorrow when the fog disperses, you can leave again.
Don't worry, don't worry.
I'm not a bad guy.
I just see the weather is not good.
So I just want to come to the roadside,
and try to get some customers.
Do you know
General Yan?
What? What is it?
Is it a secret language?
There should be no problem.
Why not go and have a look?
Well, Master.
Although she doesn't know General Yan,
what if she is, is a bad person?
I mean bad human beings. Then what should we do?
Should we be afraid that she will take advantage of the blackmail?
That’s right, we're not afraid of anything.
Since we're out here, we're playing the game of blackmail.
Go.
Please lead the way.
Okay.
Although my hostel is simple,
the beds and food here
are very good.
I can guarantee that you will sleep comfortably.
You won't wake up in the middle of the night.
It's just ahead.
[Rose Hotel]
This is our Rose Hotel.
Rose Hotel.
What a strange name.
It's called that in the West.
So many people are staying here.
The weather is bad today.
Many people choose to stay overnight.
Others come to rest and eat.
The restaurant is on the first floor.
Rooms are on the second floor.
I'll take you upstairs to have a look.
OK.
Wait a minute.
I want to talk to you.
I don't have anything to say to you.
Dengdeng doesn't want to talk to you.
Can't you understand?
It's not safe here at night.
Be careful.
He's going to do it.
He's going to cut my stomach open.
It's only more dangerous with you around.
If you leave, everything will be fine.
Young boss.
Get three rooms.
Okay.
Don't follow me.
I want two rooms too.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll arrange it for you right away.
Miss Yu, the rooms are on the left.
[Booming Business]
Master.
Didn't you say you were coming to have a look?
Why are you staying here?
Besides, we're living with Lu Yan.
Will there be any danger?
Look out the window.
Master.
Well...
How is it foggy so quickly?
It's bad luck to go out now.
It's better to stay here.
At least there are many people here now.
He doesn't dare to do anything easily.
If he really dares to do it,
I'll shoot him with my gun.
Master.
You are so powerful.
My admiration for you
is like a rolling river that goes on and on.
No wonder they say…
Master.
Why are you shaking?
I'm...
I am also afraid.
Master.
Let's hurry up and make the pouch.
Make some more. Smoke him.
Yes, smoke him to death.
If it doesn't kill him, just make him dizzy.
Well.
Is this okay, Master?
That's enough.
I'll do it.
Hurry up and fill the wormwood.
Miss Yu, your meal is ready.
Please come down for dinner.
Even if we have to die,
I don't want to die of hunger.
Let's go.
[Booming Business]
Master. Master. Master.
It's okay, it's okay.
Why are you two looking like this?
You don't understand.
This is the latest and most fashionable look.
Yes, it's all designed by my Master.
Young boss.
Why are these all vegetarian dishes?
Let's get two meat dishes.
What would you like to order?
No need.
Vegetarian dishes are fine.
Good.
Master, let's have a meat dish.
We've been hungry all day.
You don't have any money?
I'll give it to you.
No need.
Chief obviously doesn't have any money with her.
And she gave back the money that we gave her.
She's so stubborn.
How about this?
I'll lend it to you.
I don't want any interest.
Just give me one of the pouches you embroidered.
Cash on delivery.
Master, Master, Master.
Isn't the pouch protecting you from the evil?
We were supposed to give it to him.
Moreover, money works better.
Where do you think I should keep my pouch?
It will get dirty outside.
But others can't see it if I put it inside.
Dengdeng,
where do you think I should keep it?
Whatever.
Then I'll put it in my clothes.
Young boss.
Sir, anything I can help you?
Please put my bedding
in front of the door of Yu Dengdeng's room.
What do you want?
To safeguard you.
Safeguard what?
Just stay
in your own room tonight.
My room is so far from yours.
I worry about you.
That'll be fine.
Master has me as her company.
Don't go anywhere tonight.
Oh,
take it with you.
What is it?
The amulet given by Second-in-command.
Will an amulet from Second-in-command
work?
Not sure.
You are not sure but you give it to me?
Alright. If you don't want it,
just give back to us.
There are only two of them given by him.
One for me, the other for Master.
Then I will take it.
I'll be fine.
I have my blood. I don't need it.
The present given by Dengdeng.
I will take it with me all the time.
I also understand
your heart to me.
I won't let you down.
What are you talking about?
What's wrong?
I won't be like someone
who is so heartless and fake.
No wonder.
Spirit clan.
They are all bastards.
How can they be sincere?
Enough.
What's wrong?
Some one did something but doesn't let others talk about it?
I will say. I...
What's wrong?
Withdraw your spell.
He said something bad first.
Lu Yan.
Fight with me if you have guts.
How can you be called a man by using spells?
[Booming Business]
Be safe at night.
Gu Beixi. Why do you pick on him?
Can we beat him?
Can all there of us
beat him?
If you keep your style,
stop sharing the travel with us.
Don't be so impulsive.
Master.
Sir,
does your bedding still need changing?
Yes.
Master.
He is going to do it.
Relax.
Don't be afraid, Master.
-He is going to do it.
-You'll be fine.
We have the amulet.
We have wormwood.
Trust me.
I won't let him
do any harm to you. Master.
You can't be
more careful tonight.
Be on alert.
Relax. Master.
Master.
Over here.
Why are you hiding here?
Will Lu Yan come or not?
I even get hungry.
I didn't eat so much for dinner.
I hear it.
Master. Listen to me.
I will find some food for you in the kitchen.
Don't. It's dangerous.
Relax. What time is it?
He will have come if he wants.
It won't take too long.
Besides, I have wormwood.
And I have the amulet.
It's okay. Wait for me.
Take the knife.
No need. Wait here.
My gosh.
Why are you here?
To safeguard you.
I'm worried that you guys will be attacked by Lu Yan
when you fall asleep at night.
I mean. Emm...
I'm going to find some food.
Do you want some?
Some food will be fine.
I know you didn't eat well, either.
Alright. Then you two wait for me.
Come in.
Don't stand there.
Finish your food and go back to your room.
The hotel
is so quiet at night.
What is it?
Six.
Two.
Three.
I haven't met the kid at dinner.
Two.
Kid.
-You don't sleep at night.
-Five.
Where are your parents?
They went out.
[Yu]
Isn't that the belonging of Senior Master?
Where did you get it?
Okay, okay, okay.
-Don't cry.
-It's mine.
-Here it is.
-Give it back to me.
Then tell me about it.
Where did you get it?
Did you get it
from an old man who wears beard?
No. Daidai
picked it up in Mysterious Market and brought it back to us.
Mysterious Market?
Look.
I have a wonderful thing here.
I exchange your dice with the pouch,
will you agree?
Yes.
No. No. No.
[Booming Business]
Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Come on. Go.
What's the matter about Mysterious Market?
I can't explain clearly with one or two sentences.
Anyway, it is a place
which spirit clan can enter freely
while normal human
will be blocked out.
In this case,
Daidai is not a human.
Then how did your dad go in there?
You said he was in Yingdu.
[Booming Business]
My dad is a spirit-hunter.
He must have his way.
Besides,
he is always hard to track down.
Maybe he stayed at Yingdu for a while
then headed to Mysterious Market.
We have to visit there.
I mean. The problem is
we don't even know how to get there.
My gosh.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
What's that?
You bastard.
Let go of me if you have guts.
Let's fight. You and me.
You dare to make trouble in front of me.
I'll teach you a lesson.
You bastard.
I won't forgive you.
It seems we witness the fight between monsters.
Leave them alone.
Let's leave now.
You bastard.
No way. I forgot to bring my gun.
What are you doing here?
Master. What shall we do?
-Freeze. Freeze.
-Dismiss.
Monsters Dismiss. Monsters Dismiss. Monsters Dismiss.
Monsters Dismiss. Monsters Dismiss.
Monsters Dismiss.
[Booming Business]
No way. I know we got tricked.
Wormwood won't work.
Don't come close.
[Booming Business]
I know I owe you a life.
But they don't.
Let them go. And you can kill me.
[Booming Business]
I'm not intended to hurt you.
This...this...
This...
What did you do to the place?
I did nothing.
That shopkeeper,
she is a spirit clan.
And she uses spells
to change the deserted house to a hotel.
She attracts customers along the road in the day time.
At night, she uses powder to knock them out
and steals the money.
Then you had a fight?
She observed that I have great energy.
So she increased the volume of the powder.
Everyone here gets so knocked out
and can't remain conscious.
Maybe it's the amulet
from Second-in-command
that has kept you safe.
What do those things of you spirit clan
have to with us?
Now
everyone in the hotel is unconscious.
I have no idea.
So I hope you can go to Mysterious Market
with me
to find a thing that can probably cure them.
You are so powerful.
It'll be easy for you to find anything.
I will bring you inconvenience.
Right?
I have to
take you with me for the travel.
Don't listen to him. In case of any trap.
Why?
You can go with your men.
They have to stay here
to guard the spirit clan
and those unconscious customers in the hotel.
If any accident happens
while you are here,
you can't protect yourselves.
You left it in your room.
Take it.
You will feel safe with it.
Don't worry.
I won't hide
if you want to kill me.
Another lie from him.
I have more guns.
But he can freeze you.
Can't shoot anything.
How come he won't hide?
Liar.
He won't say a single true word.
Isn't he say it on purpose to threaten me?
Gosh! It is a complete threat.
It's too dark.
No way.
I can't leave Dahai and Beixi here.
Or
you go to Mysterious Market yourself.
You can't go.
He must have his purpose.
I know.
Then why should we go?
We planned to go there
and find my dad.
Now there is a guy taking the lead.
It will save the search. Isn't that better?
But...
You are a man.
Why are you being so indecisive?
When we arrive there,
we will sneak and find my dad
when he doesn't pay attention.
Let me see
how he will
deal with my father, the world’s first spirit-hunter...
I have got the news.
The nearest entrance to Mysterious Market
is at Qianhe Town.
You stay
and guard those customers.
I will be quick.
Sir.
It will be enough for you to take Chief.
Now you have to bring Gu Beixi and Dahai.
If spirit clan there found out,
will it bring you trouble?
You'd rather go there yourself.
And that will be quick.
There have been spirit clan
who tried to attack Yu Dengdeng for many times.
I haven't found out
what does the culprit
on earth want.
So I can't leave her here.
Besides,
I found that
Yu Dengdeng resists spirit clan
after getting along with her these days.
I want to take the chance and bring her there
to feel the lives of the species.
Maybe
it can change her opinion.
[Fortune]
Isn't it Qianhe Town?
Where is the market?
Let's go.
Come on.
Alright. Alright. Alright.
[Mysterious Market]
[Baocheng Silver]
[Fengyu Medicine]
See.
[Joy Gate]
Alright. Alright.
Look up.
Another one.
[Fengyu Medicine]
So magical.
Look. Look at that one.
[Fengyu Medicine]
Ears of you two.
Master. You have it too.
Me too?
You two look so ugly.
You did it, right?
This is where the spirit clan live.
You won't draw their attention
dressing like this.
In case of any accident.
That makes sense.
How come you don't change yourself?
Shall we?
Steamed dumplings. Steamed dumplings.
Master.
Big steamed dumplings of ten-year energy.
The guy looks so familiar.
Newly made.
Isn't that the shopkeeper
in Qianhe Town in the day time?
Have a bite.
And the mother and daughter.
Say hi.
Have a look here.
But it's not Qianhe Town.
Mysterious Market is a spirit space.
Its gate only appears
with the energy of spirit clan.
Qianhe Town is one of the entrances.
What is a spirit space?
It's a place run by energy
for avoiding human.
Do you understand?
Why is that difficult?
That's the thing.
You can regard it
as a place where spirit clan live,
trade and have fun.
Take the guy you met as an example.
He sold normal steamed dumplings with meat fillings
in Qianhe Town dressing like a human.
But here,
he can sell food which increases energy.
Double. Then he must be rich.
Food of spirit clan is very rare.
So they
have to work hard and make money.
Only to buy food.
I thought you just rob people
or directly kill people.
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
Some human can
be extremely evil.
But most human
are kind people.
The same with spirit clan.
Though some of them can be evil,
most of them
are kind and work hard to live.
So there is no difference besides species
between human and spirit clan.
Really?
I don't believe it.
How can spirit clan be good?
Alright. Alright. Alright.
Nothing. No big deal.
Alright. That's okay.
That's okay.
They look so beautiful.
So beautiful.
That must be
[Angaochang Yixi Firm]
the parade of the most popular courtesan in the brothel.
Chief Gu,
♫The moonlight was shining all over the ground♫
won't you give her some money?
Why don't you do?
I'm a beggar in a white suit,
poor and clean.
♫Take a close look to your figure♫
So elegant.
If Dengdeng likes it,
♫Sight makes us forget the distance♫
I will give more money.
Alright.
Okay.
♫My heart will beat faster in the next moment♫
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
It's okay, it's okay.
♫To feel the the passing of time♫
Hold on.
♫Two hearts are also awakened♫
♫A deafening sound was heard♫
-Be together!
-Be together! Be together!
♫When light years have changed♫
♫I will still be with you♫
♫Because you I do not want to get out of the dream♫
Most of them
are kind and work hard to live.
♫Our love has been across light years♫
[Angaochang Yixi Firm]
So there is no difference besides species
♫I met you in the crowd♫
between human and spirit clan.
♫You made me believe in fate♫
-Be together!
-Be together! Be together!
♫There is a destined magic♫
♫It's me who must be in love with you♫
Be together!
Be together! Be together!
♫I don't care about the future or the past♫
It's for you.
Book of spirit clan.
♫I believe all♫
Have a look.
[Bailing Spectrum]
[Blue Wormwood]
One more.
[Purple Whirlwind]
Good.
One more.
[Snow Vine]
Actually spirit clan eat two basic types of food.
One is human's food.
To make themselves full.
The other is the food that can raises energy
which is recorded in the book.
[General Yan]
General Yan.
Violent and sadistic.
[Violent and sadistic.]
Eat enemies alive.
Cramp their skins and shatter their bones.
No one can come back alive after seeing him.
Actually we have another food.
You can add the energy of spirit ball
into food you like.
Then you will have a delicious food
which can also raise your energy.
What's wrong with you now?
How can it be no difference?
What did you say?
Nothing.
Buddha bless me. Buddha bless me.
Make me safe until I meet my dad.
When I find my dad,
I will ask him to beat the stupid spirit clan.
[Fengyu Medicine]
[Thousand Years For You]
♫What if♫
♫What if love can be sensed♫
♫Miss will♫
♫Miss will be heard♫
♫In life♫
♫Most beautiful scenery in life♫
♫All I hear is♫
♫All I hear is about you♫
♫When two hearts are so close to each other♫
♫When the whole world is occupied by you♫
♫I'll call out your name so hard♫
♫Until you respond♫
♫You're the only one for me♫
♫The scenery that I walk into♫
♫This encounter with the seasons♫
♫Fate is carved into love♫
♫How lucky I am♫
♫The decision I made for you♫
♫When two hearts are so close to each other♫
♫When the whole world is occupied by you♫
♫I'll call out your name so hard♫
♫Until you respond ♫
♫You're the only one for me♫
♫The scenery that I walk into♫
♫This encounter with the seasons♫
♫Fate is carved into love♫
♫How lucky I am♫
♫The decision I made for you♫
[iQIYI]