[iQIYI Present]
♫Spirits in between heaven and earth are scattered♫
♫Spirits in between heaven and earth are scattered while snow blossoming♫
♫Thousand years of time is immortal like amber♫
♫I'm still obsessed♫
♫Twilight is falling into chaos♫
♫Twilight is falling into chaos and past life is hard to let go♫
♫Tears are falling, my love♫
♫Tears are falling, my love is deep like see♫
♫Fate rises and falls♫
♫Fate rises and falls, my heart is sealed♫
♫Love and hate are pouring down♫
♫ Love and hate are pouring down following me♫
♫Lonely safeguarding, going faraway, roaring in anger♫
♫Lonely safeguarding, going faraway, roaring in anger, but never let go♫
♫It's me♫
♫It's me staring at you♫
♫ It's me lighting you up♫
♫It's me♫
♫It's me running towards you♫
♫It's me merging into you♫
♫It's me♫
[Thousand Years For You]
[Episode 15]
[Yingdu]
[Great Bright Theater]
Well.
Okay.
Master, why don't we look for Senior Master
but set up a stall here?
[Xinshengtai]
[Jutou Old Brand]
Since my father wants this Millennium Memorial so badly,
I just want to set up a stall to lure him out.
[Xinshengtai]
But you know... Yingdu is so big.
Senior Master even doesn't know that
we're setting up a stall here.
[Great Bright Theater]
He may doesn't know now.
But words will spread from mouth to mouth.
It's bound to spread to him.
All right.
[Jutou Old Brand]
The rooms are all set.
You haven't sold a single book yet.
It seems that you can't do it without me.
You're not going to look for your child-betrothal bride?
There's no hurry. Let's find your father first.
We'll talk about child betrothal later.
As for my opinion,
Chieftain Gu,
you're not young.
It's lucky to have a girl who's interested in you.
You're still picky.
Yu Dengdeng, are you trying to make me angry?
Just kidding, just kidding.
Then thank you, Chieftain Gu.
You put aside your own business
to help us.
Thank you so much.
When I find my father,
I will open ten jars of good wine to treat you.
Remember what you said today.
Books for sale! Books for sale!
[Carlo's Head]
Please have a look.
Buy one book and get two free!
[Grand Theatre]
Come on, take a look.
Take a look.
Millennium Memorial is so good. Millennium Memorial is wonderful.
[Red Sorghum]
Millennium Memorial is great.
[Xinshengtai]
If you don't buy these good books,
where will they go?
-Please take a look!
-Take a look.
Come on, take a look!
[Xinshengtai]
I want two.
Millennium Memorial. Please take a look.
[Grand Theatre]
Master!
There is no one coming to buy books,
not to mention that we may meet Senior Master.
The world is getting worse.
Why people nowadays
are so unmotivated to read?
They are taking Millennium Memorial, the rare book of spirit clan
to the street stall for sale.
But nobody wants to buy.
What a strange thing!
Sir. Xin.
Sir, I have dealt with
the matter of the Rose Hotel.
OK.
The Millennium Memorial is useless now.
Take it back to Lu Yan.
Sir.
Why is the Master selling books on the street?
[Xinshengtai]
You three are here to set up a stall.
Do you have a business certificate?
Show me your business certificate.
Hurry up!
Sir. Sir.
[Huasheng Watch]
Yes, we do. How can we not have one?
Wait a minute, we'll show you.
Hurry up!
-Wait a moment.
-We are finding it right now.
I'm finding it right now.
We will show you. I'm trying to find it for you.
I'm finding it.
[Xinshengtai]
[Grand Theatre]
After them!
Go, go, go! Stop!
Catch them!
Don't run!
Sir!
Should we go and help?
Should we?
Don't worry.
If there's any danger to Dengdeng,
I can feel it.
You want to chase me?
You don't even know who I am.
Who are you?
Why are you following me?
Are you a pervert? What are you smelling?
It's really you!
Despite only a broken skin is left.
If you don't want to get shot,
get out of here!
You heroic man.
We've never met before.
We don't have a grudge, do we?
I have things to do. I'll leave now.
Don't come any closer!
What do you want to do?
Don't force me to fight.
You are really good at Kung Fu.
I admire you. I admire you.
It was a misunderstanding. A misunderstanding.
[Yideli]
Well, I'm no match for you.
Why do you freeze me? It's not necessary.
General Yan's strength is
still as strong as ever.
The one who poisoned Qingquan Stronghold
and sucked out human essence
is you, isn't it?
Compared with human essence,
I prefer your energy core.
Just you?
Watch out!
What the hell is this guy?
Why did he just disappear?
Where is he?
He's gone again.
He's gone?
Dengdeng!
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm fine.
Who the hell is that guy?
Why did he come after me?
I'm not sure who he is yet.
Are you being too nervous?
I think that monster
is just bluffing.
He didn't even beat you with a single move.
Let me take you back to the hotel first.
That masked man came prepared.
His eyes have been on you for a long time.
You should be very careful these days.
Let me help you
to find your father.
No need.
I mean, I can just find him myself.
That masked man
must have been hurt badly today.
I don't think he's going to come after me again for a few days.
Okay.
Then I'll do what I always do.
I'll watch over you from afar.
If anything happens to you,
just use the hair pin to call me.
[Tongjia Inn]
Then you
have an early rest.
[Red Sorghum]
Lu Yan.
Our grudge is quite another matter.
Thank you for today.
[Tongjia Inn]
Master, you're back at last.
When did you get in?
Are you trying to scare me to death?
Why is this monster here again?
It's not your business.
Yu Dengdeng, you won't be soft-hearted, will you?
Don't forget that he tried to kill you before.
Dengdeng.
I did it for your own good.
We grew up together.
I won't harm you.
You do well to be the chieftain of the stronghold.
But as a woman,
you don't have much experience getting along with men.
Nowadays, men can do anything
to cheat women.
Pretend to be cool or handsome. Or pretend to be a hero to save women.
If you do not become more careful,
sooner or later you will be cheated again.
Why are you still talking about this?
Dahai.
Do you have any news about my father?
Yes, Master.
Let's get down to business.
I've been waiting for a long time.
I've been setting up my bookstall for half a day.
But I haven't seen Senior Master yet.
Well.
That's strange.
Isn't he always looking for
Millennium Memorial?
Why hasn't he appeared yet?
Is it possible that he's not in Yingdu?
No, I don't think so.
Well, Master.
I'll go to the city later.
I'll go to the gambling houses and mahjong parlors.
And check them one by one.
Maybe Senior Master has gone gambling.
Dahai.
You go first.
I'll take care of your Master for you.
In case she is fooled by Lu Yan again,
and makes a mistake.
Okay, okay, okay.
Master. I get it. I get it. I get it.
Chieftain Gu, come with me.
Let's go.
Don't look back. If she punches you,
you are not strong enough to bear it.
Come on, let's go.
Don't look, don't look, come back and look again.
Let's go. Let's go.
OK.
Master, take care of yourself.
Who is that person?
Could it be…
[Chunxiangqi Delicious Pastry]
[Gold and Silver Jewellery]
Sir.
What just happened?
Someone just attacked Yu Dengdeng.
That person.
How?
Three thousand years ago,
when I fought with Zhu Rong,
he used the golden butterfly
to create an illusion.
It helped him disappear and reappear.
[Kingsley Hotel]
And the person who just attacked Yu Dengdeng
also used this spell.
[Kingsley Hotel]
But Zhu Rong
died right in front of you.
How could he come back from death?
Could it be...
Someone is imitating Zhu Rong?
Or maybe it's
the spirit clan related to Zhu Rong?
I've scouted the whole city of Yingdu.
There is no aura of Zhu Rong.
But no matter who this person is,
since he has threatened
Yu Dengdeng's safety,
I must find it out.
[Trading Company]
Xin!
Call all the clansman in the city that can be mobilized.
Gather them all here.
Pick a few good ones
with strong energy
to protect Yu Dengdeng.
Sir!
I was just about to report this to you.
Originally, there were many spirit clansmen in Yingdu.
But in the past two months,
a lot of strange things have happened.
Not many spirit clansmen can be gathered now.
Lu Yan.
It's been three thousand years.
You're still as skilled as ever.
You haven't changed at all.
Three thousand years ago, I was able to kill Yun Xi.
Three thousand years later,
I won't let you have an easy time either.
Lu Yan.
I will make you obediently
hand over the energy core.
Chieftain Gu.
Why do we come to these whorehouses early in the morning?
If Master finds out,
she will beat us to death!
How old are you? You're still saying “Master” all the time?
Can you act like a man?
Me?
Not like a man?
If you are a man, hold up your back.
Well.
You, what time is it?
You still want to come to hang out?
[Chunman Courtyard]
Besides, people come here usually at night.
It's daytime now.
You can't even find a door to enter in daytime.
Who says I'm here to have fun?
I'm here to help your Master find her father.
I don't know this place very well.
We need to use some connections and relationships.
Connections and relationships?
It means people in various parts of this society.
Do you see those guys?
[Fortune]
Not soldiers and not bandits.
If you call them bandits or hooligans,
[Chunman Courtyard]
they have their own names.
They are commonly known as
Pa Menzi.
So they are pimps?
Not even close.
Pimps are handymen in restaurants.
They are subordinates.
But those people serve regular customers.
[Fortune]
They also look out for information
and do bodyguards and fighters work.
It all costs money to hire them.
They have seen a lot of people.
They must know a lot of things too.
In Yingdu,
they must be the most well-informed people.
Let's go.
Let's meet them.
Come in and have a seat.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
[Yideli]
-Drink, drink, drink.
-Come on.
We are eating and drinking.
[Fortune]
You two look so strange.
Is it your first time here?
I'm Gu Beixi from Nanfeng Stronghold,
Qingquan Mountain.
I'm new here.
You may not know me.
But do you know Wang Wu from Xiongya Stronghold
or Liu Mazi from Jiufeng Mountain?
Liu Mazi?
What a coincidence!
That's my uncle.
-Yes.
He is your uncle?
He is also my brother.
Well, we just finished drinking that day.
Is it true?
[Fortune]
Then we're family.
-It is really a coincidence.
-We are family.
-Drink together.
He is your uncle and also my brother.
Hey, brothers, I need to know something.
Has an old man in his fifties
been in Yingdu lately?
His hair is long and dirty.
He walks with a limp.
A paralyzed man who can not move when he sees a gambling house.
Is there one?
I see gambling people every day.
But the person you just said…
Have you seen him?
No, I haven't.
-No, I haven't seen him.
-No.
It is not peaceful in Yingdu lately.
You must have seen that the police station at the city gate is very strict
when you entered the city.
The number of people allowed to enter is not many.
Well.
He doesn't even go to the gambling house anymore.
There must be something wrong with him.
Who is this little brother?
I am…
Well.
He is my wife's apprentice.
Then he is our brother too.
Come on, let's drink.
Drink!
-Come on.
It's not so good to drink in the daylight.
What do you mean?
You don't want to give face?
Wine... It is also another kind of water.
It's fun to drink in the daytime, isn't it?
Come on. Let's drink.
That's right.
-Come on, come on, come on.
-Let's drink.
-Let's eat.
-Please enjoy yourself.
-Don't be shy.
Oh my god.
It's over. It's over for me.
Dahai, what are you doing?
What is this?
Do not give me face?
No, it's a misunderstanding, bro.
He's from the countryside and has never seen the world.
He can't enjoy good wine.
Come on, let's drink.
-Let's drink. Let's drink.
-Let's drink.
Country boy.
-Come on, come on.
-Let's drink.
-Come on.
Drink!
It's over! It's over!
Sober-up soup.
Where can we find it?
If Gu Beixi finds out about this.
I'll be over.
Sober-up soup.
[Vinegar]
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
In the middle of the day.
A girl bumped into my arms!
Get out of the way, I don't have time to talk to you.
And a grumpy girl.
Don't look, go away.
[Vinegar]
Peng Dahai.
Where did you go?
There was a man just now.
He ran there.
You're fooling me.
I'd know you if you were ashes.
What happened?
[Vinegar]
[Yideli]
That's the thing.
Who knew that after the monster of spirit clan died,
I haven't changed back yet.
Anyway, my master said that
when we find Senior Master,
she will help me solve it.
So...
You are the bridesmaid that day?
Well, if it wasn't me,
I wouldn't have found you to be a good person.
How could I have helped you go after my Master?
Isn't that right?
Well, Chieftain Gu.
What…What should we do to this guy?
Don't worry.
He won't die.
Then I'm relieved.
[Yingdu]
[Police Station]
It's too soon.
This guy is a police captain.
[Police ID]
And he saw what you look like.
How dare you two attack a police officer?
It's over.
This time he also saw what you look like.
[Tongjia Inn]
[Yuan's Oil Shop]
[Guanshengyuan Pastry]
Master!
Don't hide, I saw it all.
Why do you draw Lu Yan's portrait?
Are you going to
change your mind and fall in love with him again?
What are you talking?
Don't be ridiculous.
Then why did you paint him?
I want to scold him.
Okay.
[Despicable]
Despicable and shameless
Lu Yan.
Insidious and cunning
old monster.
[Despicable and shameless Lu Yan]
[Insidious and cunning old monster]
How is it?
Good scolding, right?
Well done!
This old monster, I'll frame it for you.
Don't... Don't…
Don't frame it.
Throw it away. Well…
Well, well…
I haven't said anything. Why are you so excited?
You must have a secret in your heart, Master.
Why do you talk so much today?
Have you heard of the saying?
A good horse won't go back to the grass.
I definitely will not fall in love with him again.
Don't worry.
Go and have a rest. I'm tired.
Rekindle the past feelings to him?
Have I fallen back in love with him again?
No, no, no, absolute not.
I, Yu Dengdeng, must not
fall twice at the same place.
I have no feelings for him.
Absolutely not.
No, I can't.
Well.
I should write down his faults
and all the bad things he has done.
Always remind myself.
First,
Lu Yan is not a human being.
He is a combination of human and the spirit clan.
[...not a human being. He is a combination of human and the spirit clan.]
General Yan.
He killed all the spirit clans
and can even eat raw human hearts.
The information of eating raw hearts
seems not confirmed.
[He killed all the spirit clans and can even eat raw human hearts.]
Second, Lu Yan is
[...mean. He is a real villian]
shameless and mean. He is a real villain.
He deceived people's feelings.
[Feelings]
But it seems that it was me that forced him back to the stronghold.
Third,
Lu Yan is
[Insidious and cunning]
Insidious and cunning.
He threatened me many times.
He is despicable.
[Tongjia Inn]
Sir, you're still awake?
What are you hiding?
Nothing.
Let me get you a drink.
Come here.
Show me.
Sir.
I advise you not to read it.
[Despicable and shameless Lu Yan]
[Insidious and cunning old monster]
Shameless, Lu Huohuo.
Insidious and cunning old monster.
Sir.
I just picked this up on the roadside.
I don't know who wrote it.
[Despicable and shameless Lu Yan]
[Insidious and cunning old monster]
Such drawing skills, such handwriting.
Who else could it be but her?
Sir.
Don't be angry with Master.
She still has misunderstandings about you.
It will be fine if you two have cleared up your misunderstanding.
I'll tear it up for you.
You can go out first.
I'll just throw it away myself later.
[Nanjing]
[Despicable and shameless Lu Yan]
[Insidious and cunning old monster]
Don't.
Don't hit my father. Don't.
Don't hit my father.
Father.
Don't.
Now,
there will be no more nightmares.
Lu Yan.
[First, Lu Yan is not a human being. He is a combination of human and...]
[He doesn't like me]
Despicable and shameless.
[He deceived people's feelings.]
[Lu Yan is a bastard who wanted to kill me.]
He deceived people's feelings.
[Lu Yan is not a good man.]
[First, Lu Yan is not a human being.]
Lu Yan is not a human being.
[Lu Yan is a big idiot.]
He is a combination of human and spirit clan.
Lu Yan doesn't know what's good or bad.
He is a big idiot.
[Great Bright Theater]
Master, get up!
Master!
Why are you still sleeping?
The sun is shining, it's time to set up the stall.
Master.
Get up, the sun is shining on your butt.
Get up, you are not a little baby. Come on!
Oh my god!
Well, you...
Why is your face painted after sleeping?
Well, well… How did you do that?
What are you saying?
Take a look at yourself.
Take a look.
Who did it?
Me?
I just got here.
That's strange.
Come here.
Here.
Have one.
Eat this.
We just saw the notice that says
[From the 6th to the 15th of this month, those who have not registered in the city]
[have to make up the entry formalities in three days.]
from the 6th to the 15th of this month, those who have not registered in the city
have to make up the entry formalities in three days.
That's right.
Isn't that time when Senior Master disappeared?
Why don't we find a way to sneak into the police station?
Check the registration form.
Well.
Where's Gu Beixi?
I don't know.
He said he knew someone here who could ask around.
He left a message and left.
Left?
-Get out of the way! Get out of the way!
-Everyone gets out of the way.
Get out of the way!
Get out of the way! Get out of the way!
[Shaluo Silk Woolen Cloth]
Who are those people? They're so arrogant!
What are they doing?
The Bai Mansion?
Is there
a famous
and powerful Bai Mansion in Yingdu?
The Bai Mansion?
In Yingdu,
there is only one Bai Mansion.
It belongs to
the police chief-Chief Bai.
[The Bai Mansion]
Go! Let go of me!
Hurry up and leave here.
[The Bai Mansion]
We don't know Gu Beixi.
We don't know him.
-Nanfeng
-Get out.
I am Gu Beixi from Nanfeng Stronghold.
You've never heard of it because you lack knowledge and experience.
Let me in!
-Are you leaving or not?
-Get out!
Go away quickly!
Please open the door.
We're here to deliver documents of missing people.
[Yingdu Missing Case]
[The Theft and Murder Case in Yingdu]
Since I can't do it publicly.
Don't blame me for doing it in secret.
Chieftain Gu.
It seems that you're not very charming.
Your father-in-law doesn't seem to know you well.
Let's get down to business.
How should we get into Bai Mansion?
In my opinion,
let's just get in
by pretending to be servants of Bai Mansion.
No way.
Even an old lady who sweeps the floor in Bai Mansion
is demanded to come from a decent family.
We are outsiders.
How can we get in?
I don't want to blame you, but you are…
What's the use of having you, a son-in-law from Bai Mansion?
You are really…
Why is it useless?
We can't get in by pretending.
But I can make him
invite us to the mansion openly.
What does it mean?
Looks like...
It's time to do something new.
You mean...
No, no, no, no.
Sir...
They want to pretend to be bandits and hijack the caravan
when women of Bai Mansion
are on their way to pay incense.
Then Yu Dengdeng will deal with those bandits.
They want to put on a play called the hero rescued beauty.
So that Chief Bai will owe them a debt of gratitude.
Then he will treat them as guests
and invite them to his mansion.
I got it.
Keep following her.
Yes.
Sir.
Maybe I go protect the Master too?
I feel worried
to leave this thing to them.
If Yu Dengdeng is in danger,
I can sense it.
I can get to her in time.
Now,
I need you to confirm one thing for me.
What is it?
Isn't this the spiritual butterfly
that attacked Master in Qingquan Town.
Come to feel
the scent on this butterfly.
Sir!
This is the butterfly of Zhu Rong's subordinate.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Three thousand years ago,
I've seen that spirit clansman several times.
This is his scent.
I thought he and Zhu Rong had died together.
I didn't expect that
he has survived till now.
There are two women from Bai family coming this time.
One is Chief Bai's newly married concubine.
The other one is the young lady of Bai family, Bai Shiqi.
Bai Shiqi.
It seems that Chief Bai has lots of sons and daughters.
As soon as the carriage arrives,
you two rush out and rob.
Don't hurt people.
I'll deal with the rest.
I'll go out with your precious apprentice
and pretend to be robbers
Don't shoot for real!
How can that work?
We should do it seriously.
I have to give you two a shot each,
which will make people believe.
Is this really necessary?
Don't worry.
The bullets will just pass by you.
No one will get hurt.
All right.
Two shots, two shots are fine to me.
We both protect our heads from shooting.
I found out that you are
a man who wants beauty more than life.
This time,
I can finally give Master
to you trustingly.
Here they come. Here they come.
Don't move! Don't move!
Hurry up!
Back up.
Get down.
Get over there!
I'm telling you guys.
From now on, Shuangming Mountain is our territory.
If you want to pass by,
you have to give us your money.
Don't panic.
Give them all our money and jewelry.
Give it all to them.
Yes, Miss.
Come down.
You brave man,
We've given all the money to you.
Please do us a favor.
Let us go.
You are straightforward.
But you've already heard my voice.
In order to prevent you from reporting to the police,
I'll have to kill you all.
Sir, there is honor among thieves.
We've given all the money to you.
Why do you have to go back on your word?
Shiqi, don't contradict them.
Don't be afraid, Auntie.
My father is the chief of police.
I can't be scared by such a scene.
If you are reasonable, take the money and leave.
If you are not reasonable,
I'm not afraid of you bandits.
Little girl.
You are brave.
Today I want to see that
why you are not afraid of me.
If you want to kill me,
I have one life.
If you want to humiliate me,
I can only die.
Ok.
Bro.
Don't move!
See if you insult her today,
or kill her?
Well, today we're here to rob.
Master is still waiting to show her appearance.
Why are you talking to this girl?
Then let us kill her.
Wait a minute.
Even if I have to die, let me know the reason.
My father has attacked Xiongya Stronghold many times.
You're here for revenge?
No.
I don't belong to any group. We are looking for money and killing people today.
Then just do it.
Who is it?
Who are you? Why are you blocking my way?
How dare you rob in a broad daylight?
It's a pity you met me.
Today
You are unlucky!
Miss.
Boss.
This woman doesn't look easy to deal with.
Let me try to fight with her.
You hero.
Throw the gun away if you dare.
Let's fight in the flesh.
It's ok.
Let me
have a fight with you today.
Master, you are really hard, you…
Your performance is too pompous.
She is almost killing me!
Please forgive us.
We have eyes but fail to recognize Mountain Tai.
Do you dare to commit highway robbery again?
-Don't dare!
Do you know you're wrong?
-We know.
Do you still want to be a bandit?
-No, no,
-No.
What happened?
Miss Yu
has fallen out with her friend?
Thank you for saving my life.
-Thank you! Thank you!
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
Can you tell me your name?
I'm Yu Dengdeng.
I'm from Qingquan Town.
I came to Yingdu
to look for my relatives.
How can I not help you when I see something unjust?
Please get in the car.
I can escort you back to the city.
Then...
What should we do to these two bandits?
It's not safe to take them back.
I've already tied them up.
I'll give them a beating later
to make you relieved.
Miss.
My father is the chief of the police.
Why don't we send them to the police station?
To prevent them from doing evil again.
Or they will harm others and themselves.
Ok.
Good point.
Then,
please get into the carriage first,
Miss Bai.
Okay.
Lady warrior! Lady warrior!
Master, you're giving us away?
Play to the score.
Can't you see that Bai Shiqi is not easy to deal with?
Your Master is wearing a buckle.
Rest easy, you and I.
Let's go.
Lady warrior.
The horse is startled.
[Thousand Years For You]
♫What if♫
♫What if love can be sensed♫
♫Miss will♫
♫Miss will be heard♫
♫In life♫
♫Most beautiful scenery in life♫
♫All I hear is♫
♫All I hear is about you♫
♫When two hearts are so close to each other♫
♫When the whole world is occupied by you♫
♫I'll call out your name so hard♫
♫Until you respond ♫
♫You're the only one for me♫
♫The scenery that I walk into♫
♫This encounter with the seasons♫
♫Fate is carved into love♫
♫How lucky I am♫
♫The decision I made for you♫
♫When two hearts are so close to each other♫
♫When the whole world is occupied by you♫
♫I'll call out your name so hard♫
♫Until you respond ♫
♫You're the only one for me♫
♫The scenery that I walk into♫
♫This encounter with the seasons♫
♫Fate is carved into love♫
♫How lucky I am♫
♫The decision I made for you♫
[iQIYI]