[Produced by iQIYI]
♫The consonance of heaven and earth flew apart♫
♫The white snow was blooming♫
♫The one thousand years' time is as immortal as amber♫
♫I'm still as obsessed as before♫
♫The broken twilight fell in chaos♫
♫It's hard to let go of the love of the previous life♫
♫Tears fell down. It was deep love♫
♫The tears formed a bitter sea♫
♫Fate rose and fell♫
♫Love was buried for a long time♫
♫Love and hatred are as overwhelming as heavy rain♫
♫Come with me♫
♫Guarded it alone, ran far away and roared♫
♫Never mentioned letting go of you♫
♫It's me♫
♫Who stared at you♫
♫Who ignited you♫
♫It's me♫
♫Who ran towards you♫
♫Who became part of you♫
♫It's me♫
[Thousand Years For You]
[Episode 23]
Lu Yan.
Look what I've prepared for you.
I made this myself.
Lu Yan.
You can even sleep while sitting.
You must have consumed too much energy
and haven't fully recovered.
Let me give you some energy.
What's going on? My energy...
The words left on the execution ground
is still in this hairpin.
No, I can't let her hear them.
You're awake.
What were you trying to do?
I saw some dust on your head,
so I wanted to clean it for you.
It's okay.
I must have got it dirty
when I was grilling fish.
You've been in a coma for a day.
Do you feel better?
Eat something to take nutritional supplements.
Guess what I made for you?
Come here.
Look.
The grilled fish I made for you
and your favorite...
No, my favorite rice cakes with brown sugar.
It doesn't look good,
but it should taste good.
Try it.
Hurry.
I made this myself.
How is it?
How does it taste?
It tastes good.
You have a good taste.
My uncle and Dahai said
I have no talent for cooking.
It seems that
we are Boya and Ziqi.
It's you who have a good taste.
Unlike them,
they are just ordinary people who don't appreciate it.
Why are you staring at me?
How is the spirit clan in the Yingdu City?
Gu Beixi has asked around.
Most of the spirit clan in the Yingdu City
have escaped from the city
after the execution.
Some of the spirit clan
haven't been discovered by humans.
They're ready to leave the city now.
Do I still have dust on my head?
Dengdeng.
Why don't you give me back my hairpin for a while?
You gave it to me before.
What? Are you going back on your word?
No.
The style of this hairpin is a bit out of date.
I can give you
the most popular one.
I think this is good.
Yes.
But I can get you a better one.
I'm not the person who despise the poor and curry favor with the rich.
I think this wooden hairpin is good.
But, this...
Lu Yan, don't act beyond your capacity now.
You can't defeat me now.
Now,
you're like the tiger who went down to level land, and you would be insulted by me.
Fine.
Since you said so,
I'll just eat the fish.
Why does it sound weird?
As the proverb goes, "the tiger went down to level land, it would be insulted by dogs!" You mean I'm a dog!
You should have reminded me.
I didn't even think about that.
You...
I'll let it go.
Since you haven't recovered,
I'll forgive you this time.
[Beautiful and colorful spring scenery reflected in the gorgeous house]
[Thousands of auspicious lights danced on the lucky house]
[The family blessed with the arrival of the New Year]
[The family is full of wealth with the spring breeze blowing]
Again.
Daughter.
Dengdeng.
You brought me food again.
I knew it.
Even if my daughter married someone,
she won't forget me.
Where is the meal?
He ate them all.
Does he know how to respect the elders?
Master,
what did Concubine Lu do wrong?
You treat him like this.
I'll teach him a lesson.
Don't get involved in their marriage.
It will be a big deal if it goes on like this.
That's rude.
-Senior Master. -Yu.
Keep your voice down.
Someone is following us.
Who?
I didn't see him, but his kung fu is good.
It shouldn't be.
Didn't Concubine Lu say
there is a skill formation
blocking the aura and energy?
Yes.
It's impossible for ordinary people to find us.
No matter who come,
they are guests.
I'll go take a look.
Wait.
The enemy is in the dark, we are in the light.
If you go out now,
you won't get any advantage.
Why don't we...
Okay.
Great!
Okay!
Master.
Do we need to tell Concubine Lu?
No need.
You don't need a knife, which is used to kill cows to kill a chicken.
If you tell him now,
he won't be able to recuperate.
Father.
I haven't finished yet. Where are you going?
Kill the chicken.
I think he has diarrhea. [Note: "killing the chicken" and "diarrhea" have similar pronunciation in Chinese.]
Uncle,
I'm too tired.
I must have a good sleep.
Be careful.
[The family is blessed with the arrival of the New Year]
[The family is full of wealth with the spring breeze blowing]
Don't move.
Why can't I move the water tank?
You have got into my Zichen Qiankun Net.
Do you want to escape? No way.
I'd like to see
who dares to mess with us.
Yes.
Open it for me.
Are you Xin?
Master.
Why are you here?
Hurry up.
What did you do?
Your ladyship
I'm here to test your reaction ability.
I didn't expect that it's great.
Great job, Chieftain Yu.
Great job, uncle.
Dahai is better.
Sir is calling me.
I'll go back first.
Your ladyship, I...
Don't force me.
I promised Mr. Lu
I won't say anything.
What did you promise?
Your ladyship, here's the thing.
Didn't Mr. Lu want the hairpin back?
Didn't you refuse to give it to him?
So I wanted to volunteer
to take the hairpin back.
What?
You wanted to steal it.
We're family.
How could you say that?
Why did he suddenly want to take the hairpin back?
What's wrong with this hairpin?
Are you going to tell me or not?
Say!
Say it.
Dengdeng.
I'm sorry.
I hoped that we can remain a devoted couple all through our lives.
But today,
I'm afraid I'll break my promise.
Remember,
I'll pay you back for what I did.
You treated me as your husband in this life.
I will marry you in the next life.
This matter is settled.
Living or dying can't change it.
So touching.
My goodness.
Concubine Lu is so straightforward. It's so cool.
What are you talking about?
He's clearly teasing Dengdeng.
I'll kill him.
Come back!
What are you doing here?
You…
Chieftain.
Dengdeng.
It's just a confession.
All of you
are ignorant.
What a loser.
All right, since we've figured it out,
it's a misunderstanding.
Go back and rest.
Let's go.
Go.
Why did you push me?
[Favorable climatic, geographical and human conditions]
[Treasures all over the world]
I'm just concerned about Dengdeng.
Let's go.
Dengdeng.
I'm sorry.
I hoped that we can remain a devoted couple all through our lives.
But today,
I'm afraid I'll break my promise.
Remember,
I'll pay you back for what I did.
You treated me as your husband in this life.
I will marry you in the next life.
This matter is settled. Living or dying can't change it.
Lu Yan.
You're asleep again.
You must be exhausted.
You fell asleep
before Xin replied.
You were usually fierce to me.
I didn't expect a general like you
has such a passionate heart
under your cool appearance.
Well, you're quite cultured.
I've experienced a lot of things.
When I heard your confession in so many people's presence just now,
I almost couldn't hold it.
Actually, I was very angry.
I was angry that you broke your promise.
I was angry that you died alone.
But for the sake of your confession,
I'll show you mercy and let you go.
Dengdeng, I'm sorry.
I hoped that we can remain a devoted couple all through our lives.
You...
Well done, Lu Yan.
You pretended to be asleep
to steal my hairpin?
Do you think I can't remember it
after you stole my hairpin?
I just heard my favorite line.
-I...  -All right.
Stop.
-Stop it. -I'll pay you back for what I did.
You treated me as your husband in this life.
Stop it.
♫If♫
♫Love could be sensed♫
♫Missing you would have sounds♫
What? You can say it.
You don't allow me to imitate?
I must do it.
In the next life, I will...
♫The most beautiful♫
What about your answer?
♫Scenery in life♫
You heard my confession.
♫All that I heard about is related to you♫
What about your answer?
I...
♫When two hearts are so close to each other♫
♫When the whole world is occupied by you♫
If you don't answer,
I'll take it as a yes.
♫I'll call out your name so hard♫
♫Until you respond♫
♫You're the only♫
3,000 years ago,
I had lost you once.
♫Scenery I've walked into♫
I almost parted with you again yesterday.
Now you know my love.
♫In this encountering♫
♫Feel the four seasons♫
♫Fate is carved into love♫
What about you?
What's your answer?
♫How lucky I am♫
♫The decision I made for you♫
We agreed to live together till old age.
If you break your promise again,
I'll lock you up in the Qingquan Stronghold
and never let you out.
Don't you want my answer?
♫You're the only♫
Listen carefully.
Thank you.
♫Scenery I've walked into♫
Thank you for showing up in my life,
and making me no longer alone.
♫In this encountering♫
♫Feel the four seasons♫
We can share happiness
♫Fate is carved into love♫
and difficulties.
♫How lucky I am♫
I want to say,
whether in the past, now,
♫The decision I made for you♫
♫You're the only♫
or in the future,
it's good that you accompany me.
♫Scenery I've walked into♫
♫In this encountering♫
♫Feel the four seasons♫
♫Fate is carved into love♫
♫How lucky I am♫
♫The decision I made for you♫
It doesn't count.
Yu, aren't you sleeping?
Why are you back?
Chieftain Yu.
What Chieftain Yu? Call him dad.
Don't let him call me father.
We've prayed to the ancestral hall and got married.
Why can't him call you father?
He has never served tea
or entered the ancestral hall of Yu.
So it doesn't count.
Besides, he wrote the divorce letter.
You have nothing to do with him now.
The divorce letter was not sighed.
It doesn't count.
Lu Yan, call him father.
He's 3000 years old. He calls me father.
That will shorten my life.
Why are you so unreasonable?
You are my daughter.
Why should I reason with you?
We will go back to the Qingquan Stronghold
to get married again.
Let him be a member of the Yu family.
We'll talk about it after the ceremony.
Go back to sleep now.
Don't mind him.
I'll go back first.
Okay.
Are you done? Let's go.
I'll talk to him when he calms down.
Let's go.
Enough.
You're my father. I can't afford to offend you.
Let's go.
I'm so mad about this.
I'm so mad.
Didn't you see Lu Yan's love for Dengdeng
in the battle of Yingdu?
Why aren't you satisfied?
Why is Dengdeng
on his side now?
Since she met Lu Yan,
she doesn't recognize me as her biological father.
A grown girl can't be kept.
You're right.
I'm her father.
Why can't I match
that guy she just met for three months?
Look at you.
How about this?
We introduce another man to her, okay?
That man is
Gu Beixi.
It's useless.
I've done everything I can.
She will be blessed.
Don't worry about it. Or she will be more rebellious.
Dengdeng gave this to you.
My daughter is the one who cares about me.
Yes, she asked you to bring some supplements for Lu Yan
when you buy cigarettes.
Bring What?
Stop whining.
It smells so good.
Put a bouquet of flowers
in Lu Yan's room later.
Flowers should match beauties.
Here's the radix angelicae and ginseng rootlets you asked for.
Thank you.
Take care.
[Fried Food]
Again.
Come on.
Don't go back on your bet.
Big! Small!
Big! Big!
I win again.
Again.
No. Again.
Come on. Come on.
Look at it carefully.
Okay, open it.
I just want to play a round.
I don't believe it.
One more round. Go.
Small.
Small again, okay?
It's yours.
Give it to me.
Yours.
Go on.
Don't go back on your bet.
Sir, let's play.
Big or small?
Are you here to make a scene?
How dare you bet just with a coin?
Go away.
Go away if you have no money.
Wait. Wait.
Not bad.
Come, have a seat.
Come on.
Sit down.
Sit here.
Let's play together.
[Tea]
Again.
Don't go back on your bet.
Big! Big!
Small. Big.
Small. Small. Big.
Be good.
Senior Master.
Why are you back so late?
I was delayed on the way.
Did you gamble again?
I can tell by smelling your clothes.
Senior Master, you can't gamble anymore.
If you keep gambling, you might...
Don't tell Dengdeng.
If you leak it,
I'll kick you out of the Qingquan Stronghold.
Senior Master, I am able to keep a secret.
I won't tell anyone.
Senior Master, don't worry.
What won't you tell anyone?
Won't..
Tell...
About...
Senior Master bought supplements for his son-in-law.
Yes, it's embarrassing.
Yes.
Dahai, bring the chicken and medicine to Dengdeng.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
I'm sleepy.
I need to go back and sleep.
[The family is full of wealth with the spring breeze blowing]
That annoying Yu.
I asked him to buy ginseng,
but he bought me some ginseng rootlets.
The chicken is even a rooster.
This rooster
looks like Dahong.
It feels like I am killing my husband.
Brother Rooster,
since you and Dahong
are chickens.
Thank you for
making a sacrifice today.
Sorry.
What happened?
Why do I feel dizzy lately?
Did I consume too much energy?
Eat two steamed buns first.
Dengdeng, what's wrong?
Lu Yan.
You took advantage of me first this time.
Not bad.
I'm so sleepy.
I want to take a nap.
Hold me tight.
Don't let go.
Dengdeng!
It's a spirit worm.
How could it be?
Why is the energy that was infiltrated into Dengdeng's body
running out quickly?
-Dengdeng. -Master.
What happened?
I put some energy in her.
She's fine now.
Lu Yan.
Dengdeng, you're awake.
Don't worry.
I'm here. Don't be afraid.
You stay here and take good care of Dengdeng.
Dengdeng!
Master.
Have a good rest, Dengdeng.
Lu Yan, we meet again.
You did all this, didn't you?
You look so weak now.
You must have spent a lot of energy to save her.
I advise you not to waste your energy.
Our Saintess Yun Xi...
No, it's Yu Dengdeng.
Now she can enjoy the taste of the spirit worm.
What are you going to do to her?
Nothing.
I just planted a worm on her.
It can absorb her power for me at any time.
The worm is here, the person is here.
If the worm dies,
you will never see
the alive Yu Dengdeng.
Back then, you took the energy core of the Saintess.
That's why you could fight me.
[The family is blessed with the arrival of the New Year]
[The family is full of wealth with the spring breeze blowing]
Now that your energy is damaged,
you'd better give me the energy core.
Back then, without the energy core,
when we met on the battlefield,
I had never been defeated.
I must have underestimated you.
We humans
don't understand the evil ways of your spirit clan.
But we know how to join hands against the enemy.
You're too naive!
Dengdeng!
Master!
-Dengdeng!  -Master!
Don't scare me.
Master!
Think of a way.
What should we do?
How would I know?
Dengdeng, I'm here.
Zhu Rong.
You just want
the energy core in my body, right?
Release Yu Dengdeng and the others.
I'll give you the energy core.
Look at you, a good-for-nothing one!
Who are you to bargain with me?
Do you think
it can be taken as you wish?
Dengdeng!
You scared me to death.
Xin, how is he?
Your ladyship, don't worry.
He is fine with the protection of the energy.
He just needs to rest for a few days
and he can recover.
Okay.
That's good.
Let me give some energy to him.
Dengdeng.
Don't you know
what's your health condition?
How can you give him your energy?
I can't leave him alone.
It was because
he gave me his energy before.
That's why he was attacked by Zhu Rong.
But with your condition...
This...
I'm fine.
Sir.
Do you feel unwell?
Come.
Let me check what's inside you.
Well...
Didn't all the spirit worms die?
This one is different from previous worms.
The purpose of Zhu Rong is
to take advantage of my weakness
when my energy ran out
and put this spiritual worm in Dengdeng's body.
Then hurry up and drive it away.
I've just checked.
This spiritual worm
is connected to Dengdeng's body.
Once the spirit worm is hurt,
Dengdeng will also get hurts.
How could this be?
It keeps evolving.
It's getting harder and harder to address it.
Is there no other way?
Think of a way.
This...
Unless
let it out of Dengdon's body
in good condition.
Hurry up!
Yes, hurry up.
Look at her.
Don't be discouraged.
Didn't you say
"the hurdles are difficult to pass, but they must be passed;
every step is difficult, but we still have to go step by step."
There's always a way to deal with it.
Only you can do it.
Don't worry.
I will find a way.
I trust you.
Chieftain Yu,
I heard that there is one clan of the hunters
who never dealt with the spirit clan.
They specialize in evil things in the mortal world,
for example, chasing corpses or using legendary venomous worms.
You mean the King of Worm is also a kind of legendary venomous worms?
The Questions In 1000 Years also said
the spirit worms are not born
but are chosen.
So I suspect the spirit worm is the legendary venomous worm.
I see.
You want to deal with it
in the way of dealing with legendary venomous worms.
As far as I know,
in the Yingdu City,
there is a hunter who specialize in legendary venomous worms.
But his whereabouts are uncertain.
Now Dengdeng is in danger at any moment.
I must stay by her side all the time.
I wonder if you can look for this hunter
for me?
What do you mean?
Of course.
My daughter's matter is my business.
I can find them.
I'll go now.
Thank you.
Sir, what are you doing?
No.
Stop talking.
Do you think
I'm going to use a hairpin to dig out the energy core for Dengdeng?
Am I right, sir?
She likes you so much.
You can't go to the dead end.
She can't afford it.
I know.
If I give the energy core to Dengdeng,
it's like giving endless energy to Zhu Rong.
It will only make Dengdeng weak more fast.
Our priority now
is to expel the spirit worm.
But you were...
The energy in Dengdeng's body has been missing continuously.
I cast a spell
in her hairpin.
In this way,
once her energy changes,
I can sense it.
Sir, your energy is damaged.
You must take care of yourself.
I injured Zhu Rong badly this time.
He won't dare to come back for a while.
Don't worry.
I'll rest well.
[Daguangming Theater]
[Tai Feng Restaurant]
I heard about it, too.
Chieftain Gu.
[Tai Feng Restaurant]
Chieftain Gu, something happened.
Director Bai was dismissed.
When the Bai family went back to their hometown,
they met Xiongya Stronghold who wanted to revenge.
They were all killed.
Where did it happen?
I'll take you there.
[Tai Feng Restaurant]
Shiqi.
Uncle Bai.
Chieftain Gu.
Look.
Is this Miss Bai?
Shiqi.
Let go.
Please arrange
and let them rest in peace.
Okay.
Shiqi.
How long have I been sleeping?
My energy...
Come in.
Your ladyship, I brought you your favorite sunflower seeds.
How are you? Did you sleep well?
I slept well.
Come here.
Sit.
Are you thirsty?
Let me get you some water.
How can you do it yourself?
Let me feed you.
Is it necessary?
You don't allow me to move or take anything.
Of course.
You are so weak now.
You need more rest.
It's just a spirit worm.
It's just a small worm!
I'm not pregnant.
I can't even move.
What? Can it fall out?
No.
Lu Yan, discipline him.
Xin should listen to you more.
It has been like this for thousands of years.
Master, come here.
He said
Chieftain Gu brought a message.
Gu Beixi?
Where did he go?
Chieftain Gu went to look for Miss Bai.
Director Bai was dismissed.
When the Bai family went back to their hometown,
they met Xiongya Stronghold who wanted to revenge.
Miss Bai is missing.
Bai Shiqi is missing.
But don't worry.
She may be in Xiongya Stronghold.
Chieftain Gu asked you not to worry.
He will save Miss Bai.
Xin,
find a way to send a message to Nanfeng Stronghold,
and ask them to come here to support Gu Beixi.
OK.
Here, bro.
Have some tea with me.
Thank you.
I hope Lady Bai is blessed.
Trust Gu Beixi.
He can deal with gangsters.
-I finally found it. -Father.
Daughter, I finally found
how to eliminate the spirit worm.
[Thousand Years For You]
♫If♫
♫Love could be sensed♫
♫Missing you would have♫
♫Sounds♫
♫The most beautiful♫
♫Scenery in life♫
♫All that I heard about♫
♫Is related to you♫
♫When two hearts are so close to each other♫
♫When the whole world is occupied by you♫
♫I'll call out your name so hard♫
♫Until you respond♫
♫You're the only♫
♫Scenery I've walked into♫
♫In this encountering, feel the four seasons♫
♫Fate is carved into love♫
♫How lucky I am♫
♫The decision I made for you♫
♫When two hearts are so close to each other♫
♫When the whole world is occupied by you♫
♫I'll call out your name so hard♫
♫Until you respond♫
♫You're the only♫
♫Scenery I've walked into♫
♫In this encountering, feel the four seasons♫
♫Fate is carved into love♫
♫How lucky I am♫
♫The decision I made for you♫
[iQIYI]