[Produced by iQIYI]
♫The consonance of heaven and earth flew apart♫
♫The white snow was blooming♫
♫The one thousand years' time is as immortal as amber♫
♫I'm still as obsessed as before♫
♫The broken twilight fell in chaos♫
♫It's hard to let go of the love of the previous life♫
♫Tears fell down. It was deep love♫
♫The tears formed a bitter sea♫
♫Fate rose and fell♫
♫Love was buried for a long time♫
♫Love and hatred are as overwhelming as heavy rain♫
♫Come with me♫
♫Guarded it alone, ran far away and roared♫
♫Never mentioned letting go of you♫
♫It's me♫
♫Who stared at you♫
♫Who ignited you♫
♫It's me♫
♫Who ran towards you♫
♫Who became part of you♫
♫It's me♫
[Thousand Years For You]
[Episode 26]
My head hurts so much.
My head hurts.
What's wrong?
Why does my head hurt so much?
Wei Du, it's getting late.
I want to go back early and rest.
General, it's still early.
Why don't we drink more?
Wei Du, let's talk tomorrow.
Okay. I'll send you back to rest.
No need.
Just ask a servant
to tell me how to go back.
Okay.
Guards!
General.
Send the general back to rest.
Yes.
I'll go back now.
Okay.
It hurts so much.
Dengdeng, how are you?
You're here.
I heard you have a headache.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Are you okay?
I think something is wrong with your lieutenant.
General.
General Yan went to Ms. Yu's room.
What?
Why did you say that?
Because he lied.
My father clearly left a mark.
He said he had gone to the direction of the underground palace.
But when he went there,
he didn't even check or look at it,
and then he denied it.
Isn't that strange?
Besides,
there are two azaleas in front of his yard.
Those are the azaleas from Dandong.
They've been developed and cultivated by a famous man within recent decades.
They're very expensive.
You can't buy them outside.
My father spent a lot of effort
to get two azaleas for my mother.
Don't you think it's even stranger that he could
get them so easily?
Your doubt is reasonable.
But Wei Du and I have been friends for more than ten years.
He is upright and kind.
Maybe he has a reason for it and it's inconvenient
for him to tell us about it.
You haven't seen him for 3,000 years.
People change.
You should be careful.
I know.
I'll give you more energy.
Then you can fall asleep in a better way.
It's not enough to merely give me the energy.
I punish you to make the bed for the chief.
Why do you punish me?
Of course I need to punish you.
Because you only care about your buddy
and forget your wife.
Are you going to do it or not?
If not, just forget it.
Your buddies are like your limbs.
Women are like clothes.
To repay me,
also help me make the bed tomorrow morning.
Okay.
After you get up tomorrow morning,
I'll come to your room to make the bed for you.
It's troublesome to run around.
How about you
stay here?
Stay here?
Okay.
Let's just sleep together.
Don't regret it.
Why would I regret it?
General.
You went to the wrong room.
Please let me take you back to rest.
Your general didn't go to the wrong room.
He'll sleep in my room tonight.
General, your room
was decorated by me according to
your preference you used to have.
Aren't you going to take a look?
Your general doesn't need to...
Alright. I got it.
I will go back to my room.
I'll take my leave.
I have to go back.
We still have plenty of time.
Forget it. I was just kidding.
I'll spare you this time.
Go back to sleep.
I'm leaving.
By the way,
people here are very sensitive to the Spirit Clan.
You need to be more careful these days.
When I'm not around,
don't use the energy.
I know. Don't worry.
You should be careful, too.
Don't sleep too deeply at night.
How dare you, Wei Du!
Let me see what you're up to.
Li was hurt by the Ghost Vines.
The wound is ulcerated.
The doctors in the city all said that it couldn't be cured.
I'm afraid
only by cutting off his arm can he survive.
General, you have the energy core of the Spirit Clan inside your body.
It is said that it can help create flesh and bones.
Please save him, general.
General Yan, this is amazing.
Say thank you to the general.
Thank you, General Yan.
Go and rest.
Yes.
This energy core is indeed a magical object.
General.
With this supernatural ability,
you can exorcise all those who are from the Spirit Clan.
This belongs to the Saintess of the Spirit Clan.
How can it be easily used to kill people from the Spirit Clan?
You are right.
Wei Du.
How is it going with inquiring about the Dust-proof Bead?
No news yet.
I've ordered people to search for it
all over the city.
I believe there will be news soon.
I'll take my leave.
Ms. Yu, where are you going?
It's time for lunch.
I'm not hungry. I have something to do.
Ms. Yu, are you looking for General Yan?
General Yan was invited
by General Wei early in the morning to discuss something.
How about this?
You go somewhere else with me?
Okay. Just go with her.
Give it to me.
Let me help you take it inside.
Let me do it.
Give it to me.
What era is it now? And you still play this?
It's boring.
Ms. Yu.
Relax, relax.
How about I teach you to play something new today?
What is it?
What is this?
-I've never seen it. -I've never seen it.
It's square. Look.
What are you doing?
Big! Big!
Small! Small! Small!
Come on. Let's play together.
Hurry up.
-Come on. -Okay. Let's play.
Place your bets.
-Big! -Small! Small!
Small.
Who dares to bet with me?
Let me do it. Let me do it. Let me do it.
Ms. Yu, what are you betting on?
Those who lose
have to take off the clothes.
Again. Again.
What? You don't dare?
How about this?
If I lose, I'll take off all my clothes.
If you lose, you only have to take off your tops.
Okay. No problem.
Let me do it.
I bet it's big.
Big! Big! Big!
Big. Small.
Place your bets.
Big! Big! Big!
Just admit defeat.
Take your tops off.
Really, Ms. Yu?
Come on.
Master,
Xin and I went to take a bath in the bathhouse,
and tricked a guard.
I saw that dragon tattoo on all their bodies.
Master, I found something.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Master, I've also checked the training field.
It's true that every soldier has the dragon tattoo.
Does everyone have it?
If everyone has it,
then I don't know
who killed my mother.
I sounded Wei Du out just now.
He denied it thoroughly.
I wonder where my father is now.
Did he discover
the dragon tattoos on their bodies?
Ma'am, I'm back.
Xin.
How is it?
Did you find any clues?
I've searched all around the casino.
I didn't find the mark left by Chieftain Yu.
You didn't find any mark?
That bastard Wei Du!
He really lied to me.
If my father has left,
it means he has finished the task.
According to his habits,
after he finishes a task,
he will definitely go to the casino to gamble.
But now,
there is no news about him around the casino.
That means
he's still in the city.
Still in the city?
Why did Wei Du lie to us?
He wants me to stay away from Lu Yan,
and tries to play tricks with me.
Let me find out what he's up to.
Where is General Wei?
General Wei went out to do something.
I heard that all the soldiers of the Shu Army are skilled in martial arts.
How about we
have a competition?
Ms. Yu.
You're good at swordsmanship.
So Lieutenant Wei is in the mansion.
Why don't we have a competition?
Ms. Yu,
you are the general's distinguished guest.
What?
Are you afraid, Lieutenant Wei?
Ms. Yu.
What? You don't dare to fight?
Blades have no eyes.
It's just a competition.
Is there any secret
in Lieutenant Wei's martial arts skills?
Are you afraid that I'll learn them?
Lieutenant Wei is good at martial arts.
If it weren't for you...
If it weren't for the Spiritual Clan...
What are you doing?
I... This...
General.
Dengdeng!
General, I...
I'm fine. I pretended it.
I know you pretended it.
What do you know?
Now, you only know
to be with Wei Du every day.
You don't care about me at all.
To be honest,
don't you think Wei Du is suspicious?
You stay with him every day.
Don't you think he's up to no good?
Back then, Wei and I fought together at the risk of our lives on the battlefield.
We were good brothers who could die for each other.
I still trust him.
Fine.
You trust him?
So you don't trust me?
Lu Yan, let me ask you.
Choose between him and me.
Which of us will you choose?
No, Dengdeng.
Stop messing around.
Who is messing around?
Why do you think I'm messing around?
Am I messing around like this?
Lu Yan, you jerk!
You have no conscience.
After he showed up,
you don't even trust me now?
It's not that I don't trust you.
There must be some misunderstanding between you two.
He's not a scheming man.
What misunderstanding? No misunderstanding.
Let me tell you.
It's a pity that
Wei Du doesn't act in a play about the fight of imperial harem.
I won't let the general repeat the same mistake.
Zhu Rong!
Zhu Rong! Come out!
Are you satisfied with the reunion with your old friend
I've arranged for you?
It's you
who lured them here to look for the Dust-proof Bead.
What you want is the return of General Lu
so as to fulfill the great cause of Shu in your mind.
As for how I brought him here,
why do you care?
General.
Come in.
But you clearly know the Dust-proof Bead is...
So what?
Are you worried that General Yan, whom you care so much about,
will abandon you
for the sake of that woman?
Our general is benevolent and cares about his subjects so much.
How would he be like that?
Good.
Bring Yu Dengdon to me.
We'll get what we need respectively, and then we'll be even.
Are all the people in the Ancient Shu City
more important
than Yu Dengdeng?
I believe you
have your own judgment, General Wei.
General, we found the Dust-proof Bead.
It's right inside the underground palace.
Ghost Vines are very dangerous.
If we want to get inside,
we have to put living things there
to attract their attention first.
Master,
I didn't expect the Ancient Shu to be so rich.
There are so many beads.
Which do you think is the Dust-proof Bead?
The Dust-proof Bead is a rare treasure.
It is said that after the first emperor of Shu passed away,
the Dust-proof Bead and other treasures were hidden
inside Shu's shrine.
Do you think
they are weird today?
They played dice and took a bath in the bathhouse
with us yesterday.
They don't even dare to look at us today.
General Wei is too overbearing.
They are so scared of him to be like this.
I think so.
Is General Wei
jealous that you're too close to Lu Yan,
so he has teamed up with them to marginalize us?
If that's the case,
General Wei can survive for at least several rounds
in a play about the fight of imperial harem.
Though he's powerful, I'm not an ordinary woman.
Gao.
The five-five-six result of the dice game
yesterday was really amazing.
Let's compete in the game another day.
What do you think?
Ms. Yu,
our army is busy with the intense training every day.
I'm afraid they don't have time to play with you.
If you can't refrain from playing the game,
I can ask someone to find
several idle men from the city
to play it with you.
General Wei, what you're saying
doesn't sound friendly.
I just want to remind you
not to ruin the good morale of my army.
-I also want to remind you... -Dengdeng.
We'd better go to find the Dust-proof Bead now.
Wei Du.
Yes.
How far are we from the treasury?
We'll be there soon.
Let's go.
Yes.
Time is running out. Let's hurry up.
Yes!
General.
Keep your voice down.
Is this your family's ancestral temple?
Please go to the Mu Pool and wash your hands.
Then take a bow
to show respect for all the former emperors of Shu.
[Memorial Tablet of Shu's Empress Gao Yao]
[Memorial Tablet of Shu's Emperor Baiguan Gaozhao]
General.
General, please.
How do I wash my hands?
Just do it normally.
Kneel.
Master.
Bow.
[Memorial Tablet of Shu's Empress Gao Yao]
[Memorial Tablet of Shu's Emperor Baiguan Gaozhao]
By doing this,
is it considered as having paid respect to your parents?
What do you think?
Since we've paid respect to your parents,
we're officially married now.
I'll see who'll compete with me for you in the future.
General Wei.
Since we've washed our hands and bowed to the ancestors,
can you take us inside now?
I'll get inside with the general.
You and Peng can wait here.
Why?
The secret treasury of the royal family of Shu is inside.
Only the members of the royal family of Shu can enter.
You and Peng are outsiders after all.
It's inconvenient for you to enter.
I'll leave these soldiers with you.
You can wait here with ease for the time being.
It won't be dangerous.
General Wei,
you're also not a member of the royal family, are you?
Lu Yan and I have got married and performed the formal wedding ceremony.
How come you can go in
but I became a outsider?
Dengdeng, you two wait for me here.
I'll be back soon.
Okay. I'll listen to you.
Come back early.
Don't worry.
General, please.
General.
Three thousand years ago,
the Spirit Clan descended from the sky,
invaded our country,
robbed and killed our people.
Wherever the Spirit Clan went, the people were living in misery.
Fortunately, the former emperor and you successively
led us to fight the enemy on the battlefield.
Tens of thousands of our people were sacrificed,
and we finally drove the Spirit Clan 50 kilometers away from Shu.
Unfortunately,
we failed in the end.
We couldn't kill all the members of the Spirit Clan.
General, the secret treasury is ahead.
General, please.
General, the thing you're looking for
is right here.
The Dragon-pattern Sword?
It used to be your personal weapon.
After the war,
I tried my best to get it back,
and has kept it until now.
On behalf of the tens of thousands of soldiers who died 3,000 years ago,
I hope you can hold the sword again,
expel the Spirit Clan of Nine Continents, and kill them all.
I didn't come here for the Dragon-pattern Sword.
Where is the Dust-proof Bead?
General,
you are such a smart man.
You let me lead the way as soon as we entered the underground palace.
You must have known
I've been in and out of the underground palace many times,
so I know everything about this place.
In that case,
I don't have to hide it.
The Dust-proof Bead is indeed hidden in this underground palace.
After you take this sword
to lead us to kill the Spiritual Clan,
I will give the Dust-proof Bead
to you.
Now the war between humans and the Spirit Clan has subsided.
I have no intention of killing with this sword.
General,
have you forgotten the will of the late former emperor to expel the Spirit Clan?
Have you forgotten
what the former emperor
said to you when the dragon pattern
was tattooed on your body?
I found the dragon pattern mark
on the ground which was left
by your mother before she died.
I think this mark
must have something to do
who killed your mother.
Why do you have dragon patterns on your body?
Back then,
the other soldiers and I
thought you had died in the jungle
to save the Saintess of the Spirit Clan,
so we tattooed the same dragon pattern
on our own bodies
in order to remember
our Shu soldiers' mission
to kill all members of the Spirit Clan in the world.
The mission of Shu soldiers
is never to kill all members of the Spirit Clan in the world,
but to protect people all over the world
so that they can live a peaceful life.
If we don't eliminate the Spirit Clan,
how can the world be peaceful?
General, we were weak back then
and we failed to eliminate the Spirit Clan.
But you have the energy core now.
It's the source of the Spirit Clan's energy.
This is our best chance to kill all members of the Spirit Clan.
It's been 3,000 years.
The worlds of humans and the Spirit Clan
have already integrated into one world.
They are closely related and cannot be separated from each other.
It's impossible for either party
to kill the other party.
Moreover,
Yu Dengdeng has inherited
the same peace faith which Yun Xi had back then.
I believe she can make
a wise choice.
I also believe
she can lead humans and the Spirit Clan
to continue living together in peace.
How can we trust
someone from the Spirit Clan?
General, don't give up your great cause.
Enough!
No more talking about the energy core.
Give me the Dust-proof Bead.
I knew
you would make such a choice.
However,
even if you're willing to return the energy core,
Yu Dengdeng might not
be able to live until then.
What do you mean?
Three thousand years ago,
you were bewitched by that woman
and almost lost your life.
This time, I won't let you
make the same mistake again.
What are you going to do to her?
It's not what I want to do to her.
Instead, it depends on
what he wants to do to her.
He?
Zhu Rong?
Wei Du, in order to stall me,
you colluded with Zhu Rong.
As long as I can kill the woman who deceived you,
even if I have colluded with Zhu Rong this time,
so what?
General.
Please take this sword.
Wei Du, oh, Wei Du.
This underground palace is well designed.
All the devices and secret passages here are dangerous.
I've been exploring this place for a hundred years.
There are still many places I haven't been to.
Besides, this underground palace can block the aura of the Spirit Clan.
No matter how powerful you are,
it's still very difficult for you to find Yu Dengdeng
in this underground palace.
General.
Don't go.
Wei Du, you're doing this
to force me to become someone like Zhu Rong,
making the whole world miserable again.
Is this your wish and original intention?
You finally got a chance to live again.
Isn't it good to live peacefully?
No!
You are not our general.
Our general won't abandon us.
You are no longer the general
who we followed back then.
I said
Yu Dengdeng
might not be able to survive.
You've underestimated her.
She's a chieftain.
According to the message Yu Dengdeng has just sent me,
we've got the Dust-proof Bead.
What?
Thank you, Wei Du.
He misjudged it.
Bastard!
The Dust-proof Bead...
It's still here.
Is there
a trick?
Delicious.
Yummy.
Eat, eat, eat.
You don't forget to eat while you're dreaming.
It's delicious.
Stop sleeping.
You're drooling on my clothes.
Look.
Master, I didn't sleep well last night.
I'm so sleepy.
Dahai,
how long has it been since you brushed your teeth?
Why does your saliva stink?
Does it stink?
Men are just like that.
It doesn't stink, master.
Smell it.
So disgusting.
It's not that my mouth stinks. I...
Master, there's a bad smell indeed.
But it smells like...
Like dead men.
Stop talking nonsense.
This is the treasury of the underground palace.
How can there be a smell of dead men?
Don't scare me.
Unless...
This is not just a treasury.
Could it be that General Wei
is jealous of you for being too close to Concubine Lu
so he wants to trap us here
and kill us?
Anyway, let's run away first.
Run towards the direction where Lu Yan has gone.
Okay. Let's stay composed.
It's good.
So tired from sitting for too long. Take a rest.
Take a rest.
My back hurts.
Thanks for your hard work. Sit for some more time.
Take a rest.
It's useless for them to run away.
What a waste of energy.
Why did you run?
I had a stomachache.
I thought there was a toilet over there.
Yes, yes, yes.
Master.
They clearly left from that direction.
Why couldn't we go out of here
by walking around?
There must be a contraption here.
That means
we were tricked by Wei Du.
Does he really
plan to trap us here?
We need to find another way out.
By the way, I have this.
Soldiers, you must be tired.
Let's play.
Have a bet.
Bet?
Didn't I teach you yesterday?
It's simple.
Big or small?
Play the game. Come on.
Big. Small.
Take a look. Come on.
Come on.
Have a bet.
Let's form a circle.
Place your bets.
Big.
-Look! -This is quite fun.
How is it? Is it fun?
Hurry up.
Have a bet. Come on.
Come on. Teach us.
Big! Big! Big!
Come on. Guess whether it's big or small.
[Memorial Tablet]
It's okay.
It must be big this time.
Again. Again.
Big! Big! Big!
-Big! Big! -Small!
Look!
Come on.
Again. Again. Again.
It must be small this time.
It must be small.
Big! Big! Big!
Hurry up! Big!
It must be small this time.
Gosh!
Just defeat me first.
Is there no way ahead?
-What should we do? -Let's go.
Go back again?
I'm exhausted.
What should we do?
Let's go.
Go again?
Slow down. Slow down.
Slow down.
Hurry up!
No, master.
No. I'm exhausted.
I'm exhausted, master.
Take a break.
Tell me whether this is a treasury
or a maze.
This place is so scary.
Do you think those soldiers
are afraid of it?
Speaking of the soldiers,
I also think they're very strange.
Previously,
they played dice
with me, didn't they?
How come they don't seem to know how to play it today?
Right. That's what I mean.
They once played dice with us
and bathed with us in the bathhouse.
Today,
they pretended not to know us.
Gosh.
That's so weird.
We can't trust Wei Du's men.
Dahai, let's go if you've had enough rest.
Find Lu Yan as soon as possible,
and leave this scary place.
Let's go.
Isn't this a mark left by Senior Master?
Yes.
It's my father's mark.
He left a mark here.
But there's no other way here.
Look.
What is this place?
Let's take a look inside.
No, master.
There's no other way out.
Master.
Let's go.
This... This is not okay.
Oh, my God.
Master, it's too dark.
Is there a ghost here?
Don't talk nonsense.
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
Let's get the tinder first.
What?
It's so dark.
What tripped me?
The tinder! Take it out!
Go, master!
-Don't be afraid. -What is this?
Calm down.
What is this?
Let's see what's going on first.
Dahai.
Something is wrong with these clothes.
Really?
Come here.
Master!
Look.
I don't know which era these clothes are from.
These...
These are from the past few years.
Master.
And these two clothes.
Look.
Aren't these two clothes the same as
what the Baile villagers outside there wear?
Take a look.
Do you think they are
Dummy's missing friends?
Actually, they didn't disappear at all.
They accidentally went into the underground palace and died here.
But Wei Du said
there are Ghost Vines at the entrance of the underground palace.
Ordinary people can't get in.
So there must be other problems in this case.
Maybe my father
found something fishy,
so he took the risk to come here.
These people
died here.
Their descendants don't even have a place to hold a funeral for them.
How pitiful.
Go to the heaven early.
Rest in peace.
Master.
Fireflies.
Am I right?
I went to a dark place.
Fireflies... Fireflies brought me out!
These are the fireflies Dummy talked about.
[Thousand Years For You]
♫If♫
♫Love could be sensed♫
♫Missing you would have♫
♫Sounds♫
♫The most beautiful♫
♫Scenery in life♫
♫All that I heard about♫
♫Is related to you♫
♫When two hearts are so close to each other♫
♫When the whole world is occupied by you♫
♫I'll call out your name so hard♫
♫Until you respond♫
♫You're the only♫
♫Scenery I've walked into♫
♫In this encountering, feel the four seasons♫
♫Fate is carved into love♫
♫How lucky I am♫
♫The decision I made for you♫
♫When two hearts are so close to each other♫
♫When the whole world is occupied by you♫
♫I'll call out your name so hard♫
♫Until you respond♫
♫You're the only♫
♫Scenery I've walked into♫
♫In this encountering, feel the four seasons♫
♫Fate is carved into love♫
♫How lucky I am♫
♫The decision I made for you♫
[iQIYI]