A long time ago, you told me
to switch to a game you are better at if you want to win.
I finally realized...
what that meant today.
Jae On...
Do not call my name with your dirty mouth.
That is enough now.
No matter what you do, the more you try, the more dangerous it will be for you.
It is not too late to go far away from Yongcheonru.
Go far away?
I have finally come to face you like this, and you want me to go far away?
It...
It was so hard for me to get here.
I cannot go until I kill you.
You killed my father.
You should also die and atone.
Do you think I killed Teacher?
Do not play ignorant.
I saw everything.
I never forgot, even for a day.
I know how you killed...
my father that night... twelve years ago.
How could you do that?
You were closer than family to us. How could you?
I have been clenching my teeth for twelve years
waiting to repay you for what you did.
No. No, Jae On.
That is not true.
- Let me explain—
- Do not blabber your dirty mouth.
Do you think my father's blood on your sword will disappear that way?
I...
did not kill Teacher.
How dare you call him your teacher?
You backstabber.
I have never betrayed Teacher. Not even for a moment.
I have never brought shame to him
or abandoned my beliefs.
Beliefs?
You killed someone and took over as the Master Innkeeper. Is that your belief?
Hong Jae On, leave Yongcheonru.
That is how you will survive
and what Teacher wanted.
He asked me until the last moment.
He asked me to protect you.
You are lying.
Stop lying!
Why did you stop?
Stab me.
If you would be satisfied by stabbing me,
if this is the revenge you have dreamed of,
go on and stab me.
Why are you hesitating?
You said you dreamed of avenging your father for twelve years.
I am not the one you should take revenge on.
Do you think I would fall for that?
You will die if you jump in carelessly.
Shut up!
Your father only worried about you while dying.
Do not make his...
sacrifice go to waste.
I noticed something unusual while investigating Cheon.
It is regarding the missing person's poster at the market recently.
Cheon had a business partner who died long ago.
He put up the posters to look for his daughter.
Why do you think he is looking for her?
I am not the one you should take revenge on.
You will die if you jump in carelessly.
♫  The round moonlight has suddenly  ♫
♫  Turned into a crescent moon  ♫
♫  But your heart...  ♫
Keep this thing with you.
You must never lose it.
Do you understand?
♫  Left alone  ♫
♫  I draw you, then erase you  ♫
Jae On, a jade ring does not guarantee happiness.
Just live happily, no matter what you find.
♫  If you cannot come, then please call me instead  ♫
♫  And if you tell me your wish  ♫
♫  I'll fly, fluttering  ♫
♫  Following this longing to where you sleep  ♫
♫  Under the same sky, no matter where  ♫
♫  I'll go  ♫
♫  Like the wind, I'll soar  ♫
What?
Prince Mu Yeong was not even in Onyang?
Are you sure about that?
Yes, Your Excellency.
I knew... the King's intention was something else.
Do you think I would leave things that way?
Does he think I would hand over the throne when I am so close?
He certainly sees me as a pushover.
Your Excellency!
Someone from Yongcheonru came by with urgent news for you.
Who? Is it Seol Mae Hwa?
No, it is not.
He apparently is an innkeeper.
Innkeeper?
He wants to talk to me directly?
Yes.
Tell him to come in.
Your Excellency.
Who are you?
That is enough.
You are handsome. You are handsome.
Today is finally the day.
I know. Hong Deok Su really is an impressive fellow.
He ended up doing it.
Jun Hwa, you helped greatly.
Both Lee Eun Ho and I were against it in the beginning.
That is also true.
But there was a reason I had to do it.
So? When will you confess?
C-Confess?
Hong Deok Su told me she is actually a woman,
but she does not know that you know it.
Should you not tell her you know before you make a mistake?
Oh, that confession? I see.
Should I?
She tries hard to pretend to be a man in front of you.
If she finds out later that you already know,
things would become awkward between you two.
That is right. I should tell her first.
Yes, tell her before it is too late.
Hey, it sure is a well-made sign.
Were you all here yesterday?
Did you put this back on?
What is this?
I am sure it was not there yesterday.
- What is that mark?
- Did something happen yesterday?
No, nothing happened.
Did you not sleep last night?
Your eyes look a bit puffy.
Did you catch a cold?
Did you get rained on yesterday or something?
Look at yourself. Your face appears puffy.
It is...
because I am nervous about Bulrakho's opening soon.
Lee Eun Ho, what happened to your hand?
What are you doing?
Bulrakho is opening soon. You cannot hurt your hand.
Was it badly hurt?
You only care about Bulrakho.
Was I too harsh?
Let us go.
Seol Mae Hwa, do you not have anything to tell me?
I am not sure.
Really?
I heard something major is happening at Yongcheonru today.
Do you not know?
I am not sure what you heard, but I will look into it if you want me to.
How could you not tell me Yongcheonru is opening a gambling house?
Were you going to play ignorant until the end?
How dare you open a gambling house?
It is against the law.
Cheon must be up to something, right?
I can smell something. Something very suspicious.
We are all ready.
Let us open.
It is a high-class gambling house in the capital.
You will have to ambush as quickly and quietly as possible.
Yes. Let us go.
- Let us go.
- Twenty-one.
Congratulations.
That is it.
Go inside and look everywhere!
Yes, sir.
This is amazing.
- Go inside!
- Yes, sir!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
- Stop!
Arrest all the criminals who broke the law!
What shall we do if the Investigation Bureau comes for a search?
Just practice. Do not worry about such matters.
What makes you so confident, exactly?
Goodness...
Because we will not break the law.
Did Master Cheon know, too?
I am sorry, but you are not allowed in here.
Wait, you are...
What is going on?
Are they from the Investigation Bureau?
This is not an official event. Go back.
Please proceed and continue the game.
My apologies.
Go, go. Get started.
Start again.
Let me help you, Your Excellency.
Please do not...
come to Yongcheonru tonight.
What?
Did I ever suggest something harmful to you, Your Excellency?
It is not the time now. Please listen to me.
Seol Mae Hwa, did you—
Goodness!
It is so noisy that I cannot choose my card!
My apologies!
Sorry, I am late. The Investigation Bureau must be mistaken.
Things were just becoming enjoyable.
- Make them leave quickly.
- Yes.
What is he saying?
Please leave now.
He is an ambassador from the Qing dynasty.
What? An ambassador?
Please enjoy yourselves.
He is an ambassador from the Qing dynasty?
Yes, that is correct.
No natives are allowed in here.
The Qing dynasty's ambassador is in Hanyang?
How do you know about matters that the ministers are unaware of?
Did His Majesty order you to do this?
How could I know what the higher-ups think?
I will keep my mouth shut about the fact that
you rushed over here.
Did I tell you Jun Hwa shares his name with someone?
There is someone who shares the name that attracts fortune.
I looked for that lost name all my life for my immature Jun Hwa.
I am starting to think...
he might have found someone else instead.
It is because Young Master Jun Hwa is blessed with good people.
I was after Prince Mu Yeong,
but I amazingly caught someone superior.
My son's fortune is a frightening one.
It certainly is frightening.
Good, good.
I will wash my hands quickly.
What should we do, Your Excellency?
I will make them pay for humiliating me.
Take the soldiers back.
Yes, sir.
Let us go.
Things must not have gone the way you wanted with the Minister of Defense.
Are you happy that things went your way?
Do you still think...
I am reckless?
How is it that you two are together?
Hong Deok Su,
you did a great job.
I will allow your reinstatement as promised.
Thank you, Master Cheon.
You agree as well, right, Master Innkeeper?
I would like you to train him well.
He is so talented. It would have been a shame to lose him.
I will do so.
Are the guests all right?
I was wondering what kind of flies would be attracted to Bulrakho.
I did not expect the Minister of Defense to come on the first day.
Let us go.
Yes.
I do not know who the rat was,
but it certainly was quick.
- Hong Deok Su.
- Yes?
When you are running a business,
you must beware of mice that put holes in your house's storage.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You killed my father.
You should also die and atone.
Teacher!
Please get up.
You need to run away.
Hong Min Shik.
You should live.
Live and see the world we have dreamed of.
Teacher, why...
Someday,
if my Jae On comes to see you,
you should care for her.
My Jae On is in your care.
Please let go.
Please let go!
Try going that way.
That way!
Jae On.
Stop lying!
My Jae On is in your care.
I knew you could be reinstated quickly.
Yes, the true man, Hong Deok Su...
came back in no time.
What are you doing? What...
Goodness, what is with you?
Goodness, seriously.
- Hold on!
- You scared me.
You need to dust your feet before entering.
All right. Here, here.
I dusted them off. Are you happy?
Dust off your clothes, too. Behave yourself, Hong Deok Su.
Are you possessed by a ghost that demands cleanliness? Why are you nagging?
He has been sneezing since earlier.
He must be sensitive because he caught a cold.
No.
Lee Eun Ho,
something is bothering you, right?
Hong Deok Su, I share a room with someone who is unclean like you. How could I be happy?
Lee Eun Ho, do you want to switch rooms with me, then?
Being excessively concerned with cleanliness is no good, either. Go inside now.
W-What is wrong with you? How bad is your cold?
- Let us go, too.
- I am happy to switch rooms anytime.
Just ask me.
You are not switching any rooms.
Welcome back, true man, Hong Deok Su.
Yes. I told you I would be back soon.
Yes. Do not blame me for what is in the past.
Rules are still rules.
- Of course, Instructor Bang.
- You went through a lot.
And Lee Eun Ho, you should return the hammer you borrowed.
Why make me come to get it back?
I am not feeling well.
Bring it back quickly.
Lee Eun Ho,
are you sleeping?
I am.
What if...
you have been running all your might
but ended up on the wrong path?
Are you talking about Bulrakho?
You worked hard on it. Do you regret it?
It is not that.
If you get to the end, you will find out
if you chose the wrong path or not.
What if I got to the end
and it was the wrong path?
You can go back and correct things.
That is what I will do.
You put the sign back up, did you not?
I just put it back up because it had fallen.
You nagged and yelled at me so much earlier.
Thank you.
Did you cry because the sign fell?
W-Who? Who cried?
It is all right to cry.
I said I did not cry. Goodness...
When I was little,
I could not cry because I had to be cautious.
But when I wanted to cry later,
I could not cry anymore.
It is all right to cry here.
Anyone could use...
a place like that.
Sleep soundly tonight.
What kind of man has such a pale face?
He looks like a painting.
My goodness, my goodness.
I did not think the Qing dynasty's ambassador would come.
Hey, Hong Deok Su is truly remarkable.
Hey, hey. I have chosen him as mine.
Do not try to steal him.
Master Cheon seems to be interested in him, too.
Yes, I heard he is having lunch with them today.
Anyway, does it not seem Master Innkeeper is falling out of favor?
This is the first time she did not attend the lunch with Master Cheon.
No.
Maybe she was not invited at all.
My goodness!
This is Seong Jin.
The Master Innkeeper asked for the Geumokdang hosting plan.
Did I not give it to her?
Here it is.
My goodness, my goodness. What shall we do?
What if he heard everything we said?
"We"? You were the only one talking.
Stop saying silly things.
What will you do if the words spread?
I heard the Bottom-Tier Room excelled in Gyohwadang this year.
Good job opening Bulrakho as well.
This meal is for you. Eat as much as you would like.
Yes, sir.
I heard you were against opening Bulrakho at first.
Yongcheonru would be in danger if we broke the law.
I cannot believe you are worried about Yongcheonru.
You have become a true innkeeper.
Your father would be truly happy.
I have learned a lot ever since I came to Yongcheonru.
I have learned how to distinguish between real and fake,
in either an object or a person.
Is that so?
How do you distinguish between real and fake?
How do you do that?
It is fake if it copies what is real.
What is the reason you made Yongcheonru just like the palace?
Do you want to be the King?
Hey.
All right...
By the way, how did you know Master Innkeeper was good at Ssangpae?
She told me once when I played the game with a Jakyakjae guest.
Was Master Innkeeper Seol around since Yongcheonru first started?
Well, you could say that.
How did she end up in her current position?
You are very interested in the Master Innkeeper.
Yes. My dream is to become one someday.
We might be from the Bottom-Tier Room,
but we are ambitious, Master Cheon.
You are so magnanimous, like a real man.
But you are as pretty as a woman.
Hong Deok Su, is your mother your only family?
Yes, my father passed when I was a child.
Is that why the fortune got mixed up?
Anyway, the more I look at your forehead, the more familiar it seems.
And the mouth, too.
You told us to eat comfortably, but you keep talking. We will not be able to digest.
Oh, right. I talked too much since I have not done this in a while.
Hong Deok Su, bring your mother to Yongcheonru sometime.
She must be a great mother since she raised her son so well.
I would love to meet her.
Yes, I will.
Tasty.
Have I upset you somehow, Your Majesty?
Why are you saying that as soon as you arrived?
I have been only loyal to you for the last twelve years.
I am so deeply disappointed.
Speak so I understand what you mean.
Do you know what I saw at Yongcheonru yesterday?
The Qing dynasty's ambassador came here secretly?
How could you do that without telling me anything?
It was an unofficial visit.
How did you see him?
By chance, did you get caught
trying to do something with that lowly Cheon?
Minister, watch what you say.
The ambassador visited for Prince Seon Yang's birthday celebration.
Pardon?
To prepare for the upcoming proclamation ceremony,
I wanted to introduce Prince Seon Yang to him.
And you could not wait to run to the palace?
Wait... t-the thing is, I...
You should have told me about it.
I am Prince Seon Yang's maternal grandfather.
Why would you hide that from me—
Prince Seon Yang is my son first and your grandson second.
What is this?
Cheon is looking for his late business partner's daughter.
I thought he had quit a few years ago, but he seems to be looking again.
That will not bring the dead back to life.
Just leave him be.
Your Majesty, Cheon has grown exceedingly powerful.
What else can I do?
Years of famine have lasted.
It is difficult to run the country without his money.
If you allow me,
I will teach him the authority of the royal family and the power
of government officials clearly, Your Majesty.
When we ate in front of Master Cheon,
I could not tell if the food was going into my mouth or nose.
Eat slowly. You will get indigestion.
It is all right. My stomach is bigger than you think.
By the way, Hong Deok Su,
when is your mother coming?
She will probably come as soon as she hears about it.
Should we all say hello to her?
Yes, that sounds good.
Lee Eun Ho, why are you not eating?
He was sick yesterday.
Did your temperature go down?
I was not sick at all.
- Hong Deok Su.
- Yes?
I need to tell you something. Please set some time aside.
What is it? Tell me now.
Later.
I need to tell you privately.
All right, then.
I will get going now.
I am done, too. Let me come with you.
Hey, hey! Stay seated.
What is with you?
Lee Eun Ho,
I would like to consult you on something.
What? A love confession?
Be quiet. People can hear you.
Are you out of your mind?
What love confession?
You cannot do it.
There is a woman I like.
I fell for her at first sight.
You fell for a woman...
at first sight?
I have never felt this way in my life.
Jun Hwa, you said...
so...
you are in love with a woman, right?
Hey, stop that!
You are embarrassing me.
Is that so?
A woman?
Lee Eun Ho,
please help me figure out how to tell her.
You came to the right place.
I am essentially an expert in that field.
I am glad to hear that.
To confess love to a woman,
you need to speak smoothly.
You need to compliment her with sweet words first.
How?
Listen.
If being beautiful was a sin,
three generations of your family will have to be executed.
- What?
- Repeat after me.
"If being beautiful was a sin..."
This really works?
- Have you ever courted a woman?
- Of course.
You would be shocked to see how many women I have back in my house.
Do you not believe me?
I mean...
How about...
a more detailed advice?
Describe the woman to me first.
When we first met, she scammed me.
Scam?
I am Hong Deok Su. Five tenths.
The first encounter was rather harsh.
Although it was not easy afterward, either.
More than anything,
her smile was definitely the loveliest part.
Look at this!
I like your smile.
Please keep smiling like that...
and stay by my side.
I like that.
What? What did you say?
Thank you, Lee Eun Ho.
I will treat you properly if my confession goes well.
Thank you.
Why did I think of that Hong Deok Su rogue?
Wake up, Lee Eun.
He is nothing but the golden key.
Why are you waving your hand?
Is it dusty?
I dusted myself off before coming in.
Where are you going?
My family is coming today. We are staying in Geumokdang together.
Lee Eun Ho. Hey.
What? Yes.
Why are you zoning out?
Are you still sick?
Why do you keep...
No, you can go.
I am leaving now.
No.
This is not right.
Goodness...
Are you feeling ill?
You do not look well at all.
My chest feels a bit stuffy.
Are you having indigestion?
I have a medicine that works well.
Sharing delicious food helps you digest.
You ate all the soup alone last time, too.
It haunts me that I never got to try Hong Deok Su's mother's soup.
Do not even bring him up!
Did he do something?
Let me teach him a thing or two—
I told you to stop, did I not?
You really do not listen.
Follow me.
Hey. Even the King would live here.
I know!
Mother, how is the air up there?
I am dizzy.
Be careful. Be careful.
This is Yongcheonru, which I have only heard about.
It is incredibly flashy.
Hey, when is Deok Su coming?
I will go get him.
You should wait inside.
Hey, hey. You cannot just walk around here.
I want to check things out.
Yes, yes.
Goodness...
This way.
This is the late Hong Min Shik's residence?
Yes.
He lived here with his only daughter.
What happened twelve years ago?
Cheon's business partner, Hong Min Shik, died
and his daughter went missing?
He created a poster to look for her. There must be a reason.
Cheon is looking for the other half of the golden key he lost.
Not the late business partner's daughter.
He must be looking for the other half of the key she disappeared with.
If so, what is the golden key Hong Deok Su has?
My late father willed it to me.
It is the only thing he left behind in this world.
He only had one daughter?
Hong Jae On.
Hong Deok Su.
Hey.
I would like to talk to you.
Right now?
I need to go in now.
It will only take a moment.
Good.
I did not notice while I was working,
but it looks so pretty looking at it like this now.
What did you want to tell me?
I... I need to make a confession to you.
Confession?
Did you do something you are sorry for?
Confession, my foot.
I forgive you for everything.
So...
If being beautiful was a sin,
three generations of your family will have to be executed.
Hong Deok Su, three generations of your family will be executed.
What?
Well, the thing is...
I like your smile.
Please keep smiling like that and stay by my side.
Your smile...
It will get three generations of your family killed.
That is not it.
Did you eat something funny?
Are you sick, too?
Do you... Do you have a fever?
Hong Deok Su,
would you go to the Summer Palace with me this summer?
The Summer Palace?
Later, I mean.
I would like to go to the Summer Palace with you someday.
Would you come with me?
There is a woman I like.
I fell for her at first sight.
More than anything,
her smile was definitely the loveliest part.
Hong Deok Su...
is a woman?
♫  The round moonlight has suddenly  ♫
I heard you were looking for some woman.
Should I look into her for you?
It is none of your business.
You are old enough to wed. You must be interested in women now.
Hong Deok Su, you should live as a woman now.
Does love make your heart pound and feel tingly?
You scared me!
I came to ask you something.
By chance, are you...
I am Hong Deok Su's best friend at Yongcheonru.
You need to trust only me.
Do not be silly, Cheon Jun Hwa.
You need to go far away from Yongcheonru immediately.
It is not too late to leave with Hong Deok Su,
Prince Mu Yeong.
Why are you...
Deok Su! Deok Su!
Are you Hong Deok Su's mother?
What a cheeky bastard.
So it was you.