What do we do now?
Are you all dressed?
I— I am almost done.
I said I would help you put it on. Why are you being so stubborn?
We are in a hurry.
Men and women need to be separated. We cannot do that.
Hurry up.
The Lord will come out soon.
Yes, ma'am.
Walk across the courtyard and go to the door.
And run without looking back at Jakyakjae immediately.
The stepping stone is shaky. Secure it.
Hong Deok Su...
Where do you think you are going?
Are there any issues?
The Lord is inside. Where are you going?
My apologies.
She is the present we prepared for the Lord.
That is the wrong way. Follow me.
Yes.
A present for the Lord?
Did she call Hong Deok Su a present just now?
That is what I heard, too.
The Lord hates waiting. I will go in now.
Strengthen the security here.
Lee Eun Ho.
Lee Eun Ho, where are you going?
Hey.
The Master Innkeeper and Master Cheon are here, too.
I scored. I scored big time.
My apologies.
It sounds noisy inside. I will go in and see.
Hong Deok Su...
Where on earth are you?
The Bottom-Tier Room bastards.
I will definitely send you home this time.
Hey, stop.
Are you the apprentices of Gyohwadang?
Bow down.
Someone was dragged in over there.
I need to hurry. Please do not stop me.
Are you bastards trying to go in there?
What did you say?
- Hey, Lee Eun Ho.
- What are you doing?
Yongcheonru provides anything the guests want. Do you not know?
I know you are a merchant, but how could you sell a person?
Merchant?
My apologies, Master Cheon.
We are taking too much of your time.
Have you already forgotten why you came here?
If you did, ask yourself again...
why you came here.
Master Innkeeper, the Lord is—
I think we should...
greet each other after he sees the present.
All right, then...
Lord, the present from Yongcheonru is here.
Would you like to see it now?
Let us go in.
Just do as you are told.
Once we go over this fence,
no one can save us from what happens next.
But we cannot let the perverted man have Hong Deok Su.
It would be fine, right?
Even Master Cheon came.
That is why I need to come, too.
We are true men of the Bottom-Tier Room, are we not?
Yes.
Let us go.
Right now?
Take the covering off and put it aside.
Hey, hey! Look!
Aigoo...
True man, my foot.
Gosh. Be careful.
He wants you to lift up the skirt and turn around.
Lift it higher!
Take off the socks you are wearing.
Pardon?
Show him your undershirt next.
Will you make me repeat myself?
Take it off quickly.
Take it off right now!
I cannot do this.
- Even the Lord—
- What did you say?
Stop this right now!
Who are you?
Cheon Jun Hwa and Go Su Ra?
What is this now?
Do you think you could get away with this?
How dare you come in here?
Yongcheonru did something terrible to the Lord.
What should I do?
- Should I ask His Excellency back home for forgiveness?
- Pardon?
He forbade her to be near men before marriage.
But we could not stop three men from coming in.
You and I will have to put our lives on the line for it.
Master Innkeeper...
Lord?
Get her out of here. These were the clothes I was going to wear.
But you made them dirty and caused a scene.
It has no value anymore.
You cannot come out. Please go in.
You cannot show your face—
It was not a perverted old man?
Everyone, leave!
Do you know what you ruined?
She is the most important guest of Yongcheonru.
You ruined our presentation of clothes for her.
Our apologies, Master Innkeeper.
We heard the perverted old man gets furious at male innkeepers.
So, did you think you could save Hong Deok Su
by climbing this fence and eavesdropping?
Did you not think your actions would put him in greater danger?
Even an important guest should not slap someone like that.
If you want to change Yongcheonru,
become the owner of it.
All of you must have come here to achieve something.
Try to acquire power first.
Anger without power is completely useless.
Hong Deok Su, the Master Innkeeper saved our lives.
Not just us but everyone from the Bottom-Tier Room.
Yes.
Do not forget the favor and be thankful to her.
Yes, ma'am.
I heard Do Gyeong went to Yongcheonru again.
She should be receiving bridal lessons at home.
Is she hiding honey at Yongcheonru or something?
That way, she will be more obedient.
She cannot go outside of Yongcheonru, anyway.
What if she meets a man in Yongcheonru?
Do not worry.
A strict bodyguard is right beside her,
so no men can be near her.
Knowing her, Do Gyeong will definitely cause trouble.
You think she would just listen to us?
You are way too kind.
You are too much of a softie.
Do Gyeong inherited a fortune since my brother passed.
I should pretend to be nice to her until I get that money.
She spends money like it is water already.
How will we end up with any money?
I think we should get her married sooner.
We cannot wait until Prince Mu Yeong returns from Onyang.
- Should I tell her to marry now?
- What?
That is a good idea.
If we marry Prince Mu Yeong to Do Gyeong,
we will remove a huge obstacle for the proclamation ceremony.
Aigoo! I knew it. You are the best, dear husband!
How come you are so clever?
You do not understand my deep intentions.
I did not come this far for no reason.
He forbade her to be near men before marriage.
But we could not stop three men from coming in.
You and I will have to put our lives on the line for it.
Master Innkeeper saved our lives.
Goodness, I cannot believe I let you see me in a dress.
Aigoo...
Thank you for earlier, Lee Eun Ho.
I told you not to behave so rashly.
You dressed like a woman to cause trouble now.
That is why you got slapped on your ugly face.
What did you say?
What?
Rub it on your face. You will feel better.
If you put ice on a swollen area—
I will go for a night walk.
Where are you going?
Try applying ice where you got slapped...
He needs to use it before it melts.
Is something going on between you and Hong Deok Su?
Nothing is going on.
You grabbed each other by the collars on day one.
You fought like cats and dogs whenever you saw each other.
And you climbed over the fence without hesitation when he was in danger?
Yet you still say nothing is going on?
I just tried to protect what I was supposed to.
Right.
What did you try to protect?
The same thing you tried to protect tonight.
How nice!
- Kim Myeong Ho, you did that on purpose, did you not?
- What did I do?
We are in this mess because you lied to Deok Su.
What? Did something happen in there?
Something entertaining must have happened.
If you get caught scheming again,
I swear I will not let it slide, then.
My precious book.
Well...
How nice.
Seriously. What a weirdo.
Oh, hello, sir.
Is Apprentice Lee Eun Ho inside?
Master Cheon wants to see you.
Go see him now.
Welcome, Prince Mu Yeong.
No, should I call you Apprentice Number 28?
What is all this?
How dare you...
Who do you think you are?
Even a fox acts like a king in his cave.
Yongcheonru is my house. So, I am the king here.
How dare you?
My apologies!
I had you reside in this humble Yongcheonru, and I have not greeted you properly.
So, I prepared the royal meal you used to eat in the palace.
Please have a seat.
You prepared this spread for me.
I will accept it.
So, did you achieve your goal here?
I am not sure.
I achieved half and...
I am sure I will achieve the other half as well.
You already achieved half while at Gyohwadang?
You are truly impressive.
If so, when do you think you will achieve the other half?
For the other half,
I will need to lend your hand.
Of course, Your Highness.
Ask me anything. There are plenty of gold bars.
I am learning a lot since I came to Yongcheonru.
My goodness.
I am so glad I was able to help you.
You could easily become an official innkeeper at this rate.
I hear the last test is coming up.
You must not be worried since you will pass easily.
Of course.
I will make sure to pass and achieve my goal.
His Majesty must be so proud.
There was an accident at Jakyakjae?
Innkeeper Ji could not have done that.
My apologies, Master Innkeeper.
It is impossible to stop those troublemakers.
Was it the However Quartet again?
Oh my...
They upset the favorite niece of the Minister of Defense.
What do we do, Master Innkeeper?
To comfort an angry cat,
you should give it something to play with.
The Hosting Department is in charge of the last test, right?
Pardon?
This is finally the last group test.
Here is the Head Host, Yu Su In, the flower of Yongcheonru.
There is a reason why the Hosting Department's test is the last one.
Ta-da! What do you think?
Is it not splendid?
You will officially become innkeepers if you pass this test.
Only one group that provided the best service patiently until the end
will receive the certificate directly from the guest.
You will have to steal the guest's heart, no matter what.
Here are the things you need to remember for the guest:
One. Never look at the guest's face.
Two. Come in one person at a time when serving him.
- Three...
- Who is it, anyway?
He said it was an important guest. Are you deaf?
Shut up.
Four. Never say the word "no."
Five...
Thank you for agreeing to assess the test despite the inconvenience.
Perhaps you could use this opportunity to teach them a lesson.
Teach them a lesson?
Things are getting fun, thanks to you.
The apprentices are male.
What if His Excellency finds out—
It is a request from the Master Innkeeper of Yongcheonru.
It is your request. Of course, I will do it properly.
You said the apprentices are arriving soon, right?
I am screwed...
It had to be the guest from yesterday.
As for the face-washing water, boil it for half an hour,
cool it for 15 minutes, and bring it.
This is our last test. We cannot give up.
Of course not. We are from the Bottom-Tier Room.
You are spitting. Come on.
We boiled it for half an hour and cooled it for 15 minutes.
This must be the right temperature, right?
Good job, Go Su Ra.
By the way, who is going to carry it?
- I will try first.
- No.
- Why not?
- The way you speak is no good.
What is wrong with the way I speak?
Do I not talk the same way... as you?
And not to mention what happened yesterday.
No, let me—
I will bring it.
The Bottom-Tier Room needs to pass.
Stand tall, Go Su Ra.
- Let us go!
- Stand tall!
The water is too cold.
Do you want me to freeze to death?
The water is too hot.
Do you want me to get burned?
How dare you put sesame seeds on it?
My parrot is a picky eater.
He should only be fed freshly picked fruits.
Parrot?
- That is it!
- We did it.
Great.
The Top-Tier Room passes.
What is with this bedding?
I said the pillow's height cannot exceed four chon and two pun.
(T/N: 5 inches or 12.7 cm)
What would it take for her to let us pass?
It is not going to happen.
Eat.
Yes, let us eat first.
Let us eat and try it again.
Yes. Well...
Let us eat.
What happened when you went to pick up the snacks yesterday?
Leave while I am giving you a pass.
Hong Deok Su...
are we not all suffering because of you?
Kim Myeong Ho, you really are trash, are you not?
You are the one who lied.
No, you are a fool for falling for it.
What is the problem? What?
What?
Hold on.
You came back late from Jakyakjae yesterday because...
Tell me.
What? Tell me!
What—
What are you so curious about?
Let me tell you everything.
Never mind.
Let go of me.
All right.
Let me hear the details later.
Go Su Ra,
you must be happy because you have friends for once.
You look very happy these days.
Hey, Kim Myeong Ho!
You must be plotting something again.
Just leave our Bottom-Tier Room alone.
"Our Bottom-Tier Room"?
It is strange that you climbed Jakyakjae's fence yesterday,
yet you came back safely.
Are you admitting that you lied now, Kim Myeong Ho?
It is suspicious.
You must have a secret, do you not?
Why?
Are you curious?
You will never know because you have no friends.
By chance, is the secret...
regarding Hong Deok Su?
What about him?
It is nothing. There are just too many suspicious things.
Go Su Ra...
think carefully.
Parrot, I hope your owner forgives me.
Our Bottom-Tier Room really needs to pass.
Please take pity on me.
You are a bird, but you will never fly.
I feel sorry for you, too.
Stay away.
What is wrong, My Lady?
There is nothing I like about you.
This fruit is no good.
Go get something fresher.
Yes.
I told the wife of the Minister of Defense that you were here,
and she was not happy about it.
I will manage.
Where did the parrot go?
He flew very well.
Pardon?
By chance, did you...
No, right?
You go find him.
My Lady!
Why are you doing this?
If you cannot find him, Yongcheonru will pay for it.
- However—
- Leave.
Parrot! Parrot!
Parrot!
- Parrot!
- Shit...
How does this make sense?
She let the bird go. How are we supposed to find him?
- Parrot!
Parrot!
Gosh, where is he? How can we find him?
Are you already tired, Hong Deok Su?
What do you mean, tired?
Let us hang in there until we find him!
If you think about it, this is good for the parrot.
He gets to make new friends, too.
He has been trapped in the cage all this time.
He must be happy being free outside.
It has a dragon carved on it.
I am sure these swords were only given to the princes.
Are you recovering from the cold?
What brings you all the way here, Minister?
Discard the medicine given by Cheon.
This is ginseng all the way from Taebaek.
This will help you recover.
I did not expect you to care for me.
Thank you.
Who will do it if not me?
Are you looking for something?
I am not.
Do you practice swordcraft these days?
I have not because no one would sharpen the sword for me.
Pardon?
I can help with that.
Then...
I will leave it in your care.
Could you teach me swordcraft when you get a chance?
Yes.
Of course!
The Minister of Defense is behaving worse and worse.
If his niece and Prince Mu Yeong get married,
Prince Seon Yang will be chosen as the crown prince, right?
Yes.
Is that why you sent the gold bars to the Minister of Defense?
I should act ahead of time
as the Master Innkeeper without detailed instructions.
It is better to be safe than sorry.
Not having enemies on any side
is the secret of tightrope walking.
The Minister of Defense will not just wait.
He will find Prince Mu Yeong somehow.
Everyone is acting unruly, but they are
all my pawns, after all.
Is this supposed to be my parrot?
I will look for him even if I have to stay up all night.
I want this to comfort you in the meantime.
I thought the parrot would feel less lonely if he had a friend.
My Lady, would you like to see something interesting?
All right.
This is a game called Ssangpae.
My Lady, would you like to play a bet against me?
A bet?
The loser grants the winner's wish.
Are you trying to get a passing grade from me?
We would love to pass, of course.
However... that is not the reason this time.
How about you go for a night outing with me if I win?
Why would I go for an outing with you?
You might run into the parrot, who might be enjoying the world.
You can win if you do not want to go out.
Two nyang.
Take two nyang and bet four more nyang.
Forget this.
Hey, hey, hey!
- Yes, Hyeongnim.
Have you seen Hong Deok Su taking a bath?
We take baths here. We would not know.
Sang Wu, how about you?
I guess I have never seen it.
He refused to take his top off when we told him to, right?
I guess so.
Was that woman really...
Gosh...
Yes, it was definitely Hong Deok Su.
We will know once we see him, right?
Well...
All right, that was just a practice.
How fascinating! Who taught you these skills?
My Lady, this is Seol Mae Hwa.
What are you doing here at this hour, Master Innkeeper?
I heard your rare laughter outside.
You must be playing a fun game.
Would you like to try it, too?
He plays unbelievable tricks.
Were you entertaining our guest?
Yes, Master Innkeeper.
It is all right. Go ahead and toss.
It is Ssangpae, is it not?
Do you know this game, too, Mae Hwa?
Of course. A long time ago—
Go ahead and toss again.
Yes.
Brace yourself, My Lady.
I will make sure to win.
You have to grant my wish since I won.
You must be having fun.
I will keep this a secret since this is your last day.
Last day?
The minister sent someone.
They will take you to Onyang early tomorrow morning.
Onyang? Why would I go there?
Prince Mu Yeong is in Onyang.
His Excellency wanted you to see him in person.
All right. You may leave now.
I will make sure to win.
Now, if you want to win a bet,
just switch to a game you are better at.
Like this?
It cannot be.
Hong Deok Su!
I will grant your wish tonight since you won.
So, you are all ready, right?
My Lady?
First of all, we will split into three groups.
My Lady, please stop!
Stop!
Go Su Ra, you will be the decoy.
Do I have to dress as a woman?
My apologies. I thought this was a different palanquin.
While the bodyguard is chasing Su Ra's palanquin,
we will climb the fence and go to the lake.
Before the Lady arrives, Lee Eun Ho, you need to
finish preparing for the perfect outing.
Everything is clear, right?
Move, move, move! Move, I said!
They are finally causing trouble.
It was worth keeping an eye on them.
Should we tell the Head Manager right now?
Yes, and I will tell Seong Jin seonbaenim myself.
Bottom-Tier Room, you are done for now.
Who goes there?
I will distract them. Go without me.
No, it will be easy to trick them because I have a similar build.
Make sure she gets to the lake safely, Jun Hwa.
That way!
Over here!
Let us go.
Why are they taking so long?
Lee Eun Ho!
What?
Are they not here yet?
What are you talking about?
You said you and Jun Hwa would bring her.
The thing is, I got caught while climbing the fence.
We split up there so we would not get caught.
Gosh, I am tired.
I barely managed to lose them.
But why are they not here? It is about time.
I suppose that was a good workout. I am hungry.
Pumpkin yeot.
Gosh, Lee Eun Ho!
How did you know I like pumpkin yeot?
I must be too hungry.
My hands are shaking. My gosh.
No problem, there is more.
Thank you.
Hey!
This place is amazing.
The stars are pretty, and the fireflies are pretty, too.
Wait quietly, please.
♫  A trembling feeling for the first time  ♫
Should we catch fireflies and put them in the lantern?
I think she would like that.
Why would you bother?
♫  The noisy world becomes completely silent  ♫
Why the fireflies...
♫  And like warm sunlight, you come to me  ♫
♫  I started to wonder since when it began  ♫
♫  How do you think of me?  ♫
Look!
♫  Is your heart pounding like mine right now?  ♫
♫  The blooming flowers sing  ♫
♫  The blowing wind whispers  ♫
We got it.
Yes.
♫  You look at me  ♫
♫  And I bloom again as the person I used to be  ♫
♫  I bloom  ♫
Master Innkeeper, this is Seong Jin.
Come in.
Master Innkeeper, we have a situation.
You might want to go to Jakyakjae right now.
What a beautiful place.
Will I be able to see it again?
It is a whole new world if you take a step outside.
The door is open now.
You should take a new path, too, My Lady.
Which path will you take, then?
I hope you reach the world you want.
Thank you.
And do not look for Parrot anymore.
I got rid of the birdcage, too.
How about you, My Lady?
Let us go back now.
I will care for you from now on, My Lady.
What is going on?
If the Minister of Defense finds out about this,
I am as good as dead.
Do not worry.
Yongcheonru's head manager found her.
He will bring her here soon.
She can leave for Onyang tomorrow morning.
My Lady!
What is going on?
You scared me!
- And what are you wearing?
- Step aside.
Go inside now.
Just wait. I can go on my own.
My apologies, Head Manager.
My apprentices gave you such a hard time.
Gosh, I am so sick of you, the However Quartet.
Do you even know what you have done?
What should I do now, Master Innkeeper?
Hong Deok Su, it is you again.
Tell me. Why did you do such a thing?
It is...
all my fault.
I gave them the order.
I was told to give the certificate to the innkeepers who satisfied me.
So, I tested them.
I will make the final decision now.
Before you make the decision,
you should punish the Bottom-Tier Room for breaking the rule.
All they did was carry out my order.
Do not punish them, Master Innkeeper.
I will follow your order, My Lady.
I have been a bit too harsh.
You work hard all day and night. You are great innkeepers.
The Top-Tier Room passes for hosting well.
And the Bottom-Tier Room also passes for understanding me.
I decided to let both the Top-Tier Room and Bottom-Tier Room pass.
The Bottom-Tier Room cannot pass!
They do not even have the right to take the test.
So, they do not get to pass, either.
Kim Myeong Ho! W-What are you doing right now?
Hong Deok Su is...
a girl.
This girl dared to deceive Yongcheonru...
and took the Gyohwadang test.
She will have to be punished harshly.
Kim Myeong Ho, shut your mouth.
Hong Deok Su...
come clean in front of everyone!
♫  The round moonlight has suddenly  ♫
Wow, petals!
♫  But your heart won't change  ♫
♫  like the moon, will it?  ♫
From now on, you must live as a boy.
No one can find out you are Hong Jae On and a girl.
Do you understand?
♫  If you cannot come, then please call me instead  ♫
♫  And if you tell me your wish  ♫
♫  I'll fly, fluttering  ♫
♫  Following this longing to where you sleep  ♫
♫  Under the same sky, no matter where  ♫
♫  I'll go  ♫
♫  Like the wind, I'll soar  ♫
♫  When a gentle breeze blows through the clear sky  ♫
♫  Like our beautiful, transparent light  ♫
♫  Leaning on each other's shoulders  ♫
♫  With excitement-filled dreams  ♫
We need to find evidence that he is a girl.
The evidence no one can deny!
Kim Myeong Ho. I need to take revenge on them, too.
Did things not go as you planned?
You need to catch him red-handed so he cannot escape.
It is not over yet.
Trip.
Trip. Trip.
Oh my...
I guess he is not taking a bath.
Gross bastard.
Take a bath. You are dirty, all right?
I am going to the bathhouse. Will you come with me?
There is something I did not get to say.
What exactly is wrong with you?
You were worked up, unlike your usual self.
Hong Deok Su...
I said a scar is not a big deal for a man.
You do not have to try to hide it.