Cheon Jun Hwa.
Lee Eun Ho.
Go Su Ra.
Hong Deok Su.
Yes.
Move!
Move, move!
Who is Hong Deok Su?
Yes, I am Hong Deok Su.
You are under arrest for the murder of Kim Man Dol, known as the Seochon murder.
Pardon?
I-I am what?
- Tie him up.
- Yes.
No, I am not a murderer.
- Follow us!
- I am not.
- He said he is not.
- Step aside immediately.
There must be a misunderstanding.
What is going on?
What is this fuss about?
You are interrupting the Yongcheonru appointment ceremony.
It must be something very important, is it not?
We have been reported that a murder suspect is hiding in here.
Reported?
Take him away.
I am innocent.
Hong Deok Su, stay alert.
Nothing will happen.
I did not do it.
I did not do it!
All you are giving me is a red card thief?
If you catch the red card thief,
someone will run after him immediately.
The louder we shake the bait, the bigger fish we will catch.
You want me to catch the big fish that chases the bait?
Are you sure it will help Prince Seon Yang's proclamation?
I assure you, you will not be disappointed.
How dare they barge into my Yongcheonru?
It looks like the Investigation Bureau found the forger of the red card and evidence of the murder.
The Investigation Bureau?
It had to be the Minister of Defense.
The appointment ceremony was ruined because of Hong Deok Su.
How pathetic is this?
Aigoo, Hyeongnim. A murderer, they say.
He committed such a scary crime pretending to be perfectly normal?
I told you I found him suspicious from the beginning.
I do not know how such an evil man joined Yongcheonru.
Where is Lee Eun Ho?
Du Shik, do you know how many beatings a person can take before he dies?
Come on. It is not even a sword.
He will not die from being beaten with a club.
You stupid bastard.
If you pour water on the butt
and hit it just 30 times,
the flesh splits, and you die.
A club can do that to you.
You know that?
Aigoo, Hong Deok Su is a small man, too.
He will die like a frog if he is beaten only ten times.
What are you doing?
Well?
I was curious how many times a person needs to fall off a chair to die.
What?
That was the first one.
Lee Eun Ho.
Lee Eun Ho, are you coming, too?
Where are you going?
You mean the Investigation Bureau?
I need to see Hong Deok Su in person.
Go Su Ra, are you coming, too?
I am from the Bottom-tier Room, too. I cannot be excluded.
Mother! Mother!
Mother!
Something terrible happened!
Gosh, what happened?
The Investigation Bureau took Deok Su!
What?
W-What happened to our Deok Su?
Aigoo, aigoo, Deok Su!
Deok Su!
Mother!
- Move!
Deok Su! Deok Su!
Mother! Mother!
- Deok Su!
- Mother!
Deok Su! Deok Su!
- Deok Su!
- Mother!
What is going on?
Step aside!
Sir, he could never hurt anyone!
Mother, I did not kill him. It was not me!
What is going on, Deok Su?
Move!
Mother!
Mother! Mother!
Stay away from the culprit. Now!
You are mistaken. You got the wrong person!
What are you doing? Drag her out immediately!
Yes, sir!
Deok Su!
Mother! Mother!
Mother, are you all right?
Take the culprit away! Now!
If you catch the red card thief,
someone will run after him immediately.
The louder we shake the bait, the bigger fish we will catch.
I cannot believe this!
People really love to watch.
How vulgar.
What are you doing? Kick all of them out!
Yes.
Just leave them.
We need to interrogate him louder,
so people learn a lesson from him.
Are they interrogating him there?
They cannot ignore the procedure like this.
Something is strange.
Bring the evidence we found at the murder scene.
Yes, sir.
This is unjust.
I did not murder Kim Man Dol.
Shut up!
Did you not take this red card from him?
A witness saw you and Kim Man Dol fighting in Seochon.
The red card...
I will split it in half since you are all about fairness.
What do you think? Share it nicely and...
make sure to join Yongcheonru.
What are you doing?
Once it is ripped, the red card becomes invalid!
I am ruined...
That man was Kim Man Dol?
Did you not kill him with this sword?
I know nothing about it. It is not my sword.
You had better be honest.
He asked if I was practicing swordcraft these days.
He inquired about the dragon sword given to the princes,
so I showed him mine.
The Minister of Defense is attempting to slander you.
If it becomes known that you did not travel to Onyang,
he will seize the opportunity to use it against you.
The Minister of Defense. How dare you.
If this is not yours, who could this sword belong to?
How would I know that?
Is that so?
Let me see if you can endure being tortured and still insist.
Look here.
Yes.
There will be a hearing tomorrow.
Keep him imprisoned.
I will interrogate him harshly until he confesses.
I will carry out your order.
I really did not do it.
I did not do it!
Hold on.
I really did not do it.
I really did not do it!
When will the bait be taken?
I did not do it.
I did not kill anyone.
Please listen to me! Hello!
I did not kill him!
Look over here!
Hold on.
Let us talk about what we will do now.
Could Hong Deok Su have... really stolen the red card?
We need to rescue our friend first.
Hong Deok Su is not the culprit.
I need to go somewhere. Go back without me.
Lee Eun Ho!
Go Su Ra, I need to stop by somewhere, too.
Where are you going now?
We left without telling Gyohwadang.
Do not worry about me.
Hey, come on.
You bastards!
Who told you to loaf around like this?
This is all Hong Deok Su's fault.
- That is right.
- Be quiet.
By the way, where did the Bottom-Tier Room bastards go?
Did you not know?
They went out without permission. They should be dismissed immediately.
That is right.
Be quiet, you bastards. You bastards.
Go ahead and clean the bathhouse right now.
Why is it always us?
Shut your mouth!
Do you mean Hong Deok Su was imprisoned?
Yes.
The Minister of Defense was interrogating him personally.
How did the search of Master Cheon's residence go?
Here is the other half I found in his residence.
You found it.
Hand me the scroll.
Is something wrong?
No.
I can try to put the two pieces together now.
What is wrong?
By chance, are you worried about Hong Deok Su?
Why would I not be? He is my golden key.
I worked so hard to find it.
He always behaves rashly and causes trouble.
It is impossible to keep my eyes off of him.
He will be released soon if he is innocent.
There is no way he is the culprit.
There are too many suspicious things.
Let us go to the palace.
I need to look into something.
He caught the bait.
I am here.
You came.
Wow, is this the new safe you got?
Would you like to see it?
It is a golden key.
Are there two keys?
You need to put those two together to open this safe.
It is a fascinating object.
I am planning to give the other half to Jae On when she grows up.
You cannot fit much into the safe.
I am more than satisfied with its size.
Satisfied?
I am not.
Look, Min Shik—
Come on, are you talking about that again?
This is our chance to create a king with our money.
We can have power, too.
Power is just like a sword.
The closer you get to it, the more likely you will get hurt.
There is a way to fly further and higher.
Why do you insist on walking with your hands behind your back?
Listen, friend. Think of Jun Hwa and Jae On.
We need to leave behind a world worth living in for our children.
Keep looking everywhere.
I see right through what you do inside my house.
Please rescue Hong Deok Su.
There is no way he is the culprit.
They will torture him tomorrow. You need to save him before then.
Have you already been to the Investigation Bureau?
Hong Deok Su belongs to Yongcheonru now.
You even gave him a certificate.
You had no interest in Yongcheonru, yet you worry about its employee.
How interesting.
Yes, I will start being interested from now on.
So, please lend me some money.
I will visit the Minister of Defense and explain things or persuade him.
The Minister of Defense?
Did you think what he wanted was money?
I asked if the reason he imprisoned a lowly employee of Yongcheonru is
because of money.
What is more effective at persuading someone than money?
All right.
Do what you want to do.
However... why do I have to give you a loan to do that?
- That is because—
- If Hong Deok Su is that worthy for you,
you should resolve this yourself.
My apologies.
Master Cheon gave a strict order about it.
Goodness. He must be trying to train me.
How far are you...
willing to go for Hong Deok Su?
I will try anything until I save him.
I am willing to sell everything I own to save him.
Could you be on my side, Master Innkeeper?
I work for Master Cheon now.
I cannot go against his will.
I understand.
I will look for another way.
You probably cannot get a private loan, either.
Master Cheon banned you from getting any loans using your name badge.
That sword was indeed mine.
If so, the murderer's sword they found as evidence is...
Who dared to enter the palace and steal the sword?
I will summon the Royal Guards and the Chief Gatekeeper immediately.
There is no need.
The culprit intentionally left the sword at the murder scene, so they would go after me.
Who could have done that?
The Minister of Defense... visited Prince Eun Seong and checked his sword.
Those swords were only given to the princes.
Princes Eun Seong, Seon Yang,
and I have one.
The Minister of Defense must have set the trap aiming at me.
Why are you so startled?
This was not stolen, was it?
Look at me carefully.
I might have been robbed,
but I have never robbed anyone.
Do not even bother.
You cannot get a loan anywhere in the market today.
I swear it is not stolen.
Do not worry about it.
I did not want to say this, but...
I am Yongcheonru's—
I have no idea why,
but Yongcheonru ordered all the private loan businesses
and pawn shops to suspend any transactions today.
Gosh.
It is such a shame, but...
Take it back.
So, you do not want it?
You probably will not see this anywhere else.
This is expensive stuff.
Well, forget it if you do not want it.
Gosh, I wonder if there is a pawn shop owner who is not scared.
Is that it?
How could you not understand the value of this at all?
Do you think all of this is worth one silver nugget?
Look,
no one will pay you that much.
No one would make a transaction with you behind Yongcheonru.
No one but me.
Take it back if you do not want it.
I am afraid, too.
Gosh, seriously...
Go Su Ra,
why are you the only one working?
- My apologies.
- Aigoo...
Three are missing from the Bottom-Tier Room.
Are they not going too far?
I will clean four people's worth. Just leave it.
They always say you are their friend, but they make you clean alone.
What kind of friend is that? Right, Hyeongnim?
You bastards. Are you cleaning with your mouth?
Gosh... Finish it quickly and leave.
Gosh, what do I do?
Do not splash water.
Hey, Go Su Ra,
do they bully you by chance?
Damn.
Move so I can clean.
One was arrested by the Investigation Bureau for murder.
Two of them make you do all the work for them.
Who says Hong Deok Su killed someone?
The entire Yongcheonru knows about it. Are you the only one in the dark?
I do not believe in what other people say.
I believe what my friend said.
"I believe what my friend said."
Go Su Ra!
Namhae Merchant went out of business because you are this naive.
Come to your senses!
Find Hong Min Shik's daughter, Hong Jae On!
Yes, sir!
Plague!
You cannot enter.
They have the plague.
Mother!
What kind of nightmare are you having?
Gu Shil, let us go.
We need to see if Deok Su is doing okay.
Wait, Mother.
You cannot leave in your condition.
Who are you?
What is everyone doing?
You are...
the son of Yongcheonru's owner?
My name is Cheon Jun Hwa, Your Excellency.
You look nothing like your father.
Cheon sure has a nice-looking son.
I returned from the Qing dynasty recently.
I wanted to greet the well-regarded Minister of Defense.
Am I well-known in the Qing dynasty?
No wonder. I am His Majesty's father-in-law
and the maternal grandfather of Prince Seon Yang,
who will become the crown prince soon.
It is not polite to visit someone empty-handed.
You are young, but you understand the fundamentals.
It is everything I own.
Everything?
Yes, that is right.
Not all treasures come in big boxes.
The smaller, the finer it is.
So, what did you want to talk about?
A friend of mine was framed and imprisoned.
He was framed?
As long as I am the Minister of Defense,
I cannot allow such injustice.
You truly are as generous as I expected.
You are a rare, virtuous young fellow.
A silver nugget?
A silver nugget, not a gold bar?
Is this box a treasure from the Qing dynasty?
I do not have much now,
but I will give you anything you want from Yongcheonru.
Not much?
The arrested man is an innocent innkeeper.
Are you saying I persecuted an innocent citizen?
Go back. I will pretend this never happened.
I could imprison you for bribery,
but since I am an old friend of your father,
I will give you a pass this once.
Your Excellency.
What a fool.
Learn and come back when you are more mature.
No one uses everything they own to negotiate.
You still have a long way to go.
You need to use it sparingly.
How many times do you have to tell me?
I understand.
I said I will get you a new one.
It is a difficult ointment to get.
It is a cure-all.
Where did you get injured that you need the whole thing?
Let me apply it for you.
Seriously.
- Here he is.
- Deok Su. Deok Su.
Mother.
- You should not have come!
- Deok Su.
I brought her because she insisted on feeding you warm soup.
- Are you okay?
- How about you? Are you okay?
Sir, you probably could use this.
I will only give you a moment.
- Hurry, hurry.
- Thank you.
Aigoo, my baby.
Say ah. Ah!
Eat this and feel better.
I am sorry, Mother.
Did you do anything you owe me an apology for?
Tell me.
I...
played Ssangpae with Kim Man Dol.
That is how I won the red card.
Gosh, you bastard!
Do you not know how I raised you?
That was the only way to join Yongcheonru.
What is so great about Yongcheonru?
So, did he really die because of you?
It is not like that, Mother.
I did not kill him.
Aigoo. Gosh, how will you pay for this sin?
I will correct things, Mother.
I can straighten it out.
Someone from Yongcheonru paid me money today,
saying it was compensation for you.
What?
Someone paid you? Who?
Are you Hong Deok Su's mother?
Yes.
This is compensation for Hong Deok Su.
That person...
gave this to me.
I pretended not to know,
but I have been having nightmares.
I feel so anxious, Deok Su.
What does that person look like? Do you remember?
She did look like a noblewoman.
Noblewoman?
Was that person...
a woman?
Why? Is it someone you know?
Per your order, I blocked all the sources of funds in the capital,
but I suppose he ended up visiting the Minister of Defense.
Have you seen Jun Hwa doing this before, Mae Hwa?
He would not flinch even if I were dying.
I will tell him to be more careful.
Just leave him.
This is just the beginning.
When he gets tired of being unruly,
he will come back and surrender.
But...
the more important thing is...
that Hong Deok Su bastard.
The one who is making Jun Hwa do this.
There is definitely something about him.
He might be able to become wings for Jun Hwa, who has been asleep.
Seol Mae Hwa.
Did she pay for my life or something?
You should rest fully today.
Tomorrow will be a busy day.
I will repay you for what you did.
Gosh.
What is this?
Sir, please help me.
The soup I had earlier...
Come on, bastard!
Please spare me, sir. I am dying.
Please, sir. Please.
Let go of me, you bastard!
You dirty bastard.
A prisoner escaped! That way!
- Catch him!
Do not let him go!
Catch him!
Hong Deok Su escaped from jail.
I knew he was not easy, but...
What should we do?
I should go myself.
Stop!
You bastard!
Kneel immediately if you do not want to die.
Let go!
Take him away right now!
No, let go! Let go!
Let go!
Damn it.
What a fool.
Learn and come back when you are more mature.
No one uses everything they own to negotiate.
You still have a long way to go.
Do you still have anything left to sell?
Buy me, Master Cheon.
You do not know the worth of what you have.
You sold things for cheap at random places.
If you sell yourself now, will you not regret it?
I must be worth as much as Yongcheonru.
Are you doing this just to save Hong Deok Su?
Hong Deok Su is my friend, Father.
Friend?
Friend.
I had an invaluable friend once, too.
You are kneeling as you promise me to follow my path.
So, I will tell you.
You cannot spend on someone weak and useless.
That is the first thing you need to learn to follow my path.
Two.
In negotiations, what the other person wants
is more important than what you have.
But you did not even know what the Minister of Defense wanted.
You messed up from the beginning.
Do you understand?
I will keep that in mind.
But Hong Deok Su will be like Seol Mae Hwa to me.
He is necessary for me to follow your path.
The Master Innkeeper is not your friend.
She is someone below you whom you manage.
Yes.
Then, save the person who will work under me.
Fine.
You sold yourself for Hong Deok Su.
I will let you have that much.
Hong Deok Su...
Hong Deok Su!
You are suddenly torturing the prisoner?
Why would you bother doing that?
That bastard got caught trying to escape last night.
I have to bring out the club myself.
Just make an officer do it.
Why would you do something so rough?
This is all a part of a game.
You should relax and prepare for Prince Seon Yang's proclamation.
Why would you dirty your hands before the happy occasion?
Last night, the only son of Yongcheonru's Cheon
caught the bait.
Pardon? Master Cheon's son?
If I find out Cheon's weakness,
it would help Prince Seon Yang's proclamation ceremony.
But, still!
Only one silver nugget in the box? That makes no sense.
Gosh, I am angry.
Gosh, why do you not just relax today?
No, I need to shake the bait harder to catch a big fish.
Your Excellency, Yongcheonru sent a present!
Is that so?
Come on in.
Gosh, why is the present so tiny?
What is this?
It is the box the son brought the silver nugget in.
Cheon, this fellow knows something.
This is like rhyme in poetry.
He apologizes for his son's mistake in the same way.
I will happily accept it.
Yongcheonru's Master Cheon must have finally decided to submit to you.
It is hefty.
It is different. Very different.
Why are you shaking that?
What if it is fragile?
What?
What is this?
Your Excellency, someone from the Investigation Bureau is looking for you.
It is a peach tree branch.
It protects you from ghosts and nightmares.
Lee Eun Ho.
Who is here, anyway? What?
Long time no see, Minister.
P-Prince Mu Yeong.
I heard you have been looking for me.
I came in a hurry because I had to talk to you in person.
Gosh, I heard you were recuperating in Onyang.
Are you feeling better now?
I was waiting for you and thought I would not get to see you before I died.
Release the innocent man you arrested because of me.
Am I not the one you are after?
I know it is your order, but...
I cannot get involved in the Investigation Bureau's officers' business.
The 10th birthday of Prince Seon Yang is coming up soon.
With his upcoming crown prince proclamation ceremony, which is an important event,
an innocent citizen should not shed blood.
That is...
true.
If so, can the...
proclamation ceremony happen soon without a hitch?
I will help with that.
Whoever takes the throne
should look after the people with virtue and justice.
I have no reason not to help my younger brother as long as he becomes a sage king.
That sounds great.
I will release Yongcheonru's innkeeper since you vouch for him.
However...
I will keep investigating the murder and catch the culprit.
The man who was slain with a sword was a citizen of Joseon.
Prisoner Hong Deok Su!
Yes.
Come out.
Pardon?
Get out of here.
What is going on?
Why are you suddenly letting me go?
How would I know? Get lost.
I made this clear, but I am against it.
Hong Deok Su is an innocent man.
He just got caught in the trap the Minister of Defense set for me.
I am against it because you are jumping in, knowing it is a trap.
Would you do the same if I were imprisoned, too?
You should be punished if you commit a crime.
And he is not the same as you.
How am I different from him?
I am disappointed.
You worried about Hong Deok Su all night.
Me? About Hong Deok Su?
You were worried about him.
That is why you took my ointment, too.
Do you not pity the man?
How could a person not have empathy?
I did not know you were so cold-hearted, Beom Ho.
Me?
A sage ruler must pity someone who has been wronged.
You act strangely whenever we talk about Hong Deok Su.
The golden key!
Hong Deok Su is my golden key.
I did not forget my goal.
I found the other half.
Once I put them together, it would all be over.
You did not compliment me at all when I found the other half.
Let us go.
How could you be like this?
Why are you so cold to me?
- Why?
- Gosh.
Cheon, are you out of your mind?
You ask me to release a murderer by sending me this?
Are you and your son mocking me together?
Goodness.
Was this not enough?
What is that?
If you do not know, it is probably better not to know.
I will take it back since you do not want it.
I mean...
you should have told me what the present was first.
Will you release Yongcheonru's innkeeper?
The thing is...
- He is gone.
- Pardon?
It is too late.
Someone came before you and had me release Hong Deok Su.
Who was that?
I will tell you if you give me this present back.
No need for that.
I will find out eventually if I am meant to know.
Well, then...
The Investigation Bureau suddenly released him.
Find him.
Yes, madam.
Move.
What brings you here so late, Master Innkeeper?
A lot has happened at Gyohwadang this year.
Yes. They were unusually strange kids.
You did a lot, Instructor Bang.
But we should clean things up now.
I want you to expel Hong Deok Su.
Pardon?
- Master Innkeeper, there is—
- Come back tomorrow.
You can report to me tomorrow.
Where have you been all day?
I waited for you for a long time.
What brings you here?
Hong Deok Su,
you show up here after causing a scene at the Investigation Bureau?
I am sorry for disturbing you.
He wanted to see you so badly. So, I brought him here.
What reason would I have to see him?
I had to let you know I was back.
Hong Deok Su has been expelled already.
He was arrested for a murder charge.
He might not be the culprit,
but he has no right to be here for forging the red card alone.
I am here to...
beg you for a chance to prove myself.
Put the expulsion on hold.
Master Cheon, to the other innkeepers...
This will set an example.
It will prove whether Yongcheonru cares about people or not.
Prove yourself as you said you would.
Yes, I will.
Once you achieve what you promised, I will reinstate you then.
That should be fine, right?
You should not have returned to Yongcheonru.
Why should I not?
I worked so hard to come this far.
You must have a lot to say to me.
No matter what anyone says,
I came this far on my own.
There is nothing I cannot do.
I came back alive from jail, too.
Hong Deok Su, you—
The person who reported me to the Investigation Bureau and framed me.
I know who it was.
I will never...
run away like a coward.
Hong Deok Su...
Hong Deok Su!
Do not go.
♫  I can't hide this trembling heart  ♫
♫  Like a child I find myself chasing after you  ♫
♫  When your hand comes close to mine  ♫
♫  Without realizing it I want to  ♫
♫  Hold you completely in my arms right now  ♫
♫  Walk with me  ♫
♫  Listen to my story slowly  ♫
♫  The more I hope to reach you  ♫
♫  The smaller I become unable to see you  ♫
♫  The more I try to hide it  ♫
♫  The bigger this heart grows  ♫
♫  I want to tell you looking into your eyes right now  ♫
♫  The flowing river speaks no words  ♫
Master Cheon will soon realize the golden key is gone.
You must make your move before that.
Hong Deok Su finally managed to come back.
This is the last chance for me.
Do you think you can catch me?
This gambling house needs to become a success.
Find another way.
I will not ask you all to help me.
This is something I need to take care of.
Would you ignore me if I were in your situation?
Are we not friends?
- You like Hong Deok Su, do you not?
- What?
Jun Hwa prepared all this for you, Deok Su.
Cheon Jun Hwa.
Why are you still at Yongcheonru?
This is not my place, but...
I know why I came here, hiding my identity.
You are very interested in the gambling house, considering you were against it.
Lee Eun Ho, where are you from?
Regarding the Bottom-Tier Room kids you call friends.
You are the one who pushed me this far.
How much do you know?
I know my friends well.
You know nothing at all.
Whatever it is, please tell me.