[Better Halves]
[Episode 9]
Hurry up! Let's go see.
Let's go take a look.
What did I tell you?
Xu Ao keeps getting promoted,
Ms. Liu certainly
didn't marry the wrong man.
♪ In this chaotic world, because of you ♪
♪ It's filled with wonder ♪
♪ Only you make me unafraid to give ♪
♪ A vow of life and death to live ♪
Ke, you...
♪ I'll promise you verses ♪
I have something to do. I'll go first.
♪ And all I want you in return ♪
Aren't you coming for the food?
♪ Who cares
who the martial legends may be too? ♪
No, I'm not going.
Let's go.
Let's join the crowd.
What is it this time?
Lord Xu is truly a good official.
[Be Kind and Benevolent]
By the mandate of heaven,
the Emperor decrees:
Vice Commander
of the Imperial Cavalry, Xu Ao,
brave and resolute, has faithfully
carried out imperial orders.
He's loyal, filial, sincere,
diligent and respectful,
who has pleased me greatly,
and is hereby promoted to
Commander of the Imperial Cavalry Bureau.
[Xu Ao, Vice Commander
of the Imperial Cavalry]
May you uphold the tradition of integrity,
[Liu Yingying, Mrs. Xu]
fulfill your aspirations,
loyally protect the nation,
and safeguard the capital.
By imperial decree.
Thank you for Your Majesty's great favor.
Lord Xu, congratulations
on your promotion.
From now on, you'll be
a close minister to the Emperor
and His Majesty's right hand.
Congratulations, Madam.
The imperial edict shall soon arrive,
naming you an honored lady
and bringing great honor to your kin.
Thank you, Sir.
Please accept this small gift.
The Xu family is deeply grateful.
Thank you, Madam.
Lord Xu, you're truly blessed.
Mrs. Xu is known throughout the capital
for her virtue and grace.
Meeting her today,
I see her reputation is well-deserved.
Mr. Li, you flatter her.
Indeed, that's too much praise.
Those words of virtue and grace
are more than I deserve.
This way, Mr. Li.
Darling, please wait.
Madam, what is it?
I've asked the Official Matchmaking Agency
for a divorce.
From now on, we'll part ways
and leave each other alone.
Madam,
why are you doing this?
My mind is made up.
Don't ask any more questions.
I don't agree to this.
Your agreement isn't necessary.
[Official Matchmaking Agency]
Marry Hua Yuerong into the Xu family
[Information Card]
and pair her with Xu Ao.
But...
But Xu Ao already has a legal wife
and he's just been promoted to Commander,
I'm afraid...
Are you questioning the Lord Marquis?
I wouldn't dare.
Hua Yuerong is
the Lord Marquis's sworn sister,
and isn't Liu Yingying
already demanding a divorce?
Forgive my ignorance.
The Lord Marquis's plan is brilliant.
Once Xu Ao gets divorced,
it will confirm that
the No.1 matchmaker in the world
has made ill-fated pairings.
Then we can marry
Hua Yuerong into the Xu family.
This will perfectly help the Lord Marquis
achieve his grand ambition.
Now that you know
go handle it immediately.
Yes, My Lord.
[A Perfect Match]
Let me tell you all,
you need to pay more attention
to that matchmaking case.
Yes.
Ke.
Where were you yesterday?
Do you know why we've been
urgently summoned?
I've been cultivating myself
at home lately.
I have no idea what's happening.
But
seeing how happy Ms. Deng looks,
it must be good news.
Maybe they want to reward you.
After all, you managed to
marry off even Shen Tongyun,
which was one of
the three most difficult matchmaking cases
in the capital.
Exactly.
Yes.
That's possible.
If I receive a matchmaking bonus,
I'll treat everyone to dinner.
Great!
Wonderful!
Quiet down,
stop guessing.
Today there is indeed a major case.
However, this case
can only be handled by the successor
of the No.1 matchmaker in the world.
Shi Fa'ke, step forward.
Ms. Deng, I wonder what case
you want to reward me with.
Rest assured,
whatever task you assign me,
I'll definitely handle it well.
[Divorce Agreement]
The divorce case
of Liu Yingying and Xu Ao.
What?
Divorce?
Who did you say wants to divorce?
You heard correctly.
Liu Yingying wants to divorce Xu Ao.
Weren't you always clamoring
to take cases
from the Official Matchmaking Agency?
This is a failed match
arranged by your mother,
so please hurry up and fix it.
That's impossible!
My mother has arranged
countless marriages.
She's never had a failed match.
It doesn't matter if she hasn't,
isn't there one right now?
Look carefully,
this is Liu Yingying's own fingerprint.
[Divorce Agreement]
[Liu Yingying, Xu Ao]
This...
Xu Ao just got promoted.
There must be some misunderstanding.
Your mother, the so-called No.1 matchmaker
in the world, made a bad match,
and now our Official Matchmaking Agency
has to clean up her mess.
If you're unwilling
to take this divorce case,
then I'll have to
personally go to your mother
and let her deal with it herself.
That won't be necessary,
I'll go.
[Official Matchmaking Agency]
Ke.
What would you like to eat today?
I was just bragging yesterday,
and now Liu Yingying
is getting divorced from Xu Ao today.
I can't talk about this.
Ke, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
I have something to do today.
Let's meet another time.
[No.1 Matchmaker in the World]
Ancestors above,
I've encountered
a difficult problem today.
Ms. Deng said
Liu Yingying suddenly wanted a divorce.
I dare not tell my mother,
afraid it would upset her.
But I can't ignore this matter.
What should I do?
Ke.
Mother.
What are you doing?
Are you speaking ill
of me to our ancestors?
Mom.
How could I ever speak ill of you?
I love you the most.
Why are you home so early today?
There wasn't much to do
at the Official Matchmaking Agency today,
so I came home early.
Mom.
I have something to ask you.
Can all couples who are in love
grow old together?
Silly child,
even teeth accidentally bite
the tongue sometimes,
how could a marriage be without any bumps?
Then what should be done
when there are bumps?
Must they separate?
Marriage is like a piece of paper,
pure and beautiful, yet fragile.
Once folded,
the crease will always remain.
It needs to be carefully kept
and taken good care of.
Have any of the marriages
you arranged had such...
Did something happen to you?
It's nothing,
I just took on a divorce case.
If I were still working
at the Official Matchmaking Agency,
I would thoroughly investigate
what exactly went wrong.
If reconciliation is possible,
you should certainly
try your best to mediate.
If reconciliation isn't possible,
when someone's heart has changed,
no matter who arranged the match,
don't force them to stay together.
Forcing them to remain bound
will only create a resentful couple.
But what if it affects the reputation
of the No.1 matchmaker in the world?
Child, come here.
[No.1 Matchmaker in the World]
If this plaque has a crack in it,
does that mean the name of the No.1
matchmaker
in the world is ruined?
If we encounter problems,
we should be the first to step up
and address them.
[No.1 Matchmaker in the World]
I see.
[Xu's Mansion]
Miss Shi, you're here.
I apologize for not greeting you properly,
please forgive me.
Hello, Yingying,
I should have visited earlier,
but my family experienced a major crisis,
and I didn't want to burden old friends,
so I couldn't come.
Please.
When you say that,
I feel rather embarrassed.
Xu Ao is a straightforward person.
He really has no connections
with the Military Headquarters,
and couldn't help Chief Matchmaker Tao.
I hope you understand.
I understand.
Don't blame yourself, Yingying.
Ke, I know why you're here.
I'm divorcing him willingly.
Yingying, you've kept this home
in perfect order,
Your efforts really show.
Commander Xu is now rising in his career,
do you really have the heart
to break up this family?
My mind is made up.
If you truly care about me,
just proceed with this divorce.
Yingying,
my mother often told me that
even teeth and tongue clash sometimes.
[Noble Feelings and Lofty Ambition]
Marriage is like a sheet of white paper,
pure and beautiful, yet fragile.
If torn too roughly,
it will be damaged forever.
For seven years of marriage,
I've poured all my love
into this relationship.
But now...
Forget it, let's say it's my fault,
I just don't want to
live like this anymore.
Yingying.
When Xu Ao came to our house to propose,
I was young,
but I remember my mother asking him
how he, with his ordinary background
and no achievements,
could marry the daughter
of the Liu family.
He swore then
that if he could marry you,
he would strive to better himself,
to earn the right
to be with you every day,
until you both grew old together,
and never betray your love.
Yingying.
My mother has met countless people.
She wouldn't misjudge someone.
Such deep love
shouldn't vanish in an instant.
Yingying, I can see
you still have feelings for him.
I'm not asking you to compromise yourself.
I can process this divorce,
but I hope you'll tell me the truth.
Xu Ao doesn't come home at night
because he stays
at the Flower House.
He has an ambiguous relationship
with Ms. Hua, the manager there,
and she's already pregnant with his child.
Mrs. Xu,
I am Hua Yuerong,
I know you must be curious about me,
so I've come to meet you.
You overthink things.
I'm not curious,
[Noble Feelings and Lofty Ambition]
nor do I want to know who you are.
Madam, you should know
that avoiding something
doesn't mean it didn't happen.
I'm sure you've already heard
that Commander Xu Ao
really likes me.
Tell him to come and speak to me himself,
then I'll grant his wish.
I heard that you've been married
for seven years without a child.
Commander Xu doesn't mind,
but
the child is innocent.
Please, Madam,
spare us, mother and child.
What a despicable couple!
How dare she come here and provoke you?
Everyone congratulates
the promotion of my husband,
but who knows
that my title as the new Commander's Madam
is nothing but an empty title.
If that's the case,
I must confront this scoundrel.
If it's really as you described,
I'll make him
stamp his fingerprint for divorce
and set you free.
If a marriage is happy
and the husband loving,
who would want freedom anyway?
[Xu's Mansion]
Here, take a look.
Come on, let's hurry.
Mrs. Li, take it easy.
Lu.
Ke.
Haven't seen you lately,
so I came looking for you
and brought you some food.
I know you've encountered some troubles.
Is it about the Xu family?
Why not tell me about it
and see if I can help resolve it?
I suppose you've heard about
the Xu couple divorce matter.
If I don't handle it,
Ms. Deng will surely
mock and harass my mother.
If I do handle it,
she'll definitely use this against me,
drive me out of
the Official Matchmaking Agency,
and ruin my mother's reputation.
Ms. Deng is vicious and cruel,
truly difficult to deal with.
I've always respected her as an elder.
Who knew she would turn on me so suddenly?
If that's the case,
just advise reconciliation.
That's impossible.
Hua Yuerong deliberately
came to provoke Yingying.
It seems those rumors
weren't false after all.
I must deal with these scoundrels myself.
Listening to only one side
leaves you in the dark.
We might as well
hear Xu Ao's side of the story.
I was thinking the same.
But I've waited for several days
and he hasn't returned.
Since he's close with Hua Yuerong,
we might as well
wait for him at Flower House.
That's right.
But if we go empty-handed,
it would seem like
we're there to confront him.
Why don't we bring a gift
to congratulate him on his promotion?
Then let's go to Xibao Pavilion
to choose something.
Alright.
Look, it's over there.
Is that it?
That's the one you mentioned, right?
Let's go take a look over there too.
Mr. Shi, do you like my handkerchief?
Mr. Shi, you're so strong!
You made me twist my ankle.
I didn't touch you,
don't try to frame me.
You suddenly pulled my handkerchief
and stepped aside.
You...
Are you trying to tease me on purpose?
My reputation is at stake now.
Now I've twisted my ankle
and suffered your humiliation.
I'm going to your home right now
to have Chief Matchmaker Tao settle this.
Let's go then.
Li Pan'er,
what exactly are you trying to do?
Well, at the moment,
I can't walk properly.
But we have so much work
at Xibao Pavilion.
Mr. Shi, you must take responsibility.
As long as you don't
report this to my mother,
I am at your service.
Actually,
I'm not an unreasonable person.
Once my foot heals,
I won't trouble you anymore.
Let's go.
Move along, everyone.
Haven't you seen someone
helping others before?
Mr. Shi looks so tall and strong,
yet he's afraid of women.
I quit.
You beat me again.
Let's start over.
How about we start over?
Let's restart, okay?
Xianxian.
Weren't you supposed to keep an eye on Ke?
Ke hasn't returned,
so why are you back?
Xianxian, why aren't you saying anything?
I...
I can't explain it clearly.
It's all because of that young lady.
Son.
Which young lady?
We can have
your mother arrange the marriage.
This is good news!
Let Ke go.
Yes, Ke can go.
Which young lady is it?
If Mother hears I tangled with
Li Pan'er on the street,
not only am I finished,
but Li Pan'er's reputation
would be ruined too.
But Ke still needs to be watched over.
What should I do?
My life is so difficult.
So difficult!
Son, what's going on with you?
Which young lady has
cracked that stubborn skull of yours?
Tell me, which family?
I didn't,
I haven't,
don't talk nonsense.
What do you mean "nonsense"?
How dare you speak like that?
Is that how you talk to your father?
Xianxian, explain yourself properly.
Father, brother.
I...
I did flirt with her.
What? Flirt?
No.
That's not it.
It's Ms. Li who said I flirted with her.
It's nothing, nothing.
Ms. Li must have been instructed by Lu Chi
to say such things.
Isn't she actually coveting
my strong and mighty presence?
Son.
Do you have some misunderstanding
about what "strong and mighty" means?
Or perhaps Ms. Li's eyesight
is the problem?
What do you mean?
I mean,
how could she
possibly be interested in you?
That does make sense.
This color looks a bit better.
None of these seem quite right.
Pan'er,
what do you think I should give as a gift?
Miss Shi, don't worry,
our Chief
probably has it all planned out.
Pan'er.
What happy news have you heard
that makes you smile so brightly?
Was I smiling?
Maybe the honest guy
is just too interesting.
Honest guy?
Who are you talking about?
[Heaven Rewards the Diligent]
Mr. He.
Thank you.
Kexian.
Ke?
What are you doing here?
Ms. Li, I apologize for the intrusion.
It's fine.
Here are the desserts you ordered.
I'll leave you two to chat.
This way, please.
Kexian, you're just in time.
I'm going to meet Commander Xu Ao.
What do you think
I should bring as a gift?
Why don't you come back with me,
and we can pick out
some exquisite desserts.
Ketian isn't still angry with me, is she?
If I come back with you,
she won't throw me out, will she?
She's not angry anymore.
She's been talking about you every day.
But bringing food,
isn't that too ordinary?
How about this gift?
Lu, what kind of scroll is this?
No matter what kind of scroll it is,
Xu Ao is a military officer,
how could he be given
paintings and calligraphy?
This brushwork looks
very similar to Mr. Lin Yuan's style.
It just doesn't have a signature or seal.
But this piece
shows stronger
and more masterful brushwork
than his previous ones.
It might just be an imitation.
How can you give someone
a painting without a signature?
Kexian, you're mistaken about this.
Mr. Lin Yuan's works are worth a fortune.
And Xu Ao has just been promoted.
If I were to give him an authentic piece,
it might look like a bribe.
This imitation has good artistic concept
and excellent technique.
As a gift exchanged between friends,
it's tasteful
and doesn't violate any laws.
That's exactly right.
Kexian,
we need to attend
to some important matters.
We'll visit you and Ketian another time.
You can go now.
Take care of yourself.
Lu.
Do you think
Xu Ao is really like
what Liu Yingying described?
I dare not make assumptions,
but seeing is believing.
Let's go to Flower House
to meet Xu Ao first,
then we can make a decision.
[Flower House]
How is the divorce proceeding?
Rest assured, My Lord.
I've sent Tao's daughter
Shi Fa'ke to handle it.
It will be done soon.
You sent Shi Fa'ke to handle it?
You're letting personal grudges
interfere with important matters.
I...
All Ms. Deng wants is to tarnish
the name
of the No.1 matchmaker in the world.
She wants to succeed
while taking all the advantage.
Little does she know
that times and circumstances change.
I finally managed to force
Liu Yingying to initiate a divorce.
Ms. Deng, you've delayed
my sworn brother's important matter
due to your selfish interests.
If my sworn brother blames us for this,
neither of us can bear the consequences.
I wouldn't dare.
Tomorrow I'll personally
go to Xu Ao.
No need.
Give me the divorce agreement.
You may leave now.
I take my leave.
My Lady.
Ms. Deng is completely useless
and almost caused trouble for you.
The Lord Marquis is still
worried about Xu Ao's matter.
Tell him to rest assured.
Xu Ao hasn't come home recently.
He sleeps in my brothel every night.
It’s all under my control.
Men, as you know,
can't bear to part with their wives,
yet can't resist their pleasures outside.
Regarding the Lord Marquis's instructions,
please handle it with care, My Lady.
Get Xu Ao to sign
the divorce agreement as soon as possible,
then marry him yourself,
to ease the Lord Marquis's concerns.
Ask him to wait for my good news.
Lord Xu.
I've brought you some wine.
My Lord.
On the surface, I'm here for pleasure,
but no one else can know about this.
I'll go answer the door,
and you leave through the window.
Yes.
Ms. Hua, since you've brought wine,
please come in
and join me for a few drinks.
Lu,
let's go see what Xu Ao is doing.
Ke.
No matter what you see later,
don't act impulsively.
Don't worry,
I know how to handle social situations.
If he's just properly eating and drinking,
I won't do anything inappropriate.
Let's go.
Lord Xu, if you do as I suggested,
any woman
would be delighted.
Excellent.
As long as it makes her smile.
Lord Xu.
Miss Shi,
what brings you here?
And who is this?
I feel like I've seen him before.
Lord Xu.
My name is Lu Chi,
the Chief of Xibao Pavilion.
Are you two guests invited by Lord Xu?
This gift is to congratulate you
on your promotion.
My mother was your matchmaker.
I've come today
to discuss something important with you.
What important matter?
You didn't even close the door just now.
I heard most of
what was said from outside.
I originally wanted
to hear your explanation,
but seeing how intimate you two are,
I don't think it's necessary anymore.
I came today
to ask you to sign this divorce agreement.
[Divorce Agreement]
Miss Shi,
my relationship with Ms. Hua
is purely platonic,
please don't misunderstand.
Stop making excuses.
I will definitely
get justice for Yingying.
Sign this divorce agreement,
and you'll have nothing more
to do with Yingying.
There'll be a clean break for both of you.
[Divorce Agreement]
I won't divorce her.
[Wife: Liu Yingying] [Husband: Xu Ao]
Every time you hand me
that divorce agreement, I'll tear it up.
You...
Things have already come to this.
Aren't you two leaving?
You two are in cahoots.
Xu Ao.
Don't think that tearing up
the divorce papers
will solve everything.
You're hanging around
with this Hua Yuerong,
clearly you're not a decent person either.
You've found someone new
but won't set Yingying free.
You're absolutely shameless!
Ms. Hua, show them out.
This way, please.
You...
Ke, let's go.
Dolls! Come take a look!
Ke, are you still upset?
But anyway,
have you thought about what will happen
to Ms. Liu after the divorce?
Originally, for my mother's reputation,
I didn't plan to break them up.
But now,
Xu Ao is having an affair,
I can't let Yingying
suffer in silence for life.
Besides, our state's laws
don't discriminate
against divorced women at all.
Remarrying after divorce
is quite common.
Yingying is beautiful
and has good temperament,
finding another good match
wouldn't be difficult.
Even if she doesn't remarry,
Yingying still has her dowry.
And if we take that scumbag's property,
she can still live a good life.
Do you trust my ability to read people?
What did you notice?
Ke.
Where has your usual keen observation
gone to?
Think carefully about what just happened.
I was so furious with Xu Ao
that I couldn't think straight.
Wait.
When Xu Ao was talking with Hua Yuerong,
the door was left open.
Could it be
that Hua Yuerong heard footsteps
and deliberately staged everything?
Very likely.
When Xu Ao asked Hua Yuerong
to see us out,
it was just like how you speak to Ms. Li,
though your tone is actually much kinder.
If Xu Ao truly had feelings for Ms. Hua,
he would treat her with constant care,
not the way he does now.
Could we have misjudged Xu Ao?
Is Hua Yuerong really
the one causing trouble?
It's possible.
So we should find out the truth
and give Xu Ao a chance to explain himself
before making any decisions.
We mustn't act on impulse
and break up a marriage.
Lu, you're absolutely right.
I was indeed too emotional just now.
Would you be willing
to help me uncover the truth
before making a judgment?
Of course.
Let's go.
Is he crazy?
Climbing over the wall
to get into his own home?
He might...
He climbed over the wall to get home,
then climbed back out again.
What on earth is he up to?
Perhaps he has some personal difficulty
he can't talk about.
I feel like he's just like
the cheating spouse
you often see in literature.
The more I watch him,
the more suspicious he seems.
Alright, let's follow him first.
Let's go.
Lu, please don't let go of me.
I don't want to lose my life
before we even discover the truth.
I won't let go,
but you must promise me something.
No matter what you see or hear later,
you must stay calm,
or our lives will be in danger.
I wouldn't get upset over some jerk,
just don't let go of me.
My Lord, have you delivered the rouge yet?
I've sent it
and left it on the dressing table
she uses frequently.
My Lord, you needn't worry too much.
Just do as I say,
and everything will work out fine.
Lu, they...
Don't worry, Ke,
he's just drunk.
Hua Yuerong, what are you
planning to do to Xu Ao?
Lord Xu and I
are merely drinking companions
with nothing improper between us.
Xu Ao is an imperial official
and a married man.
With your beauty,
you don't need to do this.
It's a long story.
Not telling you is for your own good.
Please go back, both of you.
Ms. Hua, you...
Ke,
let's go.
Pan'er,
do you have any better rouge in your shop?
Of course we do.
Wen.
Actually,
this is a sample
specially ordered by a customer.
There was only one box
of the actual product,
and the buyer picked it up yesterday.
Miss Shi, you can only have a look.
I'm afraid it's no longer available.
This color is beautiful.
Ms. Li,
you've been hiding such a nice item
and won't sell it to me.
I wonder who
specially ordered such beautiful rouge?
It was...
Xu Ao.
Commander Xu.
It's him?
He must have bought rouge
as a gift for that person.
[Xu's Mansion]
Madam, Miss Shi is here.
All of you, please leave first.
Yes.
What is this?
Yingying, look.
Why is it on my dressing table?
What's going on?
Yingying,
if you want to know,
come with me and find out.
[Revelry of Peace]
Bravo!
Very nice.
Nice dance.
Indeed.
Lu,
you could have brought me here,
why made me stand in the cold outside?
I thought you could
hear more clearly from outside.
Besides,
did you expect me to
hold both of you
while eavesdropping by the window?
Lord Xu, you usually
wait until your wife falls asleep
before coming over.
Why didn't you go back today?
I wonder if she saw
that box of rouge.
Will she like it?
Yingying has been
increasingly cold to me these days.
I'd better not go back.
I'll wait a few days
until her anger subsides before returning.
Mrs. Xu is so persistent
and still misunderstands you, My Lord.
My Lord, do you
still truly not want to divorce her?
Of course not.
When I was still a nobody,
she followed me without hesitation.
It's all my fault
for not taking good care of her.
But since we made our vows,
I should never leave or abandon her.
Please forgive me, My Lord.
I have something to confess to you.
What is it?
Lord Xu, do you know
why Mrs. Xu asked for a divorce?
Why?
My Lord, you often
visit my Flower House,
so someone forced me to seduce you,
and marry into your household.
But you never crossed the line,
and to protect myself,
I had to lie to Mrs. Xu,
claiming I was pregnant.
What?
This...
No wonder Yingying
suddenly wanted a divorce.
I thought she despised me
for being uncouth
and not taking good care of her.
Xu Ao.
Dear.
Darling.
I have never despised you.
It's just that since our marriage,
I haven't been able
to bear you any children,
so I feel I've let you down terribly.
Besides, you've been distracted all year.
You haven't been talking to me.
I thought you had grown tired of me.
How could that be possible, Dear?
How could I ever tire of you?
I can't get enough of looking at you.
It's just that I have
important matters on my mind.
I often neglect your feelings.
Children come to us by fate,
and if they don't, it's heaven's will.
As long as I can grow old with you,
I dare not ask for more.
But you're the sole male heir
of three generations.
Your parents, before they passed away,
instructed me
to continue the family line.
How dare I not listen?
My silly wife.
If we truly cannot have one of our own,
and you still insist on having a child,
we could always adopt one.
Lord Xu speaks wisely.
A marriage is built by two people,
how can it depend on children?
If Lord Xu were to
divorce you over children,
then he wouldn't be a good husband anyway.
Miss Shi speaks the truth.
Do you truly feel this way?
I married you because I love you.
I would never divorce you over
this so-called inability
to continue the family line.
To have a husband like you,
I could ask for nothing more.
Madam.
Lord Xu.
I must have a word with you.
You sent rouge
but didn't tell Yingying about it.
If I hadn't overheard,
when would Yingying have seen it?
It's entirely my fault.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have distrusted you.
Neither of you is at fault.
Blame me
for not eavesdropping earlier.
Ke, what exactly is going on?
Didn't we agree not to meet these days?
Why the rush to send a message
to ask me here?
Don't listen to those rumors out there.
There's nothing between Xu Ao and me.
It's just...
I have difficulties
that are hard to explain.
Just wait for me two or three more days,
once I finish what I need to do,
we can run away together.
Ms. Hua, what's troubling you?
Feel free to tell us.
Ms. Hua, won't you be honest with me?
Miss Shi, Chief Lu.
That letter was written
by Feng himself.
What have you done to him?
Rest assured, Ms. Hua.
Mr. Li is safe and sound.
Yuerong.
Feng.
Chief Lu is here to help us.
He can help us
get out of this predicament.
Lu.
These two share a deep bond.
I believe Ms. Hua has her reasons.
Chief Lu.
For everything before, I was indeed wrong.
I deeply apologize.
The reason I did this
is because I was coerced
and have difficulties I cannot speak of.
Who forced you?
Chief Lu.
Please forgive me
for not being able to tell you.
Don't worry, Ms. Hua.
I promise you
I will safely escort
both of you out of the capital.
Not just the two of us,
but our family of three.
Chief Lu.
Just bring Ms. Liu here,
and once the misunderstanding is cleared,
I can complete my task and leave.
Ms. Hua, you're straightforward.
When the truth comes to light,
I will send people
to escort you and Mr. Li
out of the capital.
Then I thank you, Chief Lu and Miss Shi.
We eavesdropped once
and found out that Lord Xu is innocent.
But Ms. Hua refused
to explain the situation,
fortunately Lu discovered the key person
and persuaded her.
Ke,
you were actually the one who noticed
the twin lotus jade pendant
at Ms. Hua's waist.
This pendant is a unique piece from
Xibao Pavilion's Qixi Festival collection.
There are two identical pieces,
meant for lovers.
Ms. Hua and Xu Ao
are not romantically involved,
so there must be someone else she loves.
I'll keep my word.
Ms. Hua,
I will ensure your family's safety.
Chief Lu, Miss Shi,
you've protected my reputation
and arranged a way out for me.
I am deeply grateful.
When all is said and done,
it's all your fault.
Fine, it's all my fault.
Why is it so hot today?
[No.1 Matchmaker in the World]
Mother.
At first, I thought no matter what,
I couldn't let them divorce,
because it would affect your reputation
[No.1 Matchmaker in the World]
and the title
of the No.1 matchmaker in the world.
But when I found out Xu Ao was unfaithful,
I couldn't use Yingying's pain
to protect our family's reputation.
So, if what Yingying said had been true,
I would definitely
have helped the two of them get a divorce.
Ke.
That day when you were
confiding in our ancestors,
[No.1 Matchmaker in the World]
I heard everything
outside the ancestral hall.
So, Mother,
you knew about their divorce matter?
I just hope
that all your decisions
come from your heart,
not because of me
or this title.
[No.1 Matchmaker in the World]
You're the best mother ever.
Then let me ask you,
even if I blame you,
will you still stay true to yourself?
I will.
What a good child.
[No.1 Matchmaker in the World]
You're a matchmaker.
Always remember
that with just a few words,
you can determine someone's happiness
for the rest of their life.
Nothing matters more than sincerity.
Whether it's my reputation
or the glory of being
the No.1 matchmaker in the world,
nothing is more important
than the happiness of two people.
That's the true essence of matchmaking.
Ke.
You've saved Liu Yingying's marriage,
why are you still unhappy?
Lu, why are you here?
Don't let my brothers find you.
I originally wanted
to tell you some good news,
but I heard you sighing.
Why don't you tell me
what's troubling you?
How would you understand?
At weddings,
I often wish couples
prosperity and many children.
Yingying's marriage is secure now,
but they still have no children.
It shows that in life,
eight or nine times out of ten,
things don’t go as planned.
That's exactly the good news
I wanted to tell you.
I've found a skilled doctor
who has examined Mrs. Xu,
and there's a treatment available.
So you don't need to worry too much.
Xu Ao loves Liu Yingying,
and doesn't care
that much about having children.
Really?
Thank you for resolving their concerns.
Lu.
If you were Xu Ao,
what would you do?
I would be the same.
If I could marry the one I love,
whether we have children or not,
my devotion would never change.