[Better Halves]
[Episode 12]
[Flower Manor]
Lu.
This is...
This is my younger brother, Lu Zhuxi.
This is the organizer
of the Flower Assembly,
Miss Shi.
You're Miss Shi?
This is the young lady
from Prime Minister's Mansion
and my good friend, Zhu Yanyan.
Mr. Lu,
how old are you?
Are you married?
What type of young lady do you like?
Miss,
we must be destined to meet.
Have we met somewhere before?
My friend here is an avid reader.
She's read almost every novel
on the market.
She has strained her eyes because of it.
Please don't take offense.
I wonder if you
have read
Neighboring Hermit's Junshan Collection?
You just angered me
by mentioning him.
I finally managed
to buy the Junshan Collection,
but when I opened it,
it was clearly just a reprint
of the old version.
It's been a month,
and he hasn't written a single new word.
Don't let me find out
who Neighboring Hermit is.
Because if I do,
I'll capture him
and lock him in my study.
And I'll whip him with a leather strap
every day.
I'll make him write.
I'll whip him just like this. I'll...
Yanyan.
My friend likes to joke.
She usually is not this ferocious.
Please.
Ke, I...
Lu, I have many things to attend to.
I'm leaving.
You...
Over there is fine.
Miss Zhu.
Zhu...
They say Prime Minister's Mansion
has strict manners,
but Prime Minister's granddaughter is
no different from the rest—
only nice to those above her.
Miss, actually, that novel...
Yanyan.
Ketian.
Young Master, this is my good friend.
Ketian. Where's your Zhu Yizhi?
He was just here.
Yizhi.
Zhu Yizhi
is nowhere to be seen on ordinary days,
but he's quite active
in attending the Flower Assembly.
[Zhu Yizhi]
Ketian.
You all chat first.
I'll go look around over there.
Ketian.
How could Zhu Yizhi
leave you here alone?
It's fine.
Ketian.
We're not married yet.
If we're always seen together,
people might talk.
That's not right.
Engaged couples should spend time together
getting to know each other,
so they won't find their personalities
don't match after marriage.
This engagement was arranged
while my parents were still alive.
Now that my parents have passed away,
even if we aren't suited for each other,
who can I talk to about it?
Ketian.
Yizhi.
Ketian is over there.
Why don't you go keep her company?
Chongshan, perfect timing.
Ketian, I think
Chongshan
is so much better than Zhu Yizhi.
If the engagement doesn't work out,
you can break off the engagement.
And if you can't find someone else,
you can marry into the Shi family.
Mrs. Shi is nice,
and Chongshan has doted on you
since childhood.
If you are willing,
he would definitely marry you.
Yanyan, stop talking nonsense.
You've... You've read too many novels.
Novels are full of life's truths.
Trust me, they're never wrong.
Enough.
Look at Chongshan, he's being shy.
Young ladies, you're here.
Long time no see.
You're more beautiful than ever.
Please, come inside.
I'm really so...
Over there.
It's starting!
Hurry up!
This way.
Truly,
birds of a feather flock together.
You've brought this upon yourselves.
Just wait.
Don't blame me this time.
[Flower Assembly]
Thank you all for coming tonight.
I now declare
the Xibao Flower Assembly
officially opens.
-Wonderful!
-Great!
Thank you all
for attending the Xibao Flower Assembly.
I hope each of you
can find your destined one today.
Now, let's welcome
the Chief of Xibao Pavilion, Lu Chi.
-Yes!
-Bravo!
[Flower Assembly]
Thank you all
for your strong support
of the Xibao Flower Assembly.
Xibao Pavilion will give
each attendee
a meal voucher.
Additionally, during the Flower Assembly,
if any young lady or gentleman
finds a match
and goes through Miss Shi,
Xibao Pavilion will also offer
a voucher for betrothal gifts or dowries.
-Great!
[Flower Assembly]
So generous.
Thank you for your generosity, Chief Lu.
Next, let's welcome
our second major sponsor—
He Kexian, the owner of He's Bakery.
Kexian.
Thank you, everyone.
At He's Bakery,
we'll also offer
a wedding cake voucher to any couple
matched by Miss Shi.
-Excellent!
-Bravo!
Thank you, Chief Lu! Thank you, Mr. He!
So generous.
Thank you, Mr. He.
I didn't expect such wonderful surprises.
♪ It seems every time I meet you ♪
Chief Lu, please wait.
♪ Misfortune turns to peace anew ♪
I believe everyone is now familiar
with the rules of the Flower Assembly.
♪ And in my memories I trace ♪
Now, Chief Lu, please unveil the event.
♪ The knots you gently did unlace ♪
♪ I thought it was mystery ♪
♪ But fate had long written our story ♪
♪ Though we still
pretend to tread carefully ♪
♪ In this chaotic world, because of you ♪
♪ It's filled with wonder ♪
♪ Only you make me unafraid to give ♪
♪ A vow of life and death to live ♪
♪ I'll promise you verses ♪
♪ And all I want you in return ♪
♪ Who cares
who the martial legends may be too? ♪
[Flower Assembly]
[List of Male Guests
at the Xibao Flower Assembly]
Ladies and gentlemen,
in front of each young lady
is a glass lamp engraved with her name.
Gentlemen whose names
are listed on the scroll
may step forward one by one.
[List of Male Guests
at the Xibao Flower Assembly]
If a young lady takes interest,
she may light her glass lamp.
Then she can ask the gentleman questions
to test his talents and knowledge.
If she remains interested
after hearing his answers,
she can keep her lamp lit.
Otherwise, she may extinguish it.
What if too many young ladies
are interested in me?
That's a good question.
Each gentleman
can choose one lady among those
who have lit their lamps for him.
Invite her to stroll the garden and chat.
If he finds no match, he can simply pass.
Then he won't be able
to find anyone, right?
-Yeah.
Then he won't be able to find anyone.
If you can't find anyone you like here,
go to the lakeside,
write down your names,
put them in lanterns,
and throw them into the water.
Let fate decide.
See whose lantern
you'll pick up from the water
and who'll pick up yours.
Perhaps that will also
lead to a fated encounter.
What if a man picks up a man's lantern?
Or a woman picks up a woman's?
Oh, you!
That's a fair point.
Marriage
is not the only thing in life.
Women have dear friends.
Men have like-minded companions.
If you pick up a lantern
of someone of the same gender,
drink together and chat.
Finding a good friend is also a joy.
-Wonderful!
-Well said!
Wonderful!
That's right!
Ketian.
Well said.
Ke really has changed.
Not long ago, she was just focusing
on the people around her,
playing matchmaker just to pass the time.
But today,
she's hosting such a grand gathering.
She may have seemed scatterbrained before,
but she's clearly got her wits
about her now.
But
she's always been muddled
in terms of her own matters.
And she has poor taste.
I don't think so.
I think Ke has great taste.
Just look at Mr. Lu.
Isn't he handsome and charming?
My brother is quite good too.
Kexian is a good man,
but ultimately,
it depends on who Ke likes.
Right?
Now, because everyone
has been so enthusiastic
about the Flower Assembly,
we've had more sign-ups than expected.
So I can't arrange for everyone
to participate in the glass lamp activity.
But to help everyone find a good match,
we've specially added a new segment
for those not selected for it.
Also,
if you didn't get a chance to register,
don't be discouraged.
The Flower Assembly is held every year.
And if there's demand,
we can even host it multiple times a year.
The Official Matchmaking Agency
will help you find a perfect match.
Chief Lu and I
will host the next segment together.
All the prizes
will be provided by Xibao Pavilion.
-Excellent!
-Great!
Now,
let's welcome the young ladies
and gentlemen
participating in the segment to the stage.
Zhu Yizhi?
Everyone, listen carefully.
In the first round,
each young lady will pair with a gentleman
to play arrow-throwing together.
Those who score
will receive a dessert gift box
from He's Bakery.
Ketian, don't be angry.
Once we're back, I'll surely
get you a proper explanation.
Lu,
this part
is intended for single individuals.
That man
is Ketian's fiancé.
He actually signed up behind her back,
went on stage,
and kept staring at other young ladies.
He's completely humiliated Ketian.
He's indeed gone too far.
I'll make him give up later.
Really?
Don't worry, Ke.
Let the arrow-throwing game begin!
Failed again?
I...
-Bravo!
The second round:
bamboo rings on glass bottles.
The next pair, please come to the stage.
I'll do it!
He dares to go again?
He...
Missed again.
This is so embarrassing.
What's wrong with him?
Step down.
Yeah.
Here.
Now,
the lamp lighting activity
officially begins!
-Great!
Each young lady has a glass lamp
in front of her.
If there's a gentleman you like,
you can light your glass lamp.
Lighting it
means you're open to further acquaintance—
to get to know him better.
Extinguishing it
means you're not interested.
If your lamp stays lit until the end
and the gentleman feels the same way—
that means
you have feelings for each other—
you'll receive a gift from Xibao Pavilion:
a spring trip to the neighboring city.
-Great!
-Awesome!
Seven days of luxury travel for free!
That's amazing! I want it so badly!
Now, let's welcome the gentlemen.
-Good!
Now, let's welcome our first gentleman—
Mr. Lu Zhuxi from Xibao Pavilion.
Greetings, young ladies.
I am Lu Zhuxi.
I enjoy traveling, exploring nature,
reading novels,
and occasionally writing as well.
Just a few words
may not be enough for the ladies
to understand Mr. Lu.
Let's welcome his family to introduce him.
Hello, everyone.
This is my younger brother, Lu Zhuxi.
He is young and values freedom.
He's straightforward and kind-hearted.
His greatest strengths
are his creativity and literary talent.
As for shortcomings,
I haven't thought of any yet.
Now, it's time for questions.
If any young lady has something to ask,
please do.
After hearing Mr. Lu's answers,
you can decide whether to light your lamp.
Mr. Lu,
is Xibao Pavilion
your family's ancestral property?
Do you have inheritance rights?
All ancestral properties
belong to my elder brother.
I do not live off family wealth,
nor do I have inheritance rights.
Mr. Lu,
who is your favorite novelist?
Miss Shi,
I would like to perform a talent.
I want to recite a poem.
Mr. Lu has volunteered
to showcase his talent.
Please, go ahead.
-Great!
Today on stage, I write a poem.
Tomorrow at home, I'll get married.
The day after tomorrow, I'll have a son.
Then I'll see if my wife is pleased.
Very straightforward.
Very interesting.
Good! Very amusing!
Mr. Lu is very humorous, isn't he?
Very humorous.
Indeed.
I'm afraid
only one person understands this poem.
Only one person understands it?
Just one person?
Who is it?
All right.
Young ladies, decide
whether you want to light your lamp.
Could it be he has someone he likes?
Someone actually lit her lamp.
Can she understand it?
Yanyan, you understand Mr. Lu's poem?
It's doggerel from the last novel
of Neighboring Hermit.
I didn't expect Mr. Lu
to recite it so fluently.
So it's a poem from a novel.
-Good!
Now, let's welcome our second gentleman—
Lu Yi from Xibao Pavilion.
Hello, everyone.
I'm an employee at Xibao Pavilion.
My name is Lu Yi.
Lu Yi is not only my employee,
but also my family.
I know him very well.
He is loyal, honest, smart, and capable.
According to Chief Lu's introduction,
we can see that Mr. Lu is very upright
and responsible.
Those traits are very important
in marriage.
Young ladies, please ask your questions.
Mr. Lu, I want to ask
if you have a house in the capital.
Where exactly is it located?
If you were to marry,
how many betrothal gifts could you offer?
At the moment, I do not own a house,
but I do plan to purchase one.
I've saved 450 taels of silver, enough
to buy a house with a vegetable plot
in the outer city.
As for the betrothal gifts,
I'm willing to give everything I can.
But if you buy a house,
you won't have 500 taels
for the betrothal gifts.
So I'll pass.
Miss,
having clear goals is good,
but you shouldn't have hurt his feelings
with those harsh words.
Mr. Lu is ambitious
and has good plans for his life.
You may not like him,
but to someone else,
he might be a perfect match.
Thank you for your guidance, Miss Shi.
I'll keep that in mind.
Young ladies,
as a matchmaker,
I also often wonder—
is it better to be wealthy and noble
or to have a simple, ordinary life?
Today, I want to speak from the heart.
Marriage isn't a transaction.
Marriage is a promise.
A promise is meant to last a lifetime.
At the core of a good marriage,
mutual affection comes first.
Money shouldn't be the primary criterion.
Miss Shi is right.
Yes.
Well said!
That's right!
Alright, young ladies,
please make your decisions.
Congratulations, Mr. Lu,
Miss Qin'er lit her lamp for you.
I'd like to ask Miss Qin'er—
why did you light your lamp for me?
I... I like a house with a vegetable plot.
Good! Good!
So romantic.
I want a house with a vegetable plot too.
Miss Shi. I also want to perform
a talent for every...
No.
I want to perform a talent
for Miss Qin'er.
Go ahead.
Great.
-Wonderful!
-Impressive!
Nice martial skills.
That's amazing!
Awesome!
-Impressive!
-Awesome!
Great martial skills!
Amazing!
Miss Shi's Flower Assembly
really is not bad.
Ms... Ms. Li,
would you like to take a walk around?
Amazing, right?
Sure.
Ketian. Would you like to take a walk?
Okay.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Now I announce
the assembly's lamp lighting activity
has successfully concluded.
-Great!
Excellent!
Great!
Everyone,
this time, we have
a total of six successful pairings.
Congratulations to them on winning a trip
to the neighboring city.
All the activities of this Flower Assembly
have now concluded.
Now, you are free
to enjoy the Flower Assembly.
May you all find someone you love.
See you at the next Flower Assembly.
-Great!
Let's go for a walk over there.
Okay.
The Flower Assembly is wonderful.
It was well prepared.
Really?
Let's go.
Give it to me.
This Flower Assembly
is truly a grand occasion.
Ke,
it's all thanks to your brilliant ideas.
I'm sure it's helped many couples
find each other.
And thank you, Lu.
Thanks to everyone who helped me,
I was able to host the event
and make everything run so smoothly.
This Flower Assembly
represents everyone's efforts.
I want to tell you something.
Lu.
How come I never heard you mention
that you have a younger brother?
It was our first meeting today.
You want to know more about me?
That's... that's not what I meant.
I was just thinking maybe I could
take on another matchmaking case.
He's quite silver-tongued,
full of mischievous ideas.
I wonder which young lady can handle him.
What is love in this world?
It's simply one thing subduing another.
I think Yanyan and your brother
get along quite well.
Don't worry, Lu.
I'll find a good match for your brother.
What about me?
If you're willing, Lu,
I can find you a good match too.
First of all,
when pursuing a young lady,
you should be proactive
and decisive.
That's not what I meant.
I was trying to say...
Ketian!
Ketian is over there.
Ke?
Kexian, go to Ke now.
I can walk around on my own.
But... but Zhu Yizhi
is nowhere to be seen.
I'm worried about you.
Kexian, just go.
Don't worry, I'm here.
I'll accompany Ketian.
Go.
Thank you, Chongshan.
Ke.
Let me take you to a fun place.
Let's go.
So the Flower Assembly is so grand
and so dazzling.
And everyone is smiling,
looking so happy.
Yes, it is beautiful.
Kexian, hurry!
Kexian, look.
There are lanterns over there.
Do you like them?
They're beautiful.
Ketian, I'll go with you
to look for Zhu Yizhi. How about that?
No need. Forget it.
Why?
Look,
Yanyan and Mr. Lu share interests.
They get along very well.
But me and Zhu Yizhi—we are different.
I'm afraid he doesn't like me.
And I...
don't feel much affection for him either.
And we don't share interests.
So why force it?
If we get married in the future,
I'll just turn a blind eye.
Life won't be too unbearable, I suppose.
Ketian,
you shouldn't
make yourself suffer like this.
If he lets you down in the future,
I...
Kexian and I
will be the first to avenge you.
Chongshan,
I know how good you are to me.
But whether he lets me down or not,
what difference does it make?
Now I just hope
you can find a girl you truly love.
Don't end up like me.
Ke...
Lu, look!
A shooting star!
Make a wish now.
Hurry up.
May the stars hear me—
I wish Ke and I will never be apart.
may Lu's wish come true.
-What wish did you make?
Wishes can't be told to anyone.
Otherwise, they won't come true.
Alright then, let's keep them secret.
So they'll come true.
-Neighboring Hermit.
Miss Zhu, you go first.
Mr. Lu,
Junshan and Caifeng
didn't end up together.
Should we send a razor blade
to Neighboring Hermit?
We definitely should.
But I think Junshan is too indecisive,
so he deserves to grow old alone.
In the upcoming extra story,
Caifeng will make him suffer.
He'll end up in a wheelchair,
full of regret.
You even know that?
Neighboring Hermit is actually...
my friend.
Really?
You...
You're close friends
with Neighboring Hermit?
That means you must truly understand him.
By the way, a few days ago,
I heard the bookstore's owner say
the extra story has been finished.
It just hasn't been printed yet.
Once it's out in a few days,
let's go buy it together, okay?
Sure.
Mr. Lu.
Since you're good friends
with Neighboring Hermit,
could you please urge him
to update his novel soon?
Okay. I will.
But...
But what?
Miss Zhu, you seem to admire him so much.
Do you...
You want to ask me
if I want to meet him
since I admire him so much?
Let me put it this way.
I love desserts from He's Bakery,
but I've never thought
about getting close to Kexian.
Another example.
I enjoy listening
to Young Master Qiujiang's operas,
but I don't want to see him every day
or spend all my time with him.
Actually, the people and things we like
bring us joy and comfort.
But when it comes to marriage,
just like Ke said,
we should choose someone
with whom we share mutual affection
and are willing
to spend our lives together.
Mr. Lu, do you understand
what I'm trying to tell you?
I understand.
Well, I have one more thing.
What is it?
When would it be convenient for you
to travel with me to the neighboring city
for sightseeing?
Well...
I need to go back
and ask my grandfather first.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
I'm going to Ke now.
♪ A girl unmatched beneath the sky ♪
♪ A flawless jade, that gentle guy ♪
♪ Who is it, too shy to speak ♪
♪ Blushing cheeks in crimson streak ♪
♪ A tangled heart in disarray ♪
Ever since I met Lu,
he has been really good to me.
♪ Whose thoughts are drifting far away ♪
I must find an opportunity
to explain everything
to that little beggar boy.
♪ Though skies are wide
and scenes divine ♪
Lu.
We've been up here for so long.
We haven't properly entertained
my brothers and our friends.
♪ This heart is bound ♪
Let's go down there, okay?
♪ Trapped like windswept cliffs above ♪
Why are you in such a hurry to go down?
If we don't go down now,
they'll come up here for us.
♪ Better to face it all with love ♪
And then
our little secret tonight
won't be a secret anymore.
Then I'll take you down.
♪ And find no regret ♪
Hold me tight.
Okay.
♪ Enough ♪
♪ Look, the peach blossoms bloom so fair ♪
♪ Youth in ribbons, fragrant hair ♪
♪ Without knowing,
something grows inside ♪
♪ Some fates don't need ♪
♪ A red thread's tie ♪
♪ So giving one's heart is the only way ♪
Kexian.
Ke.
Why didn't you go on stage today?
You already have someone you like?
Yes.
Really?
Did she come today?
I can go find out how she feels for you.
-Ke, actually, the one I like...
-Ke, let me ask you.
You and Mr. He are like siblings.
What if you don't like
the girl he likes?
I grew up with Kexian.
So I like whoever he likes.
Even if I don't like her,
as long as they love each other,
I would support them.
Don't worry, Kexian,
I'll be your matchmaker.
By then,
I'll arrange everything perfectly.
You won't even need to pay the agency fee.
No need. It's too early
to talk about that now.
It's not early.
The sooner you tell me,
the sooner I can start preparing, right?
We'll talk about it later.
I'm going to take a walk around.
You two chat.
Let's go take a walk around too.
Let's go.
Excuse me, how do I get to the garden?
Would you kindly show me the way?
Miss Zhu.
Oh, it's Chief Matchmaker Deng.
Would you please show me the way?
Don't move.
Miss Zhu,
I know your eyesight is poor.
You can't see clearly. I understand that.
But what about the others?
Why do all of you ignore me,
as if I'm invisible?
Why does everyone
only pay attention to Shi Fa'ke?
Fine. Today, I'll show you
who I am!
You're just not as good as Ke!
You ungrateful wretch!
You lost the money,
and you couldn't even handle
a mere Shi Fa'ke!
I think
you'd better hand over your position
as the Chief Matchmaker soon
[A perfect match]
and let someone more capable take it!
I am the Chief Matchmaker.
I'm the Chief Matchmaker
of the Official Matchmaking Agency.
I am the Chief Matchmaker.
I'm the Chief Matchmaker.
I am the Chief Matchmaker!
No one can take my place!
Help!
Someone!
Help! Someone!
Help! Someone please!
There's a fire!
A fire?
Ke, it's too dangerous here.
Let me get you out of here! Come on!
No, I can't leave!
I'm the organizer of the Flower Assembly.
Everyone else can leave, but not me.
I need to save the others!
Chief!
What's the situation?
Fa'ke!
The fire is too strong!
There are still people inside!
Take Qin'er and get out first.
Then go get the fire brigade.
No, it's too dangerous in there!
Listen to me. Go get the fire brigade!
Yes.
Qin'er, go with Lu Yi to get help.
Be good. Go with Lu Yi first!
Let's go.
Help!
[Chief Matchmaker]
Someone!
Ketian.
Be careful!
It's too dangerous here.
Ms. Li, let me escort you out first,
then I'll come back.
I want to go with you to save people!
Alright then. Stay close to me.
I'll keep you safe.
Everyone, stay calm!
I'm Shi Xianxian,
a constable from the magistrate's office!
Follow me!
I'll lead you out of here!
Yes, everyone, don't panic!
Follow Mr. Shi.
He'll get us out of here!
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
I won't let go of you,
and don't let go of me.
This way!
Yanyan!
Hurry, this way! This way!
This way!
Yanyan, where are you?
Mr. Lu, help me!
Mr. Lu!
Yanyan! Yanyan!
I'm over here, Mr. Lu!
Help me!
Yanyan!
Help!
Mr. Lu!
I'm here!
Yanyan!
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
[Chief Matchmaker]
Yanyan, let's go!
Let's go!
Watch out!
I'll definitely get you out of here.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
-Run!
Ke, have you seen Kexian?
Ketian, go out with Chongshan first.
I'll go find Kexian.
Yes, Ketian.
You go first, I'll find Kexian.
-Be good.
-Hurry! Be good. It's too dangerous here!
Be careful!
If you're not leaving,
I'm not leaving either.
I'll stay and look for him with you.
Ketian.
Don't push! Everyone, slow down!
Make way!
Zhu Yizhi, have you seen Kexian?
Is this the time to worry about him?
I...
Let go! Don't pull me!
Zhu Yizhi, do you even have humanity?
Ketian.
Be careful! Don't push!
Be careful!
Everyone, stop pushing!
Lu, I need your help.
Everyone, listen to me!
Listen to me!
I am Shi Fa'ke.
I will lead everyone to safety!
Now listen.
All gentlemen,
assist the young ladies beside you!
Form a line, and walk out safely!
Everyone, follow me!
Line up!
This way!
Okay.
-Let's go.
-Let's go!
Over here!
Xianxian.
Xianxian, Pan'er,
I'm glad you're both safe.
Pan'er, go with Xianxian.
He'll get you out safely.
We still need to save the others.
It's very dangerous here.
Take the others and leave first.
Don't worry, Chief Lu.
I'm a constable
and Ke's brother.
I will get everyone out
safely.
It's my duty.
Remember, be careful.
Xianxian,
you must take good care of Pan'er.
Don't worry.
Please take good care of my sister too.
Rest assured, Shi.
I will protect her with my life.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go!
-This way!
-Let's go!
Keep up.
Hurry. Let's go.
Are you alright?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
This way.
That way.
-Hurry!
Over here!
Hurry!
Let's go!
Help!
Is anyone here?
Kexian!
Mr. He!
Kexian, where are you?
Can you hear me?
Kexian!
Ke, don't come over here!
Leave now!
Kexian!
Ke, watch out!
Lu Chi, get her out of here!
No, I must save Kexian.
Ke, trust me.
I will definitely rescue Mr. He.
It's too dangerous to go in now.
Wait for me somewhere safe.
Lu,
be careful.
I'll wait for you and Kexian to come out.
Okay.
Hurry, get up.
Get up.
Why did you come to save me?
-I'd save anyone. Let's go!
-I know you like Ke.
Stop talking. Let's get out first.
Let's go.
Kexian.
Lu Chi, thanks.
But let me make it clear.
I will never give Ke up to you.
Good, I won't give up either.
Kexian, are you alright?
I'm fine, Ke.
Where is Ketian? Is she okay?
I think they've gotten out now.
Lu, I still don't see Ms. Deng
or Yanyan or the others.
I need to go find them.
Ke, calm down.
Wait for Lu Yi to bring the fire brigade.
We'll go after the fire is put out.
It's too dangerous to go now.
Lu Chi is right.
It's too dangerous in there.
You can't go now.
-Chief!
-Fa'ke!
Hurry!
Chief, the fire brigade is here.
Fa'ke, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Lu, look. The fire brigade is here.
The fire will be put out soon.
Let's go find Yanyan and the others.
Okay, but don't take unnecessary risks.
Fa'ke, please be very careful.
Lu Yi,
have the fire brigade put out the fire.
Get Mr. He and Qin'er out first.
Ke and I are going to find the others.
Yes. Be careful, Chief.
Hurry.
-Be careful.
Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Hurry!
Over there.
Help!
Help! Someone's trying to kill me!
Ms. Deng!
Help!
Ke!
Ms. Deng, don't be afraid!
I'll get you out of here, Ms. Deng!
Ms. Deng!
Go find someone to save her! Now!
Okay.
Go get the fire brigade!
Shi Fa'ke.
Ms. Deng.
Don't be afraid. I'll save you.
I joined
the Official Matchmaking Agency at 16.
Ms. Deng.
I've worked diligently
and dedicated my entire life to this work.
I've arranged marriages for so many,
but I never had a lover or a child myself.
All I wanted
was to become the Chief Matchmaker.
But...
But Heaven
sent your mother to overshadow me.
No matter how hard I worked,
I was never as good as her.
Just because
she was born as the heir
to the No.1 matchmaker in the world.
That's not true, Ms. Deng.
No one sees what I've done.
No one even remembers my name.
Even after I became the Chief Matchmaker,
they still wouldn't see me.
All they see
are you and your mother.
That's not true, Ms. Deng.
You're a good marriage broker,
hardworking and diligent.
I was immature and often slacked off.
I admire you the most.
You never miss work
and always work hard.
Ms. Deng, you're a good marriage broker!
A great marriage broker, Ms. Deng!
Ke, do you mean that?
I mean every word.
You and my mother both are
great marriage brokers.
Ms. Deng!
-Hurry!
-Ms. Deng! Ms. Deng!
-Bring water! Hurry!
Lu, what should we do?
Ke, leave.
I lost my way.
-Ke, it's dangerous!
-Ms. Deng!
Ms. Deng!
I was...
I was wrong.
Ms. Deng!
Ms. Deng.