=Love in the Edge of Divorce=
=Episode 27=
(Emergency, First Aid)
Thank you for today.
If you hadn't arrived in time,
I don't know what would happen.
Xiao Yang failed today.
He'll try to hurt you again.
Sheng Mian, move in with me.
Wen Zhao, what's wrong?
Do you feel unwell?
Yes, a little bit.
I feel suffocated.
I can't breathe.
What's your problem?
I got hit on the head.
It aches again.
Is it the after-effect?
My chest is so tight.
I can hardly breathe.
I feel really bad.
My chest hurts.
I can't move my arm.
Is it broken?
Why can't I feel my leg?
I...
Am I paralyzed?
Will I be paraplegic?
Your CT reports have come out.
You're both OK.
Just some bruises.
You need some ointment.
Oh, Sheng Mian.
It's getting late.
I'll drive you home.
OK.
Let's go.
Stay safe.
Thanks for driving me back.
It's late.
You go home.
OK. I'll watch to make sure you go in.
Bye-bye.
Welcome home.
How did you get in?
We're a couple.
I certainly walked in here.
Don't bother about that.
You didn't have dinner. Taste it.
Did you make the dishes?
Come on.
What happened?
Nothing.
I cut my finger when I cooked.
How careless.
If I remember correctly,
it's the bamboo shoot
from Maqiji Restaurant.
This is the stewed chicken
from Wangtian Restaurant.
This is the spicy pork
from Tai Restaurant.
And this.
I also tasted it.
So, which one is your dish?
Sheng Mian,
I wanted you to have hot dishes
when you came back.
So, I went to your favorite restaurants
for signature dishes.
And your finger?
I indeed cooked for you.
Then, I cut some fruit.
It's still in the fridge.
Where's the cut?
I'm a man.
Such a minor cut
recovered very soon.
Give it to me.
What?
My spare key.
What if I don't?
Then, I'll move away.
Drop the act.
The doctor said you're OK.
Sometimes, the doctor is wrong.
And I haven't done checkups.
Maybe something's wrong.
My chest hurts.
My heart hurts.
I can hardly breathe.
You may have a heart problem
because you have too many schemes.
You act quite poorly.
Go back and practice more.
The doctor said you're OK.
You just had bruises.
You can't fool me.
Like I said,
I haven't done checkups.
Since ancient times,
no man has confessed his weakness
in front of his romantic rival.
A man will only let down his guard
in front of his sweetheart.
Fine.
I'll call Qi Chen.
He'll take you to the hospital
for a full checkup.
No need.
I'll just lie in your bed for a while.
Fu Yancheng, come back!
Fu Yancheng, why did you get in here?
Sheng Mian,
your bed feels so good.
I feel all right now.
Get up.
You get up.
Don't pretend to be sick. Get up.
I'm not pretending.
I have lovesickness.
Your scent is my miracle cure.
Then, smell it more.
I contacted Chinese and foreign clients.
They'll buy our products.
We'll accomplish our goal.
What's wrong?
What's on your mind?
My father had a wish.
He wanted to invent
a children's fabric
green, breathable, and waterproof.
But before his wish came true,
he passed away.
Wen Zhao,
can we...?
Sheng Mian,
our top priority
is to attain our goal
within a month.
It's not time to put our energy or money
on the research.
I see.
Sheng Mian,
don't worry.
I'll help you accomplish it.
For everything else,
after you hold down your job,
we'll sort it out.
OK?
OK.
I'll go back to work.
(Grandpa Fu)
Mian, did you quarrel with Yancheng?
The other day, he came back
and took away his passport.
He didn't tell me where he would go.
I got information from the airlines.
He flew to Europe
and then North America.
He's flying all over the world.
Has something happened?
When we had the video chat,
everything was OK.
Grandpa,
don't worry.
We're doing all right.
He must have gone out for an emergency.
Oh, I see.
Glad you're all right.
OK.
What has Fu Yancheng been doing lately?
Why would I think of him?
(I always wanted)
(to draw the line with him.)
(Now, I finally get what I want.)
(I should be happy.)
♪The sky is enormous♪
♪The sun melts the stars♪
(Michelle Corp)
(developed a new kind of fabric)
(green, breathable, and waterproof,)
(and filed a patent.)
♪It's no longer bustling♪
♪Eternal or transient♪
♪It's all about you♪
♪You, it was always you♪
♪It's not a secret♪
♪It was only you♪
♪I listen to you,
watch you, and follow you♪
Do you miss me?
You...
♪My life starts to shine♪
♪I dream of you,
think of you, and love you♪
♪You're who you are, so...♪
Is this what you want?
How do you know I want this?
I know everything I want to know.
I had a hard time
to get this fabric for you.
Check if this is it.
♪Time never stops♪
♪It fluctuates like a wave♪
♪You always make ripples♪
♪I keep smoothing them♪
♪The poem between lovers♪
♪Lingers in my mind♪
♪It's about destiny and miracle♪
You haven't said if you miss me.
Yes.
I almost forgot you.
♪It's not a secret♪
I guess it's time to relive the past
and remind you of everything.
♪I dream of you,
think of you, and love you♪
♪Nobody but you♪
♪Gives me such a great life♪
♪You're the only one I need♪
♪You're the only one I want♪
♪You're the only one I see♪
♪You're the only one I dream♪
I can hardly breathe.
Then, I'll give you mouth-to-mouth.
Stop it.
I have an important meeting tomorrow.
I'll go get prepared.
♪The only dream I dream is always you♪
♪You♪
♪The one and only♪
Ms. Sheng has worked
for only half a month.
But our sales
have increased by 25%.
I believe under her guidance,
our company will go through a new peak.
Then, Ms. Sheng, please explain
why we have more orders
but a far lower annual rate.
I spent some money
on Michelle's patented fabric
to fulfill Dad's wish.
You bought a patent?
Do you know how much it costs?
You don't own this company alone.
Don't make everyone
pay for your idea.
It's not a month yet.
Sheng Mian is still in charge.
In my opinion,
it's time for her
to quit her job now.
I dare you.
♪Cross the border of the rain♪
♪To sunny days you've experienced♪
♪As a light shines♪
♪I think of your gentle prophecy♪
♪You'll beat everything♪
♪And come all the way to me♪
♪In the fairy tale world♪
♪The sweet story♪
♪Will last forever♪
♪When beautiful things disappear♪
♪When the world is sleepless♪
♪Will you dream of meeting again?♪
♪Or will you pity our separation?♪
♪I break into the page where you are on♪
♪When the wind blows
in the seaside forest♪
♪Half of the moon lights
up the other half of the world♪
♪Someday you and I have never been♪
♪I unknowingly turn the page you're on♪
♪Half of the fairy tale
will disappear before it's done♪
♪The eternal story in my mind♪
♪Turns out to be unfinished♪