=Love in the Edge of Divorce=
=Episode 11=
(Penny, Design Director)
Hello.
Penny, what's up?
Send me the proposal for Lanyang.
OK. I'm on it.
Oh, Penny.
Do you know where I am?
Where are you?
At Fu Yancheng's villa.
He invited me over for a drink.
(Oh no.)
(I haven't told Liang Hanqing
about the husband thing.)
I'll be right there.
I have something to tell you.
OK. I'll be waiting.
I'll hang up.
Mr. Fu, you chose our studio
to design your villa.
This is really my honor.
You're being modest.
You have Penny, such a good designer.
I'm quite jealous
of your career and family.
That's right. Umm...
Fa... Family?
Hanqing.
Here I am.
Penny, what took you so long?
Come have a seat.
Mr. Fu and I
are talking happily.
Mr. Fu, why did you
suddenly invite Hanqing over?
Mr. Liang made efforts at my villa.
So, I invited him over
- for a drink.
- Thank you.
I'm quite curious.
When did you meet each other?
Penny and I
met in college.
At that time,
she was a very good student.
She studied very well
and did part-time jobs.
So, I knew
she would be a success.
After she graduated,
she rejected the offer
from big companies
and started a business with me.
When you first started a business,
did you think of getting closer?
Getting closer?
Yeah.
We not only got closer
but also got better.
Right, Hanqing?
That's right.
We need to do better.
A toast to you.
Very well.
When I first got to know you,
I didn't know you were a couple.
We didn't want people to gossip.
You know.
If privacy and business mix,
it'll be confusing.
How could you be so careless?
Let me wipe it.
Pretend we're a couple.
Don't give ourselves away.
I'll explain later.
Don't drink too much.
Penny asked me not to drink too much.
That's good.
Are you cold?
No, Mr. Fu.
No need, Mr. Fu.
Don't move.
Mr. Fu,
are you cold?
Put on my coat.
The Spring Hotel owned by the Fu's
will open next week.
It offers many relaxing services.
You have to come.
No, thanks, Mr. Fu.
You're invited, too.
You also have to come.
A real man, indeed.
Penny,
isn't it inappropriate?
Here he comes.
Smile.
I can't smile.
You have to.
I...
Honey, are you OK?
Come and let me see.
Come on.
Are you OK?
Don't move.
Hug me.
Hug me. Come on.
Right now,
come to the lounge.
Did he leave?
Yes.
Will we give ourselves away?
I don't think so.
He was too far to see.
Fine.
I'll go get a drink.
Sorry, sir.
Your pool is in need of repairs.
Please move to another pool.
- Please come.
- It was all right just now.
- Why...?
- Come, please.
Come on.
♪Time never stops♪
♪It fluctuates like a wave♪
♪You always make ripples♪
♪I keep smoothing them♪
♪The poem between lovers♪
♪Lingers in my mind♪
♪It's about destiny and miracle♪
♪The whole world is about you♪
♪You, it was always you♪
♪It's not a secret♪
♪It was only you♪
♪I listen to you,
watch you, and follow you♪
♪Because of you♪
♪My life starts to shine♪
♪I dream of you,
think of you, and love you♪
♪Nobody but you♪
♪Gives me such a great life♪
What do you want?
It's the girl's locker room.
Are you insane?
What do you like about Liang?
I'm better than him in every way.
Penny.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
You go out.
I'll wait out there.
Mr. Fu,
what's bothering you?
Qi Chen,
I have a friend.
The woman he loves ignores him.
She only stays with her husband.
Mr. Fu,
I think you should...
No.
Your friend should
keep her working overtime at midnight.
She'll stay away from her husband.
By then, your friend
can do something.
He'll succeed.
Mr. Fu.
I got you here so late.
I'm sorry.
Did I disturb your sweet hours
with your husband?
It's OK, Mr. Fu.
This is my job.
Be seated.
I got you over urgently
because I want to discuss with you
the decoration style.
Today, I had some inspiration.
You know.
When I have inspiration,
I must talk to you about it.
Only in this way
can we find a spark.
Got it.
Mr. Fu,
go ahead.
For my living room,
I want the style of ancient Egypt.
The furniture
should be made of wood
with simple and low lines
as well as round corners.
The floor should
be made of terra-cotta or bricks.
For the bedrooms,
I want the style of ancient Rome.
It should be simple and majestic.
The most popular cedar wood will be used.
Only in this way can the house
bring out the best in me.
Mr. Fu, the style of the living room
is actually the Mediterranean style.
The style of the bedrooms
is actually from old Egypt.
People
sometimes have the wrong inspiration.
I get it.
Anyway,
you want me to redesign
your villa.
Right?
Right.
No problem.
(Documents of Interior Decoration)
Mr. Fu,
I've modified the design
and emailed it to you.
My work is done. I should go.
Who said it's done?
You need to read these documents.
We're on a serious time crunch.
These days, you'll have to stay and work.
I'll finish my job.
(You must be taking revenge.)
(How narrow-minded.)
(Documents of Interior Decoration)
♪Cross the border of the rain♪
♪To sunny days you've experienced♪
♪As a light shines♪
♪I think of your gentle prophecy♪
♪You'll beat everything♪
♪And come all the way to me♪
♪In the fairy tale world♪
♪The sweet story♪
♪Will last forever♪
♪When beautiful things disappear♪
♪When the world is sleepless♪
♪Will you dream of meeting again?♪
♪Or will you pity our separation?♪
♪I break into the page where you are on♪
♪When the wind blows
in the seaside forest♪
♪Half of the moon lights
up the other half of the world♪
♪Someday you and I have never been♪
♪I unknowingly turn the page you're on♪
♪Half of the fairy tale
will disappear before it's done♪
♪The eternal story in my mind♪
♪Turns out to be unfinished♪