["Love in the Moonlight"]
["Itaewon Class"]
["The Sound of Magic"]
♫ Like the stars in the sky ♫
[Young Actors' Retreat]
[Young Actors' Retreat - The Third Story]
["A Dramatic Summer Night"]
It's three against three against three.
[A game with dinner on the line, "Answer Consecutively"]
Because right now, we have a three-way tie at 3:3:3...
the team that answers the last prompt
will become the winner of Game A.
Like the word "jwipo,"
("jwipo" means dried filefish, but the first character "jwi" also means mouse)
- What?
- what's food that's not actually made
with the ingredient in its name?
This is hard!
[The highly-difficult prompt for the last question flusters everyone]
...with the ingredient in its name?
Danmuji!
[Already...?]
Boonguh bread!
(Boonguh = translated as carp bread, but it is made with red beans, not carp meat)
S-Squid bread!
- Incorrect!
- Squid bread!
- Incorrect.
- Why is it wrong?
[There's squid in squid bread]
- Danmuji!
- Nalwoochoban! Hanchi bread!
(Hanchi = Arrow Squid)
[Staff] There's hanchi in hanchi bread.
I don't think hanchi bread has hanchi in it.
I've eaten a lot of hanchi bread.
There is hanchi in it.
[Jeju buckwheat | mozzarella cheese | hanchi]
[Chagrin]
- I've eaten it many times, though.
- There is hanchi in it.
- Danmuji!
- Danmuji! Danmuji!
- Boonguh bread!
- Chrysanthemum bread!
- Yinguh bread.
- Poop bread!
(Yinguh = European Carp)
Banana bread!
- Banana bread...
- Banana what?
[Banana bread from the olden days don't have bananas]
There's none! There's none!
- Banana bread has banana in it.
- What?
[Banana bread these days have bananas in them]
- But it doesn't even taste like bananas.
- I've never had banana bread that had bananas in it.
Bananas are in it? Real bananas?
Nowadays, there is Banana in Banana bread.
[Banana bread with bananas in them are currently being sold]
That's so unfair!
My childhood memories are to blame.
[So entertaining]
- Nalwoochoban! Nalwoochoban.
- Nalwoochoban!
- Sora bread.
- Boonguh bread.
(Sora = Conch shell)
- Yinguh bread.
- Pokemon bread!
Guk Jjin bread!
There could be a pokemon inside!
[Nervous | Anxious]
Correct!
[Nalwoochoban gets the correct answer!]
[Bummed]
[Eyebrow dance]
- It's okay. It's okay.
- It's okay, it's okay. It's okay.
- It was the last prompt.
- Correct.
["Answer Consecutively"]
[Nalwoochoban wins]
Nice.
[Winner's spirit already]
- Well done, well done.
- That was a win.
[Accepts the game results]
We're good at this.
Thus,
- the total score for "Answer Consecutively" is...
- We have a knack for games.
Team Cheongbaji, three points. Team Danmuji, three points. Team Nalwoochoban, four points.
Not too big of a difference.
[Not much of a difference]
This isn't the final score.
We'll play a second game
and combine the score from that one,
- to determine the final winner.
- Winning is more than possible then.
We have three points, so we're still in this.
[A turnaround is more than possible]
[Staff] The second game we're going to play is...
"Elephant Nose! Water Gun Shooting!"
What's that?
Water gun shooting?
[Staff] There's no need to shoot it properly. Just lightly...
- No need to shoot it properly.
- I think we're all going to shoot properly.
I'm ready to fire.
[Sergeant Park, ready to fire]
I think we're all going to shoot properly.
But not directly at the face, right?
"Elephant Nose! Water Gun!" is...
[Directly at the face]
[Three targets and three players from each team]
After the players do 15 elephant nose spins,
they'll bring the water gun
and the first team to shoot the water gun
at the face of the other team's target players will win.
First place gets three points, second place gets one point,
and third place will get zero points.
[Completely understands]
Shoot the other team first?
["Elephant Nose! Water Gun!"]
[Men's Round]
[Three targets]
Come at me.
[Nalwoochoban - Ryu Kyung Soo | Cheongbaji - Park Bo Gum | Danmuji - Park Seo Joon]
We can just shoot from here, too?
[Three players]
We can shoot sitting down, right?
- Kwak Dong Yeon, fighting!
- Yeah!
Fighting!
- Fighting!
[Danmuji - Kwak Dong Yeon]
- "Youth...
- "Youth Is Now"!
Hwang In Yeop, fighting!
Get it together! Get it together.
[Cheongbaji - Hwang In Yeop]
- Jinyoung, fighting!
- Fighting!
I'm really bad at this.
[Nalwoochoban - Jinyoung]
Just looking at them makes me dizzy.
[Three people who must do 15 elephant nose spins]
[Three people about to be shot at with water guns]
[Dry lips]
Huh? What the?
[Start]
- Two... Three...
- Four... Five...
Six...
[Dizzy already]
- Nine...
[The audience of the three teams observing the other teams' players]
[The only one about to bounce out]
Thirteen...
Whoa!
One more spin! Jinyoung, one more spin!
Good!
[One spin]
One more spin! Jinyoung, one more spin!
Good! Good.
[Innocent Dong Yeon spins one more time]
- Good!
- It's enough!
[15, 16]
That's enough! Stop! Stop!
[Stop spinning, stop!]
[Hurriedly, in a rush]
[Dong Yeon has the lead]
[His target is...]
[Nervous]
[Lips tight]
[Bo Gum, Cheongbaji]
"If there's one person I have to trust in this world, it would be you."
[Dong Yeon even gave his life for Bo Gum in the drama...]
[but shoots Bo Gum's face in reality for pork belly]
[Seriously betrayed by Dong Yeon, who he trusted]
[Your Highness...]
[One more person while he's on the job]
[Why me, too...]
[Dong Yeon is first place!]
[However, they're still fighting for second place]
[Falling down]
[In Yeop is on the chase]
[Who'll be the one to take second place?]
[Totally excited]
[In Yeop, who was staggering along...]
It's over, right?
[trips on his own leg and falls]
[Seo Joon - Jinyoung]
[Splashed with water while shouting joyfully]
-That's it, right?
- It's over, right?
[The first match for men, finished]
I couldn't shoot...
[In Yeop, Cheongbaji]
I can't see...
I can't see.
First place is Kwak Dong Yeon.
[Gaining three points]
Second place is Jinyoung.
[Second place: Jinyoung of Team Nalwoochoban]
Fighting, Jinyoung!
- Third place is Hwang In Yeop.
- I couldn't shoot.
- It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
[Lost, but fought well]
You did well.
- It's fine!
- It's okay. It's okay.
[Not okay]
Why did you shoot two people, Dong Yeon?
Don't you win by shooting more people?
[It's okay]
- Be careful.
- Fighting!
["Elephant Nose! Water Gun!"]
[Women's Round]
Is it better to spin slowly?
No, you have to...
If you spin fast
[Dong Yeon, an expert first place, gives out tips]
focus on a point on the ground.
[Dong Yeon's tips]
- Ah, just one point?
- Yes, something like that water gun on the ground.
[1. Choose a reference point before you spin]
- Okay, while looking at the water gun...
- And don't take steps that are too big.
[2. Spin with small steps]
Since you can fall while spinning in big steps...
We're all from the Sound of Magic!
[Three players]
They're all from Team Magic.
Wait, that's true.
- Ji Hae Won, fighting!
- Fighting!
[Ji Hae Won of Team Danmuji]
Sung Eun, fighting!
[Choi Sung Eun of Team Cheongbaji]
Kim Bo Yoon, fighting!
Fighting!
[Misses the beat]
[Kim Bo Yoon of Team Nalwoochoban]
- Dong Yeon, will you be okay?
- Sure.
[Time for changing the targets]
It's okay. It's okay.
Seriously, don't be like this.
[You did well, I'll take it from here]
No, really...
[Young-On couple's love is stronger than the water gun]
- It's really okay. I'll do it.
- You don't have to.
[Bo Gum came right back.]
It's okay, really.
[Nalwoochoban - Ji Chang Wook | Danmuji - Kwak Dong Yeon | Cheongbaji - Park Bo Gum]
[Dong Yeon runs to his teammate, Hae Won]
He's giving her tips?
- Spin to your left.
- To the left.
If you spin to the right, you'll go right.
- So turn left and think about shooting Ji Chang Wook Sunbae.
- Okay. Okay.
[Dong Yeon, Danmuji]
Do it like that!
[Being happy without knowing anything]
What are they whispering?
Making plans for this kind of thing is difficult.
[Preparations complete]
You've got it!
[Start]
- Two...
- I don't think this is going to work.
- Three...
- Four...
- Seven, eight...
- Nine...
- Nine.
- Seung Eun, fighting.
Choi Sung Eun, fighting!
You're done!
You're done, go, go.
Go!
Twelve! Oh, wait─
[Everyone has finished with the elephant nose?]
- Calm down now! Calm down!
- Focus!
That's it! That's it.
[Splat]
- Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
- Shoot! Shoot! Second place is still open!
[The sole leader]
[We lost the first place...]
Whoa!
[Sung Eun, who took the lead above everyone...]
[hits Kwak Dong Yeon right on target]
[Choi Sung Eun is the first place]
Shoot! Shoot! Second place is still open!
[On the other hand, Bo Yoon, who fell completely...]
[can't recover]
[Roadblock]
[Hae Won, who sprinted out in second place...]
[hits Chang Wook right on target as planned]
Nice, nice, nice.
Nice, it didn't work.
- Well done, well done!
- I did it!
[Finish]
- You did a good job.
- How many times did I spin?
- I think you spun like 16 times.
- What? Really?
-You did a good job.
[Rather a satisfactory result for Team Danmuji]
- Was it 16 or 17?
- I spun too many times.
Whoa! I really...
[Couldn't hit anyone in the end...]
You're really dizzy, right?
How did you do it?
Hold on. Your shoelaces...
No, no. I-I'll do it for you.
No need to bend down.
[Joo Young's mom during the day and Bo Yoon's mom at night]
- Yes, yes.
- You're all set.
[Such a sweetie, Kwon Nara]
I'll reveal the results of the game now.
[Women's game results]
[Smirk]
First place is Ji Hae Won.
[Daebak]
You did so well!
First place is Ji Hae Won.
Really?
- Didn't we shoot first?
- Weren't we the ones who shot first?
[Staff] Choi Sung Eun only spun 10 times around.
I spun 15 times... Maybe I didn't?
[Out of her mind from the dizziness]
Really?
- [Staff] So you're disqualified and at third place.
- Oh, really?
Oh no.
[Shocked]
It's okay! It's okay.
[Third place is Choi Sung Eun of Team Choengbaji, gaining zero points]
That's too bad...
[Aww...]
Bo Yoon is in second place.
[Second place: Kim Bo Yoon of Team Nalwoochoban]
[Final results of the evening games]
[Third place: Team Cheongbaji]
[Answer Consecutively: 0 pts, Elephant: 3 pts, Total: 3 pts]
It's okay, it's okay.
[Second place: Team Nalwoochoban]
[Consecutively: 4 pts, Elephant: 2 pts, Total: 6 pts]
[First place: Team Danmuji]
[Consecutively: 3 pts, Elephant: 6 pts, Total: 9 pts]
Wait, is this... is this the end?
[Staff] Then, we'll go and eat dinner now.
[Their expressions show their chagrin]
[Let's go eat]
[The fierce games of Actors's Retreat for the dinner menu end]
[Dinner Time]
Everyone, great job with the games.
Applause for our first place team, Team Danmuji.
[Sashimi set, kimchi jjigae, Jeju black pork BBQ]
[Brilliant]
Our second place team─
[Second place: Team Nalwoochoban]
[Second place]
[Spicy braised seafood and]
[Ramen, which can't be missing at an retreat]
The third-place team!
[The dinner menu for Team Cheongbaji, the third place is...]
[Rice, gochujang, sesame oil, dry seaweed]
[and that's it...]
[On the other hand, Jeju black pork BBQ that's being cooked on the spot]
♫  Us against the world ♫
[Wishful thinking for the second and third place teams]
[A famous restaurant owner is cooking it himself]
[Staff] The meat happened to be cooked next to the third-place team!
What to do, the smell of the food must keep making them look in that direction.
[Disappointed...]
[Although they try to smile, their eyes are already wet...]
- So cruel!
- You're so evil.
- Enjoy your meal!
- This looks so good.
Thank you for the food!
[Time to dig in]
- Shall we eat?
- Let's eat the sashimi first!
It's going to take a while for this one to boil.
[First place, Team Danmuji, tries the sashimi while the meat cooks]
[Picks up one piece of sashimi]
Whoa, this is it.
[Her eyebrows tell the truth]
It's delicious. The sashimi is really good.
[Team leader of Danmuji, Seo Joon, also tries the sashimi]
[Eye-opening]
[Chewing]
[One more piece right after!]
I'll probably have indigestion.
[And sad to leave out of a retreat...]
- Oh my!
- Wow!
[Pow]
- Oh my!
- Wow!
[Drop]
[Short-lived deviation of the bottle cap]
Good work, everyone.
[While Team Danmuji enjoys sashimi and beer...]
The mood feels really different, doesn't it?
Thank you!
[At the second place team, Nalwoochoban's table...]
You cut them like this...
[Team Leader Chang Wook himself]
[cuts the seafood]
It looks really good.
I know, right.
[He bones the clam meat]
- My friends, dig in now!
- Okay.
[Yum]
It's really good.
The braised seafood is really nice.
It's good.
[Glancing]
[Next menu after braised seafood]
The ramen is going to be really good, what do we do?
[The flower of a retreat, ramen]
[Full of chewy noodles]
Wow!
[Whoa, Gasp, Wow]
[Glancing]
I love al dente ramen noodles.
[Slurp]
- It's so delicious.
- It's really so delicious.
[Blissful]
[Sad]
[Drips the sesame seed oil]
The sesame oil right from the start...
- She was the test subject.
- The sesame oil got me too.
Aigoo.
[The one who quietly poured the sesame seed oil first]
Me too. A little bit...
- Please enjoy your meal.
Thanks for the meal.
It looks tasty.
[Pouring in the simple ingredients of rice, gochujang, sesame seed oil]
[Takes a sad bite]
Does anyone care for some beer?
A beer, is there anyone?
[At least beer is fair for everyone]
Whoa! Aigoo!
[Gurgling]
I have napkins here.
Are you okay?
- Even the beer spills for our team...!
- That team has such bad luck.
- and we also don't have meat...!
- You didn't shake it
- before you gave it to us, right?
- It spilled everywhere.
[Why does this only happen to Team Cheongbaji...]
It's pretty warm.
W-What?
[Flapping]
- The dried seaweed is flying away...
- It's so sad.
The dried seaweed is flying away...
[A lot has flown away...]
- Dried seaweed is good.
- Let's still toast, saying "Cheongbaji"
with confidence!
- Of course.
- Are we really going to?
Let's go.
Ready, set...
Youth is now!
[We're okay... we're okay...]
I'm so embarrassed.
My heart breaks...
Stay strong.
The rice is...
kind of like barley rice!
- Right.
- It's really good, though.
[Really delicious]
[Team Cheongbaji still enjoys their meal, despite its shabbiness]
[Among them, the sole leader, "Eat" Bo Gum]
[Big bite]
They should give more rice, at least, right?
- Wouldn't rice be all-you-can-eat?
- That's true.
[Finishes rice in relief]
[After clearing the rice, his eyes look to...]
[hmmm...]
[First place team's meat]
[Flutter]
[Jeju black pork is grilled golden brown]
[Served to the first place team's table]
Wow. I've been looking forward to this.
This is the salted seafood that I told you about and...
it goes well with the meat.
[Can't take their eyes off of them...]
It's good if you eat with this.
[On top of the well-cooked meat, plus the salted pollack roe]
Dip this here.
[plus wasabi]
Do I put this on, too?
[plus pickled bracken]
[and lastly, the salted melons]
Oh my god.
[Electrified]
It's almost like art how the flavors come together.
[Smiles spill out of her face]
It's really delicious.
Whoa, this is really good.
- What's this?
- It's so good!
What's this, seriously?
[Team Cheongbaji on the next table are watching the mukbang]
[The mindless glancing type]
[With his Adam's apple reacting]
[The miser type, eating rice while looking at the meat]
[Would pay to watch]
[Salivating mouth, wide open]
[Smirks]
Didn't we agree not to look over there?
Did we say that?
Yeah, we did.
Okay, let's eat with confidence.
[I'm not jealous... not even the slightest...]
- This tastes good, right?
- Yes! So good.
[Team Nalwoochoban is still praising the braised seafood]
The seasoning was so good.
[Still praising the seafood stew]
It's like a mukbang.
Kyung Soo, is it delicious?
It's delicious.
[Jinyoung replies, "It's really delicious"]
It does look delicious.
Do you want some since we have a lot?
[Can I receive the other teams' foods?]
[Keeps looking to the staff for approval]
[Staff: ...]
[Deep in thought]
- We've got a little too much braised seafood.
- Yeah, right.
I think it's not fitting... for the sentiment nowadays...
to have leftovers of this precious food.
I'm so touched.
- It's really good.
- The braised seafood...
In that case, let's make it simple.
[A special offer for Team Cheongbaji]
One success with the "Perfect Pitch" game gets you one bowl of any food you want.
The one where you go, "Tomato, tOmato, toMato...", like that?
Yes, that's correct. "Perfect Pitch."
If all five of you do it within the time limit of two minutes,
we'll allow you a "one-bowl-full-of-food voucher" for any food.
We have two minutes. So take your time.
[The word: big chestnut sweet red bean bread]
Two minutes are longer than you think.
[Big chestnut red bean bread]
Big chestnut red bean brea─
That's quite hard to do without looking at the word...
That's really difficult, wow.
[Everyone is focused on Team Cheongbaji]
[Crunch, crunch]
[except this man, who's focused on lettuce]
[Staff] I'm sorry, Team Leader Park Seo Joon, but could you look this way?
[Totally into the food]
Look at them for a second.
Please don't talk to me.
[Busy eating]
[Joking]
Now...
[There's only one chance. Will they succeed?]
You have two minutes. Ready...
Sta...
Big chestnut sweet red bean bread.
[The staff is taken aback]
We didn't start yet.
I was going hard at it...
Ready, set, start!
Big Chestnut Sweet Red bea...
- Wrong!
- Slowly. Do it again. You can do it!
Big chestnut sweet red bean bread.
big Chestnut sweet red bean bread.
big chestnut Sweet red bean bread.
big chestnut sweet Red bean bread.
big chestnut sweet red bean Bread.
Big chestnut sweet red bean bread.
big Chestnut sweet red bean bread.
big chestnut Sweet red bean bread.
big chestnut sweet Red bean bread.
big chestnut sweet red bean Bread.
Big chestnut sweet red bean bread.
big Chestnut sweet red bean bread.
big chestnut Sweet red bean bread.
big chestnut sweet Red bean bread.
big chestnut sweet red bean Bread.
Big chestnut sweet red bean bread.
big Chestnut sweet red bean bread.
big chestnut Sweet red bean bread.
big chestnut sweet Red bean bread.
big chestnut sweet red bean Bread
[Only if Bo Gum passes, they get the "one-bowl-full-of-food voucher"]
[What's the end of this challenge that even Seo Joon is watching?]
Big Chestnut sweet red bean bread.
big chestnut Sweet red bean bread.
big chestnut sweet Red bean Bread!
[Attempts "Perfect Pitch" while biting his lips cutely]
[Applauds right away without second thought]
Is it a success?
[Staff is discussing among themselves]
[Staff] Some of them think it was unclear.
- What was?
- Which part?
First and second place teams, what do you think?
[The judgment is now up to the first and second place teams]
- It was accurate and precise to me. Yes.
- It was accurate?
- You think so?
- They were so accurate!
It's really difficult...
It was clear.
[Thanks to the two teams, Team Cheongbaji succeeds!]
Whoa...
- Get the meat.
- Thanks for the food.
[In his socks]
How should I... Oh, with this?
[Obtained the bowl]
Bo Gum, you need to wear your shoes...
- He must have been hungry.
- Could you please?
[Does not care]
- Meat?
- He went out barefoot...
Put your shoes on, Hyung.
["Eat" Bo Gum the Barefoot]
- Yes.
- Okay.
[Shyly presents the bowl that he went out to get while barefoot]
- You can give me all of it.
- Okay.
[Just happy]
[One bowl completely filled!]
Big sweet red bean bread...
- Please have some.
- Thanks.
It's delicious!
It's delicious.
[Moved]
You're right. It's way too tasty.
- This is really good.
- It's really tasty.
[Ju Young eats one big ssam (meat wrapped in leafy greens)]
It's so great.
[Dilated eyes]
It's great...
- It's really delicious.
- I'm glad you like it.
[Glad]
[Glances]
[Staff] If Team Nalwoochoban also wants some meat, we'll let you challenge for the voucher.
- Meat?
- For us?
Do you guys want to eat some?
[A chance for Team Nalwoochoban to also have some Jeju black pork BBQ]
- Shall we try?
- Sure.
- Yes! We'll try it.
-There's no way we could say no to eating.
[Challenges "Perfect Pitch"]
- Shall we go for it?
- Yes.
- Kyung Soo, do you want to go first? Should I go first?
- Yes!
Me first?
Hyung, you should start by saying Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh?
[Challenge direction]
Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh?
- Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh?
- Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
[The word: Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh]
- Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh?
- It's easy. Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
kung-Duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-Ruh-ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-ruh-Ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-ruh-ruh-Ruh.
[Yum]
You left one out, I think?
Really?
[Seo Joon doesn't know about that!]
Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh...
Ready, set, start!
[What about Team Leader Chang Wook's Nalwoochoban...?]
Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
kung-Duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-Ruh-ruh-ruh.
- Nice going.
- kung-duh-ruh-Ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
[Kung-duh-ruh-ruh... ruh, brain freeze]
Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh...
He did it!
He's broken...
- Wait a minute!
- You did it.
Hold on. Time out.
[Time out]
Time out. The word is...
The word is a bit mysterious.
You start first.
[Resumes the game]
Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh. kung-Duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-Ruh-ruh-ruh. kung-duh-ruh-Ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-ruh-ruh-Ruh.
Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh. kung-Duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-Ruh-ruh-ruh...
[Fast-forwarding three times because they're too good]
[Passes through Nara]
Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh. kung-Duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-Ruh-ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-ruh-Ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-ruh-ruh-Ruh.
[Youngest Bo Yoon also flies by]
Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh...
[What about the team leader Chang Wook?]
Kung-duh-ruh-ruh-ruh. kung-Duh-ruh-ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-Ruh-ruh-ruh. kung-duh-ruh-Ruh-ruh.
kung-duh-ruh-ruh-Ruh.
[Chang Wook also passes, earning five coins as well]
Success!
[Team Nalwoochoban succeeds nice and neat]
I'll give you the meal ticket.
[Earns Jeju black pork]
I ate too much.
Isn't the meat so delicious?
This is great, seriously!
Shall we make a toast?
- Just us, you know?
- Yes!
- Yes, sure.
Please raise your glasses!
Anyhow, I know it's just us here, but thank you
[Fill-in, Kyung Ho] for comfortably playing with me too. And I think I was able to
- have fun, thanks─
- I'm sorry, but did you come as the instructor today?
[The perfect comparison]
Shall we make a toast to "Danmuji"?
It's a bit embarrassing to just say cheers.
[A clever professor material]
Have a good time tomorrow and the day after, too.
- Thank you.
- It was nice to meet you.
- Shall we make a toast on "Nice to meet you"?
- Sure.
One, two, three!
Nice to meet you!
Whoa, Hyung...
[Although the first meeting was awkward...]
[The youths got closer while playing games and eating together]
It's the youth because you wish for more.
["It's the youth because you wish for more" - Professor Yoon]
[The harmonious and fun dinner is over]
[The first night of the Retreat deepens...]
I wonder where we're going this late at night.
[Through this pitch-black darkness, three cars head somewhere]
Ah, what's waiting for us?
We're driving for 38 minutes?
What? 38 minutes?
- We're going further than I expected...
- You're right.
Seriously, what game are they going to make us play this far out?
Is it a haunted house experience?
Doesn't it feel like they would do something like that?
A real haunted house experience...
[At that very moment...]
[Mysterious friends are waiting for the members]
[Youth horror story | Coming Soon]
[In the darkness, Team Nalwoochoban is...]
You know...
I think it's so nice that we can talk like this when we met for the first time.
[Jinyoung, Nalwoochoban]
- Yeah.
- That's true.
Oppa, you're "I," right?
[MBTI]
Me? I'm "I."
(I personality = introverted)
What about you, Oppa? "I"?
I'm "E."
(E personality = extroverted)
- I'm also "E."
- Oh, really?
And you?
I'm "I."
- Three "I"s and two "E"s...
- Don't we look like "I"s?
I'm an "I".
[Unexpectedly introverted trio]
But isn't this more like...
[LOL]
- You're laughing?
- No, no.
[Kidding, kidding]
This team is so funny!
[You're mistaken, Sunbaenim]
I'm an "I" type who tends to be a bit more social.
- Fortunately, Kyung Soo did a drama with me before.
- Right.
["Lovestruck in the City"]
- Nara, you, too, did one with me.
- Right.
["Suspicious Partner"]
Bo Yoon also did one with me.
["The Sound of Magic"]
And I've heard about Jinyoung a lot from a close friend of mine.
- So I was a bit...
- Oh, from a friend?
[He's glad to meet his fellow actors again at Young Actors' Retreat]
So I was really relieved.
There's something I really wanted to know.
[Nara] You know how Chang Wook Sunbae makes you feel at ease?
But on the other hand... Sometimes, did his kindness feel burdensome...
What I mean is, did it ever make you feel like he was unapproachable?
I was really curious because that was the case for me.
You were tough to approach for me.
I think I know what you mean, though.
So you're really gentle and nice, but...
[Can't hear]
- She says she knows what she means.
- No, no, it's okay.
[Hurt]
- To me, you know...
- Oh, I see.
I was a rookie, but you were a sunbaenim I've only seen on TV...
He is hurt.
No, no. What I mean...
[Hurt]
I must have made a lot of mistakes...
[Chang Wook] - I just did my best to be nice, since they were younger friends.
- No, no.
A very nice and comfortable sunbaenim.
- Since it was so comfortable...
- She said, "I think I know what you mean, though."
I was fine with what Nara said, but
I was more hurt when you said you think you know.
She didn't say, "I'm fine with it, though." But said, "I think I know what you mean, though."
[Peace breaker]
[In the meantime, while Team Nalwoochoban's peace was breaking apart...]
No one here has ever seen a ghost, right?
[Team Cheongbaji starts the engine on scary stories]
I've seen a ghost before.
Yoo Jung said she has seen one before.
Tell us about that story.
It was while I was filming a historical drama.
[Youth Horror Story: "The Filming Set" by Yoo Jung]
It was when I was shooting the drama "Moon Embracing the Sun."
There are shaman ladies that come out on the drama.
[Yoo Jung] On that day, I was leaving after the shooting.
On the other side...
really far out on the other side...
there were three ladies
who play the shaman roles standing.
[Focuses]
"They must've come to do the shooting."
"I'll go say hi later," was what I thought,
but they were not there when I went.
[Gulp]
Later I was told that the shaman ladies were not scheduled for a shoot that day.
[Later she was told that the shaman ladies were not scheduled for a shoot that day]
[Grasps]
You're scared, too, Hyung?
You're not scared, are you?
It's not that. The seat belt keeps wrapping around my neck. Why is it like this?
I have a scary story about a car.
There are so many of those, like the one about the freeway...
- What's it about?
- The freeway one is really famous.
- You don't know the freeway story?
- No, I don't know.
This one is a true story.
[A true story?]
[Bo Gum] Supposedly, a man was going through a tunnel when the car kept shutting down.
He was wondering why the car kept shutting down, and it was in the middle of the night.
Then suddenly, thudding noises started coming from the car.
[Eyes shaking]
He was so scared,
he was like, "No, no!" and drove away as quickly as he could.
He's really selling it!
You're doing an excellent job!
[Bo Gum] So he dropped off the car at an auto shop.
The auto shop owner said, "There were so many handprints on the car."
And the car owner asked, "What do you mean"?
[In suspense]
But apparently, the handprints were on the inside of the car.
[What!]
They had tried to wipe down the handprints from the outside, but couldn't wipe them.
Because the handprints were made from the inside.
But how do you know that's a true story?
It has been passed down by word of mouth...
That's what people say.
[Meanwhile, Team Danmuji...]
My wife...
after we got married...
[Kyung Ho] It was the first time living with another person.
On a summer night,
something felt wrong, so I opened my eyes,
and my wife was just standing next to the bed like this.
Stop! Stop, stop!
- Who?
- My wife.
Oh, your wife.
[Kyung Ho] But it could be a sleeping habit I didn't know about, you know?
I was so scared.
I was like, "Honey! It's me!"
What's wrong?
[Kyung Ho] But she stood absolutely still, and she was holding something in her hand.
- In pitch darkness... Yeah.
- Like this?
Yeah. She's standing there like this. How scary is that?
I was thinking, does she have a sleepwalking problem?
So I was like, "Honey! What's wrong?"
[So... why was she like that?]
A mosquito.
It turned out she was holding a bug spray to kill the mosquito.
A mosquito. A mosquito.
[A completely unexpected turnaround]
- I'm going crazy.
- Oh, Sunbaenim.
She couldn't turn on the light because the mosquito would fly away and hide.
She was in that position to catch the mosquito?
Turns out that what she was holding was a bug spray.
You must have been pretty scared.
[Soon, the three cars enter a narrow road]
Oh, we must have arrived.
It's so dark...
[What's up...]
I have a feeling it's going to be difficult.
[...with this place?]
Man, we came to a strange place...
Oh, no, what is this? I really don't like this type of stuff...
I'm scared.
[But what exactly is this place that they've come to?]
Gosh!
I'm so scared!
I just got out of the car, and it's so scary!
- What is this?
- What the... there is a school here!
- Ah, what is this?
- This is crazy.
- Man, that school...
- It's an abandoned school...
- It looks like a Middle School.
[Just looking at it gives you the chills]
Ah, what is this?
It's bigger in scale than I expected.
[A deserted school]
I mean, what is this!
- And why are there tents?
- Tents?
Are they telling us to sleep here?
Hey, no way...
[Two tents are set up in front of the closed school]
- Sleeping outdoors?
- There's no way!
[Two tents are set up in front of the closed school]
- If something goes wrong, do we have to sleep here?
- In the tents?
What are those tents?
I know, right?
My goodness, there are actually sleeping bags in the tents!
- Wait, really?
- There are two or three sleeping bags in each tent.
- Don't joke around like that.
It's probably for the production staff to sleep there...
Each team has five members, right?
I think they have two tents, one for female members and one for male members.
- Whoa!
- What is that!
[The thing that scared everyone is...]
- That startled me!
- What? What happened?
[The thing that scared everyone is...]
Someone's outside!
That startled me.
It's just a member of our staff. It's okay.
It's not a bad person.
- It's okay.
- My heart is still racing.
[Everyone is disturbed by an abandoned school in the middle of the night]
That was really scary.
[Gulp]
[Chang Wook] Kyung Soo, you already look nervous.
Well, a school is a bit too much.
A school is a bit too much?
The highlight of a summer retreat. It's bravery training time.
[Ah...]
One member from each team will go as a representative.
- What?
- It's just one person?
- Just one person?
- Just one.
So, based on the order in which they finish the training, the ranking of the team will be decided.
- So there's a ranking.
- Based on the ranking, there will be a penalty for the team in last place.
- Man, we really can't get a penalty for this one.
- Right.
As long as it's not this place...
- [Kyung Soo] No... I think they're going to tell us to sleep there.
- Yeah, I think so.
The other teams will choose who will represent your team.
I see.
[Yoo Jung] Choose someone on the other team who will be helpful to us.
So we should choose someone who, we think, will take the longest.
[Chang Wook] It won't feel good being chosen.
Can we get together and discuss this?
Yes, of course!
But I feel bad about choosing someone for this.
But they said there are 5 sleeping bags inside.
[The direction for choosing: Team Cheongbaji > Team Danmuji > Team Nalwoochoban]
[Yoo Jung] Since we don't know each member very well, why don't we share information about our team members?
How is Hae Won?
I think she'll do pretty well.
Oh, really?
[Bo Gum] Should we just pick Park Seo Joon Hyungnim?
I think he'll do everything unfazed.
- That's true.
- It would be scary.
[Sung Eun] But personally, I really want to see Dong Yeon's reaction.
- Because he'll be really funny?
- Yeah, I think he'll be really funny.
I think his reactions will be funny, but I also think he'll do well.
But even so, we can just do better and get first place!
As long as we don't get last place, it's okay.
I think sleeping in those tents is the worst team penalty.
[Kyung Ho] From what I can tell, the girls are pretty strong opponents.
What about choosing between Chang Wook or Jinyoung?
- Do you think Jinyoung Oppa gets scared easily?
- I think so.
A long time ago, Jinyoung gave up during a bravery training because he was so scared.
- But aren't you being a bit heartless, choosing him knowing that?
- What to do, it's so cruel.
That's a bit...
We can't let people slide with things like that here.
Yeah, but we still don't know exactly what the penalty is...
- If we go easy on them, we might get the penalty.
- True.
It's one of these two. Jinyoung or Chang Wook.
What should we do?
[Team Nalwoochoban is also deep in serious discussion]
I don't think Yoo Jung will be scared.
From what I can tell, Yoo Jung has a strong competitive spirit.
- Even if she gets scared
- She really seems that way?
it seems like she'll do well.
For Joo Young...You can just tell she wouldn't get scared.
What about Sung Eun?
I think Sung Eun will just get angry.
What about Park Bo Gum?
[Chang Wook] Well, it hasn't been that long since Bo Gum returned from military service.
- He'll probably have that... yeah.
- His military training...
- So, I don't know about him.
- Oh, really?
On the other hand,
In Yeop is pretty low on energy right now.
Is there a correlation between this and energy level, Oppa?
It hasn't been that long since he finished his last project.
- So should we...
- In Yeop. Let's pick In Yeop.
Okay. We're all set.
[After a logical(?) analysis, they chose In Yeop]
I guess that team has already chosen.
But we've been so focused on this that we forgot that we could be chosen as well.
It doesn't feel like it's going to be me.
Why is my heart suddenly pounding?
I think they're going to pick either Bo Gum or Yoo Jung.
At least, that's what I think.
[What are we going to do about this?]
Did Team Cheongbaji decide who will go for Team Danmuji?
Yes, we decided that...
Hae Won...
might be good,
or Soo Bin Unni...
We'll choose the actor Kwak Dong Yeon.
[Relieved]
We shouldn't be laughing right now.
[Unhappy]
[Everybody's anticipating Dong Yeon's Bravery Training]
We shouldn't be laughing right now.
Dong Yeon, you're quick. I noticed you were quick earlier.
Yeah, I'll get scared more quickly than anyone else...
He said, he'll get scared faster than anyone else.
[Looking forward to it more than anyone else]
But I... I'll go through this like my life depends on it and win it.
He might say that, but I don't think he'll be good.
Okay then. Did Team Danmuji choose a representative?
Yes, we chose... one, two, three!
Ji Chang Wook.
- Oh, great!
- No.
[Team Leader Ji is flustered]
- It's okay, that's fine.
- Wow, that's great!
As for me...
[And the remaining four team members are happy]
First of all, my team members are relieved that they weren't picked.
We were just relieved that we weren't chosen!
It's great!
[Dong Yeon] I met Sunbaenim outside the restroom earlier, and there was a small bug on his shoulder.
[Wait, wait!]
I saw it, too!
- He was making such a fuss for just a bug landing on his shoulder.
- I want to say something.
It was definitely not small at all!
There was this huge fly that literally searched my body.
Sunbaenim, on your shoulder!
[A fly is searching(?) Chang Wook's body]
Sunbaenim, there's another one on your arm!
There's another one!
On my arm, my arm!
- What's wrong with you?
- I really hate bugs.
I'm a bit scared of bugs.
- Sunbaenim spun three times in one second.
- Good job.
After seeing that, we thought, ahh...
Please tell us which member of Team Cheongbaji you chose.
Okay, for us...
Whoever gets chosen, I wish you good luck.
We chose...
[Gesturing politely with two hands]
We're sorry.
- Me?
- Yes.
Me?
[They chose Hwang In Yeop]
[Staff] Weren't you both in the same "The Sound of Magic" team?
But we're not right now.
Sunbaenim, we're in the same room... W-Why? Why?
[Chang Wook] Everyone else on Team Cheongbaji seems pretty tough.
Oh, really?
[Tough, tough, tough, tough]
Compared to everyone else, In Yeop looks pretty weak.
[Tough, weak, tough, tough, tough]
So for this mission, we're going to time each person.
[Complete the passcode using numbers hidden within the school]
[Use the passcode to open the locked staff room and return with the mission item]
The rankings will be decided based on how quickly you bring back the mission item.
If you bring back the wrong item, you will be disqualified, and your team will receive the penalty.
I don't think that's going to be easy...
It's a good thing I'm not going.
All right, we will proceed in the following order. First, Dong Yeon, then In Yeop, and finally Chang Wook.
The two members waiting to go can wait inside the tent.
I'll be back in a flash. Within three minutes.
In three minutes! Okay.
Let's cheer on Dong Yeon.
Fighting, fighting!
[The anxious posterior of the first challenger]
- Man, my heart is heavy...
- We'll be watching you.
- Don't worry about it.
- Fighting, fighting, fighting!
Good luck!
But no, really...
- Fighting!
- You can do it!
- Team Cheongbaji, fighting!
No way we'll sleep here, right?
No, we won't.
Don't worry about it. Don't worry.
Do I look that weak?
Our In Yeop Hyung is looking a bit thin, though.
- Yeah, that's true.
- I know
Asking if we brought vitamins and stuff.
[Meanwhile, the abandoned school is awaiting the challengers]
[Full of creepy ambiance]
[And ghosts who are after the challengers]
[Will they be able to escape the abandoned school safely?]
[It's time for Team Danmuji's Dong Yeon to pick his mission item]
- Dong Yeon, fighting.
- Fighting, fighting!
Fighting! Oh, wait...
- He's not on our team.
- Yeah, you can't do that!
Okay, this one! Actually, this one!
- Okay, what is it?
- What is it?
Back scratcher, okay!
- Back scratcher!
- Back scratcher. Back scratcher.
Back scratcher. Okay!
Back scratcher. All right!
He has got a lot of fighting spirit in him.
- I'll be back!
- Fighting!
You'll be fine!
Challenge started!
[Team Danmuji's Dong Yeon takes off]
[Whew]
Wow...
[Entering the first course, taking deep breaths]
The water faucets.
[The water faucets]
[The first number of the passcode is hidden here]
The water faucets.
[Where is the passcode...]
[Even the people watching from the monitors were scared]
But the ghost looks really scary.
Okay! Okay! Next!
I'm going to the next one!
Next. You're doing a great job.
- The ghost is feeling a bit awkward.
- She unsure of what to do.
What's the number? Eight? Did you say eight?
Eight.
Eight? Okay. Okay, I got it.
- He's doing well.
- He's actually pretty bold.
[Sobbing]
[Whew...]
[He was actually terrified...]
All right, okay!
Okay!
Okay! Whoa!
[The more scared he gets, the louder he becomes]
Aigoo, man, I'm so nervous!
[The art and physical education room]
[Where he can find the second number of the passcode]
[Enters the classroom, full of fear]
I'm sorry... Oh! I'm sorry!
[Stepping backward as soon as he comes in]
[What is that?]
This is so scary...
Whoa, is that a person?
[Filled with haunted moving busts]
[The art room's horror-filled mission]
[Find the microphone and sing along to the song]
Gosh... Where should I look for it... Where could it be?
[Found the microphone]
What song do I need to sing?
♪ What is this on such a good day ♪
[Written and composed by Jinyoung]
[In the middle of absolute silence, a voice starts singing]
[He starts to sing along]
♪ When we go oyster picking ♪
[Two]
[Frightened]
♪ When we go oyster picking ♪
Okay!
[Obtained the second number]
Whoa!
Where do I need to go from here?
[Ugh... ugh... ugh...]
[Arrives on the second floor, making groaning sounds]
He seems to be quite nervous.
Keep going. Keep going.
[His teammates are also nervous]
[Needs to go to the science room]
[The hallway to the science room]
First grade, classroom 1. Second grade, classroom 1.
Oh, it's here. Okay.
[The science room]
Whoa! Whoa! Ah! Ah!
[His voice is getting much louder]
Man, what is this...
Oh, man...
[Walking back as soon as he opens the door]
[A place filled with creepy decorations]
[The science room]
[Enters the science room hesitantly]
[Umm... Uhh...]
[Question: Seo Joon bought 5 boxes of soju. Joo Young, not knowing this, bought 3 more boxes. Then, Nara and Kyung Soo borrowed 3 boxes each. How many boxes of soju are left?]
Okay, 5 and then─
[The answer to this question is the last number of the passcode]
Whoa! God! Sheesh!
[A wig drops from the ceiling softly]
[Whoa...]
There's no way you can't get scared by that.
[He can only escape by solving the question quickly]
It's two!
[While he was focused on solving the question...]
[Suddenly grabs]
Oh! God!
Director, thank you!
[Ah!]
Okay, t-two... f-five...
[In fear, his brain has stopped working]
Five, one, two!
[Just barely manages to finish calculating]
Please stop!
[Goodbye!]
[Finally, the passcode is complete: 822]
[Heading toward the staff room]
[The staff room is at the end of the long hallway]
[In fear, he just bolts through it]
[Puts on the brakes]
Whoa!
Geez, hello! Whoa!
Oh, man!
[Sobbing]
[Barely makes it to the staff room]
Is he in front of the staff room now?
He must be entering the passcode already.
[Breathing raggedly, he is focused on opening the lock]
[Door opens]
[Entering carefully]
So, now I need to find it.
[There are many things hanging in the staff room]
[But the staff room as Dong Yeon sees it...]
[Utter darkness]
Why is it so dark?
It must be really dark in there.
How do you find anything in there?
Back scratcher..
[Dong Yeon's objective is finding the back scratcher]
[Tries touching everything that he can grab with his hands]
Okay, that's it! Let's do it like that.
[Squid slaps]
What is this?
[After touching all sorts of things like this...]
[A tap]
[Found it!]
Done! I'm done!
[Team Danmuji's fate is in Dong Yeon's hands]
- Done! I'm done! I'm done!
- You're out?
You didn't bring the wrong thing, right?
[Dong Yeon comes out of the school confidently]
Back scratcher...
Back scratcher... what is it?
Wait!
What did you bring back?
[The object that Dong Yeon brought back was...]
Hold on, isn't that for shoes?
[A shoehorn]
You have to go back if you don't want to go to the tents tonight!
Run!
What kind of spatula-looking thing is that?
[The person who recommended Dong Yeon is very satisfied]
[At a loss for words...]
- I can see how you could be confused.
- This was what they were going for.
That's why they said you can be disqualified...
But he did so well.
[Same texture, different object]
You really did so well.
- So well.
- So, he's disqualified just like that?
[Applause for Dong Yeon trying his best]
- But he tried so hard.
- But this can be really confusing.
He's sweating so much on his back!
- But he did so well.
- He did.
[Team Danmuji's Dong Yeon is unfortunately disqualified]
[Meanwhile, In Yeop is waiting in the tent]
[Screams]
[Only able to connect with the outside world through sound]
[In Yeop] I keep imagining all sorts of things because I'm alone.
[And after In Yeop imagines all sorts of things...]
Dear fellow Team Cheongbaji members...
[He suddenly pens a letter to Team Cheongbaji...]
It appears...
that the situation and conditions aren't good right now.
Yes.
It seems like we're almost guaranteed to be in last place.
Bo Gum said he didn't get to sleep much because of jet lag.
I feel bad that
I'm having him sleep somewhere like this.
I'm sorry, Team Leader.
I'm really sorry. Yeah.
But I'll do the very best I can.
I'm feeling...
nervous and anxious.
[Staff] Hwang In Yeop. Please come out now.
Fighting! Fighting!
[Finally comes out into the world...]
[The object that In Yeop needs to find and bring back]
You want me to find seaweed?
- Wait, what?
- Seaweed.
- Seaweed?
- That's not easy.
Fighting!
[He heads to the abandoned school to find seaweed]
- Fighting.
- Fighting!
Start!
[Team Cheongbaji's In Yeop takes off]
Whoa, what is that? What is that?
It's nothing, right? It's nothing, right?
Don't do this to me.
He just started.
[Within one second of starting...]
Something about him makes me worried.
He'll be okay, right?
My dear Team Cheongbaji members, my eyesight is not great.
I am really sorry.
Bo Gum, you're probably really tired,
but all because of me...
He keeps saying something to himself.
Murmuring to himself.
[Hesitant]
Yes. Wait, is it not?
What's supposed to be here?
[What do you mean? There's obviously a ghost here]
Stop!
[Freeze]
[Release]
Wow. Hello.
[Glancing over]
I don't think this is right. Oh, my. Oh, my.
[Social distancing]
Hold on.
[The ghost keeps following him to tell him the number]
Go away now. You've already done your job.
[Suddenly commanding the ghost to go home]
Why is he fighting with the ghost?
Go away...
- Is this it?
- Six...
Gosh, I told you to go away!
Huh, what is this?
[Come on]
No, no, no.
What is this? Oh!
What is this? Oh, what is this!
[Extremely on guard]
Six...
Oh...?
What the... What the...
[And In Yeop leaves the water faucets area]
Did he see it?
I don't think he saw it!
What was that?
[Did he hear what I said?]
The ghost must feel like she has unresolved business.
The ghost keeps reaching out to him,
so she can tell him the number.
I'm so scared...
[Come on]
You can just leave it over there, can't you?
- I'm telling you the number is six.
- What?
- Six...
- Yeah, I know.
- Then go.
- Yeah, I will.
[The chemistry displayed in the back and forth with the ghost]
I told you it's not that, Bo Yoon.
Oh, man, he's so funny.
Okay. I understood.
[Past the water faucets and now into the abandoned school]
Man, this is no joke.
I feel like this is going to appear in my dreams.
[Enters the abandoned school, constantly murmuring]
What did they say again?
Did they say it was the art room?
[Thud!]
[Freeze]
[Release]
It's here, it's here!
Oh, please, I beg you...
Ah. I really mean it.
Wait a second! What was that?
That art room was the most aggravating.
The people sitting there are so scary...
[Long-haired friends who never get up]
[And fake busts ready to start moving]
Wow! Whoa, ah!
Hold on!
[Runs out of the room]
Wow! Whoa, ah! Hold on!
[Ran out instinctively, but naturally re-enters]
What do I need to do?
[Find the microphone and sing along to the song]
Is this the microphone?
Is this the mic... oh, no, it's an easel.
[Microphone (X), Easel (X), Art Tube (O)]
Wait a second! What is that?
[Been getting scared all by himself]
So, what... microphone... This is the microphone.
[As soon as he grabs the microphone, the song starts playing]
♪ When we go oyster picking ♪
[With microphone in hand, he steps back as far back as he can]
[Four]
[Freeze]
[Release]
Got it!
Watching this is so fun.
Okay, now I think I'm getting the hang of it.
Okay. I got it.
[Runs up towards the science room]
Science room.
Man, this is driving me nuts.
I can't see anything...
Science room.
[As soon as he turns around, the window ghost appears]
[Look at me!]
[Freeze]
[Release]
Is this the science room?
Oh, here it is. I can't see anything right now.
What are we going to do at this rate... whoa!
Peek-a-boo.
[Welcome to the science room]
Just by opening the door...
[How does he get scared from just opening the door...]
- He's going to freak out at this rate.
- I'm worried about him...
Isn't he going to fall over from the shock?
Ah, seriously.
[Can't step inside easily...]
No, seriously, Director...
Don't do it, don't do it, don't do it!
Chang Wook... Sung Eun...
[Peek-a-boo!]
[Left a deep impression...]
Geez, we're screwed...
What is that?
[As he's looking upward warily]
[An ambush from below]
Please don't.
[A guy worth targeting every time]
This is really...
Wait...
[It's scary, but I have to solve this question...]
So they were given ten pieces of paper...
[Sits down gently onto the chair]
I can't think straight...
So, they were given ten pieces of paper...
2, 2, 2, 4
[Focusing on the question, sitting prettily]
He's on top of the chair!
He's so cute.
That's cute.
What's going on? Hold on.
[A simple arithmetic question]
I guess it's arithmetic.
Since you're so scared, I guess you might struggle to calculate.
One...
Okay! I finally got it.
Don't do it! Don't do it. Don't do it.
[Bye!]
Is this the staff room?
[He opens the door and finally enters the staff room]
[Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang!]
[This knocking noise]
It's here.
[This knocking noise is a signal for something big coming]
He's going to lose it here.
But what did they...
Whoa! Wait! Wait! Don't do it! Stop!
Stop it! Please don't do it.
[Fancy footwork]
[The audience, who were looking forward to the hallway ghost...]
[were extremely satisfied]
Whoa! Man, gosh, goodness...
Don't do it! Whoa!
This is the right place... whoa!
[Bang snaps crackling]
Whoa! What is this!
Seriously...
[Getting scared every single time]
That's right...
[Finally reached the staff room at the end of a difficult journey]
I can't see anything...
I did it! It's over!
[I did it! It's over!]
- It's not over...
- It's not over yet.
It's just the start...
All he has to do is find it now.
- The seaweed.
The light...
[Enters the staff room]
The light isn't on here... The object...
[Now, all he has to do is find the seaweed here...]
The back scratcher's right over there!
You were so close to it.
It was right in front.
[It was just hanging right there...]
Oh! What is that?
[But while you're here, you can't see anything]
[A sliding noise]
Oh, please! I beg you. Give me a moment!
Don't close the door! Please, don't close the door...
Please, don't close the door...
Please don't close the door?
He can't leave the door behind. He can't let go of it.
Oh, please! Don't close it.
I beg you! Don't close the door...
I think this is it...
This is it.
Or is it not?
This is right.
He's just grabbing something in front of him and is coming back.
He looks like he's bringing back something else, right? Yeah, I think he's bringing back something else.
Don't do it, please. Don't do it. No, really.
[Will the object in his hand be the right one?]
You've worked hard.
[In Yeop finally escaped from the abandoned school]
- Wait, is that right?
- Oh! It is seaweed!
Is it really seaweed?
Isn't that seaweed?
[Please...]
- Come here.
- Isn't this seaweed?
[The thing that In Yeop brought back in his hand was...]
Isn't the thing I brought back seaweed?
[Seaweed!]
He's right!
- He brought back seaweed!
- Is that seaweed?
[In Yeop, Mission Success!]
- Is this right?
- Whoa, it is seaweed!
[A splendid feat achieved by overcoming his fears]
I'm done for.
[In Yeop's final record was 9 minutes and 31 seconds]
You did well!
- It's so scary in there...
- Are you all right?
It's so scary.
[Returns to his seat to the cheers of his fellow Team Cheongbaji members]
Hyung, you were so cute.
- What?
- Really cute. Absolutely.
- We were all cracking up.
- What?
We were laughing so hard.
Oh, really?
[He's still dealing with the after-effects of the abandoned school]
You were awesome. And cute.
- What?
- You were cute.
Why couldn't I add or subtract properly in there?
[Team Cheongbaji is currently in the first place]
[Meanwhile, having waited in the tent and unaware of what's to come...]
- What is it?
- It's an easy one.
[The last challenger Chang Wook naively picks his mission object]
A leek?
[The object that Chang Wook needs to bring back is a leek]
Fighting!
He seems like he's not afraid at all.
- I know, right?
- It looks like we picked the wrong person.
He might do well.
[Worried that he might do too well]
Challenge started!
[Team Nalwoochoban's Chang Wook takes off]
Fighting!
[Team Leader, fighting!]
[He enters the water faucets area briskly]
[He tries turning on all of the faucets...]
Whoa!
God... man... that scared me! Whoa!
Oh, God... man... that scared me...
Okay. Here it is.
Four...
The water doesn't come out.
Four, four, four? Four?
What's four?
[Not really paying close attention to the ghost's hint]
The one where the water comes out...
[But instead, he completely focuses on the faucets]
[Did he not understand what I said?]
The ghost is a bit flustered.
The ghost is staring at him wistfully.
It's four?
[And with that, Chang Wook leaves...]
Where do I have to go?
Four?
[He finally left...]
The ghost is really going through a lot today.
Four?
[He enters the abandoned school]
What's that? Someone's sitting there...
Oh, this is that.
Oh, God! You scared me!
But he's not getting that scared.
He's really not getting that scared.
Oh... What is this?
[Chang Wook, who really doesn't get scared easily...]
Whoa. Wow. What's that? You scared me.
[Obtains the second number quickly]
That startled me.
[Unfazed]
- What! He didn't get scared!
- Wow! Really!
How does he not get scared by that?
Ah, it's 4.
[And calmly figures out the last number]
Four one four.
The staff room.
[Arrives at the staff room within four minutes]
[Once he opens the lock, it's the last course]
I can't see it.
[He spends a while struggling with the lock...]
Oh, is this how you're supposed to open it?
At this rate, he's going to waste a lot of time...
I think we're in big trouble right now.
- He did everything so well, but he got stuck there.
- I know, at the lock.
He's pretty brave, though.
[He has got a lot of bravery, but his eyesight is weak]
I can't see anything
[And time kept passing without much success...]
Aigoo, why is this not working?
[Time's over!]
You've been disqualified. Please come out.
[Disillusioned...]
- Oppa, you really weren't scared at all!
- Yeah, you were really brave.
More importantly, I couldn't see any of the passcodes.
- Oh, in there? Because it was so dark?
- It was so dark.
[The final results for the bravery training]
Hwang In Yeop brought his item in 9 minutes 31 seconds.
[A valuable victory earned by facing his fears]
Daebak.
Ji Chang Wook and Kwak Dong Yeon were both disqualified.
They did well. They did really well.
I know, right? They did really well.
So we prepared a battle among team leaders.
A battle among team leaders?
The team leaders will go in and...
[Do we have to do it again...]
[Eyes shaking]
The team that brings back the exemption voucher will win.
Yoo Jung, you can do it!
But shouldn't we be exempt since we won?
- Is our team exempt from this?
- Are we exempt from this?
- Yes. Because your team won, you are already exempt from the penalty.
- It's okay, it's okay!
It's okay, it's okay!
Oh, man. I was really...
The Team Leaders' Battle will take place
[A Team Leaders' battle without Team Cheongbaji, which is already exempt]
[With an upgraded level of scariness in the bathhouse]
[The team that loses here...]
[will face a very scary penalty!]
[Potential last-place teams, Danmuji and Nalwoochoban]
[What will be the results of the final battle?]
[The next episode]
Whoa! You scared me!
[The horror is not over yet]
Whoa! No! God! Stop it!
This is why I said I don't do variety shows!
[Which team will be in last place at the end of the bravery training?]
[The next day, the young actors leave on a friendship trip together]
[It's so exciting!]
If you speak casually to me, I'll also speak casually to you.
- Okay?
- Okay.
[The Young Actors' Retreat members grow closer]
- Please wear a safety helmet. Come in one by one–
- What–?!
[And finally...]
What's going on? Oppa?
[Itaewon Team's last member, Ahn Bo Hyun, arrives!]
- Oh, it's in the back, I see.
- You put your head through here.
[Jang Geun Won taking care of Sae Ro Yi]
Oh, so it's supposed to attach right here.
[Sweet in real life, the chemistry between these two, coming soon]
♫ If we’re together in our youth ♫
♫ Will always be here ♫
♫ Oh, happy day ♫
♫ We make the way nobody goes ♫