♪I lament on the cruel
and untimely love♪
♪Yet I come to realise it's a daydream
when the bubbles burst♪
♪A city of spring flowers♪
♪Sinks into
the indifferent autumnal frost♪
♪A snowflake falls into the river♪
♪The biting cold stalks over♪
♪All assumptions are nothing♪
♪But a disguised makeup♪
♪I bid farewell♪
♪To the passionate gaze
behind the mask♪
♪Love and hate are
the most unforgettable feelings♪
♪Overwhelmed by my longings♪
♪I tear off those old scores♪
♪I bid farewell♪
♪To the irretrievable past♪
=Little Mad Doctor=
=Episode 14=
It's not your fault.
This is a coincidence.
No, it's not.
(I know.)
(It can't be so coincidental)
(to just happen today)
(of all days.)
It's fine, My Lord.
We will get married
six months later.
It's the same.
Jinghong.
Will you still marry me
six months later?
That sounds odd.
Are you
going to turn down the marriage
after taking advantage of me?
Of course, I will marry you
as long as you nod your head.
I believe in you.
I believe
that one day,
you will put on the golden armor
riding on iridescent clouds
to marry me
with the blessings from the people.
(Jinghong,)
(will you hate me)
(if you find out)
(the wedding is called off
because of me?)
What have you found?
It's the same as in previous cases.
Superficially,
the victim died from being
completely drained of blood.
Recently, there have been frequent
bizarre murders within this capital.
I'm afraid something is looming over.
Yes.
What can I receive
if I uncover the truth?
Anything you wish for,
Princess Jinghong.
Anything?
I will give you anything
I could.
For the rest of our lives,
I will give you anything
I could.
Fengxing.
Can you please
inform Lord War to come?
I need to speak to him.
Yes.
(Maybe...)
(Maybe I've overthought.)
Feibai.
Why are you here again?
Didn't I tell you
he's my man?
Can you stop pestering him?
So, this is how you treat someone
who saved your life?
I didn't ask for your help though.
Jeez.
Feibai.
I made you your favorite sweet corn
with pine nuts.
My Lord.
This is your favorite sweet corn
with pine nuts.
Bao'er.
Behave yourself.
I cooked this for you.
How could you say that?
Let's go
and eat it inside, all right?
I'm on a mission now.
I don't have time for that.
Let go of me.
No.
My Lord.
Jinghong.
Why do you ask for me?
Well.
My Lord.
There has been
a serial murder case in the capital,
I'd like to seek your assistance.
Me?
Yes.
That serial killer
resembles you.
I'm worried
someone is trying to plot against you.
Therefore,
we must take the initiative to act
before them.
Yes.
Jinghong.
I do support you.
Right.
Well,
let's go home.
Ah.
Let's head back now.
Bao'er.
I will send you home now.
Feibai.
Am I that annoying?
What has Chu Jinghong done to you?
Why are you so infatuated with her?
Bao'er.
As I said,
I will look after you
and protect you
even without the presence
of Chu Jinghong.
You may head home by yourself
if you're upset with me.
I have something to attend to.
I'm off.
Feibai.
My Lord.
Why don't you
fly me back while carrying me?
My Lord.
I'm talking to you.
Carry me back.
If you don't,
I will walk home myself.
No.
I will carry you.
Come on.
Am I that heavy?
Jinghong.
My Lord.
You look weak today.
You flew better last time.
I...
I have something to attend to.
I need to go now.
Hey.
My Lord.
Please don't go.
I feel ill at ease.
Can you
sleep with me tonight?
Jinghong.
I have something to attend to now.
Maybe next time.
Hey, don't go.
Hey.
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
♪Except for you♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪Even though time wears thin♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
♪Exists beyond time♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪For the chance
to be forever by your side♪
♪Hair turns grey in one winter night♪
♪The appearance remains
in spite of the thick frost♪
♪Time slips by in that dream-like world♪
♪Life is always full of splendor♪
♪We part when the flowers fall♪
♪Desolate chills blow away
several autumns♪
♪Eternal love is all I seek♪
♪Though the sweet dream fades at last♪
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
♪Except for you♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪Even though time wears thin♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
♪Exists beyond time♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪For the chance
to be forever by your side♪