"Love After Addiction"
(Episode 2)
I heard you think the
funds are already in place.
So you think no one else matters?
Like you can do whatever you want.
But do you wanna bet?
As long as our Yoki Baby quits the show.
They'll withdraw the investment right away.
You think that won't happen?
Directors are a dime a dozen.
Are you leaving, or is Yoki Baby?
Who do you think they'll pick?
Guys like you.
You might only get one
chance like this in your life
to be in this position.
Don't you dare mess it up!
How stupid can you be?
All of this... is for love.
Hey.
My baby Yoki
I already chewed out that
selfish director.
Calm down first, okay?
I just hope
that you won't leave.
We're in a tough spot right now,
you know that too.
If you wanna turn things around,
you gotta endure a little hardship.
That's why I didn't ask you to
bring an assistant.
I really hope you'll stay.
Good boy.
Then get a good night's sleep, ok?
Wait.
You're still answering calls this late?
Another sleepless night?
Not exactly.
I think I've found
my magic cure.
This feeling of deep sleep is truly
long overdue.
So nice!
Pervert!
I love my wife very much.
My wife made me who I am.
My wife became my wife.
My house became my home.
She's a very virtuous woman.
Get to the point.
Mr. Yoki.
I was wrong about what happened today.
This variety show,
I've been working for it for eight years.
I don't want to lose my wife.
You're going to quit?
But you're a volunteer.
Do you know what a volunteer is?
We haven't even started
rolling and you're backing out.
What are we going to do about this?
But.
If you really don't want to participate,
I will never
go against your will,
but Lanwan Village
will be in trouble.
I know what to do.
Village Chief.
Magic cure Yang Meng.
Miracle for insomnia.
Here he comes.
Mr. Yoki.
Where are your shoes?
I can't find them.
It's okay, this is fine.
Seriously?
A man with nothing to lose
fears no man with everything to lose.
You'll definitely win!
Mr. Yoki.
It hasn't started yet.
The first segment.
Our guests have to compete for.
Lanwan Village's specialty ingredients,
and then
cook a dinner themselves.
In other words,
what you eat for dinner
depends on what you grab.
Ready?
Brother Yoki.
Good luck!
You too!
Take your positions!
Alright!
Please continue the competition, everyone!
Don't be affected!
What's wrong, Yoki?
Slow down, slow down, slow down.
Let me check.
It hurts.
Be careful!
Slow down.
Take it easy.
It hurts so much.
Then be careful!
Slow down, slow down...
Walk slower.
Okay, slow down...
I... I...
What's wrong with your program team?
Leaving the guests injured like this
and doing nothing about it—it's dangerous!
He's totally different from
how he was in high school.
He's changed so much.
Don't move!
Didn't expect you're quite professional.
I'm a volunteer in the village now.
The work is quite diverse.
I need to know a little bit of everything.
Nice jawline.
Great skin too.
How come I didn't
notice that in high school?
He's quite handsome.
It might hurt a bit.
It's okay.
Do whatever you want with me.
Anything is fine.
Ouch...
Just kill me...
It's okay now.
All done.
Are you a mermaid?
I'm injured.
Give me a hand.
Stop being so dramatic.
Could you check the wound please?
A trip and fall isn't a real injury.
Fine, I'll get up myself.
Alright, alright, I'll help you.
I...
Are you trying to save me
or kill me?
Bad start.
Mr. Yoki.
It's a successful first battle.
Idiot.
Damn pervert!
Brother Yoki.
Didn't expect you'd get injured
at the beginning.
Do you need me to
take care of the wound again?
No.
It's fine.
I just want to see
how serious your wound is.
What are you doing?
Just checking, I'm worried it's serious.
Told you it's fine!
Did he just glare at me?
I don't know.
No need
I'm afraid it hurts.
It doesn't hurt at all.
The tide's gone out.
Let's go tide pooling!
Mr. Yoki.
We're about to move on to
the next round.
You made ten tiny bites
out of that one green onion.
Are you reluctant to eat it
or waiting for someone to feed you?
No, not at all.
It looks delicious.
Alright.
Great.
Tonight
our accommodation
will be determined by drawing lots.
Everybody,
what kind of house you want to live in
depends on your luck.
Who wants to go first?
Mr. Yoki.
Please go ahead.
What?
A yellow mud house.
Director,
is the yellow mud house better
or
my luxurious sea view room?
What do you think?
Of course,
each has its own merits.
Damn pervert!
Yoki.
I don't feel right about this.
Why don't you come stay with me?
There's definitely enough space.
Follow the program team's arrangement.
Alright,
but if you really can't get used to it,
promise me you'll come find me.
What are you looking at?
You want to eat it?
Come here.
So violent!
But so charming!
What are you doing?
What are you eating?
Is it good?
Give me a bite.
It's delicious!
You...
Are you avoiding me?
No, I'm not.
You're scared of me.
N-No, I'm not.
No?
Really?
Really.
Alright.
The place I'm staying tonight,
I can't read the map.
Show me the way.
I'm only responsible for
safety issues.
Ok fine.
What kind of old classmate are you?
Haven't seen each other for eight years,
no wonder there's no friendship left.
Leaving me here
on this lonely island
to fend for myself.
Coincidentally
I'm on my way to do something.
If you can get on,
I'll give you a ride.
Are you out of your mind?
Yang Meng,
Why did you bring me to your house?
This is where you're staying tonight.
This is where I'm staying!
Come on in.
We're here.
This is it.
Live here alone?
I might die here
and no one would know?
Impossible.
Look,
this open-air space is cool.
This curtain,
this table,
this bed is square
and sturdy.
Sturdy?
Maybe...
I can make you a hammock.
Or.
Or... or...
Why don't you stay here
and sleep with me?
I'm really scared living alone.
Didn't you plan this
from the beginning?
No.
How could I?
Fine.
Then I'm not helping.
Clean up by yourself.
What's wrong with you?
I... I have a toothache.
Where exactly does it hurt?
Toothache.
It's an old problem acting up.
Let me see.
Open your mouth.
Is it here?
A little further in.
Here?
Further in.
This one.
Come back.
Let go.
It's a bit salty.
H-His tongue.
What are you doing?
I have a toothache.
Then go to the clinic.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
Turn around.
Why do I need to turn around?
Stop talking nonsense.
It hurts like hell, hurry up!
Hurry, turn around, hurry, hurry.
Hurry and stick out your butt.
Stick out your butt.
Hurry up!
Hurry, hurry, stick it out.