"Love After Addiction"
(Episode 9)
Tastes good.
Did it sell?
Say something, please.
Wait a sec.
Is that you in your profile picture?
What profile picture?
Muscle guy, do you take private gigs?
Private gigs?
Let's be friends.
Forty thousand living expenses a month.
Forty thousand living...
Yoki.
This is the great idea
you were talking about?
To be honest，
why not try live streaming?
Live streaming?
Friends!
Our oysters are on special offer.
Buy five catties, get five catties free!
Lanwan oysters, Lanwan oysters!
And our crabs，
friends，
our friends，
and our crabs
are
twenty for a pound!
Really big.
Our crabs are also on promotion today.
Our Lanwan crabs
are 199NTD
for three.
And it's a good deal for a pound.
Everyone, look.
They're lively and jumping around.
Can you do it or not?
We just... we just
I have to take over.
Our Lanwan crabs
run about three to a pound.
Five hundred grams.
Welcome everyone.
Are my eyes deceiving me?
This is Best Actor Yoki?
What Best Actor? He's
already fallen from grace.
Daring to show his face again.
No,
babies，
I think he's really handsome.
Everyone is lucky today.
Lanwan Village seafood clearance sale!
199 yuan for three crabs.
Not enough?
Besides the three big crabs,
we'll also give away
two big oysters for free.
Is that enough?
Not enough!
Yeah, not enough!
Besides the two big oysters,
we'll give two small yellow croakers too.
Is that enough?
Enough, enough!
Enough, enough, enough!
Still not enough!
Besides the two small yellow croakers,
we'll give away a big fish too!
Is that enough now?
Enough, enough, enough!
All of these for just 199 yuan!
Now I'll start the countdown—...
Three, two, one!
Link up!
The numbers are even bigger
than we hoped!
Yeah.
This solves the problem.
Little Meng，
I heard you sold hundreds
of thousands of orders
and sold them all out.
Thank you.
These are pickles I made myself.
Hope it's okay.
Thank you, thank you.
I also have a bottle of cola here.
Alright, alright, thank you Auntie.
You're welcome, you're welcome.
As expected of our
Lanwan Village's favorite.
They all gave you gifts of thanks.
What about mine?
What do you want?
That's it.
Just one touch.
What else do you want?
One more.
The other side.
No.
Fine.
Close your eyes.
Are they closed?
Really closed?
Hurry up.
I'm coming.
You...
Pull it out.
So cold.
Cold, cold, cold?
Cold, cold, cold!
Really cold, really cold, really cold!
Cold, cold, cold, cold, cold!
Okay, okay, that's enough!
I was wrong, I was wrong.
It's mine...
As a reward,
I want you to take the
initiative to come to my bed.
Dream on.
Go to sleep quickly.
You've worked hard all day.
Didn't you say 'dream on'?
I...
I just came to check
if you're sleeping well.
Are you still taking sleeping pills?
Haven't taken them in a long time.
You're much more
effective than sleeping pills.
Go answer the door.
You go.
Hurry up, it's so loud!
Who is it?
Who is it, this early in the morning?
Surprise!
Aren't you going to let me in?
Let's talk outside, the room is messy.
Wait for me.
Sleep a little longer.
I have something to do, I'll be right back.
About that little girl,
why didn't you tell me?
I didn't lose an arm or a leg.
Do I have to report this too?
No, not really.
But this is a great opportunity
to build your public image.
Are you planning to
publicize this for attention?
No, that's not it.
You know too,
everyone likes
this kind of topic.
You should make good use of it.
You finally got some popularity now,
of course I want to take this chance
to promote you well.
Right?
Whatever you decide.
There's more good news
do you want to hear it?
Fang Xiaotian is admitting that
during the time she was dating you,
she was kept by a sugar daddy.
I plan to use this matter
to make her...
No need.
Just clarify our relationship.
She's a girl after all
and she has to live her life later.
Oh my god!
You came to this small fishing village
and got enlightened by Mazu.
Hello.
Yoki, this is your friend?
This young guy is?
My name is Yang Meng.
I'm Yoki's high school classmate.
Now I'm a volunteer here.
High school classmates.
As I see it,
why are you willing to stay
in this small fishing village?
Is it because there's no opportunity
in the big city?
Why are you asking these questions?
It's just regular communication.
I'm fine right where I am.
I'm very content.
An unknown volunteer
and a famous superstar,
actually being high school classmates!
So, this is life...
It's quite amazing when you think about it.
That's enough.
Do you know?
He will ruin you!
I confessed first.
It has nothing to do with him.
I think you're really crazy.
Do you still remember
why you came here?
What if people find out?
Then we'll go public.
I shouldn't have hidden my
sexual orientation anyway.
Brother!
You finally
made a comeback.
About that little girl
I haven't had time to promote it yet,
and you're going to ruin yourself
for someone like him?
All these years,
you made me do all
those hypocritical things.
I don't want to continue anymore.
I've had enough too.
Fine.
If you've thought it through
but you need to know,
the words you said today,
you can't afford the consequences.
I'll give you one day
to think it over.
I hope you'll take back these words.
Where's your agent?
He can't get used to the food here,
so he went back to the homestay first.
The things he just said,
don't take it to heart.
I didn't take it to heart.
Then why did you say
we're just friends?
I don't want you to get into trouble.
You don't have to worry about me.
When the time is right,
I'll make everything public
and give everyone an explanation.
Trust me.
I love you.
I trust you.
Thank you for your liking.
But
I already have someone I like.
Then can we still
be friends in the future?
Of course.
I'll still treat you
like my little sister just like before.
So you swing both ways, huh?
Alright.
Since you don't have anything else
to tell me,
then I wish you two
a long and happy relationship.
Why... why does it hurt?
Even more of a scumbag than before.
I never want to see him again.
Never again.
Kneel down.
What does this mean?
Choose one.
I said choose one!
Come here.
Look up.
Look at me.
Tell me
your safe word.