Are you friends?
Can you explain what happened again?
So there's this kid, Oh Beom-seok.
He goes to Byuksan High School.
- Oh Beom-seok?
- Yes.
He called me over to a café.
He wasn't alone--
Yeong-i.
Are you okay?
Where did the others go?
I was alone.
Young man.
You can be honest with us.
Don't worry.
I was alone.
What are you doing?
Never tell Su-ho
about what happened today.
What?
Hey, Si-eun!
Si-eun!
Beom-seok.
Yeah.
Stop this. Now.
Leave Su-ho alone.
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
DIVIDING NUMBERS WITH TWO AND THREE DIGITS
I'm just asking what you were doing
when he got hurt.
Is that so wrong?
You think you're the only one who's busy?
Do you think I'm just resting at home
while you're working?
You said that we'd do this together.
That we'd raise him together!
That we should have this child--
I had no idea back then!
I didn't expect him to get hurt
all the time like this.
Si-eun.
Si-eun, open the door and talk to me.
Si-eun, please open the door.
Si-eun.
Si-eun, please talk to your dad.
Yeon Si-eun.
We weren't fighting. We were just talking.
Si-eun.
Si-eun. Yeon Si-eun.
It's all right.
Tell me the truth.
Were these the same guys as before?
It's the truth.
I fell down some stairs.
Be honest with me.
Why were you there?
No reason.
You'll transfer schools.
That's final.
I don't want to.
Seriously?
What's wrong with you?
I'm trying hard to raise you.
Why won't you listen?
Father.
I've been wondering.
Since when have you cared about me
so much?
What?
Never mind.
Yes?
Beom-seok is at home.
How did it go?
I handled the police at Seocho.
I talked to his school principal.
The assemblyman's wife is on Jeju Island,
so stay there and watch him.
We don't know what he might do.
Find a school in the Philippines.
They'll send him soon.
Yes, sir.
How did you know?
From Mr. Park.
He said you'd be in there.
I meant about yesterday.
The police contacted us.
Yeon Si-eun…
He just wanted to let it go.
He said you were friends.
What were the protestors' demands?
It's important.
Hey, wake him up.
- Wake up!
- Su-ho.
Ahn Su-ho.
Where were we?
No answer?
Which page was it?
Page 100. The Japan-Korea Treaty of 1876.
I see. In that case…
turn to page 109.
Let's discuss
the Donghak Peasant Revolution.
So, let's continue.
In order for us to understand
the Donghak Peasant Revolution…
AHN SU-HO
SOMETHING CAME UP AT HOME
SO I CAN'T COME TO SCHOOL FOR A WHILE
Why didn't you come home?
You ignored my calls.
What?
Is this supposed to be a birthday prank?
Has it ended yet?
Stop it. It's not funny.
It's not a prank.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
FINAL EXAM
IN 1 DAY
- Hey!
- God.
Let's go smoke.
Why isn't Beom-seok here?
Not sure.
Did you call him?
Aren't you guys close?
His phone was off. Do you know anything?
Tell him to pay for my repairs.
Yeah, okay.
What?
What repairs?
It cost me 800,000 won.
If you don't pay, I'll kill you all.
Answer me.
Okay.
JEONG-CHAN
The number you have called…
Fuck, Beom-seok! Pick up the phone!
Fuck, we need to take care of Su-ho.
Hey, why isn't Si-eun at school?
He didn't die, did he?
- I mean, Yeong-bin fucking overreacted.
- Hey.
You're the ones overreacting.
If he were dead, we'd be at a funeral now.
Shit.
Wait!
Beom-seok called you at first,
but he took the girl instead
to draw you out
because you didn't answer.
What?
You know.
That girl who lives with you.
But Si-eun showed up.
- Keep going.
- Right. Okay.
Beom-seok paid
one of Yeong-bin's friends to beat you up.
Beom-seok did it all.
We were just bystanders.
What is it?
Which hospital is Si-eun in?
He got out today.
I'm sorry I caused this.
Hey!
Si-eun didn't want you to find out.
Don't cause any trouble.
Who is it?
Delivery.
What's up?
Why are you asking?
I'm thirsty. Give me some water.
Hey.
You doing okay?
Yeah.
What is it?
Nothing.
Just stopping by.
Are you okay?
What?
Will you be at school for finals tomorrow?
Yeah.
I need to be.
All right. Yeah.
See you then.
He's inside?
Yes.
Are you fucking crazy?
You piece of shit!
You.
I told you not to fucking embarrass me.
What's wrong?
Hey! What's wrong with you?
Fucking piece of shit.
All you had to do was listen,
do what you were told,
and keep your head down.
Was that hard?
Was that so hard?
Son of a bitch!
You fucking idiot!
You fucker!
Hey.
You're going to study abroad.
Do whatever you want. I don't give a shit
if you kill yourself with drugs.
Just don't tell anyone you're my son.
Is that understood?
Hey!
Keep an eye on this punk.
I never asked you to raise me.
Beom-seok.
Let go, fuck.
I said let go.
- Where to?
- Just drive.
MISSED CALL: SU-HO, JEONG-CHAN
YEONG-BIN, TAE-HUN
SU-HO
IMAGE
ANSWER THE PHONE,
OR I WILL KILL YOUR FRIENDS
Please, wait.
So then,
go get Beom-seok.
I don't know where he is either.
Honestly! I can't reach him!
Then an eye for an eye.
BEOM-SEOK
Where are you?
Where the fuck are you?
Why?
Oh Beom-seok.
Stop hiding.
Shit!
OH BEOM-SEOK
What's up?
Let's get Ahn Su-ho.
I'll pay.
Hello?
Hey.
Have you talked to Su-ho?
Yeah.
He came by earlier.
Su-ho knows everything that happened.
What?
He didn't come to work,
and I can't reach him.
Did he say anything to you?
He wouldn't
go after Beom-seok, would he?
I'll try to reach him.
Are you making a movie?
You're fucking crazy.
What is this?
Where's Beom-seok?
Long time no see.
You should have taken it out on me.
Not on those kids.
They did nothing wrong.
I'm sorry.
For upsetting you.
I apologized.
Now you apologize to Si-eun and Yeong-i.
I don't want to.
I have nothing to apologize for.
Do it, please.
I said no.
Then I'll beat you up
until you come to your senses.
Hey, Ahn Su-ho.
Get in the ring.
You seriously paid this asshole
just to beat me up?
You're so fucking pathetic.
One sec. Let me warm up.
I guess you've been working out.
You almost look like a pro.
Did you forget
I once beat the hell out of you?
Come on, then.
Well!
The time has come, guys.
I told you I got owned
back in middle school,
so this will be my revenge.
This time, we'll fight
in an official match.
Wish me luck.
- This is it.
- Let's make it exciting.
- Okay?
- Please.
Please, Woo-yeong. You're our only hope.
Cut the crap.
Fuck, that was close!
The old injury's there?
So what if it is, punk?
Behind you!
- Woo-yeong!
- Go, Woo-yeong!
Woo-yeong! Get your revenge!
That's it!
Good job!
Feeling lucky?
Fuck you, asshole.
Kill that son of a bitch!
You fucker!
Hey, fuck you!
Hey, he's fucked up.
Fucker.
Oh shit.
- That fucker.
- That punk was tough.
Hey.
Now who's the pathetic one?
Say it again.
Who do you think you are?
Always looking at me like that.
Looking down on me.
Hey.
Please come to your senses.
Stop blaming others, Beom-seok.
Hey.
Fuck you. Keep my name out of your mouth.
Fucking bastard.
Fuck, let's join in.
- Fucker!
- Bastard!
- You fucker!
- Son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch!
- Asshole!
- Motherfucker!
Motherfucker! Son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch!
Fucking son of a bitch.
Beom-seok.
Oh Beom-seok!
Oh fuck.
Let's go.
Don't touch me.
Come on.
Seriously, let go.
I said let me go, fucking asshole!
Hey, Ahn Su-ho.
Ahn Su-ho.
Hey, he isn't breathing.
What?
Hey, Ahn Su-ho!
Oh fuck!
You two were the last to hit him.
If you leave now, it'll get worse.
I'll fix this, so stay here.
Su-ho.
Su-ho, please look at me.
Let's go.
Stop. Come on.
Beom-seok.
Get him out of here!
Su-ho isn't opening his eyes!
Su-ho isn't…
Wait!
Wait, please.
Si-eun!
Where's Su-ho?
He's not here.
He won't answer my calls.
Seriously, where is he?
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS SHOWN
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL
Subtitle translation by: James Webb