Your Highness?
Father, it isn't what you think!
Your Majesty, please allow me
to explain myself!
Your Highness.
Wretch, it was you!
That's enough!
=The Architect=
=Episode 23=
(Today will be)
(the last best day of your life)
The state of Daliang is
governed with propriety.
How dare you two
do that in front of us?
You two...
Do you two have no
regard for the palace?
The royal family is utterly embarrassed
because of you two!
Your Majesty, please
practice wise judgment.
I didn't do anything.
After I received the decree,
I was heading back
to reflect on my action.
But when I passed by
the royal garden...
Was it you?
You ordered your men to knock me out
in order to frame me!
Prince Duan, if you wish
to malign someone,
you have to show us some evidence.
You'd better stop pretending!
Xiao Huaijin!
Say no more.
Father,
although Xiao Huaijin and I
were lying on the same bed,
we did nothing at all.
I'm innocent.
Innocent?
All of my subjects
witnessed it themselves.
How dare you say that you're innocent?
So what?
Do they get to dictate
my innocence?
I'm the princess of Daliang.
If they dare to gossip about me,
Father, you should
rip out their tongues instead.
According to the law of Daliang,
those who corrupt the royal court
will be executed.
Your Majesty, please be appeased.
I have a solution
that can protect the
name of the royal family
and serve Prince Duan
and Her Highness well.
What is it?
I've heard about this rumor long ago.
It was said that Prince Duan
and Her Highness were in love.
Your Majesty, why don't
you grant their wish?
Not only can they be together,
but it can preserve the dignity
of the royal family.
No!
Father! I don't want to be married to him!
Yu, I only want to be married to you!
Shut up!
Since it has come to this,
you don't get to make the call.
Eunuch Li,
draft a decree now.
Appoint Xiao Huaijin, Prince Duan,
as the princess's consort.
He shall marry the princess,
Li Wan'er, tomorrow.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You wretch.
Do you think you can
get rid of me like that?
I was just returning
the present you prepared
to you exactly what it was.
What's the matter?
It's okay for you to hurt someone else,
but it's not okay for you
to be hurt, huh?
I'll kill you right now!
Stop!
Yu.
That wretch was
the cause of everything!
I'm innocent!
Your Highness, today's
your wedding day.
Please return.
Yu,
you and I knew each
other from a young age.
We were childhood
sweethearts for years.
Do you actually
have no feelings for me?
There's no way to force a relationship.
It has already come to this.
There's no need to make it worse.
Yu!
Back then,
when you saved me from bandits,
I swore to only marry no one but you.
I can change my ways if I was wrong.
I promise I won't pick on her again!
She can become your concubine,
your co-wife,
or anything she likes!
I'm begging you,
Yu!
I truly fancy you!
Please don't abandon me!
Yu!
Your Highness,
the auspicious hour is nearing.
Let's return to the palace.
Nanny!
Your Highness.
Yu is the person I fancy!
Why must I be married to Xiao Huaijin?
Let's get up.
No matter what Li Wan'er
has done to me,
she's sincere toward you.
It's merely her selfish
desire to possess.
Not only did we avoid their scheme,
but they also received
their just deserts.
Don't let this matter
trouble you anymore.
♪As the western moon sinks,
the cold lamp burns low♪
♪No one comes knocking
at the mountain gate♪
♪The frosty wind and moonlight
touch me first♪
Although the view is impeccable,
it's fleeting.
It vanishes in an instant.
♪Pear blossoms fill the courtyard,
yet love and hate are plucked away♪
♪One robe of discipline
cannot tame desire, obsession, or anger♪
Although everything
vanishes eventually,
we will encounter wonderful moments
as long as we keep moving forward.
Look.
Look at all of the lanterns.
♪When one look lasts forever,
how do I let myself go on?♪
One of these lanterns
used to be lit for me.
But now,
no one will light any lanterns there.
♪Past matters and old memories
cannot cleanse the six senses♪
Do you trust me?
Once all of this is over,
I'll light the brightest
lantern for you.
♪Fate has long since taken root♪
♪In the mortal world,
it's just the two of us♪
♪Trapped by love♪
♪The dim lamp lights nothing
as one enters the empty gate♪
♪Past matters and old memories
cannot cleanse the six senses♪
♪You are in my dream but
there's no one outside of it♪
♪Bound to a single thought,
I wander adrift in the ocean of pain♪
♪I can never forget
the stars in your bright eyes♪
♪Fate has long since taken root♪
♪In the mortal world,
it's just the two of us♪
♪Trapped by love♪
Are you here to mock me?
You and I once promised
to see each other off
on their wedding day.
Although you failed
to keep your promise,
I have to keep mine.
Shen Changning.
Do you think you've won?
Do you think I've won?
What have I won?
My parents,
my family,
everything I cherished,
all of them are gone.
What makes you think that I've won?
What has that got to do with me?
Is that so?
Do you truly think
that no one would know
that you sold Shen Yunqi
and Lian
to a slave broker?
What a shame.
I'm not the only one
who knows about it.
Pei Yu knows about it as well.
So what if he knows?
So what if he hates me?
So what if you're still alive?
I will forever
be the noblest princess of Liang
and Father's most loved daughter.
All of you will die
as long as I will it!
Has it never occurred to you
why His Majesty took you
as his goddaughter
and allowed you to act brazenly
without disciplining you?
Of course I know.
It's because my father
died for the sake of the state.
He was the hero of Daliang.
Father caused me to be an orphan.
And, I was smart and sensible, too.
That's why he doted on me.
Indeed. General Li
was indeed the hero of Daliang.
But His Majesty,
do you think he truly
cherishes and loves you?
(Someone in the Li Army)
I'm sure you can
(is plotting something)
recognize this handwriting.
Isn't this Father's handwriting?
Back then, the Li Army
was trapped in a valley for six months.
They were running out of supplies.
The casualties were numerous.
Countless people starved to death.
And, reinforcements
were nowhere to be seen.
Our enemy managed to
penetrate their defense.
The Li Army suffered heavy casualties.
General Li
fought until his last breath.
Reinforcements were nowhere to be seen
because heavy snow
had blocked the pass!
It was due to a natural disaster!
Is that so?
If so, why did General Li make
such a chilling remark
before his death?
The formidable Li Army,
were they annihilated by our enemies?
Or did someone plot to do them in?
Someone plotted to do them in?
After the battle of Feiyan Valley,
General Li died on the battlefield.
The Li Army lost more
than half of their men.
His Majesty took you
as his goddaughter.
Not only did he comfort the emotions
of the remaining
members of the Li Army,
but he also managed to enlist them
into the royal family's
Imperial Guards.
Since then,
Daliang lacked an iron-blooded army
capable of matching
the prowess of the Imperial Guards,
had one more spoiled and
overbearing princess,
and had
the most compassionate
emperor in the world.
Nonsense!
Father truly loved me!
From a young age,
no matter what I did,
no matter if they were right or wrong,
he would never punish me!
He didn't punish you
to show the world
his compassion toward you
and the Li Army!
The bigger the mistake you commit,
the more he's able
to show his compassion.
He knew that I fancied Pei Yu.
Thus, he granted us a marriage!
Don't you get it yet?
You were always a pawn.
In the past,
you were a testament
to royal benevolence.
After that,
you're the bind that shackles Pei Yu.
Li Wan'er, just look at you.
Look at who you're getting married to!
Now, you're merely the veil
that covers the royal family's shame.
He granted you a new
marriage to Xiao Huaijin
and didn't defend you
because he knew better than anyone else
that you'd committed too many mistakes.
If he tried to defend you again,
he'd only be reviled
by all under heaven
as an incompetent and inept emperor
who nurtures villains!
As for you,
you're doomed to be a sacrificial pawn.
Enjoy your wedding night.
From today onward,
you'll realize
that today will be
the last best day of your life.
Where's Her Highness?
Your Highness,
Her Highness has been resting inside.
At least she knows her place.
(End of Episode)
Sister.
Since you want to prove
that you are unrelated to them,
just burn
their bodies.
♪Loneliness♪
♪How do I cross it?♪
♪Whom have I ever failed♪
♪Incense burns through a few sticks♪
♪Can the rest of my life be redeemed?♪
♪The flowing years pass
through desolation♪
♪Unwilling to forgive past mistakes♪
♪Blaming myself for not protecting♪
♪Our vows as I should have♪
♪Sorrow♪
♪Counting it carefully♪
♪Who stayed by my side through hardship♪
♪There will eventually be a pure land♪
♪Where all karmic burden is cast away♪
♪Not until worldly splendor fades♪
♪Can one understand
what cuts to the bone♪
♪At dusk, with white hair♪
♪I still cannot fathom destiny♪
♪After countless struggles
across the waters♪
♪At last the lotus heart awakens♪
♪Drifting across three lifetimes♪
♪Just to wait for your
once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
♪The distant mountains
fade along the path home♪
♪I walk with you through morning bells
and evening drums♪
♪Our story lies in the mountains♪
♪Like an ink-washed immortal painting♪
♪Where blossoms fall♪
♪I'm glad the fragrance
in our hearts stays the same♪
♪Youth slips away♪
♪Just to wait for your
once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
♪Dreams wander back
to the old road where we met♪
♪Watching you gently play the zither♪
♪Time rests upon the strings♪
♪Waiting for someone
to brew a pot of tea♪