Characters, actions, locations, occupations, and events in this series
are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Ken.
Have you heard of Shin’s story
when he was in Udon Pithak?
The Tsunami cannot dominate here
because I’ll get them.
Shin. Don’t.
Saint, aren’t you embarrassed
being his gofer?
Since you’re rich enough to pay the fine
for your friends,
What are you doing, Chadjen?
From now on, you better pay for us too.
The heck are you doing?
Everyone, stop.
Everyone, I told you to stop.
Besides improving our curriculum,
We think the school environment
is also important.
We have renovated the buildings
to look modern and beautiful.
Shall we continue?
Thamnithit!
What happened, Saint?
Who trashed the room?
Tell me, did you do it, Saint?
Explain it before things get out of hand.
Why does the classroom look like this?
Did you do it?
What were you thinking?
Class 2 is unbearable.
All they do is cause trouble and chaos.
They never pay attention in class.
Now, you vandalized school properties.
Yes.
I did it.
You live up to the reputation of Class 2.
That’s right.
I’m the president of Class 2.
I need to set an example
for my classmates, Principal.
What do you mean?
Isn’t Cable the president of Class 2?
The year, the class voted
to select a new president.
Saint received the highest votes.
A troubled kid like him
is selected to be the class president.
Ms. Jan and Mr. Sung, what criteria
did you use to select the new president?
For you, Saint.
You’ll be punished and take responsibility
for all the damages.
A BIG WAR
Shin.
How do you go home?
Do you want me to give you a ride?
I can go home by myself.
Do you have any problems?
You can always tell me.
If you have problems with Ken,
I can help you.
You are our class president.
But I don’t need to tell you anything.
I’m glad.
About what?
At least, you accept me as your class president.
Nonsense.
I chose you to be the class president
because I wanted you to learn
about responsibility.
So you won’t treat others like sh*t,
the way you did to me.
I’m sorry.
Hey!
Stop saying you’re sorry.
Your apology is irresponsible.
Stop trying to be nice to me and my friends.
Everything that you do,
It’s useless.
Saint.
Yes, Ms. Jan.
Did you finish cleaning the toilet?
Yes.
Can I ask you something?
What happened in the classroom?
What was the problem between you guys?
You can tell me.
Why do you want to know it?
So I can help you.
Help me?
Why?
I think there is more than what I saw.
Why do you want to know the truth?
Every teacher in this school
sees Class 2 as trouble kids.
I’m asking you.
Let it end with me.
Can you take responsibility for all the damages?
It’s a lot of money.
Tell me the truth.
So I can talk to the principal about it.
If I can’t pay it, you can expel me.
That’s not a solution to the problem, Saint.
So what?
You can’t fix the problem for us.
Then explain to me.
So I can help you.
Can’t you figure it out by yourself?
Don’t you say you have more life experience?
You know everything.
You can judge everything from your perspective.
Saint.
You don’t need to understand us
if you already judge us.
Hello, Dad.
Huh? Police station?
What happened?
Okay, I’ll be right there.
I can give you a ride.
No, I can go by myself.
You didn’t bring your motorcycle today.
Let me give you a ride.
I want to help.
Stairs ahead.
Watch your steps.
I got it.
Slowly.
When are you going to get it, Saint?
Huh?
Listen to me.
From now on, don’t take a blow for me.
The debt is mine. I’ll take responsibility for it.
Even if they hit me to death, let them do it.
You don’t need to take the hit for me.
Dad.
Everything that you did,
It’s useless.
It hurts me even more.
Go thank your teacher for giving you a ride.
I’ll take Pok home.
Watch your steps.
I got it.
My dad told me to thank you for the ride.
It’s not a big deal.
Where is your house?
I can give you a ride.
It’s okay.
My dad and I have to take Pok home.
Pok?
Our noodle cart.
You’re creative with the nickname.
Take your dad home safely.
Yes.
Saint.
You can carry the weight of the world
on your shoulders.
You have a future.
You need to prepare yourself for it.
It’s okay.
I want to do it this way.
Just let it be.
Are you sure you can take
all the responsibility for what happened?
If I take the blame,
the problem will be over.
This is the best solution.
Thank you for giving me a ride.
Why is that trouble kid your class president
instead of you?
Whose idea was it, Cable?
I…
I stepped down.
Stepped down?
Cable, what were you thinking?
I…
I want to focus on my study.
Being a class president took a lot of my time.
I told you besides your grades,
activities are also important for your portfolio.
It’ll increase your chances
for admission interviews.
It’s not easy to get into a law school.
I’m sorry, Mom.
Go study.
Mom.
Can’t you put Thep Burapha and Udon Pithak
students in separate classrooms?
If they are put in the same class,
there will be more problems.
Some students will be bullied.
Some will get hurt.
But it’s the plan that the school board and I have.
Your only job is to focus on your study.
You don’t need to hang out with those kids.
You will be the top student in that class.
Do you get it?
Yes.
Go.
Hey, they are here.
Oh, they brought sticks for us.
I’ll take one. You’re so kind.
I’ll take one.
I’ll take another one.
Thank you.
You, let’s be my partner.
I want to compete with you for some time.
Hey.
You’d better watch out.
If I see you try to mess up with Chadjen again,
I’ll hit you.
So scary.
Please don’t start a fight.
That’s right.
Otherwise, we all will be punished.
Go away, Principal’s son.
Don’t butt in.
You guys are assh*les.
You bully even your friends.
Thep Burapha friendship is so fake.
Watch your freaking mouth!
Should I hit your mouth?
No.
You? Ptooey!
- Assh*le.
- Bring it on.
What’s going on?
Nothing.
We are just practicing.
I’m practicing this attack move.
Bang, bang, bang.
I almost broke his head.
I told you to pair up and practice,
not gang up.
I don’t have a partner.
Is there anyone wanting to be his partner?
Ken.
Do you have a partner?
I don’t want to be his partner.
I’ll do it.
Okay. Go practice with your partners.
The girls, too.
Practice what I taught you.
Don’t just sit around.
I’ll give you 20 minutes to practice.
I’ll be back and start the test.
Go.
Come on, Shin.
I’ll be your partner.
Bring it on.
I think Shin really hates Saint.
Fight back, Saint.
No.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I’ll never hurt you again.
If this is not enough for you,
you can hit me.
Then I’ll do what you said.
Hey, stop it!
Do you want to be punished?
It’s so hot.
Damn. I feel so sticky.
Let’s go play video games.
I don’t have money. Do you have money?
Don’t worry.
We can find money around here.
Good idea.
You can find money from anywhere.
But don’t try to get it from my friends.
So what?
I kind of like your friends’ money.
It’s easy to get.
I don’t need to work hard to get it.
Stay away from Udon Pithak kids.
All of them.
Why do I need to do that?
I warned you.
Are you my dad?
Why do I need to listen to you, assh*le?
If you are the boss of Udon Pithak,
I’m the boss here.
If you are that worried about your friends,
I can arrange it for you.
I’ll arrange a match for you.
I’ll make you and your friends crawl to me,
begging me to leave your retarded friend.
Assh*le.
Come here.
Stop it.
Go away, jack*ss.
Guys, stop it.
Shin.
Stop it.
That’s enough.
Udon Pithak is such a pr*ck.
You think you are better than us?!
Things turn out this way
because your friend started it.
Don’t start another fight.
We should stop them first.
What the f*ck?
Who do you think you are to order me around?
Then why did you blame us?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Stop it.
Drop your act. It’s so annoying.
Shin, stop it. I’m begging you.
Let me go.
Let me go first.
- Let me go.
- You let go first.
Let me go.
Another hot content, everyone
They are brawling.
This is live entertainment.
Come on.
This way is also fun.
Let me go.
Let me go, Eve.
Peeta, let me go.
This way is also fun.
You’re an idiot.
Shin.
Stop it, assh*le.
Your job is studying,
not fighting.
Tell me, who started it.
They started it.
Yes, they picked up a fight with us.
It wasn’t my fault.
These b*tches provoked me.
Yes.
Stop lying.
You two hit us first.
Oh.
How did you control your friends?
Why did they hit our girls first?
Why did they badmouth my friends?
But they shouldn’t hit our friends.
Teachers, they attacked us.
Why the hell did you hit my friends?
Teachers, they hurt my friends.
I’ll slap you.
Everyone, that’s enough.
Stop arguing.
Ging, what did you do?
I was filming them.
Do you want to see it?
I recorded everything.
Why didn’t you try to stop them?
Then I wouldn’t get new content.
Fine.
Do you want to get new content?
I’ll punish all of you.
I don’t care who started it.
Since you had a fight,
all of you will be punished.
But I wasn’t a part of the fight.
This way, you will get new content.
Isn’t it good?
In the end, you take your students’ side.
That’s not true, Shin.
We aren’t taking anyone’s side.
But you didn’t listen to us.
You believe what they said.
You only care about Thep Burapha kids.
Shin, we are now one.
There’s no us or them.
All of you are Siamwit students.
No way.
Udon Pithak will never become one
with Thep Burapha.
We can never live in harmony.
That’s right.
Why do we need to be with them?
We don’t want to be with you either.
Enough!
Why are you following me?
I’m not.
My house is also this way.
Stop lying.
You are not good at lying.
You know me well, Shin.
What are you talking about?
Come on.
We are alone.
You don’t need to be shy.
Shy about what?
I’ll punch you.
Sorry. I’m kidding.
Why are you so quiet when you’re at school?
It’s so not you.
Why are you acting like that?
You talk so much when you are with me.
I talk a lot
only with people I feel comfortable with.
But I don’t feel comfortable with you.
But you once did.
Then I still have a chance to make up with you.
Damn it.
Shin.
Don’t worry about Chadjen.
I’ll take care of it.
I’ll help your friend.
I’m not asking for your help.
If you were me,
you would have done the same.
Stop acting like you know me well.
My friends are upset because Ken
and his minions are picking on Chadjen.
I know that.
That’s why I’m doing this.
Do you think if Ken is punished
for picking on Chadjen,
will the problem be solved?
They will be even angrier at Udon Pithak kids.
I’m doing this
for you and your friends.
What you are doing is useless.
Udon Pithak and Thep Burapha
can never live in harmony.
Just like you and me.
You are here.
I’ve been looking for you.
Looking for me?
Why?
I want to thank you.
Thank me?
For what?
You took the blame for me.
Otherwise, I would have been suspended.
My dad would be mad at me.
You don’t need to thank me.
It’s not a big deal.
No.
If someone helps me,
I need to thank them.
To repay your friendship
When we are friends with someone,
friendship is the most important thing.
Shin told me that.
Are you close with Shin?
Yes.
Shin is my best friend.
He always protects me
when someone teases or bullies me.
But you are often bullied here.
Wouldn’t it be better to move to a new school?
No.
I want to be with Shin.
I guess Shin is your only close friend.
Yes.
He is the best friend I’ve ever had.
That’s true.
He’s the best friend.
Saint.
Should I tell the teachers?
That I threw the chair out of the window.
Don’t do it, Chadjen.
It’s best to let them believe that I did it.
Why?
If you are going to be punished,
Shin will never let it happen.
Things will get worse.
I’m so sick of school lunch.
Look.
Damn it.
What the f*ck are you doing?
Sorry.
I’m just throwing trash into a can.
I guess I missed it.
You can get corky anywhere.
But not with me, jack*ss.
Tew.
Who did this?
Let’s call it an even.
An even? F*ck you.
We didn’t pick up a fight with you this morning.
I’ll make your mouth unable to eat anything.
Assh*le.
Shin.
Stop it. Go away.
Stop it. Let her go.
Don’t butt in.
Don’t do it.
If you have a fight here,
the principal will know it.
F*ck you, Saint.
Are you betraying our fellows?
No, I’m just stopping them.
Don’t butt in.
Go away.
F*ck off.
You, brat.
Did you hit me?
I got another content.
Shin.
You did this to Thep Burapha kids.
You want to start a war,
don’t you?
You also want to start a war, right?
You started it.
Eve and Peeta are being attacked
by your friends in the lady’s room.
That’s Airy’s business, not mine.
But if you mess up with Udon Pithak kids,
I’ll punch you in the face.
That’s easy
After the last class is over,
Come to meet me at the basketball court.
So we will know…
whether Thep Burapha
or Udon Pithak,
who is the king?
Shin, don’t do it.
Saint, assh*le.
Don’t butt in.
Do you hear me?
I warn you.
If you lose,
you and Thep Burapha kids have to stay away
from Udon Pithak kids especially Chadjen.
Don’t ever come near him.
If you lose,
that dork and you will be crushed.
We’ll see.
Miss Jan.
I was the one
who threw the chair out of the window.
What happened, Chadjen?
Why did you do that?
I…
Ken and his friends extorted money from me.
And…
Shin helped me.
So they were hitting Shin.
I was scared
and didn’t know how to help him.
So I…
I threw the chair out of the window.
Everyone, get out of the room.
The principal is downstairs.
Go.
Ken, go.
Girls, you too.
I’ll take the blame.
What are you doing this for?
You should get out
before the teachers get here.
Take your friends with you.
Go.
It’s okay, Chadjen.
It was not your fault.
I’ll punish Ken and his friends.
Please don’t do that.
Don’t worry.
I’ll make sure they will be punished.
If you do that, things will get worse.
Why?
What did they threaten you?
If you punish them,
they will be mad.
After that,
there will be a bigger war among the students.
A war?
What are you talking about?
Umm…
This evening, Ken and Shin…
They are going to have a fight.
I knew that Saint didn’t do it.
But I didn’t think
that Chadjen was also a part of it.
What are you going to do about it?
I’m thinking.
If I tell Mr. Pokpong about this,
he will tell the principal.
It will become a big problem.
The students might be expelled.
But we should detain Ken and his friends.
At least, we can stop the fight.
It’s just like what Saint did.
We just delay it.
If they want to have a fight,
they can use anything as an excuse to start a fight.
So are we going to do nothing about it?
No.
I’m gathering evidence.
What evidence?
The evidence to convict Ken and his friends
for extorting money from Chadjen.
Shin.
Is there no way for me to stop you?
You know the answer.
What do I need to do for you to stop?
Stop bugging me. It’s annoying.
I’m worried about you.
Don’t worry about me.
Stop it.
I’m begging you.
I told you.
You and I are not friends anymore.
So I don’t care what you think.
I don’t believe you.
Look at me in the eyes.
Say it again.
Say that you don’t care about me.
I won’t do it.
I hate you.
Let’s find out…
who will rule Siamwit.
Let’s end it today.
I don’t care who will rule this damn school.
Just stay away from my friends.
I’ll break your damn skull.
You’re freaking annoying me.
I’ll hit you.
Hey.
Ken, stop it.
Don’t fight with our classmates.
Saint, assh*le.
What the f*ck are you doing?
Get out of the way.
I’m asking you.
You know whose fault it was for what happened.
Saint, whose side are you taking?
Aren’t you a Thep Burapha student?
I’m not taking anyone’s side.
Saint, if you don’t want your ass to be kicked,
then get out.
If you want to kick someone’s ass,
Then do it to me.
Fine. I can do it.
I’ve been waiting for this chance.
What the f*ck is wrong with you?
You’re a Thep Burapha fellow, jack*ss.
Do you hear me, assh*le?
What the f*ck is wrong with you?
What the heck is this?
They are attacking their own fellow.
Did Saint lose his mind?
Your body is made from steel or something?
Guys.
Stop it.
Stop hitting him.
Miss Jan.
This teacher is f*cking annoying.
Please don’t hurt her.
Get out of my way.
Saint, how dare you?!
Let me go.
You finally show your true color.
Let me go, Saint.
(Kasidit, Nattaphat, Nattakit.)
(Come to meet me in my room now.)
(I repeat come to see me right now.)
What the f*ck is this?
(If you don’t come to my room in three minutes.)
(I’ll call your parents.)
Damn. This is so lame.
Guys.
Let’s go home.
See you.
I’ll call you when I am done.
Come on, assh*le.
Damn it.
Saint, are you okay?
What?
Chadjen, what are you doing?
Where are you going?
Since you’re rich enough to pay the fine
for your friends,
from now on, you better pay for us too.
You extorted money from Chadjen.
Then you had a fight with Shin
when he tried to help Chadjen.
Ging, did you betray us?
I didn’t tell him.
But he thought that
I probably have the video clip of the incident.
A good thing about content seekers,
They’re always present where troubles happen.
Damn it.
Damn you, Ging.
What about you, Eve and Peeta?
Are you telling us off
to get away from your penalty?
I didn’t tell him anything.
Mr. Sung told us to come here.
You not only refuse
to own up to your wrongdoings.
You also threaten your friends.
You guys are so wussy.
If I show this video to the principal.
You will be expelled.
Your parents will be okay with it, right?
What do you want?
It’s simple.
Stop fighting.
Stop bullying your classmates.
If I find out that you’re still doing it,
I’ll show this video to your parents.
At least, you will have to pay a fine.
Because you damaged school’s properties.
Are your parents willing to pay for it?
Why did Thamnithit take the blame alone?
He didn’t want Udon Pithak students
to have a fight with Thep Burapha students.
If they both were punished,
Udon Pithak students would never stop
until they got their revenge.
These kids only use force to solve problems.
That’s why Thamnithit took the blame.
To be honest, I was wrong about this kid.
Although his past doesn’t look good,
he’s a good kid.
He’s a good kid?
I don’t believe it.
Just wait and you’ll see
that he will cause another problem.
Are you going to punish
the kids who were involved in the fight?
What about the damages?
The damages have been paid already.
Who paid for it?
Chadjen’s father.
It seems that Chadjen
will not finish this semester here.
He will move to another school.
I have an announcement to make.
From today on,
If you are late for school,
You will be fined 100 baht
and memorize 50 English words with me.
What?
I don’t want to do it.
Or if you don’t want to
memorize 50 English words,
you can memorize Thai poems with Miss Jan.
I don’t want to memorize anything.
You are so annoying.
Should I increase it to 100 words?
No, I don’t want to do it.
150 words?
Class.
You don’t need to do that.
Class 2.
You know that you caused embarrassment
and damages to our school,
with your fight and vandalism.
You cause trouble almost every day.
This time, we will not punish you.
It’s an exception.
But we want to have an agreement with you.
From now on, if any of you use violence,
or start a fight in school,
If you are caught, you will be expelled.
Stay. I’ll leave.
About Ken,
I think you shouldn’t play his game.
It’s not worth it.
I’ll do whatever I want.
If you don’t stop, you will be expelled.
Listen to me.
You have a future waiting for you.
How can you say that?
My future has been ruined since then.
Because of a sc*mbag like you.
I’m sorry.
I’ll do everything you tell me to do.
But can you do one thing for me?
Can you be my friend again?
That friend of mine.
He was honest.
He never abandoned me.
He never ran away from problems.
Jack*ss.
Aren’t you going to pay me back?
Why don’t you pay me back?
Shin.
What are you doing to my friend?
He doesn’t pay me back.
So he’s getting beaten up.
Take my money.
300 baht is not enough.
He owed me over 1,000 baht.
Fine.
I’ll find money to pay you back.
If you can’t pay me now,
I have to kick him as a deposit.
No.
Saint.
Won’t you pay me back?
Jack*ss.
Assh*le.
Get out.
Saint.
Pr*ck.
Bastard.
Come on.
My head.
Are you okay, Shin?
You should worry about yourself first.
Why did you take their kicks for me?
It’s less hurt if we share the kicks.
One more thing, I’m a man of steel.
This can’t do anything to me.
My head really hurts.
Let me take a look.
Okay, it’s not broken.
Come on.
Give me your other hand.
Damn.
Get up slowly.
Stop and sit down.
What are you doing?
I’m carrying you.
Get on.
No. I don’t need it.
I can walk.
Get on.
Saint.
Give me the other hand.
One, two.
Damn it. My back!
Saint.
What?
Thank you.
You don’t need to thank me.
We are friends. It’s not a big deal.
I’m sorry.
You are getting hurt because of me.
It’s okay.
I can take the pain for you.
Jack*ss, don’t act so proud.
I’ll bite your ear off.
Dumb*ss, why didn’t you say anything
when you were beaten up?
You laid on top of me
when they were kicking us.
You were so damn heavy.
Stop talking, assh*le.
Unfortunately,
that friend of mine…
he was dead.
A guy like you can never replace him.
Hello.
Is this okay?
Did you defeat him?
I hadn’t started yet.
They stopped the fight first.
I knew you were losers.
Ken, do you want to join my gang?
Of course.
Listen to my words.
If you can’t defeat Udon Pithak kids,
you will never get to join my gang.
I’ll give the three of you another chance,
Defeat Shin.
Crush him.
Do everything to make sure
that he has no place in Siamwit.
Yes.
What the hell are you doing?
Nonsense.
What nonsense about it?
My little worm is cute.
Are you and Shin close?
I want you to make Shin shed tears.
If you can do it, I will forgive the debt.
You all will have to suffer
more than my friend does right now,
you bastard.
Beat him up.