I don't feel disgusted at all.
Qingkong
there's also
that's because I saw you.
Just by standing in front of me,
you've achieved your goal.
You again.
People who make the same mistake twice are really stupid.
But this time,
I not only have an audio recording,
but also a video.
Just you wait.
I'm going to report this right now.
What are you afraid of?
Yi Xinran is the one at a disadvantage now.
I just wanted to disgust Yi Xinran
and disgust Qingkong as well.
Do you have anything else to say?
Teacher,
my senior and I didn't do anything.
The photos
were secretly taken by Bai Qianyu using camera tricks.
In the end,
she was also the one who spread them.
Alright,
you two can go back first.
As for the outcome,
wait for the school's notification.
Bai Qianyu.
What can I say about you?
What about school?
This time, we can't keep you here.
Teacher,
I...
Why?
Everyone likes you.
Yi Xinran.
On what grounds?
You must be very happy now.
Qingkong likes you.
Even Jia Yan has gone from being your enemy to admiring you.
Not everyone is like you.
I don't know why,
but ever since my plan failed that time,
my hatred for you
has only grown stronger.
You still don't understand,
do you? Your own problem?
You always think it's someone else's fault.
The development of things always has its inevitability.
No snowflake is innocent.
Isn't that right?
Hello, dorm supervisor.
Please carry on.
Can you forgive me then?
Why don't you just call 110?
Could it be that after that time travel,
I changed Bai Qianyu's fate?
To fall for the same person twice,
This time it's Qingkong again.
It's him again.
What on earth does he see in you?
Is Qingkong helping me again?
I'm about to leave.
Qingkong should be leaving today.
Yi Xinran.
Stop right there!
Yi Xinran, don't think you can just walk away.
If it weren't for you,
how would I have ended up in this situation?
I won't let you off the hook.
Let go of me!
Yi Xinran!
Die!
Qingkong.
It's so good to see you.
You used your special ability.
You'll be punished.
I don't want you to hurt yourself for me.
I just want you to be healthy and well.
It's enough for me just to see you.
Every time we travel through time,
it creates a butterfly effect.
If one of us
has to be punished,
let it be me.
I don't want you to suffer.
Even if it means annihilation,
I don't want you to be annihilated.
Stop it now.
Yi Xinran.
I love you.
Qingkong.
I can't forget him.