[English subtitles are available]
[New Life Begins]
[Episode 7]
[Danchuan Palace]
[Danpei Hall]
Madam,
the people from Xinchuan have entered the palace.
So what?
[Madam Danchuan: Shangguan Yan]
If my sister doesn't want to go back, she doesn't need to do that.
Sister.
But the situation is serious now.
Lord Xinchuan sent his two sons here.
If I don't go back,
I will put you in danger.
Peace alliance of the nine regions?
It means sacrificing women to maintain a relationship.
I've made up my mind.
Three years later, Danchuan women won't participate in the selection.
I can protect them, and I can protect you, too.
Sister.
Danchuan has been flooded many times.
No matter how immature I am,
I know that we need Xinchuan's help now.
Three years?
It's too long.
We can't fight against Xinchuan now.
No matter how weak Danchuan is,
there's still the strongest Navy in the nine regions.
No matter what, Xinchuan has to be cautious.
Don't worry about that.
Just ask yourself if you're willing or not.
If you don't,
I can protect you
even if Lord Xinchuan comes.
Where should I sit?
You can't let me sit there.
That should be your lady's seat.
Well.
I...
I can't stand here.
I don't even deserve a seat, right?
You're bullying me.
Madam Danchuan is here.
You've come a long way. Don't stand on ceremony.
Have a seat.
Offer a seat for him, too.
You've had a long trip today.
We've prepared hot pot of Danchuan.
Please enjoy it.
Please.
But, theirs are two-flavor hot pot.
Why is mine this?
You are the son-in-law of Danchuan.
Of course you should follow the customs there.
I specially ordered someone to prepare Spicy Hot Pot, which is Jing's favorite.
Please have a taste.
These dishes just look scary,
but they are actually quite delicious.
Maybe Madam Danchuan wants to test the Prince Qi.
Don't worry.
The first one, fish eye
is most suitable for those who are blind.
This is...
It's not bad.
The second one, Huanghou
is the cardiac tube of the cow.
In Danchuan, people who are dishonest are like this cow.
I think these dishes suit your taste.
Offer the last dish.
What is this?
This is the pig brain.
If the son-in-law of Danchuann mistreats his wife,
we wouldn't mind eating his brain.
Since Madam Danchuan asked us to come back to wait for news,
don't worry.
I'll sleep on the couch tonight.
You are the boss.
There's no reason to let you sleep on the couch.
I don't think anyone sleeps in the same room with his book.
It's because the Prince Qi is here.
It's better for us to sleep in the same room.
It'll be bad if they know we are fake couple.
All right.
Let me sleep here.
You have to go to the palace tomorrow.
It seems that it is not easy to deal with Madam Danchuan.
You have to take a lot of trouble.
Have a good rest.
Danchuan is the only place in the nine regions that has a night market.
Do you want to take a look?
Sure.
Okay.
Let's go. I also want to.
Let's go.
Rest early if you're not feeling well.
Zheng.
Listen to me.
Listen to me, your brother.
Here's the thing.
This is my analysis.
Our life is so hard.
We should have fun while we're alive.
We don't know what will happen tomorrow,
right?
And my stomachache is empty.
I'm afraid I'll starve to death in the toilet if I continue to have diarrhea.
It's embarrassing.
Eat something.
Let's go! Li Wei.
Right! There must be something in my stomachache.
Let's go.
[Night Market in Danchuan]
So many people.
That's too much.
It's OK.
Pork skewers.
Freshly roasted trotters.
Would you like some trotters?
Sir, give me a portion of trotters.
OK, a big trotter.
Here you are. Take care of it.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Prince Qi.
Would you like one?
It's coming.
I... I need to go to the toilet.
Walk around to wait for me.
Excuse me.
Take care.
Thank you, Sir.
Buy again if you like it.
Don't miss it.
Fruits ice jelly tastes good.
What would you like?
Sir, I want some longan ice jelly
and some oranges.
You can eat oranges as many as you want.
Do you want it?
Sir,
how could you ask your wife to peel an orange for you?
Exactly.
As a matrilocal husband,
it's a shame to let your wife peel an orange.
You understood. He is not...
What do you mean?
Let me show you. Watch carefully.
How should you take care of your wife?
Exactly.
Learn from him.
Watch carefully.
Boss.
May I borrow your sword?
Go ahead.
The fruit plate is here.
See?
Your Ladyship,
please enjoy.
This is so delicate.
Do you like it?
Your wife obviously likes it.
Learn it quickly.
Yes.
These are the basic skills.
How did you get a wife
if you can't do these?
I've been in Danchuan for so long,
but I've never seen such a bad matrilocal husband like you.
Really.
You know nothing about how to be a matrilocal husband.
Peel an apple for your wife.
Don't you understand?
Everyone,
thank you for teaching my matrilocal husband.
We have to go now.
Let's go.
Your Highness.
I overstepped my boundary just now.
I shouldn't call you a matrilocal husband.
Please forgive me.
Although they speak harshly,
they really love their wives.
If people love each other,
it's not bad to be a matrilocal husband.
If they don't love each other,
even if it's an imperial order,
it's hard to compromise.
It's the fast mask-changing in Danchuan Opera!
♫The south wind meets the clouds and the moonlight calls the candle♫
♫As far as the eye can see, it's just a regular sight♫
♫Why am I being absent-minded? And why am I hesitating?♫
♫I'm worried that you'll see through my mind by my eyes♫
♫My words are not surprising. Nor is my language inaccurate♫
♫I've got some affection towards you♫
♫I don't speak in an excessive way. Nor do I express my feelings♫
♫Who should I tell about the one I love?♫
♫By now, my words have turned into wind, and my missing of you has melted into fog♫
♫I wrote about the past into a letter♫
♫If you and I know each other well, there's no need to write more♫
♫My mind runs wild, and I don't where is the way to go back♫
♫I love you deeply and there's nothing else I ask for♫
♫I only wish the two of us could love each other as one soul, eat three meals together and spend the four seasons together♫
Excuse me.
Zheng.
You're still acting tough in a terrible health condition.
Is this the fast mask-changing that Shangguan Jing mentioned?
It's so lively.
I'll watch it in the front.
Where are you going?
Great!
The order of Madam Danchuan:
Ying Qi, the son-in-law of Danchuan,
is filthy,
and unforgivable
with a sharp tongue.
He must pass the exam for husbands,
and then he can see the princess.
Please enter the palace immediately.
Lady-in-waiting,
what is the exam for a husband?
What is it?
It includes husband's appearance,
husband's words,
husband's virtues,
and husband's skills,
aiming to test the moral integrity of a man.
Husband's appearance
means appearance.
Prince Qi is obviously not good enough in this aspect.
And he disappointed us in the husband's words and virtues.
Now he can win a round just in the husband's skills.
The first thing is winning in the Mahjong.
If a man from Danchuan can't win in the Mahjong,
he's not a capable man.
Prince Qi,
please.
Self-drawn!
I win!
Three Characters.
Pong.
No.
I made a mistake.
He regretted his choice, reflecting that he has bad qualities when playing Mahjong.
Three Dots.
Kong.
He is not good at calculating the numbers of cards, reflecting that he is not smart.
Eight Dots.
Do you want it?
Stop dawdling.
One Bamboo.
Are you sure?
Let me think.
Let me see.
He discarded, reflecting he that he has bad characters.
He is hesitate, reflecting that he is narrow-minded.
You can't make it.
You can win by seven pairs.
They are cheating.
Will it work?
One Character.
Eighty Characters.
Four Dots.
Nine Characters.
Five Characters.
Three Bamboos.
One Dot.
Seven Dots.
Five Dots.
Three Bamboos.
Four Dots.
Seven Dots.
Eight Bamboos.
Seven Bamboos.
Three Bamboos.
Nine Characters.
One Character.
Five Bamboos.
Four Dots.
One Bamboo.
I know.
Nine Dots.
I win.
Seven pairs.
I win!
All of you have to give me chips.
Hurry up.
Give me the chips.
All of you!
I finally see the money coming back.
Is he the sixth Prince, Yin Zheng?
Yes.
It's a necessary skill
for matrilocal husbands of Danchuan to take care of their wives.
Ear cleaning is an important skill to serve their wife.
Hang in there, Su.
Su Shen!
Su.
Butler Su!
Prince Zheng is calling you.
If you like it,
you can come to Danchuan to enjoy it.
What did you say?
Your monthly salary is gone.
He's not good at it.
Right.
Be careful, the Prince Qi.
I was hurt when someone cleaned my ears.
So I beat him to death for half a year.
How come?
Your Highness,
you should make chili oil with them
and let the Princess choose randomly.
If she chooses yours,
you can meet her.
How is that possible?
I have tracheal inflammation.
I almost coughed out my lungs while cooking chili last time.
You're making things difficult for me.
In the name of the alliance,
you marry the Princess but treat her bad.
You are making things difficult for us.
It's our fault.
We accept it.
Fine.
As long as Madam Danchuan can calm down,
I accept it.
All you're thinking is to calm Madam down.
You really don't understand.
What does this mean?
Hurry up.
They're all gone.
I see.
The lady-in-waiting just said we didn't understand
because we only wanted to finish the task
in the beginning
to please Madam Danchuan.
But the reason why we came here
is to change Jing's mind.
Prince Qi,
think about it.
Although you don't like Danchuan,
this is Jing's home.
Women are the most respected here.
She lived a carefree life in Danchuan.
But she's lonely in Xinchuan.
You're the only one she gets along with every day.
But you treated her well just to get a concubine.
She must be sad.
Actually, they're not trying to torture you.
They just want to tell you how women of Danchuan live.
Think about it.
You feel uncomfortable here.
Shangguan Jing is also uncomfortable in Xinchuan.
Please have a taste of these five chili oil.
Spicy stuffing.
Since you know which one is made by him,
it also means you don't have to choose that one.
The order of Madam Danchuan:
Although I said
if the Princess recognized the chili oil made by Prince Qi of Xinchuan,
they can meet.
Princess has chosen Prince Qi's.
Prince Qi is not virtuous.
Madam Danchuan has withdrawn her order.
What? You're fooling me.
Prince Qi.
I am just fooling you.
You have had someone in your heart.
You don't know how to deal with your marriage.
Even on the Mid-Autumn Festival night,
you used every means to fawn on my sister.
She was so happy.
But you were actually fooling her.
Just to get a concubine to fill your emptiness,
how could you fool my sister?
Of course I'll let you have the same feeling.
Madam Danchuan,
this is an order, which will be shown to Lord Xinchuan.
You're being childish.
Are you going to embarrass Xinchuan?
Prince Zheng,
we both know what's going on.
If it goes up to the level of bilateral relationship,
do you think we will be afraid?
Please mind your words.
You've seen
how much Xinchuan care about Danchuan.
But backtracking
is not the right thing for Madam Danchuan to do.
Do you think the King of a region
can sacrifice their own interests for others?
But I'm not like that.
If I can't protect my own people,
I don't deserve to be Madam Danchuan.
So you mean
you want Prince Qi and the Princess
to divorce.
If Prince Qi is not someone who can make my sister happy,
divorce may be good for them.
Ridiculous!
How dare they!
Your Highness!
Calm down!
I can't stop you.
You can't make Prince Zheng fail the mission.
Don't worry.
I won't implicate Zheng.
Tell them I ran away from home.
Ask Lord to arrest me.
Why are you wanted?
Get out!
Well.
Move!
Go away!
Prince Qi.
Don't touch me.
Prince Qi,
you can't just care about yourself.
What about others if you leave?
What about me?
What should I do?
If Madam Danchuan goes on like this,
I can't live.
Prince,
you have to think like this.
If you leave,
there must be a dispute between Xinchuan and Danchuan.
If they don't get along, they might fight.
If they fight,
you will be remembered forever.
Enough.
What does it have to do with him?
Brother.
I support you.
Zheng.
You just escape.
I will arrest you immediately.
You're helping me get my badge of honor.
But father might break your legs.
If you can't walk, I'll help you.
It won't hinder you from taking a concubine.
Run now.
Legs...
Prince Qi.
You're a mature man.
Why are you still immature?
Why are we here?
As a prince,
shouldn't you think about the peace between Xinchuan and Danchuan?
I know you don't like Shangguan.
I don't like Prince Zheng either.
But I stay here for the sake of Jichuan.
I mean,
I don't deserve you
and you don't like me.
I think you are very shabbily treated.
What? What are you talking?
It's my business!
What should I do?
We have concerns.
They also have concerns.
After all, they want to vent their anger.
Let's make a pledge
and talk to Madam Danchuan directly.
The pledge should be sincere.
Just accept any punishment!
Maybe you can be saved by this.
Will it work?
[Danpei Hall]
[I, Yin Qi, the fifth Prince of Xinchuan promised never to take a concubine in my life to Shangguan Yan, Madam Danchuan and Shangguan Jing, Princess Danchuan.]
[Take this as proof.]
Madam,
Prince Zheng of Xinchuan wants to see you.
Madam Danchuan.
You can be frank, Prince Qi.
This marriage is the proof of the alliance between Xinchuan and Danchuan.
You help the Princess vent the anger
because you want her to have a better life
after going backing.
But I guess
Madam Danchuan has been dissatisfied with the century-old peace alliance for a long time.
You want to take this opportunity to demonstrate to Xinchuan.
How can you say that?
In the nine regions election every three years,
Danchuan usually made many excuses to evade it.
Only when you suffered floods,
and needed our help,
you would unwillingly choose a suitable girl for the peace-making marriage.
Madam Danchuan treated women equally.
You can't bear to let the commoners suffer.
So this responsibility
should be taken by your family.
That's right.
You look down on women,
regard women as objects,
and sacrifice them in exchange for profits.
Danchuan is not like that.
Besides, it's Prince Qi's behavior that
humiliated Danchuan.
Even if I agree to let Jing go back,
I'm afraid my navy won't agree.
Danchuan suffered floods and was saved by Xinchuan.
And the other regions relies on Xinchuan.
Once the war starts,
Danchuan will be alone and helpless.
Are you threatening me?
I dare not.
But we both know
peace is good for everyone.
The century-old peace alliance can't be shaken.
I just want to make a deal with you.
A deal?
What deal?
It's not impossible to change
the rule that forming peace alliances by peace-making marriage.
Now is not the time but it will be in the future.
I'm willing to give you a promise.
If I have the power one day,
I will definitely reform this unreasonable old system of peace-making marriage.
You are good at the maneuver of the skilled diplomats.
But why should I believe you?
You're the prince of Xinchuan.
Will you think about Danchuan?
It is not only for Danchuan,
but for the nine regions.
It's hard to force people to get married.
Instead of making two people be enemies,
it's better to use profit as bases.
Now, we all emphasize on business.
Isn't business more reliable than marriage?
Times change and things should be different.
If Xinchuan is too conservative, it can't be Xinchuan.
Prince Zheng,
I didn't expect
you are so frank in Danchuan.
Madam and I share the same view.
It doesn't matter to be frank.
Besides, if the Princess is willing to return to Xinchuan,
we will definitely restrain Prince Qi.
We won't let her be mistreated again.
That's all I have to say.
Please think about it.
I will practice archery and train soldiers
with my sister in the afternoon.
Thank you, Madam.
I didn't expect her to be so powerful.
Surprised?
Do you regret not treating her well?
I thought
she only used 30% of her power to hit me.
Otherwise, I would've been dead.
Nice shot.
Shangguan.
Well.
Listen to me.
Shanguan, it's not easy for me to get here.
Shangguan.
Listen to me.
It's not easy for me to see you here.
I've written a pledge that I'll never take a concubine.
Can you forgive me this time?
-You don't know that I've gone through a lot to see you. -Stop him.
I've never seen those things before.
Madam.
Let me wrap it for you.
It's so hard.
Sister, don't scare him.
He can't stand being frightened.
Are you okay?
I'm OK. Don't worry.
What are you doing?
That's too much!
I just came to see her.
What?
Do you still want me to die?
You can't see the Princess Danchuan as you wish
unless you pass our test.
Come on.
Let's compete in archery.
If you win her,
I will let my sister give you another chance.
What?
You dare not?
He dares.
Why would I dare?
I don't know how.
You don't know how? Learn it!
Learn what?
Can I make it now?
How about I compete on behalf of my brother?
What does this have to do with you?
Why not?
We are blood relation.
My Fifth Brother is indeed not good at archery.
Even if your Lady-in-waiting wins,
it would be unfair.
Okay.
Since Prince Zheng joins,
let me compete with you.
Request for comment.
But you have to shoot the target on the boat.
So this is the target on the boat.
I think I can do it at such a close distance.
I'll do it.
Who said you would shoot with your eyes opening?
There is a bell under the jade pendant.
You should recognize its location by the sound.
Zheng, you do it.
You can do it.
No, no, no.
You do it.
Don't be humble.
It is so urgent now!
I trust you.
Come on.
Prince Zheng.
You flatter me.
Please.
Don't be nervous.
You lost.
You have to admit defeat.
Wait.
How?
Prince Zheng shot the central of the jelly pendant with his arrow.
Impressive!
Prince Zheng.
I lost.
You are flattering me, Madam.
Can you give my brother a chance?
I have my own plan.
Shangguan.
How can you be so good?
You must have practiced secretly behind my back.
You took all the archery classes I didn't attend, right?
You didn't work hard but blame me now.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
You're really something.
Let's go.
Here, eat more.
This tofu is delicious.
Do you like it?
Is it spicy? What do you think?
A little, but I can take it.
Is your hand okay?
Yes.
Actually, I'm in a dilemma now.
I came here
to persuade you to go back.
But as a friend,
I hope you can make your own choice.
Although your sister said if Prince Zheng wins,
you can give Prince Qi a chance.
But it's not the first time that she has broken her promise.
If you're really pushing yourself...
As if someone is talking about me.
Madam.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Have a seat.
Sit.
Jing told me
you were her first friend in Xinchuan.
I have to thank you.
Eat.
Here.
The beef is very delicious.
Actually, I feel very good in Danchuan this time.
It's really nice.
It's like coming back to my hometown, Jichuan.
In Jichuan,
everyone chooses a partner according to their wishes.
But my father's official rank is too low.
I had no choice but to marry the prince of Xinchuan.
Were you forced?
Do you mean you didn't want to marry him?
Of course.
Who would like to marry someone they don't know?
So,
we are...
Yes.
We are the same.
Marriage is just a business.
I can order
to let you stay in Danchuan for a matrilocal husband.
Good idea.
At least one of us can get out of this suffering.
Right?
No need.
Prince Zheng
is a nice person.
We get along like friends.
And he never forced us to be a real couple.
So I'm doing fine.
Thank you for your kindness.
Eat up.
What did Shangguan Jing say?
She didn't say yes.
What? Didn't we pass?
Didn't Zheng win the archery?
Why isn't it working?
What's wrong with them?
Prince Qi,
if you want to take her back
because of the order of Lord Xinchuan,
it would be unfair to her.
You should ask yourself
if you want to live with her.
I...
In Danchuan,
we eat hot pot and play mahjong together.
It's so happy.
Although a woman is the head in Danchuan,
we live a peaceful life.
It's not as scary as you said.
I'm not unwilling.
This room is a little hot.
I need some fresh air.
It's too stuffy.
You guys talk.
It's too hot.
Dryness-heat.
Actually, it's very possible for him and Shangguan.
I didn't know
you are so good at archery.
You're holding the book upside down.
You're not reading at all.
Did I do something wrong
that made you angry?
If they don't love each other,
even if it's an imperial order,
it's hard to compromise.
I don't like Prince Zheng either.
But I stayed here for the sake of Jichuan.
Zheng.
The people from Danchuan Palace are here again.
Let's take a look.
Coming.
The order of Madam Danchuan:
If the alliance between the two regions is based on the engagement,
we would like to invite Prince Zheng of Xinchuan to marry Madam Danchuan
as a matrilocal husband,
contributing to the peace between the two regions.
What is this?
I can distinguish "Zheng" and "Qi".
But
what does it have to do with him?
♫The weather is cool, the clouds are light♫
♫Flowing waters greet people♫
♫In the breeze♫
♫Your gentle smile♫
♫It is remembered in my heart♫
♫The red cherry blossoms fall with the wind♫
♫Weapons run out, time passes♫
♫Everything goes with the wind♫
♫As I remember you♫
♫I will have a nice day♫
♫My life is related with you♫
♫The chance meeting made me fall in love at first sight♫
♫Rain and wind♫
♫Wet the footprints♫
♫You're the reason I'm here♫
♫Mountains and rivers stretch for thousands of miles because of you♫
♫We enjoy at the grassy grass at the pavilion♫
♫My love♫
♫Won't change♫
♫No matter the ends of the earth, I will wait for you♫
♫The red cherry blossoms fall with the wind♫
♫Weapons run out, time passes♫
♫Everything goes with the wind♫
♫As I remember you♫
♫I will have a nice day♫
♫I'll give you the rest of my life and we'll be together♫
♫We have fallen in love with each other as time goes♫
♫Rain and wind♫
♫Wet the footprints♫