[English subtitles are available]
[New Life Begins]
[Episode 1]
The world is divided into nine regions.
Different regions cultivate different local conditions and customs.
[Mochuan]
Mochuan in the north has a strong army.
The herdsmen live scattered there.
[Cangchuan]
Cangchuan in the northwest is dry and arid.
There's a lack of resources.
Daichuan in the midland has criss-cross mountains.
[Daichuan]
It has rich mineral resources.
[Yanchuan]
Yanchuan in the south has small and barren land,
but it produces flowers and fruits.
Yingchuan in the southeast has abundant rain.
[Yingchuan]
It's evergreen all year round.
The nine regions mostly worship men.
[Jichuan]
However, Jichuan in the southwest subscribes to monogamy
and equality of men and women.
Danchuan where people love spicy food is dominated by women.
[Danchuan]
Women are forthright,
and there are more matrilocal husbands.
Jinchuan in the east is a coastal region,
[Jinchuan]
where trade is prosperous.
They have been doing business for generations there
and they respect the rich.
Xinchuan is the head of the nine regions.
[Xinchuan]
They value the hierarchy of wife-concubine offspring the most.
Men are superior and women are inferior there as well.
The nine regions had fought for years
until Xinchuan won.
They established a century-old peace alliance,
according to which, each region shall select girls of the right age as a tribute
to marry the princes of Xinchuan.
No one can disobey it.
[Yingchuan]
[Yanchuan]
[Daichuan]
Why is there a donkey carriage?
Stop searching.
Do you remember what we practiced at home?
Yes.
Have some peanuts, Father.
[Junior official from Jichuan, Li Wenbi]
What if they ask about your family background?
My family has been farmers for three generations.
Only my father passed the exam.
But his post was so junior
that he couldn't get into Jichuan Palace.
I come from an ordinary family.
We have nothing but a small plot of land.
Don't forget to act like you're poor too.
Okay.
What if they ask you if you've been educated?
[Boss of the family, Zhuge Xiaolei]
Have some pancakes, Mother.
No.
Are you educated?
I'm not that literate,
but I can read some menus.
[Little brother, Li Cang]
Play ignorant.
Okay.
What if they have to ask what you are good at?
I'm Li Wei, from Jichuan.
[Girl for selection from Jichuan, Li Wei]
I don't know much about
the Classics and Rites,
or needlework.
The only thing I'm good at is tasting cuisine.
Don't worry.
How can I get selected
if I say things like this.
Princes of Xinchuan won't like me.
What if they are blind?
Our family is so unlucky.
Tell me.
Is there anyone from Jichuan
that's willing to marry into such a shabby place to suffer?
If it weren't for your father's incompetence,
our daughter wouldn't be in this fire pit to start with.
It's all my fault.
Father.
What happened?
Why did it stop?
Slowly.
Madam.
The donkey carriage is not moving.
-It's not moving. -What happened?
We are in a hurry to enter the city.
Don't block the way.
A donkey chauffeur is here to for the selection as well?
Sorry.
We'll fix it right away.
What's the hurry?
Come on.
Let's go.
Li, push harder!
Why is it not moving?
You two are so stubborn.
If you don't behave, I'll turn you into donkey burgers.
Don't use violence.
You need to convince the donkeys with virtue.
Right, Mother.
The more you push them, the more they won't go.
It's getting late.
You can't send me into the palace.
Let's part here.
What about the donkeys?
I have my own way.
It works.
Great.
Sis, you are amazing.
Father, Mother.
Go back now.
Don't worry about me.
Wei.
Be careful.
Wait for the good news of me losing the selection.
Looking forward to the good news of your failure.
Come back soon.
Sister.
Take care of yourself.
[Xinchuan Palace]
Carriages, stop here.
Girls from the nine regions, please get off your carriages
and line up
to enter the palace.
Go in.
Anything from outside the palace
is not allowed to be brought into Xinchuan Palace.
Please be aware and behave yourselves, girls.
[Identity files]
[Nanny Yang, who's in charge of education]
[Nanny Liu, who's in charge of management]
What are these?
[Girl for selection from Yingchuan, Ruan Sisi]
You can't bring these in.
Go in.
Princess Danchuan is noble.
Lord specially asked us to allow you to bring your spear into the palace.
[Princess Danchuan, Shangguan Jing]
But this package must be left here.
My family is poor.
I didn't bring anything.
Go in.
How dare you hide food?
Search her!
There's nothing.
Nanny.
Search.
That's all.
Enough.
Behind.
Leave me one.
-Nanny. -She even brought an apple.
Alright.
Search carefully.
Nothing's left.
How inappropriate!
The palace is a noble place.
You can't simply bring things in like this.
If everyone does that,
is there any rule left?
Nanny, please don't be mad.
She knows she was wrong.
Let her go.
[Girl for selection from Yanchuan, Hao Jia]
What are these?
Besides, look, Nanny.
There are so many people behind.
Let's finish the check
and get off work early.
Forget it.
Go in.
Take it away.
This is my file.
What is this?
This is the perfume I made with orange peel and osmanthus.
This is the liquid rouge made of rose juice.
Am I not allowed to bring them into the palace?
Then please keep them, nannies.
This is the book Commandments for Women that I always carry with me.
Can I bring this into the palace?
It's fine.
Take it with you.
Judged by your gesture and manners,
you'll have a bright future.
Please look out for us in the future.
I'm flattered.
Please look out for me in the future.
Go in.
Wei.
Hao Jia.
It's really you.
It's me.
It's been years
since my parents took me to Yanchuan to visit you.
More than five years.
You're still as beautiful and lovely as when you were little.
You're pretty and lovely too.
Don't be afraid
if something like this happens again in the future.
I'm here.
I'll protect you.
These nannies
look a little bit strict,
but they won't do anything to us.
Besides, they just confiscated some food from you.
They'll distribute food in the palace later.
It's okay.
They didn't take all of it.
Oh my god, there's still some left.
It's delicious.
[Princes' Study Hall]
Many beauties from different regions are here
for the selection.
Unfortunately,
Princess Yuanying from Jinchuan couldn't make it.
[The Tenth Prince, Yin Yue]
She is a top beauty among all the beauties.
She's at least a nine for me.
[The Seventh Prince, Yin Yan]
As for the one point deducted,
it's because I heard that she's overly elegant and arrogant.
It's really boring.
Where did you get the portrait?
This girl
is not even as pretty as me.
This is the only one
selected by Jichuan,
Li Wei.
But I heard
she's a weirdo who came in a donkey carriage.
But when it comes to beauty,
as the poem goes,
"The reeds and rushes are green, the white dew becomes hoar-frost.
The beauty is somewhere near the stream",
named Hao Jia from Yanchuan.
She never cares about the trivia in the outside world,
and only reads books of female virtue.
She's of top quality.
Worth 10 points.
Well,
you've gone too far rating people like this.
It's just a portrait.
So exaggerated...
This is indeed...
This one is good.
What's her name again?
Hao Jia.
Commandments for Women.
It's not Commandments for Women.
Know yourself and your enemy.
Win every battle.
Lord Xinchuan
has 11 sons.
But the Eighth Prince died young.
So there are ten princes left.
The older four princes
have already got their legal wives.
After the court meeting,
they began living outside the palace in their own mansions.
The remaining six princes
live in the palace.
This selection
is for the marriages of the rest six princes.
The Fifth Prince, Yin Qi,
is naive and honest.
The Seventh Prince, Yin Yan,
is a quiet but kind man.
They are both good men to marry.
The last three
are still young
[The Ninth Prince, Yin Han; The Tenth Prince, Yin Yue; The Eleventh Prince]
and not suitable for marriage yet.
Looks like you also like Hao Jia, Qi.
This girl looks like
a fairy in an opera.
By the way,
Yan,
although you don't talk much,
I heard Ruan Sisi
from Yingchuan
is also a dull person.
She's a good match for you.
Unfortunately, she's a three.
Yue.
It's not appropriate.
They are innocent girls,
and you are rating them like this...
Fine.
Others can judge me,
but you're not even getting married.
Why do you care?
I...
Who is this?
Princess Shangguan
from Danchuan.
Her looks...
I'll give her eight.
But she's from Danchuan,
so I'm thinking, one point.
What's wrong with Danchuan?
Yan, you know that
women are mostly in charge in Danchuan.
So ridiculous.
Naturally,
it's hard for local girls to get married there.
So they only seek matrilocal husbands.
God bless us.
Father can give anyone to me,
but not
this one.
I don't want to be a matrilocal husband.
Well...
Hao Jia,
right?
Look at her.
[The Legitimate Eldest Prince, Yin Song]
[The Second Prince, Yin Song]
This is
the Second Prince, Yin Song.
He's Lord's legitimate son.
He was conferred the title as the Legitimate Eldest Prince.
Look at him.
Handsome and well-educated.
Wise and courageous.
Good one to marry.
But it says
he's already married.
How can he be considered a good match?
He's the Legitimate Eldest Prince,
the future Lord Xinchuan.
Silly.
Greetings, Legitimate Eldest Prince.
[The Fourth Prince, Yin Jun]
No wonder Mr. Dai said
they haven't been studying well recently.
Turns out
they paid all their attention on women.
Playboys without ambition.
Shameless.
Yue.
We have the same mother.
You should set an example for our brothers.
Yes.
Everyone,
copy Tao Te Ching three times.
If you get even lower grades in the test two weeks later,
the punishment will be kneeling in the ancestral hall.
Yes.
What about Prince Zheng?
Why isn't he in here?
Is he dead too?
No.
He's here.
When you play Go,
your style is quite different from usual.
[Princes' teacher, Dai Di]
You don't stick to the rules,
but storm and attack by force.
Your Highness, you are about to be 20,
yet Lord hasn't allowed you to meet him on court yet.
In my opinion,
you should watch for the proper moment for action.
My illegitimate elder brother stationed in Mochuan.
Now all the land outside belongs to my legitimate eldest brother.
Although Father loves and indulges my third brother,
he still needs to bow to him.
My fourth brother also follows his leadership.
That's why he managed to open his mansion and go to court meetings.
But he only got a leisure job at the Ministry of Rites.
If I don't want to an idler,
[The Sixth Prince, Yin Zheng]
I'm afraid I'll have to act servilely.
Prince Qi is naughty and neglected his studies.
Lord hasn't allowed him to attend the court meeting.
It won't be easy for you
to surpass your elder brother.
But you got the first place
in all the exams this year.
I think
Lord should have noticed that.
I have nine brothers,
but Father only has two eyes.
To get his attention and get a good position in the imperial court,
I have to plan carefully.
Lord may overlook you
in the selection this year.
It's boring to climb the throne by marriage.
I can earn
what I want by myself.
Thank you for letting me win.
I know
you are quite ambitious.
But you should find
a wife from a reliable family.
Danchuan and Mochuan have powerful armies.
Jinchuan is rich.
Daichuan has mines.
But Jichuan.
It has nothing
but good feng shui.
Then it's not bad
if I get a girl from Jichuan.
I can get
good feng shui for my burial.
If we scheme too much on our marriages,
I'm afraid Father will be annoyed.
The scheme should be appropriate.
If too much,
it may backfire.
Since you chose me,
please believe that
I won't let you down.
[Zhongyi Hall]
The selection begins.
Princess Shangguan, please come forward.
[Madam Xinchuan  Lord Xinchuan]
How is your family background?
You've already called me Princess.
Don't you know what my family background is like?
[Head of the Ministry of Internal Affairs  Head Nanny]
Greetings, My Lord, My Lady.
I'm Hao Jia from Yanchuan.
My parents are still alive.
My father and brother both work for the imperial court,
and my sisters are all married to noble families.
Li Wei from Jichuan.
Did your family hire a etiquette teacher for you?
My family has been farmers for three generations.
Only my father passed the exam,
but his post was too insignificant to get into the palace.
I come from an ordinary family.
We have nothing but a small field.
My Lady.
What did you ask
just now?
Did you read any books back at home?
Book of Tactics.
It's a book for men, right?
I never knew
books are gendered.
I think a lady should study
to serve her husband better.
We're not marrying an ordinary man,
but the distinguished prince of Xinchuan.
So, the external affairs can't be avoided.
For example, people's livelihood and political history.
Women shouldn't read about these.
As for internal affairs,
such as the prince's daily affairs,
education of children,
the relationship between different levels
and accounts in the mansion.
I've read about all these
back at home.
I won't let you down.
The Classics and Rites,
and needlework
are things I don't know well about.
But I'm good at tasting good food.
I want to ask
what other rules have you learned
about serving your husband?
In fact, in Jichuan,
we subscribe to monogamy.
We won't use the word "serve".
If two people love each other,
they will go to the God of Matchmaking Temple to make a vow
and then register in the county government.
If anyone
breaks the vow between husband and wife,
the villagers will criticize him.
Then what's your plan
for the future?
If it can go as I wish,
I would like to travel around the nine regions
and help the ones in need.
I hope in the future,
I can see my husband smile every day.
I haven't thought that much
about the future.
The backyard will be beautiful and peaceful.
We'll have three children.
When we grow old,
we can go to the backyard
and enjoy sunlight together.
But as a princess,
I indeed shoulder more responsibilities.
I can only practice my spear well
and protect the people I should protect.
But I think
the future
is composed of every day from now on.
The two people should respect,
understand, and tolerate each other,
and live every day to its best.
Not missing one single meal
is the most important.
You may leave now.
All candidates, please wait outside the palace
for good news.
[Head eunuch, Liang Shi]
The kid from Jichuan is inappropriate.
I like Hao Jia quite a lot.
Qi told me about her too.
Qi is incompetent.
If she can be his wife,
he may become more mature.
I didn't expect their questions.
Do you think
I'll be chosen by them?
Given your answers,
you will definitely realize your dream
and not get selected.
I'm relieved then.
Wei,
can you find a way to go to the Prince Mansion over there?
Why?
Didn't you say you didn't have much for lunch?
The kitchen of the Prince Mansion
cooks great dishes.
Don't try to fool me.
Tell me, what do you want?
I'm not lying.
I lingered for a while just now and
heard Lord Xinchuan say that
he wants me to marry Yin Qi.
I don't want to.
The one I want to marry is Yin Song.
Who is Yin Qi?
And who is Yin Song?
Why can't you tell them apart?
Lord has ten sons.
How can I recognize every one of them?
Yin Qi is the Fifth Prince.
Yin Song is the Legitimate Eldest Prince.
Yin Song is the legitimate one?
Then if you marry him, you can only be his concubine.
I know.
My mother said
women can only make a living in the imperial harem.
The imperial harem
is the career of women for a lifetime.
It's nothing different from running a shop.
The husband is the boss.
His wife
is just a troublesome steward.
Since I'm here to work,
I'll choose the best region, Xinchuan.
Since I'm already in Xinchuan,
I have to find a boss with the best prospects.
Isn't that the Legitimate Eldest Prince?
You can't think like that.
You are a great girl.
You should find someone who loves you and protects you.
Wei.
I'm not like you.
Your father only has your mother.
Of course you have expectations for marriage.
But I...
My father is not a good boss.
My mother has been his concubine forever.
But just because of the words of his legal wife,
I was regarded as the legitimate daughter
and was sent out for peace-making marriage.
I have no one to rely on.
So I have to plan
for my own future.
Is the food from the Prince Mansion
really delicious?
Let's go.
Can this work?
It must.
They are coming.
We meet again.
You...
It's not easy to deliver food at noon.
Let me help you.
Who are you?
I'm Wei from Prince Zheng's palace.
Have you forgotten?
We met a few days ago.
You're so forgetful.
What do we have for lunch today?
Potatoes and sweet potatoes
can't be put together.
Potatoes prefer lower temperatures,
while sweet potatoes like it warm.
If put together,
either the potatoes will sprout,
or the sweet potatoes will turn bad from inside.
I can tell you rarely go into the kitchen.
Let me tell you.
You...
We are together.
Raw food and cooked food
shouldn't be put together either.
They will taint the taste of each other.
If the taste is tainted,
just separate...
After the selection,
you will get married.
Father also said he wanted you to open the mansion and attend court meetings.
But you've been fooling around all day.
The articles you submitted are always full of wrongly written characters.
Even I can't stand it.
The Ministry of Rites assesses the princes that attend court meetings every month.
They won't let you save face.
Brother.
What did they say about you this month?
They used the words from Inspection of Mice.
"Mice have skin,
but men may have no manners."
The next line of this poem is "A man without manners may as well die."
The position I gave your fourth brother
is the supervisor of the Ministry of Rites,
which is their superior.
They even dared to impeach your fourth brother.
Think about it yourself.
The Ministry of Rites wouldn't scold you anyway.
Of course it's easy for you to say...
If you have a problem with me,
you can write a memorial to impeach me.
But don't write a memorial
full of wrongly written characters
to embarrass Xinchuan.
Qi.
Apologize to Legitimate Eldest Prince.
Do you still want to open your mansion
or not?
I just don't understand.
There are so many brothers who are incompetent.
Why do I have to be the one who's getting scolded?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry
for disturbing.
Zheng
solved my game of Go.
What do you know about Go, Zheng?
Stop teaching a fish how to swim.
That's right.
What do you know about Go, Zheng?
Song has left the final phase here for days.
No one could solve it,
but you did?
If you're interested in learning Go,
why don't we have another match?
My stomach...
Are you okay?
You sicko.
Why are you pretending
to be a crazy about Go?
You have a stomachache again, right?
You...
Brother.
You know that Zheng hasn't been in good shape.
Go back first.
Thank you.
Qi.
Take me home.
I'll see him off.
Why did you get involved in this mess?
You solved his game of Go.
Don't you know he's...
Zheng.
What I just said was
"I'll see you off", right?
Go.
I'll see you off.
Go back and take some medicine.
Brother.
You were right just now.
I know I was wrong.
How about this?
I'll collect the fishing rod for you.
I'll go get the rod.
Let me do it.
Miss.
Where are you going?
I'm Hao Jia, the candidate from Yanchuan.
I got lost.
Please show me the way back, Your Highness.
It's over there.
Just go this way.
You'll pass by a willow tree.
Then turn right and walk to the end.
Then turn right after you pass the gate.
You'll arrive at Zhongyi Hall.
Thank you, Prince Qi.
How do you know I'm Prince Qi?
No one else can be so silly as you.
I was just guessing.
Seems that I guessed it right.
Amazing.
Yes.
Let's go.
I'll take you there.
Come on. Be careful.
Here.
This game is interesting.
The one who solved this game is of average intelligence.
It seems that he found it out by luck.
But the one who set the game
is good at the strategy of nudging and blocking,
which made black unable to expand.
It seems that the offensive side
is resourceful
and extraordinarily wise.
Black played better.
But I'm sorry.
You're not the Legitimate Eldest Prince.
Sorry. I thought I was smart and talked too much.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Never mind.
You were right.
The Legitimate Eldest Prince won't blame you.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I have some preserved almonds with me.
I made them myself.
Take it as a gift for your kind guidance.
It's nothing valuable.
Please don't mind.
Okay.
Great.
Your Highness.
I didn't bring enough preserved almonds.
If I can see you again,
I'll bring more to you.
It's okay.
The preserved almonds are so sweet.
How did you know I like sweets?
You guessed it again,
right?
Your Highness.
Which direction
did you say just now?
I forgot.
It's okay. You don't need to remember it.
I'll take you there.
Wait.
Your Highness.
But I...
This is...
What is it?
Don't just sweep the floor.
Clean that place up too.
OK?
Then go over there.
Your Highness.
Didn't you go visit the Legitimate Eldest Prince?
Why are you back so early?
I was too lazy to socialize,
so I told him I had a stomachache and came back.
You're indeed my prince.
You've always had stomachaches.
[Head supervisor, Su Shen]
And you used it as an excuse without hesitation.
Ordinary people can never be so quick-witted as you.
You don't have to fawn on me.
Anyone can think of this.
How could it be?
I can't.
Your Highness, there's no need to keep pretending.
You're still covering your stomach now that you're back.
Thoughtful.
Prudent.
It really hurts.
It really hurts?
So your old illness is acting up again.
It must be that you didn't eat much for lunch
to cater to Mr. Dai's taste, right?
Look at this.
You've never liked meat or fish.
Look what those people have done.
Go get some rest.
No.
You should eat first.
I'll go ask them to serve dinner right away.
Chef Liu Baoquan once received your help.
He is one of us.
The food is ready.
The ribs
have been blanched through hot water.
Can you stop talking?
I'm starving.
Why isn't Hao Jia back yet?
I'm so hungry.
This is the last dish.
It's past time to eat.
There's still so much left.
It'll be a waste if I don't eat it.
Baoquan.
Liu Baoquan.
Are you there?
Are the dishes ready?
Hurry up.
Prince Zheng is back.
His stomach illness is acting up from hunger again.
The dish serving...
You're still caring about etiquettes
at this time?
I...
Supervisor Su.
Just in time.
Prince Zheng's stomach illness has acted up again.
Serve the meal first.
He needs to take medicine right after the meal.
Prepare the medicine
according to the old prescription.
OK?
Hurry.
I told you to run.
Liu Baoquan.
I've cooperated with you.
Why didn't you tell me the dish is ready?
Steamed egg with pumpkin.
Hurry up with the next dishes.
Coming.
Steamed egg with pumpkin.
Your Highness, warm your stomach first.
Where is the egg?
There must be a mistake.
Wait a moment, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Osmanthus cakes.
Broiled broccoli.
Broad beans with lily bulbs.
Broiled asparagus.
Oh no.
There's nothing left to place on the plate.
Liu Baoquan.
This one.
I'll give you one last chance.
It's no use hiding from me.
I won't let you off if you mess it up again.
The damn palace rules.
Bed spareribs.
I'll deal with you later.
Broiled
spareribs.
It must be because I'm the one who opened it the past few times.
Please do it yourself this time.
What?
This is the jade pendant of the female candidates for selection.
Why is it here?
Your Highness.
This looks much better.
It's still crooked.
You don't understand.
Oh no.
This man wears luxurious clothes,
and he lives in the Prince Mansion.
Probably a prince.
What do you do?
I'm the poison tester here.
The dishes served to the princes
have to be tried by me first
before served.
These dishes are fine.
I'm leaving.
I've never seen
someone who tests poison with his/her own mouth before.
Which mansion
are you from?
Which mansion...
I heard that Prince Zheng is weak and sick.
It's hard for him to achieve great things.
So Lord Xinchuan doesn't care about him that much.
The palace is full of snobs.
Naturally, people
don't care much about him either.
In that case,
he has a low sense of presence here.
Prince Zheng.
Prince Zheng?
Tell me what he looks like.
He...
He is
quite vague.
Vague?
Tell me about it.
He has a low sense of presence.
It's hard for you to find him among a group of people.
Even if he stands right in front of you,
you may not recognize him.
It feels like he's not even in the palace.
Your description is quite accurate.
I'll ask him to reward you
when I meet him someday.
No need.
I'm just a poison tester.
Well,
since everything is fine here,
I'll get going.
What's wrong with you?
An old illness.
Stomachache.
Stomachache?
Stomachache... We need to go see the imperial physician.
Go see the imperial physician.
Let's go.
Get up.
Hurry. Let's go to the imperial physician.
Are you alright?
One.
Two.
Three.
-I can do it myself. -Let me.
Sleeves.
My stomach is not the only place that hurts now.
Turn left.
I don't remember which mansion he's from.
I don't know who he is.
I don't know if his stomachache gets better.
I wanted to send him to the Imperial Hospital,
but he insisted that he was busy
and asked me to send him back to the Prince Mansion.
He had such a severe stomachache.
Why did he go back to the Prince Mansion?
Was he trying to report me?
Will I die?
No, you won't.
Don't be afraid.
You don't know him.
He doesn't know you either.
Besides, there are so many girls
in the palace for the selection today.
Even if they want to investigate,
they might not be able to trace it back to us.
It's getting dark soon.
The sedan to take you out of the palace may arrive
before dark.
After you get back to Jichuan,
how can they catch you
from so far away?
If I can rush back home,
it'll be the time to eat lotus roots.
I wonder if I can be in time for that.
Miss Li.
The sedan for you is waiting at the gate.
They're here.
I didn't expect them to come so soon.
Great.
It must be hard to fit in Xinchuan Palace.
You'll be alone from now on.
You must be careful.
I'm leaving.
Go.
When I get home,
I'll send you lotus roots.
In such a big bag.
I'll send them all to you.
Hurry up. We are all waiting.
Why is this sedan
red?
Of course it's red.
You're the first one to get the marriage bestowed by the Lord.
Marriage?
I knew that
you must have a promising future, Concubine of Prince Zheng.
Concubine of Prince Zheng?
The Sixth Prince's concubine?
Right. Prince Zheng.
What?
Get on the sedan. Don't miss the time.
Nanny.
You must be mistaken.
No.
I was surprised too.
How could you not fail?
Let's go.
What's the finest delicacy in the world?
Heating up a pot of tea and feeling the time pass by silently
Apricot flowers flowing in the stream where fish is thriving
Just drink up the fine wine in our glass
What are you longing for in the passage of time?
Boiling morning dew that reflects the moon and starlight
Snow falling in winter, drunk in the spring breeze
Followed by poetic charm and pictorial splendor
Despite the various beautiful scenery all year round
The most fortunate thing is my encounter with you
Watching the myriad twinkling lights and dim candlelight of the city
One of them is waiting for me to come home
Ordinary meals can be so tasty and enjoyable
The most important thing is to be with you every day
It's the best time of harvesting red carps and green plums
The finest delicacy in the world
Is to be with you from dawn to dusk
What are you longing for in the passage of time?
Boiling morning dew that reflects the moon and starlight
Snow falling in winter, drunk in the spring breeze
Followed by poetic charm and pictorial splendor
Despite the various beautiful scenery all year round
The most fortunate thing is my encounter with you
Watching the myriad twinkling lights and dim candlelight of the city
One of them is waiting for me to come home
Ordinary meals can be so tasty and enjoyable
The most important thing is to be with you every day
It's the best time of harvesting red carps and green plums
The finest delicacy in the world
Is to be with you from dawn to dusk
Ordinary meals can be so tasty and enjoyable
The most important thing is to be with you every day
It's the best time of harvesting red carps and green plums
The finest delicacy in the world