♪The greedy heart shuttles, unrelenting♪
♪The lonely sadness feels no sin♪
♪Fearing no false names
being forced upon me♪
♪Who is sneaking in spite
as night falls♪
♪Quietly enjoying the dark world♪
♪I only look forward to dawn's beauty♪
♪The sun's warmth burns away guilt♪
♪Killing the innocence
that redeems love♪
=Marry to the Enemy of My Enemy=
=Episode 14=
How much money do you want?
My mom founded Zhongxia.
You guys almost bankrupted it before.
And my mom brought it back to life.
My mom believed
I'd carry Zhongxia forward.
But you disagree.
Why don't we make a bet then?
Sure, bet on what?
This crisis was started by me.
If I'm unable to solve it,
I will resign and leave.
Okay.
But if I solve it,
Uncle Zhou and the other board members,
please don't interfere
in the company's operations anymore.
Nuan, they just...
Uncle Zhou agreed.
Let's bet.
We'll bet with you.
I won't be intimidated
by a girl like you.
Deal.
Nuan.
It's okay.
There must be a way.
I'm fine.
Nuan.
Yizhe, why are you here?
You're in trouble.
How can I sit and do nothing?
You have a way?
Aren't they arguing now
that I got hurt because of Nuan,
and Nuan turned to you
because I was disabled?
We can clarify to them
that your arranged marriage
was just a smokescreen
meant to protect me.
To protect you?
In fear I'd get hurt again.
Before the danger is eliminated,
She only...
Wait.
You mean, when all this is settled,
Xia Nuan will leave me
and then be with you again?
That's right.
Right now, this is the best plan.
Is this the best plan?
Or is it your best chance?
Nuan, leave him.
You still have a chance.
The reporters are here. Let's go.
Ms. Xia,
is the marriage contract online true?
Yes, we do have a contract marriage.
I'm very sorry to have lied to you.
Did you do that
because your fiancé was disabled
and you didn't want
to marry him anymore?
First, I'd like you all
to respect Yizhe.
(He can't stand up for now
due to the injury.)
(Please don't use)
(Zhongxia Group's Press Conference)
(harsh words to describe him.)
My
and Meng Yizhe's
marriage contract
was just a joke
from my mother back then.
All these years,
(she had treated him as her own son.)
(So she hoped we would become a family.)
So you had a contract marriage...
Because of me.
It was due to my selfishness.
They say that time and patience
melt the hardest heart.
But his heart
didn't melt
after I held it for a long time.
So I used the excuse
of being the heiress
needing a stable partner to have
a fake marriage with him.
A fake marriage?
But now I want to ask,
after being together for so long,
will you...?
There's no reason for a girl to propose.
Xia Nuan,
will you marry me?
I will.
Oh, my God.
Big news.
(Zhongxia Group's Press Conference)
Zhong Xuan,
you've hidden your identity well.
Good for you.
You still remember me.
You've fooled all of us around.
You've got something.
Much smarter than your dead dad.
But you're still too green
and can't keep calm.
Be sensible.
Keep your mouth and hands in check.
You probably don't want
to end up like your dad did
with your reputation ruined
and all lost, right?
What happened?
Ji Yantao discovered my identity.
It seems that what happened back then
is indeed related to him.
Hello?
Ms. Xia, we found something.
Those accounts that leaked
are all marketing accounts
from Meng Media.
From the Meng family?
Yes.
Yizhe?
I didn't expect you
to be the most underestimated one.
In just a few hours, you were able
to mobilize so many resources
and stir up such big news.
I'm flattered.
I just wonder if Nuan will hate me
in the end.
No need to worry about that.
Your years of bond with Nuan
won't be easily affected.
She was just
bewitched by that Zhong guy.
Have you heard of vixens?
Yes, I've heard of vixens.
But a male vixen?
It's the first time I've seen one.
You need to know.
Women always turn their desire
for a man's power and money
into what they call love.
Every woman will actively step
into the trap of power and money.
What you need to do is become stronger.
Mr. Ji, I'm not a hunter.
Nuan is even less of a prey.
Let me introduce someone to you.
Come in.
Yizhe, did you miss me?
Zhao Qing? You...
Yes.
This was also sent to you by me.
Yizhe?
Everything is gone.
Hello, Yizhe. Have you moved out?
Nuan, let's meet up.
Yizhe, when did you buy this place?
After college graduation.
Nuan,
before your mother passed away,
she left me a letter.
My mom?
When did she give it to you?
Uncle Xu from Tianhong
sent it to the hospital I was in.
I just received it.
It's my mom's handwriting.
I can't believe my mom.
She took a joke so seriously...
It's not a joke,
Nuan.
Yizhe, we are siblings.
♪You said you wanted
to be my guardian angel♪
♪In wind and rain,
even if with broken wings♪
♪It wouldn't stop you from loving me♪
♪I wanted to thank you
for giving me courage♪
♪Carry me out of this trouble and soar♪
♪But when I turn around,
you've already left♪
♪Why should I love you
without hesitation♪
♪Falling from paradise
all the way to the ruins♪
♪In your net called love♪
♪Why am I just a pawn at your whim♪
♪Why should I love you
without hesitation♪
♪In exchange for the complete defeat♪
♪Don't you have a bit of mercy♪