=Recruit a General to Lead the Troops=
=Episode 5=
You wretched woman, I will cut you down.
Hey.
Wretched woman, caught by me at last.
Hmm.
Today I will kill you, wretched woman.
You must not kill her.
Why?
With a living hostage right here,
why not use her?
Oh.
Right.
Let us do it this way.
Good.
This is bad.
Shihou Stronghold
has come to challenge us.
Listen inside.
Send out Chen Xinrou.
Or I will kill Tao Lianxin.
Leader.
The fourth boss is in their hands.
Li Chengyu has not been captured.
Big boss.
Second boss.
Surrender.
Li Chengyu, how dare you.
To collude with Shihou Stronghold.
We are only thirty feet away
from entering the stronghold.
We will be inside at once.
Lower your banner and surrender quickly.
Surrender.
What is this?
(Qingfeng Stronghold)
Did not expect that, did you?
When I turn ruthless,
I care not even for myself.
You truly are ruthless.
Tao Lianxin.
I will kill you right now.
(Qingfeng Stronghold)
Oh no, I cannot take it.
I am going to faint.
You are awake. How do you feel?
I am fine now.
Thank you.
What is that sound?
Ah, tonight
is the ceremony
for Best Stronghold Member.
What is Best Stronghold Member?
You do not know this?
It is chosen once every month.
The one who contributes most
to the stronghold
is elected as Best Stronghold Member.
They may then enter the Treasure Pavilion
and choose a gift they like most.
There, the bandaging is done.
You may leave now.
Hey.
The secret lies
within the Treasure Pavilion.
(To enter the Treasure Pavilion
and find evidence,)
(one must
first become Best Stronghold Member.)
I told them to cancel it for now.
Too much has happened
these past two days.
Let everyone rest. We will speak again
at the start of the month.
By the way,
I asked you to follow Li Chengyu
and see why he went down the mountain.
Could it be that he truly colludes
with Shihou Stronghold?
No.
He and I were captured together
by Shihou Stronghold.
In the end, he saved me.
He saved you?
When you have rested, spread the word.
Say that we have captured someone
from Shihou Stronghold.
If they dare to send people to rescue,
we will seize whoever comes.
I already told Minmin
to bandage Li Chengyu.
Then send him down the mountain at once.
Li Chengyu!
My apologies.
During this time,
I have troubled you.
I shall take my leave.
You may stay.
Very well.
You may stay to recover.
But while recovering you must work.
The stronghold does not feed idlers.
Who is an idler?
You.
Hmph.
Hey.
What?
All of them were captured.
Where is Huzi?
Captured.
What?
Awake?
Oh.
You are awake too.
Are you not about to hold a ceremony
for Best Stronghold Member?
It has been delayed.
Why?
Because of...
If you have something to say,
just say it.
- Can I take part?
- You want to enter the Treasure Pavilion?
(Is it that obvious?)
No, it is not that.
I simply wish to contribute
to the stronghold.
(How could someone
like her commit treason?)
(I do not know why,
I just find her so adorable,)
(not like someone who would rebel.)
(To enter the Treasure Pavilion
one must become Best Stronghold Member.)
The environment
in Qingfeng Stronghold is so harsh.
(Hot spring, rest area, shower area)
Even Chen Xinrou finds bathing difficult.
(Bathing area, hair combing area)
If I build them a hot spring,
so they can bathe with ease,
would they not be deeply grateful to me?
In that case, becoming Best Stronghold Member
would be nothing at all.
I truly am a genius.
And there is one more person.
One more person?
Who else?
Why stop halfway through?
In this time I could have said
my name several times.
Put your foot down.
Why are you still awake?
I dropped a book.
By the way, Young Master Li,
I think...
We have captured someone
from Shihou Stronghold.
(It feels as though something is wrong.)
Enter.
Let us out.
Release us.
Set us free.
Help!
Help! Help!
Help! Save us!
Open the door!
Open up!
Murder!
There is killing inside!
Who is it?
Why are they all dead?
I do not know.
It was already like this when I entered.
Perhaps suicide.
They are death warriors.
(Could this mark be...)
Aiya.
Young Master Li,
thank you for saving my life.
That Liu Pitang
sent people to kill me.
Why would he want to kill you?
I do not know.
Per... Perhaps because
I know too many secrets.
What secrets do you know?
That... I do not know.
What secrets?
No secret is worth killing me over.
So Liu Pitang
never truly saw me as a brother.
He treated us like dogs.
You are my brother.
My good brother.
I do not care,
I will stay in Qingfeng Stronghold.
Qingfeng Stronghold is my home.
You are my big brother.
(The bathhouse hot spring
cannot be built so quickly.)
(A few laborers are indeed needed.)
(Can't have the girls do it.)
(These men will do just fine.)
You may stay,
but Qingfeng Stronghold
does not keep idlers.
You must all work.
Fine, we can do any work.
Any work at all.
Qingfeng Stronghold does not keep men.
Am I not a man?
Enough, I will go speak to the leader.
It is raining, everyone up.
Report!
What did you say?
Cold Tiger is dead.
♪If you've never seen a bloom,
you can't know hope♪
♪If you weren't here,
I wouldn't have come♪
♪On a soda-lit night,
only the wind knows my love♪
♪It's a helpless kind of feeling♪
♪Like a feather of morning love
falling into the deep sea♪
♪Being unnoticed,
yet I still tell you I love you♪
♪But my confession
is drowned out by the wind♪
♪You can't hear it♪
♪I also want to rush forward♪
♪To give you all my heart♪
♪Yet it's pushed away by you♪
♪Whether love is spoken
or left unspoken♪
♪I know you understand♪
♪It's just an accident♪
♪You longed to wander once more,
by my side through the throng♪
♪I know you weren't really here for me♪
♪Yet still, who else could bring
a surprise quite like you♪
♪After you left,
I didn't want to let go♪
♪You brushed past me,
leaving your trace in the crowd♪
♪I didn't shut you out♪
♪But I couldn't wait for you to stop♪
♪Yet I seem to clutch you,
unable to let you fade into the crowd♪