(DNA Lover)
(Choi Si Won)
(Jung In Sun)
(Lee Tae Hwan)
(Jung Eugene)
(DNA Lover)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
Now,
I will never let you go.
(Episode 12: The Oblivion Gene)
Go on inside.
Keep yourself warm as you sleep.
Okay.
Thanks.
(Yeon Woo)
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
But whenever I'm with you, I start acting strange.
I want to tell you that I love you even though I'm afraid.
Gosh, why do I keep...
Just like how you found the courage to come here today,
I'm working up my courage to say this too.
Can you stay by my side?
Goodness.
I mean, it makes no sense.
After saying all that stuff to me,
how could he do this?
He didn't have a secret...
he couldn't tell me about, did he?
(World's Best Firefighter Seo Kang Hoon)
Hey, Kang Hoon.
Were you sleeping?
No, not yet.
I left some medicine outside your front gate.
You looked like you had a cold earlier.
Be sure to take it, even if it's a hassle.
Okay. Thanks.
No need to thank me.
Don't think about anything and get some good sleep.
I'll call you again tomorrow.
There wouldn't have been any pharmacies open at this hour.
(Internal medicine)
Hey, A Ri.
Ms. Park Eun Jung is coming early to hear her results today.
Let's have her chart ready.
Okay.
What's wrong with your face? Are you sick or something?
You look particularly ugly today.
It's nothing. I think I have a bit of a cold.
It doesn't seem like nothing.
I'm in front of the center. Let's meet up for a minute.
This seemed like something important to you.
I wanted to give it back.
When you meet your real DNA lover next time,
you should give it to him.
Is this the first thing you say to me?
Shouldn't you at least explain to me first...
what happened yesterday...
and why you acted like that all of a sudden?
How could you do that?
You should at least say something.
Why on earth are you acting like this?
And if you were going to be like this,
why did you do those things that night?
It was for no big reason.
I only truly wish for...
your happiness.
You're saying...
this is for my happiness?
It might be hard now, but for later on,
I think this is right.
At least there won't be...
any reason for you to be unhappy.
What does that mean?
You said so.
If your partner is not your DNA lover,
you may not be unhappy in this moment,
but you might become unhappy someday.
- Yeon Woo, that's... - Besides,
you've discovered...
that your true DNA lover is Kang Hoon.
Will you be able to date me while knowing that?
It's clear...
why we're breaking up, right?
I wish you well.
(Sim Sung Hoon, Yeom Jang Mi)
(Sim Yeon Woo, Han So Jin)
(Thanks for everything, So Jin. And I'm sorry.)
Those two phrases ended our relationship?
How?
He never put in any emotions, so it's easy to end things too.
The aftermath of heartbreak phase has begun once again.
Binge eating, insomnia, and mood swings.
How long will it last this time?
Don't worry.
This time, I'll get over him quickly.
Humans have...
a gene called CCR5. The Oblivion Gene.
(The Oblivion Gene, CCR5)
In order to block out my unhappiness,
this gene will...
So Jin, you didn't know this, did you?
How desperately I ran to you.
It took me a while, right? I'm sorry.
It will manipulate my memories...
So Jin, don't you know how much I like you?
It will help me to delete those memories.
So Jin, do you only see me as that kind of man?
A man who will lose interest in a woman he likes because of this?
He's not even your DNA lover!
Why can't you get over him?
Take down that darned photo of Sewer first!
(Potato cheese fries)
(Convenience store steak)
(Jackson spaghetti)
(Beef bone soup)
I knew that guy would do this!
That hairy man.
He's so ugly too.
What an ugly guy.
(Sim Yeon Woo)
So Jin! Open up!
So Jin!
Open up!
Kang Hoon.
What are you doing right now?
What?
Hey!
- Goodness. - Hey, you can't put this out.
You're playing with fire for an experiment again, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Then what is this?
(Test Results)
I was just getting rid of things I should get rid of.
Seriously...
Seriously.
You're such a firefighter.
Do you want me to light the fire again?
Forget it.
Kang Hoon.
Today,
I met Yeon Woo.
And...
we really decided to break up.
You've done nothing wrong.
You loved him the best you could.
(18 selected)
(Move to trash)
(Deleting)
(No photos)
(Seo Kang Hoon)
What do you have to say?
Yeon Woo.
Are you really going to break up with So Jin?
Yes, we've ended things.
"Ended things?"
Is that so easy for you?
Weren't you sincere about So Jin, at least?
I was sincere.
That's why I helped her.
I sincerely wish So Jin to be happy.
What does that mean?
How is that making So Jin happy?
You're saying the same thing.
She seems to have been hurt badly.
You should take good care of her by her side.
I hope you don't regret telling me that.
Kang Hoon.
She was someone I wanted to protect for the first time.
So Jin.
My affection for her kept growing,
but I became scared.
If I can only end up hurting her...
because I get swept up in this emotion called love,
I think it's right...
to let her go now before things get deeper.
I'm not sure I can watch So Jin...
as she grows unhappy by my side.
Because there will be no such thing as everlasting love.
Where is Yeon Woo?
He's gone.
Hey, Kang Hoon.
So Jin, what are you doing tonight?
I just want to rest at home.
Don't do that. Come on out. Let's go somewhere together.
Bye.
What do you think? Don't you feel so refreshed inside?
You said it was somewhere close.
Seoul is close enough.
We can go anywhere if there's an emergency.
All right.
You know, you should use your body at times like these.
Follow me at my pace.
Okay.
Like this.
Time out.
The moon is bright.
It's fascinating, isn't it?
You can only tell that the moon is so big...
when you look at the shadows of the moon.
So Jin.
Do you know why you can't see the moon during the daytime?
You told me this when I was in elementary school.
The moon circles around the Earth,
but the Earth circles around the sun.
So, when the sunlight is too bright, you can't see the moon.
The moon is always by the Earth's side,
but the Earth doesn't look at the moon.
So, the moon is sad.
I told you that because you said science was hard.
Why is science always so sad for you?
Hey, everyone without a partner is always sad.
Look around you.
There are some people who only have their eyes on you,
like the moon.
At times like these,
Kang Hoon seems to be my Healer Gene for sure.
But...
It's so strange.
How can you be scentless?
It's odd.
How can you not smell like anything?
Isn't it you that can't smell it?
- I have the nose of a dog. - My goodness.
So Jin. I'll go and buy some water.
- Wait here for a minute. - Okay.
- I'll be right back. - Okay.
So Jin.
What took you so long?
Sorry. Here.
You want me to wear these?
They didn't have any slippers at the store here.
I went to an underground shopping mall nearby,
but these were the ones they sold at the only open store.
Here, try them on. That way, we can go home. Go on.
What's this?
Why are they lighting up?
Anyone would be able to tell it's you from 100m away.
This is funny to you, isn't it?
What if I chase after you with these on?
- What? - Come here.
- Hang on. - Come here!
Wait, So Jin!
What are these?
- This is so embarrassing! - Bye.
Darn it.
Dr. Sim, I came on a hotel vacation with the tickets you gave me.
Who do you think I came with?
(Annoying Punk)
Wait.
I can't remember if it was a super single or a double bed.
Isn't a super single bed too small?
It's a bit small.
Jung Tam.
What are you doing?
Aren't you going to check in?
Oh, yes. Let's go.
So...
May I help you with checking in?
Whose name is the reservation under?
A super single? A double? A super single?
I can't wake Sung Mi with my sleeping habits.
Still, isn't a double bed too big?
Yes, a super single would be better.
- Sir? - Let's go with the super single.
Jung Tam.
- Yes? - So...
Whose name is the reservation under?
Oh, a super single.
Pardon?
Oh, right!
- It'll be under Yeo Jung Tam. - Yes.
- Oh, yes. Mr. Yeo Jung Tam. - Yes.
I'm fine.
It's really okay.
- One moment. - So...
I feel embarrassed to show you my feet.
Why? They're the prettiest feet in the world.
This side too.
There.
- It tickles. - Wait.
You're getting water everywhere. Hold on.
Oh, my.
You know how to do things like this?
Of course.
- Is it comfortable? - Yes.
Now, stop looking.
- Okay. - All right.
You're not looking, right?
No. Don't look.
Stop it.
Ta-da! It's done.
Oh, my.
It's so cute.
Is it okay?
- Yes. - I'm glad.
If so, can I do...
what I want to do?
Pardon? What...
That was...
Wait. Hold on.
Sung Mi.
Hold on.
I knew you wouldn't tell me where you were even if I asked,
so I asked So Jin.
I see.
Here.
I hope your mom can hear this music box in her dreams.
How are things with So Jin?
We broke up.
Because of me.
Do you regret...
breaking up?
Have you ever seen me regret a decision?
Yeon Woo. Should we go for a drive?
I'll drive. Let's go out for a bit.
You used to like going to Chuncheon.
No.
I feel bad...
leaving my mom here.
Yeon Woo.
You think your mom doesn't know that you're staying by her side...
with that sad look on your face, don't you?
She knows.
When the patient is sick,
their guardian should stay strong and eat well. Aren't I right?
Thanks.
This is a grass tree.
It's a flower that only blooms when the tree burns up.
It was found in a fire that occurred a month ago.
Isn't it a bit strange?
The same flower being found in two different fires?
I'm sure it was a coincidence.
This photo was found at the site of the fire.
Is it someone you know?
It's a grass tree.
It has no flowers right now, right?
That tree only blooms when it burns in a fire.
Isn't that fascinating?
Mom.
Dad, I'm back.
Hey.
- Give it to me. I got it. - Thanks. Table number two.
Here is your meal.
Enjoy.
(So Ri)
Hey, So Ri.
Kang Hoon. Why are you calling so late at night?
Can I ask you for a favor?
So you're going on a date today?
With who?
As long as it's not someone like Han So Jin.
Why? What's wrong with So Jin?
What? Is it really So Jin?
No.
Goodness.
It's a bit off.
- So Ri. - Yes?
Do you smell anything on me?
You don't use cologne.
No. I mean, do I give off any smell naturally?
What are you talking about?
Are you becoming like So Jin?
No. Someone told me that I had no smell.
Stop talking about smells.
This won't do. Go and change. Let's go somewhere else.
Just pick something easy for me.
Just leave it up to me.
Go inside.
What time are you meeting her?
Is it okay?
You look handsome.
Here.
It's too normal.
Next.
This isn't bad.
Let's try the next one.
Hurry.
So Ri.
This is it.
- Is it okay? - Yes.
Look.
You look handsome.
And the cologne you bought.
Okay.
This is the Cellular Gene Treatment Seminar.
I'm sure you looked at the chart. It should all be...
content that you already know.
It's nothing difficult.
I think you should just keep two main things in mind.
The first thing...
Do you know him?
He...
is a new breakthrough for So Jin.
A breakthrough.
Here. You're not allergic to these flowers, so don't worry.
Why did you bring flowers...
Wait. What's up with you today?
Are you going somewhere?
You said you'd be done early today, right?
Yes. I'm almost done with work.
Let's go...
on a date together.
What?
You said you wanted to go to an ice skating rink.
Let's go together.
Are you feeling sick?
No. I'm being serious.
I'll wait until you're done.
You can just go now.
We're almost done with all of the preparations.
A Ri can finish the rest of the work.
Is that okay?
I'd be very grateful.
No. But...
No. You should leave early for once.
You should have days like this once in a while.
We'll wrap up...
the rest of the work.
We?
Yes. You should go.
Don't worry about us.
Thank you.
So Jin said she was working with great people.
- She was right. - Stop it.
What are you doing? Hurry up and go.
Oh, okay.
I'll get going, then.
A Ri. Make sure to finish things up nicely.
I'll see you again next time.
Are you wearing cologne today?
Yes.
Can you smell something on me now?
An artificial smell.
It's very different from what Shai smelled.
A date?
What are you doing?
Right.
It's nothing. Let's go.
- Be careful. - It's been so long.
Do you see those kids skating?
You need to be as good as them.
Right foot, left foot.
There you go.
That's what you get for teasing me.
Here.
Oh, gosh. This is embarrassing.
Are you okay?
Yes.
What is it?
What? Nothing.
Should we go?
So Jin. I'm going to make a call.
Okay. I'll wait for you here.
- Wait here. - Okay.
(Slow mailbox)
Oh, gosh.
What's wrong with me?
Hey! Move!
So Jin!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Do you think you can get up?
- There you go. - Slowly.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Skate carefully.
Hold on.
Don't get yourself hurt next time.
I didn't have time to think about that before jumping in.
That's why you always get hurt too.
Don't take after me in that way.
Why does it feel like something always happens when I'm with you?
Because you're a troublemaker.
I'm okay. Let's go.
Okay.
You need to let go of this first.
Right.
I'm really okay.
Mr. Seo is waiting. You should head in now.
I'll see you off first.
What?
What is this?
(As the streetlamp repair was delayed, I installed LED lights.)
(I'll take them down once the repair is complete. Seo Kang Hoon)
What?
Did you do that?
When I came here the other day to give you medicine...
As the streetlamp repair was delayed, I installed LED lights.
I'll take them down once the repair is complete.
Seo Kang Hoon.
I did it since I was already here.
It's dangerous at night.
You should've told me. I didn't know.
It's no big deal.
(As the streetlamp repair was delayed, I installed LED lights.)
(I'll take them down once the repair is complete. Seo Kang Hoon)
(Real-time analysis of 2 million brainwaves per second!)
(We'll find your destined partner by analyzing your brainwaves.)
Thank you for agreeing to this clinical test.
(4 years ago, Hanguk University)
(Neuroscience and Cognitive Science Research Lab)
Ms. Han. You really are just friends...
with no romantic feelings...
- with this male friend here, right? - Yes.
For this particular test,
we can only use people who aren't couples.
- We're not. - We're not a couple.
I can't believe that.
Here. Look.
These red areas here...
are the activated parts of the brain.
As you can see, your red areas are identical.
Even the brightness levels are the same.
How can they be so identical?
Having the same functional activity in the brain...
means your six senses respond in the same way...
when you see and feel something together.
Concerns, excitement, sadness, and fear.
All of your emotions are identical,
as if you were born that way.
Now that I think about it,
the person who was always by my side...
was Kang Hoon.
Head inside.
I had fun today.
Aren't you going to go?
You should go in first.
Bye.
Father Andrea.
Did something bad happen?
Do you regret...
breaking up?
Have you ever seen me regret a decision?
Is now the time?
Thank you.
Mr. Sim. You're making that face.
That expression you get after a breakup.
Did you break up with Ms. Han?
It feels a bit different this time.
- Really? - What should we do?
Do you want me to set you up on a blind date?
- It's okay. - Don't be like that and try.
I'll set something up.
With someone just your type.
Let's see.
Are you Sim Yeon Woo?
Hello.
Was the traffic really bad?
The traffic was fine, but I was horseback riding today,
and Brian was a bit sick.
Brian is the name of my horse.
That must've been tough.
What do you like?
What kind of hobbies do you have?
I don't really have a hobby.
My hobby is visiting good restaurants.
I'm getting a little sick of visiting five-star restaurants...
in Korea.
I had a fine dining experience at a hotel recently,
but it tasted so cheap.
Are they selling instant food?
Shall I introduce you to a restaurant I go often?
Ta-da!
It's not as good as a restaurant, but give it a try.
It's delicious.
Isn't it? Isn't it good?
See?
So you know how to smile after all.
- Pardon? - That was the first time...
you smiled in front of me.
I see... Right.
Yes! Just chew them all up!
Look at what they're doing to So Mi!
Just wipe them out! Kill them all!
You must like action films.
I guess so.
What about you?
I hate anything that is dangerous.
What a dangerous date you're on.
Hello.
I'm this man's ex-girlfriend.
Right. This guy...
has a debt of 34 million dollars.
The hospital doesn't belong to him either.
Are you okay with that?
Isn't 34 million dollars too much?
You looked like you were suffering,
so I got rid of her for you.
What brought you here?
I came here with the editor of my publishing company.
Then I saw you.
Yeon Woo, should we go someplace nice?
The weather is so nice.
Isn't this a great place for a walk?
It's nice.
You should come here with your boyfriend.
Are you seeing anyone these days?
I broke up with them a while ago.
- With who? - With all of them.
Why?
I want to give my heart to a single person now.
I plan...
on giving my full attention...
to him and only him.
It's late. Should we go home?
Is there any place we can go?
Don't you want to go home?
Not really.
It feels too empty.
Are you feeling lonely?
If you're feeling lonely,
should I move into your place?
Come on, don't joke.
I'm not joking. I'm serious.
- Stop that. No. - Well?
I mean it!
Seo Kang Hoon has the healer gene for me.
Kang Hoon is my healer,
and I'm his healer.
This means he has both...
the Indecent Octopus Tentacle Gene and the healer gene.
Does that mean...
(So Jin's dying gene)
our healer gene relationship...
put his Indecent Octopus Tentacle Gene...
(Kang Hoon's Indecent Octopus Tentacle Gene)
into dormancy?
(World's Best Firefighter Seo Kang Hoon)
How is your wrist?
Try not to strain it.
Come over to the restaurant tomorrow night for dinner.
Really?
Unfortunately, your heart rate is on the rise.
We can't delay the operation.
I see.
Don't worry. It will go well.
Okay.
When Pu Reum comes out,
you'll suddenly lose a lot of blood and bodily fluids.
But I'm certain your heart will endure it.
I'll be beside you so that you can endure it.
Doctor.
When I almost made the wrong choice that night,
Yo Han was the first to find me.
He thought we were fated to be.
Actually, my little sibling is sick too.
People think...
I'm single because of that,
but I suffered depression for years.
It was my sibling who consoled me daily.
Without my sibling, I wouldn't be alive now.
The more I hear about his life,
the more...
I feel like...
he's someone meant for me.
I feel the same, Young A.
I never expected a situation like this,
but the patient needs to go in. Please finish your talk.
- Doctor. - Yes?
About that person...
who persuaded me on the rooftop...
It's thanks to her...
Pu Reum and I are alive.
Please, keep on living.
Don't die.
Would you please tell her...
that I'm sincerely thankful?
I will.
It's 4:57pm.
Ms. Yoo.
Congratulations.
I'll close you up.
Okay.
Doctor, something looks off with the mother.
She's losing consciousness.
Young A, open your eyes. Young A.
Young A, open your eyes!
She lost more than 2,000cc of blood.
Give her some uterotonic,
and prepare the balloon catheter.
Hurry!
Her oxygen saturation is dropping!
She lost more than 3,000cc of blood.
Her blood pressure is 65 to 34.
Yo Han, stay focused.
- Start the arteriopressor. - Okay.
Ms. Yoo, aren't you going to hold Pu Reum?
You have to meet Pu Reum. Ms. Yoo!
Ms. Yoo!
More.
To some people,
that single moment to meet each other...
might be more precious than anything in the world.
The bleeding won't stop.
- Hurry. - Her uterus is unstable.
Keep on living.
Both you...
and Pu Reum.
Please, keep on living.
Don't die.
Her blood pressure is rising,
and her heart rate is dropping.
They're now stable.
Ms. Yoo,
thank you for hanging on.
Good job.
- Good work, everyone. - Good work.
Mom.
I met a nerdy woman.
Her name is Han So Jin.
You know her too, don't you?
I hear you know each other.
What do you think of her?
I hear you are close with her.
After breaking up with her,
I can't help but think of her every day.
This never happened to me before.
What is this I'm feeling?
You must know.
I'll be back.
In the last 3 years, 193 accidents happened...
on mud flats,
and 27 of them lost their lives.
This year, there were 33 accidents up to last month.
Here is the next story.
Around 8:33pm this evening,
a fire broke out at a detached house...
in Yongdo-dong, Seoul.
Jeongin firefighters dispatched after receiving the report...
and attempted to rescue the residents of the house,
but firefighter Seo who is in his 20s was trapped inside...
and was transferred to Yeonsung Hospital.
The fire first started on the second floor...
and engulfed the whole building.
It was put out in one hour.
Firefighter Seo is currently in a critical state.
- Mister... - No way.
It can't be Kang Hoon.
(My Son)
He was known to have passed the Critical Care Paramedic exam,
which was known to be difficult to pass among firefighters.
Many are showing regret to the turn of events.
- Fire authorities say... - Won't he pick up?
Why isn't he picking up?
When the news of his critical state was announced,
the treatment towards firefighters...
The car...
The car is over there.
Okay, let's go.
I'm okay.
I'm okay...
Hey! Are you okay?
- I'm fine. - Are you okay?
Try getting up.
- Are you okay? - I'm okay.
- Try getting up. - My legs are weak.
- Mister. - Mister!
- What happened? - Yeon Woo.
- Hey, Yeon Woo. - Yes?
- Kang Hoon... - Yes?
Kang Hoon was admitted to a hospital.
Could you drive us to Yeonsung Hospital?
We better rush there.
- He's at the hospital. - Okay.
- He's at the hospital. - We should go.
Mister.
You know Kang Hoon always follows all the safety rules.
I'm sure he's fine. Please don't worry.
He's right. Kang Hoon would never die...
and leave us behind.
Please breathe slowly.
Gosh.
Hello.
- Kang Hoon... - So Jin.
Sung Mi, did something happen to Kang Hoon?
No, you got it wrong.
I have to check for myself.
Please calm down.
Kang Hoon!
- What happened to him? - Sir.
What happened?
Please calm down.
You got it wrong.
So Jin.
That was when I realized...
the truth I've been struggling to neglect.
I'm sorry.
I'll be good to you in my next life.
But thanks to the time I spent with you and our children,
I enjoyed brief happiness.
I could hardly believe...
that the moments belonged to me.
I wish to see my family one more time.
I love you.
Dad!
No...
The worst day of my life happened four years ago.
My forgetful gene erased everything from that day.
Both the sadness and Kang Hoon who was with me.
Hey.
If you die, I'll...
I won't die.
How can I die?
I'd never hurt Dad...
or you in that way.
Was that why?
I forgot about someone precious who was always beside me.
He was always by my side.
Whenever I was in my worst moments,
he made me smile.
My DNA lover...
was him all along.
Hey! You jerk!
I thought something happened to you!
I thought something happened,
and I was going to go with you!
Hey.
I told you to always be careful.
You have the hero gene,
so death is always near you!
How could I die and leave the two of you behind?
More than that,
I'm worried about my colleague Seo Min Kyu.
Right. How is he?
Is he in a bad state?
You're lucky.
(DNA Lover)
Did you officially confess?
Not yet.
This is your opportunity to snatch her!
Love is all about timing.
No.
I care more about how she feels than how I feel at the moment.
This volunteer work is full of love.
This is why I never believe it when people say they broke up.
Please stop choking me.
He keeps on showing up whenever I'm about to forget...
and gets me shaken up.
I'll wait for you one more time.
Go to So Jin and confess sincerely to her.
But if it doesn't work out again,
you should come to me.