(DNA Lover)
(Choi Si Won)
(Jung In Sun)
(Lee Tae Hwan)
(Jung Eugene)
(DNA Lover)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
Goodness, are those bubbles?
I guess so.
Where are they coming from?
They must be from over there.
- Try holding it.
- Me?
How did you do that?
What? That's cool.
My dating history for
the 32 years of my life.
Eleven crushes and
nine confessions of love.
Seven awful breakups.
Hey, look at this.
Goodness.
And today.
I...
found my DNA lover.
What should we do? The tables
are full, and there's a long line.
They have delicious paella,
so I wanted to have it with you.
Is that so? That's too bad.
Let's come back some other time.
Okay.
Then, should I show you
one of my favorite spots?
That place is really popular.
Gosh, this place really
is popular, as you said.
Look at this line.
Bye.
- Yeon Woo.
- Yes?
- Hurry up and grab a table.
- What?
Hurry. Grab a table!
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Ta-da.
It may not be as good as
a fancy restaurant, but try it.
This is good.
Right? It's pretty good, right? I told you.
You must come here often.
I could tell you've done this
more than a couple of times.
Oh, I come here every now and then.
You know, some days are like that.
"Is this life only hard for me?"
I come here whenever I feel that way.
But isn't this too humble
for a day like that?
This place is a popular
place in a different sense.
It's popular for people watching.
I see.
Last time, some kids were crowded around,
trying to feed snacks to a street cat.
That was so cute to watch.
As I watch people, I can smile,
and then, my worries and
concerns disappear too.
What do you think? Isn't this
a very cost-effective therapy?
You're right.
What about you?
When you feel tired or sad,
is there a place you go to
for a therapeutic moment?
- "For a therapeutic moment?"
- Yes.
I think I should give it some thought.
Shouldn't you have some
breathing room, at least?
Let me know if you think of one later on.
I showed you a new popular place today,
and I told you a new way to
have a therapeutic moment.
I gave you too much for free.
Next time, you have to treat
me to something delicious.
Saffron. The gem of Persia.
One must dry 500 pistils...
for a single gram of this spice.
With a few strands, the
scent can fill the entire house.
And it has anti-inflammatory
and antibacterial qualities...
and lowers blood pressure as well.
This is perfect for soothing my stomach...
from the irritations of instant
foods from a convenience store.
So Jin seems to like junk food.
I haven't seen her eating
any healthy foods either.
I must let her know...
how important food is.
The man with pheromones
of the heavenly garden.
The healing gene that will
save me from the dying gene.
Despite all the signal interferences,
he received my telepathy...
and appeared before me.
My DNA lover.
I will love him forever.
I should fall in love slowly.
Very slowly!
(Sim General Hospital's Sim Yeon Woo)
What were you doing?
Me? Oh, I...
It's a secret.
Should we meet again tomorrow?
We've only been apart for an
hour, and you want to meet again?
Slowly. I have to cherish
these meetings with him.
How about we meet on the weekend instead?
I have to see patients this Saturday.
Let's go and eat something
delicious after work tomorrow.
There's a very delicious Bulgarian
restaurant run by a local chef.
I'll make the reservation.
Bulgarian? I've never tried that before.
If you send me the
address, I'll meet you there.
Goodnight, Yeon Woo.
I can't believe it!
Are you two dating?
Hey, how can we start dating right away?
We're just having a fling first.
What if you end up having a fling only?
Nowadays, people call it a fling...
even if they break
up after living together.
Really?
Then, should I just go ahead and
say that we're dating tomorrow?
That can't happen.
(Episode 7: Gut Racing, Not Heart Racing)
- Hello, Auntie.
- Would you like some sundae?
Yes, give me lots of liver and
intestines, not so much sundae.
Thank you.
- Hello.
Can I get some tteokbokki and sundae to go?
And please leave out
the liver and intestines.
Why won't you eat this when it's so good?
You must eat all your meals here.
Try it.
You won't be able to stop
eating this once you try it.
I don't like liver.
I don't like people who
try to steal your guts too.
Was that a joke?
How funny.
Since you bought me
food last time, I'll pay today.
Here you go.
Then, if you don't like liver,
do you not like fois gras either?
I love it.
I read an article about
that. Isn't it animal cruelty?
If you eat fatty liver, it'll only
increase your cholesterol levels.
Try to quit eating it.
Thank you.
They raise geese naturally
these days. It's fine to eat them.
- Have a good day.
- Bye.
Hey, Mr. Seo!
You're missing out on a great
joy in life without fois gras!
Goodness, what a shame.
He's cute.
Excuse me.
I believe we've never met. Who are you?
Just ignore me.
Today is a special day for me.
I mean, I've never seen you
like this over the past five years.
Who is this guy?
My partner.
"Partner?"
I'll be going, then.
Wait, but...
Goodness.
This feels ominous.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
- My goodness.
- I wasn't hurt.
You called?
Oh, I pressed it by accident.
Oh, I see.
Mikael, have you been well?
Well, it's always the same for me.
By the way, I've never
met this lady before.
Oh, this is the Bulgarian chef.
His cooking is totally Korean-style.
I see. I'll look forward to it today.
All right.
Thank you.
This place...
Their signature dish is...
It's been a while, Mikael.
The guy you always came
with. Yeon Woo. He's back there.
Oh, really?
He already took the window seat I like.
Should we go somewhere else?
I know another place
with a great window seat.
No.
Let's go to the table next to it.
Okay.
- This is...
- Yeon Woo.
Hey.
When did you get here?
Just now.
Hello, So Jin.
Oh, this is...
Oh, it's nice to meet you. I'm Cha Yu Ram.
Oh, right.
Nice to meet you. I'm Sim Yeon Woo.
This is Ms. Han So Jin.
It seems like you haven't ordered yet.
If it's all right, could
we share the table?
This is an important
dinner date. I'm sorry.
I think it would be better for
you two to enjoy your time.
Don't mind us.
- We'll eat over there.
- Yes, okay.
Hey, why don't we...
Yeon Woo, shall we just share the table?
I've been wanting to talk to Mi Eun too.
- With me?
- Yes.
I saw you on Yoo Myung
Hee's social media before.
You know Ms. Yoo Myung Hee? How?
Oh, I'm her daughter.
Not like a social relationship.
Her actual daughter.
I've always wanted to meet you someday.
So, you were her daughter.
What an interesting relationship we have.
I know.
Yeon Woo, we can sit together, right?
Yes, sure. Have a seat.
So Jin, does it taste all right?
Oh, yes.
As Yeon Woo said, the
chef must be very talented.
It's good.
I'm glad.
I used to come here often with Yeon Woo.
Yeon Woo has a pickier
appetite than you think.
I'm not a picky eater.
Try this too, So Jin.
It must not suit your taste, So Jin.
Pardon? Oh, no, it's fine.
I mean, why are they such a good match?
Are they best buddies or
soulmates or something?
Why would you eat pork sirloin like that?
It's only salty and greasy.
By the way, are you two lovers?
- Pardon? Well...
- Well...
We're getting to know each other.
Oh, Mi Eun and I
interfered on your time, then.
Hey, you ordered this wine.
- Do you remember?
- Brussels.
So Jin, you should definitely
go to Belgium later on.
Oh, you two must've
been to Belgium together.
Well, the traveling club.
Oh, you were that guy.
The guy in the traveling club with
the same taste and preferences...
as if you were twins.
You have similar values,
so you agree on most things,
and you broke up, but you
still feel like you're dating.
I read it in your book.
You broke up twice over three years.
But you dated again
three times or something.
- Cha Yu Ram.
- Leave him alone.
He must like you a lot.
You should stop acting
like you have manners.
Mi Eun.
I don't think I can carry on
with this abnormal relationship.
I'll be going.
I didn't mean to do this
when we sat down together.
I'm sorry about this, So Jin.
Sorry, Yeon Woo.
I'll get going first.
Let's eat.
Try this too, So Jin. It's good.
He's forcing his preferences on someone?
Yeon Woo is doing that?
He has the Indecent Octopus Tentacle Gene.
How did he date Jang
Mi Eun for three years?
And how can you not have
any sense in this situation?
You're talking to yourself again.
Why aren't you going inside?
- Hello.
Look at this.
You didn't use to drink this
beer. Why are you copying me?
I got hooked on it
because of you. Goodness.
No!
Hey! Ham and tuna mayo is my favorite!
Ham and tuna mayo used to be my baby food.
You should let me have it.
So Jin,
you should definitely
go to Belgium later on.
That's oddly bothering me.
What is?
You know, Yeon Woo.
He has an ex-girlfriend
he really gets along with.
- Oh, Ms. Jang Mi Eun?
- Yes.
What? What's this? How do you know Mi Eun?
Oh, I just do.
From what you can see,
what do you think is going
on between those two?
Well, I'm not sure.
I don't care about other
people's dating lives.
What?
So, why do you care so
much about my dating life?
You're different from them.
So, what? What's bothering
you about Jang Mi Eun?
You said she was his ex anyway.
Well, we happened to
have dinner together today.
Yeon Woo, Mi Eun,
and Mi Eun's boyfriend.
No.
Should I say he's her ex-boyfriend?
What kind of combination is
that? Could you even eat properly?
Well...
They're just like friends
of the opposite gender.
I don't think I should be bothered by it.
Oh, my. That's so not like you.
Why are you being so nonchalant?
When you break up with a guy,
you get rid of everything
related to that guy by burning it.
That's because I broke
up with them in a bad way.
No matter how you break up,
people who have dated before...
have no reason to see
each other after breaking up.
Is it hard to go past a
certain line with someone...
when you've already crossed it once?
There are guys like you.
And there must be guys like Yeon Woo.
I think those two...
will never break up.
How can you be so sure?
Can't you tell they're so similar?
Those two are the same types of people.
Yeon Woo and Ms. Jang Mi Eun.
They see and feel the same things.
Meeting your destiny...
and having them as your
own are two different things.
Yeon Woo is your destiny?
After many experiments,
I concluded that he's my DNA lover.
Let's go now.
You can go ahead.
I'll go home with A Ri when
she's done with the mass.
- In these hands - In these hands
- That hold the body of Christ
- Give me the power - Give me the power
- To be safe - To be safe
- In my ears - In my ears
- That have heard your word
- Let them block out - Let them block out
- The noise of the world
Brothers and sisters,
shall we finish up here?
Father, Sister Anna has
packed a boxed meal today.
That sounds delicious.
- I love it.
- How nice.
- I know.
- Right?
It's delicious.
I mean, how can you cook so well?
You really are.
I like this gimbap.
It's so delicious.
- This is good.
- It really is.
- Good work.
- It's delicious.
Sister Anna. Thank you for the food.
I like everything with minari in it.
Really? Me too.
We have similar tastes in food.
Why...
Oh, you have something...
I got it.
You're so funny.
(Whoever needs it can take it.
It'll be hauled away in a week.)
Hey, wait for me.
What?
I was waiting for you in the park.
When did you get back?
You usually walk through
the park on your way home.
I took a different route today.
Oh, my.
You could kill someone
with that tteokbokki.
Even when I want to
die, I still have an appetite.
That gives me a reason to live.
Why are you putting minari in tteokbokki?
Minari is good in anything.
Father Andrea also likes
anything with minari in it.
They say food preferences
affect personalities.
For the first time,
I thought Father Andrea and I...
may have something in common.
It must be nice that you guys are similar.
What?
("Will We Be a Good
Fit?" Author Jang Mi Eun)
(Chapter 8, Can I see
my ex-boyfriend again?)
(A guy from a travel club with
the same preferences as me!)
(A guy I broke up with but
who I still have feelings for!)
(I want to tell you the reason
why my ex-boyfriend K and I...)
If this K in this book really is Yeon Woo,
it means they were
together for three years...
and that they broke up 2
times within those 3 years.
They dated, broke up,
dated again, and broke up again.
Why did they break up?
No. Why couldn't they break up? Why?
It could be that the 100
types of germs in their guts...
are drawing them to
each other like magnets.
They may have similar food preferences.
You're right, A Ri. They have
very similar food preferences.
It's called, "like-attracts-like germ."
"Like-attracts..."
It's something I've
been researching lately.
When two people have
similar food preferences,
they have "like-attracts-like
germs" in their guts.
Those germs change the
concentration of their sex pheromones...
and cause those two people...
to be attracted to each other...
as potential mates.
Wait.
I know that theory.
In the fruit fly mating experiment,
the male fruit fly was attracted...
to the female fruit fly
with similar germs to itself.
If so, is love done by
the germs in our guts,
instead of by people?
Because like always attracts like.
That makes sense.
If the microorganisms
connecting the gut and the brain...
are similar types of germs,
it's only natural to like each other more.
It was three years.
Yeon Woo and Mi Eun
were drawn to each other...
because they ate similar things.
That's why they got back
together even after breaking up.
If so, do they not only
have the same taste in food,
but they also share
moods, personalities, tastes,
and the way they think too?
You're going that far?
It's unfair.
They must've eaten...
the same food at least 5
times a week for 3 years.
It could've been that way
since they were babies.
This won't do.
From now on, I'll make him eat what I eat.
Three meals a day?
No. At least one meal a day.
Is that possible?
Where there's a will, there's a way.
"Impossible" is not part of my vocabulary.
I'm going to give him...
my "like-attracts-like germ!"
Ms. Nam!
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Doctor.
We ran into each other again.
Well, that's true...
I heard early morning runs
were good for endurance,
so I thought I'd give it a try.
It's six in the morning.
Is it really a coincidence that
we ran into each other here...
at this time?
To tell you the truth,
I asked your coach about
your workout schedule.
I'm not a stalker or anything.
I...
Well...
I wanted to do the same thing as you.
Every day...
I'll get going!
Doctor.
You'll get sick if you work
yourself too hard on your first day.
It's not that. I was late
downloading the bicycle app.
Wait here for a second.
This is where I do a 1km sprint.
I'll be right back.
Let's go together on my way back.
Well...
Together...
Let's go, Nam Sung Mi!
(A goddess in the ring, Nam Sung Mi, )
(dominates the National Lifetime
Sports Martial Arts Competition!)
Let's go!
Tell me.
You always drink tons of Coke
when you're worried about something.
What's on your mind?
Well...
It doesn't seem like an accident.
Oh, that fire at the apartment?
We couldn't identify the cause.
It wasn't a gas explosion
or a short circuit.
It's strange that the flowers didn't burn.
The police aren't dumb, you know.
I'm sure there was a reason
they said it was an accident.
Right.
I've been...
randomly running into
a guy every day recently.
But it's strange.
When I saw him today,
this part,
no, this part...
had this tickly feeling.
And right now as well.
I'm just thinking about him,
so why does it feel like
my mouth is drying up...
and my eyes are getting hot?
Who is that guy?
You don't need to know. A guy...
who is very different from me.
I see.
- What are you looking at?
- Look at you.
(Ha Ga Hee)
I heard she had many family
members that she had to support,
but the chief mourner is a
friend from the hostess bar.
How did you know about this?
Of course, I should know.
It involves my husband.
(Ha Ga Hee)
Thank you for coming even though Ga Hee...
only came to church with me once.
Will Ga Hee be able to go to a good place?
Death is what ends sins
and allows for resurrection.
Today's dinner menu.
What do you think of miso ramen...
made with shiitake broth and miso paste?
I found a good restaurant.
I'm telling you. Ms. Ha Ga Hee
was Chief Director Sim's mistress.
They met at a hostess bar.
Didn't you see Ms. Ha the other day?
She was covered in designer goods.
I heard he bought her a foreign
car, an apartment in Gangnam,
and all of that.
I can't believe she
ended up dying in a fire.
She really got punished.
I heard she was also pregnant
with Chief Director Sim's baby too.
So it was her goal to become
the chief director's wife.
Gosh, what a bad girl.
Hey.
Watch your mouths. There
are expecting mothers here.
Yes, ma'am.
You're here. Would you like some tea?
Let's have a quick chat.
Ga Hee and my child died.
You seem to know already.
Did you hear from your mom?
Your mom...
came by Ga Hee's funeral.
But she looked too happy. It was strange.
So what?
I met with Doctor Kim,
your mom's psychiatrist.
I heard your mom stopped
taking her medicine recently.
Ga Hee wouldn't have died like that.
Wasn't it an accident?
Your mom waited for me her whole life...
solely based on the belief
that I wouldn't abandon...
the woman who gave birth to my child.
She's the type to do
anything if she found out...
that Ga Hee was pregnant with my child.
Was hurting Mom all of her life not enough?
Are you trying to frame
her as a murderer too?
Your younger sibling
died. Don't you care at all?
Even if they weren't your sibling,
they were your patient and her baby!
Do you even deserve to be a gynecologist?
Hearing that...
from you...
makes me laugh.
What?
Do you deserve to be a father?
Do you deserve to be a husband?
Think about that first
deep inside of your heart...
before you question...
what I deserve to be.
I find what you said so
disgusting and offensive.
Have you found anything?
Ms. Yeom finished her
appointment at Iroun Genetic Center...
and just went back home.
Keep an eye on her.
- Hey.
- There's an issue...
with Ms. Joo Min Ha's placenta.
If her uterus ruptures,
we may need to remove it.
It would be helpful if you
were there for the delivery.
Okay. I'm on my way.
So Jin. I have to go into
an emergency surgery.
I'm sorry. Let's eat miso
ramen together next time.
"Like-attracts-like germ" strategy.
It's only the first day, and
it's already not going well.
It's finally time.
We waited a whole year for today.
Let's try 18 courses of these oysters...
that are full of flavor
at this time of year.
They are delicious when
the weather gets cold.
And this chef has been cooking
with oysters in Boryeong...
for 30 years. How will his dishes taste?
So Jin. You don't like oysters.
You're right.
Why do they look so good?
I've made several delivery
orders while watching this show.
Watching them enjoy the food
makes me impulsively buy things.
That's right.
That's what I should do.
What?
What is it?
(We're always together.)
What?
Mr. Seo. Just once. Please?
- Just help me out once.
- It's not even sushi.
Why do you want to make
something like that here?
With the hardwood interior
and the lighting on the bar,
this place is so luxurious.
I get so hungry whenever I come here.
Also, that "We're always together."
It's so memorable.
It feels like food that you
want to eat with the person...
you always want to be with.
Okay.
Just for the three days
I'm gone to go fishing.
After you're done, you
have to clean up really well.
Yes, of course!
Mr. Seo.
Since you're letting me use the place,
could you let me use that too?
That? My chef's hat?
No. This is mine.
Just once.
- Hey.
- Just once.
Then you can use a new one.
You should use a new one.
Here.
What do you think?
It suits you. You look like a chef.
- Oh, yes!
- Oh, my!
Yeon Woo. Did the surgery go well?
You haven't had dinner yet, right?
Yes. I'm sorry I couldn't
keep our promise today.
Let's have dinner together tomorrow...
Okay. It's time for "Han
So Jin's Five Meals A Day."
When I'm craving...
Italian food after
working late into the night,
I eat pasta covered in a
warm blanket of cheese.
The dish I have prepared today...
is Jackson Pasta.
The secret recipe of the number one dish...
on the Convenience Store Yumchelin Guide.
You can get all of these
ingredients at a convenience store...
just three minutes from your house.
Okay. I'll get started now.
Pour some water on the pasta...
and cover it up.
While the noodles cook,
prepare the tteokbokki too.
I'll microwave the
tteokbokki for three minutes.
Okay. What will we do while
we wait for three minutes?
We'll begin preparing the ingredients.
We just need to add all of
these ingredients and mix.
Wait.
You should be salivating...
by this point in the video, Yeon Woo.
The limitless world of flavor...
that you can't experience
without tasting this is coming soon.
I'll add the cheese on top.
This color...
and this smell.
- Cheese!
- Did you see that cheese pull?
I'll give it a taste.
Dad, I'm back...
What's going on?
It's so delicious!
Mr. Sim.
You always want carb-heavy
foods after surgery.
There's something else...
I really want to eat right now.
What is it?
Okay. My eating show will continue...
tomorrow evening.
See you tomorrow, Yeon Woo. Bye.
Bye.
Look at you.
But this isn't Ms. Han's pasta.
If I'm going to eat pasta,
it should be really nice.
Isn't it good?
Yes.
Why were you doing that?
Oh, nothing.
A new strategy I'm trying out.
I wonder if Yeon Woo
followed my recipe well.
Did you eat all of that?
You and I have very
similar food preferences.
We were like that as kids too.
So we always fought over food.
You're right.
We both always loved aged
kimchi and braised pollack.
- And salmon too.
- You're right.
Oh, right.
What now?
You and I must share...
so many "like-attracts-like germs."
"Like-attract-like" what?
When you look at me, instead
of your heart beating fast,
don't your intestines beat fast?
Thump, thump.
- Isn't your stomach pounding?
- Stop it.
Don't be ridiculous.
Also, what is this?
Why are you wearing my father's hat?
Hey, no.
Stop it. You punk. Stop it!
There.
Put it back.
- That's a better look.
- Before I get angry.
- You're really pretty now.
- One.
- You are...
- Two!
Okay.
What are you looking at?
What?
Well...
Why? Do you think I look like a real chef?
You're pretty.
Hey, you punk.
You should say things
like that out loud. Again.
"You're pretty."
Hey.
I thought you downed the food way too fast.
Drink this. Drink it up quick.
You're too old for this.
Why did you eat so fast?
When you look at me, instead
of your heart beating fast,
don't your intestines beat fast?
My gosh.
I'm out of my mind.
Yes.
Let's run. I'll run. I must run.
Yeon Woo. What did you eat last night?
I had cheese pasta, of course.
How could I eat anything
else after your eating show?
Torturing someone
with food is a tough skill.
Where did you learn that from?
Did it really work? What a relief.
What's a relief?
I'm relieved that you ate well.
You won't know what I mean.
Today's dinner...
I'm really sorry, So Jin.
I'll call you back soon.
That's right.
My convenient restaurant
cooking and eating show...
will make you eat anything.
He should have tens of millions
like-attracts-like germs now.
Just wait.
I'll fill your intestines
with germs just like mine.
(The Battle of Kindred Germs)
How about beef bone soup for dinner?
(Day 2, Project Create Kindred Germs)
Beef bone soup and dumplings.
Whenever I feel under the weather,
a bowl of this beef bone soup...
heats me right up.
The broth is hot and spicy.
Shall we try it?
You eat so well. So why are you so short?
(Day 3)
Today... Drumroll, please.
A really simple
convenience store version...
of cheesy fries.
Pour it in like this.
Okay.
My gosh.
Doesn't it look appetizing?
I'm starving.
Let's see.
(Let's meet! 7pm today, Grilled Town)
(What memories. I haven't
been in ages. I'm in!)
(I'm definitely in. Time
works too. I'll be there too!)
Dip it right in and...
Hey, camera guy.
I need you to focus. The angle's not right.
Oh, sorry. The food looked so good.
- My gosh.
- Cheers.
You're right.
It's still good. The fries too.
Try it.
- Isn't it good?
- It's good.
It's so good.
Shai.
We ate the same foods for three days.
We should have a billion
like-attracts-like kindred germs.
My plan is going so smoothly.
What will happen next?
(Always Sushi, Chef's recommendation)
(Sim General Hospital's Sim Yeon Woo)
It's Yeon Woo.
So Jin, will you do an eating
show this weekend too?
Yes. What are you doing right now?
I left work after my morning shift.
I prepared something amazing.
It'll be worth looking forward to.
I'll be waiting.
Okay. Shall I check the
state of his intestines?
Hey, Yeon Woo. Did you notice a change?
Like, do you feel unusually constipated,
or do your feces have a different color?
The color?
Are we close enough
to discuss such details?
Oh, well, no, but...
I was wondering if you followed the recipe.
If you get the recipe wrong,
it could ruin the dish and
give you a stomachache.
The recipe?
After watching you live yesterday,
I went to a restaurant famous for
their cheesy fries, so don't worry.
(Day 3 experiment failed)
You went to a restaurant...
instead of a convenience store?
On your own?
No, with my travel club friends.
Oh, the travel club...
Was Jang Mi Eun there too?
Yes, she's a member too.
Then what about...
the cheese pasta three days ago?
Oh, that, I had at a
restaurant with Jung Tam.
(Day 1 experiment failed)
The day after, with Jung Tam,
I had beef bone soup at a famous place.
(Day 2 experiment failed)
Is something wrong?
(Project failed)
No, well...
Yeon Woo, I need to hang up.
(Project failed)
Did I do something wrong?
Yeon Woo and Mi Eun...
ate the same food again.
So what?
"So what?"
It means they increased
their number of kindred germs.
Those two!
Put that knife down. Drop it.
What is this germ that
you're making a fuss about it?
According to a body of research,
when pigs were fed
lactobacillus that humans take,
they became very amicable towards humans.
The like-attracts-like kindred
germs created a sense of kinship.
Like you and me.
Okay, but that was about pigs.
What about it anyway?
I want to do what Mi Eun did and create...
a kind of kinship with Yeon Woo.
A kinship that they have...
and we don't.
But I don't think it worked.
(Always Sushi)
So that was it.
A sense of kinship.
I feel bad now.
What should I do?
What should I do to not mind?
(Black pepper jjajang popcorn is out!)
(New message)
So Jin, do you want to come
over to my place tomorrow?
It's an official dinner invitation.
At his place? With him?
Forget the eating show.
Let's eat the same thing at the same table.
Okay?
So Jin.
Han So Jin makes that
face whenever she's in love.
She smiles with a slight wink.
Like when she eats a sour tangerine.
Tomatoes, celery,
lettuce, bell peppers,
abalone, gochujang,
a baguette, milk,
ricotta cheese, feta cheese,
whipped cream, fresh cream.
I'll mix ingredients that could
never work together to make...
a symphony.
So Jin has the taste buds of a child.
She likes sweet foods and loves cheese.
She likes rose pasta,
so she loves fresh cream.
To make her eat the ginseng of the sea,
I must coat this...
with instant noodle powder and butter.
(Jang Mi Eun)
Yeon Woo.
It's my birthday today.
I want to spend it with you
minus the travel club members.
Ta-da. I even brought some wine.
Oh, that's too bad.
I invited So Jin over for dinner.
I see.
Then I'll just stay for some tea.
Sorry. I'm cooking right now,
and I'd like to focus just on that.
What?
Let's celebrate your birthday
with the group another time.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Let's do that, then. You can keep this.
I will, thanks a lot.
Get home safely. Sorry.
Where are you? Do you want naengmyeon?
I'm with Jung Tam and Sung Mi.
Hey, Seo Kang Hoon.
No. You can eat enough for me too.
- I'm going to Yeon Woo's.
- Over here.
- I'll have something nicer.
- Seo Kang Hoon.
Kang Hoon?
Hey. So what now?
What did she say? Will she join us?
She can't make it. She has other plans.
Does she? We can go without her.
Is she making an excuse
to avoid coming out?
Well...
She went to Yeon Woo's to
have dinner with him. Alone.
At Yeon Woo's place?
I doubt they'll stop at just having dinner.
Yeon Woo does have women over often.
His bathroom's full of
amenities you'd see in a hotel.
The sneaky punk.
I think...
you'll need to go without
me. I can't join you.
Why not? Come with us!
This will feel so awkward...
Shall we? Go? Now?
Okay.
This room,
and that puzzle. Do you remember it all?
It took me a long time
to put it back together.
Can you delete that memory?
I can't. I'll think of it
whenever I feel down.
Hang your jacket up there.
Okay.
Do you like the food?
Yes. I love it.
Why...
did you suddenly decide to invite me over?
Do I need a reason to do so?
Sharing good food,
going to nice places,
enjoying things together.
I wanted to create a
sense of kinship with you.
A sense of kinship?
Out of the blue?
It's not out of the blue.
That's weird.
Let's eat before the food I
worked hard to prepare gets cold.
Okay.
Start with the cream pasta.
Sure.
Try the cheese tteokbokki too.
I'm so full.
How was it?
It was delicious.
Yeon Woo. It's the first time
food made me this happy...
What's wrong? Do you feel unwell?
No.
I'm slightly lactose intolerant.
This happens when I eat
something heavy on dairy.
It settles with time. Don't worry.
Are you sure you're okay?
I am.
Shall I make you some coffee?
Yes.
Okay.
Not now. This is bad.
The coffee smells great.
It does. I can smell it from here.
What a lovely aroma.
It hurts so bad.
The coffee smells amazing today.
My gosh.
Thanks.
Do you feel hot?
I turned the heater
on in case you felt cold.
Oh, is that why? Thank you.
Just in case the food was too greasy,
I made the coffee extra
strong. I hope that's okay.
Extra strong coffee?
I like strong coffee.
If I drink this too,
my anal sphincter might give in.
Shall we...
go and...
watch a movie now?
Shall we?
I can keep it in. I can do this.
Hang in there. Just a bit.
I can do this.
Han So Jin.
No. I can't do this.
What if I make a bigger scene?
Let's try to get to the couch first.
Are you okay, So Jin?
Yes. Is the movie on already?
Act like I'm in no hurry.
Look natural, as if I'm looking around.
Focus on where I place my feet.
You still feel hot?
How long...
- can I last like this?
- You're sweating a lot.
No way.
I feel butterflies in this situation?
I'm fine.
Hey.
This is...
A guy like you doesn't deserve to be loved!
The day you barged in,
the sight of you with chopsticks
in your hair left a huge impression.
So I got this.
Come closer.
It's pretty.
Sorry.
I can't do this.
I...
What?
I think...
I must go home.
- What do you mean...
- Do not follow me!
Just...
let me leave.
- Please.
- What's the matter?
So Jin.
Why... Your jacket.
Your jacket.
This is so bad.
Kang Hoon. I need you to come get me.
I think I'm going to die. It hurts so bad.
So Jin. You sound weird. Where are you?
I'm in the public toilet...
of Yeon Woo's apartment building.
So Jin.
Han So Jin!
So Jin, stay with me. Where does it hurt?
My stomach hurts so bad.
Help me.
- So Jin, what happened...
- Yeon Woo.
I can't talk for long.
I'm taking So Jin to Sim
Hospital's ER. See you there.
- Hang in there.
- It hurts so bad.
(DNA Lover)
Kang Hoon. To So Jin...
- Are you okay?
- What are you?
There are people you want to
share your hurt and struggles with.
And there are people you want
to share just the good things with.
- Kang Hoon.
- Be careful.
I like So Jin?
No!
I know it's not right.
But I want him.
So Jin, you're not alone.
Before the surgery, on the
way to the operating room,
and inside the operating room,
I'll be by your side.