=The Forbidden Flower=
=Episode 5=
(Barber)
Hi.
Anything?
Something has really happened this time.
Father.
Father?
You...
You have a child?
He's my father.
I told you
not to call me this outside.
So,
she's not your child?
She's my elder brother's child.
Why is she calling you father?
Can you be my father?
Can't you be my father?
Why don't
we talk in the house?
I have some nice food.
We can talk and eat at the same time.
How did you get to know her?
I was in the supermarket buying...
Actually, it's nothing.
I was buying something
in the supermarket
and I bumped into her.
The painting fell out.
Then
I brought her back here.
I'll go get something.
Child, eat an apple.
Don't call me child.
You're a child.
I'm a child,
but you shouldn't call me child.
Was the guy in the supermarket
your boyfriend?
I can tell something is wrong
with you two.
He's not my boyfriend.
Why were you feeling nervous?
Weren't you feeling nervous, too?
After all, you were lying.
Fine.
When your uncle comes back,
I'll tell him the truth.
After all, I can explain myself.
As for you,
I'm not sure.
When I have money,
I'll pay you back the money
for the painting materials.
Are you saying that we shouldn't mention
anything that has happened?
Liar, bad woman,
troublemaker!
Quanquan.
Listen to me.
Stealing is bad.
You can't take something
that's not yours.
I can ask your uncle to
send you to my studio.
I can teach you for free
and give you brand new
painting materials.
How does that sound?
In my hometown,
I normally get the good first
and my grandmother
would pay for it later.
I thought it works the same here.
I know I was wrong.
I won't do it again.
Can you teach me painting?
It depends on whether you trust
the liar or not.
I wanted to ask him
to thank you personally.
I didn't expect he ran away
just like that.
You're being too kind.
You insisted on giving me money
in the hospital.
Now, you've giving me a job.
I should thank you instead.
You mentioned a friend just now.
What? The drink is too hot?
It's nice.
What's going on with your friend?
Is he a great horticulturist?
Yes.
Let him handle your garden.
He'll do a great job.
What's your friend's name?
Xiao Han.
You're back.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
Wash your hands and eat.
Are you busy lately?
Yes.
You're busy? Great.
When you're working in the daytime,
I'll take care of Quanquan for you.
Let her come to our studio.
I'll teach her painting.
When you get off work...
No need.
I'll send Quanquan back
to hometown tomorrow.
Quanquan.
Don't listen to him.
Just eat.
Let me check him out.
You're not eating?
I'm waiting for you.
I'm still working.
It's okay.
I'm not hungry.
Let me stay here with you.
There are mosquitoes in the greenhouse.
You'll get bitten
wearing like this.
What should I do?
Change into your pants.
I didn't bring any pants.
Why don't
you help me get
some mosquito repellent?
What flower is this with the big leaves?
Epiphyllum.
So, this is epiphyllum.
The legendary
flower that only blossoms for a second.
Epiphyllum hardly blossoms.
Has it blossomed before?
No.
Why?
I guess it's not time yet.
You...
There's a mosquito.
It's flown away.
It's on your leg.
What's it?
A mosquito.
What's wrong with you?
I was bitten by the mosquito
and you didn't kill it for me.
It stopped on you. I can't kill it.
I think you did in on purpose.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Is your hand okay?
- I'm sorry.
- Don't play a fool here.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to fall down.
♪When the night shines♪
♪I'm holding out♪
What about this time?
I did it on purpose this time.
♪When you whisper♪
♪I hear you loud♪
You're not buying anything.
♪When the night shines♪
♪I'm holding out♪
What's going on?
Is your hand okay?
Sit down there.
Why did you go to the kitchen?
I'm thirsty. I was getting
some water in the kitchen.
The water dispenser is
in the living room.
I wanted to get a bowl to get the water.
There's paper cup on
the water dispenser.
Didn't you see it?
I didn't.
Are you blind?
All right.
It's getting late. Go home first.
You're already chasing me away?
Uncle, I'm sleepy. I want to sleep.
No, I...
Look at how bad my legs are bitten.
I can't handle this in the studio.
Do you have
green balm for me?
It's at the second floor.
I'll got get it in the bedroom.
I'll go. I'll get it for you.
Why
is the mosquito
not biting you?
It only bites me alone?
Maybe it prefers
people that're not pure.
Which one
are you talking about?
Is it the mosquito or you?
The mosquito.
What about you?
I didn't bite you.
I'm asking you.
Do you like people that're not pure?
This question...
♪And I see you♪
Why don't
♪You are the only one for me♪
you take a guess?
♪I finally found someone♪
♪I'm willing to give♪
♪I Found someone♪
Go back first.
Thanks for your green balm.
You're welcome.
I'm going back.
Guess it slowly at home.
♪I finally found someone♪
♪I'm willing to give♪
♪I Found someone♪
This question...
Take a guess.
♪Meeting you♪
♪and I see you♪
♪You are the only one for me♪
I'm asking you.
Do you like people that're not pure?
♪I finally found someone♪
♪I'm willing to give♪
♪I Found someone♪
♪I finally found someone♪
♪I'm willing to give♪
♪I Found someone♪
♪You are the only one for me♪
Why aren't you sleeping?
Are you sending me back tomorrow?
I'm used to living alone.
I don't eat on time. I'm afraid I...
Can I stay a few days longer?
Go to bed now.
I'm not a picky eater.
I can eat instant noodles
if you don't cook.
I'll be nice.
Tell me if you don't like anything.
I promise I won't do it.
Send me back only
when the school reopens,
okay?
Actually, when you see this painting,
you may ask me,
is there such a flower
in the world?
Actually, there's none.
All right, you can
write down the flower
that you want to paint.
We'll talk about it later.
Okay, Ms. He.
Good morning.
That day, you told me that
I can send Quanquan to the studio
and you'll take care of her,
does that still count?
Of course.
I happen to have something on
these few days.
Please take care of her.
Come on.
Look. They're my students.
Isn't it great?
Okay, it's recess time.
Go have fun.
- Thank you, Ms. He.
What do you think
about the paintings?
It's great.
Really?
I painted all these.
It's not good then.
What a shame.
Why?
I wanted to teach you myself.
But since you don't like that,
then I can't.
You're willing to teach me?
It depends on my mood.
You can say something nice
to make me happy.
I'm not saying it.
You're stubborn.
You like painting flowers?
Yes.
My uncle likes flowers.
Is that the reason why you like him?
Reason?
I just like him.
I like him as how he is.
You won't understand.
Let's go.
I'll show you over there
the new painting materials
and painting frame.
You must thank me for that.
Let me do it. Take a rest.
You're Xiao Han?
I brought water. It's there.
You can drink it.
Okay.
Thank you.
Why are you here?
What?
What are you talking about?
Why can't I come here?
Where's He Ran?
She's sleeping.
I'll look for her upstairs.
No.
Wait!
Yu!
Slow down.
Wait.
What?
Well...
Ran
is not feeling well today.
She's sleeping after
taking the medicine.
Why don't you come again another day?
She's not feeling well?
What's going on?
Is she having anemia again?
No.
She's caught a cold.
She just needs some rest.
Okay.
I'll look for her upstairs.
What now?
Well, this is the best timing.
You're here just in time.
Well, Yu.
The light in the kitchen is damaged.
Ran and I are not tall enough
to reach it.
I'm getting ready to go out
and get someone to fix it.
And you're here.
That's great.
Why don't
you help us fix it?
I think
you're tall enough to reach it.
Are you joking? I'm 1.85m tall.
Really?
You're really tall.
You're also very handsome.
That's great.
Not too bad.
That's the light.
No problem. Leave it to me.
Do you need a stool?
Are you joking?
Do I even need a stool?
You're right.
Give me a stool.
Here you go, Yu.
Well, Yu,
go ahead.
I'll go get you a glass of water.
Sure.
(Ran, come home quickly.)
(Han Yu is here.)
Help me take care of her. Thank you.
Where are you going?
♪O mio babbino caro♪
♪Mi piace, è bello bello♪
It's so tiring.
How did it go?
It's so easy.
You're good.
Here. Drink some water.
That's why I said
Yu is the best.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
I almost forgot.
I need to look for He Ran.
Yu, well...
Have you taken
lunch?
I haven't. What's the matter?
Look here.
I've made some buns.
It's freshly baked. Give it a try.
No, I'm on a diet.
You're so skinny.
Why do you need to lose weight?
No.
Come on. Don't be shy.
Have a taste.
You're also very handsome.
That's great.
Yu is the best.
You're so skinny.
Why do you need to lose weight?
Well, I need to check on He Ran.
Let go.
Hey, you should
watch your manner.
We should keep a distance.
Hold on.
What's wrong with her?
How did you handle the rubbish?
Why did you throw it in my yard?
The night willow herb
that I've just planted
is all dead now.
I'm sorry.
We were not being careful
when we threw the rubbish.
Not being careful?
That's all you can say?
What about my night willow herb?
The flower has withered.
If the owner was asking for it,
who would take the responsibility?
I will.
What herb is dead?
I will take the responsibility.
Tell me about it.
Who are you?
I'm the...
No.
I
am the host of this house.
Tell me if there's anything.
Don't shout here.
Do you know you're so noisy
that others can't sleep?
You simply threw rubbish everywhere
and I'm shouting here?
Why am I shouting here?
How am I shouting here
Stop shouting.
It's just rubbish, right?
Let me tell you.
I'll give you a lesson today.
No.
Let's talk nicely.
Stop talking nonsense to me.
You can't hit me.
Let me tell you.
You must not act recklessly, young man.
What?
Don't be angry.
Look. Let me tell you.
You can't hit me.
You're young. So, you don't know.
I'll hit you!
Why did you hit
me?
Ma'am.
You're finally back home.
Did Han Yu find out that I was not home?
No, I've been stalling him.
Okay, thank you.
- I'll go up now.
- Go ahead.
Han Yu, why are you here?
What happened to your face?
Did someone hit you?
I fell down accidentally.
You're not a child anymore.
Be careful when you walk next time.
No.
You...
You were sleeping.
You didn't know that
someone was here to make a scene.
Who was that?
A man from next door.
I don't know who he is.
He was shouting downstairs
and he didn't want to stop.
But, no worries.
I've kept him under control.
I took him out with only one arm.
I've kept him under control
totally.
And you were hit by him?
No, I...
I said that I fell down.
Well, the thing is,
I wanted to see you
so badly that
I didn't watch where I was going.
That's
your response?
I got hurt because
I was trying to protect your home.
Shouldn't you...
Shouldn't you
apply some medicine for me
and check the wound?
Ma'am,
apply some medicine for him.
Coming.
No need to trouble her.
I mean it.
Come on. Let me help you.
Don't get infected.
It's not good to have a scar.
Your skin is all scratched.
Hold on. Stop.
You...
Don't move.
It just occurs to me that...
I'm leaving now.
No, clean your wound first.
He's leaving.
Thank you for your help today.
No problem.
Luckily you came home in time.
The gentleman next door
was helping us, too.
I asked him to help.
Thank him for me.
Sure.
Go up and take a rest.
I'll call you when the meal is ready.
Okay.
Why is there someone else?
Usually
he'd only allow others
to take the soil and water for him.
Why would he allow others to
handle the garden?
They're having fun.
No wonder he won't allow me
to go to his garden.
I want to see how this guy looks.
Aunt.
I'm at home.
The restaurant in Xiaozhou Village?
Okay.
I'll be there.
Okay. Bye.
Ms. He, bye.
Bye.
Something happened to me today,
I'm not going to teach you painting.
You looked for your boyfriend,
didn't you?
I've told you many times.
He's not my boyfriend.
I don't believe you.
It's up to you.
Let's go. Pack your stuff.
Ms. He, someone is looking
for you outside.
Okay, thank you.
It must be your boyfriend.
It could be.
See?
I was right.
Are you here to pick up Quanquan?
Buy us dinner.
The man in the supermarket!
He Ran, it's your boyfriend!
Quan.
Quanquan.
You can't talk like that.
My student in the studio
has just sent me a WeChat message
saying that she left her keys there.
I need to go back and get it for her.
We're not eating dinner
together tonight.
Well,
I'm a member
of this cafe.
Bring Quanquan there for coffee
and accumulate some points for me
to redeem a children's gift.
See you at the studio tomorrow.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Why are you here in Xiaozhou Village?
It's because of my uncle.
I wonder why he's behaving
strangely lately.
He stays in his garden
for his plants.
My aunt asked me to come
and manage the restaurant.
Actually, it's nothing.
Don't hang out here. Go home early then.
No, wait.
What do you by "hang out"?
Forget about me. Let's talk about you.
Why do you come to
Xiaozhou Village every day?
Didn't the caretaker
monitor you closely?
Speaking of
your caretaker,
she...
She's abnormal. Let me advise you.
Why is she abnormal?
Her
behaviour
is out of the boundary.
Did you find out anything?
Let me tell you.
Let's stay out
of her business.
I'm serious.
When I was looking for you
at your place in the afternoon,
she didn't allow me to go in
and she also
praised me.
She said that I'm skinny and excellent.
She even said that I have a good temper
and I'm helpful.
She said I've done her a huge favour.
It's disgusting.
No.
Isn't that the little girl
in the supermarket?
She came here with you?
No, she came...
She came here with her relative.
Stop looking.
That's your friend?
Yes.
The guy next to him?
That's your friend?
Yes, he's my friend.
You really have a wide range of friends,
even friends of this age.
It's none of your business.
Well, it's none of my business.
But,
what's wrong with you?
Your mother
allows you to come out alone?
I...
I came here with my mother today.
She is here?
Where is she?
She's doing something
and she'll pick me up later.
I see.
Then...
Have fun. I'm leaving.
What fun am I having?
I...
Let me help you.
(Fine Art Academy)
Okay, start painting.
Are you not going to teach me?
I can't help it.
You didn't keep your word.
You didn't keep your word either.
That's the result
after you've betrayed someone.
Okay, ten minutes.
It's about time.
(Dongfeng Studio)
Where's the girl sitting there just now?
I didn't notice. What's wrong?
It's okay. Carry on with the painting.
Carry on with the painting.
I'm sorry.
(Next episode)
Ranran, trust me, okay?
You're stabbing my heart
with a knife.
Stop abandoning me.
What are you hiding from me?
♪don't walk away♪
What are you still hiding from me?
I'll only tell my secret
to my boyfriend.
Are you
thinking of...
♪You lead me on♪
What am I thinking?
♪I'm falling down♪
♪I'm falling into you♪
♪Night and day♪
♪You're in my head♪
♪I need you now♪
♪Don't you say goodbye♪
♪You're the one that's♪
♪Always on my mind♪
♪Oh Can't you see♪
♪I'm on my knees♪
♪Just take my heart♪
♪Set me free♪
♪I'm looking out for you♪
♪Are you just a fantasy♪
♪Or a reality♪
♪Set me free♪
♪I'm looking out for you♪
♪You're the one I need♪
♪Remember now♪
♪To save me♪
♪Don't you fade in my dream♪
♪don't walk away♪
♪Come, come away with me♪
♪Take me back to your side♪
♪Come and hold me tonight♪
♪You lead me on♪
♪In my dream♪
♪Tik tok♪
♪You're on the clock♪
♪Like on the cloud♪
♪Tik tok♪
♪We're running out of time♪
♪Tik Tok♪
♪Please stay with me♪
♪Tik tok♪
♪Don't be away from me♪
♪Tik Tok♪
♪Your'e all I need♪
♪I need you here♪
♪Right now♪