♪Green grasses grow; willows sway♪
♪Ripples spread before my eyes♪
♪I want to ask if you know my heart♪
=Coming For You=
=Episode 5=
(Mansion of Prince Su)
You have to teach me
how to act like you usually do.
In this body of mine,
you can freely do what you want.
I'll handle
everything for you.
(After years on the battlefield,)
(I'm used to facing everything alone.)
(It's the first time
someone's cared about me.)
(This must be what Mother meant)
(by being cared for.)
I didn't expect you
to be taken down by a bowl of ice jelly.
Feeling better?
I had them make you some soup.
Drink it now.
I can do it myself.
It's very hot; let me feed you.
You'd spill it.
It's okay.
Being able to drink it
means you'll recover quickly.
You must take good care of my body.
I want to change back soon.
Are you worried about me
because you're afraid I'll die
and delay your return?
Not entirely.
You don't want to remain a woman, right?
You should also take good care
of my body.
Speaking of which,
I remembered it.
When it happened,
it was thunder-storming.
Next time we try,
should we check the weather?
I've told you so many times.
Don't act like a girl using my body.
Who wants your body?
If I could switch back, I wouldn't wait.
Who asked you to go
to the forbidden area?
(Should I tell him why
I'm after the painting?)
(He may know where the painting is.)
(No.)
(Will he think I'm crazy?)
I...
I think I'm the master of this mansion.
Well.
The fake master.
I should understand the taboos
and the reasons behind them, right?
Your Highness,
the emperor needs you.
You rest easy; I'll be back soon.
I have many enemies.
There are often dangers.
Let Luoyun protect you by your side
to take care of you.
Okay.
You flirted with a lady,
offending the prince of Great Zhou.
Truly our God of War.
Your power remains
out of the battlefield.
Where did you hear such rumors,
Your Highness?
I live a clean life.
How could I flirt?
It's useless to tell me that.
They've got dirt on you.
If that prince insists on pursuing this,
how will the two countries resolve it?
Great Zhou is testing our bottom line.
I just cut off his delusions to avoid
future troubles.
I hope it really goes as you said.
I shall wait and see.
Your Majesty, listen.
What the prince said about his concubine
is a misunderstanding.
I ran into a woman on the street.
She was covered in wounds
and looked terrified.
I heard she was beaten by her husband.
Out of love for the people,
I cared about it.
I did nothing improper.
Nothing improper?
Who can know for sure?
It is my personal matter
to discipline my concubines.
Why did you need to intervene?
You can't say that.
Ignorance is no crime.
I didn't know that this lady
was your concubine.
What's wrong
with helping her?
Prince Su admitted to encouraging
my concubine to run away.
He's openly humiliating me.
Please don't be angry.
There's a misunderstanding.
Please let Prince Su explain.
Explain? What is there to explain?
He was wrong and hit a lady.
You must that brutal husband
who hits her
at every little thing, right?
Hey.
How could her fragile figure
withstand your strength?
Beating women, are you still a man?
How unreasonable.
You did something wrong first,
yet now you're humiliating me.
Your Majesty,
is this how you treat guests
in Great Yan?
If so,
there's no need to sign
the alliance treaty.
Now, you're giving me a tough problem.
How ridiculous.
I just thought that girl was pitiful
and helped her a bit.
How did I get myself into trouble?
Truly speechless.
I didn't think it through.
I'm willing to bear the consequences.
Is that so?
What do you intend to do?
Lead troops to storm their gates?
That's not possible.
Why is that not possible?
(Nonsense.)
(If I were to fight,)
(I'll be dead before the war starts.)
The war wastes soldiers and resources.
If we can resolve it without bloodshed,
that would be perfect.
That's precisely what I'm worried about.
But how can we do that?
It's very difficult.
I have some connections with Zhou.
If Qianyu is willing,
we can go to persuade the prince to sign
the alliance treaty.
So, what we want is
for the prince to sign
the alliance treaty?
Of course.
To get the client to sign the contract?
I'm familiar with this.
No need to trouble you.
I will certainly fulfill the mission.
♪Gazing at distant mountains far away♪
♪Waiting for the peach blossoms
to bloom on the branches♪
♪With petals falling on the balcony,
you step into the morning glow♪
♪Painting a scroll
of splendid mountains and seas♪
♪In the depths of the clouds,
leaving space for you♪
♪Wandering together,
no need to wait any longer♪
♪Green grasses grow; willows sway♪
♪Ripples spread before my eyes♪
♪I want to ask if you know my heart♪
♪The spring breeze
stirs my thoughts in the painting♪
♪The summer rain
sends my letters in dreams♪
♪Whether the ink is dark or light♪
♪The sea and the fields change;
I wish to see you again♪
♪The autumn moon hides deep in poems,
holding affection♪
♪The winter snow sighs
for the passing years♪
♪I only wish
to watch the world with you♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)