♪Green grasses grow; willows sway♪
♪Ripples spread before my eyes♪
♪I want to ask if you know my heart♪
=Coming For You=
=Episode 18=
Qi Xuan, you finally came out.
Have they made it hard for you?
With me around,
who would dare to do that?
I hope it's as you said.
If I can't protect her,
then no one in the world can.
Oh, enough.
The cause of the poisoning is unknown.
If you two really have energy to spare,
go help me investigate leads
and throw back the blame
others have given me.
- Fine.
The ingredients are clear.
I personally made this icing.
It shouldn't have any issues.
But the silver needle did change color.
What could be the reason?
Have you ever thought
that what changed the color
wasn't the ingredients?
Maybe someone poisoned it in the palace.
But Su Qianyu didn't...
I'm fine.
But the empress dowager did faint.
Who is so intent on framing me,
poisoning here?
Today, the Crown Prince
and Ms. Yue were targeting you two.
It's not the person but the treasure
you possess that brings you trouble.
(Full of Fortune)
Su Qianyu!
I'll go chase.
Are you okay?
Someone come!
Luoyun!
Nai!
Hurry, someone!
Someone come!
Su Qianyu!
(Did the man in black
deliberately lead me here?)
(The Crown Prince is the main suspect,)
(but this doesn't seem like his style.)
(Unless the one
giving the orders isn't him.)
How cautious of you,
using the empress dowager
to divert their attention.
They think it's a frame-up,
but they don't know
my target
has always been Su Qianyu.
After this,
Su Qianyu will likely be
in great danger.
Since we are to act,
we must plan meticulously.
Su Qianyu was poisoned,
but I can only rest easy
once I see the poison act up.
What if anything goes wrong?
That'd be a pity.
Mother!
Empress Dowager!
I understand Su Qianyu.
Once Qi Xuan was accused
of poisoning the cake,
he would certainly prove her innocence
by eating the poisoned cake.
Qi Xuan is indeed his Achilles' heel.
He inhaled the drug added
to the incense burner that day,
so, the man in black
was sent to provoke him.
The poison surely has acted up.
They should never have suspected
that the empress dowager's slumber
was a diversion.
The one we truly want to poison
is him.
Prince Su called you "Sister"
for over a decade.
You really are heartless.
My life has long
been returned to his family.
I'll make sure to avenge my family
for the wrongs done sooner or later.
That's not enough.
I will seize
whatever they want.
The emperor has ordered.
Princess Su poisoned
the empress dowager and Prince Su.
She is to be arrested immediately.
I never expected
to see you here.
Princess.
How can you help the Crown Prince?
Su Qianyu always regards you
as a true sister.
Regards me as a true sister?
I was once my parents' cherished jewel.
I had parents and a younger brother.
If it weren't for the late prince,
how could I end up relying on others?
The late prince ruined my family
and adopted me out of guilt.
Should I be grateful for this?
You hate the late prince?
Does Su Qianyu know about this?
What if he knows?
What if he doesn't?
In any case, my family's lives
need to be repaid in blood.
Regardless of whether
there's any truth to it,
he was just a child back then.
Why does it concern him or me?
Why does it concern him?
If my family hadn't taken the blame,
would his family have the glory today?
Everything he enjoys
was built on the lives
of hundreds of my family.
Am I wrong to seek revenge against him?
This is your goal.
You used me to drag Su Qianyu down
to kill him.
At least I'm more merciful than you,
allowing you to die knowing the truth.
Is this the result you want?
I just wanted you to suffer
from losing everything in an instant.
The painting you want will be ruined.
That's just a start.
Is this the result you want?
The result I want?
Even if you lose everything,
what I want
won't come back.
(What does she mean by that?)
(She's ruined that painting?)
(It's impossible.)
(The painting must still be there.)
(I will definitely go back.)
Tell me. Who sent you?
Take her away.
Yes.
Su Qianyu!
Someone wants to kill me.
Yue Yunwan said
she wanted me to lose everything.
It's okay now.
I won't let anything happen to you.
She wants my life.
Su Qianyu.
I...
I want to leave. Take me home.
I've dragged you down.
- I'm sorry.
- I want to leave here.
Take me away from here.
Soon.
I'll take you away soon.
♪Gazing at distant mountains far away♪
♪Waiting for the peach blossoms
to bloom on the branches♪
♪With petals falling on the balcony,
you step into the morning glow♪
♪Painting a scroll
of splendid mountains and seas♪
♪In the depths of the clouds,
leaving space for you♪
♪Wandering together,
no need to wait any longer♪
♪Green grasses grow; willows sway♪
♪Ripples spread before my eyes♪
♪I want to ask if you know my heart♪
♪The spring breeze
stirs my thoughts in the painting♪
♪The summer rain
sends my letters in dreams♪
♪Whether the ink is dark or light♪
♪The sea and the fields change;
I wish to see you again♪
♪The autumn moon hides deep in poems,
holding affection♪
♪The winter snow sighs
for the passing years♪
♪I only wish
to watch the world with you♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)