Xiao Qiao.
(Shouldn't Su Xiaoqiao walk like this?)
Xiao Gao, stop lingering in the outhouse.
Xiao Qiao has entered the Armory.
=Swap Face=
=Episode 10=
(Armory)
(Su Xiaoqiao is skilled with various weapons)
(I must imitate her closely)
(To deceive those at the Yamen)
Xiao Qiao,
your wound hasn't healed yet,
but you're rushing to the Armory.
Sir,
Xiao Qiao's wound is fine now.
I have nothing to do today,
so I came to the Armory.
You're usually so untidy,
but today,
you cleaned the Armory so well.
I'm usually a bit messy,
but today's dust was overwhelming.
So, I came to tidy up.
Xiao Qiao,
on the wedding day,
what exactly happened?
Where have you been these days?
That day,
I was knocked out,
and woke up in a dark room.
Managed to escape with difficulty.
The people who imprisoned you,
were they from Clear Breeze Fort?
Xiao Qiao isn't sure.
They were masked that day.
Couldn't tell
if they were from Clear Breeze Fort.
But I can confirm one thing,
they're the same group
that attacked me yesterday.
Fortunately, Sir arrived in time,
and saved Xiao Qiao's life.
(What's happening to me)
(Why does Xiao Qiao)
(feel so unfamiliar)
It's getting late today,
better rest early.
Why is she so distant?
Could it be,
she's sensed something?
Here I come.
Just in time.
If we're late,
the grilled chicken will be gone.
Xiao Qiao,
why aren't you eating the grilled chicken?
The grilled chicken is too greasy.
Getting injured makes you eat so cautiously.
The doctor advised me to eat lightly.
Plus, my injury hasn't fully healed.
So I naturally eat a bit slower.
You know, since Xiao Qiao returned
these two days,
the Armory hasn't exploded even once.
Isn't that something?
My constipation is cured.
Xiao Qiao,
are you not making gunpowder?
My injuries aren't fully healed,
I can't handle the smell right now.
(Why does Xiao Qiao seem different?)
(Like a completely different person.)
Miss,
I swear I didn't break the vase.
If not you, then who else?
No one entered after you did.
But Miss,
it truly wasn't me.
Stop talking.
I don't need clumsy people like you.
Leave at once.
Miss,
I've been with you for years.
You're dismissing me over a vase?
For the sake of our time together,
keep this silver for yourself.
Hurry up and leave.
Go quickly!
Gu Qingdai,
I knew you would come for me.
How does it feel to be Village Chief?
I've searched the entire village.
Even Du Chong's room,
was turned upside down.
I couldn't find the Brocade Box.
Are you lying to me?
Really?
You blew up Du Chong's room.
Why didn't you use more gunpowder?
You might as well have blown him up too.
That's enough.
Where is the Brocade Box?
I also want to know where it is.
You're playing me.
I want to know its secrets even more.
So many have died for it.
The secret of the brocade box,
is only in Qingfeng Village.
Can you find it?
It depends on your own skills.
I'll trust you one last time.
(In the dead of night)
(Why is she in Xiao Qiao's room?)
Lord Chu,
what are you doing?
I wanted to ask you,
where did this wooden fire lance come from?
Did you pick it up again?
I stole it.
I just returned from the Justice Pavilion,
it looked intriguing,
so I took it.
What were you doing at the Justice Pavilion?
Tell me honestly.
To be honest,
where I go is my choice.
It's none of your business.
I'm your husband, I do care.
We're only so in name.
By the way, I inform you.
From today onward,
we have no relation.
What do you mean?
I mean,
I've decided to leave you.
Divorce you.
Now I've secured the Chief of the Fort.
Keeping you serves no purpose for me.
Such a simple truth.
Surely, Sir, you understand it.
I see.
Very well.
We were always using each other.
Indeed.
So from now on,
don't come back again.
There's nothing between us anymore.