Hey, what's wrong?
I think I twisted my ankle.
Come on, let me help you up.
Be careful.
Try moving it like this.
It really feels better.
This is for you.
What is this?
A wooden fire lance.
Keep it with you from now on.
This way, you can protect yourself.
=Swap Face=
=Episode 11=
The three-day deadline is up.
I agree to marry you.
I can also give you the Chief of the Fort.
But I have a condition.
We will only be husband and wife in name.
At any time,
there must be no overstepping boundaries.
I'm afraid
this is inappropriate.
All you ever wanted was Chief of the Fort.
As for me,
this is my boundary.
The Chief of the Fort,
if I desire it, I can achieve it.
Don't you understand yet?
In my heart,
this is the fourth time
you've aimed a Firearm at me.
No woman has ever dared to defy me like this.
Don't push me.
You must promise me.
Or we'll both go down together.
If it comes to a fight,
I might not lose to you.
Fine, I promise you.
(Enjoy your moment of triumph).
(Once I find the Brocade Box
and return to the Yamen),
(I'll ensure you face justice).
Sir,
I just stoked the fire.
Oh.
Sir, you're making medicine yourself?
In the entire Justice Pavilion,
only Xiao Qiao receives such care.
Even heroes fall for beauty's charm.
Nonsense!
She was injured on duty,
I must take good care of her.
You like her but won't admit it.
I told you before to make a move early.
But you insisted on being cold.
Now you're ignoring her.
Why are you talking so much today?
Wait a minute.
When Xiao Qiao first
joined the Justice Pavilion,
Sir, you've always taken extra care of her.
(One year ago)
Sir, I'm the new arrival.
My name is Su Xiaoqiao.
My connection with her is deep.
Naturally, I treat her well.
Hmm...
Forgetting friends for beauty.
Don't just stand there, get a bowl.
How long has Xiao Qiao been here?
About a year or so.
A Junior Constable not yet official,
what enemies could she have?
They sent assassins to kill her.
There's more to this than meets the eye.
Could it be a Blood Feud?
It's not impossible.
Alright, go quickly.
Find out more about her background.
Understood, Sir.
Blood Feud.
(Justice Pavilion)
Hey, how many times must I say this?
No unauthorized entry allowed.
I'm here to deliver clothes to Master Chu.
I'll leave right after.
Even a tailor can't enter.
You.
Just hand the clothes to me.
(I'll remember this for now.)
(Wait till I return.)
(See how I deal with you.)
Chu Yan.
Chu Yan, come out!
Oh, sister-in-law is here!
So bitter!
Ah.
It's so bitter.
Sir, she is...
She's the one I mentioned earlier.
The Eldest Miss of the Gu Family.
Ah.
So, this is Miss Gu.
It seems I came at a bad time.
I'll take my leave now.
Hey, Miss Gu,
it's getting late.
Why don't you stay for a simple meal?
Xiao Qiao never cared about dressing up before,
but lately, she's dressing more femininely.
She's no less charming than Miss Gu.
Has Sir shifted his affections so easily?
Su Xiaoqiao.
Have a chicken leg.
Miss Gu is our guest, you eat.
It's alright.
I heard Miss Su loves chicken.
Come on, you eat.
No, you have it.
- You eat.
- No, you eat.
- Please, you eat.
- You first.
Alright.
Everyone gets some.
Let's eat together.
Make way.
What would you two singles know?
Tch.
Sir calls this
sharing affection.
Balancing two interests elegantly.
One day,
you might slip.
Flirting even while eating.
How vulgar
runs fast.
Check who the lord prefers.
(Sùzhèng Pavilion)
(This Gu Qingdai flirts with the lord)
(Can't delay anymore)
(We must find the brocade box quickly)
(I know you deliberately sent me away)
(It was for my safety)
The leader has forgotten
I've taken lives right in front of you.
I'm giving you three days.
Surrender the Chief of the Fort.
Become my Village Mistress.
Otherwise,
both she and Chu Yan will die.
Don't worry,
I won't let you face this alone.
It's so late,
what does the Alliance Leader want?
The Village Chief has finally returned.
The Justice Pavilion's dinner must be tastier.
Alliance Leader, just say what you mean.
Last time, you mentioned stealing some
gunpowder from the Justice Pavilion.
I see that Chief Gu has some skills.
So, I want to ask you a favor.
Help me rescue someone
from the Justice Pavilion's prison.
Alliance Leader, you must be joking.
I'm only good at petty theft.
I can't handle such a major task
as a prison break.
You should find someone else
as the leader.
Yes, I think the Second-in-command
would be a good choice.
Miss Xiaoqiao, there's no need
to refuse in haste.
What did you just call me?
How capable do you think you are?
Oh, I know your abilities very well.