Sorry.
They threaten me with my daughter.
I have to do this.
=Swap Face=
=Episode 19=
Xiaoqiao,
if the City Lord bends the law for
personal gain,
I will sue him.
Lord Chu,
don't lie to me.
Did you go to Qingfeng Village
to look for
the brocade box?
(Map of Qingfeng Village)
I saw the marks you made on the map.
The evidence that Lord Chu
told me last time
was probably just an excuse.
I'll take it as your consent.
Xiaoqiao, let's not
speculate on each other before
there is solid evidence.
The City Lord is your father,
so you dare not to doubt him.
Right?
Xiaoqiao,
Lord Jia is dead.
Your mom's revenge has been avenged.
Give me some time.
I will get to the bottom of this case.
I'll uphold…
Gang leader Gu.
I have something to ask you.
Thanks to you for saving me before.
Thank you.
I didn't mean to save you.
I'm here to ask
who the noble is who bribed Lord Jia?
Besides,
has the City Lord been protecting
Lord Jia?
It seems that Chu Yan still
hasn't told you the truth.
I don't know the details either.
But,
yesterday, Uncle Chen…
I don't know who that noble is.
But yesterday,
after I told Chu Yan about this,
he was very excited.
He should have guessed who
that person was.
It seems that he has a close
relationship with that noble.
Who could be the person that
Lord Chu
openly protects?
(Lord Chu is hiding something from me.)
Miss,
why are you so interested
in the Medicine Lady?
Uncle Chen may not know
that she is Su Xiaoqiao, the
daughter of the Medicine Lady.
She had swapped faces with
Miss Gu before.
The hatred of killing one's
mother is irreconcilable.
Miss Su,
you have to find him out.
Humph.
Why are you laughing?
Because you're stupid.
You will die
of revenge.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
If you want to achieve your goal,
you have to take risks.
You overestimate yourself.
He's more powerful than me.
Huh?
You want to die for me?
I'm serious.
I'm not joking.
Anyways,
thank you.
To be honest,
you have helped me twice.
Twice?
When was the last time?
Who?
Have a look.
No one.
It's a wildcat.
What do you want?
I want you to marry me to the
village in a grand manner.
Su Xiaoqiao.
Su Xiaoqiao,
here she is.
Great.
Get out of here.
Are you ready to die?
Hold on.
I know what you want.
You want to kill me,
and…
Come with me.
(Hua Pianpian, Mysterious Man,
Medicine Lady)
Who is this mysterious man?
How did you break in?
What are you here for?
What am I here for?
I'm here to see my wife.
You…
If you dare to act recklessly,
I will shoot you.
I should have thought of it.
Gu Qingdai can't use a gun.
You are not Gu Qingdai.
Are you drunk?
Cut the crap.
You
are not Gu Qingdai.
Who told you?
How did you know?
I didn't expect that you, a constable,
have become a bandit now.
Hua Pianpian, that crazy woman,
wants to attack Yunjiang City.
You're not her spy, are you?
What are you talking about?
(Contract Wuzhai Tribe Attacks Yunjiang City)
Do you think she
will take the bait?
Definitely.
She will be affected by the
mood of revenge.
With her assistance,
our plan has a better chance
of winning.
Attacking Yunjiang City is
no small matter.
Are you sure about it?
Yes, I have made up my mind
Yunjiang City needs a new owner.
Uncle Chen,
will you support me?
It is also my wish to avenge
your brother.
Give me the handkerchief.
If I give it to you,
will you kill me?
I can
kill you if I want.
I'm going to die anyway.
Let me know who you are.
There's no one else.
Let me see
who you are.
Okay.
I will fulfill your wish.
Chu Feng.
(City Lord?)
You killed so many people
for that brocade box.
What secrets are hidden in it?
What is your motive?
You
don't have to know.
Give me the handkerchief.
Do you think…
Do you think you can keep
hiding it forever?
(My mom's death was indeed
related to the City Lord.)
If you want to know who
killed your mother,
follow me tonight.
You want to use yourself as
bait to lure out the murderer.
No, it's too dangerous.
Why not?
If I die,
Lord Chu will be your man.
No worries.
I have my
own way to get out.
(If it weren't for Gu Qingdai,)
(I'm afraid I would still be in the dark.)
This is your last chance.
Give me the handkerchief.
You're right.
Now it doesn't matter to me
what is in that broken box.
(No.)
(Gu Qingdai,)
(Why are you so stupid?)