[Candle in the Tomb: The Lost Caverns]
[Episode 14]
As a cock crows and the candle
dimes out, stop robbing.
We're not welcome here.
Leave now.
Quick.
Open the coffin.
Fifth brother.
Hurry up and leave.
Hurry.
Li Chun Lai, go.
Be quick.
Hurry up and leave.
Old Jin.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Come here.
Brother.
Fatty.
Old Jin.
Go.
Old Hu.
Go up, Mr. Jin. Hurry up.
Old Hu, what is this?
This is mercury.
Cover your mouth and nose.
Okay.
Elder brother, up there.
Old Hu, what should we do?
Do you think I was God...
always having a solution?
Hurry.
Hurry. Go. Go.
It's my fault for being clumsy.
Old Jin, it's pointless to say that。
Didn't we say we should live and die together?
It's too late to live together,
but we're going to die together.
This is too fast.
Old Hu, look.
It's here too. Go.
Hurry. Go.
Go.
Go. Head in.
Come on.
Hurry.
Old Jin, hurry up.
Come on.
Go up the pillar.
Okay.
Oh, no.
What should we do?
We're doomed.
Old Jin.
Old Jin, are you okay?
Why are you acting like this?
What's wrong with him?
He might have inhaled
too much mercury and poisoned.
He's hallucinating.
Old Jin.
Old Jin, wake up. Old Jin.
-Old Jin.
Stop singing, Old Jin.
Old Hu.
I think I can't make it.
Shirley Yang...
Hold on.
Li Chun Feng was appointed
as imperial historian.
Old Hu,
this pen can be taken down.
I see.
Old Hu.
What did you discover?
Mechanism.
The mechanism is the armillary sphere outside.
Crap.
We need to go out now.
Shirley Yang, are you okay?
The chives taste weird.
Brother.
Hu Ba Yi, come out quickly.
Hurry up.
Fatty, jump with Old Jin.
Got it.
Old Jin. Jump.
Shirley Yang...
Hurry, jump.
-Do it quick.
-Quick.
Hurry, pull hard.
Hurry.
Old Jin. Get up. Get up.
Old Jin. Get up.
Hurry.
Be careful.
Tui Bei Drawing is just a cover-up.
Li Chun Feng understood human's weakness.
He placed the mechanism...
in the most obvious place.
Hang in there, Old Jin.
Be good.
Hurry.
Old Hu.
There are words here.
This is the sexagenary cycle.
It should be a cryptosystem.
The password should be...
It should be a year.
The 7th year of Zhenguan.
At that year,
Li Chun Feng invented a new armillary sphere.
No.
It should be the 22nd year of Zhenguan.
During the 22nd year of Zhenguan,
Li Chun Feng was appointed
as imperial historian.
He was in his prime that year.
What's the sexagenary year of
the 22nd year of Zhenguan?
Sexagenary year? What year is it?
No, I don't know...
What year am I...?
No, what year is it now?
How would I know?
This is so hard.
Where is Old Jin?
Old Jin.
Mr. Hu.
Are you dead too?
Tell me,
The 22nd year of Zhenguan,
what's its sexagenary year?
Why am I being tested in hell?
If you won't answer,
we would die soon.
Old Jin.
Old Jin, wake up.
The first year of Zhenguan
that Li Shi Min ascended the throne
is 626 A.D.
The 22nd year of Zhenguan should be...
648 A.D.
One cycle is 60 years.
Add 1320 years from the nearest.
It should be the year 1968.
My mother was 60 years old in 1969.
That year should be Earth-Rooster year.
So the year 1968 would be...
Earth Monkey.
Look for Earth-Monkey year.
Look for...
Earth-Monkey year.
Old Hu, it's here.
Be careful.
[Earth]
This.
[Monkey]
Why is the floor moving?
Dizzy. I feel dizzy.
What is this thing?
Brother.
We're done for.
This time, we're done for.
Old Hu, why is it spinning?
The door isn't open.
Were we wrong?
I must have missed something.
The New Tang History mentioned that...
Li Chun Feng's armillary sphere...
has three spherical layers and a base.
Why does it have only two orbits?
It's not here.
Here.
Be careful.
Brother.
It isn't spinning.
I see.
We did it.
We're safe.
Old Jin.
Let's go.
What is this?
The 28 mansions.
The 28 mansions?
What does it mean?
We have to...
find the correct answer...
among 28 mansions.
Choose one out of 28?
How to choose one out of 28?
How can we do that?
If we don't choose, we'll all die.
I would be wrong
even if there were only two choices,
not to mention choosing one out of 28.
How should we choose?
That's right.
It's too hard.
Stop it.
Let him think.
Dipper,
the head of Xuanwu...
is formed by six stars.
It looks like...
It looks like the Big Dipper.
It is also known as Sagittarius.
Is this what Taoism means...
Sagittarius is destined to live,
Big Dipper is destined to die?
Li Chun Feng was also a Taoist.
Old Hu,
go ahead.
I will follow you whether to live or die.
Die? I don't want to die.
Old Hu, look.
Go.
The door is open.
-Hurry up.
-Go.
Fatty.
I finally come to myself now.
Me too.
Let me tell you,
when the door closed,
I wanted to kill myself.
When the door opened,
I wanted to praise myself.
Why?
Without me,
Mr. Jin...
What is this place?
Why is it so dark here?
Yes.
Look at both sides.
Wait, let me see whether it's deep or not.
Don't.
You might not reach the bottom.
Come on. Walk in the middle.
Old Hu.
This is...?
Be alert.
There should a bottomless abyss on both sides.
Walk in the middle.
Moreover, there might also
be mechanisms in front.
What?
There are mechanisms?
How many mechanisms are here?
You can return and drink the mercury.
Be careful, everyone.
Walk in the middle.
It's fine.
Slowly.
Walk in the middle.
Old Hu,
why is it strange here?
The torchlight...
can only light up five or six steps ahead.
This may be an ancient...
light-absorbing coating.
We can't turn back.
We can only go on.
Stick with me.
Eldest brother,
the Mojin Xiaowei...
lives up to its reputation.
For our trip,
without Hu Ba Yi,
some of us might die here.
Yes...
Just now, the cave was spinning.
How did he stop that?
He's really capable.
That's right.
Mojin Xiaowei
does get something.
Their skills...
What's wrong?
Being too afraid to walk?
How about lighting up for you?
I didn't say anything.
Hurry, let's go.
The key to it is to learn a lot, right?
He has a wide range of knowledge.
I think...
How skillful a Mojin Xiaowei is.
There's a saying,
the mighty dragon is
no match for the native serpent.
But I think...
the dragon and serpent are one family.
They don't fight.
Shaanxi is vast...
with many treasures underground.
Let's have a long-term strategic partnership.
You're thinking too much.
We'll see after we get out of here alive.
Eldest brother,
I think we should leave here alive first.
Find the way.
Why did you stop?
How long have we walked?
My watch stopped.
For about...
half an hour.
This path is too long.
Look at this.
Old Hu,
what is this?
This should be...
a symbol to count used by the ancient people.
I saw this crescent symbol before,
so we may have come back here.
What?
You mean...
all of us...
were walking in a circle?
Is this another mechanism?
Shut up.
Stop talking nonsense.
Listen to Mr. Hu, the Mojin Xiaowei.
If I had a solution,
we would have left by now.
Mojin Xiaowei?
He's just like us,
being stuck here.
Eldest brother,
since we're in this situation,
we shouldn't force him.
Give him some time to think.
It's fine, Mr. Hu.
Think carefully.
It's fine.
He has said he didn't have a solution.
Normally you're full of ideas, right?
Say something.
I... Brother...
Second brother,
At the crucial moment,
you become silent.
Brother, if I throw a bomb,
it'll blast and light up.
We'll know everything then.
Shut up.
If you throw a bomb and blow everything up,
we'll have to die.
How many times have I told you?
Use your brain.
Use wisdom.
Let's not talk about wisdom.
Old Hu.
How do you know...
this is...
the symbol that you saw previously?
What if many symbols are the same here?
Fatty.
Either it is the one we saw
or they are the same,
we can't leave here now anyway.
Even if we can't leave,
we should find out the reason.
384.
If this symbol...
is the one I saw,
that means for the past half an hour,
we've walked...
384 steps.
Mr. Hu,
you're so scrupulous.
Enough, stop flattering him.
Forget about it.
Old Hu.
Let's walk one round again.
Let's see if it's the cycle you're talking about.
If there are 384 steps...
and we have 12 people.
Leave one person on every 35 steps.
The last two persons...
just need to walk past 34 steps...
to know if they would come back again.
What if this isn't a circle?
What if we lose each other?
Use a rope.
How long is our rope?
Around 100 metres.
That should be enough.
I will be the first one.
No.
What if you escape?
You'll be the first one then.
That won't do either.
What if you push me down?
What do you suggest then?
Together.
[Similar to "Italy" in Chinese]
Italy?
What do you mean?
We'll go together.
Fine.
Fatty,
light a candle.
Stay here.
Be the first one.
Sure.
I won't budge an inch.
Italy?
What is this place?
It's the same whether I open or close my eyes.
Old Hu.
You are...
No more talking.
Tell them to return.
♪ How to find the light
and escape from this plight ♪
♪ It's all endless cycle with
unanswered questions ♪
♪ Deities beneath Cang Mountain
long to listen to their sounds ♪
♪ Even if I set off ripples,
I will never know her heart ♪
♪ Thinking about it ♪
♪ But I've long been locked outside ♪
♪ Falling into the marsh,
but God isn't around ♪
♪ Let it be ♪
♪ How many of us are sick
but pretending to be good ♪
♪ Half of the earth is gone,
nothing's left but bones ♪
♪ The world is troubled ♪
♪ Let's go on an adventure ♪
♪ The wind is blowing in the mountain ♪
♪ The water is all around us ♪
♪ It's a carefree life
full of challenges ♪
♪ You're my sworn brothers ♪
♪ It's all fate ♪
♪ It's a raging world ♪
♪ Can I see things clearly
in the midst of hardship ♪
♪ Can I grasp morality
in the broad daylight ♪
♪ Can I stay true to myself
after all I've been through ♪
♪ Only by facing the scarred truth
can I know the only one ♪
♪ Endlessly falling into the abyss
gives me sleepless nights ♪
♪ Secretly wiping my tears at night ♪
♪ Dead end makes me brave ♪
♪ I'm no longer afraid of having
my back eroded by the reflection ♪
♪ The world is troubled ♪
♪ Let's go on an adventure ♪
♪ The wind is blowing in the mountain ♪
♪ The water is all around us ♪
♪ It's a carefree life
full of challenges ♪
♪ You're my sworn brothers ♪
♪ It's all fate ♪
♪ It's a raging world ♪
♪ Hiding myself without
waking up the sleeping dragon ♪
♪ I go anywhere I want,
for it's a boundless world ♪
♪ It's hard to tell who's being sincere,
I can only keep all this to myself ♪
♪ Every problem can be solved easily,
for it's an empty world ♪
♪ Can the footprints lead you to me ♪
♪ All the traces left behind
is consequences ♪
♪ A nameless fire in my eyes ♪
♪ It's hard to tell the truth
from the lie, who's becoming a crazy ♪
♪ The wind is blowing in the mountain ♪
♪ The water is all around us ♪
♪ It's a carefree life
full of challenges ♪
♪ You're my sworn brothers ♪
♪ It's all fate ♪
♪ It's a raging world ♪