[Candle in the Tomb: The Lost Caverns]
[Episode 3]
Go to the cabin now!
Okay!
Brother,
don't just stay there waiting for death!
Do something! We can't let the boat sink!
You need to save your son!
That's right!
Tell me,
do you have any useful tools here?
Yes!
They're in the cabin!
Fatty!
There are steel pipes behind!
Okay!
Please save us, God!
Fatty!
Install the pipes!
Okay!
Fatty,
I'm counting on you two to save me!
It's killing us!
Old Hu!
Fatty!
Help!
Mr. Hu, be careful!
I'm here!
Old Hu, come up now!
Give me the harpoon!
There you go!
Fatty, get me the another one!
Old Hu, are you alright?
Dad.
My son.
Don't be afraid.
It's over.
Why did you tie yourself up?
Of course, I did,
otherwise, I would have fallen into the sea.
Let me untie you.
I wouldn't come with you if I knew this earlier.
Old Hu!
Hu Ba Yi!
Why are you yelling at me?
Can't you let me...
take a nap?
You're scaring me.
I thought you're dead.
Nonsense.
Come on. Move aside.
It's so tight.
The God of Rive has shown himself.
That happened right after we reached here.
I wouldn't come with you if I knew this earlier.
I shouldn't have come here.
I've never experienced that before.
It's all because of that shoe of yours.
My...
My little baby.
Thank you, bosses!
Thank you so much.
How's your son?
My son, he's fine.
If it hadn't been for both of you,
my son and I would be dead by now.
I'll give you a free boat ride.
I won't accept your money.
I get it.
Go take care of your child.
Thank you, bosses!
The weather is unpredictable.
Old Hu,
I'm telling you,
When I was in the water,
I was feeling so scared.
I thought...
I'd die here.
I could have been killed...
by that gigantic fish.
Look at yourself.
You don't sound like
a courageous worker at all.
Shame on you.
No, I'm courageous.
If it hadn't been for me,
you would be dead by now.
Right?
Both of us...
joined hands to deal with that fish.
Don't you forget that.
I'm having a headache with dizziness.
I'm feeling so unwell.
Hey,
you've become heavier...
from being in the water.
I'm dizzy.
Mr. Jin!
I need your help here.
You Fatty.
I'm so tired.
We've crossed the Yellow River.
Gulan County is over there.
Shanxi is behind there.
I'm taking you all to the guest house...
for hot bath.
You can't fall sick. Let's go now.
Excuse me.
Careful.
We're here.
This is the best guest house in our county.
It provides anything you want.
Very convenient.
A room for three.
I'll pay you in one shot.
Old Hu,
it's unlucky.
that's a bad beginning.
Take a hot bath to get rid of our bad luck.
Old Hu,
you can't live without me.
I'm the one who help you all along.
Okay.
Both of you are masters.
Awesome!
Please rest well.
I'll bring the stuffs here tomorrow morning.
Sure.
Encore!
What an excellent singing!
Their singing is so bad.
I sing better than them.
For thousands of years, the rash curse
has been bothering my people.
My people were desperate...
and suffered a lot.
Like our ancestors, my people
were killed eventually.
There're not many people left.
Things are getting so bad.
I went to the Mount of Vase...
with my juniors Old White Man and Hua Ling.
I knew Dust Bead's at
the Black Water City of Western Xia.
But I felt sorry for my late juniors.
Uncle Chen,
what's the matter?
It's so itchy.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
Here.
It's so itchy.
What a shabby place.
I can't even take a hot bath.
Be grateful.
It's just a small county.
This isn't home.
That's right, Fatty.
Just clean our body with some hot water.
That's fine.
Yeah,
we're lucky enough to survive that boat ride.
You're right.
We never thought
Dragon King of Iron Head was there.
That's why...
we can't blame the locals
for being superstitious.
Anyone would...
worship a big fish like that.
That's a superstition.
No god would eat humans.
They should stop worshiping that stupid fish.
Fatty,
don't say so.
Mr. Hu's Tomb Calming Skill...
is based on...
the "feudal superstition".
Am I right?
Mr. Hu,
I've been meaning to ask you something.
In the...
history of China,
from Qin Shi Huang to Puyi, there're...
hundreds of emperors.
Feng shui talks a lot about dragon-like terrains.
How many pieces of dragon-like terrains...
did they use to bury these emperors?
Probably a battalion.
Here's the thing.
Actually,
dragon-like terrains do exist.
But there're many arguments.
In terms of feng shui, dragon terrain...
has two important elements,
shape and position.
Shape is about the topography of...
where the tomb is.
State is...
the conditions of that topography.
It's mentioned in Finding Dragons that...
dragons do exist,
but they don't show themselves.
A dragon gives birth to nine babies.
In terms of temperament, talent, and look,
they're not the same.
Same goes with dragon-like terrain.
And it's complicated than dragon
giving birth to babies.
In that case, it has scientific evidence.
Shape and state. I don't understand any of them.
But I know...
there are emperors who died young.
I don't buy...
the idea of dragon-like terrain.
You're right.
It's an unreliable concept.
The shape and state of
a dragon-like terrain...
make sense in the Taoist philosophy of world,
but not in our society.
Feng shui doesn't...
determine history.
An earthquake, flood...
or changes in a stream
may alter...
the original shape and state of a land.
An earthquake...
could turn...
an auspicious cave into an inauspicious one.
We humans can't do anything about it.
That's why...
it is superstitious...
to build tombs as ancients did.
But we can...
find out a tomb...
using the theory of shape and state.
And that's a scientific method.
Mr. Jin, you heard it right.
It's science.
I can't argue with you...
because I'm a layman after all.
Right?
But do you know?
Li Chun Feng is tomb is in this Gulan county.
You're nothing...
compared with him.
Mr. Jin.
Li Chun Feng is tomb is in this county?
Who's that?
Li Chun Feng was a feng shui master
during the early Tang era.
And he was from Gulan County.
His body was buried here.
Everyone knows about it.
The early Tang era?
That makes it a Tang tomb?
Yes.
Surely there are many valuables...
in his tomb, right?
Stop talking nonsense.
Clean yourself and go to bed.
Yeah.
I was just joking.
Fatty,
why is there a red mark...
on your shoulder?
Really?
Old Hu, take a look at it.
Wait a second.
You have one too.
Are they the same?
Yes.
I think...
we're bitten by that fish.
Nonsense.
It could have...
eaten you alive.
Okay, it's nothing.
Once we go back home,
I'll hire a master to scrub my body.
And it'll be gone instantly.
As clear as candlelight,
as accurate as turtle-shell divination.
Everything is complete.
Chen Tuan reincarnated...
as King Wen of Zhou.
Old man,
that's a confusing poem...
for your entrance.
Wait.
Why are you here?
You're scaring me.
I don't want you all to die here.
That's why...
I'm giving you a clue.
I'm blind.
But I know the principles of Taoism.
Since you all...
survive the disaster,
why don't you ask for my advice?
How did he know that?
I know right.
He probably heard what we said.
Old man,
aren't you a fortune teller?
Stop embarrassing yourself here.
It's late, you should go home now.
Guys,
what's buried in the earth
are good stuffs indeed.
But you must handle with care.
Western Paradise is where
the dead people want to go.
They just want to rest in peace...
without being disturbed by outsiders.
Among you all,
there are two persons with strong yin energy.
I'm afraid...
something bad is going to happen.
Wait.
Who are you talking about?
Both of you?
You're talking to him.
Feeling curious?
Just follow me.
Old man,
you have a nice stall.
what's your name?
I'm a fortune teller.
And I'm blind.
You can call me Blind Chen.
Why are you still here?
Why didn't they catch you
by then?
Tell us.
Why is something bad going to happen to us?
Tell us now,
otherwise I'll break...
your stall.
What are you talking about?
You're such a vulgar man.
You have no wisdom at all.
You're not worth my time.
But...
I'm willing to talk to this man.
Wait, what do you mean?
Does he look down on me?
He doesn't want to talk to you...
because you said you wanted to break his stall.
I didn't...
What are you doing?
Wait. What are you doing?
Let me touch it.
Touch what?
Your bone.
No, wait a second.
It's okay.
The inherited hexagram.
An exquisite face.
A bamboo tube full of secrets.
Things foretold using a few copper coins.
No, please don't...
Just touch one's bone.
And you'll know who he is.
What's the use of touching your bone?
Stop it.
So, what did you find out?
Old man,
can you stop hoaxing us?
Here's my advice.
One mustn't be superstitious.
The Party shall lead one to the right path.
Get it?
It's strange.
It's truly strange.
You look like...
the young version of me.
What do you mean?
Did you just take advantage of me?
No, I didn't.
That's a compliment.
Where a snakeman closes one's eyes...
is where a state ruler is.
It seems that you're a famous imperial official.
A state ruler?
In our society,
its equivalent is a state commander.
It can be a governor...
or military commander.
Old man,
do I look like a governor
or military commander?
We got you now.
You're such a bad liar.
You should have said that...
his son would be a state ruler.
That's a perfect lie.
Old man. Old man.
You keep calling me an old man.
People will laugh at you...
for disrespecting an elder like me.
Then, I'll call you...
Forget it.
Old man.
The hexagram and feng shui secrets
contained in Yi Jing.
They're all profound and diverse.
And they have their own functions.
You shouldn't use it to trick people for money.
That would be an insult to
the wisdom of our ancestors.
Am I right?
You're right.
The hexagram of Yi Jing
is profound indeed.
And there're many
unknowing secrets of feng shui.
Except for Mojin Xiaowei...
who know Finding Dragons,
nobody else knows how profound it is.
And how dare you laugh at me.
Old man,
you're right.
We're...
Old man,
you said something bad...
was going to happen to us.
Fine.
You'll fortune-tell me.
Let's see what it could be.
Yang for the word and yin for the back.
Good job, Mr. Hu.
He didn't get one of them.
It'd be better if he got it too.
Right?
The sky prevails.
It's a Possession hexagram.
Old man,
it's a fine hexagram.
You get it, old man?
It's a Possession hexagram,
not a disastrous one.
You seem to know...
a thing or two about hexagram.
But it's such a pity.
You don't know...
everything about it.
Then tell me.
What's this hexagram about?
Look carefully.
Where are all these copper coins facing?
Northeast.
He determined the direction by hearing?
And please check.
What time is it?
8:30 p.m.
Does all this have to do with time?
It's 8:30 p.m. That's it.
The date is Guihai and the time is Renxu
according to the Chinese calendar.
A death door is located
at the Northeast direction.
A burning sky with a death door...
I'm afraid...
you'll have to die from being arrogant.
Mr. Hu,
why is there a death door?
A death door?
Where is it?
Which is the death door?
Rest, life, harm, delusion,
scenery, death, fear, and open.
The death door is one of
the eight doors in Qimen Dunjia.
I was once told that...
a master fortune-teller...
would always determine
the position of eight doors.
I never thought this old man would know that.
That means...
he's a master?
In that case,
I'll save you all.
Here's a hexagram for you.
Have you heard of...
Gentle hexagram?
One for yin, two for yang,
three for yang, four for yin,
five for yang, six for yang.
And that's...
a Gentle hexagram.
Is he really blind?
Gentle is the wind.
It also means obedience.
But here's the problem.
Between the host and the guest,
who shall be the obedient one?
Old man,
I'm impressed by you.
it's late. Do rest well.
We're leaving now.
See you.
It's...
fate that we met.
No matter what, you told a fortune for us.
I was trying to find out if he's really blind.
That's none of your business.
A lonely boat by the beach.
There's a barge pole but no water.
So, nothing can be done.
The occasional rain and wind
make the river rise.
Now, one can move freely.