♬〜
(Yurie Sasano) I'm home...
Kota?
Ah...!
(Voice of Tsubaki Kizawa) A robber broke into a house in Kofu City, Yamanashi Prefecture around 10 o'clock last night.
Kota Sasano, 30, who lived in the house, was killed.
The person who discovered it was his mother, Yurie, 57 years old.
I had just returned from work.
A total of 1 million yen worth of cash and precious metals from the house was stolen.
Yamanashi Prefectural Police First Investigation Division→
On-site inspections and interviews have begun.
(Hiroshi Shiratori) Isn't this the job of the Yamanashi Prefectural Police?
yes! As expected of Shiratori-san!
However, it is. (Mio Amao), right?
(Suguro Hanji) Does that mean we're heading to the Yamanashi site...?
Yeah! That's right!
(Momoko Nakazawa) What are you so excited about? Don't waste your time!
Ah yes. (sound of keys hitting)
This is footage from a security camera near the scene.
A suspicious person was spotted walking around the victim's house.
Facial recognition is performed and checked against the National Police Agency's database.
The person's address is Hachioji City, Tokyo.
Chido Fukazawa 65 years old.
I retired from a securities company and am currently unemployed.
The Metropolitan Police Department began monitoring the movement.
(Norifumi Akase) So it's a wide-area crime, spanning Tokyo and Yamanashi.
I think the odds are high!
(Suguro) Well, the Metropolitan Police Department and the Yamanashi Prefectural Police... Look, at that time...
It was difficult. It was.
Last year, a joint investigation headquarters was set up to deal with the fraud case.
Ah, there it was.
A manager from the Metropolitan Police Department came onboard →
I don't think he was showing favoritism to Tokyo.
Huh? Did something like that happen!? (Suguro) Ah.
Yamanashi Prefectural Police made a fuss about boycotting work, and the investigation headquarters collapsed!
Since then, we've been like dogs and monkeys.
I see...
The Metropolitan Police Department and the Yamanashi Prefectural Police are on really bad terms!
What are you happy about?
No, because in that case, we should step in between...
It's our Mobile Investigation Division's turn!
Stop being so positive about work.
♬〜
(Teruhiko Nemoto) Don't run around!
Please don't run into me.
Are you still angry about what happened the other day?
This wide ocean will soothe you.
(sound of tapping) Wow!
Don't step into my memories!
Sorry. Don't know about Momoko-san's sadness.
I don't plan on speaking for another two years.
That's it... You're apologizing, aren't you?
I'll do anything for Momoko-san.
Would you really do anything? yes!
Then be my slave.
yes! ...Eh, slave?
When you stop at the next parking lot, buy me a canned coffee.
That's Pasiri... something?
No, because if you're a slave, you'll use words like attacking him or stepping on him with heels.
Are you really an idiot?
♬〜
(Yu Masuda) Ugh...! Ugh… Ah….
Mobile Investigation Division.
Wow! Eh, are you okay!? Hey...
Huh...? Um... your name... OK!?
It's Masuda-san!
(Nemoto) Don't let us into the scene. Just kidding.
(Nemoto) Yamanashi Prefectural Police used violence against the Metropolitan Police Department!
Arrested! Arrested!
(Keisuke Yamauchi) It's not violence. It's sports!
Japanese representative of Yuan Judo, Fujimi Torosuke!
That Fujimi Gosuke!?
Angry bull fu... Gosuke Fujimi!?
He beat me!
3 days of complete recovery!
If you criticize the Yamanashi Prefectural Police, you'll be in trouble.
Hey, Ichibanboshi.
I knew you would come, but are you already holding back?
What? Hey. That's what the first star is.
Quickly get out of Yamanashi!
(Investigator) Yes! Get out!
(Investigator) It's not your turn! (Investigator) Go home!
Who is the next opponent?
chef! It's a sold fight. Come on!
Huh? Is it me?
(Nemoto) Hey, you're always working out! (Swan) Muscle training...
Hey, you muscle guy.
Sigh... Wow!
Momoko-san is big. Yeah. Huh?
bud.
yes.
You said you'd be my slave, right?
Kick that guy away!
Huh!? Ah... Wow!
♬〜
Do you know why it's called "Ichibanboshi"?
We defeat evil in the world and solve cases →
The first star that shines in the sky like the morning star is us!
Uraa! Wait a minute!
♬〜
Oh, nice.
I'll leave it at that for today. (Mio) Yoshimoto new comedy!
Chief! What are you doing! Get your inro out quickly!
Oh, is it me?
This incident is a wide-area incident involving the Metropolitan Police Department and the Yamanashi Prefectural Police.
Therefore, our Mobile Investigation Division will be in charge of a joint investigation for 72 hours.
There may have been a lot of trouble in the past, but...
This time, let's all work together.
This is for the early arrest of the culprit.
From now on, this truck will become the joint investigation headquarters!
This is a drama about a moving investigation headquarters vehicle, commonly known as Ichibanboshi, that solves cases.
Please excuse me.
Thank you for your hard work. Wooss….
This is the room of my murdered son.
Ah~... Were you a shut-in?
Looks like it.
(Suguro) Your son lost his mother. What do you do for a living?
(Yurie) I haven't done anything...
(Suguro) Your son is 30 years old, right? (Yurie) I'm sorry...
No, no.
Is your family other than your son?
My husband passed away from an illness five years ago.
There are only two of us.
♬〜
(Bio) Chido Fukazawa.
I live in Hachioji, Tokyo.
(Mio) He is an important reference in this case.
Don't you know?
No, I don't know.
♬〜
Jaan!
The chef made it for me. Let's have it.
yes. I'll take it. (Mio) Wait!
(Mio) It says onigiri gacha.
Onigiri gacha? That means...
I don't know what's inside.
Another chef prank.
I can't tell from the outside...
Is this it? Oh, let's go.
Then this is it. (Mio) Then this.
I'll take it. I'll take it.
I'll take it.
Yes, everyone please report the victims.
(Suguro) I asked my neighbors, and it seems like they've been holed up at home for a long time.
She lives dependent on her mother.
He said he could sometimes hear yelling coming from the house.
It appears that there was also violence against the mother.
There were bruises on his neck.
Huh! Okay! meat~!
Me! Salmon! safe!
(Suguro) Okada. good!
What about the section chief?
Me too... Salmon.
♬〜
why….
Strawberries!
A bud? Huh….
Eat everything.
♬〜
What is your connection with Fukazawa, who is an important reference person?
(Suguro) He said he didn't know.
(Mio) Yeah. I didn't feel like I was lying.
I think it's just a sneaky robbery.
The straight line distance between Tokyo and Yamanashi is 100km.
I don't have any other clues...
Okay! Let's listen to this man named Fukazawa voluntarily.
Yeah. (All) Yes.
Is it delicious? ...There's no way!
♬〜
(Masuda) The first star is...! (Nemoto) It's here again!
I'm from the Mobile Investigation Division.
(Tomodo Fukazawa) Move... Investigation Division?
Yeah. Could you tell me your story?
(Masuda) We are listening. Please don't interrupt!
Ah, is your waist okay?
Sorry! That lady!
Please report it to the police. A suspicious truck has stopped.
a little bit…. Why!
Mobile Investigation Division. It's okay. Um... it's the police.
Ah... yes. yes. yes.
ah~. Get out of the way right away. Yes, sorry.
Please excuse me. (Mio) Excuse me.
Please excuse me.
What is the story?
Mr. Fukazawa, what about your family?
I live with my daughter.
How old is your daughter?
I will be 23 this year.
(Telephone)
please.
Ah, no, it's okay.
(Telephone)
Excuse me, but what about your wife?
Ah... My wife and I divorced five years ago.
Do you know someone called Mr. Sasano?
Sasano?
I live in Kofu City, Yamanashi Prefecture.
i don't know. What is that better?
My son was killed by a robber last night.
Is that something to do with me?
(ringtone) Ah...
it's okay.
(ringtone)
(Misei) Estimated time of crime A person who looks like you was seen in front of the victim's house...
Ah... it certainly looks like me, but it's not me.
Where and what were you doing around 10 o'clock last night?
I was at home.
Alone? (Fukazawa) Yes.
Haven't you been to Yamanashi?
I haven't been. There's no reason to go.
(Mio) What time did your daughter come back?
I haven't come back.
(Mio)...What do you mean?
I come back occasionally →
I don't usually know what I'm doing.
(Telephone)
ah~….
♬〜
something?
no….
Come to think of it, Kuro-san, your daughter was there, right?
ah.
Are you meeting?
Like Miku? Yeah.
I'm seeing you. I'll be back on the weekends.
I'm getting married soon.
Ah, that's right.
Every time I come home, I hear horror stories.
Huu~u~. (Suguro) Huh... hah.
♬〜
(Swan) It's done. (Mio) Yes.
Good...
Wow... it feels good.
Ah, wait a second... a little more here. A little more... a little more around here.
Is it this way? Over here!
Ah, this way? Oh so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so such…!
Tsubmin.
Tsubomi? Hehehe….
I'm so sorry.
Please give me my shoulder later.
It's hard like dry French bread.
I decline your request. (Mio) Huh? Why?
I'm not rubbing Momoko's shoulder.
I... I'm a slave...!
Huh?
I heard about the Fukazawa case...
Ah yes.
I'm a little concerned about saying it's Shiro...
(Suguro) What was it? How many phone calls have you received?
The window glass in the bedroom was broken, right? yes.
Or rather, I'm more concerned about something...
What is it?
I don't know why, but there are hiking goods at the entrance.
Why do you care? I wonder why?
Ah! Even at the entrance of the victim's house!
(bud voice) Huh? (Momoko's voice) Yes, that's true!
So, do you both have a hobby of hiking?
(Suguro)...Maybe. It's getting interesting.
That's a good combination.
Especially. It's not a combination.
Yeah?
I don't like loud noises.
You're a slave!
Hahahaha…. No, it's a good combination.
(Momoko/Tsubomi) Why!?
No... because I'm a detective.
Sigh…. Huh?
(Suguro) Huh? Oh la la la la….
Hehehehehe…. I'll enjoy having this.
(Reception sound) Ah!
I received clear footage from the security camera.
(sound of keys hitting)
Ah... (Swan) Yeah.
There are hiking tools at the entrance.
Is it your hobby?
If hiking is your hobby, you've probably been to Yamanashi Prefecture.
There are many mountains suitable for hiking and mountain climbing.
From here, you can get there in one hour by train.
Are you familiar with Kofu City, Yamanashi Prefecture, where the incident occurred?
Mr. Fukazawa.
Mr. Fukazawa!
♬〜
I did it….
(Fukazawa) I went hiking in Yamanashi and was walking through a residential area on the way back →
I found the back door unlocked.
(Fukazawa's voice) When I was looking for gold in the living room...
ᗕ(footsteps)
♬〜
(Stinging sound) (Kota Sasano) Ugh...! Wow...
Is the goal money?
I was in the red due to stock management...
(Telephone)
Do you really not know about that house?
i don't know.
Mr. Sasano also enjoys hiking.
I'm not lying. i don't know.
♬〜
Noise? yes.
I heard a strange sound in Fukazawa's voice.
That's what mecha guys always say, right?
People and machines are the same.
That person might be lying.
(Swan) Chief, how was it? admitted the crime.
Aren't you going to arrest me?
Yeah….
The Metropolitan Police Department and Yamanashi Prefectural Police say they want to investigate.
Don't just proceed with the investigation! Tell me the situation!
This guy looks like it will be celebrated on Respect for the Aged Day!
My bent back won't recover!
Hand over Fukazawa to us. Let me investigate.
Let them do it before the Metropolitan Police Department!
What do you do?
That he's lying.
yes.
perhaps.
(Suguro) Chief, take a look. ah.
(Mio) Hiking is a hobby of Fukazawa and the victim's mother, right?
This is where the Fukazawa family is now.
Mr. Sasano's house is here.
(Bio) Orange Mountain.
It is a low mountain that is a tourist attraction and suitable for hiking.
♬〜
Okay... let's listen.
(All) Yes!
Hey bud.
yes! Master.
Sunburn.
Sunburn? Because you'll get sunburned.
Huh? What should we do?
hat. Buy me a hat!
I got it! Hat... Yes.
I am grateful that you have agreed to accompany me voluntarily.
(Mobile phone ringtone)
(Yamauchi) Huh? Did the Mobile Investigation Division voluntarily accompany Fukazawa?
ah. Apparently he took her to a place called Mt. Orange in Yamanashi.
Orange mountain? What on earth are they thinking...?
(Mio) Do you know these two?
(Female) Have you ever seen it? Do you have it?
Why are they a pair?
♬〜
ᗕ(Motorcycle running sound)
(Kurumi) Phew!
(Souichiro Midorikawa) Hmm... Hohooi!
(Kurumi) It feels good!
♬〜
Mecha old man!
(Midorikawa) This one definitely catches my eye.
It was visible from two valleys away.
(Kurumi) What is it? Like the advertising truck running in Shibuya?
I made it. Power up the engine →
The inside was converted into an investigation headquarters. Shall we take a look?
Oh, sorry. We are currently listening to an important witness...
Is that impossible? yes.
Kurumi-chan Next time.
I mean, why are you here, mechanical guy?
Touring with Kurumi-chan.
Hey? hey~! Who is this person?
The owner of the car. policeman.
Ah... Thank you for your hard work! Thank you for your help.
We became acquainted through a certain incident when I was in the police force.
Mecha old man: He used to be a policeman...
He was a detective in the First Investigation Division.
Bang bang! I was firing a gun.
It's going well!
After that, I moved to the equipment department, but I had a close relationship with this guy.
chasing the same prey.
(Midorikawa) Kurumi-chan.
No matter how great the other person is or how much money they have →
There are things that people don't like.
As long as I'm alive, there are things I can't forgive.
I don't understand... I want an explanation!
So... if Kurumi-chan wanted to break up with me, wouldn't I hate it?
I say I won't drink anything like that.
As long as I'm alive, I don't want to break up with you. That's what I mean.
It's time for mecha!
You're young, aren't you?
Can I afford to die? I still have a promise with you.
Isn't that so?
Hey, let's go quickly, old mecha.
Ah... haha... Do you like hiking?
Well. It's a low mountain so I don't get tired so much →
I meet people and have lively conversations.
Is hiking like a matching app?
Oh... So the two of you went hiking?
Ah... I called out to him because he came alone.
Hahahaha…! Fufufufu….
Go quickly! The sun is setting.
See you, Chief.
take care. (Kurumi) Hehehehe...
(Kurumi) Let's go!
♬〜
Wow, that's a good place.
I feel like I've seen this place somewhere...
Huh?
Please excuse me.
I had a photo of this waterfall at my house in Fukasawa.
After all, Mr. Fukazawa has been here before.
(Momoko/Tsubomi) I'm sorry. I'm a police officer, but...
Although the two homes were far apart, there was only one incident.
Mr. Fukazawa.
You know the victim's mother, Ms. Sasano, right?
I found out through interviews.
I saw you two together at a waterfall in the middle of the course →
It has been seen by several hikers.
We must have met many times on this mountain.
Sorry...I was lying.
I know that woman.
What is your relationship?
What can I say... I don't really remember.
It's the young lady at home...→
He seems to be very loyal to his host.
(Suguro's voice) I was shown my daughter's room.
There was a host club information magazine and a catalog introducing hosts.
I see it often too.
Mr. Kuro?
(Suguro) Hahahaha…!
It's not that I'm obsessed with the host.
It's my daughter.
(Suguro) It's embarrassing, but my daughter is actually addicted to hosting.
My family is in trouble because of my daughter.
He lies to his friends that he and his daughter are doing well, but...
My daughter Miku is 24. Close to your daughter.
I left home a few years ago.
I broke the relationship of trust with my daughter at work...
Well, that's a good story.
Anyway, my daughter left and I still can't contact her.
But he's a detective.
(Suguro) I'm better at finding people than you.
My daughter was in the downtown area of ​​Shinjuku.
(Suguro's voice) Going to the club→
I got hooked on hosting and ended up losing a lot of money.
To make money…→
I also worked in the sex industry.
(Suguro's voice) I found him and tried to bring him back.
♬〜
Miku!!
(Suguro's voice) I don't want to get old.
Even now, I sometimes go to Shinjuku to look for it, but I can't find it.
He could have died.
(Suguro) After consulting with my boss →
He told me to make sure the sparks didn't fly here.
And here it is.
He was sent away from the criminal division.
I'm ready to quit.
As a police officer, I'm embarrassed.
No, before I was a police officer...→
He's a failure as a father.
I only have a daughter...I couldn't raise her properly.
Mr. Kuro...
The day I find my daughter is the day I quit being a detective.
You too, right?
…yes.
I have the same thing...
(Sound of window glass breaking)
ᗒ (noise)
(Fukazawa) Who is it!?
(Male) I apologize for not making an appointment.
At the request of Host Club Idesis, I came to collect the money lent to them on their behalf.
Where is my daughter?
What are you saying when I haven't even tried to find it myself?
Scum parents...
(Fukazawa's voice) My daughter also ended up going into host clubs and racking up debts...
From that day on, they appeared every day→
I want to return the money I lent...
So how many times have you called?
Every day from morning till night...
My daughter still borrows money and contributes to the host.
(Fukazawa) What should I do now?
I needed money.
I met a woman in the mountains →
I followed him and located the house.
(Fukazawa) I found out that the woman was away at night due to work →
I started stealing.
(Fukazawa's voice) I found out that the woman was away at night due to work →
(sound of door opening)
Please come here.
♬〜
Don't come here!
I asked.
I asked for my son.
…different.
It's true. I want you to kill my son...
No, that's not it.
Shall I make some coffee?
Mr. Fukazawa... That's enough.
but….
please.
When I make noise, my son gets angry and becomes violent.
Every day was like hell, I couldn't even breathe even at home.
Just on Sundays, I go hiking to escape...
So with Mr. Fukazawa... Isn't that so?
(Yurie's voice) This person also ran away from home to the mountains...
(camera shutter sound)
♬〜
(Fukazawa) Um...
Excuse me, are you alone?
(Fukazawa's voice) Everyone looks like they're having fun→
He was alone and looked gloomy...
That's it. We started talking every time we met...
(Fukazawa's voice) We both like Iruka's song ``Nagori Yuki''...
(Yurie's voice) Also, Kaze no Kaigandori.
(Fukazawa's voice) We hit it off.
So we meet every Sunday →
As we talked about each other's lives...
I know I'm in a similar situation...
What... did you do?
Yesterday, I was grabbed by my hair and dragged around.
``It's payday for your part-time job. Give me the money.''
I don't want to go home anymore.
But I have to go home and make some food...
(whimper)
♬〜
I'll... finish it.
(Fukazawa's voice) I will end my son's life→
The money he took will be used to pay off his daughter's debts.
Let's do that...
I refused, saying I didn't want my son to die.
But that night →
When my son asked me for money and I refused...
(Yurie's voice) I was strangled and lost consciousness...
(Yurie's voice) I...
My heart died at that moment.
I said please do that.
It was mutually agreed upon.
That's what we both wanted to do...
My family and this family →
There was no way to solve it.
♬〜
What money did you take?
to my account. Haven't used it for repayment yet.
Mr. Fukazawa is suspected of robbery and murder, and Mr. Sasano is suspected of concealing the perpetrator...→
I will arrest you.
♬〜
Please wait!
Don't the police just make arrests?
Is that why you work as a detective?
We...we, the police, could have done something earlier...
I wish I could help you sooner...
I was able to listen to the voices of people who were suffering and empathize with them.
Keep that feeling in your heart.
(sound of handcuffs)
♬〜
(Mio) Sleeping comfortably...
Probably because it freed me from suffering.
Regarding my daughter... could you please shut up?
If possible, I would like to work at Ichiboshi for a little longer.
Knowing that doesn't change your perspective.
Mr. Kuro is an excellent detective.
A must-have for the Mobile Investigation Division.
♬〜
Where are you taking me?
Let's watch the sunrise, Momoko-san. Huh...?
Look, the sky is getting brighter...
Huh?
Even though it's bright, I can't see the sun. why?
Well... →
This is the west, right?
yes.
When does the sun rise?
East... right?
Then there's no way you can see the sun!
Ah, I see.
Is that so? Wow... I did it again.
♬〜
Thank you for your hard work. Please excuse me in advance.
Yes, thank you for your hard work. (Mio) Thank you for your hard work.
Regarding Manager Akase, there has been no suspicious behavior so far...
We will continue to monitor.
(Sound of keyboard hitting)
♬〜