=The Fevengers=
=Episode 14=
(Why aren't you picking up?)
Mister,
take me to the location.
Okay.
Artistic Sofa Gallery on Haibin Road.
I can't...
I mustn't
be defeated just like this...
Open the door!
Jiayi!
The spare key is in the shoe cabinet.
Jiayi.
Hurry.
Let's get out of here.
Let me help you.
Lin Jiayi,
hang in there.
I mustn't let them know
I've escaped.
Them?
I didn't expect
Gu Yancheng's accomplices
to come to my house to kill me.
I'll take you to the hospital.
No.
It's too dangerous to go anywhere now.
I know a place we can go.
Who's it?
I need your help.
Come in first.
Quick.
Be careful.
Jiayi,
he's Shang Yu.
I trust him very much.
Please rest assured.
Now isn't the time for this.
What's going on now?
I can't explain it to you right now.
She's Lin Jiayi.
I need you
to shelter her for a while.
Okay.
I'll go get the first-aid kit.
Sorry,
I didn't know Gu Yancheng
could be so dreadful.
I'll report them to the police
and bring Gu Yancheng
and everyone who's harmed you
to justice.
They destroyed
all the evidence I collected.
If we don't have enough proof,
we'll only alert them.
Does it hurt?
No.
I've endured
worse pain.
You were right.
My marriage with Gu Yancheng
is nothing
but his scheme.
The pig head
I keep dreaming of these days
is actually him,
trying to worsen my condition.
You've discovered this.
You're not so hopeless.
What should I do?
I suspect
he's already transferred my assets.
He switched out
all my valuable jewelry pieces.
I know about that money.
He cashed out 30 million
from your jewelry
to silence me
and keep me
from investigating further.
No wonder he has that recording.
If you don't believe me, listen to this.
Do you really think I'd be satisfied
with merely 30 million?
What I want
is everything you have.
He even tampered with my phone.
He blocked your number.
Speaking of recordings,
I have a clip of a conversation
between him and his mother.
You need to hear it.
I want to know everything
about Gu Yancheng
as detailed as possible.
Here are two flight tickets
to Phuket Island, Thailand.
Once you arrive there,
find a way to make her ill.
Any accidents
that happen in that place
won't raise any suspicion.
Afterward,
come back here,
and tie up loose ends.
So you hit me with a car that day
to save me?
Don't worry.
I'll gather all the evidence.
How do you need me to help?
Act as usual
in front of Gu Yancheng.
I can't expose myself yet,
so I need someone who can move around
without raising his suspicion.
Uh...
Do you want the egg cooked
or a bit raw?
Stop listening in on us.
When the time is right,
I'll tell you everything.
All right, then.
Just let me know
if you need any help.
I do need your help now.
I need you to check
the status of all the assets
under my name
without letting Gu Yancheng find out
if possible.
Sure.
Leave it to me.
It won't take long.
All right.
I'll get out of your hair now.
You're still pregnant, you know.
It seems he
likes you.
Don't get us wrong.
Shang Yu and I
have been friends since we were kids.
We trust each other like family.
What's wrong?
Let's sit down.
Are you all right?
Feeling better?
Have you taken
any mental health medication lately?
Your symptoms seem a bit...
(Gu Yancheng)
Yes?
Dear,
how are things in the office?
Should I come pick you up?
No need.
I...
I'm about to head home.
All right.
Drive safely.
When you get back,
you need to be careful
with the food Gu Yancheng gives you.
Once you notice something's wrong,
contact me immediately.
(Although I need you)
(to collect evidence
of Gu Yancheng's crime,)
(I don't hope anything bad
happens to you.)
(Do you understand?)
(Don't worry.)
(I will not allow)
(the slightest fear or cowardice)
(overcome me.)
Mom?
What brings you here?
Ruoyun,
you're pregnant.
How can you stay up all night to work?
Dear,
Mom worries I can't look after you well,
so she came.
Thank you for your concern, Mom.
Oh dear.
We're family.
Don't thank me.
Well,
I'm a bit tired.
I'm going upstairs to rest.
You didn't eat
the supplements I brought regularly,
did you?
Look at your poor complexion.
Come on,
eat this
before you go to sleep.
Yancheng.
But I...
I...
I'm too tired from work.
I don't want to eat it.
If you don't take care of your health,
how will the baby
grow strong?
Dear,
just listen to Mom.
Eat the supplement
before going to sleep.
I'll feed you.
Here.
(You and your fake smile.)
(I was so blind)
(to think of you
as a good mother-in-law.)
When you get back,
you need to be careful
with the food Gu Yancheng gives you.
Once you notice something's wrong,
contact me immediately.
(Is something wrong)
(with this?)
Didn't I tell you not to call me
for now?
What's wrong with you?
Why did you give such a childish gift?
Anyway, as long as it's your gift,
I like it.
Yan Fei,
what are you talking about?
I'm saying,
Love you. Love you. I love you.
Love you forever.
Can you get rid of Wen Ruoyun
and marry me as soon as possible?
You're at it again.
Why are you eating
instant noodles again?
You never take good care of yourself.
You're nagging
like an old granny.
All right.
I'll eat less of it.
Yi,
don't worry.
I'll take good care of myself.
Yi,
I'll avenge you very soon.
(Why is there a red ink stain
on my finger?)
(I've totally lost my consciousness.)
(It has to be something)
(in the supplement.)
Ruoyun.
Mom.
What are you doing?
Well...
Do...
Don't you think
the trash bin
smells bad?
Maybe we should take the rubbish out.
Don't worry
about such trivial chores.
You're carrying a baby now.
Stop coming
into the kitchen from now on.
All right.
Thank you, Mom.
Luckily, here's the leftover.
Dear.
Dear,
I'm in the bathroom.
♪That crimson stain on the collar♪
♪That alluring scent♪
♪All excuses sound so pale and empty♪
♪What cruel sarcasm♪
♪Oh, women, they never learn♪
♪When your heart flutters,
it's bound to be broken eventually♪
♪Midnight, a piercing chill♪
♪Wakes you up from a shattered dream♪
♪Heavy mist shrouds the truth♪
♪A steadfast retaliation comes alive♪
♪Oh, men, those smarty-pants♪
♪The backfire of your overflowing charm♪
♪Has no mercy♪
♪May your life be barren♪
♪May you tread on a thorny path alone♪
♪May you vanish into thin air♪
♪Lies will adorn your tombstone♪
♪Release me from this hatred♪
♪Free me from this excruciating cage♪
♪Let me go to light♪
♪Let's never meet again♪
♪When I use your words♪
♪And your ways♪
♪You blame me for being cruel♪
♪Life is ironic♪
♪I want your end♪
♪To be lonely♪
♪With no one to hate♪
♪You will live in endless nightmares♪
♪Rise♪
♪From the ashes♪