=The Fevengers=
=Episode 20=
If you don't trust me,
let's stop contacting each other.
I don't want to be someone
who doubts me.
(I didn't want to lose him,)
(so I did what he said)
(and took out an online loan
for the investment.)
(But after I transferred him the money,)
(he disappeared.)
(I couldn't reach out to him.)
(He blocked me)
(on social media.)
Don't think you're safe
to hide inside silently.
Pay up now.
Believe it or not, I'll kill you.
Open the door!
You owe me two hundred thousand
and pretend nothing happened?
I know
who your sister is.
Believe it or not,
I'll sell you to Thailand.
Open the door!
Open up!
Now!
(I borrowed so much money,)
(and the debt collector
came to my house.)
(I'm sorry, Xin.)
(I'm too ashamed to carry on.)
So
the man who deceived your sister
was Gu Yancheng.
At first,
I didn't know who that guy was.
I tried many ways to investigate,
but all I could find
was his IP address in Southeast Asia.
Perhaps
my sister's soul was helping me.
I accidentally heard his voice
in a video
about what he said to my sister.
He's hot.
What does he do?
You shouldn't work so hard for money.
It should be
the other way around.
The investment market
is promising now.
I know you've worked very hard
for money,
that's why I suggested
you invest in crypto with me.
Yi,
don't worry.
I will get revenge for you.
I'm Wen Xin.
I'm here to apply
for the assistant position.
Wen Xin?
You may want to
look at this.
When you went to Taocheng,
I visited every woman
on this list.
I discovered
they all shared one thing in common.
They had bought sofas from Gu Yancheng.
It's Xiaoman.
(Shen Xiaoman is worth one million.)
Previously,
I found
Wen Jewelry Employee Information
in his office.
At first, I couldn't figure out
what it was for,
but when I visited Shen Xiaoman's family
and learned
of her death,
everything started falling into place.
It turns out
(Wen Ruoyun is worth three billion!)
that he's selecting potential piggies
to send to the overseas gang.
Overseas?
To think that what we experienced
isn't merely a marriage scam
but a well-planned and massive scam
from a professional
overseas organization.
To them,
we are piggies to the slaughter.
So Xiaoman
didn't just disappear.
It was all because of me.
I've indirectly caused their deaths.
It's all because I trusted Gu Yancheng
so easily
and married him,
giving him the chance
to leech off of me.
The girls at the company
and Xiaoman...
It's all my fault.
No, Ruoyun.
Gu Yancheng is the one to blame.
It has nothing to do with you.
Exactly.
Gu Yancheng and his gang
should take the blame.
They used our feelings for them
to fool us.
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
But I
realized one thing.
What is it?
There may be more girls
like Xiaoman
who might be falling victim
to romance scams.
I have to go back
to collect more evidence
of his crime
and bring them to justice.
No.
We and Gu Yancheng
have already discovered
each other's identities.
It's too dangerous if you go back now.
That's right, Ruoyun.
There must be other ways.
I must find a way
to go back to him.
If not...
If not, those girls...
They could've lived a good life.
But...
Jiayi,
Wen Xin.
Stop trying to convince me.
I've made up my mind.
All right.
I'll support you, then.
You must make sure
of your own safety.
Ruoyun,
I installed
an app
to listen in real time.
Test it now.
Gu Yancheng,
just you wait.
From now on,
both of us will take turns to monitor
and protect you.
If anything happens,
we'll be there immediately.
Contact me
once Shang Yu has returned.
All right.
He is dead.
Lin Jiayi and Wen Ruoyun
took my money.
My identity is exposed.
The entire plan is falling through.
This is the final one.
Don't run.
You're not Gu Yancheng's mother.
Now tell me.
Who are you?
I...
I'm just an actress
Gu Yancheng hired.
I didn't do
any of this.
I didn't know
he would do that.
What did he do?
Tell him.
Gu Yancheng!
You can't die just like this.
It's not fair if you die.
Dear,
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stop them
from hurting you.
I know
I've done so many wrong things.
Dear.
Dear,
even if you die now,
it won't help.
Dear,
I don't know...
I don't know what to do to protect you.
I can only use this way
to escape their control.
Stop saying.
I beg of you.
Stay alive.
Let me...
Let me help you up.
(Hold on.)
(The cut is shallow.）
(How could it possibly)
(cause so much bleeding in the tub?)
(Gu Yancheng,)
(it's your trick again.)
Dear,
will you forgive me?
Gu Yancheng,
what actually are you trying to hide?
We're married.
We should bear everything
together.
I'll tell you everything.
Dear,
thank you for not leaving me.
I've made up my mind.
For you
and our child,
I'll turn over a new leaf.
Here's my plan.
Once our child is born,
I'll turn myself in.
Ruoyun,
please give me one more chance.
One last chance.
I don't want to lose you either.
I'll do everything in my power
to help you through this hardship.
But you have to tell me
the whole truth.
At first, it was just a small loss.
Kevin,
could you lend me a bit more?
If I win,
I'll pay you back with interest.
Sure.
Three percent per month.
How much do you want?
I can lend you the money.
Never mind,
three percent is too high.
I should get going.
That won't do.
Kevin.
Since you've already asked for my help,
I must do you this favor.
I'm not taking your money.
Kevin.
Continue.
Later, I realized
the whole thing was a setup.
So,
as planned,
I lost all the money I borrowed.
I couldn't pay it back...
I couldn't pay it back,
so they locked me up
in the water dungeon and tortured me.
They even filmed a video
to blackmail my mom.
Stop beating me.
Beat him.
Please.
Stop beating me.
Stop.
Kevin.
I have money.
Bring money to get your son back.
He gambled and got himself
into a butt-load of debt.
You won't see him again
if you're late.
This piggy's family
has no more money.
Sell him to the park.
Yes.
Kevin.
I have money.
I... I will pay you the money.
Kevin.
Kevin, I beg of you.
Hu Chuntao.
19 years old?
You're young.
Can you use a computer?
Yes.
Take her to the telesales team.
Zhou Wen.
Introduce yourself.
My name is Zhou Wen.
I studied advertising design.
I'm 19 years old.
My hometown
is Taocheng County.
Good-looking.
Take him to the model team.
Model team?
Wang Qiang.
From now on,
you'll be in charge
of the characters in these manuals.
Memorize everything.
I don't want to do anything
immoral.
But Ruoyun,
I had no choice.
I was trapped there.
If I didn't do what they said,
they would torture me.
But what you did later
wasn't forced by them.
Yes.
I've done many wrong things,
but I had no choice.
I was trapped there.
They brainwashed me
every single day,
and I finally lost myself.
It's their task for me
to approach you and Lin Jiayi.
I had no choice.
I really had no choice.
I'm just a pawn,
a tool to make money for them.
I thought
to myself
that I would numb myself.
I stopped thinking.
I just did whatever they asked of me.
But I...
But I realized
that I've fallen in love with you.
♪That crimson stain on the collar♪
♪That alluring scent♪
♪All excuses sound so pale and empty♪
♪What cruel sarcasm♪
♪Oh, women, they never learn♪
♪When your heart flutters,
it's bound to be broken eventually♪
♪Midnight, a piercing chill♪
♪Wakes you up from a shattered dream♪
♪Heavy mist shrouds the truth♪
♪A steadfast retaliation comes alive♪
♪Oh, men, those smarty-pants♪
♪The backfire of your overflowing charm♪
♪Has no mercy♪
♪May your life be barren♪
♪May you tread on a thorny path alone♪
♪May you vanish into thin air♪
♪Lies will adorn your tombstone♪
♪Release me from this hatred♪
♪Free me from this excruciating cage♪
♪Let me go to light♪
♪Let's never meet again♪
♪When I use your words♪
♪And your ways♪
♪You blame me for being cruel♪
♪Life is ironic♪
♪I want your end♪
♪To be lonely♪
♪With no one to hate♪
♪You will live in endless nightmares♪
♪Rise♪
♪From the ashes♪