OUR UNIVERSE
Let me just get to the conclusion.
Based on a comprehensive review
of all your documents and stories
you two are
currently deemed unfit
as Woo-joo's guardians.
What do you mean?
"Unfit"?
We're his family. How are we...
The child is
currently in emotional distress
due to his parents' sudden absence.
But you're always working overtime
and he had multiple babysitters
over just a few months.
Ms. Woo, nothing in your life seems
to make a nurturing environment
for the child.
Not only that, but Mr. Sun,
you had family issues.
That is also a huge factor to consider.
Moreover
I saw what happened to him
with my own eyes
so it's hard to say
I am convinced that you two are fit
as Woo-joo's guardians.
We're really doing our best.
We'll make sure
that we don't let
anything you mentioned happen again.
Could you please reconsider your decision?
I don't have the final say.
The judge does, in court.
But...
That's my girl!
Hey, lovebirds!
Welcome back.
Were you a good boy, Woo-joo?
Of course. We told him you two were busy
and he was so patient.
Would you like some sikhye?
Mrs. Park made it.
It's not too sweet, so it's perfect.
You want some, Woo-joo?
- You want some?
- No?
- No.
I'll have it, then.
I'll head in first.
What's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
No, I'm just a bit tired.
I also need to clean the house.
Yeah, head in and get some rest.
I'll bring Woo-joo later.
Okay, thanks.
See you around, then.
Bye.
What...
Did something happen?
Did something happen in court?
Oh, well...
What? "Unfit"?
What kind of nonsense is that?
What? It's not just anyone.
How can you and Hyun-jin be deemed unfit?
That's really a stretch.
We'll just have to prove
that's not the case next time.
No wonder Hyun-jin looked so glum.
This must be so hard on her.
But
I could be wrong
so I'll go and see it for myself.
I'll visit your home,
where you live with the child
and closely observe some other factors
for consideration.
Yeah, we still have a chance.
We just have to make up for this time
next time.
I got this, Woo-joo.
OUR UNIVERSE
EPISODE 12
A bold image is definitely better
since it's for social media.
Would FILMPLUTO be okay
with an earlier date for the shoot?
The shoot?
Our latest release,
the tteokbokki meal kit, is
all over social media right now.
We need to work extra hard
while we're on a roll.
We have to keep pushing.
I saw it online, too.
It's gone totally viral.
How about the 20th?
That works best for us.
We're free that day, too.
It's not like we have any shoots that day,
do we?
That's perfect. So, the 20th?
The 20th?
I guess there's nothing we can do.
You have to go to the shoot.
But I should be there
for the home visit, too.
No, I'm taking a day off that day, anyway.
We don't need both of us there.
Just don't worry and focus on the shoot.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Oh, right.
I'll pick up Woo-joo today.
Okay.
Why do you look so down today?
I'm not down.
Alright, you're all recharged now.
See? You're so pretty when you smile.
Hurry. Seung-taek must be waiting for you.
See you later at home.
Bye!
Woo-joo!
Hop!
You have to wear your shoes first!
He ran out here as soon as I told him
you were here.
He absolutely adores you.
You can pass me the shoes. I'll do it.
See you.
- Thank you!
- Bye.
Let's get your shoes on.
Right on.
Good boy! Other foot.
- Auntie.
- Yeah?
- Are you that happy to see me?
- Yeah.
I didn't know you'd be so happy.
- Auntie.
- Come here!
I should pick you up more often, right?
- Yeah!
- Hold my hand.
Let's go.
Aren't you cold?
You've got a runny nose.
Let's wear a sweater.
Are you heading to work now?
Yeah.
Isn't the home visit in the afternoon?
Why are you so restless already?
The house is sparkling clean.
There's nothing to clean.
I just want it to be so clean
that anyone will think it's a nice home.
Are you sure you'll be fine alone?
I would've stayed with you
if it weren't for the shoot.
Don't worry about us and just go.
I'll come home as quickly as I can.
Call me if anything happens.
See you, Woo-joo.
Bye-bye!
Good boy!
- See you.
- Have a good day.
Bye!
I opened all the windows,
and it still smells like bleach.
Woo-joo!
When did you take your socks off?
Let's put them back on.
Run!
You're running a fever.
Open it.
Come here, Woo-joo.
Your ear. Stay still.
I need to get you some Ibuprofen.
I don't have any.
Hey, Hyun-jin, what's up?
Woo-joo's suddenly getting a fever.
Do you have any Ibuprofen at home?
Oh, no, I'm out right now.
Is his fever bad?
It's just a light fever.
Maybe he's catching a cold.
Everyone's catching a cold
because of the sudden temperature drop.
Do you have
any emergency medicine at home?
Well, it'd be best to take him
to a doctor.
I don't have time for that.
Oh, the home visit is today, right?
What should we do?
Doo-sik and Mrs. Park are also out
for Mrs. Park's physiotherapy.
Okay, I'll do what I can and let you know.
Okay, thank you.
Woo-joo!
We need to take him to the hospital.
You let him get hurt this time.
It's not what you think this is.
Neglect is also considered abuse.
Being absent
when the child needs your attention
is neglect, and therefore, abuse.
What in the world is going on?
Woo-joo!
Oh, no, Woo-joo!
What's going on?
How is this abuse?
That's too far-fetched. What's going on?
I don't know what happened
but that's not a word
you can just throw around.
Hyun-jin abusing Woo-joo?
She would never.
We'll wait and see.
YUSEONG VILLA
Okay, I got it.
What?
- Ms. Woo.
- Yes?
We're here to investigate
a report of potential child abuse
after receiving
the family investigator's report.
Abuse? I would never...
Based on what's happened
and the investigator's testimony
we have no option but to conclude
that the child is in danger.
He'll be taken
under an emergency protective measure
for his safety.
What? Emergency what?
What does that mean?
What are you doing with him?
An immediate separation is required
so please excuse the child's sudden leave.
"Separation"?
Are you saying you're taking Woo-joo?
No! How could you take my Woo-joo?
Wait.
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
How could you separate the child
from his auntie?
What did she do to deserve that?
The protective measure isn't a punishment.
It's our way of ensuring
the child is safe.
Protecting the child comes
before evaluating the case
in cases of child abuse.
If the investigation shows
there was no abuse
the protective measure will be lifted.
Please understand and cooperate.
We should take him
to a doctor first.
I can explain everything!
I was just doing something for a second!
I'll die without Woo-joo!
How can you take Woo-joo
when I'm right here?
Protecting the child is our priority.
Doing this won't do you any good.
Are you kidding me?
So, what are you going to do, then?
You may be arrested
for obstructing a legal investigation.
Woo-joo!
I'll come to you soon, Woo-joo!
There's definitely been a mistake.
We know how she is with him!
We know how hard Hyun-jin worked
to be a mother figure to him!
That's exactly what I mean.
And this happened
when she was looking for his meds!
Shouldn't they take that
into consideration?
Why isn't he picking up?
Tae-hyung's back.
Is the investigator still here?
What took you so long?
Unbelievable!
Well...
Don't be too shocked when I say this.
CHILD PROTECTION SERVICES
Hyun-jin!
Are you okay?
It's all my fault.
I messed up everything.
Only if I didn't get distracted...
No, only if I made sure
he didn't catch a cold...
None of this would've happened.
You can't say that.
You were just looking for meds for him.
- Let's get up.
- I'm just not good enough.
I don't deserve to be his guardian.
That's why all of this happened.
I feel so bad for Woo-joo.
Sorry, Woo-joo...
He must be so scared right now.
Oh, gosh.
You're up early.
Where's Tae-hyung?
He must've gone out for a bit.
Yeah?
Come in, then.
Come and have some fruit.
Doo-sik got
a huge basket of fruit.
It's too much for us to finish.
No, I'm fine.
No, come and have some fruit, okay?
Come in.
Have some fruit.
I'm stepping out for a bit.
Did you not get any sleep?
What happened to your face? Did you cry?
Cut the nonsense and just leave!
Fine.
So, when do we get to see Woo-joo again?
Where is he?
He's with a foster family.
- Oh, no.
- First
they have to separate him from us
for 72 hours
as an emergency measure.
He may return or not
depending on how the investigation goes.
He'll be back soon.
No need to worry. He'll be back.
- Just leave already.
- Fine.
My mom's the best listener.
Tell her anything you want.
Hey, just leave, okay?
- Fine, I'm leaving!
- Just leave already!
Gosh, maybe I should talk
to the chief at the police station.
These are so sweet.
Here. Have some.
You look like you have no energy.
Have you eaten anything?
No.
I didn't feel like eating.
Hold on. I'll bring you
some nurungji and gatkimchi.
No, it's fine.
I'm really okay.
You have to eat, though.
I know it's hard.
No
I'm sure it's harder for Woo-joo.
He had to leave home so suddenly
without knowing why he had to go.
I really don't deserve to raise him.
I don't know
if I can replace my sister for him.
I really don't know anymore.
I wanted to be
a family Woo-joo could always count on.
You know, in life
things don't always go
the way we're told they do.
Did you know
that Doo-sik and I aren't related at all?
So...
He's my son-in-law.
I don't know
why she had to leave us so early.
She got sick.
Even just breathing and being alive
felt so dreadful that I wanted to die.
But Doo-sik just moved in with his stuff
one day.
He left his house and insisted
on staying with me
to check on me
talk to me, and bother me.
I told him he didn't need to be here
when his wife was already gone.
I called him crazy, slapped him
and pushed him away, but he persisted.
He kept making lame jokes
and I got so sick of it one day
so I sat him down and said
"Why are you here? Go and live your life."
He answered
"This is my life
for as long as you're here with me."
That was what he said.
So, Doo-sik held my hand tightly
and became my family
by staying by my side.
Nobody needs to prove themselves
to be good enough in a family.
You're so worried about Woo-joo
that you're barely holding on right now.
That's what it means to be family, okay?
Look at me.
People would look at us and think
we're really weird.
My daughter's long gone
but my son-in-law is still with me
sharing every meal, laughing, crying,
and arguing all the time.
But now that I've gone through everything
I now know that's all there is to living.
You're not family
just because you're blood-related.
The days
you keep each other strong with love
add up, one by one
and that's how you become family.
So, in Woo-joo's eyes
you're already his mom and family.
What do you mean you're not good enough?
Not at all!
Don't worry.
You're doing above and beyond.
You're doing amazing.
I'm so proud of you.
You're doing great.
You're everything to Woo-joo, okay?
Stay strong.
Here. Have some.
Where were you?
I was just bringing some stuff.
What are you doing?
I want to go out for a bit.
Right now? Where are you going?
You know Woo-joo can't sleep alone.
He must be so scared without us.
I'm thinking
maybe he'll sleep better with this.
Let's go together.
- I'll take it.
- Okay.
Here.
Woo-joo had a bit of a cold yesterday
so we brought Ibuprofen and other meds,
just in case.
And Woo-joo has sensitive skin
so he gets really bad diaper rash.
Please use these diapers only.
Oh.
And this is Woo-joo's favorite toy.
I'm guessing he's very shocked right now.
This might make him feel a bit better.
It'll be easier to make him sleep
if you make him go to bed before 9 p.m.
Once it's past that time
he has a habit of fighting sleep.
Oh, and
he sometimes cries,
looking for his mom and dad.
Just carry him in your arms and pat him
and he'll feel better in no time.
Okay.
Don't worry too much.
I know it's only temporary
but please take good care of our Woo-joo.
Please take good care of him.
Okay.
I'm really not hungry.
You need to eat well and stay strong
at a time like this.
You haven't eaten anything
since yesterday.
Here.
Do you remember that day?
When you asked me
if I wanted to take custody of Woo-joo
at the memorial
and I said
I wasn't someone
who could be responsible for someone else?
Of course, I do. How could I forget?
I really believed that back then.
I couldn't even love anyone
let alone be responsible for someone.
And I would've never realized otherwise
if it weren't for you.
Even earlier
no matter how scared and tired you were
you thought about Woo-joo first.
Remember what you said?
You told me to trust you
who believed in me.
This time
trust me.
I believe
that you're a wonderful guardian
for Woo-joo.
You don't need to try so hard
to be everything for him.
I can be what you can't be at times
and sometimes, you can do the same for me.
We can do it together. Don't you agree?
Thank you.
I can't live without Woo-joo anymore,
either.
We're Woo-joo's family.
How can we let anyone take him from us?
That's right.
We're his family.
We'll bring him back, no matter what.
Let's eat up and get on it.
Okay.
I did some research
and they check the measures taken
after an accident.
That's how we can prove
this was an accident and not neglect.
So, I got some baby gates and cameras.
Thanks. You really have my back.
It feels so empty without Woo-joo.
Let's straighten things out
and bring him back soon.
Okay.
So
Woo-joo's been taken from you?
Sorry, I was such a mess.
I just saw your missed calls.
No wonder.
I called because I was worried
that you suddenly took a day off.
How are things going now?
Is there any way I can help?
No, they just need to have
another home visit
to see if he can return
and continue the guardianship assessment.
So, we're just fixing up the house a bit.
This must be so hard for you.
Are you okay?
Of course.
I'm just going to focus
on bringing Woo-joo back for now.
Yeah.
Let me know anytime if I can help.
Okay, thank you.
Hey, it's me.
Yeah, I've been well.
I just have a question.
Do you know anything
about child separation measures?
I heard you were fixing up the house.
How are you fixing it up?
We're installing some cameras
and baby-proof fences.
I'm the perfect guy for that.
I'm basically MacGyver.
You want some help?
Really? We'd really appreciate that!
No need to thank me. Is that trash?
I can do it!
No, just head up. I'll be there.
It's all good now.
Is the camera working well?
Do I look handsome or what?
No, looks like it's working.
- Damn you.
- And you?
The fences are perfect now.
Who am I?
The MacGyver of the neighborhood!
Hyun-jin!
- Oh, gosh! Damn it!
- Damn it!
Sorry, just give me a sec.
We heard you were fixing things up
and brought a few things.
We used these for Bom and Yeo-reum.
I also brought a few things I was gifted.
Thank you.
No need to thank us.
We're all parents here.
So, I did some research
on online mom groups
and the best way to appeal
against separation is
providing objective evidence.
Evidence?
- What's this?
- This should make
the officers reconsider.
What's this?
A record of our call.
Hey, Hyun-jin, what's up?
Woo-joo's suddenly getting a fever.
Do you have any Ibuprofen at home?
Oh, no, I'm out right now.
Shouldn't this prove
that you weren't neglecting him
but you were just busy
looking for meds for him?
- Yeah.
- You're right.
Her shaky voice proves
she was very worried, too.
This could prove it all. Perfect.
Absolutely! This should work, for sure.
Good job.
All sorts of things happen in a blink
when you have a baby at home.
This will definitely show them
what was going on.
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you so much
for all your help, everyone.
It's nothing.
Come on.
What should we do first?
- You owe me a lunch.
- What's this?
I'm leaving! You sort it out yourself!
I thought you were busy.
What brings you all the way here?
I was wondering how it was going.
- Is this it?
- Yeah.
I just sent the docs
to the police and relevant offices.
As you can see,
all the neighbors and the daycare teachers
have nothing but good things to say
about Ms. Woo.
I guess she really loves her nephew.
So, everything's good?
I don't think there's much to worry about.
Thanks, I owe you one.
How about an expensive dinner?
So, who is this?
How important is she
that you're asking me for a favor?
Is she your girlfriend?
You know.
My first love.
Oh, gosh.
What can I do to make you stop?
Aren't you tired?
Come on, stop.
- Please be strict...
- Woo-joo?
Okay, I'll call you back.
Okay.
Is something wrong?
The boy's refused to sleep for days.
He hasn't stopped crying.
He keeps looking for his aunt and uncle.
I can tell they really love their nephew.
You can tell from this petition.
Anyway
the police investigation is over
and we sent the report
to the regional office
so we should hear back soon.
Can I read the petition?
Of course.
Sorry I'm late.
Huh? What?
I thought you took the morning off.
You're here so early.
Why are you here so soon?
I have a lot of work.
And I haven't been at the office for days.
Come on.
Don't feel bad.
They're your vacation days.
You're too strict on yourself sometimes.
That matches your previous testimony.
I received the petition this morning
and realized
there'd been a misunderstanding.
We take child abuse very seriously
so we sometimes go overboard
after misunderstanding the situation.
What do you mean by a petition?
Oh, that.
This is a petition to claim
that Ms. Woo didn't abuse her nephew.
As you know, witnesses and evidence are
really important in such a case.
Who sent it to you?
Did you not know about it?
It's from Mr. Park Yoon-seong.
He also signed the petition.
LIST OF SIGNATURES
PARK YOON-SEONG
TEAM LEADER OF PLANNING 3, PARK YOON-SEONG
I thought you took the morning off.
You're early.
Oh, hi.
Is Mr. Park out today?
I think he's out all day today.
The international fair seems to be going
pretty global.
Even the US branch was considering
participating in it.
I have to thank him.
Hello?
Sorry?
Thank you! Thank you so much.
Come here, Woo-joo!
Woo-joo!
My baby!
Your fever's gone. Look at me.
Do you have any idea
how much I missed you?
Thank you.
It's nothing.
I'm also here for the home visit
I didn't get last time.
Woo-joo's aunt?
There must've been a misunderstanding.
Woo-joo bolts out of the classroom
on the days she picks him up.
Woo-joo's uncle and aunt are
almost overbearing.
They're far from being abusive.
Moms can tell right away.
She always feels bad
because she feels like she's not enough.
That's Woo-joo's aunt.
Isn't that how moms feel?
Nobody cares about Woo-joo
more than his aunt!
Remember that day?
She had her slippers on the wrong feet
and was crying for her life!
I felt heartbroken for her!
Woo-joo and his aunt and uncle
are a family.
What else is there to say?
Please help them, Mr. Lawyer.
I can sign this a million times.
LIST OF SIGNATURES
As her supervisor, old friend from school,
and just as another human
I can testify
that she's nothing but wonderful.
She's compassionate, caring,
and very responsible.
Please help her.
PETITION
LIST OF SIGNATURES
This is a photo album of Woo-joo
from his uncle.
YOU FINISHED YOUR FOOD!
LET'S ALWAYS BE HAPPY
US AT THE RESERVOIR!
I knew there'd been a mistake
when I saw these photos.
You can tell from her face
that she really loves Woo-joo.
And he seems so used
to getting so loved.
Woo-joo sure loves his aunt.
I think that's enough for today.
See you at the court hearing.
- Have a good day.
- Bye.
Woo-joo!
You missed me, right?
I bet you did! Are you okay?
Did you miss me?
He smells like a baby.
It's nice, right?
He always hates bedtime
but it looks like nothing can wake him.
I know.
My Woo-joo. You've been through so much.
Good job, my Hyun-jin.
I wasn't the only one who had it hard.
It would've been better for me
to go through this alone.
You can't say that. We're a family.
I think Woo-joo and I
will sleep in the main bedroom
from now on.
Really?
I did some research
and apparently, children struggle to sleep
if their play space isn't separate
from their sleeping space.
It might not be a big house,
but it's better for his development
to have separate spaces for each purpose.
That's true
but are you sure?
At first
just the thought of my sister made me cry.
I couldn't stop feeling guilty
for having been so harsh on her.
But not anymore.
Even without her here
the love she's given me
and the time we were together are
all still in me.
Come here.
Let me hug my Hyun-jin.
Thank you, Tae-hyung.
SEOUL FAMILY COURT
SEOUL ADMINISTRATIVE COURT
Gosh, I'm getting nervous.
It'll go well.
What's there to worry about?
What are you doing?
Stop being so embarrassing!
The kids are learning from you!
Shh! I think I can hear them.
- What?
- I can hear them! Come here.
- Hurry!
- You can?
- Can you hear them?
- This case is
one where the child's safety
and protection
must be considered in priority
over anything.
The court made
a very careful decision
made in consideration of the impact
it will have on the child's upbringing.
Based on all submitted documents,
your interview
and home visit reports
the court has determined
the legal guardian to be
most suitable as the child's guardian.
Therefore
the court confirms Ms. Woo Hyun-jin
as the guardian
for Mr. Sun Woo-joo.
We did it, Woo-joo!
Yeah!
I think it's done!
Is it really?
It sounds like it.
Tell me how it went! Don't just guess!
Did it really go through?
How did it go?
What happened?
It's been approved.
Hooray!
- Woo-joo!
- Congratulations!
- Cheers to Yuseong Villa!
- Hooray!
Thank you so much, everyone.
We couldn't have gone through it all
just by ourselves.
Thank you.
We promise to return the favor big time.
You don't need to return the favor.
Just make sure
Woo-joo grows up to be
a strong, healthy boy.
And maybe stop arguing, you two.
Live happily ever after with Woo-joo.
That's how you can return the favor.
- Don't you agree?
- Well
since you want to return the favor
we had to skip lunch to come here today.
You know, my mom hates skipping meals
more than anything.
Alright, let's go!
Lunch is on me.
- What?
- Really?
Let's go!
- We want beef!
- Beef!
- One, two, three.
- All done!
- Done!
Let's see.
You want to see the photo?
This.
- I love it.
- It looks great.
Perfect!
We just have to wait now.
All done.
I should've brought my camera
from the office, too.
Why? It looks great as is.
But I'm a professional photographer!
My pride is on the line.
It's his homework, not an exhibition.
Right, Woo-joo?
What?
- Red.
- Red?
Yeah.
Blue.
White.
Huh?
Look. You like it?
Show your auntie.
It looks so clear, right?
You're right. It's so clear.
It's so easy to use, too.
I can't believe he's
already getting homework. He's baby!
My Woo-joo can't be stressed already!
He's running away
because I mentioned homework.
- I'm glad he's having fun.
- Yeah.
Get up.
- Why?
- Why else?
We have to finish cleaning the bedroom.
Can we stay here for a bit longer, honey?
Did you just call me "honey"?
Are you crazy?
What?
I just want to stay here with you
for a bit longer, honey.
Stop it, you're making me blush.
- You're so cute.
- Honey!
All done.
Anything else?
Thank you, Tae-hyung.
What's with the sudden hug?
You know.
I'm just so happy
that you're with me in this house.
Should we take a family photo?
- A family photo?
- Yeah.
Let's take a photo with Woo-joo
and hang it beside that one.
You know that means
we'll have to be a family forever, right?
Come on.
What?
Just a kiss? No answer?
Are you really not going to answer me?
I love you.
Thank you for staying with me
and being my home.
I love you, too.
Lovebirds
Let's run away
No
We can't run away
Are you sure about this, Yoon-seong?
The US office needs a manager
for the international fair
and it's just a great opportunity.
Of course, it's a great chance for you
but I'm just sad to see you go.
Who will replace you
if you go to the US?
You're making me sad here.
It's all thanks to your mentorship.
Hyun-jin.
Yoon-seong!
Do you have a minute?
I had something to tell you, too.
You can go first, then.
No, you can go first.
I heard it.
That you prepared the petition
and the notarization.
You took care of everything for us.
Thank you for all that,
especially when you've been so busy.
Thanks to you, Woo-joo is back,
and I'm his guardian now.
Everything's sorted.
I'm glad it all worked out.
I didn't have to do much.
I have a friend who's a lawyer
so I had fun pulling some strings.
But still.
Thank you so much.
I wanted to thank you sooner
but you haven't been in office
in the last few days.
I'm moving to the US office soon.
The US office?
I'm just a friend from college now
and no longer your supervisor.
When are you leaving?
In two weeks.
That soon?
Yeah.
I'm in a rush
because of the international fair.
But I'll get to give Woo-joo
his birthday present before I go.
His birthday's next week, right?
Yeah.
Wait, what?
No way. Next week?
Yeah.
I knew it was coming up soon
and that I had to get ready
but I didn't know
it was already next week!
I've been so busy
that I didn't even know what date it was.
Where do we start?
Where do we host the party?
Where else? Right here.
No, that's not fun.
It's his first birthday with his uncle
and you as his official guardian.
It's not his first birthday or anything.
Renting a venue would be overkill.
And I'm sure all venues are already booked
for next week.
You think so?
What do we do about the food?
We're going to have to cook a feast
for all the guests.
Why?
Huh? Nothing.
Do you think he knows everything?
What?
I'll look into that.
Really? How?
There's a studio I always go to
for photoshoots
and they sometimes rent the space out
for events.
Bro! No, Mr. Kim!
Have some more ham.
You're the best.
Don't be so weird about it.
But second birthdays aren't usually big,
are they?
I know!
I keep telling him so,
but he won't listen.
Nope.
This is his first birthday party
hosted by his uncle.
I'm going to make it as grand as possible.
So grand that everyone will be jealous!
You have to add every topping to the pot!
Okay, I'll be the photographer, then.
I'm an expert for baby birthdays.
Of course.
I'll be the host, then.
I'm quite the chatterbox.
Perfect.
- Let's go!
- Alright!
You guys are the best.
I'm an expert at that.
Cooking for a party takes so much work.
You can't do it alone.
But I feel so bad.
We were just going to hire a caterer.
Cooking for birthday parties is
all about love.
And Woo-joo isn't a stranger to me.
He's basically my grandson at this point.
That's true.
And Mrs. Park's cooking is
better than any caterer you'll find.
She's cooked a lot for me, too.
Why don't I bake a cake for him?
Time to whip out my baking skills!
I'll make a two-tiered cake.
What are you baking for?
Look, Mom, we're matching!
For Woo-joo's birthday party.
It's going to be a big one!
What? He's turning two already?
And it's a big party?
A party? A big one?
I want to sing, then.
I used to train to become
a K-pop star trainee.
I was a trainee to be a trot singer.
Let's sing together.
- Sure.
- We'll sing a song.
- What's your genre?
- Hip-hop.
The tteok from the last time was amazing.
I want to put in a custom order this time.
Isn't it too big? How did you rent it?
I pulled some strings.
Hey!
What?
What's all this?
I got some friends to help.
Right on.
Woo-joo loves animals.
Make sure they're visible.
Okay, you heard him, right?
Let's start setting up.
- Alright!
- Let's go!
I'll be your love
And you'll be my universe
What are you even singing?
That's not how it goes!
Get up.
First, shake your hips.
I'll be your love
Shake it more!
And you'll be my universe
More!
La la la
Keep it down!
Try some sikhye.
Don't touch it too much.
It'll ruin the shape.
They look so pretty.
Of course, a pretty person made them.
And you're handsome, huh?
You're flattering me.
Hey, sing properly.
That sounds more like a chant.
I can't work with him.
Forget singing together.
Ta-da!
The cake is ready!
Hyun-jin, do you want to write
on the cake?
What? Yes! I'd love to.
I want to try it, too!
- What's that?
- Write?
Write on the cake.
You write a message on the cake
and make it look pretty.
Sure, let's go for it!
- Let's get writing!
A celebratory message.
- Celebratory?
- Yeah.
You screwed it up.
- No, it's fine.
- You ruined it.
- It's okay.
- Oh, no.
It's okay.
- It's okay!
- Let's get dressed.
- No.
- No?
But you have to put it on.
- Woo-joo!
- No.
- No?
- Yeah, I want pink.
Let Woo-joo wear what he wants.
He's the star today, after all.
Should I?
- We should get changed, too.
- Okay.
I'll get changed and come back, okay?
You did all of this by yourself?
- Yeah.
- No!
He used me.
Hello.
Finally, a proper introduction.
I'm Kim Ui-jun.
He's my photographer friend.
Oh, Ui-jun! Tae-hyung's told me
a lot about you.
Same.
Hyun-jin!
- Hey!
- Congrats!
- Good work!
I can't believe Woo-joo is already two.
I'm tearing up...
- Woo-joo!
When did you grow so big?
Ms. Choo! Moo-saeng!
Hey, Tae-hyung!
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Where's the baby?
Happy birthday, baby.
Take it with both hands.
You didn't have to.
It's not even his first birthday.
You know how expensive gold is, right?
Promise me you won't quit anytime soon.
- Woo-joo!
No running, kids!
Oh, wow.
- Look at that!
- My gosh.
- You look stunning, Mrs. Park!
- Welcome!
- Congrats.
- Beautiful. Just get married!
Doo-sik, I haven't seen you
looking like a researcher in forever!
A researcher?
My son-in-law is
back to his job
since his sabbatical is over.
Doo-sik.
I thought you were jobless!
Hey, call me Chief Bae from now on.
Chief Bae
you should quit smoking.
Yeah, stop smoking.
You'd better remember
how much gift money we prepared.
You still owe us a million won
for the heater!
- You made it.
- Yeah.
I wanted to get on Woo-joo's good side.
You like it, Woo-joo?
Hey, Yoon-seong!
The whole team is here.
Welcome!
Thanks for coming. I know you're all busy.
Alright.
Mr. Sun Woo-joo's second birthday party
will begin soon.
Everyone, please be seated.
OUR UNIVERSE
Before we begin
Woo-joo's second birthday party
we'll hear a word from his uncle first.
I thought he was just our Woo-joo
but it seems like he's everyone's Woo-joo.
Thanks to the love
from every single person here
the three clueless people
became a family.
Hyun-jin, you've trusted and helped me
through thick and thin.
Thank you.
Let's continue to do our best.
Thank you for coming, everyone.
- How lovely!
- Me?
Woo-joo shines extra bright today
because he's with all of you.
From the bottom of my heart
thank you!
Should we sing "Happy Birthday"
for Woo-joo now?
- Sounds good!
- Yeah!
Alright, in one, two, three!
- Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Woo-joo
Hyun-joo!
What? Really?
Is she pregnant?
Choo!
It's perfect!
Look here.
Look here!
Woo-joo!
Here we go!
"IT TAKES A VILLAGE TO RAISE A CHILD."
- AN AFRICAN PROVERB
Our Universe!
Let's start.
Booger.
That way?
Woo-joo!
Bye!
Alright!
Are you sad?
Mommy!
Are you sleepy?
All good.
Woo-joo!
That hurts!
No.
Thank you for watching Our Universe.
Subtitles by: Min-sun Kim