Sometimes you fall in love
before you know it.
Just like the spring breeze
and moist rain drops,
your heart slowly gets soaked with love
before you know it.
Love gets into our hearts.
At some point, you will come to realize
that a certain someone is holding
a special place in your heart.
-Is this all true?
-Are you the murderer?
Do you admit the charge?
How do you feel now?
-Please give us a comment.
-Share a word.
-What was your motive?
-Please answer our questions.
Some say for one to fall in love,
0.2 second is more than enough.
The time I needed to fall in love
was only 0.2 second.
It was love at first sight.
SEONHO DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
This is why I'm going to confess my love.
I'll confess that I love him.
I'll tell him he's my only present,
my only love, and my destiny.
I think that we...
met by fate.
I also think you're my destiny--
An ill-fated encounter.
So...
let's never cross paths again.
Hey, Bong-hui.
I wanted to give you this.
What is this?
This tea is good for insomnia.
How did you know that I have insomnia?
For about two months,
I worked as your underling...
I mean your trainee prosecutor.
I was bound to find out.
Believe it or not, I know you quite well.
I didn't delve into your private life
or pry on you. Don't worry.
By the way, considering your condition,
you don't look tired,
or have dark circles. Did you know that?
At a glance, people might think
you sleep like a baby at night.
It makes me realize the importance
of skin once again,
and I'm rambling on, aren't I?
-Yes.
-I'm sorry.
You must be, but go on
whether you want to ramble on
or have something to say.
This will be the last time anyway.
Last time...
There are so many things I'm sorry about.
I mistook you for a pervert before.
Because of me,
you were fired from your position.
I'm sorry for everything.
Okay.
And I'd like to thank you too.
To me, you are a hero, Prosecutor Noh.
I won't change you for Iron Man.
Really?
Yes.
And...
I like you.
And?
And... What was it?
Oh, right. The real culprit.
I think I ran into the real culprit.
What?
But you don't have to worry about that.
From now on, I won't bother
or harm you in any way.
I will take care of this on my own.
You lost your job because of me.
It doesn't matter if I lost my job or not.
You should've told me
if you saw the real culprit.
Well... I wasn't completely certain.
What do you mean?
Well...
We sort of met through a song.
A song?
The sound of the whistle I heard
on the night of Hui-jun's murder.
I also heard it in court.
I believe that the real culprit
came to my trial.
The whistle...
What kind of song was it?
Gosh.
Is this music from the third world?
How should I put it? This is quite unique.
Repeat it again.
Again?
Yes.
Gosh, this is bitter.
Gosh, this isn't good.
This is bitter and not tasty.
Hey, stop it. That's enough.
Stop with this odd melody.
What does he look like?
How old does he look?
-Well...
-Yes?
I won't accept your help again.
-What?
-You went through a lot for me.
I will take care of this on my own.
You don't have to worry about that.
I wasn't worried about you.
I was just curious.
Goodness, Bong-hui,
you don't know anything.
Seriously, this is so bitter.
You eat, sleep, and breathe
in a place where my son was murdered.
You are alive and well.
How dare you be alive?
I'm also heartbroken...
about what happened to your son.
I really mean it.
However,
I really didn't do it.
I know that you don't believe me,
but that doesn't mean...
I can admit something I didn't do.
I didn't find any evidence
that proves you didn't murder my son.
With all due respect,
there is no evidence that I did.
There is.
Only if Noh Ji-uk
didn't mess up the trial,
you would have been in prison
serving time for your crime.
That evidence...
was fabricated.
What?
Please forgive me...
for saying this.
However,
the prosecution has to prove my guilt.
According to the presumption of innocence,
I'm innocent.
If you believe that I'm guilty,
the prosecution ought to prove that.
There is no responsibility on my side...
to prove that I'm innocent,
but...
I'm going to prove my innocence.
I'll do it for myself,
Prosecutor Noh,
and my mom.
I will...
catch the real culprit for you
and Hui-jun. I'll make sure...
I didn't know
how you won my son's heart...
with what kind of means or abilities.
I was wondering how you put
Noh Ji-uk under your spell
to get you out and regain
your freedom so brazenly.
I get it now.
Now I know that you aren't a typical girl.
-Sir--
-However,
you are going to regret
acquiring your freedom again.
I'm going to catch you by all means.
I'm definitely going to punish you.
As long as you and I are alive,
I'm going to make you suffer,
and I won't forget to punish you.
THE LATE NOH YEONG-SEOK
Dad.
I resigned.
Before I could even solve
the last case as a prosecutor,
I quit.
What? You want to be like me?
Yes, when I grow up,
I'm going to be just like you.
My goodness, what an honor.
There is no greater honor than a son
wishing to be just like his father.
I'm sorry that...
I failed to become like you.
I'm sorry.
For not keeping my promise.
LAWYERS NOH JI-UK AND JI EUN-HYEOK
Welcome, Noh Ji-uk!
My gosh.
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm sincerely welcoming you
because I really like you.
Get lost.
No, wait.
What? Tell me anything you need.
I had an ill-fated relationship.
You did? With whom?
-Just listen.
-Okay, I will.
It's fine as long as I'm not the one.
You're the worst one ever.
I already hate you.
My gosh.
Anyway, I told someone
that we have an ill-fated relationship,
and to never show up in front of me.
But the thing is,
I need to ask that person something.
So if I contact that person first...
Come on. That'd be humiliating.
-Do you think so?
-Of course.
You'll look silly.
But it'd be nice.
If it were me, I'd like
it. I'd be more touched and excited
if someone called me
after saying that they won't.
That's how I felt
when you contacted me first.
The less you expect,
the bigger the surprise.
Get lost.
That's what I'm talking about.
You say that and then call me again.
It makes me have butterflies
in my stomach.
Hey.
Just because I act like nothing happened,
don't get delusional
and actually think that way, Eun-hyeok.
Okay.
-Please disappear.
-But, Ji-uk...
This is also my office.
This is your desk. That's my desk.
Where should I disappear to?
I really can't stand this lecture.
It's so boring.
Bong-hui.
Do you want to eat with us?
-Hey, stop it.
-Hey.
You can't ask her.
Let's go.
Let's go eat.
I decided to listen to all the music
in the world
until I find the source of that melody.
LOOKING FOR A WITNESS
WHO SAW A BIKE HERE ON MAY 11, 2015
I even sent a message to the culprit.
I let him know that I was looking for him,
so he should come find me too.
Hey, culprit.
Let's have a head-to-head battle.
This is the only place the culprit
left a trace.
Where did the culprit go after that?
No way.
They always return
to the scene of the crime.
Bong-hui?
Mr. Noh?
You scared me. Why didn't you
tell me who you were?
You didn't ask me.
How could you not reveal yourself
at such a shady place like this?
Then am I supposed to say my name
out loud while I walk
when nobody even asked?
It's a shady place.
Of course I mistook you for the culprit!
You're the one who came here
alone at this hour.
I was looking for criminal evidence.
Were you worried about me?
No. Of course not.
Of course, you weren't.
My gosh.
Why did you come here, Mr. Noh?
The fact
that a competent prosecutor like me
failed to solve his last case...
How should I put it?
It hurts my pride
and it doesn't sit right with me.
I see.
I'll help you restore your pride
by finding the source of that melody.
Forget that. I'll give you
the CCTV footage of the court.
So check the culprit's face and...
I never saw his face.
You said you saw him.
I did, but I told you
that I met him through a song.
He passed me by on a bicycle,
and in court, I only heard the melody--
What?
Melody my ass!
Why are you getting angry?
Okay, fine.
What did the bicycle look like?
What kind of bicycle was it?
What does it look like?
All bicycles look alike.
They have two wheels.
I didn't know that there was a difference.
My goodness, I had no idea.
I thought you had a clue or something.
I was so curious to know what that was.
Because of that, my insomnia
got worse, and I couldn't work.
I came here despite looking silly!
My gosh, Bong-hui.
That's why I said
I'll solve this on my own.
How are you going to solve it?
Tell me how!
Coming here at this hour?
You're making me think that
you're worried about me.
You're right.
Does that mean you're not mad
at me anymore?
You told me to get lost and said
we have an ill-fated relationship.
So I thought I'd never get to
see you again.
That's true too.
Sorry?
As your former mentor and guardian
for two months,
I did worry about you quite a lot. But...
it ends here.
Not anymore.
So please stay out of trouble.
And live safely.
I'm really going to find a clue.
I'm going to find the culprit.
I might visit you after that.
That's okay, right?
I'm going to become successful,
and I'm going to repay you.
I'm going to change our relationship...
from an ill-fated one to a good one.
JURISTIC ACT
I lived a diligent life.
And sometimes, when I had a tough time...
I'm so happy.
Congratulations! I'm so jealous.
Why are you jealous?
I'm not the only one who got appointed.
You've all landed a job at law firms, too.
All of us did pretty well.
Except for someone.
From time to time when I felt like
life was suffocating me,
I took a little break...
by peeking at you.
Okay.
That way. Yes, good.
Pull it a bit more towards you.
Okay!
Let's secure it now.
Go ahead and secure it.
Okay. I think it's good.
Thank you for your help.
I got it done easily thanks to you.
Are you the witness by any chance?
Are you going to report yourself?
Thanks anyway.
PLEASE CALL THIS NUMBER
ADD TO CONTACTS
LOOKING FOR A WITNESS
WHO SAW A BIKE HERE ON MAY 11, 2015
Goodness, this is...
Well...
Even if the injured party won't settle,
you can't threaten him like that.
A sincere apology and self-reflection
should come first.
Of course, he won't accept your apology,
but--
We are also victims here, Mr. Noh.
Why are they
turning it into such a big deal?
Boys will be boys, punching each other!
Why are they treating him
like a brutal criminal?
That's an understatement. Look at this.
He's been instigating the bullying.
He's in for confinement
and group assault as well.
The victim was released
from the ICU only recently.
That bastard deserved to get beaten up.
Be quiet.
He's saying that guy deserved it.
He should've behaved himself.
Everyone has a breaking point!
Aren't I right?
We're not asking him to settle for free.
I offered more than the hospital bills
but he said it wasn't enough.
They obviously want more.
I get that they're poor,
but how can they try to make money
off of their injured son?
Anyway, my son's future is in your hands.
Please make sure he gets suspension
of prosecution or sentence.
Okay, let's say we get out of this.
But what about the next time?
After his upcoming birthday, he'll
no longer be considered a minor.
What do you mean...
I'm a lot more experienced than I seem.
I passed the exam very young.
I mean, I passed the bar exam
before I even graduated.
What a show-off.
Yes, I'm showing off.
Because I have a lot of experience
as a prosecutor, I've seen jerks...
I mean, I've seen many boys like you.
Hey, isn't this your third case?
I see here that you almost raped
a girl and threatened her...
-almost bribing her.
-That girl was a gold digger.
Right, of course. I'm sure
he's never done anything wrong.
-It must be everyone else's fault.
-Goodness.
You've been, and will be backing him up
with your money and connections.
So he never learned his lessons.
Nor he will ever learn.
He'll continue to commit bad deeds
because he doesn't know right from wrong!
If he gets in huge trouble
that you can't fix
you'll send him to a school abroad.
Then he'll get into drugs...
and won't even be able to graduate.
Then he'll return to Korea
and exercise violence against those
who are poorer and weaker than him.
Then he'll pay his way out of it. Well!
Everything will be okay.
Your mom will take care of everything.
Ma'am, you'll have to live longer
than your son does
because you'll have to fix his mess
all your life.
For goodness' sake!
Money take cares of everything.
What an amazing world we live in.
Well, you know.
I'm just saying.
That's how the world is.
Shall we...
start over from the beginning...
with a refreshed mindset?
Let's start from a sincere apology
and self-reflection.
Lawyer Noh!
You're no longer a prosecutor.
You're a lawyer now.
It's already been two years since
you gave up your prosecutor badge.
Why are you still
acting like a prosecutor?
Who are you to demand
self-reflection from your client?
Look at you. "I'm not listening."
"You can talk all you want."
Is that what you're thinking now?
No, that's not really what I'm thinking.
You should reflect on yourself.
Don't just demand it from your client.
You do it first.
My life motto is, "No regrets."
But I'm starting to regret...
bringing you here.
Good grief.
PROSECUTOR NOH JI-UK
PROSECUTOR WOO MYEONG-SIK
Let's go for food.
I'm busy.
Let's eat. Come on.
I'M BUSY
I think the food at Goyang District Court
is the best.
Then you should eat there.
Why do you come here every day?
I can't go all the way to Ilsan--
You have a lot of time
because you don't have much work.
Aren't I right, Prosecutor Noh?
I mean, Lawyer Noh.
I heard you had a team dinner
two days ago.
Guys,
have you watched the movie,
The Devil's Advocate?
In that movie...
a lawyer...
sells his soul to a devil.
You see, it shows
that some of us are even willing...
to defend a devil for wealth and fame.
How should I put this?
I think that movie...
captured the nature of lawyers
very precisely.
Anyway, I hate lawyers so much.
Even devils have the right to be defended.
All of us here, including me, are lawyers.
Mr. Noh. We rarely get to have
everyone gathered like this...
for a company dinner.
Ji-uk made the rare company dinner
even more special.
Hey, you're really...
Don't be ridiculous.
Let go, you punk.
Why are there so many lawyers
in this world?
You used to criticize prosecutors so much
when you were a prosecutor.
Now that you're a lawyer,
you badmouth them all the time.
I bet there are many ridiculous stories
you can share with me.
Prosecutor Noh. I mean, Lawyer Noh.
Isn't this a bit too salty? I prefer foods
that are low in sodium.
Chameleons, lizards, and octopus.
Even those creatures change colors
and blend in with their surroundings
to survive.
You should at least be on par with them
if you can't surpass them.
For goodness' sake!
I'm really not cut out for it!
I like convicting criminals. I hate
having to defend people so much.
Gosh, I absolutely hate it.
When I was about five or six years old,
I realized, I have to do things
I don't want to do at times in life.
That's when I learned it.
Goodness. Don't worry so much, Mr. Bang.
You get hammered down when you're prickly.
I'm trying to toughen him up.
Right?
But he'll never become rounded
no matter how much he gets beaten.
His consistency is so charming.
I am very consistent.
I despise you consistently.
Where are you going?
Isn't he so consistently mean?
Which one of you?
Gosh, you just hurt my feelings.
He's doing that a lot these days.
He's just lonely
from being an outcast for a long time.
He talks to the walls
because he has no one to talk to.
I never even run into the one
I miss so much,
but I keep bumping into my enemy
in this hallway.
What are you talking about?
You don't even get to come here often
because you have no clients.
I'm saying I see you whenever I'm here.
You have bad comprehension.
You're so...
You look so bad.
I get that you're broke,
but still, try to be presentable.
You have horrible sense of fashion.
My clothes are cheap, but so what?
My soul and body are so classy.
They can make up for everything.
Your heels are about to turn into flats.
I saw your heel dangling
when you were walking.
It's fixed.
Are we good now?
We sure are.
The CCTV footage from the scene
the prosecution submitted as evidence
can't be used to confirm
the identity of the defendant
due to its low resolution.
Also, seeing that no crucial evidence
such as
fingerprints or footprints
were found at the crime scene...
The defendant is guilty.
He is guilty, Your Honor.
You're saying that he's guilty?
Did I say that? You must be mistaken.
The defendant is not guilty.
He's innocent.
Next.
Case number 2017-G-66390.
How embarrassing.
The defendant admits to his mistake.
He has sincere regrets for what he did.
He also did his best to settle
with the victim,
and they succeeded in reaching
an agreement.
He has a family to take care of
and has no criminal records
of the same... Okay.
I'm sorry.
He has no...
He has no previous criminal record
of the same offense.
Please take that into account, Your Honor.
Mr. Ji?
It's been so long.
How are you, Ms. Eun?
Thanks to you, I'm still alive.
How have you been doing?
I'm also still alive, thanks to you.
You must've been peeking at Ji-uk.
Peeking?
-I was just looking.
-Hey.
Ji-uk's coming out now.
I'll be right back.
Hi, Ji-uk.
Gosh, you can at least say hello.
No.
I love you nonetheless.
I love you,
Ji-uk.
How pretty.
SHOE REPAIR
Hello, I'm Lawyer Eun Bong-hui
always available wherever you are.
Yes.
In 30 minutes?
Okay.
Okay. I'll see you in 30 minutes.
Sir, can I have my shoes back?
I just started repairing them.
I was loaded with work.
Here.
My goodness.
What should I do?
Should I wear these? No, I can't do that.
Okay.
Hey, Ji-hae.
Hey, Prosecutor Na.
Where did she suddenly come from?
Don't come near me.
What are you doing?
How pretty. Your size must be 240mm.
So?
-What?
-Here. Wear these. There you go.
Just think of this as a small payment...
for always being...
so mean to me.
My shoes are over there.
Sir, give her the repaired shoes.
-Who's going to pay?
-She'll pay.
Hey, you crazy wench!
I hope this client is a normal person.
I really hope so.
Please be a normal person.
Up until now, 90 percent of all my clients
were not normal.
I want to...
kill my husband.
But I don't know how.
I heard that you succeeded in...
killing your boyfriend.
There's so much evidence against you
of committing murder.
-How can I prove your innocence?
-I know you have your ways.
You know how to get away with murder.
I'm not a professional killer.
I met these kinds of people.
My gosh.
My goodness.
Let's put these away.
It's good, right?
So please let this one be a normal client.
EUN BONG-HUI LAW FIRM
Yes, come in.
I am...
a so-called stalker.
There was a woman I loved.
We both liked each other very much.
The story he told me from then on...
was very similar to mine.
Just like how I did,
he also fell in love at first sight.
Let's talk, Na-eun.
Don't ever show up again.
-Na-eun.
-Just like me...
-he also had to disappear.
-Hey!
But again, just like me,
he kept wandering around her,
and in the end...
I received a restraining order.
After that, I hadn't seen her
for a year and a half.
Then suddenly, two days ago...
It was really a coincidence.
We both pretended like we were strangers,
but it was so awkward.
So I thought it'd be okay to say hello.
Na-eun.
No.
It can't be a coincidence.
I'm sure...
it wasn't.
I admit that running into him
could be a coincidence.
I made sure that he didn't know
my place nor contact number.
But the fact that he got on the bus
cannot be a coincidental happening.
I'm sure of it.
I'm sure he was trying to stalk me...
in order to find out where I live...
and where I work.
COURT IN SESSION
Case number 2017-GD-22520.
Plaintiff, Jeon Seong-ho.
Defendant, Lee Na-eun.
PLAINTIFF, DEFENDANT
According to the medical report
that I've submitted,
Mr. Jeon injured his wrist that requires
eight weeks of medical treatment.
He also injured his ankle
which requires four weeks of treatment.
He asks for a compensation
regarding his medical fees,
loss of earnings, and
psychological damage.
The plaintiff had received
a restraining order.
This happened while he was in violation
of the given orders.
It means the plaintiff
was the cause of his own damage.
The defendant doesn't accept
the responsibility
for the plaintiff's injury.
Ergo, I ask that you dismiss
the monetary demand of the plaintiff.
After the restraining order was issued,
the plaintiff didn't stalk
the defendant even for a moment.
Their encounter on the bus
was pure coincidence.
There is no evidence
that it was a coincidental encounter.
Even if it was, isn't that
in violation of the restraining order?
Even if that's true,
it doesn't change the fact
that the defendant physically
harmed the plaintiff.
The defendant still doesn't have
the right to harm the plaintiff.
The defendant was
psychologically traumatized
due to the constant stalking.
Your Honor, pushing the plaintiff
can be seen as a self-defense mechanism.
Your Honor, when the plaintiff
stalked the defendant,
there wasn't a single incident
the plaintiff caused any physical harm.
Physical harm isn't
the only type of abuse.
Stalking itself means psychological
and emotional stress and abuse.
The plaintiff only...
observed the defendant from afar.
Don't you think it's too much...
to condemn it as an assault?
Why is he looking at me?
Unwanted attention is also
a form of abuse.
When someone whom I don't like
observes and tails me from afar,
the feelings of fright, anxiety,
and unpleasantness can't be understood...
by someone who hasn't had the experience.
Is this meant for me?
Due to the stalking, the defendant
was forced to move constantly.
The defendant also had to cut off ties
with most of her acquaintances.
She even had to give up her job
which she loved the most.
Bingo. This is about me.
Everything was...
her desperate attempt to escape
from the plaintiff.
As I have mentioned before,
it was a coincidence...
I knew it.
You knew that I was stalking you,
didn't you?
Everything you say...
is aimed at me under the pretext
of a trial, isn't it?
Plaintiff's counsel.
I was asking you
if it would be possible...
for you to settle this incident.
It was the defendant
who refused to settle.
The plaintiff, Jeon Seong-ho,
is willing to dismiss both criminal...
and civil cases if the defendant
makes a sincere apology.
The defendant has no intention
to face and apologize to the plaintiff.
With this opportunity--
You do not have to worry about that.
The plaintiff is currently preparing
to emigrate to another country.
If needed, I will submit documents
regarding this matter.
Good work.
Okay. Well, I will contact you
after I talk to my client.
All right. I'll get going.
The door is closing.
By the way, Prosecutor...
Hasn't it been so long
since we last met, Mr. Noh?
It hasn't been that long.
I saw you in court when you argued
that the defendant was guilty.
Right. You saw that.
By the way, why are you being so formal?
You used to call me by my name
and treat me casually.
You were my person back then.
That only lasted two months,
and I haven't seen you for two years.
It'd be weirder if I treated you casually
due to those two months.
It's not weird. It feels distant.
Of course, you should feel distant.
We are meant to be distant.
Oh, I see.
The door is opening.
Bye.
That way.
Let me say this again.
After the settlement agreement,
you can't ever ask Ms. Lee's contact
or approach her. Do you understand that?
Even after this settlement,
the restraining order and injunction
are still valid.
Don't worry, I won't do anything
that Na-eun doesn't like.
But you stalked her.
I just know how she feels
when I look at her.
Her outfit, hair,
and the look on her face.
From the first day we met, I knew
everything by looking at those.
So you don't need to worry.
Okay.
With this, it is settled
that the plaintiff will drop the lawsuit,
and the defendant will not press
charges or file a lawsuit
for the violation
of the restraining order.
Do both of you agree?
Yes.
Hey, I will call you later.
Are you going to be okay on your own?
I will be. Thank you, Mr. Noh.
I'm sorry to leave first.
Don't be. Please go.
Thank you for your work.
Sure.
Bye.
He didn't even say goodbye.
Make a U-turn right now.
Sir, please hurry.
Thank you for your work.
How could he smile?
It was the last time
he would see a girl he loves.
Even if it ended on good terms,
how could he smile?
Can that be possible?
The melody.
LAWYER EUN BONG-HUI
The number you have dialed
is not available at this moment.
Please.
If you tell me the address,
I can go by myself--
How can I...
I don't trust the plaintiff's counsel.
Okay, then. Excuse me.
It's just a bad feeling I have.
It's highly likely to be nothing.
What is your bad feeling based on?
The look on Mr. Jeon's face.
It wasn't a look someone would have
after letting his loved one go.
Also, small coincidences?
-Coincidences?
-For instance,
the melody before.
You are still obsessed with the melody.
It's not that.
I'm talking about the ringtone.
It's still fresh in my mind.
The song that played
on the very first day I met Na-eun.
In my opinion, perhaps,
Mr. Jeon Seong-ho might be mistaken...
that Ms. Lee Na-eun wore
the same outfit for him...
and chose the ringtone.
He might be thinking that
these are her signals for him.
I think he might be deluded.
I hope you are right.
JUNGNAM APARTMENT BUILDING A
I'll go in first. What's the address?
Unit 308 in Building A.
Okay.
Hey, Bong-hui.
Do not get involved
even if anything happens. Got it?
Okay.
You just talked casually to me.
Hey!
Na-eun.
I looked everywhere for you.
I missed you, Na-eun.
Na-eun, I know everything.
Come on out.
Na-eun, let's talk. Come out.
Open the door.
Na-eun.
Na-eun!
Lee Na-eun!
Na-eun.
Na-eun, open the door.
Come out, so that we can talk. Na-eun!
Na-eun!
Mr. Jeon!
What do you think you're doing?
Are you out of your mind?
You're...
Don't come closer.
Don't interfere, please.
Please don't get in my way!
Hey, Bong-hui.
Hold on.
Don't come closer.
Don't come.
I said, don't come closer!
A lawyer...
shouldn't beat up her client.
There he is.
-Is he the stalker?
-I guess so.
Please step back.
Move out of the way, please.
He looks completely normal.
Go on.
Hey.
Did everything get sorted out
on the scene?
Yes, almost.
How's Ms. Lee? Is she okay?
She's okay.
She's actually relieved
that things turned out like this.
I'm glad to hear that.
Here.
Thank you.
I...
I never thought about the possibility.
Mr. Jeon...
I mean, that scum. I can't believe
he's a complete psycho.
I thought he looked normal.
Don't beat yourself up too much.
You see,
those scums usually look
completely normal.
Still, I can't help beating myself up.
We could prevent a big mishap
thanks to you.
Thanks for saying that.
It's true.
Let's get up.
You need to give a witness statement.
Right.
By the way, do you realize
that you keep talking casually to me?
No.
Because you grabbed the bat,
-Ms. Lee...
-I told you I never hit her.
Why would I hit the woman I love?
You kept banging on her door--
I'm telling you I never did such things.
-Why did you pick up the bat...
-Did you see it? Did you?
That's the statement we got.
Don't you raise your voice at me.
Not being loved back by the one
you love is like torture.
But in a way,
being loved by someone
you don't want to be with...
and being forced to love
that person back...
could be a bigger torture.
What is the scope of love?
Where does it end,
and where does obsession begin?
And I...
-Why is the office in this area?
-At this moment,
between love and obsession,
where am I standing?
Physical harm isn't
the only type of abuse.
Stalking itself means psychological
and emotional stress and abuse.
Unwanted attention...
is also a form of abuse.
I would...
like to give myself a restraining order.
Arrived at the destination.
Ending voice navigation.
This is the address according
to the navigation. Is this it?
Sorry? Oh...
Yes, this is it.
Thank you for the ride.
I just don't want you to worry.
Other than for work-related things
or bumping into you unexpectedly,
I'll stay at least 100m away
from you at all times.
What exactly do you mean by that?
I literally meant what I said. And...
And?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I don't like you.
I may have looked like I do
since I feel grateful and indebted to you,
but don't worry or get the wrong idea.
I have no feelings for you whatsoever.
Really. I'm serious. Please believe me.
Drive safely.
Hey.
I couldn't even date him.
How many times do I have to get dumped?
"If you keep looking for me,
I'll find you first"?
PLEASE CALL THIS NUMBER
If you keep looking for me,
I'll find you first.
Someone was in my office.
It's you, isn't it?
Are you worrying about me now?
I came because you kept on begging,
but I don't know if I should.
Noh Ji-uk and Eun Bong-hui were together?
I keep getting this feeling...
annoyingly protective feeling
when it comes to Eun Bong-hui.
I'm going to go back
to my ex-boyfriend whom I betrayed.
Come back to me.
Come work with me,
Bong-hui.