[Adapted from the novel
Sweet Sixteen by Zi Yue]
[Sweet Sixteen]
[Episode 13]
I believe Mr. Qu
and your excellent partner
will be able to do it.
Otherwise, there will be no reason
for us to collaborate.
Okay.
Three days.
I wish you success then.
Excuse me,
Miss Annie.
Mr. Qu, you're here as I expected.
You've never changed
the way you do things.
I said what I needed to.
What else would we need to talk about?
I've made things clear.
Miss Annie, you've misunderstood.
Actually...
Did I let you sit?
In three days,
we'll give you the best proposal.
I heard you're about to get married.
I'm here to congratulate you.
Mr. Qu, have a seat.
You're indeed well-informed.
Are you planning
to prepare a big gift for me?
That's for sure.
Your fiance, Tang Xiaotian
is my best friend.
Really?
How close are you
that he's never mentioned you?
It's unavoidable that friends
have some misunderstandings.
I heard you like to drink strong liquor.
This bottle has
an 80 percent alcohol content.
You should try it.
Actually,
I don't have a problem
with your proposal.
You just don't like
our design director,
right?
I'll get straight to the point then.
If you replace her,
we can collaborate.
Thank you for your kind intentions.
However, I won't replace
our design director.
She's just a designer.
You don't have to
let her affect
such an important collaboration, right?
She's my wife.
We got married four years ago.
Your fallout with Xiaotian
was because of this?
Miss Annie,
I can assure you
the two of them are over.
You don't have
to worry about this at all.
I must give you some respect, then.
A gentle reminder.
It appears your wife
may have another suitor as well.
Thank you.
Do you not like this alcohol?
Why are you here?
Making sure I study?
It's your first day of school.
I have to come and reward you.
Let's go.
Alright, look here!
Eat.
This is your way
of rewarding me?
You want a feast?
Then you have to do well.
Step by step.
Our store's 18th anniversary!
20 percent off for couples
who take a photo.
Why don't you take part?
Sir,
you already know us.
Why not just give us the discount?
Just take the photo...
Alright, here!
Look here.
Three,
two,
one!
I'll do it.
You...
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I...
I've been eating light lately,
so I'm
craving something
more flavorful.
I'm full.
I'm going to work.
I'm going to be late.
Wait.
I need to go to the bookstore.
Can you give me a lift?
Be careful.
Bye.
Mr. Qu, how can I help you?
Nothing much.
You thought of a brand new proposal
within three days,
so I wanted to reward you with a meal.
No need.
This is my job.
Let's talk about Xia Mu.
Mr. Qu,
you forgot I don't drink?
Yawang,
four years ago,
you were willing to marry me
because of him.
Today,
you're willing to eat with me
because of him.
I'm curious
how far you're willing
to go for him.
♪SO RE MI♪
♪I can't help thinking♪
♪A happy or sad ending♪
♪Is up to us♪
♪Lovers are always forced to part♪
♪How dramatic♪
♪Doing my best to run to you♪
♪And our happy ending♪
♪If I can meet you again♪
♪And write this story again♪
♪I don't believe in fate♪
♪If I can hug you again♪
♪I don't care♪
♪About the bitter past♪
♪Let all our partings♪
♪Indifference and struggles♪
♪Return to when we met♪
♪As the crowd disappears♪
♪It's still you♪
♪Watching the sunset with me♪
♪If we start again♪
♪Can our ending be changed?♪