[Chae Jong Hyeok as Kim Min Joon]
[Seong Seung Ha as Choi Jin Hwan]
[Business as Usual]
Min Joon, are you okay?
Have you been sick?
I felt like I was coming down with the flu.
The flu?
I was worried because you never take a day off.
I just took a day off and got to rest.
Take good care of yourself.
[Choi Jin Hwan]Are you okay?
[Choi Jin Hwan]
I don't understand this part, Min Joon.
How should I take it from here?
Just check for typos again and...
- Okay.
- And...
The next sentence is...
I think it's fine.
Should I check again from here?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Thank you. I think I understand now.
I'm glad.
Min Joon,
you went to the same school as Jin Hwan, right?
He must've been really popular.
I guess he was.
Right?
- See you at the meeting later.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- Right?
- The true identity...
That's why it's important.
Including what you found,
we can connect them and finish it like this.
I think that'd be nice.
The checklist. Your Crush Checklist.
I love that.
We need to go to the meeting.
And please check the message.
It's work-related.
See you later.
You seem busy.
Our company does exploit people like dogs.
I heard you work here.
You heard I work here?
I wasn't exactly asking around.
Woo Hyeok mentioned it to me.
- Choi Woo Hyeok?
- Yeah.
He knows what I'm up to. Interesting.
You studied abroad, did you say?
Yes.
I was a bit lost there.
Anyway, you can say stuff like that now.
What do you mean?
Voicing displeasure.
I need to say what I have to say.
I suppose.
It must've been tiring to adjust.
It is tiring.
Good work.
What do you mean?
You must've worked so hard.
You've forced yourself to
behave this way so effortlessly and got used to it.
You're early.
Here's coffee.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Thank you. I'll enjoy it.
Yes, enjoy.
Here's the concept of the Dating Manual.
It's a simulation game with
the 2000s Y2K sensibility.
You play it by choosing from different options.
There's a strategy guide, too.
The story in each part will be
explained by a friendly NPC.
The next table of contents
is like a game tutorial, as you can see.
The artist sent a few concept references.
So, I added them here.
Do you have any questions?
[Table of Contents]
[First loves never work out]
[Does dating life come with a manual?]
Do you think dating life has a manual?
I'm not sure.
People who struggle with dating
could certainly use a guide.
I do believe that.
Because I dated submissively myself.
[Episode 2: Min Joon's Submissive Dating]
Some students think
this class is easy because of what the seniors said.
It's actually true.
But I'll give you
small and pesky assignments weekly.
This is an orientation, but there is an assignment.
Write about what you wanted to do
as a college student when you were in 12th grade.
I guess you can say what you "dreamed" about.
That's what I mean.
You have to date in college.
- A campus romance.
- Become a singer.
- Drinking. Drinking.
- Drinking?
A campus romance for you.
A campus romance...
[My dream - Taking a class with someone I like]
Taking a class with someone I like.
That's it for today.
We'll start the class next week.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Wait for me.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Are you alone?
Well, yes.
Your first time here?
Would you like to drink with me?
Well, I haven't ordered a drink.
It's okay.
A glass, please.
Bottoms up.
You're very handsome.
Thank you.
Even more so when you smile.
I ran out of liquor.
Well, let me buy one.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I'll order the same one, then.
- Okay.
We'll have another bottle.
Thank you.
Hey, what's this?
You ordered a fancy one.
Good work. Good work.
Hey, give me some.
Give me your glass.
[Total 250,000 won]
Wow, it looks amazing.
How did it go?
Gosh, of course, he's handsome.
Cheers.
I've always been the underdog.
He and Ha Neul broke up.
Did you get dumped? What's with you?
I heard she cheated!
I don't know yet, I said.
You got dumped? Really?
Daebak.
Don't bring her up anymore.
But it's too fun.
You can't bring her up anymore with me.
Hey, but it's too fun.
Don't you think you're better off?
Yes, you got duped.
That's it for today.
See you next class.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
Thank you.
By the way, your facial expression earlier...
Pardon? Me?
Yes, you.
You had the same expression earlier, too.
Pardon?
On the bridge earlier.
You disappeared quickly as if you were sick.
Oh, then?
Yes, I was in a hurry.
You didn't run away because of the eye contact?
I'm kidding.
Sophomore? Or a freshman?
- Yes.
- We're the same age.
Can I speak casually?
Yes.
If so...
Give me your phone number.
I'm Choi Jin Hwan.
And you?
I'm Kim Min Joon.
Your name fits how you look.
How I look?
It's pretty, I mean.
I actually saw you recently.
I saw you hitting your head on a table.
At a bar.
You were cute then, too.
What's so cute, anyway-
The way you're acting now.
I'll go to the next lecture, then.
Okay. See you.
I'll be in touch.
[Choi Jin Hwan]
Min Joon, what are you up to?
I'm going home now.
How about you?
Huh? Jin Hwan.
Let's go to the club, I said.
I don't want to.
You always say no these days.
Why do you hate clubbing?
No one goes to pick-up bars anymore.
A pick-up bar is better.
It's bright in pick-up bars.
You're better off somewhere dark.
What are you saying?
Let's eat.
Seriously, you don't get it.
Ask Choi Jin Hwan later, then.
What's taking him so long?
Guys, look.
Isn't the sky* so pretty today?
(Sky is "haneul" in Korean)
Geez, what are you doing?
Don't do that.
I'm just saying the sky is pretty. Why?
Look at the sky.
The sky does look pretty.
- Shit.
- Hey, hey.
Let's leave Choi Jin Hwan.
Let's go on our own.
You'll find someone prettier than Ha Neul.
The wind feels nice.
It is.
I love weather like this.
It clears your mind.
Let me have a bite of the sausage.
- I don't want to.
- Just a bite.
I said I don't want to.
Give me some. Who bought you that?
- You should've-
- It was me, wasn't it?
- I don't want to.
- Just a bite.
[Woo Hyeok]
Aren't you picking up?
I'm sure it's not important. I can call back later.
Hello?
Kim Min Joon, you're with Choi Jin Hwan, right?
Well, yes.
I need to talk to him, but I can't reach him.
Tell him to answer my call.
Should I put him on the phone?
No, I'll call his phone.
I'll go when I feel like it.
Don't they have homework?
They always want me to go out.
Guys are flipping out since you aren't coming.
Just show up briefly.
You ran away earlier, too.
You can go see them.
You seem close to your friends.
It's nice, and I'm envious, too.
Really? Want to come with me, then?
No. Not really.
I'm not close to them.
Come on. Who cares?
You're friends once you know their names and faces.
I won't go, either.
Let's go, then.
Really?
Okay, let's go together.
Don't say what you don't mean.
Choi Jin Hwan, I haven't seen you lately.
You came because Woo Hyeok called.
I brought my Min Joon today.
Hi, Min Joon.
Hi.
Your Min Joon?
You hurt my feelings.
Kim Min Joon, don't trust Choi Jin Hwan.
He'll betray you later.
What do you mean?
Min Joon is different than you guys.
What's wrong with us?
We can't pick up girls without you, Choi Jin Hwan.
We lost a few already. You'd better take care of it.
Why would I? Just be grateful I came.
Here you go flipping out again.
Hey, hey, hey, daebak.
What do you think of them?
Pretty good.
Jin Hwan, come with me.
They're so-so.
Help us, please.
I don't want to. What a hassle.
Woo Hyeok, how about you?
Huh?
He's prettier than me.
What's this about?
I'll tell you later.
- Going or not?
We still got it.
- Let's go.
- Still!
- Got it!
- Cross!
I was right, wasn't I?
They bother me so much.
What's this?
You're sitting so closely.
Don't answer, Min Joon.
He's not worth it.
What?
Ditch him and join me, Min Joon.
Let's have a drink.
Give me a break.
It's my loss to be nice to you.
Are you jealous right now? Choi Woo Hyeok is?
I'm not jealous. I'm telling the truth.
Are you jealous, my Woo Hyeok?
Stop pretending. It's annoying.
Are you really jealous?
- I said I'm not.
- You are. You are.
Come on.
Geez.
I can't calm down.
Why?
They all have boyfriends.
Why hang out at a place like this, then?
Hey, let's just drink among us. Let drink.
Okay, let's drink.
- Let's drink.
I'll never date anyone like Park Ha Neul anymore.
Gosh, don't even talk about that.
What kind of type will you date, then?
Hey.
What are you saying?
Someone with long, straight hair and fair skin.
Fair skin?
A bookworm type. A pretty girl. That's what I want.
Studious. That's the ticket.
I like a sweet bookworm type.
Hey, Kim Min Joon.
What type do you want to date?
Huh? I'm not sure.
"I'm not sure" isn't good.
- Let's drink.
[Choi Jin Hwan]
What's your relationship with Choi Woo Hyeok?
How to tell if someone's leading you on.
They try to touch you from the beginning.
They might be after something else.
If they don't call when they're with friends,
it means you aren't as important.
Check if they're only nice to you.
If they're nice to everyone,
you might not be special to them.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I've changed since then.
I just need to focus on my job now.
Get it together.
Min Joon.
Message me with work-related stuff.
Give me your number, then.
My number?
I wanted you to give it to me.
You changed your number.
We work together now.
Let's get along.
I'll be in touch.
His number hasn't changed.
Min Joon, you're still here?
No. I have stuff left to do.
Stop working overtime and go on dates instead.
Okay.
I'm going on a date.
Work hard.
Okay, see you.
See you.
[Choi Jin Hwan]
Hello?
Do you have plans afterward?
Let's grab a bite.
We reunited after eight years.
Can I be free from...
my sick and tired first love, Choi Jin Hwan?
♫ I'll be standing right here ♫
♫ I hope tonight isn't too late ♫
♫ The smile you gave me while looking at me ♫
♫ I'll be standing right here, so you can find me anytime ♫
[Epilogue]
What are they doing outside?
Are they dating or something?
Bullshit. They're friends. Come on.
Hey, Min Joon might actually believe you.
But there's definitely something going on.
They never said so, but they've been
close for a long time.
Since mysterious Choi Jin Hwan treats him like that,
their relationship must be special.
It must be this!
Isn't he the rich boy, Choi Jin Hwan's
arranged partner or something?
Don't think so. You scared me!
♫ So you can find me anytime ♫
[Business as Usual]
Have you been well?
Of course, I have.
Are you seeing someone?
Not really.
I don't want to, either.
Why not?
Anyway, that's a relief.
- It's not funny. Stop.
- Stop what?
Smiling and sounding me out like that.
It's not funny.
I'm not sure.
Isn't that your specialty?
What are you so unhappy about?
You must've come for a reason.
You think I came to sleep with you?
Just spit it out.
We have a lot to say about our relationship.
What relationship?
Excuse me, it's been eight years.
Everything changed already, Choi Jin Hwan.
You're good at talking now.
Why were you like that then if you can speak up?
What are you talking about?
Make yourself clear.
Let me ask you this time.
Did you even like me?
Choi Jin Hwan, get your facts straight.
You're the one who took advantage of me.