Lu Qi, Yang Zhenzhong, Zhang Kai.
Actually,
compared to a calm and peaceful relationship,
I prefer intense love.
Only through intensity
can I feel truly loved.
You know perfectly well
that I can give you everything you want,
don't you?
Your father is a powerful figure in the music industry.
Your connections are extensive.
But I
am content with my current life.
I have a happy family
and an adorable daughter.
Is that so?
You didn't mention having a virtuous wife.
Do you ever get the feeling
that your daughter is like a bottomless pit
that will drain all your savings?
Think about it.
Honey.
The awards at this art festival seem quite prestigious.
I'm definitely going to win a prize.
You're so confident.
But I believe in your abilities.
By the way,
you mentioned you were under a lot of stress.
Can you tell me why?
Your daughter is like a bottomless pit
that will drain all your savings.
You fell asleep in the music room again.
What is real,
what is fake?
Xiaoting.
Sister Yazhi,
you're awake.
Where's Yiyi?
She went to school.
What about Chen Mo?
Teacher Chen went to work too.
How are you feeling?
Did you sleep well last night?
Did you have nightmares again?
I'm fine.
Sister Yazhi,
I made breakfast
and I'll get you a bowl.
Sounds good.
Yazhi.
Teacher Chen repeatedly reminded me
to remind you to take your medicine on time.
I already took it this morning.
May I ask you something personal?
How long have you been like this?
For quite a while now.
When I was in school,
I tutored at a lady's house.
She was also a housewife
who stayed home alone every day
without anyone to talk to.
After a few years,
she developed depression.
Later,
I started visiting her regularly just to chat.
At first
I was just talking non-stop
and she wouldn't respond.
She gradually started telling me about herself.
Back and forth like this,
her emotional knots began to unravel.
And guess what happened next?
Her depression was completely cured.
Housewives
are prone to depression.
Yazhi,
if you have anything troubling you,
you can talk to me about it,
I've got nothing but time anyway.
Enjoy your meal.
I want to see how long you can keep up this act.
I wasn't always like this.
Before I got married,
I was an OB-GYN at the hospital.
One of my patients,
suddenly had severe hemorrhaging.
How is she, Doctor?
She lost the baby,
and probably won't be able to conceive again.
A classic case of drug-induced miscarriage.
Yazhi.
I'm sorry,
it's not your fault.
Yazhi.
Since then,
I've been traumatized.
And after giving birth to Yiyi,
I had postpartum depression
and never really recovered from it.
So what happened next?
What happened to that pregnant woman?
I never saw her again.
It's like she vanished into thin air.
It's been seven years now.
But recently,
I've been having this strange feeling.
I keep feeling like she's back,
like she's right beside me.
How do I explain it...
It's like
someone is watching me.
It's all in your head.
Dr. Chen already told you
that you're just imagining things.
Stop thinking about all this.
Think about something positive.
For instance,
Yiyi hasn't wet her bed for several days now.
Not once yesterday.
The electrical therapy device is working after all.
I've never told anyone about this before.
This matter
has been weighing on my heart like a stone,
making it hard for me to breathe.
But after talking to you today,
I feel much more relieved.
Oh, Xiaoting,
would you come with me to pick up Yiyi today?
I'd like to get out for a while.
Sure.
By the way.
You seem to feel like someone's watching you.
Actually,
I feel the same way.
I remember
there was a woman.
It's happened several times.
Acting all suspicious.
Where did you see her?
At the school gate,
when I was picking up Yiyi after school.
She was standing not far away.
This woman is strange,
she wasn't there to pick up any child.
She was just in the corner staring at me.
Staring at me the whole time.
It hasn't just happened once or twice.
Did you see what she looks like?
What does she look like?
She has a pointed face.
She was wearing a mask and a hat.
Yiyi.
Why is this child's face red?
Mom, you don't understand art,
this is a dead child.
Why would Yiyi draw a dead child?
Mom,
would you kill me?
Yiyi.
What are you talking about?
Mommy loves
you and your daddy more than anyone else.
Mommy won't let anyone hurt you.
Mom,
have you ever killed children?
Who told you that?
You did, Mom.
I
never said that.
I have never killed any children.
Never.
Mom.
Have you ever killed a child?
Would you kill me?
I've never killed a child.