Lu Qi, Yang Zhenzhong, Zhang Kai.
Honey.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
You're back so early today.
I'm tired.
I skipped one lap.
Just finished showering.
Right.
Use your knife and fork.
Sit up straight when eating.
Got it?
Honey, what's wrong?
Honey.
Are you feeling unwell?
No, I'm fine.
I might have a bit of low blood sugar.
I'll feel better after I eat something.
Thank you.
Coffee will be ready soon.
Those two
seem like they've known each other before.
Xiaoting,
where's your food?
I can just eat in the kitchen.
Come sit down and eat with us,
don't be shy.
Yeah,
don't be so formal.
Bring your food and join us.
Here, let Daddy help you.
Let me explain your job duties.
You'll take Yiyi to school every day
using my car.
I happen to be free these next couple of days,
so I can go with you
and show you the routes.
Honey,
you should just rest.
I'll go with them.
After school today, Yiyi has
a one-hour English class.
On Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays, after English class,
take her directly to horseback riding lessons.
On Tuesdays and Thursdays, she has gymnastics in the evening,
and you can rest on weekends.
Yiyi has neurogenic urinary incontinence,
so make sure she brings her electrotherapy device with her.
Don't worry.
You two go ahead and eat.
I'm going to take a shower.
Why do I always feel so uneasy?
Why are my slippers wet?
Honey,
Tingting and I are taking Yiyi to school.
Okay,
be careful
and come home early.
Will do.
Strange,
why isn't he leaving?
Is he waiting for her here?
Get in.
Let's go!
Hurry, let's go, quick!
You don't like it?
No, I don't.
Yazhi isn't doing well emotionally,
you're taking such meticulous care of her,
don't you...
What can you give me?
And what can I give you?
Are you afraid I'll cling to you,
or do you think I'm not good enough?
Get out.
That's it.
I was overthinking.
Let's go back.
Sis.
I actually think you should
worry more about those female clients at your brother-in-law's studio.
Last time I passed by his studio,
all the women coming out were both rich and beautiful.
Sis,
what exactly does his healing studio do?
They say it's some kind of psychological healing,
but I don't know the details.
A therapist?
Something like that.
Chen Mo says music therapy can soothe the nerves
and relieve stress.
I doubt that
they're just using music therapy as a cover,
who knows what they're really up to.
I'm sorry,
I just took a phone call.
Why does he look so similar to Li Meng?
Could it be...
Chen Qingyu.
Director of Avex Listed Group,
emotional anxiety,
chronic insomnia.
Chen Qingyu.
Let's begin.
I don't know why,
but I always feel that Mu Xiaoting
resembles someone I know.
Who's there?