Lu Qi, Yang Zhenzhong, Zhang Kai.
Qi, Yang Zhenzhong, Zhang Kai.
She's right here.
Stop it.
It's fine.
I've hypnotized her.
She won't wake up anytime soon.
Professor Chen,
you're so devoted.
Even when she's this sick,
you still take such good care of her.
Of course.
Without her,
how could I have such a good life?
But she's about to...
What?
Are you going to kill her?
Chen Mo.
What are you doing?
What are you all doing?
Honey,
what's wrong?
You bastard!
Honey.
Honey, what did I do?
Where are they?
Where did you hide them?
No.
You're dreaming.
Are you dreaming, honey?
There's nobody.
You're dreaming, honey.
I don't believe you.
What are they doing?
Honey.
There's no one here,
honey.
Honey.
Calm down.
What's wrong, honey?
Honey.
Impossible.
Mr. Chen.
You still have a long way to go.
Not to mention you don't understand your clients well enough.
Teacher Chen,
I'm sorry,
I've failed again.
You know I'm afraid of cold,
so you created a scene with heavy snow
by a fireplace.
But you didn't consider that
someone who truly fears the cold
would never want to live in such a place.
I'd rather be lying on a beach in Bali.
More than this,
I prefer the sound of ocean waves.
Keep trying.
I'm sorry,
but why does your piano music
make customers feel so relaxed?
My music can be tailored for each customer.
Can you do that?
Mengjie,
our studio focuses on music therapy.
But you
want to be a hypnotist.
What's the difference?
They're completely different.
Yiyi.
Why are you here all alone?
Would you like Mommy to play with you?
Yiyi.
Come here.
Let's not play with kids who are jealous of us, okay?
Let's go.
Off we go.
Taking off now!
Coming!
Who is it?
I finally found you.
Xiaoting.
Who are you looking for?
Hello,
may I ask who you're looking for?
there's a new swimming pool that just opened nearby.
Are you interested in swimming?
Not at the moment,
sorry about that.
Xiaoting,
close the door.
Two days,
100,000 yuan,
I promise they won't know.
Then I'll get straight to the point.
I want to borrow 100,000 yuan from you.
I'll transfer it to you after signing.
After this, find an excuse to resign from my wife's company.
I don't want to see you again.
You don't think I'm blackmailing you, do you?
You might have misunderstood.
I'm just borrowing.
It doesn't matter.
If you need money,
consider it my help.
If this is blackmail,
I hope this money will make it go away.
I love my wife very much,
and don't want to complicate things.
Is it possible
that I just couldn't control myself?
Who says only men have desires?
You're so perfect,
standing naked in the bathroom in the morning,
water droplets on your abs,
what woman could resist?
It's okay,
I'll pay you back,
worst case, take it from my nanny salary.
Why was Meng Xiaoting coming out of Chen Mo's office?
What was she doing here?
Li Meng.