We were just passing by
and heard quite a commotion inside.
Who was it that spoke of evident filial piety?
Your Majesty,
Consort Su mentioned to this servant...
that the Empress Dowager once praised the Late Empress in tender-leaf yellow,
calling it dignified and elegant.
That is true.
Today, Noble Consort Meng and...
Consort Su...
are both wearing this color.
It is a gesture of respect for the Empress Dowager...
and remembrance of the Late Empress.
Your Majesty,
it is not as she says.
The Empress Dowager interfered in politics...
and was unworthy of her position.
Your servant holds no respect for her whatsoever.
Then it seems...
you have no respect for the Empress Dowager,
nor any remembrance for the Late Empress.
Your servant...
Your servant did not mean that either.
Then what did you mean?
I...
Your Majesty,
your servant is indeed mourning the Late Empress.
Then...
what of the Empress Dowager?
Your Majesty is wise.
The Empress Dowager's merits and faults are for Your Majesty to judge.
Consort Su dares not discuss them rashly.
She merely observes the etiquette of a consort...
and maintains a heart of filial piety.
Your Majesty,
today is the Empress Dowager's posthumous birthday.
Noble Consort Meng and Consort Su speak only of filial piety.
The harem must not interfere in politics;
the imperial consorts keep this firmly in mind.
You...
Raise your head.
You are quite bold.
You dare protect your master like this before Us?
This servant is terrified.
This servant protects Your Majesty's divine prestige...
your benevolence, filial piety, and generosity...
and your virtue that wins over the masses.
What a sharp tongue.
You are even flattering Us now.
Enough.
The Empress Dowager's burial in the Imperial Tombs was Our decree...
and the Late Empress's dying wish.
Do not discuss it rashly in the future.
Your servant obeys the decree.
He actually buried the Empress Dowager in the Imperial Tombs,
and claimed it was my dying wish.
You have done a fine job.
Causing This one to lose all face.
My Lady, this fabric was... Feng Qing...
it was Feng Qing who prepared it.
She knows people at the Bureau of Imperial Attire, so...
Sister Bi Hen,
I only embroidered the patterns on this dress.
It was clearly you who had the Bureau of Imperial Attire prepare it.
My Lady,
many servants can testify to this.
This servant heard Sister Bi Hen say with her own mouth...
that this tender-leaf yellow palace dress...
was specially prepared by her.
This servant... this servant heard it too.
You witch!
You dare to set me up?
When have I ever suffered such humiliation?
Keeping your worthless life...
how can it quell the hatred in my heart?
Guards!
Get this lowly servant out of my sight.
My Lady!
My Lady, spare me! My Lady!
My Lady, spare me!
My Lady!
Even if Sister Bi Hen is at fault,
she blundered only out of loyalty.
If she dies, you can replace her.
Yet now you speak for her.
It seems you are not only loyal...
but also lack ambition.
This servant only seeks to serve My Lady.
Remember well the taste of today.
If there is another mistake,
do not blame me for showing no mercy.
Thank you, My Lady.
Thank you, Sister Feng Qing.
Today, Feng Qing loyally protected her master.
Reward her heavily.
In the future, she may serve as a personal attendant.
Consort Su
In that great fire,
what role did you actually play?
My Lady, are you feeling unwell somewhere?
Thinking back on today's events, I still feel shaken.
Imperial Noble Consort Wan is just a paper tiger.
She cannot handle Noble Consort Meng at all.
Please calm down, My Lady.
Within the palace, no flower blooms for a hundred days.
If Noble Consort Meng stumbles one day,
everyone will push the wall as it falls.
That is true.
The Late Empress was a model for the realm,
yet didn't she also turn to ash in a fire?
There are no evergreens in this harem.
If the Late Empress were still alive,
Noble Consort Meng would not dare to be so impudent.
The Late Empress was very strict in the past,
but she was always even-handed in her dealings.
When she was in the harem,
Consort Cao and Noble Consort Meng were actually well-behaved.
My Lady, you were startled today.
I heard
that you have a type of incense from the Western Regions here.
It is especially good for calming the mind and spirit.
Why don't this servant find it and light it
to help you relax?
Western Regions Calming Incense?
Very well.
Go take it from the shelf and light it.
It is the very incense from the mourning hall that day.
This Western Regions Calming Incense
is vastly different from ordinary incense.
It must be extremely rare and precious, right?
Others may view it as a treasure,
but for my Su family,
it is just a common item used to bribe the various palaces.
I award the remaining half-packet to you.
Thank you for your grace, My Lady.
You may withdraw.
She seems to bear no ill will toward this one.
This calming incense
was also casually gifted to others by her.
It seems I must find another way to test her.
Sister, you are now My Lady's personal maid.
Let us do these chores.
Good sister,
when you served My Lady yesterday,
did she mention me?
My Lady was just angered by Noble Consort Meng,
so she took it out on you, Sister.
She also said,
"If the Late Empress were still here,
how could Noble Consort Meng be so impudent?"
My Lady always wanted to seek protection
from the Late Empress.
She even specially crafted a solid gold ruyi scepter,
intending to present it on the Empress's birthday.
But who would have thought,
the Empress would pass away so unexpectedly.
This one's birthday had not yet arrived,
yet she had already prepared a birthday gift.
The person who engineered the fire
should not be Consort Su.
Sister, you have suffered.
I thought
My Lady treated you differently,
that it wouldn't be like with Wen Tang.
How do you know about Wen Tang too?
It was her bad luck.
When combing My Lady's hair,
she accidentally pulled out some strands.
In a fit of rage, My Lady
stabbed a hairpin into her neck.
Are the lives of servants worth no more than grass?
Isn't that the truth?
We have to keep the masters happy.
How about this,
I will go pick some crabapple flowers
to make rouge for My Lady.
You go pick some peach blossoms too, alright?
I'm off then.
Wen Tang died a tragic death,
just because she combed out a few strands of her hair.
Su Dai, you treat human life like grass.
This one will surely seek justice for Wen Tang.
Halt.
This servant greets Your Majesty.
Blessings to Your Majesty.
We remember you.
The loyal one who spoke up for Consort Su.
What are you doing here?
This servant came to collect peach petals for rouge.
How dare you!
Your Majesty has decreed...
...picking from this peach tree is forbidden.
Violators receive thirty strokes of the cane.
Let's see what you have to say this time.
This servant could never bear to pick flowers.
I came here only to wait for the wind.
To gather some fallen petals.
You actually still have an excuse.
Sophistry.
Flowers bloom and fade in their own time.
The beginning and end of a bond is beyond our control.
This servant does not pick flowers...
...because I cannot bear to disturb...
...this already fleeting blooming season.
Do not pick it.
Flowers bloom and fade in their own time.
Why must you pluck them?
When the wind blows,
the fallen petals are just as beautiful.
You may withdraw.
This servant takes her leave.
The beginning and end of a bond is beyond our control.
Could it be that our bond ends here?
This endgame...
Is there no one left to solve it for We?
Excuse me, sister.
Is Feng Qing here?
Feng Qing has gone to serve as a maid in Consort Su's palace.
What?
She went to Yongfu Palace.
My Lord, if you have urgent business with Feng Qing...
I can pass on a message for you.
She seems to have a close relationship with Feng Qing.
The matter Feng Qing asked you to investigate...
Is there a result?
She hasn't asked me to investigate anything.
You are lying.
What do you know?
I... I don't know anything.
Don't come any closer.
Speak.
Tell me everything you know.
Lord Gu, how imposing you are.
Bullying a weak woman.
Without a shred of grace or dignity.
What is this scar about?
It seems when you asked me for medicine,
you were hiding something from me.
Have you considered the consequences?
I can explain this matter.
Lord Gu, do not involve the innocent.
Wen Xin, you go out first.
Tell me, what have you found out?
He questions so unscrupulously.
If he learns the truth,
I fear he will do something even more dangerous.
I haven't found anything yet.
Nothing?
Please believe me, Lord Gu.
Give me a little more time.
You have already wasted one chance
to make me trust you.
If you find nothing,
her life will pay the price.
A healer's blade...
...should protect the people.
Lord Gu, as a healer,
how can you use a blade meant for saving lives
to harm people?
A healer's blade...
...should protect the people.
A-Xuan, remember this.
A healer holds a blade to save people,
not to harm them.
I want results within three days.
Otherwise,
I will no longer leave any room
for someone unworthy of trust.
I'm sorry.
I got you involved.
It's okay.
I wasn't really hurt.
How did you provoke him?
It's a long story.
If you meet him in the future,
you must stay far away.
Feng Qing, you came to find me so late.
Is something the matter?
Regarding your sister Wen Tang...
I have asked around for you.
Just for messing up a few strands of hair,
she had to pay with her life.
She was only sixteen.
Su Dai has a violent temper.
She takes her anger out on others at the slightest provocation.
I will make her pay the price.
She will reap what she sows.
Thank you for helping me so much.
From now on, no matter what happens,
I will listen to you.
About the matching outfits...
His Majesty didn't even pursue it.
On what grounds did Noble Consort Meng withdraw my name tag?
His Majesty is busy with state affairs.
I tried so hard last month to get him to stay the night once.
Now with this situation,
His Majesty will remember me even less.
My Lady, do not be anxious.
This servant has a plan.
It can win His Majesty's favor for you, My Lady.
What method do you have?
In this servant's opinion,
you might as well
cater to his preferences.