=Glory Back=
=Episode 10=
Feng Qing, is this velvet flower hairpin
on the ground yours?
I only wore one today. This isn't mine.
It must be someone else's.
I'll ask around.
Do you need any help here?
I'm all done. Thank you.
Su, your complexion looks wonderful.
It must be a strong little prince
growing in your belly.
Our Jingya has been longing
for a little brother.
How kind of you both to say. Thank you.
His Majesty said yesterday too,
it looks like a little prince.
My lady, it's done.
I had this soup simmered for four hours.
It's best eaten before it's cold.
My lady, wait!
The soup is a bit hot.
Be cautious with anything
you put in your mouth.
Your people are truly meticulous.
(Saffron isn't poison.
How could a silver needle detect it?)
(Once something happens to Su,
Feng Qing, you will take the blame.)
Cao, the tangerine peel in this soup
is 10-year-old second-grade peel?
It's a bit bitter.
At home, I always used first-grade peel.
It makes the soup sweeter.
Su, you were indeed raised
in a wealthy merchant family.
What a discerning palate you have.
I have some 20-year-old first-grade peel
gifted by His Majesty.
I'll have some sent to you tomorrow.
How thoughtful of you.
Thank you, Your Majesty
and Noble Concubine Meng.
Your Majesty, the chrysanthemums
in the garden are blooming beautifully.
Shall I accompany you to see them?
Very well.
(Hualin Garden)
My lady, these flowers
are truly beautiful.
Let's go look over there.
Didn't you say the soup would give
her unbearable abdominal pain?
Why hasn't Su Dai shown any discomfort?
I find it strange too.
Caiping personally put
the saffron into the soup bowl.
And I saw Su eat
that soup with my own eyes.
Useless!
Fortunately, I have another plan.
Find an excuse to take
her over to the rockery.
My lady, you intend
for her to have an accident there?
Su now enjoys
His Majesty's special favor.
And she has
that clever Feng Qing by her side.
If we don't act amidst the chaos today,
we'll never get another good chance.
But...
If Su doesn't have an accident today,
tomorrow, it will be
your entire family that suffers.
Yes.
(If she miscarries from bad soup,
I can still pin the blame on Feng Qing.)
(But if I lure her to the rockery,)
(I can't distance myself from it.)
These flowers are pretty.
(If Su has an accidental miscarriage,)
(I need someone of high rank
to share the blame with me.)
De, I hear the scenery
by the rockery is quite nice.
Shall we go for a stroll there?
Alright.
My lady, Princess Jingya
has an upset stomach.
Sorry, I must hurry back
to check on her.
(Seems I need another plan.)
(I can only lead Junior Concubine Su
to the rockery and leave immediately.)
Your Majesty.
Is the banquet up to your standards?
Very good.
Bihen, stay close to me later.
Feng Qing, stay here and keep watch.
As soon as I shout loudly,
say I've had an accident
to draw His Majesty over.
Follow our plan.
Yes.
You two, go see if the chrysanthemums
over there have bloomed.
Cao, where are you heading?
I thought I'd take
a stroll by the rockery.
Perfect, I wanted to go too.
Let's go together.
(Excellent! She's going there
of her own accord.)
(Everyone harbors their own schemes.
The drama is about to begin.)
Look, how beautiful
the chrysanthemums are this year.
(It seems Yingzhu plans
to use the black cat to frighten her)
(to make her fall
and tumble down the slope.)
What are you thinking about?
That you will soon lose your position
as head of Yongfu Palace?
Well...
Once my child is born,
it will be my turn.
You're quite the braggart.
Don't choke on those big words.
When the time comes, I'll repay you
for all your care
over the years bit by bit.
If you want to beg for mercy then,
start practicing sweet talk now.
Don't celebrate too soon.
It's still uncertain
who will have the last laugh.
Your Majesty.
Shall we go take a look
at the dark chrysanthemum?
Alright.
Su.
What's wrong?
I've twisted my ankle.
(Her ankle is sprained?)
My lady!
(Perfect, just leave
her here by herself.)
(I'll be completely in the clear.)
Your mistress has sprained her ankle.
Quickly help her over
to the rockery to rest.
I'll go fetch a physician
right now. Hurry, hurry!
Yes. My lady.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, Junior Concubine Su
has twisted her ankle.
Could you go see her?
Take me there quickly.
Yes.
(It's just a twisted ankle?)
(Why has His Majesty come?)
Hurry up! His Majesty is coming!
My lady!
What's wrong?
It hurts! It hurts so much!
My child!
Physician! Summon a physician quickly!
Yes.
How did you fall, Su?
Your Majesty, save our child!
Why are the bees swarming around you?
The handkerchief! The scented powder
on it attracted the bees.
Cao gave me this handkerchief!
I...
Why would you harm me like this?
I didn't! I didn't do it!
Your Majesty, I am innocent!
(The drama begins.)
Well?
Your Majesty,
sorry, but I failed
to preserve the imperial baby.
Cao! How cruel you are!
Why did you cause me
to fall and miscarry?
(I need to create
a diversion to clear my name.)
(That's right! There was saffron
in that bowl of soup.)
How can we be sure Su's miscarriage
was solely caused by her fall?
What if she ate something
she shouldn't have?
I am innocent, Your Majesty.
I beg you to see the truth.
Physician Chen, did you
examine her carefully for me?
In my opinion,
an ordinary fall leading to miscarriage
shouldn't cause severe hemorrhaging.
It could be due to something she ate.
At today's banquet, I only ate
the warm soup prepared by Cao.
I never once left my seat at that time.
If something's wrong,
it's Su's maid who served the soup!
White is white.
Black is black.
I'm completely innocent.
Doubt the soup? Then have it tested.
Your Majesty, the pot of soup
Concubine Cao prepared today
and the bowl Junior Concubine Su had
have both been brought here.
Well?
Your Majesty,
the soup prepared by Concubine Cao
shows no abnormalities.
And the bowl she ate?
My lady, Junior Concubine Su's soup bowl
also shows no issues.
Both bowls show no irregularities.
(Concubine Cao, you had
Caiping drug the soup.)
(And you wanted me to take the blame.)
(Did you really think
I'd let you succeed?)
(Caiping must have tampered
with the soup just now.)
(Luckily, I had Chief Li come here
in advance to cooperate.)
Your Majesty.
The physician just confirmed
there was no issue with the soup.
The one who caused my miscarriage
is Concubine Cao!
Your Majesty, please see clearly.
I am truly innocent!
How would I dare to harm
the imperial child in front of everyone?
Your Majesty, harming
the imperial child is a capital offense.
She'd never do such a thing.
Su's miscarriage
might just have been an accident.
Your Majesty, I demand justice!
Cao used a handkerchief with pollen
to attract the bees, causing me to fall!
Your Majesty, you saw it
with your own eyes!
I didn't give it to you at all!
Clearly, you stole it!
You're framing me!
It was you who actively gave me
the handkerchief to wipe my sweat!
Would I personally harm my own child?
If you didn't intend to harm me,
why lead me to that secluded rockery?
I didn't! It was clearly you
who asked to go there with me!
Your Majesty.
Enough!
Concubine Cao acted
improperly and recklessly.
Demoted to Noble Lady.
Confined to Yongfu Palace.
Junior Concubine Su has miscarried.
Promote her to Concubine.
As some small comfort.
(Su Dai, do you know? The higher
one climbs, the harder they fall.)
Do not grieve excessively.
Focus on recuperating.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
excessive drinking harms the body.
You should drink less.
What do you need?
Eunuch Xu.
Concubine Su was frightened today.
She can't sleep and is crying right now.
She had me invite His Majesty over.
His Majesty is this drunk.
How can he go?
Glad you're here.
Noble Consort Wan will personally
bring sobering soup for His Majesty.
I'll go greet her.
You watch over His Majesty for now.
You... why haven't you
made your move yet?
Hurry up.
(You still love finding someone
to play chess with when drunk.)
(I actually prefer playing chess
with you when you're drunk.)
(Without so much weighing
of pros and cons and worry.)
Make your move quickly.
It seems your mind is troubled today.
Already struggling so much by mid-game.
Mid-game duel.
An inconspicuous piece
placed in an unexpected spot
can instantly turn defeat into victory.
♪Fate in haste, looking back
countless times, you swayed for me♪
Qing, Qing.
♪Among a vast sea of people,
faintly seeing the old self♪
♪Drawn to you, I've never forgotten.
Nothing can keep me from flying♪
♪Fate may not fulfill our wishes,
but I just hope you are well♪
♪A drifting life, stained with hardship,
mottled into the past♪
♪Countless thoughts,
all settled because of you♪
♪Scenery along the way,
looking back, love finds its echo♪
♪Watching the bustling world together,
we write more verses♪