=Glory Back=
=Episode 8=
This library
has been abandoned for years.
You know how to pick a spot.
Meeting at the Imperial Medical Office
isn't convenient.
This place usually
only houses old scrolls.
Few people come here,
and there's no guard.
It's a quiet place.
What do you need?
Don't rush.
First, try some osmanthus cakes
I made myself.
(Xuan has always loved these.
This should please him.)
I'm not a three-year-old child.
Why would I like such sweets?
Just say it. What do you want from me?
To be frank, there is indeed
a matter I must ask of you.
I want an Amenorrhea Pill to help
Junior Concubine Su fake a pregnancy.
How do you know
about such a forbidden drug?
With thousands of volumes here,
secrets can be found.
The Amenorrhea Pill
was originally for menstrual regulation.
But after taking it,
the pulse reads as pregnant.
In a previous dynasty, a consort faked
pregnancy with this. Then it got banned.
I'm here only for investigating
the fire at the mourning hall.
Not for harem struggles.
You've asked the wrong person.
Junior Concubine Su wants to fake
a pregnancy to crush Concubine Cao.
I'll let them fight it out
and then swoop in
to get close to Concubine Cao
to facilitate the investigation.
If that's your only goal,
such elaborate measures are unnecessary.
This plan of yours clearly aims
to utterly ruin Junior Concubine Su.
Say it. What is your real purpose?
For a friend.
Su Dai is cruel and ruthless,
disregarding human life.
If heaven won't punish
such an evil person, then I will.
I can give you an Amenorrhea Pill.
But now you and I are tied together.
I don't want to be dragged down by you.
I won't implicate you.
You only need to let slip
the location of the pill
to Lady Liu of the Imperial Pharmacy.
The pill's effect
only lasts half a month.
Once exposed, how can you
guarantee your own escape?
To deal with Junior Concubine Su,
are you going to gamble your life?
Does living quietly
and obediently guarantee safety?
Only by removing the evil master
like Su Dai, who treats subordinates
like dirt, can we survive.
Karma coming late
is better than not at all.
Have you found any clues on Su Dai?
Previously, Su Dai and Cao Zhen
were the most suspicious.
(Calming Incense, Su Dai, Cao Zhen)
Sir,
have you got any clues
from Noble Consort Wan?
She said her ice silk is missing.
I've eliminated Su Dai.
So it seems
the most suspicious one now
(Cao Zhen)
is Cao Zhen.
You believe Gu Wan's story?
After Qing died, she
benefited the most. She...
I understand what you thought.
But the Noble Consort
is the late Empress's own sister
and your second elder sister.
You are family. Don't let
misunderstandings create distance.
Being family means she's innocent?
In harem struggles, many climb
over the bodies of their kin.
You've got a sharp tongue.
Eat something sweet.
Don't waste these osmanthus cakes.
I hope you'll act wisely.
(Why do these osmanthus cakes
taste exactly like the ones Qing made?)
Qing.
You're here.
Qing, why didn't you add sugar?
Last year, you had a toothache.
I invented osmanthus cakes
with hawthorn.
Sourness can enhance sweetness.
♪With a glance, ripples begin to stir♪
Is it tasty?
♪Mortal ties entwine,
brushing past the palm♪
♪Affection quietly blooms♪
♪The marks of fate intertwined♪
♪Jade falls silently,
laying hidden clues♪
Physician Chen.
The Vice Director said we must store
the scarce Amenorrhea Pills carefully.
Did you handle the storage
of Amenorrhea Pills last month?
Yes, I did.
(Physician Chen)
The box on the third shelf of West Wing.
(Lady Liu, Imperial Pharmacy)
With my seal on it on the lid.
You're always so meticulous.
Have you improved, My Lady?
What's wrong?
My headache is severe.
Feng Qing, go to the Imperial Pharmacy
and get some pain-relieving medicine.
Yes.
It's already Hai hour.
Physician Chen, you can go back.
I'll finish portioning
this medicine soon and lock up later.
Alright.
Ms. Liu, did you get the thing?
Yes, I got it.
You didn't disappoint me.
Now I can hold my head up
in front of my mistress.
This money is a reward from her.
How generous.
Although the Amenorrhea Pill
can make one's pulse read as pregnant,
its effect only lasts
a little over half a month.
Tell Her Ladyship she must
proceed with extreme caution.
Thank you.
It's raining.
Your leg ailment always
flares up on rainy days.
I'll bring you Western Regions ointment
from Her Ladyship tomorrow.
You're very thoughtful.
I'll get you an umbrella.
Don't get soaked on your way back.
How is it?
Your Ladyship, everything
has been taken care of.
In the end, it's you
who truly understands me.
Though Feng Qing is clever,
she has a seductive appearance
and is skilled at chess.
If she ever thinks of catching
the Emperor's eye, she'll be a threat.
Your Ladyship,
when should we get rid of her?
Don't rush. Now is not the right time.
If something goes wrong in the future,
whether it's this pill
or Lady Liu's life,
as long as Feng Qing is proven
to be the last person who saw her,
how could it ever be traced back to us?
You're brilliant.
The day I'm firmly seated
as mistress of Yongfu Palace
will be the day
that wretched maid meets her end.
Congratulations.
The pulse is slippery, rapid,
and strong. You're pregnant.
Pregnant? I'm carrying the royal heir!
Judging by the pulse,
it's been over a month.
I will prepare
some fetal stabilizing medicine.
This is a small token of gratitude.
Such momentous and joyous news
should be reported to His Majesty soon.
Thank you, Your Ladyship.
I will report to His Majesty right away.
Congratulations on achieving your wish.
But the menstrual records
at the Imperial Bedchamber Office...
Your last menstrual period was recorded.
Don't worry. My father
has already taken care of it.
My family's tribute silver
can surely buy off a few lowly maids.
Your Ladyship, it's a risky move.
The pregnancy is ultimately false.
We should prepare for accidents early.
No rush.
I've been bullied by Concubine Cao
for so long. I'm going to make her pay.
Both of you, come with me
to Lanzhi Palace now to pay respects.
- Yes.
(Su Dai, you truly haven't
disappointed me.)
(Since you've started this play,
you can't step down easily.)
(Lanzhi Palace)
What time is it now?
Junior Concubine Su puts on great airs!
She is usually the most diligent
in morning and evening greetings.
Today, perhaps
something has delayed her.
Ridiculous!
If she doesn't come,
are we supposed to wait for her forever?
Junior Concubine Su has arrived!
Greetings, Your Highness.
Take your seat.
You arrived later
than even the others today.
Could it be that you think
the Noble Consort is lenient,
so you can break the greeting rules?
I heard you suddenly fell
seriously ill a few days ago.
I've been praying for your recovery
every morning. That's why I was late.
Your complexion is so sallow.
Could you be terminally ill?
You're cursing me!
It was my poor choice
of words. Please forgive me.
You!
How dare you!
I despise people who sow discord
and stir up trouble the most.
The harem will absolutely not
tolerate such troublemakers!
Drag Junior Concubine Su out!
The one who dares to stop me.
I will teach her a lesson today!
(Why is she so provocative today?
There must be something fishy.)
(I cannot act rashly.)
Imperial decree has arrived!
(Just as I expected. The rewards
have arrived at the perfect time.)
His Majesty decrees,
Junior Concubine Su, for her virtue
and for conceiving an heir,
is awarded 10 hu of East Sea pearls
and 20 bolts of Shu brocade.
That's all.
I receive the decree.
What's wrong?
I'm afraid to say.
I fear someone will accuse me
of causing trouble again.
My Lady was agitated
just now, disturbing the fetus.
If delayed, I fear...
Escort Junior Concubine Su back.
Get a physician. From today, you are
exempt from morning and evening rites.
Thank you, Your Highness.
(Yongfu Palace)
Why are you only back now?
His Majesty rewarded Her Ladyship.
She's generously rewarding everyone now.
I was just stopped
at the gate by Eunuch Xu.
He asked which one
in our palace knew how to play chess.
I don't know why he
suddenly asked about that.
Go claim your reward quickly.
(Xiao Luo already suspects
there's a chess master behind Su Dai.)
Long live Your Majesty.
What is your name?
Your Majesty, Feng Qing.
When did you serve Junior Concubine Su?
Last month.
Being so loyal after only a month.
Isn't that a bit too fast?
I'm dull-witted. Is being fast not good?
Bamboo grows fast,
yet its toughness cannot be broken.
Moss grows slowly,
yet it serves little use.
How dare you!
(This girl has such a sharp tongue.)
(It's quite amusing.)
(She doesn't fear me.)
(He's still so suspicious.)
If there's nothing else,
I shall take my leave.
I've never heard Junior Concubine Su
enjoyed playing chess before.
Why did she suddenly learn it
when Feng Qing arrived here?
Long live Your Majesty.
I am deeply delighted
by Your Majesty's generous rewards.
When you give birth to our son,
I shall reward you even more.
I am in high spirits today.
Why not play a game of chess with me?
(Why chess again?)
Are you certain you want
to place your piece here?
I made a mistake.
That day at Hualin Garden,
you bested me by half a point.
But you can't hold your ground today?
It's like you've been replaced.
Perhaps the pregnancy has unsettled
my mind, causing this loss of composure.
You are pregnant. Indeed,
you should not overexert yourself.
You two have been serving Her Ladyship.
You must know a little about chess.
Who will step in for your mistress
to finish this game with His Majesty?
His Majesty is the supreme ruler.
How could two maids be his opponents?
On the chessboard,
only black and white matter,
not rank or status.
You then.
Since you are so loyal to your mistress,
come and share her worries.
♪Once a lonely sail,
without a guiding light♪
♪With the warmth you lent me,
how could I fear loneliness♪
♪Day and night together,
sharing joys and sorrows♪
♪Searching all under heaven,
my heart won't change♪
♪Fate in haste, looking back
countless times, you swayed for me♪
♪Among a vast sea of people,
faintly seeing the old self♪
♪Scenery along the way,
looking back, love finds its echo♪
♪Watching the bustling world together,
we write more verses♪