♫I want to walk every long street with you♫
♫Hold hands as the street lights flicker♫
♫I don't bear to read the chapters with you in them♫
♫How I wish I could freeze time♫
♫You said you love long nights the most♫
♫My love is never cowardly♫
♫Every season with you♫
♫Even the wind is gentler♫
♫The night breeze blows through a sky dotted by starlight♫
♫I ask it to bring you my overflowing longing♫
♫Snowflakes suspended in the air, drifting happily♫
♫You gradually notice all of my love♫
♫The night breeze blows through a sky full of moonlight♫
♫Just like my passion spreading throughout your world♫
♫It will never diminish, it will never subside♫
♫Every day with you is a special one, love will never end♫
[Since I Met U]
What are you looking at?
Are you looking for something?
Are you okay?
Yes.
Good.
Rui Rui and I are going out today.
It's on your way.
Let's go together.
On my way?
Where are you taking Rui Rui?
We'll just hang out.
Term 4 of the Cohabitation Agreement.
Tell me where you're going and whom you'll go with.
To the dessert shop.
To Sweet.
I have an appointment with my class president.
Why are you going there?
I'm a food blogger after all.
Isn't it normal for me to go to Sweet?
Oh.
It just occurred to me
that I don't need to work today.
Okay.
Rui Rui, let's go.
-Let's go eat desserts.
-Let's go.
Let's go.
It's just your class president.
Are you that happy?
[Give the lemon some time]
[Sour is immature sweet]
[Episode 6]
[Sol Dessert]
Don't you open at 10 am?
Why isn't your boss here yet?
Miss, since you came in,
you've asked me this question
10 times.
I...
Boss.
Morning.
Cheng Mu.
You're finally here.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
I don't know her.
Who are you looking for?
Sorry.
Have you calculated the money for washing the clothes?
I'll ask them to give you the money.
I didn't come here for this.
Then you...
I want to ask you
whether you and my brother's classmate
are in a relationship.
It has nothing to do with you.
Yihang, take care of the guest for me.
Also,
don't let anyone disturb me.
Cheng Mu.
Miss,
you can ask me if you have any questions.
I'm the official spokesperson of my boss.
Miss.
You said you'd bring Rui Rui with you.
So I changed the place to the park.
It's more comfortable.
Rui Rui can play happily.
And we can talk.
You're so thoughtful.
Muzhou, actually I'm here today
to ask you
about you plagiarizing
Sol's new dessert.
Did you bring it?
I knew it.
Not only do they look the same,
but they also have similar tastes.
But after I tasted it carefully,
I knew it's different from the one made by Cheng Mu.
But ordinary customers
can hardly tell the difference.
I've already told the headquarters
about the plagiarism problem Cheng Mu told me.
They said the dessert was purchased by the company.
So there's no possibility of plagiarism.
Could there be a misunderstanding?
Impossible.
I watched him make it at home.
You and Cheng Mu...
You're dating?
No.
We just take care of Rui Rui together.
My sister and brother-in-law...
As husband and wife, they...
You know.
Yes.
Blogger Jiang,
you're a food blogger now.
When will you help me promote Sweet?
The articles written by you are excellent.
Of course. It's my pleasure.
Have a taste.
What I brought today are all our new products.
Here.
So many new products.
It seems that Cheng Mu has met his opponent.
Your reputation is well-deserved.
Aunt, you're eating secretly.
Come, Rui Rui.
Eat with me.
No.
Why not?
How can one eat the desserts of two shops?
Something is wrong.
What's wrong?
I think so too.
Our boss has never added acidity to his desserts.
But today, he spent all his time
cutting lemons in the kitchen.
That's really strange.
There's something stranger.
This girl is indeed strange.
What girl?
She's been staring at the kitchen for the whole morning.
She looks mysterious
and furtive.
She's from Sweet.
Her brother is Han Muzhou, the person in charge of Sweet.
No wonder.
Is she trying to steal our ideas again?
Should I stop her?
No.
You can't.
Don't underestimate me.
I can.
Yihang,
I have a difficult task for you today.
What?
Stop her
from getting close to the boss.
Understand?
Yes.
I'll fulfil the task.
Miss,
shall I recommend
our desserts for you?
This is called Encounter.
And
it's very soft.
What's your boss's hobby?
He likes to launch new products
and compete with Sweet.
Can you tell him
I want to make friends with him?
No problem.
As long as our boss takes action,
he will definitely win.
I'll just take some photos.
I won't do anything else.
We are both dessert shops.
My boss hopes that we can compete fairly.
Are you sure
no one has read the notebook
except you and Cheng Mu?
I'm sure.
I was holding the notebook,
then I gave it to...
To whom?
Just give it to me.
Thank you.
Rui Rui!
Rui Rui.
You finally remembered to call me.
Hello, what's up? I'm busy.
Where are you?
You're tough.
You didn't cry at all.
This is a reward for a good kid.
Thank you, Uncle.
Although you hurt me when you patched me up,
I'll forgive you
for the sake of this candy.
Thank you, doctor.
You're welcome.
In the future,
when you take the kid out,
you must be careful.
We will.
Let me see.
Doctor, is he okay?
He's fine.
I've told the details
to his parents.
You can talk outside.
Next one.
Godfather, it doesn't hurt anymore.
His parents?
No.
Rui Rui, come with me. Be good.
No. Listen to me.
It's a misunderstanding.
Sihan, let's meet another day.
I'm sorry for today.
I didn't take good care of Rui Rui.
It's okay, Muzhou.
It's not your fault.
I didn't take good care of Rui Rui.
I'll write the article for you.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
See you, Uncle Han.
Okay.
Take the front passenger seat.
Mr. Shen.
I haven't had time to congratulate you
on getting promoted to the second-in-command.
There's no need
to be so polite with me.
Sit.
Nice environment.
Mr. Shen.
This is the information about our company's artists.
I've signed the business and agency contracts with them.
Have a look.
Are you this cold to your ex-boyfriend?
I just sat down,
and you started to talk about work.
How about this?
Let's have dinner together tonight.
Take it as a compensation for me,
who was abandoned by you.
Do you think
the long-term endorsement contract
I have in my hands
is not worth a meal?
You should know
what it means to sign it.
It equals
your company's business volume in a year.
Mr. Shen, that's not what I meant.
I just think
we don't need to
talk about the past.
After all these years,
you still
put your brother first.
You can choose to break up with your boyfriend
as long as your brother doesn't like him.
I don't understand. It's been so many years.
Does your brother know it?
I don't need him to know it.
This is what I should do as a sister.
Is your brother more important
than your lifelong happiness?
Yes. If he's not happy,
I won't leave him alone.
You are still the Cheng Yu I know.
I can trust you.
Take a look.
As for the contract,
I still need to discuss the details with you.
How about this?
Let's have a cup of coffee
and talk.
Please.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
You don't look natural.
I don't look natural?
You are strange.
Both of you are strange.
Rui Rui, does it still hurt?
You're good.
You're not like her,
who didn't keep her promise.
What do you mean?
The Cohabitation Agreement.
Didn't I tell you?
I said I had an appointment with him.
Where did you go?
The park.
After that,
would you have a meal together?
After the meal, would you find a place
to have a drink, talk about the old days,
and reconnect?
I don't want to talk to you.
Ms. Cheng, you're really busy.
Since we sat down,
you've kept receiving messages.
You admirer?
Spam messages.
I wonder
if you're interested in
the artists of our company?
Whether I'm interested or not
doesn't matter.
You know,
after all these years,
I...
After all these years,
do you still like coffee?
Try this.
See if it suits your taste.
Cheers.
Stop pretending.
The story
about Miss Moon's previous life and current life
written by Taro, Jiang Sihan,
is about you two, right?
And the rose crystal ball
in your room.
The one you don't let me touch.
And
Miss Moon and the rose flavor
are all related to Jiang Sihan, right?
You're so affectionate.
You love her so much.
Your godson, Rui Rui, fell over today.
Jiang Sihan sent Rui Rui to the hospital with her class president.
Look.
Taro's crush is back.
They may get back at any time.
You haven't done anything yet. You're being overly relaxed.
No, bro.
You really have to do something.
I must help you.
No one can stop me.
Cheng Yu
is my one true love.
But I, Li Jingyang,
have been chasing after her
for so many years.
I'm better at pursuing girls
than you,
right?
We're almost the same.
You two are living together.
But you haven't done anything yet.
Bro, let me ask you one thing.
Did you kiss?
No way. You really kissed?
When?
A year ago.
A year ago?
You kissed a girl a year ago.
A year ago.
Now the girl went to the hospital with her class president.
We haven't finished drinking.
Where are you going?
I'm going to sleep.
You deserve to be single forever.
Cheng Mu, Jiang Sihan.
Cheng Yu, Li Jingyang.
Perfect.
You're back.
Where's Rui Rui?
He's asleep.
Did you drink?
A little.
♫Take my hand♫
♫I know how cold the world is♫
♫Don't be frightened now♫
♫My precious love♫
♫Come to me♫
♫When you have run your miles♫
♫For the thousandth time♫
♫You are perfect now♫
♫Just as you are♫
♫At the end of the day♫
♫I will come for you♫
♫Run to you anyway♫
♫When the sky seems so gray♫
♫I am yours to save♫
♫Yours to save always♫
I guess
♫I will run to you however slowly♫
you'll never forget it again.
♫Please be my one, my one and only♫
My real first kiss is gone.
He is drunk,
but I am sober.
♫Let me be the one♫
♫Whose heart you take as true♫
I miss you.
[Cheng Yu recalled a message]
Yesterday,
we...
Yesterday...
I was drunk yesterday.
Drunk?
Come to think of it,
I gave the notebook to Bai Bin.
You can ask him.
Okay.
♫Take my hand, I know how cold the world is♫
♫Don't be frightened now, don't be frightened now♫
♫My precious love♫
♫Come to me, when you have run your miles♫
♫For the thousandth time, you are perfect now♫
♫Just as you are♫
♫At the end of the day, I will come for you♫
♫Run to you anyway, when the sky seems so gray♫
♫I am yours to save, yours to save♫
♫Always♫
♫I will run to you however slowly♫
♫Please be my one, my one and only♫
♫Let me be the one whose heart you take as true♫
♫As true♫
♫I will run to you however slowly♫
♫Please be my one, my one and only♫
♫Let me be the one whose heart you take as true♫
♫As true♫