SHOW ME THE MONEY 12
GLOBAL PRELIMINARIES D-DAY
RETURNS ON A BIGGER SCALE
UNPRECEDENTED GLOBAL PRELIMINARIES
FOR SHOW ME THE MONEY
I'm from Brooklyn, New York.
I'm from Namibia.
- I'm from Russia.
- China.
- I'm from LA.
- Sweden.
- Canada.
- I'm from Japan.
- France.
- Thailand.
- Hong Kong.
- India.
I'm from Türkiye.
Taiwan.
Yes, sir!
CONTESTANTS FROM 32 COUNTRIES AROUND
THE WORLD JOINED THE PRELIMINARIES
This program
has many Asian viewers.
People may not know Hong Kong
hip-hop, but they watch SHOW ME THE MONEY.
I feel like
this is the biggest rap show.
I applied because I thought
it was a great opportunity for me.
Many people around the world
watched SHOW ME THE MONEY.
And it has that much impact.
It's a global show.
Korean hip-hop is growing more and more.
THE GLOBAL CONTESTANTS ARE GATHERED
Everyone,
thank you for coming.
I'm glad to be here.
I'm very excited
and kind of nervous at the same time.
Rap, passion, and energy...
I want to hear and feel all that.
I hope you show everything
you've prepared today.
Since there are language barriers...
In the end,
I think that the emotions I feel
from their rap are most important.
It's all music in the end.
So whatever language they use,
whatever the meanings they contain...
I'll be able to sense good rap.
Professional rappers
can recognize each other.
So if they're good, we'll recognize them.
I'm so excited.
We ready?
Show Me the...
Money!
THE GLOBAL PRELIMINARIES BEGIN
WAITING ROOM
Yo, yo, yo!
A CONTESTANT ENTERS AMID CHEERS
EYES
FOLLOWING HIS MOVEMENT
THE JAPANESE CONTESTANTS
ARE ESPECIALLY FOCUSED ON HIM
Everyone in Japan knows him.
Every Japanese rapper
would know him.
Red Eye.
RED EYE IS ALREADY KNOWN BY THE JAPANESE
I'm Red Eye, a rapper from Japan.
RED EYE IS LEADING JAPAN'S HIP-HOP TREND
WON THE NATIONAL
HIGH SCHOOL RAP COMPETITION
WHEN HE WAS 18
PERFORMED SOLO AT THE BUDOKAN IN 2025
ARTISTS LIKE THE BEATLES, BTS, BLACKPINK
PERFORMED AT THE BUDOKAN
RED EYE WAS THE YOUNGEST HIP-HOP ARTIST
TO PERFORM AT THE BUDOKAN
I heard I could
show off my rap outside of Japan.
That's why I'm here.
I will prove my skills
with Japanese rap.
THE RAPPER WHO SHOOK JAPAN
HOW WILL HIS PRELIMINARY AUDITION GO?
I have no regrets
Walking my own path
I came all the way here
It's go big or go home
Lyrics I wrote after conquering
Numerous challenges
My value soars every time
Story of my unfortunate past
But now I have the wealth
I laugh it off
Ever since I was born
I never wanted to become anyone else
What would have happened
If nothing changed?
I would've died or got handcuffed
When I think back
Everything was so sad
But I still thought it was okay
Papa
Brother
But look at me now
Not the Yakuza, not a dealer
But a rapper
Did you think I'd stop there?
Did you think I'd lose to him?
But I'm showing the opposite results
That's why you're so angry
Did you think I'd stop there?
I'm climbing higher without hesitation
But it's all right
I'll treat you after I win
Yes!
HOW IS THE EVALUATION FOR RED EYE?
JAPAN'S RAP STAR RED EYE PASSES
Thank you.
That was the first time.
It was the first time I got goosebumps.
Thank you.
I was surprised by how focused he was.
The words and rhythm
really stuck in my head.
The music seemed to play in my mind.
RED EYE SURPRISED ZICO
WITH HIS INCREDIBLE SKILLS
It was like he pressed the "Play" button
right in front of me.
SHOW ME THE MONEY!
GLOBAL CONTESTANTS IN VARIOUS STYLES
GATHERED FROM AROUND THE WORLD
SOME CONTESTANTS STEAL OTHERS' GAZES
Camera shy.
I'm Torin, and I'm from Bali.
I'm from the States.
I'm Koni.
My rap name is SHURU.
AND A CONTESTANT WHO CAUSED A STIR
WITH HIS APPEARANCE AT THE SCENE
He's so handsome.
Is he a celebrity?
HIS IDENTITY IS...
Yo, what's up?
Sexy and hot, shining forever.
HE ZONG XING GAINED THE SPOTLIGHT
IN BOYS II PLANET
WITH HIS VISUALS AND UNIQUE CHARACTER
He seems to have charisma.
I'm HE ZONG XING,
ready to show you my sexy charms.
HE ZONG XING IS REALLY
APPEARING IN SHOW ME THE MONEY?
I WAS IN SHOCK HEARING
HE ZONG XING IS JOINING SHOW ME THE MONEY
HE ZONG XING?
Yes, I'm HE ZONG XING.
Hello.
FANS RECOGNIZE HE ZONG XING
FROM BOYS II PLANET AND GATHER AROUND HIM
Today, I've got to be hot.
HE ZONG XING IS FOCUSED ON PRACTICING
BEFORE THE EVALUATION
I just finished BOYS II PLANET
but I really love hip-hop and rap.
I hope I can express
the music that I want in this program.
How have you been?
Can I do the interview later?
I have to practice a bit.
Cool. Nice.
HE ZONG XING IS EVALUATED BY JAY PARK
You're an idol?
Oh! You were in BOYS II PLANET.
Don't look at it.
Just feel my rap.
I LIKE YOUR CONFIDENCE
Okay.
Whenever you're ready.
Just feel the rhythm.
- Okay, go ahead.
- Yeah.
Yeah
Yeah, yeah
I'm only eighteen
Explode this stage
Of course, it's tough
But I working every day
Everyone lines up
Hoping I would hit rock bottom
I don't care about this
Will you shut your mouths?
Time don't wasted
I don't believe anything you say
I'm hot crush shot shining
Now I got you in my feeling
I brought my dream
I pour my confidence into this
Nobody wanna close
Nobody wanna see
No one can reach my heart
Nobody want me sexy
Want me sexy
But I endure it
Even in darkness and fear
I grit my teeth and go on
Tell me time
Okay, cool. Nice.
Good job.
I'm going to hear everybody.
HE'LL MAKE A ROUND
I'm going
to hear everybody and...
HE ZONG XING'S EVALUATION POSTPONED
He said he'd look around
and come back,
so I think I still have some hope.
LUNCHTIME PASSES
Thank you, guys.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
BUT JAY PARK NEVER RETURNED
TO HE ZONG XING
Let's go, baby!
HE ZONG XING ELIMINATED
I did get a feeling,
but I wasn't sure about it.
I felt I had to hear
all 20 contestants to be sure.
In the end,
I could tell the difference.
I didn't get
the necklace today,
but I won't give up my dream
of doing music.
WHILE GLOBAL RAPPERS
ARE CHATTING TOGETHER
SOMEONE IS PRACTICING ALONE
GLANCE
FOCUSED ON PRACTICE
DESPITE THE GAZES ON HIM
WHO IS THIS CONFIDENT CONTESTANT?
Yo, what's good?
It's your boy Saint from Canada.
I'm here to apply
for SHOW ME THE MONEY 12.
JUNHYUK ENTERS FOR HIS EVALUATION
CONTINUES PRACTICE EVEN AFTER ENTERING
ZICO ENTERS AS THE JUDGE
Let's go.
Hello.
I was pretty confident.
HOW IS JUNHYUK'S RAP?
They can't make a
Lasting impression
Your sweet 16s
Put on some awkward makeup
Me, I
Keep my word as my bond so I'm
Agent 007, fake love
Fishing for green
Hurry up and order your poke
Caught in those 4k's, huh
Still room for growth
Now it's looking like y'all are my sons
My resume UT but I will go dummy for real
Move out of my place
Like this my parking for real
1 step 2 step, my toes
Stand on 10, 10 that's
Mike jack I'm like that so see, see
I get back at those who laughed at me
The heehees and hahas
Now they see me on Show Me on TV
On Wi-Fi look pretty
The heehees and hahas
Now they see me on Show Me on TV
On Wi-Fi look pretty
STUMBLING
Will you come here?
JUNHYUK PASSES
I passed.
It's crazy.
THUMBS-UP
Wow, he's something else.
This is what makes this fun.
It's giving me an endorphin rush.
When I first saw him,
I did think he stood out.
GLANCE
ZICO HAD HIS EYES ON JUNHYUK
AS SOON AS HE ENTERED
I thought,
"Let's see how unique his rap is."
But he switched his flow
and rapped something like,
"Heehee, haha, hoho."
I give back the heehees and hahas
Now they see me on Show Me on TV
On Wi-Fi look pretty
It could seem a bit old.
But he added his own vibe to it,
which was really good.
I'm really going
to be a rock star on the next stage.
- A lot of people uploaded their videos.
- Yeah.
36,000 APPLICANT VIDEOS WERE UPLOADED
Ever since the applications began,
we were searching
and watching all the videos.
We did a lot of digging to see
what kind of applicants there were.
WHICH APPLICANT WAS THE MOST MEMORABLE?
THINKING...
For me, DOUBLE DOWN.
His video was witty and fun.
DOUBLE DOWN'S VIDEO IMPRESSED HUKKY
Hello.
My name is DOUBLE DOWN.
HIS INTRO STANDS OUT FROM THE START
I'll show you for free. Only this time
WINK
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO DOUBLE DOWN
DOUBLE DOWN IS SO FUNNY
DOUBLE DOWN IS JOINING?
HE WAS UNIQUE IN RAP:PUBLIC
DOUBLE DOWN IS REAL HIP-HOP
DOUBLE DOWN IS AMAZING
I LIKE DOUBLE DOWN BECAUSE HE'S UNIQUE
I HOPE HE DOES WELL
WOW I WANTED TO SEE DOUBLE DOWN
HIP HOP=DOUBLE DOWN
ALREADY ATTRACTING ATTENTION
WITH HIS APPLICATION VIDEO
HOW IS HE
AT THE PRELIMINARY AUDITION SITE?
MESSY LONG HAIR
INNOCENT LAUGH HIDDEN BEHIND
HIS INTENSE LOOKS
SIGNATURE HAIR STYLE
My name's DOUBLE DOWN.
I'm an American rapper from New York.
There are a lot of good
Korean rappers, but most of them...
What was the word?
Their style is a bit tacky.
Is it okay to say that?
GLANCING
I'll show you what I've got.
Bring it on, everyone!
SO MUCH CONFIDENCE
BUT FAILED TO BEAT JET LAG
I applied
to SHOW ME THE MONEY 12 because
I wanted to give my mom
some money this time.
Mom, I'm doing my best.
Don't worry about me.
So you don't have to worry.
YOU TRUST ME, RIGHT?
HOW WILL GOOD SON
DOUBLE DOWN'S RAP BE?
Hello.
My name is DOUBLE DOWN.
I know you, DOUBLE DOWN.
I'll do my best.
ALREADY FUNNY
I'll start right away.
Mom, please forgive me
They all lookin like a fake rapper
please don't tempt me, I
Brr-brr, click-click-click
Until that go empty
You don't wanna stumble
In the same neighborhood as me and AP
Do you wanna get beat
Yes or no, maybe
It's easy like stealing candy from a baby
Wah, wah, wah
Smoking up like a barbecue
Big choppa like the army do
Bullets 2+2 like when you buy drinks
The face of the Korean flag
Like a flag I up the pole
When I grip the choppa feelin like a thief
Hit you in your nose
That's the third nostril
WHAT IS DOUBLE DOWN'S RESULT?
That was good.
DOUBLE DOWN PASSES
Thank you.
How was DOUBLE DOWN?
He was perfect.
He had everyone laughing.
DOUBLE DOWN doesn't look like
he'll make people laugh.
His face makes everyone laugh.
DOUBLE DOWN, DOUBLE PASS
Double Pass.
This is my bag.
FEELING EXCELLENT
Hey, guys. Do you have this chain?
I do.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
A CONTESTANT ENTERS THE QUIET ROOM
EVERYONE CHEERS AT HIS ARRIVAL
JB!
WHO IS THE MAN WHO STIRRED UP
EVERYONE IN THE WAITING ROOM?
JB, A RAPPER ACTIVE IN HONG KONG
WON SEVEN AWARDS
AT THE HONG KONG HIP-HOP AWARDS
INCLUDING THE ARTIST OF THE YEAR AWARD
JB.
- Oh, Hong Kong!
- Hong Kong.
He can sell out a 2,000-seat venue
in Hong Kong.
From the Philippines.
FILIPINO PIONEER OF CANTONESE RAP
THE OG RAPPER JB,
AN ICON OF HONG KONG HIP-HOP
JB CAN PERFORM ANY TYPE OF MUSIC
AND HIS MELODIES ARE VERY STABLE
THIS IS THE BEST RAP
I HAVE HEARD IN MY LIFE
KING JB / YOU'RE THE BEST! / SO COOL
SWAG / HIS RAP IS SO NICE AND ADDICTIVE
He's like a hip-hop legend
at this point, for real.
He's our icon!
- No! No.
- Icon.
Half the people in Hong Kong
know who he is.
- He's my hero. Yeah.
- No.
PHOTO HE TOOK WITH HIS HERO JB
SEVEN YEARS AGO
I feel like JB was like a hero.
HOW DID JB END UP APPLYING
TO SHOW ME THE MONEY 12?
I hope many people can see
Hong Kong hip-hop through this show
and understand the language we use.
I'm really sincere.
Nice to meet you.
WHAT WILL BE THE EVALUATION
FOR HONG KONG'S LEGENDARY RAPPER JB?
JB from Hong Kong.
I'm finally here right now.
I don't think you'll understand.
I said I'm finally here right now.
You guys are going to lower
your body here right now
I never thought I'd rap
In Cantonese here, it's a surprise
But at the same time
I feel so free and comfortable
They call me JB a.k.a. JIGGIE BOY
I keep my attitude light
But still keep it real
Have fun until morning
Keep dancing when the music's on
If you can, bring it on
With your most RAW touch
You only mimic the appearance
You can't even compare to us
We're the RAW GREYTONE
Not like you who are only talk
My rap comes out automatically
Spitting bars off the top
A little more, ya
It won't be easy to follow this flow
If you really have the skills, show me
Pay attention to the name
Freshest in the game
Got the juice and the flame
So your crew ain't the same
My flow so smooth
And a little boogie
What's your flavor?
You better show it to me
Words are different
But the lips move the same
Show off your skills
Maintain the teamwork
Wherever we go, we have fun
Raise your glasses in the air
Half-drunk, good trip
Oh, a fun journey
I said, I rise
We rise with my brother baby
Good trip
Korea with my brother baby
Thank you.
That's insane.
JB FROM HONG KONG PASSES
What's your name?
JB, from Hong Kong.
But I'm a Filipino,
born in Hong Kong.
How old are you?
I'm old.
I'm 33.
ZICO, AGE 33 / OLD MAN
Same age.
Same age?
I'm old.
FORGET AGE, I'M JUST EXCITED
Thank you, man.
Two old men.
- You were born in 1992 also?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
OG!
Let's go!
Show me the Money 12.
Hong Kong, I made it.
First of all,
his style was really unique,
and he rapped to his own beat
while expressing the most
of his voice and character
for his performance.
I grew really curious
how he would rap to music.
DURING THE AUDITION OPENING
THE GLOBAL CONTESTANTS
WERE GATHERED TOGETHER
THE LIGHTS DIMMED JUST BEFORE THE START
ONE CONTESTANT WAS SHINING BY HERSELF
EYES FOCUSED
COOL
WHO IS THIS SHINING CONTESTANT?
I'm MINAMI,
who was in World of Street Woman Fighter.
APPEARED AS TEAM OSAKA OJO GANG
ON WORLD OF STREET WOMAN FIGHTER
MINAMI WON FIRST PLACE
WITH HER AMAZING SKILLS
Crew OSAKA Ojo Gang!
ON THE DAY OF THE AUDITIONS
CAN I TAKE A PHOTO?
MANY CONTESTANTS RECOGNIZED MINAMI
AT THE RECEPTION BOOTH
This is MINAMI.
I'm a huge fan. I was like,
"Oh, my God. That is so cool."
WHY DID THE DANCER MINAMI
APPLY TO SHOW ME THE MONEY 12?
For the D.League,
the Japanese dance league,
there's a theme song,
and our team sang the song ourselves.
THE THEME SONG
MINAMI AND HER MEMBERS SANG
MINAMI DID THE RAP
People around me told me
my rap was pretty good,
so I applied for SHOW ME THE MONEY 12
as a challenge.
HER APPLICATION VIDEO CAUSED A HUGE STIR
GO MINAMI
LET'S GO MANY COLLEAGUES ROOTED FOR HER
Aren't you a famous dancer?
I am.
I saw you on the show.
WILL THE FAMOUS DANCER MINAMI
GET A PASS?
Imma MINAMI
Let's keep going.
Again?
MINAMI GOT ANOTHER CHANCE
AFTER HER MISTAKE
Imma MINAMI
BUT SHE MADE ANOTHER MISTAKE
One more... Last?
Imma MINAMI
Carry it all and stand here
Heavy problems
I overcome them all
I rewrite history like Ohtani
With a well-honed dream
I get more money
Spit and blow, slamming flow
This movement is unpredictable
Push aside everyone who gets in my way
I finish it in one shot, okay
Thank you.
WHAT IS THE RESULT FOR MINAMI?
I'm sorry.
MINAMI IS ELIMINATED
I'm pretty upset
I didn't do as well as I practiced.
But this was a great experience for me,
so I'll take on the challenge again
after I've improved.
CHEERFUL VIBE IN THE WAITING ROOM
WHILE EVERYONE IS CHATTING
SOME CONTESTANTS APPEAR
GAINING EVERYONE'S ATTENTION
INCREDIBLE SWAG
THE CONTESTANTS APPEAR
WITH AN AUTHENTIC HIP-HOP VIBE
GAZES
FOCUSED
I go by the name of
Victory Success Opportunity and Progress,
VSOP SITY.
What's up, world?
It's Bing Nation, BING.
It's your boy TOOX.
We're from Brooklyn, New York.
We're the Cooper family.
We are the Cooper family.
SHOW ME THE MONEY 12.
I've never been to Korea.
Halfway around the world for hip-hop.
I want to see what other countries
are doing.
You know what I mean?
Do I strike you as a serious person?
I'm happy, man.
I'm happy to be here.
Hey, everybody. How are you all doing?
NONSTOP TALKING EVEN WHILE WAITING
All right, now. What's going on?
RELENTLESS ENERGY
You? I see you, baby. What's up?
FILMING THE GROUP OPENING SHOT
Show Me the...
TOOX SPEAKS AT THE CENTER
Money!
VSOP SITY HOLDS THE FLAG
BING NATION IS DOING HIS BEST
TO REACT ENTHUSIASTICALLY
HYPING UP THE OTHERS DURING BREAK TIME
SHOW ME THE MONEY!
EXPLODING WITH ENERGY
EVEN BEFORE THE EVALUATIONS
Okay.
STILL FULL OF ENERGY DURING THEIR MEAL
Bring it back for three more.
CHEERS
WHAT WILL BE THE RESULTS
FOR THE HAPPY COOPER FAMILY?
- What's up? How are you doing, man?
- I'm good, how are you doing?
Can you tell me
a little bit about yourself?
Yeah. Well, my name is TOOX.
I'm from Brooklyn, New York.
I've been rapping for about 18 years.
18 years?
Since I was 13.
Okay.
Cool, man. Whenever you're ready.
Breakin' backs with
Broken bats holding the axe
Who's the ***, they ask
No one's holding this crack
Able to crack boards
With the cord of my mic
They're hype wondering how he writes
This flow is tight
With an old school punch
I take your lunch
A major crunch, I made you crunch
Your chips in front of your friends
The fun begins
Once this dunce gets played
For what he really is, a reject
I rejected the rejects
Because they rejected the realness
People hear this, then they heal quick
Still allergic to the bird
Heard that verbs
And words coming swift
Can make me a word smith
I got it a lot like Stockton
When I'm rockin the 12 poppin shots
At ya whole crew
Or give it to the mail man
To send my message
Through instant message, fool
That's what I'm sending you
FUMBLING
Oh, man!
COOPER FAMILY'S FIRST, TOOX PASSES
I can tell you've been
rapping for 18 years.
AFTER TOOX'S PASS
Oh, man.
HOW WILL BING NATION DO?
How you, my brother?
You hate when I'm winning
All of that tough is out of the window
When I get to grinning
But that ain't my business, so
I wanna rap like y'all
Humbly wanna act like y'all
Dumb little *** wanna go
And get a fitted get identical
When really wanna cap like y'all
BING NATION PASSES
OTHER CONTESTANTS CONGRATULATE
THE COOPER FAMILY
LAST MEMBER VSOP SITY BEGINS
BSV, you ain't never find a set
Imma make the haters eat they words
Until they choke to death
Yes, you listening to the realest
You ain't cut from my cloth
Then you probably ain't gon feel it
I was wild n out
They called me Chico Bean with the skillet
Kicked me out the classroom
I had to pick it up and kill it
WILL VSOP SITY ALSO PASS?
EVERY MEMBER OF THE COOPER FAMILY PASSES
They seemed more sincere
than anyone.
They were battle rappers.
I had no choice but to let
all three of them pass.
Cooper family and South Korea!
Say "cousin"!
Cousin!
South Korea, say "cousin"!
Say "cousin"!
Cousin!
There was such a variety of people there.
It was really a global sound.
UNIQUE GLOBAL CONTESTANTS
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
Girl, you're so pretty
Welcome everybody to Chengdu city
Blood pressure up and down
Up and down
SERIOUS
Up and down up
Buckwheat is the best for a fever
Buckwheat jelly and buckwheat noodles
Buckwheat will lower your fever
So I will eat all the buckwheat
My head is burning.
It's so hot!
Buckwheat is the best for a fever
Buckwheat jelly and buckwheat noodles
NO NEED FOR BUCKWHEAT
I love ramyeon the most.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
GRAY IS EVALUATING SOMEONE
Please...
I enjoyed your rap.
Really?
APPROACHING
GRAY.
GRAY, please.
Hang on.
Why?
I really want to understand.
I didn't make any mistakes.
I know. Many contestants
didn't make mistakes.
Please give me a chance.
DESPERATE
Please...
I'm sorry.
I won't be able to go home if you do this.
I'd feel too bad.
I'm refraining from reading my DMs.
DING
It must be a DM.
DEAN, not GRAY.
ANOTHER CONTESTANT AT THE AUDITION
IT'S ME
FLOWSIK
WHEN THE TRAILER WAS RELEASED
FOR SHOW ME THE MONEY 12
*** is really here?
PEEKABOO
ENTHUSIASTIC RESPONSE
AT THE NEWS OF FLOWSIK'S APPEARANCE
Yo, wassup! It's your boy Flowsik.
Hello, I'm Flowsik.
It's been a while.
Long time.
JOINED SHOW ME THE MONEY 5
AS A RAPPER FROM NEW YORK
FLOWSIK SHOWED POWERFUL RAP
WITH A HUSKY TONE
HE MADE A STRONG IMPRESSION
HIS VOICE AND FLOW ARE TOP-TIER
SHOW ME THE MONEY 5'S
TRUE WINNER IS FLOWSIK
HE WASN'T EVEN RAPPING IN ENGLISH
HIS RAP WAS INSANE
NO ONE CAN IMITATE HIS RAP
Hasn't it been a long time
since you entered SHOW ME THE MONEY?
SHOW ME THE MONEY 5, AIRED IN 2016
SHOW ME THE MONEY 5?
That means he's participating
after nine or ten years.
I'm so excited.
I wanted to take a break,
so I returned to New York.
I stayed in New York for four years
and did various work outside of music.
I worked at a tech company,
and did other things too.
HE HAD A FOUR-YEAR BREAK IN HIS CAREER
It's been a long time since I did music,
but I want to keep doing it.
I'm still an artist,
so I want to keep doing music.
I'm participating
in SHOW ME THE MONEY again this time.
So I thought,
"Okay. I'll do it one more time."
I decided to set my pride aside
and apply for this show once more.
HOW WILL FLOWSIK'S EVALUATION BE
10 YEARS AFTER HIS RETURN?
- Shall I begin?
- Yes.
Ya!
Is he Korean?
Is he an American?
All my life I was a foreigner
This kid is far from human
He's different
That's right man
He came from Andromeda
Out of this realm
From the heavens, a blessing
He's shining cuz God put a star in him
I started from age 15
Started killing emcees
Too much for the coroner
Flamethrow fueling the fire
I did too many times
I blew too many minds
'Til this day you pray for my demise
I'm wise
But no longer will I put down my pride
Fell for the trap
Started rapping over trap beats
But I'm way too fast for the track meet
Pull a U turn
Can't pass me
The backseat take the trunk
Frisbee let it go
Then I bring it back, yo
Far from luck I'm back
I've bottoms up
Got a lot of love but obviously not enough
Man, I'm breaking the quota
Get my bodies up
Never sell out I'll up
Monday to Sunday my best day
I am insane in the membrane
Still rapping
Like I gotta get the rent paid
Pump these weights no rest days
Way I run it everyday is leg day
Is he Korean?
Is he an American?
All my life I was a foreigner
WILL FLOWSIK RECEIVE A PASS NECKLACE?
FLOWSIK PASSES
FLOWSIK PASSES WITH A POWERFUL FLOW
He's incredible.
He was just different.
There are rappers like him
whose rap
may not be your style,
but you just can't ignore.
His skills and effort are just...
undeniable.
You can't help but acknowledge him.
Flowsik is someone like that.
That's right. Totally.
STRANGE SOUNDS
RINGING OUT IN THE WAITING ROOM
THE PERSON WORKING OUT WHILE MAKING
STRANGE NOISES IS...
MILLI
Hi, my name is MILLI.
I'm 22 years old, and I'm from Thailand.
THAI RAPPER MILLI EATS MANGO STICKY RICE
ON STAGE DURING COACHELLA PERFORMANCE
THAI MANGO STICKY RICE SALES SURGE
AFTER SWEET TREAT'S COACHELLA CAMEO
FIRST SOLO ARTIST FROM THAILAND
TO PERFORM AT COACHELLA
DID VARIOUS COLLABORATIONS
WITH KOREAN ARTISTS
SUCH AS STAYKIDS' CHANGBIN,
JAY PARK, BIBI, AND PH-1
ALREADY RECOGNIZED AS A SKILLED RAPPER
BY KOREAN HIP-HOP FANS
AFTER APPEARING ON A SURVIVAL PROGRAM
AT THE AGE OF 17
PERFORMING AT INTERNATIONAL FESTIVALS
SUCH AS COACHELLA AND LOLLAPALOOZA
MILLI SHOWED OFF HER PRESENCE
Oh!
This artist uploaded an application video
using the SHOW ME THE MONEY format,
so I was pretty intrigued.
I was quite surprised.
Show me the power
#SMTM12APPLICATION
Show me the money
SHE USED A HASHTAG SHE WROTE IN KOREAN
A RAPPER WHO PERFORMED AT COACHELLA?
SHE'LL BEAT EVERYONE, THIS WILL BE FUN
MILLI IS SERIOUSLY APPLYING?
SHE'S GOING TO WIN FOR SURE
WOW, MILLI IS JOINING?
IS THIS POSSIBLE? IS IT REAL?
FOR REAL? OH, MY!
HEIGHTENED EXPECTATIONS
AT THE NEWS OF MILLI'S APPLICATION
She's really skilled,
so I'm looking forward to seeing her rap.
I believe the other contestants
should be on their guard.
MILLI IS ENJOYING HER TIME
CHATTING WITH OTHER CONTESTANTS
I know MILLI
because MILLI is a big star in Thailand.
Even my mom knows MILLI.
It's so cool
that I met her here.
I'm so happy
that MILLI followed me.
ANOTHER CONTESTANT RECOGNIZED MILLI
AND APPROACHED HER
I saw
your performance two years ago,
and the part
where you jumped rope on stage
was really extraordinary.
You were so cool in your music video too.
HOW WILL THE GLOBAL ARTIST MILLI DO
AT THE PRELIMINARY AUDITION?
WHEREVER SHE IS
SHE'S FULL OF ENERGY
STILL HYPED UP DURING THE INTERVIEW
WHY DID SHE APPLY
TO SHOW ME THE MONEY 12?
I heard it's going to be
like a global audition.
It feels like an Olympic competition.
You know, I'm from Thailand.
I feel like a hometown hero from there.
This is really hard for me.
This is like a test for me.
You'll see something good from Thailand.
I think you might like it.
THEY'RE MEETING AS A PRODUCER
AND CONTESTANT AFTER A COLLABORATION
MILLI!
MILLI.
EVERYONE IS LOOKING FORWARD
TO MILLI'S EVALUATION
Oh, my God
I don't know why I'm here
But I will shoot my shot
Run around in the field
I ain't got no fear
But sometimes I cry
Wiping my own tears
Somebody know me from Rosetta
Maybe Coachella
I rap something with mirror, mirror
Not sure you understand
I was performing
If you remember
I wanna be better and better
That's why I come to get ya
Now all of you please
Listen to the mother
With respect MILLI is gonna be your Omma
Let's be real when I look into this oppa
It's time to enter the arena
To soar to a higher level
Never deal with devil
I will steal that medal
I will eat your soul like I eat my pretzel
Sadhu in temple, wish me luck in battle
I won't show you money but I show my mango
Where the hell my man go?
I don't have a man, yo
I'm the greatest woman
From Bangkok, Thailand
Let's roll
'Cause I gotta go, yeah, I gotta go
Bro, give me the chain, yeah
I need to show
You know flow in my throat, rhyme
Tone in my coat
If you don't know my worth
I can be your coach
Let's go
ENTHUSIASTIC RESPONSE TO MILLI'S RAP
I was about
to give you my phone.
Thank you so much.
Wow.
You're a very good singer.
Thank you!
Very soulful.
- MILLI was really good. I mean...
- I'm so curious.
She began by singing,
but she was so good at it.
It was full of soul.
And then she rapped,
then at the end she was like,
"I can be your coach."
I can be your coach
Let's go
She proved that her skills
weren't overhyped.
I'm so glad.
This is heavy, for real.
GLOBAL ARTIST MILLI PASSES
I watched the previous seasons,
and they were so viral in Thailand.
Even if you don't rap,
you listen to music, and you know K-pop.
That's why I came to Korea.
Because I want to know the culture.
I feel like in Asian countries,
Korea has the strongest hip-hop scene.
CONTESTANTS FROM VARIOUS REGIONS PASSED
THE GLOBAL CONTESTANTS
ARE CELEBRATING TOGETHER
I love it
I love this necklace
Ouch! That hurt.
SHOW ME THE MONEY 12.
SHOW ME THE MONEY.
A TOTAL OF 44 GLOBAL CONTESTANTS PASSED
Yes, sir.
SHOW ME THE MONEY 12'S
GLOBAL PRELIMINARIES ARE OVER
WITH THAT,
ALL REGIONAL PRELIMINARIES ARE OVER
The next mission will be a real stage.
You have to show your skills.
The Fire Pit is just around the corner.
I'm looking forward
to that fire.
It must be pretty warm.
It's so cold right now.
Is it really hot?
It is.
- It's really hot.
- It is?
Even if it's far away?
Yeah, it is.
Isn't that too cruel?
SHOW ME THE MONEY'S SIGNATURE MISSION
ALL PASS.
THE 60-SECOND FIRE PIT RAP MISSION
Everyone has to do it.
I know I can do it.
THE SKILLED RAPPERS
BEGIN THE FIERCE COMPETITION
I could sense the depth.
INTENSE BATTLES BETWEEN ROOKIE RAPPERS
TO WIN A PASS NECKLACE
This kind of fresh vibe is what we wanted.
UPGRADED STAGES BY GLOBAL RAPPERS
WHO PASSED THE GLOBAL PRELIMINARIES
AND...
That's such a bummer.
We can't be responsible
for everyone.
WHICH RAPPERS WILL BE ELIMINATED?
THE 60-SECOND RAP MISSION
WILL BEGIN SOON!
A NEW ERA OF HIP-HOP WILL BEGIN
SHOW ME THE MONEY 12
MC KIM JINPYO
A place where limitless potential
is proven,
a place with an even bigger
and hotter stage,
SHOW ME THE MONEY 12.
Gwangju,
Jeju,
Busan,
Seoul,
and beyond Korea, to global auditions.
A record-breaking number
of 36,000 skilled rappers...
participated in the preliminaries.
And among them,
only 152 survived.
Standing at the line
between survival and elimination,
will the rappers be able
to keep their necklaces?
They will only have 60 seconds each
to prove themselves.
The countdown begins now.
WAITING ROOM
Oh, ***!
Busan.
THE FIRST CONTESTANTS TO ENTER
AFTER THE REGIONAL PRELIMINARIES
Say Busan!
BUSAN
THE BUSAN CONTESTANTS HAVE ALL ARRIVED
NEXT ARE THE CONTESTANTS FROM JEJU
OKASHII is a crew
with a young and cool vibe.
JEJU
Dbo?
Is Dbo the one with the long hair?
There were Dbo and OKASHII from Jeju.
JEJU CONTESTANTS HAVE ALL ENTERED
They surprised me a bit.
FLEEKY BANG and Tray B from Gwangju.
I was excited since there were rappers
active right now.
GWANGJU
FLEEKY BANG and Tray B.
GWANGJU CONTESTANTS HAVE ALL ENTERED
They're powerful contestants.
TIME FOR CONTESTANTS FROM SEOUL
WITH THE BIGGEST NUMBER
They're here.
CONTESTANTS FROM SEOUL KEEP POURING IN
- Royal 44.
- Royal 44. Wow.
He was dressed
like Michael Jackson.
I've always
been a fan of OXYNOVA.
OXYNOVA is cool.
NOSUN,
ZENE THE ZILLA.
Hey, it's Khundi Panda.
Yo, Microdot.
MANY WELL-KNOWN RAPPERS ARE ENTERING
Is he still great at rapping?
SEOUL
Hello.
There were lots
of skilled rappers
among the Seoul contestants.
Seoul really is packed
with strong contenders.
- Oh, hi.
- Marv.
What's up?
THE WAITING ROOM IS SOON FILLED
WITH CONTESTANTS
ANOTHER CONTESTANT ENTERS
NOWIMYOUNG.
HAON.
The one who seemed
to have the most powerful aura
was without a doubt HAON.
NOWIMYOUNG was next to him.
WOW
This is insane.
Seeing HAON in person,
ALL CONTESTANTS FROM SEOUL HAVE ENTERED
it felt even more surreal.
GLOBAL
CURIOUS
Wow.
ALSO CURIOUS
Global?
THE GLOBAL CONTESTANTS
BEGIN ENTERING STRAIGHT AWAY
Wow. This is insane.
They're really
global contestants.
GAZES FOCUSED ON THE GLOBAL CONTESTANTS
AS IT'S THE FIRST TIME FOR THE SERIES
GLOBAL
And from Japan, maybe Red Eye?
He's really popular in Japan.
JB.
I heard he's really famous.
ARTIST OF THE YEAR / BEST MALE ARTIST
BEST LIVE PERFORMER / BEST HIP HOP ARTIST
IMPACT SONG OF THE YEAR: 'I'M WAITING'
BEST ALTERNATIVE SONG, GOLD: 'LIGHTER'
BEST LYRICAL SONG, BRONZE: 'I'M WAITING'
HONG KONG HIP-HOP / R&B GENRE AWARD
WHAT'S GOOD MUSIC AWARDS 2022
WON AS MANY AS SEVEN AWARDS
He's like the godfather
of Hong Kong hip-hop.
He's going to be a bit scary.
I got overpowered by his aura.
THE GLOBAL CONTESTANTS CONTINUE ENTERING
DOUBLE DOWN?
He's cool.
ANOTHER GLOBAL CONTESTANT ENTERS
It's Flowsik.
Flowsik is here too?
I never imagined.
I was like,
"So Flowsik really did exist."
THE WAITING ROOM IS COMPLETELY FULL NOW
ONLY ONE SPOT LEFT
Is *** still not here?
I want to see ***.
I want to see *** too.
WHO IS THE LAST CONTESTANT
THAT EVERYONE IS EXCITED TO SEE?
GAZES
FOCUSED
THE LAST CONTESTANT TO ENTER
MILLI
She's finally here.
Wow, it's MILLI.
MILLI's a superstar.
She's a rapper and singer
that everyone in Thailand knows.
She performed
at Coachella.
Is she here
to win first place?
They can't bring a superstar here.
WITH THE SHOCKING ENTRANCE OF MILLI
ALL 152 CONTESTANTS HAVE ENTERED
FOR THE SECOND PRELIMINARY ROUND
Today is the 60-second rap mission.
Wow!
It really is a Fire Pit.
A Fire Pit.
Do you guys want to enter the pit?
No.
I don't even want to get close to it.
I'd like to try standing there once.
The name itself is really intense.
You have to bring your own beat.
And show off your rap within 60 seconds.
It's a mission where we can see
the contestants' musicality.
I'm aware that many global contestants
passed the first round.
That means there are a lot
of skilled rappers.
We'll pick out some cool rappers.
Let's do this.
Wow.
Yo.
This really is a huge scale.
This is cool.
When did this place
turn into a whole city?
Right?
SUDDENLY USING OPERA GLASSES
They put in so much effort
for even the tiny details.
This is amazing.
Is someone living here?
This is like Gotham City.
Wow. Cool.
This is so cool.
It's huge.
That's where
we're going to be when we're rapping?
It's going to be so cool
when we're performing.
This is going to be so fun.
It'll be awesome.
For the 60-second rap mission,
if you get a FAIL
from all four producer teams,
you'll be eliminated immediately.
But if you get a PASS
from at least one team,
you'll go onto the next stage.
That's it!
THE 2ND PRELIMINARY ROUND, THE FIRE PIT
THE 60-SECOND RAP MISSION
STARTING NOW!
WHO WILL START OFF
There will be a lot of pressure.
THE 60-SECOND RAP MISSION?
Who will go first?
I'm so curious
who the first contestant will be.
The second preliminary round.
The first to go is...
Who's going to be the first?
THE FIRST CONTESTANT TO GO ON STAGE...
Luci Gang.
For real?
Wow...
No way.
She's really good.
Really?
She's popping these days.
LUCI GANG HEADS TOWARD THE STAGE
WHILE RECEIVING SUPPORT FROM THE OTHERS
I hope she does well.
OHHHH
We can see them over there.
We can see their silhouette.
First contestant, please enter.
LUCI GANG
Luci Gang.
Hello.
PAUSE
You can walk up to the front.
Okay.
Wow.
It's your first time
on SHOW ME THE MONEY.
- Yes.
- And you're the first contestant.
How do you feel right now?
This feels so unreal.
Honestly, I can't believe
this is happening right now.
Then shall we hear your rap
to make it believable?
- Yeah.
- If you're ready,
take a deep breath and go.
You must be nervous.
I FEEL NERVOUS TOO
I can't believe she's going first.
She seems nervous.
Good luck.
Start the beat.
Let's go!
Good luck!
'SK8BRDER' PROD. LUCKY BANDO
Yeah, okay, okay
Okay, okay
I only do what I please
I just got it started, I'm not parking
Cut off my middle finger
8 Fingers like cartoon characters
I'm gone in a flash
Adios, I leave no trace
Open up a path, move everyone aside
Slide through and take the lead
Catch me if you can DiCaprio
Nice.
Paint over your scenario
Draw a line over it like Basquiat
Step out of the same orbit
Fill the blank spaces
If you're going to hesitate, move aside
Your destination is my starting line
- Baggy jeans likes a skateboarder
- What?
- They pressed one.
-  On my feet
I'm getting off the wall
From spring to winter
Sliding across the packed road
Gotta go, gotta go
Gotta go, gotta go, no return
- That was better than I expected.
- Thank you.
The first contestant.
3 PASS.
She did well.
That was good.
That was a good start.
FIRST CONTESTANT GOT A PASS
THE MISSION GOT OFF TO A GOOD START
3 PASS is pretty good.
You seemed pretty nervous at first,
but while performing on stage,
I felt that you loosened up a bit.
That was good.
What I liked the most
is your unique voice.
AGREE
It was nice.
Thank you.
Congratulations!
PAUSE
See you at the 3rd round.
Where should I go?
Exit to your right.
Okay. Thank you.
We did think Luci Gang did great, but...
Rather than a FAIL,
we thought her performance
wasn't good enough for an ALL PASS.
I'll do my best
to prepare for the next round.
Next contestant, please.
OXYNOVA
Wow.
OXYNOVA.
Wow. OXYNOVA.
I'm excited to see OXYNOVA.
Oh! OXY!
Everyday happy rapper.
Let's go.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Hi, I'm OXYNOVA.
He's so bling-bling.
BLING BLING
DAY OF THE SEOUL PRELIMINARIES
I'm here to show my support.
OXYNOVA ATTENDED THE AUDITION
WITH SUPERBEE'S SUPPORT
We're here.
Yng & Rich. Come on, what's up!
OXYNOVA IS IN SUPERBEE'S AGENCY
RAPPER OXYNOVA JOINS YNG & RICH
LABEL YNG & RICH RECRUITS RAPPER OXYNOVA
RELEASED A TOTAL OF 17 ALBUMS
SINCE HE DEBUTED IN KOREA IN 2022
OXYNOVA IS PROVING HIMSELF
THROUGH CONSTANT EFFORT AND RESULTS
Were you a good student?
Yes!
What school did you go to?
McGill University in Canada.
ATTENDED MCGILL UNIVERSITY,
ONE OF THE TOP 3 UNIVERSITIES IN CANADA
I lived in Korea until I was about three,
then lived the rest of my life in Canada.
I never applied to this show before
because first of all,
my Korean was lacking.
I've known about this contestant
for about two years.
His songs are all in English.
When I first met him,
he hardly spoke any Korean.
Has your Korean improved a lot?
Yes, it's been about
three years since I came to Korea.
Right? You've improved.
Yes.
I studied Korean really hard.
I thought this was my chance
to rekindle Korean hip-hop here.
And my grandma, grandpa,
my mom, dad. Hey, Mom and Dad.
I miss y'all.
I wanted to say hi to them on TV.
That's nice.
OXYNOVA, you always seem
to have a positive vibe.
What's your secret?
I believe there are many things
to be grateful for in any circumstances.
So I try to always be happy.
Gratitude.
Yes, sir.
Okay. Shall we hear it, then?
Let's go! Come on!
I'm excited for this.
'TRAP IDOL' PROD. KNUCK BEATZ
Let's go.
Look
Play after play
Like I'm a movie star
My mom told me to be humble
I answered, you know
I was born to ball
All the resolutions from my childhood
I done did it all
My future dream in elementary school
Make some big money
I don't do anything shameful
'Cause I'm big stunting
The type to pull up in a 458
Self-introduction, OXYNOVA
Mister never ever late
Show me the money
I'll blow out the candles, bring the cakes
I do great at anything
I'm the ace of my life, man
My life's a marathon, I'm still on my way
I turn back and see
I been doing pretty great, uh
Check my temperature
It's 100 degrees, uh
My name's finally hung on a TV show
Even if my Korean's awkward
I still defeat everyone
He wrote a lot of Korean lyrics.
Baby, I'm a pop star
Turned trapstar turned rapstar
I came to show you hip-hop
This my backyard
If I can do it, you can do it too
ALL PASS
And this money makin music
You can't *** my crew! Wassup?
OXYNOVA ALL PASS
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
ALL PASS!
Wow.
His rap is really stable.
Fire.
Thank you.
Was that the first ALL PASS?
Yeah.
Cool.
There were a lot
of Korean lyrics this time.
AGREE
Yeah, the verse...
The first part was all Korean.
That helped me get immersed.
My mom told me to be humble
I answered, you know
I was born to ball
All the resolutions from my childhood
I done did it all
I think I swayed to the beat
for the first time during OXYNOVA's stage.
I smiled sincerely
for the first time too.
That was so touching.
You lost a lot
of weight too, right?
Yes. I wanted
to become like you, so I worked out.
How much weight did you lose?
I think I lost about 10 kg.
You said you studied
a lot of Korean.
What's your favorite Korean?
HAHAHA
"Favorite Korean"?
What do you mean by that?
Korean word? Are you talking about a word?
- A sentence or whatever.
- A sentence?
My favorite Korean word
is "morning."
Morning.
A new beginning.
"A new beginning." Wow.
You really have great energy.
Yeah. Your attitude is awesome.
I wanted to say something.
Can I say it here?
The reason why I applied
to SHOW ME THE MONEY 12
wasn't just for fun.
I'm not doing this as a joke, either.
I wanted to show everyone
how I'm improving and how much effort
I'm putting into this.
So please keep watching and supporting me.
He seemed
really energetic and positive.
He seemed to have a really healthy vibe.
He's someone I want to support,
and he even has the musicality,
skills, and diligence.
I feel like he'll keep gaining momentum.
I just love
the kind of energy he's giving off.
Yeah, it shows.
It does.
I'll work hard as if there's no tomorrow.
I'll do my best and return
for the next round.
Thank you. Let's go.
I kind of regret
asking what his favorite Korean was.
The question was a bit weird.
"What's your favorite Korean?"
It wasn't even,
"What's your favorite Korean dish?"
He said he studied Korean for three years,
so I asked what he liked the most.
That was good.
That's your charm.
What's your favorite English, then?
Me? "Morning."
USED TO HIS HUMOR
Okay. Nice one.
NEXT IS 2KEY
2KEY!
How many keys do you have?
2KEY.
Xiaolongbao!
I get why NOWIMYOUNG
is so popular.
LOOK AT HIS HANDSOME FACE
We look too similar.
No, not at all.
THE THREE SEEM QUITE CLOSE
DURING THE JEJU PRELIMINARIES
STARTING WITH RAF SANDOU'S PASS
Thank you.
MASON HOME ALSO PASSES
Congratulations.
JEFFREY WHITE ALSO PASSES
Thank you.
HIP-HOP CREW OKASHII WHICH STARTED OFF
AS A CLUB AT Y UNIVERSITY
GETTING ATTENTION FOR THEIR EXPERIMENTAL
AND TRENDY SOUNDS
RAPPING AND SELF-PRODUCING AS WELL
ALL THREE PASSED
THE REGIONAL PRELIMINARIES
Next rapper, MASON HOME.
MASON HOME IS THE FIRST OKASHII MEMBER
TO DO THE 60-SECOND RAP MISSION
Hello.
"OKASHII"?
MASON HOME.
Hello.
Wow, you look pretty cool.
I'm MASON HOME from the crew OKASHII.
Nice to meet you.
I love OKASHII.
I'm curious to see
how the OKASHII members will do
in SHOW ME THE MONEY 12.
I'll take a deep breath
and begin.
- Yes, sir.
- Okay!
Okay. I hope this is good.
I'm excited.
'MASON #1' PROD. BY MASON HOME
I'm on that
I'm on that high like a free throw
You know I never miss these
You all talk too much
Ain't real talk
I'm on that
I'm on that level
You're in the back
One time, one
I don't fall back
Unless it's trap, okay?
I'm back on the stu, not tired
My trap, my ego
It'll never be yours
Bringing that back my cheat code
Okay, discovered chronicle
Crack that, crack that, crack that
Okay, still focus
My life surreal hypnosis
Their income sources, nonsense
FAIL
You'll never get it
Okay, just make a choice
Okay, staying strong forever
Okay, keeping someone in check
Okay, teammates forever
PASS
Thank you.
MASON HOME 3 PASS
It wasn't an ALL PASS.
3 PASS.
Thank you so much.
It's been a long time
since we saw someone
who had such a good mix
of visuals, beat, and rap.
A well-rounded rapper.
You had a unique vibe.
I loved it.
I feel like your tracks
will do really well.
Thank you.
MASON HOME's rap was really my style,
so I gave him a pass for the first round.
I was even more impressed today.
OKASHII'S FIRST CONTESTANT
MASON HOME GOT A 3 PASS
He really is something.
I feel like he'll be able
to do a lot of different styles.
RAF SANDOU
NEXT IS OKASHII'S RAF SANDOU
I'm excited for Raf Sandou.
SQUEEZE
Raf Sandou!
Hello.
He's so nervous.
I read through your profile,
and I found something interesting.
You studied in Japan for 16 years
and attended the same
middle and high school as me.
That's right.
Tokyo Korean School?
Yes.
Were there any good stories
about me at TKS?
HAHA
You're asking that yourself?
TRYING TO SPREAD
GOOD STORIES ABOUT HIMSELF
You know...
Since I was in middle school,
Block B was already huge.
Then when you came to film at our school,
there was a huge buzz.
Were you there at the time?
Yes.
That's so cool.
WHAT A SURPRISE
You asked, and you're surprised.
What is this?
This won't affect your evaluation, right?
Of course not.
I was just joking.
COME ON...
Shall we hear it, then?
Okay.
TKS, let's get it.
Give me that.
'26' PROD. BY MATTHEW
1, 2
Swervin around the city
On that flow
Imma tap it in
Went in circles
Coast to coast
Now I'm back at it
I feel like my waist
Is gonna touch the ground
Cuz I'm saggin it
People talk behind my back
But there's peppermint in my mouth
The morning sun comes up
And I stay up all night again
And at the stu I go insane
I go Toy Story
While everyone's asleep
I change these flows, uh huh
I ain't got break
He's good!
It's nice.
Yeah, I'm taking all the swag
Pop out I go low now
I startle everyone
Yeah, I look like a ghost
Mad pressure on em
Puttin that for bottom
My feet are touching the ground
I bring new pronunciations
Yeah, 247 I'm on a roll now
I dress up head to the toe now
I'm back to the road now
I know my life going crazy
Sign the contract
And change my bracelet
Chain hanging, taking responsibility
That's the real deal business
ALL PASS
Stick to the code we doin the most
Deeper than music
RAF SANDOU ALL PASS
Thank you.
That was so cool.
ALL PASS!
CHEERING
Thank you, senior.
"Senior"?
Hey, that's a bit...
THE SENIOR IS HAPPY
You got an ALL PASS, not a 1 PASS.
Why are you only thanking your senior?
STARTLED
There are other judges here too, you know?
I...
I'm so upset!
Thank you all so much.
Shoutout to TKS!
TKS!
- I'm so relieved.
- I told you he'd pass.
As soon as I heard it,
I loved the beat.
Yeah.
And right when I wanted to hear
something else, you switched the beat.
And you even changed your tone.
That was really interesting.
I go Toy Story while everyone's asleep
I change these flows, uh huh
I ain't got break
RAF SANDOU MADE VARIATIONS
TO HIS BEAT AND TONE
The OKASHII members are so good.
You all have great instincts.
Thank you.
To be honest, I...
Hello.
Thank you.
I'm LOCO.
During the first preliminaries,
I gave the other two OKASHII members
a pass necklace.
TELLING A GOOD STORY ABOUT HIMSELF
Why are you suddenly saying that?
I'm the one who gave you
a pass for the first round.
Right.
Then the OKASHII members
were all picked by GRAY and LOCO's team?
- Yeah.
- We're trying to coax them.
We could say it's fate.
Then I want to ask just in case...
- Yes?
- Do you have
a producer team you have in mind?
ANXIOUS
A team you want to work with?
We'd love anyone who wants us.
When it's time to choose teams,
everyone starts picking.
We'll be the ones
getting desperate.
You were really cool.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
OKASHII...
They're good. They're cool.
OKASHII members are great at making beats.
Yeah. It was really classy.
It was flawless.
Raf Sandou...
I like that guy.
AM I TREMBLING?
Next rapper.
HE MUST BE ANXIOUS
Last member of OKASHII,
JEFFREY WHITE.
Let's go!
Spike your hair up a bit more.
JEFFREY WHITE
Hello.
I'm JEFFREY WHITE,
and I'm in a team called OKASHII.
Your other members got a PASS.
Yes.
So I'm curious
how you're feeling right now.
Honestly, I'm so relieved.
And I believe I should do
just as well as them
and get a PASS too.
Don't you feel a bit pressured?
Pressure? Well... I'm anxious.
I'm pretty nervous.
Okay.
Shall we begin?
All right.
I'll begin.
DJ! Let's go!
'PROTOOLS' PROD. MATTHEW
By chance, just give her back
Wirye? That's just too far
It's changed again
Why are you talkin like that
My girlfriend is a secret
Gwang BEI Seoul Tokyo London
Lights out, and it's a blink away
Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow
Tomorrow, and tomorrow
Leave and go home
Miss you already that gon
Make her boyfriend
Keep ringing but keep moving
I keep my distance, leave it empty
- It's a little disappointing.
- Yeah.
Time to go to Jeju
That's enough
Babe stop showing ur talent
I'll press FAIL.
FAIL
The rappers
Are the kindest in the club
When I hold you, a stranger
And take you outside
It changed again
And they say Jeffrey Jeffrey Jeffrey
Thank you.
PASS
JEFFREY WHITE 1 PASS
Congratulations.
Good job.
JEFFREY WHITE GOT 1 PASS
RAF SANDOU & MASON HOME ARE RELIEVED
For me, there's a clear reason
why you only got 1 PASS.
Your live wasn't as stable
as the other members.
Right.
But I'll look forward
to your rap in the next round.
Okay.
Before you started rapping in Jeju,
I think you used a Yadom inhaler
to relax your nerves.
What?
STARTLED
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
What do you mean?
I learned about Yadom then.
Oh, Yadom. Yadom. Yadom.
Yes. "Yadom."
DURING THE JEJU PRELIMINARIES
Let me use this first.
INHALE
SNIFFLE
Do you use that before rapping?
Yeah, we all use this.
Really? Can I try?
SUDDEN SMELL TEST?
Breathe in hard.
I like this too.
You have one as well.
This is mine.
I've been using one ever since I tried it.
DON'T MIX UP THE TERMS!
Yadom!
The inhaler.
OKASHII SHOOK THE JUDGES
That startled me.
Gosh...
I thought you said something else.
Get your heads out of the gutter!
It seemed like you forgot
to inhale it before your rap.
Yeah, I forgot.
Right?
- Use it next time.
- I will.
I'm sure you'll do better.
Anyway, great job.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
Congratulations.
Don't forget the inhaler next time.
All right.
Watch your pronunciation.
- Yadom!
- Yadom. Okay.
Be careful.
I keep getting startled.
ALL MEMBERS OF OKASHII HAVE PASSED
I FORGOT TO USE THE INHALER
THE NEXT CONTESTANT APPEARS
JUST BEFORE GOING ON STAGE
IS HE MAKING A CALL?
Next contestant, come on out.
Let's go.
GIDORA
What?
What? Is he making a call?
He's calling someone on stage?
Are you calling someone?
Hello.
Hang on.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Why is he on the phone?
Can you introduce yourself
and tell us why you applied?
STILL ON THE PHONE...
Why don't you hang up first?
Later. Okay?
FINISHED HIS BUSINESS
Okay.
Who were you calling? We're curious.
CURIOUS
Who were you on the phone with?
It's a secret.
Okay...
HAHA
That's a strange concept.
He has a lot of secrets.
I'm excited for his rap.
Shall we hear it, then?
Okay.
Should I be anxious?
Drop that man
He has a clear concept.
HELLO? CAN YOU HEAR ME
FROM THE WAITING ROOM?
YEAH, WE CAN HEAR YOU
With a concept like this,
he'd better be really good.
STILL STICKING TO HIS CONCEPT
RINGING
'ROAR' PROD. BY HAN
Don't hide it, your owner's GPT
You're scheduled for replacement
Being human pays off
Guys stuck in forums
Take your copy-and-paste leashes
Take them to a bar
Wash it down with soju
And call it paradise
Then...
It's a FAIL, right?
NOD
FAIL
Pillow on my cheek
Instead of a gunstock
SHAKING HIS HEAD
3 FAILS SO FAR
He's not up to par.
GIDORA IS ELIMINATED
FIRST ELIMINATION
FOR THE 60-SECOND RAP MISSION
EVERYONE EXCLAIMS
Oh my god.
Thank you.
Great work.
STILL STICKING TO HIS CONCEPT
I got eliminated!
Tell us who you were calling.
It's a secret.
He's really calling
on the phone?
Just fake.
I've never seen anyone like that before.
I'm really curious, though.
Yeah.
What kind of concept was that?
I guess I kind of overdid my concept.
I'm so disappointed.
AFTER THE FIRST ELIMINATION
NERVOUS
THE CONTESTANTS GROW NERVOUS
AFTER SEEING THE FIRE PIT
I feel so nervous.
I ain't going nowhere.
The Fire Pit...
Did you see that square?
It's ready to retract.
Next contestant.
$TILL.J.CARK
A global contestant?
J.Cark?
He's Japanese, right?
The first global contestant.
Let's go!
CHEERING FOR THE FIRST GLOBAL CONTESTANT
Nice to meet you.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm $till.J.Cark,
from Japan.
Nice to meet you all.
Wow, he's cool.
How did you end up applying
to SHOW ME THE MONEY 12?
I thought it was
a great opportunity for me.
It says you're a salesman.
Could we ask
what kind of stuff you're selling?
I'm working
at an electronic product shop.
NERVOUS
How do you feel right now?
I'm very nervous.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Drop that! Drop that!
'ARCHIVE' PROD. HAAKE
Lower my position and take'n do again
Red eyes, riding the turbulence
I like his tone.
Shake night weekend
Mayday
If losting guidance
Come ma hood
Endless pain
Crushing pressure
Those who can't even try
Are on sale
I'm not cheap
Not lowering my price
Endlessly kick kick kick ballin
Slip out and wear it
Shouting from the real I can't escape
Wavering with no anchor
Unshakable confidence
The road ahead isn't clear
Things that are too right
I don't wanna this
Justice and evil
Are a matter of perspective
Fly the night
Go forward and dive
Having fun is my style
If I don't stand out
There's no meaning in ma life
Pulse pumping 1, 2
2&3 No tap
Pride shield while you're scurrying away
I work and scrawl it down again
Still doing the build-up?
This is a limited model
Why why rely on someone else?
Even when I cross the sea
Trash ma self
The roots only I have
I stand tall with that
$TILL.J.CARK ALL PASS
FIRST GLOBAL CONTESTANT WITH AN ALL PASS
ALL PASS!
Seeing the rapper I picked
for the preliminaries
get an ALL PASS...
SHOWED A POWERFUL RAP
AT THE GLOBAL PRELIMINARIES
AND GOT A PASS NECKLACE FROM HUKKY
This is what it's like to feel proud.
It's the first time I felt that.
You have a powerful energy
when you're rapping.
While I'm rapping,
I feel like I can truly be myself.
Your energy is incredible.
I loved it.
I love it!
Thank you.
Weren't there Korean lyrics at the end?
"I stand tall"?
Was it "I stand tall"?
The roots only I have
I stand tall with that
It was charming.
The rap was entertaining.
Thank you.
You were cool.
FIRST GLOBAL CONTESTANT
TO GET AN ALL PASS
I got an ALL PASS.
I'm from Japan,
and I am no joke, so keep watching me.
Wow.
He has a unique style.
He's pretty handsome.
He has the vibe of an idol.
He has a cool look.
He's handsome.
You're really cool.
Everyone
had their own unique styles,
so it's quite fun to watch.
They're all different.
I'm not sure if it's because
it's my first time on this program,
but everyone seems so stylish.
I think their visuals and outfits
really stand out for this season.
Yeah.
Their own branding stands out.
And if they have the musicality as well,
that would be an even bigger plus.
We can't ignore that factor.
"I am young."
"I'm young."
NOWIMYOUNG.
- Hello.
I'm NOWIMYOUNG,
and I'm a rapper from KC.
UP-AND-COMING RAPPER NOWIMYOUNG
WENT VIRAL ON SOCIAL MEDIA WITH ONE CLIP
I CAME FOR THE MUSIC
BUT I GOT DISTRACTED BY HIS FACE
HE'S TALL AND HANDSOME
You're really
good-looking and tall.
I love your style too.
You're getting a lot of attention
in the hip-hop scene these days.
I'm curious whether you feel
a bit pressured by that.
No, I'm not pressured.
You're not?
Everyone knows
I'm not someone
who only raps,
so I'll do my best.
Okay.
I'm excited for this.
Let's go.
I'm excited for NOWIMYOUNG's rap.
I wonder how he'll do.
Let's go.
'AH AH' PROD. BY SUDO
He's starting.
Yeah, yeah, let's go
KC, KC
I don't fall for obvious schemes
If you're gonna copy me
Do it properly
It's crazy here
A fan of a fanboy
Viral marketing is lame
No matter how much you try
Your songs are only pocket change
All the money you spend on it
I use it thoughtlessly
Go wild, there's no meaning to success
In other words, no self-esteem
In other words, pathetic kids
2017 Not what you grew up with
Copying someone's silhouette
Extra million, borrow drama
Now see ya, it's about you
- I don't think that's an ALL PASS.
-  Let's go again
I drownin'
Myself
Cryin
This place
Too obvious
I'm not sure about him.
KC, KC, that's KC, KC, yo
NOWIMYOUNG 2 PASS
Congratulations.
Thank you.
That was fun and nice.
The track was great.
That was pretty good.
Personally,
I think you'd be strong on record,
but your performance on stage
was a bit lacking in several factors.
So it would be better if you could work
on improving that.
Thank you.
From the next round,
there will be missions
where you compete with others,
so I think you should make
preparations for that.
I understand.
You did great. Good job.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
NOWIMYOUNG 2 PASS
Good job.
He's a kind of rapper we need, though.
What do you mean?
Songs like that
could add some uniqueness during a battle.
Battling with that kind of rap
could actually be helpful.
I'm looking forward to the next round.
I did see his potential,
so I think he'll play a great role
in SHOW ME THE MONEY 12.
I'd like to see him grow and improve.
I'm excited to see that.
Me too.
Q. ARE YOU PLEASED WITH THE RESULT?
I'm happy.
I survived. That's good.
Awesome.
Next contestant, please enter.
Let's go.
ILLHWAKCHEONGEUMBOYY
Illhwakcheongeumboyy.
That's a cool name.
What does that mean?
- Hello.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, I'm illhwakcheongeumboyy
from Suyu-dong.
Why is it "illhwakcheongeumboyy"?
I'm guessing it means
you want to earn a fortune.
- Something like that.
- Yes.
Okay. Why did you apply
to SHOW ME THE MONEY?
I thought about it,
and I'm just desperate for this.
I saw my friends
appearing on TV and audition programs
and succeeding.
While I was doing part-time jobs,
everyone else was earning
a living with music and releasing albums.
I really envied that.
All right.
Then relax your nerves
and call the beat when you're ready.
Yo yo!
Check illhwakcheongeum!
Give me the beat.
"Check illhwakcheongeum."
'HEY ARCHER GIVE ME THE BEAT'
PROD. BY BRIAN
I feel like I lost myself, I turn back
Numerous problems I can't overcome myself
When I thought again about the cause
I realize I need money to live
My head's filled with more money
They say they'll earn money
And throw it around
But I don't get it
That's why I'm keeping my distance
Those pretending to be okay in real life
I'm different from them
Getting all this stolen
Other rappers are all just copying
They think it's natural
That's why you're not ripe
But who would challenge them
Sorry for acting so tough
But I'll just continue
It doesn't matter now
If anyone tries to stop me
I don't need you either
So please just get lost
God, what else must I do
This is the path I dreamed of for 10 years
She's leaving me too now
It's driving me crazy
What do you mean
I've been doing this for 10 years
So what else must I do now
Would things change tomorrow?
Should I hold on?
Or should I think about what I did wrong
And repent and pray again?
How desperate must I be
For them to give me a glance
All those people, they're so cruel
How much should I crumble
For them to give me a glance
It hurts too much to ask for love
How much should I crumble
For them to give me a glance
How desperate must I be
Reality drags low
While my dream is up so high
It'll be different this time
I'll earn it this time, Mom
Okay.
ILLHWAKCHEONGEUMBOYY ALL PASS
ALL PASS.
Thank you.
His desperation must've come through.
I got the chills.
But honestly,
I really teared up.
Me too.
It was like he was inviting us
into his own life.
TOTALLY AGREE
He really expressed his desperation.
He made the whole stage his territory.
Yeah.
Thank you so much.
In a way, it was a fast-paced rap,
but the music was really chill.
They actually made a good combo.
I think it helped deliver his emotions.
Instead of hearing a verse,
I feel like we heard his story.
When it was over, I just wanted
to go and give him a hug.
"It's okay. It'll all be okay."
You know what I mean, right?
It made me want to comfort him.
The rap was full of emotions,
but I'm curious how you'll do
with music that is more laid back
and less emotional.
All right.
I'll prepare something like that.
Thank you so much.
Great job.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
HIS PERFORMANCE MOVED THE PRODUCERS
This feels
like a dream to me.
It's actually my ninth time
applying to SHOW ME THE MONEY.
I've never passed the first round before.
I just wished that my voice
could reach one team,
but it reached all of them.
I'm so happy.
He didn't even need any rhymes.
But there weren't
many performances
like that in SHOW ME THE MONEY 11.
I think the three-year gap
along with the recession in this industry
made them more desperate.
Sincerity
really moves people's hearts.
How was the first round, guys?
It was my first time being a judge,
but everyone was so good.
We can't be sure yet.
We don't know how they'll do on stage.
Yeah.
Drip Dawg.
A RAPPER JAY PARK SELECTED
IN THE SEOUL PRELIMINARIES
Hello.
I gave him a pass
on the first round.
His tone was very stable,
and his lyrics seemed sincere.
DRIP DAWG'S 60-SECOND RAP BEGINS
DRIP DAWG IS ELIMINATED
Good job.
ANGO, WHO JAY PARK PICKED
ANGO IS ELIMINATED
Thank you.
- Thank you.
You judged him
for the first round, right?
He did a really solemn rap
for the first round.
But he did a singing rap this time.
It wasn't that natural.
THE RAPPERS JAY PARK PICKED
IN THE FIRST ROUND ARE GETTING ELIMINATED
It's too bad.
DKAY
DKAY.
Hello, I'm a rapper from Australia.
I'm DKAY, 25 years old.
Hello.
DKAY.
DK? Isn't it him?
The singer from December?
CONTESTANTS ARE NOT FAMILIAR WITH HIM
He's pretty cool.
SUDDENLY INTERESTED
The reason I applied
is because I wanted people to hear
Australian rap and hip-hop
and show more love and support for it.
He's even holding his mic
in a really cool way.
AUSTRALIA SWAG
All right, then.
COPYING DKAY
Shall we hear your rap?
Let's hear it.
Let's get it.
Drop the beat, my bro.
'BOUNCE' PROD. DANCEWITHTHEDEVILZ
Stacking paper
Getting cheddar, I've been making changes
They can tell that I've been different
Wanna know my name is
Been a couple years brother
I've been making moves
I like u and her baby
Please don't make me choose
Don't get the wrong idea
Look at me
He's cool.
Yeh my girlies
So I told her it's okay
Told her pipe down we could do this
In the dark, so tell me
A boi that go harder than me
K town what I'm prouder to be
I've been stacking and flipping
I keep wanting more money
Every day
I've been thinkin'
About that money domino
I pray to God
Make a milly on my pay days
I don't wanna be broke
Yeh I hustle on my cake day
You're just a drunk
Stop talking and just listen
Come here and blow it twice, not once
Sun up till sun down
I gotta go and hustle baby
They think I'm nonchalant
Ain't with these people lately
I've been working overtime
Yeh I think I'm crazy
Shawtie wanna get it on
But I just tell her maybe
ALL PASS
Thank you.
- ALL PASS
- Let's get it!
ALL PASS.
That was cool.
DKAY!
Love Jay Park.
I knew it. Let's go!
Thank you very much.
You were really cool.
Wow.
He's really good.
That was cool.
ALL PASS!
I feel like Australian English
has a bit more punch to it.
And it showed
when he was rapping in Korean too.
I loved it.
Thank you.
My friends too...
You know? They are...
There are good rappers.
There are so many rappers
who are more skilled than me.
I wanted to show that there
are great rappers in Australia too.
I evaluated him
for the global audition,
and he had a strong Australian accent.
I could feel the weight,
and his rap skills backed it up.
I'm excited to see your future stages.
Thank you.
DURING THE GLOBAL PRELIMINARIES
DKAY SHOWED OFF HIS PRESENCE
WITH HIS AUSTRALIAN ACCENT
There are a lot
of people from Australia and New Zealand.
You're the first person
with an accent so strong.
I love it, though.
DKAY WON JAY PARK OVER
WITH HIS STRONG AUSTRALIAN ACCENT
His style,
and the way he talks...
His rap...
It's the kind of vibe only people
living in Australia can give off.
That was pretty unique for this season.
That kind of Australian accent.
So the rap itself was unique.
I liked how he brought out
the uniqueness of his country.
Anyway, I really enjoyed it.
We'll see you at the 3rd round.
Okay. Thank you.
Great job.
Good job, bro.
DKAY FROM AUSTRALIA, ALL PASS
His Australian accent is so cool.
HIS ACCENT MAKES THEM WANT TO MIMIC IT
Pay day
Yo! Show me the money, Baby!
AUS, represent.
You know what it is!
I'll call out the next rapper.
This contestant is quite famous.
A FAMOUS RAPPER?
A repeat applicant for SHOW ME THE MONEY.
GETTING EVEN MORE CURIOUS
AFTER HEARING THE INTRODUCTION
It's ***.
Wow.
Good luck.
WHO IS THE RAPPER?
Let's go! Let's go!
I'm so curious about ***.
Isn't he quite a hot topic?
Next contestant.
Come on out.
EVERYONE IS FOCUSED ON THE NEXT RAPPER
MICRODOT
Wow.
It's really the Microdot we know?
It's been a while.
Microdot.
- Hello.
How have you been?
I've been doing well.
Tell us why you applied
for SHOW ME THE MONEY 12.
I had some things
to take care of until now.
I finally took care of the matter,
but I got too used to spending time alone.
I had no sense of togetherness in my life,
so when I heard the news
about SHOW ME THE MONEY 12,
I wanted to take on the challenge.
I prepared diligently
with the mindset of a rookie rapper.
Wow. A rookie rapper.
I always find myself
rooting for you, Microdot.
You debuted at such a young age,
so you must have gone through a lot
and had a lot of struggles.
But you're always smiling.
I sense a positive vibe from you.
There are a lot of sad people
in the world,
so I should try to be happy.
I love that attitude,
which makes me root for you.
You're so cool.
Thank you.
That's really cool.
I love his mindset.
Now that all my issues are resolved,
please give me the trumpet sound.
I hope he does well.
Microdot, let's get it.
I'm so excited for this.
'99' PROD. STONER TUNES
SHOW ME THE MONEY 12
I'm not a perfect design, no no
But I still got the fire inside, burn slow
Time to start running again, oh oh
99% that left me
Thanks to that, my shoulders are light
Thanks to that, I'm stronger than ever
Thanks to that, I can shout confidently
I protected my place
I'm just a bit smaller and lonelier
Now tell them I've payed them back
Now I'm back in action
Vivid color, only spitting facts
- A rapper, beat, done, checkup
- It's a bit disappointing.
This my new chapter
Even when time has passed, don't miss this
In the end, next to my name
- I tried to dot the periods
- I'm not sure about this.
Show me rappers
High school rappers, overrated rappers
MICRODOT IS ELIMINATED
Good work.
- Great work.
- Thank you.
Good work.
I'll keep supporting you.
- We support you.
- Thank you.
THE WAITING ROOM IS IN SHOCK
No way.
I never imagined
he'd get eliminated.
That's too bad.
It's too bad.
Too bad.
There were some good parts to his rap,
but the way he expressed himself
felt a bit old.
He has talent,
and some factors were good,
but I feel like he needed some guidance.
Still, like Jay Park said,
I can't help
but root for him.
It's really nice
to see him keep trying his best.
He hasn't been active recently,
and he spent a lot of time
without any friends in this field,
so I felt that he was a bit confined
in terms of music.
So I'll be looking forward
to seeing his growth.
I feel really disappointed.
Gosh...
I do feel really upset and disappointed,
but this isn't the end of my career.
I got eliminated
from SHOW ME THE MONEY 12,
but I'll keep doing my best
to get back into music.
So please show your support.
Thank you.
Next contestant, please enter.
Who is it?
TRAY B
- Tray B.
- Hello.
It's him!
Tray B. Wow.
This guy's pretty hype.
I'm so excited.
He's one of the rappers
I'm looking forward to the most.
Hello.
Tray B.
Hello. I'm Tray B,
and I came here
because I thought I was ready.
He's ready.
What did you think was lacking before
that you've improved now?
I think I'm ready
to introduce myself to the world now.
Wow, that's cool.
When you said
you were applying,
what did your agency CEO say?
He told me to do it, no matter what.
He said I could win first place.
Then let's see if he was right.
Shall we hear it?
I'm so excited for this.
I think Tray B will do great.
Drop the beat.
'ANIMAL' PROD. TRAY B, SIG SAUER
Hey, Tray B
Hey, hey
Still with my bros
And we move too tactical
Nobody can't tame us
I'm feelin like I'm animal
Everything I touch turns gold
That so magical
Even if you don't look
My enemies are screaming
Play on the radio
He think he a real
But he's a Mysterio
I can't deal with you
You drink soju, I drink Pérignon
And my flow so flow like Evian
And my flow so tight like her Lululemon
Why are you always going to the studio
It's always the same
And my flow so mad, but I'm not a clown
Every song I release is a hit
Me and my pops
If you dissin' brother
I make the body drop
Me and my brothers
Still outside anybody get dropped
I don't do vibing with your music
I don't do that
I don't get your words, I don't do that
They say someone dissed me
Just tell them to do it
I don't do that
With kids weaker than me
Acting all friendly and badmouthing me
I don't do that
Things trending these days
I love it.
Things you do everyday
I don't do that
2025 eat it dirty pay
That was awesome.
That's it!
That's what I'm talking about!
TRAY B ALL PASS
He's so good.
That was incredible.
Tray B, Tray B!
EXCITED
Tray B, Tray B, Tray B!
He did amazing since the intro.
That was so cool.
And...
the beat gave me the chills.
When you stretched the syllables
from Evian to Lululemon...
THE PART THAT SHOCKED ZICO
I was like, "That's it!
That's what a true rapper is!"
That's what we call a rhyme push-and-pull.
A rhyme push-and-pull.
I was a bit worried at first
because just before he began,
I could see him mouthing the lyrics.
So I felt worried,
but he was so confident until the end.
You kept your head straight
and performed well.
Thank you. I did my best.
But were you a bit nervous?
Yes, I was extremely nervous.
Really? Wow.
You must have practiced a lot.
I want to watch it one more time.
I want to hear it once more too.
- Seriously.
- Yeah.
ENCORE REQUESTS
Can you show us one more time?
Just one more time?
Encore! Encore!
Call the beat.
Shall we hear it one more time?
Let's go.
I can do it.
- Let's go!
- Let's go, let's go!
Drop the beat.
'ANIMAL' PROD. TRAY B, SIG SAUER
Hey, Tray B
Let's get it!
He's performing again.
It's the first encore
in SHOW ME THE MONEY.
They wanted
to hear it again?
Let's go, let's go!
Still with my bros
And we move too tactical
Nobody can't tame us
I'm feelin like I'm animal
Everything I touch turns gold
That so magical
Even if you don't look
My enemies are screaming
Play on the radio
He think he a real
But he's a Mysterio
I can't deal with you
It's that part!
ZOOMING IN
You drink soju, I drink Pérignon
And my flow so flow like Evian
And my flow so tight like her Lululemon
Why are you always going to the studio
It's always the same
If you dissin' brother
I make the body drop
Me and my brothers
Still outside anybody get dropped
I don't get your words, I don't do that
2025 eat it dirty pay
Tray B, Tray B, Tray B!
Tray B! Tray B! Tray B!
He's good.
Why don't you say something
to your friend FLEEKY BANG before you go?
Jaehak,
I showed them.
It's your turn now.
Among all the contestants so far,
you got the most enthusiastic reactions.
For real.
Thank you.
An even an encore.
Great job.
Thank you.
Great work.
Good job.
This is giving me a dopamine rush.
Yeah, a dopamine rush.
I'm so stunned.
Tray B.
Today's MVP.
He made us all stand up
and ask for an encore stage.
He stood out.
He was really memorable.
I feel like he showed us
100% of what he had.
I loved it.
A performance and rap like that
is worth watching again.
Just come to our team.
THINKING OF HOW TO COAX TRAY B
How should I put it?
I want to coax him.
COME ON
Don't stick
your tongue out like that.
It was perfect.
I still remember his line.
IN SYNC
Lululemon.
I told you I'd show them.
THE WAITING ROOM IS STILL STUNNED
BY TRAY B'S STAGE
Tray B, Tray B.
Wow. He's incredible.
He had so much impact.
He totally crushed it with his rap.
Tray B did so well
for the 60-second rap mission,
so I think he could win first place.
Tray B's a top contender.
Tray B.
MANY CONTESTANTS PICKED TRAY B
He's so good.
AS THE TOP CONTENDER
Tray B.
I think Tray B
is the top contender.
TRAY B RETURNS TO ENTHUSIASTIC APPLAUSE
You were insane.
The response here
was crazy too.
I think the producers will love you.
YOU'LL GET AN ALL PASS, TOO
WHAT WILL FLEEKY BANG'S RESULT BE?
Next contestant.
VICE VERSA
I'm VICE VERSA. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
How did you end up applying
to SHOW ME THE MONEY 12?
I...
VICE VERSA SHOWED INCREDIBLE PRESENCE
WITH A UNIQUE AND POWERFUL TONE
BUT HE KEPT MISSING THE BEAT
IN SHOW ME THE MONEY 9
IT WOULD'VE BEEN NICE
IF HE JUST RAPPED LIKE USUAL
HOW DID HE BECOME A RAPPER
WITH NO SENSE OF RHYTHM?
IT SEEMS HE NEVER HAD A SENSE OF RHYTHM
IN THE END, VICE VERSA GOT ELIMINATED
AT THE THIRD ROUND
I feel like I didn't do
so well last time,
so I worked hard for this season.
His vibe seems a bit different.
You can begin once you're ready.
Good luck.
Could I...
Could I have about 5 to 10 seconds?
Sure!
Thank you.
He does look pretty anxious.
Do you think you're ready?
Yes.
Let's go!
Run that!
Okay.
I'm excited for this.
I hope he shows his true potential.
Yeah.
'FAQ' PROD. BY JUSTY
He switched his energy.
I keep my middle up
I turn on the music
My stance is always here
In my eyes
There's no such thing as friends
I am an animal, I am a beast
Unlike you I enjoy hunting
There's nothing free for a predator
I devour other predators
Don't linger around my territory
It's just reckless, I could kill you
Don't you dare to test me
I might really put you on a voo doo
I ride the clouds to calm myself
You've just provoked the Monkey King
When I'm angry I burn the staff
I love a lit flow
Furry, it is
Ain't got nothing but hit lick
Still, I have big dreams
Hell yeah I do love me some big hits
Furry, it is
I done a lot, silly
Just pass me the cake, Lil P
It's a war between the beasts
Furry, it is
Ain't got nothing but hit lick
Still, I have big dreams
Hell yeah I do love me some big hits
Furry, it is
I done a lot, silly
Just pass me the cake, Lil P
It's a war between the beasts
VICE VERSA ALL PASS
You did it!
Congratulations.
He's so good.
- That was charming.
- It was.
I was absorbed until the end.
I loved it.
Thank you.
I'm actually a huge fan of yours.
I love that raw kind of rap.
I think you're the only one
who can give off that sort of vibe.
I feel like you're teetering
at the edge of a dynamic rap.
It makes me feel anxious,
hoping you won't fall.
We feel anxious.
YEAH
Right.
But I'd like to enjoy that anxiety
more comfortably.
That anxiety
is completely different
when it's intentional
and when it's not.
Yes. Exactly.
I think I was really anxious.
I'll work harder as I keep going.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
I saw him for the first time
on SHOW ME THE MONEY 9,
and I feel like he's become more mature
and a bit more grounded.
It seemed like he went through a lot
the past few years.
I could sense his desperation too.
I liked seeing that change.
He's the best when it comes
to insane rap like that.
Yeah.
His presence was crazy.
- At the intro?
- Yeah.
VICE VERSA ALL PASS
Next contestant.
Wez Atlas.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Wez Atlas.
I'm from Tokyo.
Are you full Japanese?
Is he mixed-race?
HALF JAPANESE AND HALF AMERICAN
DURING THE GLOBAL PRELIMINARIES
WEZ ATLAS RAPPED ONLY IN ENGLISH
Are there
any verses in Japanese?
There are.
HE THEN RAPPED IN JAPANESE AS WELL
AND RECEIVED A PASS NECKLACE FROM ZICO
Man, the opportunity...
Just being able to be around
so many people that share the same passion
is really fun.
Whenever you're ready, bro.
Okay.
Drop the beat.
CUTE
"Drop the beat."
'200 PROF' PROD. BY REO ANZAI
New beginning
Had to burn a few bridges
Yeah I used to play the role
Cuz the shoe fitted
Was painful
But I'm glad I went through with it
2 hunnid proof
Only put truth in it
In the booth like a church confessional
My soul live inside
Every verse I ever wrote
It's really not about the money for me
I'm dedicated to the art
Of discovering things, hey
Chilling in Seoul
Let the soju flow
Grab my hand
Pop the confetti
My friends are from
Tokyo, Kyushu, Nowon-gu
Shout it out one more time
Come on!
Let's keep things light
Just try to catch a groove tonight
And feel alive
Feel this moment
Uh huh, let's ride
Yeah!
WEZ ATLAS ALL PASS
ALL PASS.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Feel this moment, oh ride
Yeah!
CLAP CLAP
JAY PARK TRYING WEZ ATLAS' RAP
Feel this moment, oh ride
Feel this moment
Thank you.
I love your voice.
That was great, bro.
It looked like
we were just watching a show,
not even an audition.
Thank you, I tried to make it a song.
It looks like you're very comfortable
with who you are,
and you know
what you need to do, what you need to say.
And how to use your story,
your uniqueness to your strengths.
So it was very delightful to watch.
Thank you.
When I heard your rap,
I felt like the structure of the rap
really suited your image.
ALL THE PRODUCERS ARE OBSESSED
You're a great singer.
I love his tone.
Among all the raps with melodies,
he had the most stable notes.
It was really stable.
And his Korean pronunciation...
I think he's the best.
Your pronunciation is really good.
FEELING SHY AT THE SHOWER OF COMPLIMENTS
I heard that line about confetti.
What... Soju?
What did you say?
ENCORE
Chilling in Seoul, let the soju flow
Grab my hand
Pop the confetti
AWESOME
Oh!
SWISH
What's your favorite Korean?
PONDERING
My favorite Korean...
"I'm sorry."
EVERYONE'S SAYING "I'M SORRY"
NOD
I'll look forward
to the 3rd round.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
WEZ ATLAS ALL PASS
Let's go!
ALL PASS, baby!
He showed himself without going overboard.
Rather than a hardcore rap,
it was kind of cool and chill.
I loved it.
Grab my hand
Pop the confetti
Shout it out one more time
Next contestant.
Please enter.
I'm so anxious.
SUNHYE
SUNHYE.
Hello.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm SUNHYE, from the group YOUNG POSSE.
Oh, YOUNG POSSE.
We have to watch this.
YOUNG POSSE'S ELDEST MEMBER
AND SKILLED LEADER
I THINK SHE'LL DO WELL
Freestyle drop
APPLICATION VIDEO GOT 1 MILLION VIEWS
Told to join Show Me, give up my vacation
PROMISING NAME IN KOREAN HIP-HOP
If I'm gonna do it, I'm gonna go get it
THE NEWS DREW PUBLIC ATTENTION
I'll hold the trophy like Sonny
How did you end up applying?
There aren't many opportunities like this
to make ourselves known.
And since we're a hip-hop group,
I thought I should
show the public our skills.
So I took on the challenge.
She came as a representative.
That's brave.
I'm curious to know
how your members rooted for you
when you joined.
My members are actually
more excited than me.
They were really thrilled
and wished me good luck.
They put their trust in me.
A lot of famous rappers
joined this program.
Yes.
What do you think
is something that makes you stand out?
I have a lot of experience on stage,
so I'm sure I can show
a great performance,
and I believe I can provide
visual entertainment.
Okay.
I'm excited for this.
Drop the beat.
'BADA**' PROD. KIGGEN, DEEVAN
Hello.
Nice to meet you all!
I'll talk formally since you're so scary
I heard you're all really dangerous
You shoot guns
Spin the block
I'm not a gangster
But let me spit some bars
She forgot the lyrics?
TO BE CONTINUED SHORTLY
'BADA**' PROD. KIGGEN, DEEVAN
Hello.
Nice to meet you all!
I'll talk formally since you're so scary
I heard you're all really dangerous
You shoot guns
Spin the block
I'm not a gangster
But let me spit some bars
She forgot the lyrics?
XXL
She forgot the lyrics.
2025 plans are perfect
Get a driver's license, work out
And win Show Me, huh
I'm not a rapper, I'm an idol
But I'm not aespa, ILLIT, IVE
So I have to spit rhymes
I need the Show Me winner title
New icon
But no drugs, no guns
I don't
Just kidding man
I'm cute, so go easy
It's not cool to get upset
I'm playing games like Eminem
And Little wayne
Beef and make it rain
Just show me a cool reaction
So I can mock you
Aha
Head, shoulders, knees, toes
Let me hit that like a freestyle
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Let me ride I'll just dance
Like an idol, nah
Beat other rappers with rap and hype up
You said you need an icon
For another hip-hop boom
But if you're going down
Just let me win
SUNHYE 1 PASS
Thank you.
THE WAITING ROOM IS QUIET
She made a lot of mistakes.
What did they like about that?
I didn't have
the time to press FAIL.
Were you pretty anxious?
Yes.
Regardless of practice...
I think you should study rap a bit more.
Right.
I think you should listen
to a lot more music.
- Okay.
- A lot.
Your skills come from how much you listen.
Right.
I hope you really work hard
and do better in the next round.
You came as a representative
of all five members, right?
Yes.
But you forgot the lyrics several times.
I hope you do better next time.
- Yes. I'll do better.
- I'll look forward to that.
Thank you.
Good work.
I'm an idiot.
But she did well until the end
despite the mistake.
It's not easy to get
back on track after missing a line.
Yeah.
But she did it.
And she even danced.
I'm so grateful
that I received another chance.
I'll really do better.
Let's do this!
YAWN
THE 60-SECOND MISSION IS REALLY LONG
WHILE EVERYONE IS GETTING EXHAUSTED
THERE'S SOMEONE FULL OF ENERGY
Give me a shout
before I begin!
EXCITED
Oh, yeah!
ENDLESS POSITIVE ENERGY
ALSO GOOD AT GETTING IMMERSED
KOREAN, AMERICAN
FROM CANADA, INTERPRETING
"Take a guess."
WELCOMES ENDLESS QUESTIONS
"One more time."
Where are you from?
Can I see your watch?
Are you the same age?
I'm a fan.
HOW WILL THE FRIENDLY ENERGIZER DO?
All right. Next contestant.
It's him next.
Let me see. Who is it?
Who is it?
Someone ZICO personally
put a necklace on?
This rapper is attending
a prestigious university in Canada.
Junhyuk Jung.
I like his style.
He's kind of dressed like a pilot.
Pilot style.
READY FOR TAKE-OFF?
Come on out.
JUNHYUK JUNG
Junhyuk Jung.
Wow.
Junhyuk.
Hello.
Hi, I'm 20-year-old Junhyuk Jung
from Canada.
Wow!
What?
That's a unique style.
My concept
is a rock-style biker.
When I'm making a song,
the flow should match the lyrics,
the lyrics should match my outfit,
and my outfit should match the video.
I put a lot of thought into the concept.
CONCEPT PROFESSIONAL
I think it'll be pretty cool.
I'm excited for this.
- Shall we hear it, then?
- All right.
Scally wag we get that bag
DJ spit that FAFAFA
This is nice.
'SCALLYWAG' PROD. BY JUNHYUK JUNG
I take your toupee off huh
Spent 4 years didn't pay off
Throw the 2 million I cuff huh
Man this fit way too tuff
These misfit's put on grunge
Looking like you got trampled on, dirty
No ginseng, sick no cold
Man, this my rag to riches
Scallywag, we all feel the same
- Hooked on money like fisherman
- This is great.
- Put the C.R.E.A.M on your skin
- I love it.
Yo Wu Tang spit that kung fu
Huh, tell me why they sleep on me
That's just spitting into the wind
I'm living my c'est la vie
My living room looks like my studio, huh
Natural reverb
Cover my socks
My pop filter
Might pop off then
Tell'em I'll walk the plank ye
Stomach needs to hurt more
Ye tell'em go hit the plank
Push-up that 50 man, 50, 50
I take you toup'ee off huh
Spent 4 years didn't pay off
Throw the 2 million I cuff huh
Man this fit way too tuff
Tuff
ALL PASS
JUNHYUK JUNG ALL PASS
Awesome.
Hey, Junhyuk!
You're so cool.
That was incredible.
That was great.
You were cool.
Junhyuk...
I loved it.
The reason why I loved it
because he didn't make it too complicated.
Everything was sharp and on point.
His formation and gestures
were all so natural.
That was cool.
He's good.
Why are you so good?
That performance
to the beat was really cool.
He's really good with the details.
He raps, then...
- It's crazy.
- Then he suddenly does something.
HIS PERFORMANCE MADE ZICO BOUNCE UP
Ay!
And he didn't overdo the rap,
but nailed the key points.
It was awesome.
Your moves were perfectly
in sync with the beat.
Thank you.
You made the beat yourself, right?
Yes, I did it myself.
Really? Wow.
You even do the producing yourself.
The moment he did that move...
I did think he would have made
the beat on his own.
I MADE THE BEAT
It was really unique.
But all those gestures...
Have you been doing music by yourself?
I like wearing earphones
and practicing
on my bed and stuff
like I'm doing a concert.
It wasn't flashy,
it was just right.
It was simple,
but I got immersed.
Your tone was so good.
It was totally my style.
I could sense his star quality.
I think his dance played a huge part.
THE POWERFUL DANCE
It was incredible.
DANCING ALONG
SAME DANCE, DIFFERENT VIBE
ME, TOO
PUNCH PUNCH
THE DANCE IS SPREADING
IN THE WAITING ROOM
What's your biggest goal
for SHOW ME THE MONEY 12?
Winning.
I think you'll do great.
He was just overflowing with charm.
I wanted to keep seeing him perform.
Great job. Congratulations.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Seeing new talents like him,
I feel really excited.
Yeah. This is great.
I'm getting a dopamine rush.
I think he did the best so far.
I'll remember you, Junhyuk Jung.
THE NEW FACE WHO SHOCKED EVERYONE
JUNHYUK JUNG, ALL PASS
Didn't I just seem
like a madman?
The good thing is
that everyone who passed so far
are all different.
It's nice that no one has the same style.
If they rap like
the previous season, they're eliminated.
The standard...
It changed. Rappers who would've
passed before got eliminated.
Yeah. They would've
passed in previous seasons.
Just being good at rap
isn't enough now.
They have to be different.
Yeah.
They need to stand out.
TO BE CONTINUED SHORTLY
It's completely different
from the first round.
The kind of rapper we've been waiting for.
We're seeing the biggest variety
of styles in this season.
THE 60-SECOND MISSION ISN'T OVER
There are still many more.
My ears melted.
ROOKIE RAPPERS WHO SHOOK THE SCENE
It feels nice to see
the rookies getting an ALL PASS.
HAON
It's him.
BIG-NAME RAPPERS CHALLENGE THEM
Seriously,
I've been waiting for him the whole time.
FOCUSED
BIG-NAME RAPPERS MAINTAINING THE THRONE
I got chills for the first time.
You too?
- Yes.
- Me too.
I came here
to seduce all the women in Korea.
HE'S SO FUNNY
CONTESTANTS WITH UNIQUE CHARACTERS
Tang, tang, malatang
AND THE NEXT MISSION IS REVEALED
The 1 vs 1 rank mission.
This is so cruel.
I just want to crush them.
I chose him
because he was getting on my nerves.
WHO WILL BE THE WINNERS
AFTER THE INTENSE CONFLICT?