=She Behind, I Before=
=Episode 1=
(Zhou Dailing, Detective of M Country)
Protect Bu Na?
(Who is Bu Na?)
Protect Bu Na.
(The same nightmare again.)
(Wake up now.)
(Zhou Daizi,
Zhou Dailing's Elder Sister)
(What does this recurring nightmare
want to tell me?)
(Daizi.)
(Bu Na.)
(Nuo Ha.)
(Feng Sa Wan.)
(Daizi's disappearance
must be related to Bu Na's death.)
(Younger Sister, Zhou Dailing)
(What is the connection between you?)
(Protect Bu Na)
(Elder Sister, Zhou Daizi)
(Where am I?)
(This is not my bathroom.)
(This is Daizi's place.)
(Why am I here?)
(A celebration party for the movie,
Deadly Secret,)
(starring the famous actress Bu Na,)
(will be held at Huating Hotel
this evening.)
(Bu Na will sing the theme song
for the movie.)
Bu Na.
Hello.
Zhou Daizi.
Why weren't you in the press conference?
Are you
a professional journalist?
Hurry up and get there now.
(I have become Zhou Daizi?)
Zhou Daizi.
(Zhou Daizi, Zhou Dailing)
(May 10, 2020)
(I've gone back to two years ago)
(and become Zhou Daizi.)
(M Country, Huating Hotel)
(Feng Sa Wan, CEO of Qiansheng Entertainment)
It's great to see all of you here today.
(Bu Na, Famous Actress in M Country)
So I'll sing this song
to everyone present.
I hope you like my movie,
and also enjoy my song.
Thank you.
Mr. Feng, the pool party is ready.
Okay, go ahead.
Sir, bad news.
Let's go.
Hello.
This is Huating Hotel.
We found a female body here.
Is it that bizarre?
Maybe so.
All those celebrities
do dark magic secretly.
I-I want to know
if the deceased is Bu Na.
Sorry.
(Yu Pengliang, Police of M Country)
We can't tell you anything.
I am a journalist.
Liang.
I'll handle it.
What's wrong?
Is it Bu Na who died?
(Police Lieutenant,
Maiji Police Station of M Country)
You are the best journalist
I have ever seen.
So, is it really Bu Na?
No.
It's Yan Yingxin,
(Zhou Daizi, Journalist of M Country)
an artist of Qiansheng Entertainment.
Right.
It's not time yet.
What?
On May 20th,
Bu Na will die.
Are you crazy?
Because of Nuo Ha and Feng Sa Wan.
What are you talking about?
One is
the chief of police,
the other is a director of the largest
film and television company here.
They're engaging in power deals.
How did you know this?
Because I am an excellent journalist.
Daizi.
This is very dangerous.
We don't have enough evidence right now.
There seems
to be a greater power behind them.
You've noticed something too?
I am an excellent police officer.
What's your plan?
Taking down Nuo Ha and Feng Sa Wan.
(Is chief of police, Nuo Ha
involved in power deals?)
(Qiansheng Entertainment artist
Yan Yingxin died mysteriously.)
(Yan Yingxin is an artist
of Qiansheng Entertainment.)
(Is her death)
(also related to the power deals
of Nuo Ha and Feng Sa Wan?)
(Local Police, Local Time, Power Deals)
(Behind the death of Yan Yingxin,)
(maybe I can find out
why Daizi disappeared.)
(Perhaps, Bu Na wouldn't have to die.)
Yu Pengliang.
Can you check on Yan Yingxin?
(Jiao, President's Assistant of K Group)
Our group is more than happy
to create newcomers opportunities.
The audience gets tired of
seeing the same face.
Right?
Yes.
As long as this is done,
then money is not a problem.
Hello, Nuo Ha.
Our super star, Bu Na,
will soon be worthless in the circle.
Who knows why?
But fortunately,
she's still considered
top quality in your place.
Okay.
Put Bu Na on it.
Okay, I got it.
In Yan Yingxin's place,
the most valuable things
are these diaries.
That's not right.
2015,
2016,
2017, 2018, 2019...
The one in 2020 isn't here.
Take them.
(Text is like memory.)
(If it's not written down,)
(can it be forgotten?)
Yu Pengliang, look.
I'll check them in the photo.