=She Behind, I Before=
=Episode 7=
Hello.
What?
After your police station lost Nuo Ha,
the efficiency is this high?
Stop talking nonsenses.
You don't know
how troublesome is the one
we're dealing with.
The person in my dream
is real?
Okay, I'll send you the information.
You take a look.
I'll go to you after I get off work.
Okay.
Hey, wait.
I got home yesterday
and found the red dot
on my forehead like that
of a kindergarten kid.
Did you make it?
I walked around all day
with that red dot.
It's so embarrassing.
It's to save you.
You police believe in
this sort of thing?
Right.
You are the police from M Country.
In the end, you woke up.
Alright, I have to go.
I'm busy here.
See you later.
Based on your description,
this is the sketched portrait
of the one in your dream.
It's K Group's CEO,
Xiong.
K Group?
K Group
operates legally and illegally,
with huge assets
and great power.
Compared with Nuo Ha and Feng Sa Wan?
He's tougher to deal with
than these two together.
How many people in M Country
could manipulate Nuo Ha and Feng Sa Wan?
Few.
But,
this K Group,
to be exact,
this Xiong
absolutely counts as one.
Are you sure you saw him in your dream?
It's him.
Take a break.
I have work to do.
Be careful on the road.
(Gate)
(Go save Yu. He's gone to find Xiong.)
Yu Pengliang.
What're you doing?
Do you know what you're doing?
I know.
You know?
Do you think you can kill him like this?
Why are you doing this?
You asked if I believe
you traveled through time.
I really do.
After taking this picture with her,
I wanted to confess my love to her,
but I couldn't say it,
yet she said goodbye.
She told me
that it might be the last time we meet.
I thought
she had understood my intentions,
and wanted to reject me.
But after a few days,
I saw her again.
No.
It was you.
You acted
as if you didn't know me at all.
I just want to know
if the deceased is Bu Na.
Sorry.
We can't reveal anything.
- I am a journalist.
- Liang.
I'll handle it.
You are Yu Pengliang?
What am I saying?
Of course, you are Yu Pengliang.
Anyway, I already know
Zhou Daizi's disappearance
is related to Xiong.