(Ok Taec-yeon)
(Kim So-hyun)
(Kwon Yul)
(Kim Sang-ho)
(Bring it on, Ghost)
Bong-pal.
I'm alive...
Hyun-ji.
She's going into cardiac arrest!
Is it cardiac arrest?
- Vitals!
- There's no pulse!
- It's charging.
- Clear! Shoot!
Shoot!
Clear!
Hyun-ji.
Bong-pal.
Hyun-ji... Hyun-ji!
Hyun-ji!
I told him to lie still on the bed!
Where did he go?
(Episode 12)
Gosh, he sure doesn't listen.
He shouldn't be moving around.
- Bong-pal!
- Hey, Bong-pal!
- Bong-pal! Bong-pal!
- Let's carry him.
- Hold on.
Hold on.
Hyun-ji, wake up!
Mom. Dad.
- Hyun-ji!
Why am I here?
Why are you crying?
You don't remember the accident?
An accident?
Me?
You've been in a coma
for five years. You don't remember?
Doctor, why doesn't
she remember anything?
Don't worry too much.
It's a minor aftereffect of being
in a coma for such a long time.
Your memories will return in time.
Let's make sure
your condition is stable first
and do a physical exam.
For now, let's just be thankful
that she's awake now.
Congratulations, Hyun-ji.
I'll see you again.
Yes.
- Thank you. Thank you, Doctor.
- Thank you.
- Hyun-ji.
Do you remember me?
Continue to follow up
on Kim Hyun-ji.
There might be
a problem with her memories
so set up a consultation with
the neurology department.
Yes, sir.
(Kim Hyun-ji)
You really don't remember anything?
Yes, I don't remember anything.
My head just hurts a little.
Don't try too hard to remember.
Those memories aren't important.
Now that you've come back alive…
I'm so happy.
It's okay.
Why are you crying if you're happy?
Don't cry.
Not you too, dad.
You've been through a lot.
Thank you for staying alive.
- Don't, Mom.
- Thank you, Hyun-ji.
Doctor, are his BP and OP okay?
He's not going into
cardiac arrest, is he?
Don't you need to intubate
him or give him an EPI?
You've watched
too many medical dramas.
That's not necessary
and his x-rays are fine.
But it seems like he's
overworked himself lately.
He's exhausted and his
nutritive condition is a mess.
I've prescribed him vitamins.
He can be discharged after
he rests for the rest of the day.
Yes, Doctor. Thank you.
I guess he eventually
collapsed after Hyun-ji left.
Bong-pal was struggling? Why?
Huh?
Well, I guess Bong-pal
and Hyun-ji were kind of an item.
An item...
Hyun-ji has feelings for Bong-pal?
I think Bong-pal has
feelings for Hyun-ji, too.
That's why he's in
this state after she left.
You know, getting hurt
from a painful breakup
is every man's fear.
So that's what happened.
Hyun-ji and Bong-pal were...
I see.
Are you okay?
- I'm okay, I'm okay.
- You're okay. You're okay.
And don't try to hurt Bong-pal.
(Flower Virgin Shamaness)
Is it true that there's
one more weapon?
I heard the head monk prepared one.
Hong Myung-hee met the head
monk before she passed away.
I heard she asked him
to prepare another weapon.
One more?
By any chance, do you
know where that weapon is?
He passed away
and that's all I heard.
There's one more weapon.
She had it made
for the sake of her son.
I'm sure having
that made was not easy.
Do you maybe think the personal
effect Bong-pal's father
went looking for…
It was the weapon.
Then the reason why that evil
spirit is hanging around Bong-pal...
It's because of that weapon.
That's his lifeline.
That's why that bastard
is chasing after him.
I have to go.
- You're leaving already?
- Yes.
Watch out for yourself.
If that punk is serious,
he won't go easy on you.
Thanks.
I'll call you.
(Kim Hyun-ji)
What should I do with you?
Oh, dear Buddha…
Bong-pal.
Where did he go?
Is this rascal in trouble?
- Hello? Who is it?
- Hello...
Isn't this
Park Bong-pal's cell phone?
Yes, it is.
In the hospital?
Which hospital is it?
Yes, I understand.
That punk!
Who is it?
I don't know.
Hello?
I told you already.
What the heck?
Bong-pal.
What happened?
He's not seriously injured.
He just passed out from exhaustion.
The doctors say he'll be
fine after a day of rest.
Goodness, he must have been
seriously heartbroken.
But who are you?
Yes... we're Bong-pal's seniors
as well as business partners.
Business partners?
- With Bong-pal?
- Yes.
Ah... this...
- Thank you.
- It's nothing great really.
We're running
a 24-hour exorcism business.
- I'm CEO Choi Chun-sang.
- I'm Manager Kim In-rang.
What's the matter?
Who are you?
He's a monk.
You punks...
You're the punks
I met at Gampo's Inn.
So, you punks are using Bong-pal
to catch ghosts, is that it?
We're not using him.
This is a mutual and beneficial
partnership we both agreed upon...
- You punk!
- Don't do this.
Don't you know how
dangerous exorcism is?
It does look a bit dangerous,
but this is the 21st century...
Why you little punk!
- I was wrong!
- Are you going to continue or not?
If you ever use Bong-pal
again, I'm going to...
The same goes for you, too!
Goodness, you rascal. You get sick
because of that one ghost.
You guys stay
right next to Bong-pal.
Don't go anywhere.
I'm going to meet the doctor.
- Yes, sir.
Goodbye.
I thought he was about to
rip my ears off. Seriously.
- Who is that monk?
- I don't know. A relative, maybe?
Aren't you hungry?
Should we go eat something?
I'll go and buy something.
Stay here, I'll be back.
She woke up after five years.
Okay, try closing your hand.
Open it up again.
Put more strength into it.
Fortunately, there is
nothing wrong with her nerves.
You need to continue to exercise
your hands to relax the muscles.
Practice using a spoon
or chopsticks often.
- Writing is fine, too.
- Yes, Doctor.
Walking is too much for now,
so use the wheelchair.
And the hospital prepared this
congratulatory gift for you.
Congratulations once
again on waking up.
- Thank you.
Congratulations.
Who is it, anyway?
It's the girl who woke up after
being in a coma for five years.
The girl from the car accident?
I'm glad to hear she's awake.
Hyun-ji...
(Kim Hyun-ji)
Is she really...
Hyun-ji.
Hyun-ji... Hyun-ji!
What's wrong?
Hey, hey! Hey.
- I have to find Hyun-ji.
- No, no. Wait a minute! Sit down!
Wait. You're burning up.
The doctor says
you have to be calm.
Stay still, okay?
Chun-sang, Chun-sang,
Chun-sang! Bong-pal!
I'm so glad you're here, In-rang.
He's frantic to find Hyun-ji.
- I saw Hyun-ji!
- What?
You saw Hyun-ji?
Yes, I saw her at the
hospital ward on the way here.
What nonsense are you spouting?
How can you see a ghost?
No, she looked exactly like Hyun-ji...
No, she's Hyun-ji for sure.
The name tag next to her
room says Kim Hyun-ji, too.
Come here.
You're burning up, too,
so get a shot while you're here.
No! People are saying that she
woke up from a five-year coma!
Hey, Bong-pal! Bong-pal!
Move! He was just
beginning to calm down!
Why did you have to
bring up Hyun-ji?
It's that way! Bong-pal!
Where did he go?
Bong-pal.
Bong-pal?
(Kim Hyun-ji)
Hyun-ji.
You're alive.
I thought you disappeared.
I was so worried about you.
What are you doing?
Hyun-ji.
Who are you?
You... don't recognize me?
I'm... Bong-pal.
Don't you remember?
Look... I don't know
how you know my name.
But I really don't know who you are.
Please, leave.
- Hyun-ji.
- Mom.
Who is he?
Do you know him?
No, I don't know him.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
I must've mistaken you
for someone else.
What the heck?
Hey.
It's Hyun-ji, right?
What did she say?
What did Hyun-ji say?
She... doesn't remember me.
- What?
- She doesn't remember?
Yes.
- Are you sure that's Hyun-ji?
- I'm sure.
Look. There's no one prettier
than Hyun-ji in all of Korea.
- In all of Korea?
- Yes.
She is pretty, I guess.
I don't know.
Hi.
Oh no, she must not
remember me either.
How can she remember you when
she can't even remember Bong-pal?
But why can't she remember?
- She was in a coma for five years?
- Yeah.
Then you're saying Hyun-ji
wasn't a ghost but a soul, right?
I guess she was in limbo.
She came back into her
own body and forgot everything
that happened with us.
What do you want me to do about it?
Excuse me... beautiful nurses.
- Yes.
- We have some questions to ask.
Sure, go ahead.
Whois he? Do you know him?
No, I don't know him.
Bong-pal. Bong-pal!
Mong Myung-chul.
Who says you can leave the hospital?
- I've been looking for you.
- How did you find me?
Your seniors or whatever told me.
I can't believe you're
friends with idiots like that.
They're of no help to you.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
You need to take
better care of yourself.
Let's go. You have to
eat well at a time like this.
Let's go and get you
something to eat.
Taxi! Hurry up.
Over here.
Stop!
Wow, the quality
of this oxtail is good.
- Monk, I'll do it.
- Go away.
I can do this better than you.
I'm fine. I'll do it.
Listen, will you?
Go and get some rest.
Okay.
Monk Myung-chul.
What is it?
I'm sorry for yelling
at you last time.
That rascal even knows how
to apologize. He's all grown up.
Let's see.
Bong-pal.
Bong... Bong-pal.
Bong-pal. Bong...
Bong-pal.
- Senior.
- Here.
Ah, you came here to bring me this.
- I could've come and gotten it.
- Well, we need to talk, too.
- What is it?
- The thing is...
So, you're not the only one
that Hyun-ji can't remember.
They say she can't remember
what happened five years ago.
Hyun-ji was a victim
of a hit-and-run accident.
I think she has problems
remembering because of trauma.
The amnesia is only temporary.
Her memories will return in time
so don't be too disappointed.
We should be ecstatic
and grateful that Hyun-ji is alive.
And at times like this, you should
be by her side, don't you think?
You punks!
Who came back alive
from a hit-and-run accident?
- Hello, sir.
What?
Bong-pal left his bag behind
and we brought it for him.
We'll be on our way now.
- Goodbye.
See you later.
Bong-pal, is Hyun-ji alive then?
Yes, she's in the
hospital I was staying at.
That child was not a ghost.
Unbelievable.
He should be jumping up and down
with joy. Why does he look so down?
We should be ecstatic
and grateful that Hyun-ji is alive.
And at times like this, you should
be by her side, don't you think?
Are you okay after
saying all that to him?
- About what?
- Well,
you're trying to get
Hyun-ji and Bong-pal together.
Have you completely
given up on her then?
Hyun-ji's happiness is my happiness.
I'm good as long as she's happy.
Plus, there's something
more important than that.
What?
We have to catch
that punk and get revenge.
- Who?
- The bastard that
put her in a coma five years ago.
It's my life's mission
to catch that punk.
- Chun-sang.
- Yeah?
Do you have
that detective's business card?
- Business card?
- The business card
we got from that detective...
The business card we
got when Sadako died.
Ah!
I have it, I have it, I have it.
I do have it. Here it is.
Let's go.
To the police station.
Let's go! To the police station!
Goodness, it's not even a case.
Why did you come all the way here?
There's something I need
to find out personally.
This is old news.
It's a simple accident.
There's nothing to look over.
Is the scene of the crime still there?
Why? You want to go there?
Yes.
Okay, he fell right here.
Anyway, he was already
dead when we arrived.
I think he died from
internal bleeding.
One of the residents discovered
the body while passing by.
She said she didn't see him fall.
That's what happened.
Is anyone there? Someone help!
A straight fall from the 15th floor.
What? You want to go
up to the 15th floor?
- Hello.
- Who are you?
- We called you earlier.
- Ah, yes.
- We're from the police station.
- I see.
- Please, excuse us for a moment.
It's nothing really.
This detective is from Seoul
and he just wants to take
a quick look around.
- It'll only be for a moment.
- Sure, go ahead.
Thank you.
There was no sign of
a struggle whatsoever
so it's hard to say
it was manslaughter.
And there was no letter or
statement left behind to indicate
it was suicide.
It was written on the autopsy
report that he drank a lot.
So he drank, smoked, and did this.
He lost his balance.
He tilted over and lost his balance.
Do you remember who
was home at that time?
When I went up...
the wife was there.
She didn't know
that her husband fell.
Was the son at home by any chance?
His name is Ju Hye-sung.
He was 13 years old at the time.
Yes, the son was home.
- Yeah, what is it?
- Senior.
- Where are you right now?
- Did you get something?
The chief is looking
all over for you.
- You need to get back immediately.
- I'm on my way.
Why are you so concerned
with a simple freak accident?
- Did you find something?
- I don't think it was.
What?
The railing is about one meter tall.
Ju Hye-sung's father
was 173 centimeters tall.
Even if he stood by the railing,
it'd be hard for him to
fall over on his own.
That's unless someone
pushed him from behind.
The only people who were home
were the wife and Ju Hye-sung.
So, what are you going to do?
I'm going to reinvestigate
Professor Ju Hye-sung.
(Hanil University Hospital)
Slowly.
Very good. Pull a little more.
- Are you comfortable?
- Yes.
I'm going to increase
the speed just a little bit.
Hello?
Yes.
- Let's stop here for today.
- Okay.
Be careful.
You're doing very well.
The muscles are responding well so
you should be able to use crutches.
Even though it's hard,
you have to keep it up.
I will.
Where did my mom go?
- Should I take you to your room?
- No, I'll do it.
- This is exercise, too.
- Okay, then.
- Thank you.
- Good job today.
- Hello.
Hello, Doctor.
- Hello, Ms. Hyun-ji.
- Hello.
This is a piece of cake.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You look tired. Where is your room?
I'll take you there.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It must be your first time
in a wheelchair.
You looked very clumsy.
Ah, yes. I've only been
using it for several days.
You should be careful. It's actually
quite harder than it looks.
- Are you a doctor here?
- No.
I used to volunteer at a hospital,
which is when I tried one out.
I see.
I hear you were in
a coma for five years.
Oh, how did you find out?
What kind of accident was it?
A hit-and-run accident.
But the truth is, I don't remember.
Not even remotely?
Yes, the doctor says
it's because of the shock.
But he says my memories
will return with time.
What a relief.
Hyun-ji.
It's my mom.
Mom.
Where were you?
I was looking all over for you.
Who is he?
Ah, this person escorted me.
Really? Thank you.
- You're too kind.
- Not at all.
I'll be on my way now.
- Good luck.
- Yes, thank you.
Who is he?
He is so good-looking.
He's exactly my type.
Oh.
A present for you.
What is it?
This is mine?
- Yes.
- Thank you!
Nice.
Come in.
What the heck? He's here again.
I'm not a weirdo
so don't be afraid of me.
I want to apologize for last time.
I didn't know you
lost your memories.
What are you doing?
It's my student ID.
I'm a sophomore business
major at Myongsung University.
Call the school if you doubt me.
Why did you come again?
You're going to regret
treating me like this
once your memories return.
Regret, my butt.
Just who are you to keep
bothering me like this?
Park Bong-pal.
Park Bong-pal?
That's right, Park Bong-pal.
Your boyfriend.
- Granted, you don't remember.
- What?
Boyfriend?
Yes.
We were an item? I dated you?
No, it's more like lived together…
That's more accurate.
What are you saying?
Why would I live with you? When?
- When you were a ghost.
- What? A ghost?
- You've lost your mind!
- I'm perfectly sane.
- You chased me around.
- No way.
You're not my type.
Get out.
You don't have to
remember right away.
I'm grateful that you're alive
and well… and haven't disappeared.
You bought a new cell phone.
What are you doing?
I'm giving you my number.
Call me if you miss me.
Get out. Get out!
- I came back to this today.
- Today?
- You're coming again tomorrow?
- Yes.
Don't ever come again.
I swear I'll call the cops on you
if you come back tomorrow!
I'm coming tomorrow
and the day after tomorrow.
I'm going to come every day
until you remember.
Every single day.
See you tomorrow.
Ah... and call me if you
want to hear my voice.
Wow.
(My Love Bong Bong)
What a crazy bastard!
What is it?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
Did you buy this?
No!
Just throw it all away.
The books, too.
It's exactly like the one
you used to use before.
- Really?
- Really.
You always used
a pink cup and toothbrush.
- Did I?
- Ever since you were little.
You threw such a fit
if I bought you a different color.
Mom, wait.
What is it?
Just leave it there for now.
You're so wishy-washy.
Here.
Let's see here.
(Bong-pal loves Hyun-ji)
This looks like my handwriting.
Hey, Kim Hyun-ji.
What is it? Are you in pain?
My head hurts.
(Hanil University Hospital)
Hyun-ji.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
For a patient who was
in a coma for five years,
your recovery speed is amazing.
- You're in great condition, too.
- Really?
When do I get discharged then?
It's so stuffy in here.
At this rate, you can start
receiving outpatient treatment
in three days.
Yes!
Is he not here today?
It's strange not seeing him.
No, what am I talking about?
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
I am going to introduce
you to a new friend today.
This fellow's name is Happy.
- It's that guy from last time.
- And he's three years old.
What is he doing?
What are all of your names? Can you
please introduce yourself to Happy?
- Yes!
- You go first.
- Hi, I'm Ji-woo.
- Hi, Ji-woo.
- Hi, I'm Hyun-soo.
- Hi, Hyun-soo.
- Hi, I'm Seo-woo.
- Hi, Seo-woo.
Now that we've introduced
ourselves, how about we get
friendlier with Happy?
Yes!
All you have to do is
gently pet him, okay?
Yes.
Gently. Happy might get scared.
- Hi.
- Be gentle.
He's so cute.
He's so soft and cute.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Yes, goodbye.
Bye, see you next time.
You look much better.
I see that you can walk now.
Yes.
He's so cute.
You said you do volunteer work.
Do you volunteer here as well?
- Yes.
- What did you just do now?
Pet therapy. It helps patients
recover from or better
cope with health issues.
It's a type of psychotherapy.
I probably need it too.
Of course.
- Do you want to hold him?
- Yes.
Here you go.
- His name is Happy.
- Hi, Happy.
Excuse me,
is this Kim Hyun-ji's room?
Yes, that's correct.
How did you get here?
- Did she go somewhere?
- She's at physical therapy.
Who are you?
Kim Hyun-ji and I don't really
know each other very well…
By any chance, are you her mother?
Yes.
Congratulations on
your daughter waking up.
This is my gift.
- Thank you.
- I'll get going.
Wait, sir.
Who should I say came to visit her?
Tell her a mean monk who once
said some harsh words to her came.
Please, tell her I'm sorry.
Have a good day.
Ah, so you're a professor.
No wonder.
The school you're teaching at
is the school I wanted to attend.
I was going to apply to Myongsung
University before the accident.
I'd probably be graduating by now.
Come visit the school
once you're discharged
and attend one of my classes.
- Really? I can do that?
- Of course.
I get discharged in three days.
Can I come then?
- Yes.
- Yes!
Why is that punk here?
Monk Myung-chul.
Hey, Bong-pal.
What are you doing here?
Oh, just because. Just because.
Why are Hyun-ji
and the professor together?
Hyun-ji?
Ah, the girl next to that
professor is Hyun-ji, huh?
Yes.
Monk Myung-chul.
Monk Myung-chul?
It's nothing.
I'm going to get going.
You scared me.
You look like you're
in a good mood today.
I was in such a good
mood before I saw you.
I was wondering why
you didn't come today.
- Were you waiting for me?
- You wish!
Wait...
Do you remember anything?
Go to a mental institute
and stop bothering me!
What about lunch? Did you eat?
What's it to you if I eat or not?
It's boring eating
hospital food every day.
I packed a lunch today.
Let's go eat it together.
No thank you. You eat it.
I brought jangjorim and meat.
Meat?
Yes, meat.
Here, dig in.
Just because I'm eating this doesn't
mean that I've opened up to you.
I'm only tasting it out of courtesy.
Okay, just give it a taste.
Shall I then?
It's kimchi stew.
- You have to put tons of meat...
- You have to put tons of meat in.
In for it to taste good…
I did. Eat it.
You're pretty good.
Here, rolled eggs.
You like this.
You've been stalking me,
haven't you? How can you know
everything I like?
- You followed me around.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Don't lie!
Here.
How can I like all these dishes?
You're a pretty good cook.
Whether you're a ghost or human,
that hearty appetite
is still the same.
It's meat.
I don't know what you're up to.
But it won't go your way.
- Hello.
- Goodness, hello.
Hello.
Is Professor Ju Hye-sung in?
He's not here right now.
Can we help you with something?
I just wanted to say hello.
- When will he return?
- He'll be back in about an hour.
- Should I give him a call?
- No, that's not necessary.
I'll come again.
By any chance…
may I use the bathroom?
Of course!
The bathroom is downstairs.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Kim Hyun-ji.
Why is her student ID here?
- You're back, sir.
- You came back early.
Yes, the appointment was canceled.
- Everything's fine?
- Yes.
Ah, sir.
Someone is here to see you.
- Who?
- The monk who came last time.
He's in the bathroom right now.
Goodness... the professor is here.
This is not the bathroom.
- I think you're lost.
- No kidding.
I went into the wrong room.
I'm full.
Since I ate all your dishes
for you, I'm going to leave now.
Already? Stay a bit longer.
I'm bored.
I wish I could, but visiting
hours are almost over.
See you. Hand me my crutches.
Hey!
- I'll walk you to your room.
- It's fine. I can do it myself.
- I said it's fine!
What the heck are you doing?
You were falling.
We almost kissed!
I haven't had my first kiss yet.
That's... not true.
Then...
You pervert!
Hey, hey, hey!
Do you want to die?
Ow!
Hey!
My first kiss what? I told you
not to mess around with me!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Jerk.
She's good at fighting.
It feels good to hit him.
Where have you been?
- I went for a short walk.
- Let's go in.
- Thank you.
- Be careful when you walk.
I will.
The professor is off today
so I came in his place.
- Are you comfortable?
- Yes.
Oh, I don't see
Doctor Kim Jung-woo either.
Pardon? Who?
Doctor Kim Jung-woo.
You know, the really tall guy.
We don't have a doctor by that name.
- Rest up then.
- Thank you.
Rest up.
My cell phone.
I must've dropped it on the roof.
She's so clumsy.
(Crazy Stalker)
Kim Jung-woo.
Kim Jung-woo?
I've heard that name somewhere.
Do you know a Kim Jung-woo?
Kim Jung-woo?
He used to work at our hospital.
You know him?
You don't know him?
About 10 years ago,
that doctor died in our hospital.
That doctor killed a patient
in the operating room.
Not only in our hospital but also
in the previous hospital
where he worked.
He killed patients during surgery.
Look at him.
Right behind you.
- There's blood all over him.
- I can't believe it.
Once the police started
to investigate, he killed himself
in one of our offices.
Bong-pal!
(Bring it on, Ghost)
Pull it tight!
What are you doing?
Ju Hye-sung is a professor
at Myongsung University.
I'm sure you'll find
something on him.
- Is it a gift for your girlfriend?
- Yes.
- You may leave now.
- Where's Bong-pal?
You don't know what kind of
person he is. Don't get too close.
Professor Ju will be in charge
of Ms. Hyun-ji's psychotherapy.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
He said he'd come, but he's not here.
Are you sure you have it?
All the evil acts you committed
will come back to haunt you.