(Ok Taec-yeon)
(Kim So-hyun)
(Kwon Yul)
(Kim Sang-ho)
(Bring it on, Ghost)
There's a water ghost there!
Was it because of me?
- I didn't do that.
- You were the only one next to her.
- Who else could have done it?
- I already said it wasn't me.
Bong-pal!
Hyun-ji.
Kim Hyun-ji.
Are you okay?
Bong-pal.
I was so scared!
Do you know how scared I was?
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay now.
12th place?
What kind of ranking is that?
You went down
from 3rd to 12th place.
Do you know how much of
a difference that makes?
What's wrong with you lately?
Get your act together!
I work my butt off to get
you private lessons! What is this?
(Bring it on, Ghost)
(Episode 7)
Hyun-ji, I'm heading out.
Hyun-ji.
(Academy for Language Arts)
Hyun-ji, wake up! Hyun-ji! Hyun-ji!
Hyun-ji.
- Bong-pal.
- What's wrong? Are you sick?
I just don't feel so good.
I wonder if it's because
you fell in the water.
Is it that bad?
I'm okay. I think I'll be
fine once I get some sleep.
- Go to my room and sleep.
- No, I'm fine.
Hello?
Bong-pal, where are you?
Seo-yeon, I'm sorry.
I don't think I can go out today.
Can we talk about
the final project tomorrow?
Why? Did something happen?
No, I just don't feel so great.
Oh? It's nothing serious, right?
It's not.
Okay, get some rest,
and let's meet up tomorrow.
Thanks, I'll see you tomorrow.
Hyun-ji, go sleep in my room.
What the heck am I supposed
to do when a ghost gets sick?
It's not like I can
take her to a hospital.
Hyun-ji, eat some of this porridge.
You didn't even eat breakfast.
She must be really sick.
- It's coming!
- Bong-pal.
Ms. Seo-yeon and...
It's the angel!
The angel…
Let's put it right in here.
How long are you going to
play that? Stop it already.
This is amazing.
- Where did you get that?
- This? I borrowed it from a friend…
Where did you get a friend?
You don't have friends.
I do... not have friends.
You shouldn't poke at
someone's pain like that.
Give it to me.
This... I mean, this...
Where did you get this? You probably
wasted all your allowance on it.
It's actually not as
expensive as it looks.
It's not...
Whether this is expensive
or not is not important!
Are you out of your mind?
Just what is wrong with you? Huh?
Look! Look! Look, look, look!
The retreat fees, gas money…
We need money for all these things.
When you start a business,
you need to spend some money.
This may not seem very important,
but our club members might...
It's necessary to help
with solidarity amongst our members.
But we're spending
more than we're earning.
That's why I have
an investment plan lined up.
An investment plan?
This measly amount of money?
We can take care of this in one go.
Don't... Don't worry!
What should we do?
Should we go meet
with our investor? Huh?
An investor?
(Acupuncturist)
What is it?
What's taking you so long?
Where are you?
Oh, did we have plans today?
Sorry, I've been out of it today.
I can't go today. I'm going
somewhere and I'm already on my way.
- Where?
- Where Bong-pal's father is.
I need to see him with my own eyes.
I have a bad feeling about this.
It's okay,
I'm perfectly fine! Hang up!
Just where is my honey?
Oh, honey! I finally found you!
Honey! Honey!
- Are you awake?
- Yes.
Why am I here?
I moved you in here.
You must be hungry. Stay here,
I'll heat up the porridge.
I told you to lie down.
Why did you come out?
I'm totally fine now.
I think I was just tired.
Really? That's a relief.
Go ahead and eat.
Thanks, Bong-pal.
It's nothing.
Why didn't you go to school?
Ah, I was kind of tired, too.
But do ghosts get sick, too?
- Yeah, our hearts race, too.
- What?
What?
It's nothing.
By the way, some of my memories
returned while I was sleeping.
Oh, really? What popped up?
I was lying down and someone
was looking down at me.
Who was it?
Well, I couldn't see their face.
Oh right, and some lady was crying.
I wonder who it was…
She was crying with such sorrow.
Have a good day.
Goodness, what is this?
Why are there so many
people looking for that man?
I mean, the acupuncturist
came last time.
What's going on today?
It's nothing really.
I came to ask some questions.
What is it?
I heard a young person came looking
for the man who lives in that room.
Yes, he came.
My eyes are bad so I didn't
get a good look at his face.
Oh, his son?
He's over there.
He was a good-looking young man.
His son?
I assumed he was his son.
Your son is here to see you.
His face got serious
when I told him his son came.
He just ran into the back mountains.
I thought he was running away
because he owed some money.
Anyway, he ran away
and never came back.
Where are the back
mountains he ran away to?
So, my honey lives
in this neighborhood!
I think Hyun-ji lives
around this area, too...
- You're here.
- Hello, sir.
What's the schedule for today?
You have three appointments today.
- I'll get changed then.
- Okay.
Even the clinic is cool
and clean like my honey.
Something bad happened.
He wasn't chasing something.
He was being chased.
Hey, I told you to get some rest.
Why are you following me?
I'm all better now.
Look, I'm fine.
I swear, you don't listen.
(Seo-yeon)
I'll see you in
the study room at 11 o'clock.
- Who is it?
- It's Seo-yeon.
We're supposed to talk about
the final project today.
- Just the two of you?
- Yes.
Wait for me!
Remember the puppy factory incident
that was a huge issue a while ago?
Should we use that as our topic?
Yeah, that sounds good.
We can include this as well.
- I think that'll be fine.
- Okay, let's go with that.
Wrap it up already.
Why here?
What do you mean why?
We came to meet the investor.
- But this is my grandma's house.
- Yes, it is.
The investor is my grandma?
That's correct.
Why do you keep bringing
this up? It's ridiculous!
You know very well that
I moved out because I don't
want any help from her.
Let's go!
We're not asking for a handout.
This is an investment opportunity.
She doesn't need one. Let's go.
Let go, let go, let go!
In-rang.
- Grandma!
- Goodness, my precious baby!
Goodness, when did you get here?
You should've come to
me first and said hello!
How long has it been?
Goodness, my precious baby!
Hello, ma'am.
Why do you have that
nuisance with you?
I told you not to hang out
with people like that.
It's good to have friends,
but you need to be more selective!
Grandma, Chun-sang is a good person.
- And he has something to tell you.
- What?
What nonsense is he going
to talk about this time?
I swear! Anyway, let's go inside!
What are you doing?
Come on in!
Dig in, my precious baby.
Goodness, you've lost so
much weight. Eat a lot.
Goodness, look at you eat.
Why are you so nervous?
Hurry up and dig in!
- Dig in.
- Yes, thank you for the food.
So, you have something to tell me?
Yes, the thing is...
We're thinking about starting
an international, trendy business...
Talk slowly, you rascal!
How dare you try
to pull a con on me!
Just get to the point.
In-rang and I are trying
to start a proper business
but we're struggling
due to a lack of funds
so we came here to talk to you.
How could it be struggling
if it didn't even start yet?
What kind of business
are you planning?
Ah, yes...
- This is our business plan.
- What is it?
Blood Sausage Soup?
When did you prepare all this?
You want to start a restaurant?
No, it's not a restaurant.
A state of the art
multi-communication system
with a speedy, thorough,
and proper 24-hour support.
We're planning to set up
an exorcism system!
You punk!
What did you say?
You con artist!
Wait until I get my hands on you!
You punk!
- Let's stop here for today.
- It's over!
Gosh, look at the time.
Do you want to eat lunch together?
Lunch?
What lunch? You're not
going to go, right, Bong-pal?
- Let's eat together then.
- Good, let's go.
What should we eat?
Whatever you want to eat is fine.
Bong-pal, let's eat some other time.
I need to talk to Professor Ju.
Sure, that's fine.
I'm really sorry. I promise to buy
you something really good next time.
- It's okay. You should get going.
- I'll see you in class.
What's up with her? She's the one
who asked you to lunch.
Right?
Let's go.
Was Byul good while I was gone?
He was very bad.
Maybe he takes after you.
What? Really?
I'm kidding. He was a good dog.
By the way, did you have
a good time at the retreat?
Yes.
You said you're in the same
club as Bong-pal, right?
- You two must be very close.
- Yes, I think so.
I see.
- Professor.
- Yes.
These are the list of
students for next semester.
- I need your signature.
- Sure.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Have a good day.
So, what did you guys
do at the retreat?
Hello, Professor.
It's good to see you again.
Yes, hello.
What brings you here today?
We didn't come here
to see you today.
- Are you Im Seo-yeon?
- Yes, that's correct.
We have some questions
to ask you about Noh Hyun-joo.
Are you free?
Hyun-joo is dead?
Yes, it's unfortunate,
but that's what happened.
When was the last time you saw her?
Well... she missed class last week.
I think that was the last time.
Do you remember how she was?
Anything you remember at all.
She looked... nervous that day.
Hyun-joo!
Hey, Seo-yeon.
I didn't see you in class today.
I just had some
business to take care of.
Why do you ask?
We received some materials to
take home from class today.
Just a moment.
Hyun-joo!
A fountain pen?
- Do you have that pen?
- No, I gave it to the professor.
Professor?
Yes, it belonged to
Professor Ju Hye-sung.
Professor Ju Hye-sung of
the veterinary medicine department?
Yes.
And there's
nothing else you remember?
I'm not sure.
(Bong-pal's father)
Please, leave
a message after the beep.
I hope nothing bad happened to him.
(Monk Myung-chul)
Tell me!
- Hey.
- Yeah?
Did your grandma deposit
the money yet? Check again.
You're really something else.
After all that abuse,
you still don't have it together.
Why can't she understand
this awesome idea?
Should we go see her again?
Well, if you want to die,
then go ahead.
Yo, Bong-pal! Long time no see.
Why didn't you come yesterday?
- Why?
- What do you mean why?
It's because we missed you.
How come we don't have any work?
You said you'd launch our business.
We just had that one gig…
and that was it.
Don't worry about that, okay?
Just think of it as
a temporary break.
Even frogs crouch and wait
like this before they jump.
Yeah, just like that.
I have something to give you.
Here, these are yours.
Those are the pictures
I took at the retreat.
Gosh, you two look good together!
You guys look like a couple.
I'm going to go.
Sure, see you.
You two really look good
together! The perfect couple!
- Are you stupid?
- What?
Get a clue.
Gosh.
My precious baby, Grandma
sent you some pocket money.
Make sure you eat on time
and buy lots of yummy food to eat.
And stop hanging around that loser.
- But who's the loser?
- I don't know, loser.
Why the library all of a sudden?
Why do you think? We came to study.
We can study at home.
It's hot at home
and it's cool in there.
Then you study in the cool
library and I'll be at home.
You're not going anywhere.
You have to study, too. Follow me.
Bong-pal, I solved everything...
What are you doing?
Huh? Ah, nothing.
- I solved everything.
- Already?
I was there, too…
I didn't show up…
(Bong-pal loves Hyun-ji)
Why are you all happy?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Did you finish grading yet?
I did a well this time, didn't I?
How can you possibly smile
at a time like this?
Did a good job? My butt.
My teaching was
such a waste of time.
Gosh, it was number four.
I was so close.
Why don't you give up on
the college entrance exams?
- How can your score not improve?
- Maybe I have a lousy teacher.
What? You will never find
a teacher who is as good as me.
This is because the student
just isn't smart enough.
If you keep putting me down,
how can I possibly improve my score?
Then what? What am I
supposed to do for you?
Don't just push me, but reward me
like you give a carrot to a horse.
Carrots, please.
Carrots, my butt.
If I do well on the exam,
you should reward me.
Fine. All right.
If you get higher than
80 points on the next exam,
I will grant one of your wishes.
Really? Will you grant any wish?
As long as it's within my budget
- and it's reasonable.
- Hooray!
You promised.
I will study really hard.
It'll be a breeze to get
higher than 80 points.
What is it?
No, I thought she looked at me.
- I must have made a mistake.
- Let's go.
Hey, you're studying at this hour?
Of course. I'm all motivated now.
Have a good night!
Wow, that's nice to see.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Good luck!
Come on, I asked you to do it
with us because Yoo-jin is good.
Isn't Yoo-jin going
to prepare for the Olympiad?
I was able to find
a very good tutor.
The tutor won't take
fewer than two students.
If we take too long,
we may not be able to get in.
Okay. I have to get
Eun-sung's snack ready now.
Okay then. Call me later.
Eun-sung. Eun-sung.
Eun-sung.
Get out.
Oh my, these look very expensive.
Seriously.
But why are we here?
What? What do you mean why?
You've never heard of
'clothes make the man'?
Look at Bong-pal.
Who would think he's an exorcist?
We should order him a suit.
Yeah, but in order to do that,
we need money first.
What do you mean?
We had that investment come in.
Investment?
How is that an investment?
It's my allowance!
How dare you.
Your money is my money.
My money is yours...
We can't treat each other like that.
Wow.
Wait, but why are you
looking at a suit for yourself?
I'm the face of our company.
Wow.
Why did you ask me to come here?
I asked you here
to order our uniforms.
Uniform? I want one, too.
- What uniforms?
- Come here.
It's okay, come here.
You should dress up like this, see?
How cool is this?
People won't look down on you
if you dress up like this.
When you're this stylish,
you will bring in more work, too.
Go put it on. Go on.
- Come over here.
- Well...
Come on. Here...
Put it on and come out.
See? We already have a client.
Hello, we provide
exorcism service 24-7.
This is Choi Chun-sang.
How may I help you?
Wow, you look cool.
You look the best among them.
Bong-pal, can you
also get me a uniform?
I'm the only one without one.
You keep asking me for things.
Bong-pal, hurry up.
Get me one, please.
Open the door! I said open it!
Open the door! Open it!
What happened?
Eun-sung...
Since that day, my child has...
Eun-sung, you're wearing makeup...
Take off those clothes. Now!
- Leave me alone.
- What?
Don't you feel sorry for the girl
that has you as her mother?
You have no idea
how much she's suffering
because of your greed, do you?
Eun-sung.
Why are you doing this, huh?
Eun-sung?
Your daughter is dead.
How could anyone live with
someone like you? It's suffocating.
That's why
your husband cheated on you.
He didn't want to live
with a wench like you.
Didn't you know that?
Get over here.
Get over here!
Ever since that night,
I've taken her to
see doctors and shamans…
It only made her symptoms worse.
You have no idea
what a good daughter she was.
I don't know what happened to her...
Eun-sung, please...
- Please, stop.
- Open the door now!
Open the door! Open it!
Eun-sung!
Let me go in.
Take this.
Bong-pal, I'm not getting
a good feeling about this place.
So please, be careful.
Don't get hurt.
I will be back.
Are you like the shaman
I saw last time?
No, you seem different.
You came with something else, too.
She's the one I saw at the library.
She also saw me then.
There's a ghost inside her body.
What should we do?
We need to take it out.
Who says you can?!
Bong-pal!
Why do you go around
with someone like her?
That's some strange hobby.
How about bringing me along instead?
Ma'am.
You can't. It'll be okay.
Eun-sung.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
What do you think you're doing?
Why do you care?
How about you?
You don't want Eun-sung to die.
This is what she wants.
She's not brave enough to kill
herself so I'm just helping her.
Don't show off
when you know nothing.
No!
Eun-sung, wake up.
Eun-sung! Eun-sung!
I told you Eun-sung was dead.
Eun-sung!
Eun-sung.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
Please, don't do that.
I did all that because
I wanted you to do well.
But I was wrong.
So please, don't do that.
Don't do that, Eun-sung. Don't.
Don't you dare call me by that name!
Please, help my Eun-sung...
Eun-sung, don't do that. Don't.
- Don't come closer. Don't.
- Eun-sung...
Don't do it. Don't.
Don't come closer. Don't.
Eun-sung! Eun-sung!
Eun-sung, wake up.
My child... Eun-sung.
Mom!
- Mom!
- Eun-sung.
- Mom...
Mom, did I do this to you?
I'm sorry, mom.
It's all my fault. I'm sorry.
No, I'm okay as long as you're okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, mom.
How can we help?
Go get some rest.
We will take care of the rest.
You go over there.
Bong-pal.
The lady I saw
in my dream last time…
- I think I know who she is.
- Who is she?
My mom. She was my mom.
She was just like
Eun-sung's mom earlier.
My mom would have
cried just like her.
It's good that you're getting
some memories back.
If it's not my mom,
at least one person misses me.
Let's go.
I need to go and study hard.
Now, it's time for the exam.
You have one hour.
Wait a minute.
I'm ready.
Now you begin.
What is it? My score isn't
higher than 80 points?
- Hm...
- Seriously?
No, it is.
Good job. Your effort paid off.
Of course, it did.
I worked so hard.
So now you have to
grant me a wish, right?
- A promise is a promise, so...
- Yes!
What is your wish?
There is a place
I've really been wanting to go to.
Where?
- An amusement park.
- An amusement park?
What are you, a kid?
Why would you want to go there?
Do only kids go there?
You said you'd grant a wish.
Let's go.
Okay. Your wish isn't very grand.
I will go with you.
Since we're on the subject,
can we go tomorrow?
- You're done with exams tomorrow.
- That's right. Okay then.
My exams will end
at 3:00 p.m. tomorrow.
- Let's say 4:00 p.m. at the park?
- Sure.
Hooray!
Sir, this is Detective Yang.
Detective Yang, what's up?
You conducted an autopsy
on Noh Hyun-joo, didn't you?
I already sent in the results.
Didn't you get it yet?
Yes, I did.
I just had a few questions.
- What are they?
- Noh Hyun-joo's neck was broken.
Is there a possibility it broke
when her dead body was moved?
That's highly unlikely.
If it broke after she died,
there would be a visible physical
trace on the surface of her body.
But there was none.
Then...
I'm certain that her neck broke
when she was getting strangled.
Can a person be strong enough to
break another live person's neck?
It's not impossible, but it'd be
difficult for an average person.
I see. Thank you, sir.
- I'll stop by soon.
- Do that.
- I'm back.
- What is it?
This is the CCTV footage
from near Ms. Noh's place.
- Did you find anything?
- Not really, but something was odd.
- What was odd?
- You might want to see it yourself.
Play it then.
This is Noh Hyun-joo here.
And then this corner here...
Someone was there.
- What's wrong?
- It stopped recording there.
They say it wasn't
a camera malfunction.
Take a look here.
It's like that
for exactly 5 minutes.
He breaks someone's neck…
And now this camera business…
What's his deal?
Who is he, huh?
Gosh, I finally managed to come in.
Oh my, this is where
my honey works, huh?
Ju Hye-sung?
Even his name sounds cool.
Wow, it's nice here.
What is this?
He's good, isn't he?
Oh my, he's so photogenic, too!
He's so cool.
Wait, where is this sound
coming from?
It sounds like
it's coming from here…
(Kim Hyun-ji)
Oh my goodness.
Came all the way in here.
How annoying…
We have a problem now.
Bong-pal, it's at 4:00 p.m. today.
You know that, don't you?
- Don't be late.
- Okay.
Bong-pal.
Seo-yeon.
- Did you just finish your exam?
- Yes.
- You, too?
- Yeah, for a liberal arts course.
- Where are you off to?
- I'm meeting someone.
- Excuse me.
- Okay, bye.
Seo-yeon!
Are you okay?
He's late...
Did his exam take longer?
Mister, please hurry.
(Bring it on, Ghost)
Hyun-ji! Kim Hyun-ji!
Hyun-ji! Did I ask you
to follow me around?
You're the one who decided to
annoyingly follow me around.
Gosh, you scared me.
Good for you. You're alive.
Do you walk around
with a ghost by any chance?
No, she was an angel.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Are you human trash?
Did we get some work? For real?
She died because of you.
Did you know that?
My angel.
She's pretty just the way she is.
But when she smiles,
she's even prettier.
Bong-pal.
I like you.
Hyun-ji!