What are you doing here?
I came to see Wan.
-I'm staying here with Wan.
-Wan just broke up with me.
What happened between you two?
Why’d you break up?
Ek cheated on me.
This is my family’s hotel, by the way.
I’d love for you to come and perform here.
It’s way better than busking, don’t you think?
Earth is a producer here.
I want the two of you to get to know each other.
You might work together in the future.
I broke up with Wan.
But we haven't filed for divorce yet.
So, does that mean Wan's new guy...
Is he a lover?
If you know who it is, could you tell me?
And what would you do if you found out?
I'd kill him.
Aren't you going to play music today?
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
I don't feel like eating much.
Why?
Are you feeling unwell?
Let me take a look.
Wan
Why didn’t you ever tell me
that you and Ek are already married?
Yes.
But I’m filing for divorce.
Then why didn’t you tell me before?
Like I said, it’s already over.
If you haven’t divorced yet, it’s not over, Wan.
Legally, that’s true.
But in terms of feelings,
it’s a different matter.
Then why did you tell Ek that you have someone new?
Because I really do.
So,
that person is an affair, right?
We haven’t done anything.
So, you can’t really call it an affair.
Wan,
I’m serious.
Ek told me he’s going to kill that person.
Someone like Ek
wouldn’t do something like that.
Who knows?
Someone who loses what they love
is capable of doing anything.
I’m scared, Wan.
What are you afraid of?
Are you…
my new lover?
You already know
who I’m talking about.
It’s obvious.
Well, no.
You’re not someone new.
But you’re the same person—
the first
and the only one I love.
So…
no matter what happens,
I’ll protect you with my life.
Just stay by my side,
and don’t disappear again.
Can you?
Pleng?
Wan.
That’s not nice.
How could you sneak a look at someone’s stuff?
I didn’t sneak a look; I was fully intent on it!
Well, still…
Didn’t you say you weren’t going to write any more songs?
Isn’t this your songwriting notebook?
I just started writing again since I’ve been with you.
But…
You didn’t see anything inside just now, did you?
I don’t know…
Not telling.
Wan.
This song isn’t for anyone else.
-It’s your song.
-Wan!
Just like how I belong to you.
Finish writing it soon, okay?
I’ve been waiting to hear it.
Been waiting for 13 years, too.
You’re so naughty.
I’ll head to work now.
Aunt Wi.
Pleng.
Hello.
How did you end up here?
Wan invited me.
When did you and Wan start meeting again?
And why does Wan trust you enough to let you stay in this room?
We only just reconnected recently.
But as for trust…
We’ve been friends, you know.
Just because we’ve been apart for a long time…
doesn’t mean our feelings for each other had to change.
Exactly.
You’ve been gone for so long.
So why did you come back?
Can’t you see that without you…
Wan's life has gotten so much better?
I can see that.
But not everything is better, right?
And what’s not better?
Her family.
I’ve heard that…
Wan and her husband are getting divorced.
He even asked Pleng for help.
And did Pleng help?
No.
It’s none of my business.
That’s good.
In that case, it would be better if you stayed away from Wan.
Sometimes, without you,
they might reconcile with each other.
And what does that have to do with me, Aunt Wi?
It has everything to do with you.
Because when Wan has you,
she doesn’t see anyone else but you.
In the past 10 years,
Wan has suffered enough because you disappeared.
So, if you leave one more time,
Wan wouldn’t feel more pain than she already has.
I’m heading out for a bit.
Excuse me for a moment.
Pleng.
You’ve met Wan’s mother, haven’t you?
So, you knew that Aunt Wi came here?
I was the one who picked her up.
To help with Wan.
Since you refused to help me.
And you think Aunt Wi will be able to help?
She’s her mother, after all.
At the very least, Wan might listen to her.
Wan doesn’t listen to anyone.
You’re the one who needs to listen to her and go through with the divorce.
And let her move on.
No.
I won't divorce.
I’m not going to let Wan be with that lover.
But Wan doesn’t love you anymore.
Even if you manage to bring her back,
it will only be her body.
In the end, your relationship with Wan
will go back to the way it was.
Can you really handle that?
I can.
Even if I end up lonelier,
more worthless,
I’ll endure it.
Because I love Wan so much.
I’m not ready to lose her yet.
See you at the hotel then.
Pleng!
Where are you, Pleng?
Mom, where is Pleng?
Did you let her stay here with you?
I'm asking you, where is Pleng?
I don’t know!
I only saw her for a second when I got here.
We talked for a bit, and she went out.
How would I know where she went?
What did you talk about with her?
Is this really the time to be worrying about someone else?
Focus on sorting out your own life first.
How could you tell Ek you’ve got someone new?
Do you actually have someone new?
Or were you just trying to make him believe it?
You don’t need to know that.
I’ve told you before.
I’m grown up now.
If it’s not necessary,
stay out of my life.
But it is necessary!
If you really do have someone new,
whoever it is, you need to break up with them.
And go back to Ek.
He’s never treated you badly the whole time you’ve been together.
He made one mistake, you should be able to forgive him.
One mistake for some people, Mom,
can ruin their whole life.
Just like what you did to me.
And to Pleng.
So you have no right to tell me
how I should handle my love life.
I’ll make that decision myself.
Hey!
Don’t be stupid.
You’ll never find anyone better than Ek.
I don’t need someone perfect.
I need someone who loves me.
And I love him.
And I’ve found him already.
I’ve known for a long time.
-Hello?
-Where are you?
I’m just out for a walk.
Where? Should I come meet you?
No, don’t bother.
You’ve got to get back to work soon anyway.
It’s a waste of time.
Okay, I won’t come then.
But, Pleng…
You met my mom, right?
It’s nothing, really.
You don’t have to worry.
Of course I’m worried.
I’m scared she’ll scare you off again.
She won’t.
I already promised you, didn’t I?
I’m not going to run away.
If I ever leave, I’ll tell you straight up.
Pleng…
I’m just joking.
Go back to work.
Don’t worry, okay?
I just need some time alone for a bit.
I’ll text you later.
-Sorry, man.
-Watch where you’re going, man!
Stop.
What do you think you’re doing?
Your friend got drunk and started messing with me first.
Wait, hold on a second!
I’m sorry on behalf of my friend.
But please, don’t start a fight with him.
Do you even know who he is? He owns this place.
If something happens, it’s going to get out of hand.
Fine, we’re leaving!
Let’s go.
Sit here!
You’re in bad shape, my friend.
It’s not even showtime yet.
Come have a drink with us first.
You too, man.
I think you’ve had enough already.
Doing this isn’t going to fix anything.
I just don’t know what else to do.
You’re right about that.
Even Wan’s mom can’t help me anymore.
I guess I’ve really hit rock bottom.
If I agree to help you,
will you stop acting like this?
Pleng…
What did you say?
I’ll help you talk to Wan.
But you’ve got to stop wrecking yourself like this.
Pleng...
Are you serious?
You’re not messing with me, right?
But I’ll only help
get you two talking again.
After that, it’s on you.
And it all depends on...
It also depends on what Wan decides.
But you have to respect her decision, whatever it is.
No matter how it turns out,
you’ve got to accept it.
I’ll help you too.
Sometimes words aren’t enough, though.
You might need to do something bigger than that.
So Wan knows
you really love her,
and want her back.
Wan.
Wan, Wan.
Yesterday you were thinking about Ek.
And today, I bet you’re thinking about your mom.
If you’re always going to be thinking about other people,
maybe we shouldn’t even be together.
Wait, Wan!
I’m not thinking about other people.
I just…
I was thinking
about finding time to take you out to dinner.
What?
I just got my first paycheck.
So I wanted to treat you to something nice.
If you’re going to ask me out to dinner,
you could’ve made it sound a bit more exciting.
So, what else do I have to do?
Why don’t you think about it?
What I might want you to do.
...might want you to do.
That’s it?
That’s already a lot.
Don’t ask for too much.
Fine.
This is fine.
It’s better than nothing.
Wait...
Can you wait here for a second?
I’ll be right back.
-Where are you going?
-Just wait, I’ll be right back.
I’m sorry, Wan.
Come back to me, please.
I told you, didn’t I?
That I’m going to divorce no matter what.
But I don’t want a divorce.
Then get ready to receive court papers.
If you want to make this a big deal.
Consider it done.
Give Ek another chance, please.
Ek really loves you.
This isn’t your business.
Stay out of it.
But Ek’s my friend.
I’ve got to help him.
Just like Pleng is trying to help you.
Pleng didn’t do it willingly.
She’s forcing herself.
I know that.
Wan,
please don’t leave me.
I can’t live without you.
Can’t live?
So what?
You gonna die?
Yes, I will.
Go ahead, then.
I’m curious to see.
Let’s see if you can really die.
It’s because of them, right?
Your new person, Wan.
That’s why you won’t give me another chance.
Who is it, Wan?
Who is this person?
They’re the one
who made me decide to marry you.
I married you to keep the promise I made to them.
And if they weren’t in my life anymore,
you’d be the only one I’d be with.
Even though
I’ve never loved you.
Are you going to stay here
with someone you just met,
or come home with me, Pleng?
Do you think
we should keep talking?
I don’t think so anymore.
But it’s good that you brought it up.
I really want to know,
when are you going to stop acting like this?
I didn’t mean to, Wan.
-I just wanted to...
-That’s not it.
I’m not talking about you helping Ek.
What I mean is...
When are you going to stop doing things that go against your own feelings?
I’ve told you to think about your own happiness first.
Why don’t you ever listen to me?
But some things...
It’s hard to only think about yourself, isn’t it?
What do you want me to do?
I’ve told Ek I want a divorce...
I’ve told Ek hundreds of times.
But Ek won’t agree.
So does that mean I have to suffer with Ek for the rest of my life?
No, that’s not what I’m saying.
I don’t want you to do that.
But you could talk to him calmly, couldn’t you?
That thing you said to Ek about dying,
I think that was a bit too much.
Because I know...
I’ve always tried to be kind when talking to Ek.
But the kinder I am,
the more hope Ek gets.
And the longer he ends up hurting.
Sometimes, a sharp pain that ends quickly
might be better.
But I think that...
Enough, Pleng.
Stop getting involved in this.
Seriously,
this isn’t even your business.
Okay.
I understand.
I’m sorry.
From now on, I won’t interfere with your life anymore.
Don’t be sarcastic with me.
I’m not being sarcastic.
In this situation,
what do you think I can do?
Tell me, please.
You...
Wan...
That’s enough.
I don’t want to do this anymore.
But I want to.
Wan...
I can’t do this.
We can do this.
You just need to let go.
Let go of what?
You know what we’re doing is wrong.
If we keep moving forward,
there’s no turning back, Wan.
If we can’t turn back, then we move forward.
Ever since I came back and saw you...
I’ve decided I’m not turning back anymore.
Wait, Wan...
I can’t do this.
I don’t want to be...
Then just stay still.
I’ll take care of it.
Wan, can you stop being so selfish?
You know what I mean.
Do you remember the promise you made to me?
You said,
if I graduated as a doctor,
I could ask for anything and you’d give it to me.
Why are you bringing this up now?
Because I know now
what I want.
What do you want?
I want you.
Wan...
No, Wan, we can’t.
We’re friends, Wan.
All this time...
we’ve crossed the line too far already.
That’s enough.
I understand now.
Chasing after someone who keeps running away
is exhausting.
I’d like to have a drink today, too.
Sure.
One glass, please.
I’m sorry.
I couldn’t help you at all.
It’s okay.
By the way,
why did you ask for a drink?
Is something stressing you out?
Did you have a fight with Wan or something?
I think I might need to find a new place to stay.
No way.
Wan’s not going to let you disappear.
Wan’s been looking for you all this time.
Wan really loves you.
She loves you a lot.
Sometimes I even wonder...
if the person Wan always talks about
is you, Pleng.
Don’t be ridiculous.
Wan and I are just friends.
No matter what, I’m still jealous.
Even though you ran away for so long,
when you came back,
Wan still gave you a chance to be together again.
But when it comes to me,
I made one mistake,
and Wan won’t even give me a chance.
I feel like...
I’m completely worthless in Wan’s eyes.
Don’t blame yourself.
You didn’t do anything wrong, Ek.
Then why does Wan love you so much?
Why does Wan still love
someone who’s hurt her for 13 years?
Do you know?
Ever since you left,
there hasn’t been a single day
where Wan smiled,
or laughed.
Wan’s been nothing but sad,
constantly blaming herself,
thinking it’s her fault
that you had to struggle alone.
Where is Pleng?
But even so,
Wan still thinks about you all the time.
Wan...
I miss Pleng.
I’ll help you find her.
Still trying to do everything
she promised she would do for you.
Still going everywhere.
Going to places where she thought you might be,
hoping to run into you.
Every day,
Wan wakes up startled at 4:00 a.m.,
because that’s the time you left her.
She’s been stuck on it,
holding onto it like a trauma.
Why does she wake up at that same time, again and again?
Pleng,
you’re in every part of Wan’s feelings,
never gone for even a second.
So, I’ll be leaving now.
Are you going to see Wan?
Yes, I’m going to see her right now.
There’s no need to rush that much.
I don’t want to wait anymore.
I don’t want to make Wan suffer because of me anymore.
I’m going now.
I told you, Guy, I need a break.
Don’t come looking for me yet.
And if you’re coming in,
you should knock first.
This isn’t a home,
so anyone can come in, right?
No need to knock.
If you want privacy,
then come home and sleep with me.
Who said anyone can come in?
This room is for doctors only.
Who gave you permission to enter?
No one did.
I snuck in by myself.
That’s terrible.
Then you should blame yourself first.
Because last time...
the reason I got into this room
was because you snuck me in.
Come home with me, Wan.
You left me to sleep alone for a night already.
Isn’t that a good thing?
But do you even think about anything?
No, I don’t.
I only think about one thing.
And that’s thinking about you.
I’m here to make up.
Come home with me, Wan.
You’re making up
because you’re scared of getting kicked out, aren’t you?
No, that’s not it.
It’s because I love you.
And also...
I want to keep the promise I made to you.
If you want me,
I’ll give myself to you.
Have you been drinking wine?
Yes.
You don’t like it? I can go rinse my mouth.
No need.
I like it.
It’s sexy.
Wan...
Say it louder.
So I know
how much you really want it.
Do you like it?
Of course I do.
But...
I still feel like it’s not really fair.
How so?
Well...
I’ve given myself to you.
So you have to be mine, too.
I know now.
Why you always wake up at 4:00 a.m.
How do you know?
It doesn’t matter how I know.
Just know that I feel really bad
for being the reason you have that trauma.
From now on...
Can you create a new memory of it?
At 4:00 a.m.
It won’t be the time I left you anymore.
But the time when
we became each other’s.
I can’t do that.
Because it was already over before 4:00 a.m.
If you really want to change that memory,
we have to start again.
Right now.
Did you come to see me for a reason?
No.
I was just out for a walk around here,
so I thought I’d stop by to see you.
Really?
It’s not because
you missed me so much that you couldn’t stand it?
I missed you.
You missed me?
Or did you miss what we did together?
Doctor Wan’s friend.
Hello, we meet again.
Pleng.
Guy.
Stop meddling, Guy.
Meddling? I just want to get to know your friend.
Last time we met, we didn’t even talk.
Understand this.
Back then, we were friends.
But now,
we’re not anymore.
So what?
This is Pleng.
-My girlfriend.
-Wan!
Got it.
So in the doctor's lounge...
-That day was...
-Excuse me, I’ll be taking Wan with me now.
Come here right now.
How could you say that?
You haven’t even divorced Ek yet.
How can you go around telling people we’re a couple?
Then what should I say?
Friends don’t do things like that.
You’re the one who said it yourself.
-But...
-Don’t worry about it.
I’ve waited a long time for this day.
I’ve always loved you, Pleng.
The kind of love that’s...
not just friends loving friends.
And I know,
you feel the same way as I do.
You’re just too afraid to admit the truth.
And I didn’t want to pressure you.
Honestly, if we had been braver back then,
we would’ve been together a long time ago.
We wouldn’t have had to wait this long.
I think it’s time.
Time for us to face the truth
and make it clear once and for all.
Besides, when we’re together...
...when we’re intimate...
Wan!
You won’t just call my name anymore.
But you’ll call me
-“darling.”
-Are you crazy?
We’re in public, you know.
“Darling, darling, darling.”
It’s cute, though.
“Darling.”
How have you been? I haven’t seen you in days.
But Ek’s not coming today.
I know.
He’s probably taking some time to heal.
But I’m not here for Ek today.
I came to see you.
Did you write this song yourself?
I really like it.
Can I buy it from you?
I was thinking of rearranging it,
and doing some mixing and mastering.
It would turn out perfect.
Sorry,
I’m not selling it.
I wrote it for my partner.
That doesn’t matter.
Whether you wrote it for your partner
or for anyone else,
I don’t care.
I only care that the song has value
and can be developed further.
I just think
it’d be a waste for you to keep it between just you and your partner.
You’ll get something out of it.
Hey,
I’m asking you seriously.
The reason you’re trying to approach me...
is it because Ek asked you to?
Yes, Ek asked me.
But if I wasn’t interested in you,
I wouldn’t be standing here right now.
I’m interested in you as a producer,
and as a man.
But if you already have a partner, that’s okay.
I still want to work with you regardless.
Are you sure?
That you can keep things separate?
If I were someone obsessed with women,
putting them before work...
By now, I’d have a girlfriend in every corner of the city.
So when will you stop being so confident?
Let’s say around 2:00 a.m., sounds about right.
Khun Earth.
Got it, Khun Pleng.
Here’s the deal...
I think you should go back and think it over.
What was the reason that made you start playing music?
If it’s your dream,
then I think it’s time to follow that dream.
And I’ll be the one to take you there.
Just say whatever it is you want to say.
If I…
wanted to take on more work,
would you be okay with that?
What kind of work?
Making music with Earth.
Wan…
I know that…
you don’t want me to do it.
Of course not.
I can tell that guy likes you.
Otherwise, he wouldn’t be bothering you like this.
But I don’t like him.
I really just want to work.
Fine,
do whatever you want.
If that’s what you want,
I won’t stop you.
Besides,
we’re already in a relationship.
I don’t want to keep fighting with you all the time.
It’s toxic.
Thank you.
But...
there has to be a condition.
You have to go on a honeymoon with me first.
Honeymoon?
Yes.
If we’re in a relationship, we have to go on a honeymoon.
That’s when it’ll be official.
Do you remember the beach...
that your dad took us to when we were kids?
Of course, I remember.
I want to go there.
After my birthday,
and once I can take some time off,
let’s go together.
Is something wrong?
I miss my mom and dad.
How should I comfort my darling?
Are you being sweet today, Way?
Don’t you like it?
I do.
But I’m just not used to it.
In that case,
let’s stick to the usual.
Smells so good.
Come here, I’ll feed you.
Do you remember
what today is?
Today?
It’s Friday.
And what else?
What else is today?
Is it the last Friday of the month?
Oh, or is it
Friday the 13th?
I’m not talking to you anymore.
Wait, hold on.
Tell me what today is first!
If you can’t figure it out,
then never mind.
How could I not remember?
It’s your birthday today!
What’s up, Ek?
I’m at the lobby.
Come down and see me, Pleng.
Okay.
Heard you took another day off today?
But I submitted my leave request in advance.
Are you going to celebrate your birthday with Wan?
What happened to your finger?
I cut it with a knife.
That’s not good.
Because someone like you
probably uses your fingers a lot.
What do you mean?
Well, you’re a musician,
aren’t you?
Let me ask you straight.
Why did you come to see me?
What exactly do you want from me?
If it’s just about taking time off,
then that’s already settled, right?
I’m going to go now.
Earth told me you have a partner already.
Who’s your partner?
And does Wan know?
I don’t have one.
I just said that as a precaution,
in case Earth tries to flirt with me.
Why?
I thought…
you and Earth
would make a good match.
If you and Earth got together,
you could finally move out of here.
And I think…
you’ve been with Wan for too long.
Ek…
What are you trying to tell me?
Nothing at all.
I wasn’t going to say anything.
I’m just trying to be considerate.
I want you to have a life of your own.
You and Wan are friends,
but you can’t stay attached to each other forever.
Thanks for your concern.
But this is my life,
and I can make my own decisions.
Surprise!
So you did remember after all.
I never forgot.
It’s your birthday, after all.
Have you seen the cake yet?
Do you like it?
What happened to your finger?
I was making a cake for you.
But not this one.
While I was making it,
I accidentally cut my finger with the knife.
I figured it wouldn’t turn out well, so I ordered this one instead.
I’m sorry, Wan.
Poor you.
Actually,
you didn’t have to make me a cake.
Because I don’t really want to eat it.
But I’d rather eat you.
Then go ahead and eat.
It’s your birthday today, after all.
Make sure you’re satisfied.
You two should die.
Ek!
I’m leaving now, Mom.
Wan...
Now that your father has passed,
come back and stay with me.
I don’t want to be alone.
I’ve told you before,
I’m never coming back to live here again.
And unless it’s necessary,
stay out of my life.
But I’m your mother, Wan.
How long will you keep punishing me for someone else’s mistakes?
Pleng is not just someone else.
She’s the person I love.
So there’s that.
Don’t you love me at all?
It’s you, Mom,
who doesn’t love me.
If you really loved me,
you wouldn’t have treated Pleng that way.
You would’ve been kind to her,
both in front of me and behind my back.
Because you should’ve known
how important she is to me.
But whatever.
Talking about it won’t change anything.
I’ve already lost Pleng.
And you’re going to pay for it.
By losing me as well.
If you still can’t accept the truth,
then that’s your problem.
Do you want to know what the truth is?
And who exactly can’t handle it?
There are some things
that make it impossible for Wan and I to be together right now.
There's an urgent document for you.
Whose test results are these?
Oh, you...
Didn’t you say you were moving in with me?
I want Wan
to give me a chance to take care of her.
If Wan ends up with no money and I have no one...
I think I’m scared.
(Just practicing)
But I want to play.
Someone’s being possessive.
Do you have kids?
How could I?
This is a doll.
Start with a kiss.
Lift the shirt first.
Lift the shirt.
The shirt just fell.
Mmm.
Okay, okay.
(Someone’s being clingy.)
Okay.
(Playfully shipping.)
(Getting dreamy.)
(Ticklish.)
(The scene is intense.)