[Jeon Hye Jin]
[Choi Soo Young]
[Ahn Jae Wook]
[Park Sung Hoon]
[Not Others]
[This drama is fictitious. The characters, organizations, locales, incidents, and circumstances featured have no relevance to real life.]
Kim Mi Jeong and Kim Eun Mi. Walk faster.
The sun will set even before we get up there.
I said we didn't have a fight.
We just had different opinions watching TV.
Hey, do you take the remote control first if someone has a different opinion?
Do you think I took it for no reason?
Shut up.
How dare you keep fighting in front of your mom?
Just punish us instead.
Why do we always hike whenever we fight?
Seriously.
We're dying right now.
Can we stop?
If you still don't know why,
you're not my daughters.
Go up!
Look at you.
You're serving alcohol to minors.
The makgeoli you drink on the mountain isn't alcohol. It's medicine.
And you graduate in a few days.
Drink up.
Cheers.
Grab it properly if you want it.
Tear it up properly.
You wanted it.
♫ The light pink skirt whirls around in the spring breeze ♫
♫ I'm biting on my jacket ribbon again today ♫
♫ On the path to Seonangdang where mountain swallows pass by ♫
♫ When flowers blossomed ♫
Dun, dun, dun, dun.
♫ We smiled together ♫
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
♫ When the flowers died ♫
♫ We cried together ♫
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
♫ That sincere promise ♫
♫ The spring days are passing ♫
[Episode 12: The things I couldn't say]
Kim Jin Hee will return to the HQ soon.
It'd be just until then.
Please manage the situation
so she won't get caught up in something and get defeated
after getting wrapped up in the hero complex again.
Got it.
What are you doing?
I thought we should eat something first.
- Coffee's okay. Right?
- Yes.
Thank you.
How nice.
Did you sleep okay?
I slept too well.
That's good to hear.
Did I move around too much or—
No.
Did I do something wrong?
It's not like that. Eat and go to work quickly.
- Oh, oh, oh!
- What?
Look at me while you talk to me.
It feels weird that you aren't acknowledging the night we spent.
Let's just...
think of it as an accident.
That'd be better for you, too.
I slept with you because I like you.
But you didn't. Right?
Just an accident?
You lied when you said you liked me, too?
I see.
That's why you were so into me last night.
Gosh. Why lie when you're not even good at it?
Let's talk for a moment.
Grandma passed away.
I'm at Seonghan University Hospital's funeral home. Come now.
What? Did something happen?
Huh?
No, together, please.
Let's put a lot of flowers there.
She liked flowe—
Jin Hee.
It's okay. Come here.
Let's send her away smiling.
Let's treat the visitors to tasty food like she used to,
and we'll chat a lot like she would've. Okay?
Let's.
Hey, where's Mom's funeral photo?
I gave it to the workers.
It'll be here soon.
Done.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Well, how did you know I was here?
What do you mean, how?
We went to the hospital, but you weren't there.
So we asked.
You're the lady with a good personality with an expensive car.
Were you Ms. Kim's family?
Yes.
Ms. Kim Mi Jeong and Ms. Kim aren't family. Right?
Why are they chief mourners together if they're not family?
You can do that for your friend, too.
But I didn't think her daughter would do that, too.
Thank you.
Didn't you get off work early to come here?
Not at all.
- Enjoy.
- Yes.
Thank you.
I'll be staying in Seoul for a while.
Why? Do you have work?
No, we broke up.
It sounds like you break up three or four times a year.
How many times have you broken up with her?
It's for real this time.
Who'd believe that?
But looking at you, I realize the world
doesn't care that Grandma died.
Huh? Tae Gyeong is here.
Tae Gyeong?
Tae Gyeong.
Hey, what about Young Hoon? I thought you'd come tomorrow.
That Hyungnim is here, too.
Hello.
I'll come back early in the morning.
Yes, that'd be better.
The chief mourners should get some sleep.
There will be more mourners tomorrow.
There will be more than today?
The second day is always like that.
It was like that with both of my parents.
You have to take care of yourself at times like this.
Cry if you want to.
If you hold it in, it becomes an illness.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Call me if something comes up during the night.
Thank you for coming.
See you, Jin Hong.
What an obvious thing to say as a doctor.
Why is he friendly suddenly? It's not like him.
He's always been friendly to the patients.
He only yells at me.
So you'd really do as Sis said?
What's the problem, Uncle?
We're doing it according to her will.
I know she said it in the will, but this isn't right.
Her direct family is alive.
But why would she give the inheritance to strangers?
It wasn't enough that she raised them, and she left them money, too?
Maybe she had dementia in her last days.
Watch what you say, Uncle.
Same with the chief mourner duty. I would've done it if you called me first.
Do you know what my cousin said when he came?
This is so embarrassing.
The children are supposed to be chief mourners.
They're not even her children. Why are they the chief mourners?
Do they share blood or flesh?
Honey, calm down.
Mi Jeong, don't be like that and help us out.
It's because we're struggling so much.
What have you been doing all this time that you are suddenly struggling?
What?
She went to the countryside because she was sick a long time ago.
You never visited her or called her.
Why suddenly care about the bloodline,
and why did your life get difficult?
Was she holding your money?
What thieves you are.
My gosh, listen to this woman.
- How dare you—
- Hey.
Did you go crazy because you're getting money?
Do you think you have the right to that money?
Yeah...
She's been giving Mom 200,000 or 300,000 won as pocket money for 20 years.
She gave her at least 10,000 won when she was struggling.
She gave her presents, took her on vacations,
and took her to the hospital, too.
Does she still not have the right, Uncle?
She cared about someone who was not even family.
Why didn't she care about her own brother? Huh? Why? Why?
I was never sad that Grandma and I didn't share blood.
Because she cherished me as someone more than that.
But what's the point now?
She's gone.
She was my mom.
She was my mom...
that I chose.
No matter what people say,
she was my mom.
[List of personnel appointments]
Your return date is set, Team Leader Kim.
When is it?
In three weeks.
Congratulations, Team Leader.
By the way, why is it happening much sooner?
I guess they're in a rush, too.
I see. We're getting a new team leader, then?
I know.
Team Leader Kim,
it's okay to be happy. Don't worry about us.
Thank you so much, everyone.
Let's have a dinner before you leave.
I'll have fun until my body breaks down.
Yeah!
I'll sing for you.
- Pardon?
- Don't do it.
Seriously, don't do it.
Why were you doing this alone?
You should've asked me for help.
Mom had more belongings than I thought.
I need to clean out her house in the countryside, too.
You just have to do it within 49 days.
Let's go together sometime.
Why did she keep this without throwing it away?
You did fine at the funeral.
Why are you getting more and more sentimental?
Hey.
Make Jin Hee move out soon.
Don't make her live with her mom for over 40 years like I did.
The reason I can't get it together is because I lived with my mom for too long.
I don't want to. I'll keep living with her.
Do you want Jin Hee to live like me?
Yes, I want her to.
Mom...
How touching is it...
that she'd think of me for so long like you?
Here.
Your mom's panty.
Mom...
- Hey, hey. Look at this.
- Mom...
It's the red long johns you got her with your first paycheck.
Isn't it so sad? Take it.
Mom's pillow.
Mom...
What else would make you cry?
Here.
Her bathroom socks.
These...
The floral long johns you got her with your first paycheck.
Mom knitted this for you after working at the restaurant without even sleeping.
You could've just bought these.
But you bothered her begging her to knit them.
Mom...
Mom!
Mom! Mom...
I'm so curious.
Yes, I'm getting my own place.
Wow, she packed her things.
Should I get my own place, too?
Really? That'd be great. Do it.
Give me a break. She's just saying that.
How do you know? You don't even know how I feel.
It's not like you'll live with me forever.
What's the reason?
There are lots of reasons if you look for them.
I think I'll return to the HQ soon, too.
Why don't you look for a place near the HQ?
Hey, nice.
Nice.
Why now?
Grandma passed away just recently.
Does my only daughter have to move out
after I said goodbye to my mom?
I was just saying that. Why are you being so sensitive?
You said you have a lot of reasons.
Tell me all of them. What are they?
I told you I was just saying that.
You're making me look bad now.
Hey.
You know something, don't you?
- No.
- I don't even know why. How would he know?
You just said there are a lot of reasons.
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
I take back what I said. Happy?
You little...
Gosh. Move!
She must be in shock because Grandma passed away.
Does she think she's the only one sad?
So you'd better not come for now.
Seriously. Of all days. Why is she...
Why is she talking about moving out now?
Gosh, you both are like girls going through puberty and having 8th Grade crises.
She didn't even act out during puberty or have the 8th Grade crises.
She was nicer back then.
Oh, right. Eun Mi, do you want to work out with me?
All of a sudden?
I've been meaning to tell you,
but even if you say no,
I have the courage to persuade you now.
Let's do it.
Oppa, I'm not the type of person who exercises.
Being a physical therapist is such a draining job.
To me, lying around and doing nothing is exercise.
Resting is exercising for me.
- Exercise? Oh, no.
- Aigoo...
You don't like that place? I—
Mom.
Ahjumma.
What are you guys doing here?
Are you ignoring what I said?
You really want to move out?
Jin Soo,
you don't like the one-and-a-half room one?
I liked that one—
My gosh, who's this Oppa?
[Snack Bar Heaven]
Looks good, looks good.
Another one?
Hey, you said you'd pay. Why did you order so much?
- This is going to cost a lot.
- It's not that expensive here.
- Don't worry and help yourself.
- Yes, yes.
You can't even drink. Good thing they have a lot of meal options.
- Gosh.
- That's perfect for soju.
Are you moving back from Jeju, then?
I am, and I'm sick of...
worrying about what people think. It's exhausting.
I won't do that anymore.
Fine. Don't get into it.
Let's drink.
What a perfect age...
You're at the perfect age, too.
You probably wanted to move out like Jin Soo, too.
- No.
- But I want you to do it later.
I don't want you to right now.
I said I won't.
Jin Soo is so youthful. Why are you all wilted?
Are you protesting against me?
Does it look like that? Maybe because I'm not having fun.
Not having fun?
Senior.
Hello, Ma'am.
So this is how it goes.
With that fool.
My Jin Hee must've slept over at the official residence often.
Well, t-the thing is...
Of course. It's for the employees.
Then, when you move out,
it'd be perfect to move into the official residence.
- Come on, I can't—
- She can't do that.
Why not?
She can save money that way.
It's for the employees.
Mom, I've been thinking. If I move into the official residence,
That's not going independent. It's cohabitation.
I'm sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Chief Constable Eun.
Yes, Ma'am.
Bravo.
She's saying you're the best.
I am?
It's sticky. This is no good.
I'll go get wet towels.
I'll—
I-I'll come with you.
Do you need something?
No.
You need a workout outfit and shoes first.
What's wrong? I can dress up when I work out.
Let's go, Oppa.
Anyway, let's take it easy since it's the first day.
I'll be totally intense with it.
Why do you like intense stuff so much? In these shoes?
Don't worry, don't worry. You know me.
- See you later.
Good luck.
Gong Ga Eul.
What are you doing?
Did you run away from home again?
- No.
- What are you doing here, then?
Do you have a sanitary pad, by chance?
Wait in the bathroom. I'll get it for you.
I just don't have extra ones.
Just give me two.
Okay. Wait here.
Hold on. I'll get them for you.
Give me your bag.
Come whenever you need them.
Thank you.
You're much nicer than that Unni
and you're so sensitive, too.
Hey.
- It's for the pads.
- My goodness.
- How about me?
- Thank you.
Hey, Gong Ga Eul.
You're okay. Right?
What's she saying? So annoying.
How strange.
Why am I not excited at all?
Returning to the HQ was all I was focusing on.
So whenever I felt drained,
I endured everything, thinking it would be fine if I returned to the HQ.
But why do I feel so drained?
I feel like I'm in a swamp.
Probably because it's not what you expected.
You thought you'd be here for a year, but it's happening sooner.
You're not ready yet.
Not ready yet?
You don't have to relay what Section Chief said again.
"Hero complex" and "Don't get caught up?"
I can manage myself. You know I can.
He's so bad at comforting someone.
What? What's this now?
Did the Section Chief say something else?
You've been doing well.
And you'll be fine.
This is not bad.
Hold still for a moment.
Don't look at me like that.
Pardon?
Hold on. Hold on.
Let's go and take an X-ray.
Watch the steps.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on, hold on, hold on...
Thank you.
Your back isn't the problem.
It started from your neck.
What are you doing? What will you do?
Wow, look how stiff your shoulders are. They're rock-hard.
That's why you should exercise every day.
This isn't a young person's body.
You started exercising a few days ago. Quit lecturing.
Everything happens in a chain reaction.
Because you have no muscles, your shoulders are supporting instead.
And since your shoulders are stiff, your back gets stiff, too.
That's why you have pain all the way to the lower back.
How is she? Is she okay?
She's okay. She just sprained her back.
Don't move too much.
- Okay.
- Be careful.
Yes, see you.
- My gosh.
- Hello.
Come on in.
- Aunt.
- Hey.
- We're leaving.
- See you.
Bye.
Gosh, isn't she addicted to fitness now?
How could she get into it so quickly?
She'll quit soon.
She's always been like this.
- Right? It won't last long. Right?
- I'm 100% sure.
Your mom said you're okay. Are you really?
I'm okay. She's an expert. I should trust her.
I couldn't move yesterday,
but I can move around today.
You should've been careful.
I made bone broth for you. I'll heat it up quickly.
Oh, nice!
Rouen Cathedral is one of the most beautiful buildings in France.
Rouen Cathedral is located in the Northwestern part of France...
Aren't you tired? Have a seat.
Okay.
[Rouen Cathedral]
I meant you should sit on the sofa.
This is fine.
What are you watching?
Do you want to travel?
Huh? No, how could I go there? I'm just watching.
Why not? You can go if you want.
It's hard for Mom to get out of work.
I can't go on my own, either.
Why? Are you scared to travel alone?
No.
I'm not scared.
Why can't you go alone, then?
Are you okay?
Why are you going in there?
I came here to have another look at it.
I was wondering why this was here at first.
But now I know why you put this up here.
What?
I'm taking tomorrow off.
Let me.
What?
We provide tour guides for landmarks in each country.
And there are individual tour guides, too.
It won't be difficult to travel at all.
So, can I choose my own lodging instead of this one?
There's a fee if you choose your own.
You can stay at an affordable place if you get everything as a package.
♫ Let's keep the same pace and walk along together ♫
♫ I can't control my heart ♫
♫ It's love, love, love. Like, I love it! ♫
♫ Somebody like you ♫
♫ It's nice and refreshing, I can taste it ♫
♫ Since you're always there ♫
♫ Somebody like you ♫
♫ You're so dreamy, I need you ♫
♫ I need you, I need you ♫
♫ You need me, my everything ♫
♫ To me. Love it. This feeling. Love it. ♫
♫ Deep down in my heart, you are the same but different ♫
♫ Together. Love it. This moment. Love it. ♫
♫ You were by my side in the shiny moments ♫
♫ To me. Love it. This feeling. Love it. ♫
♫ Deep down in my heart, you are the same but different ♫
♫ Together. Love it. This moment. Love it. ♫
♫ You were by my side in the shiny moments ♫
Look at you.
I told you to walk carefully. Are you feeling better now?
You probably didn't drink.
Why are you blushing so much?
What is all that?
I'm going on a trip, Mom.
When?
- Within a month.
- Geez.
Hey, we should've planned together.
You can't just schedule it like that.
I'm going on my own.
I'm backpacking all over the world.
For how long?
- A year.
- Are you crazy?
I told you not to move out. But now you're running away to abroad?
I'm not running away. I'll be traveling, Mom.
That's the same thing.
Moving out is permanent, but I'll come back home after traveling.
I'll be back.
You won't be by my side, anyway.
A year? Are you serious? You can't!
Mom, do you know what happened to me in the past few months?
I got demoted.
Jin Hong showed up.
You went through an ordeal.
My so-called blood relatives suddenly showed up.
And Grandma passed away.
I thought...
I had handled all those things well and moved on.
But...
it turns out I didn't.
I was just hanging in there without even knowing how to.
You told me when you were giving me physical therapy.
That everything is a chain reaction.
That everything gets damaged because I have no muscles to withstand the weight.
That you have to fix everything in the beginning so things don't break down.
You're going backpacking?
All over the world?
Yes.
Is that too much?
You've never been outside the country on your own.
Will you really be okay?
Exactly. That's why I want to do it on my own.
Leave.
You can.
You're more than qualified to enjoy yourself.
I fully support you.
I'm on your side, no matter what.
So...
I have to let go of Jin Hee...
so she can let go of me, too.
That's the right thing to do. Right?
For me to let her go first?
Because I'm an adult
and her mom.
Yes.
That's probably right.
By chance,
even if...
you're not satisfied with Jin Hee at some point,
let's say she's going through the puberty stage
that she went through without acting out.
Let's tolerate, forgive, and wait for her.
And in the end, she'll come around and be by our side again.
She'd do even better without me.
Of course. She's Kim Eun Mi's daughter.
How come you don't suggest living together these days?
Have you given up?
No, I'm waiting.
Although I don't know when that will be.
You know, I think...
it'd be ideal if we could see each other whenever we want.
Isn't it nice to miss someone?
But...
if I still feel lonely, even though
I spend every day with you,
I won't be able to stand that.
If you do that to me, I'll kill you.
Why are we going in that direction now?
I'm telling you never to be too sure about our relationship.
No one knows what'll happen.
All right. I won't guarantee anything.
Each day,
Day after day, I'll just...
like you, adore you, and be happy.
I'll live that way.
Cheers?
Cheers.
What are you doing?
I'm studying.
Why are you studying when you're going on a trip?
You just go straight up.
What? Spain?
What should we eat here today, Unni?
Why don't you get something sweet?
- That's right.
- Hello.
Ms. Kim. Ms. Kim's daughter.
Yes, yes.
We'll buy you coffee. Join us.
No, it's okay.
We go to this cafe often.
We're regulars. Just come with us.
They have amazing coffee.
Shall we, then? Why don't you treat us?
I will.
- Let's go.
Would you like to order?
Well, do you like something sweet or nutty?
What's she saying?
We're choosing beans right now.
Oh, I see.
One decaf iced Americano.
Three light roast coffee.
One Einspanner. And a croffle, too.
Put everything on this card.
Wow, Unni, you're so cool.
- Let's have a seat.
- Sure.
Here you go.
I want to try this.
Is it tasty?
The coffee's so good.
Try it. Try it.
Try this one.
A pretty person needs to do it. It's not for everyone.
It's so tasty.
Okay, okay.
Is it that tasty?
Daughter, this is tasty.
Yes, yes.
It's corn.
You have to have them together.
That's the right thing to do. Right?
For me to let her go first?
Because I'm an adult...
and her mom.
Yes. That's probably right.
Should I button up or down?
Here.
Yes. Let's switch spots.
Huh? Do we have to?
Yes, I have to stand there because I'm her granddaughter.
It has to be the daughter.
Mom.
Let's get started now.
One, two, three.
Let's go one more time.
- One, two, three.
- Say kimchi.
Let's say grandma.
Grandma.
Nice. Let's take another one.
One, two, three.
Jin Hee.
[Jin Agu]
Here.
Ta-da.
You, too? Gosh. Thank you, Aunt.
Spend the money wholeheartedly.
Let me know if you need more.
Yes, you have to sleep somewhere nice.
I'm sure you'll eat well.
What are you guys talking about?
Don't you know what backpacking is?
She's saying she wants to suffer.
Just let her be.
But still. She's going abroad alone for the first time.
Don't be so uptight.
I'm sure she's already worried.
I'll be strict about it.
Use it conservatively
and if you run out, make money yourself.
Okay, I really won't call you. Okay?
Ahjussi. Aunt. Thank you.
I'll use it really well.
Okay.
Here it is, here it is.
- Gosh.
- Thank you.
- It's huge.
- Wow.
This is boneless agujjim, right?
I'll have fried chicken first.
Let me get it for you.
I'll do it for you.
- Okay.
- Jin Hee, you have to stay in touch.
I hate "No news is good news." Okay?
Aunt, I'll make a travel blog before I go.
You can hear updates from me there.
- That's for keeping a journal and posting photos. Right?
- Yes, yes, yes.
I love that.
Send me the link to the blog, too.
Of course. Make comments. Okay?
Should we all sleep in one room tonight?
We won't be seeing her for a year.
It's an early morning flight, apparently.
She's staying at a hotel near the airport and leaving from there.
Really?
We should've seen each other sooner, then.
It's so sad. My baby.
I've been...
feeling very anxious lately.
You probably didn't know.
You've been anxious?
About what?
I felt impatient for no reason.
What if...
I die suddenly?
Die alone like Grandma while you're not around.
You said you wanted to look cool and die alone.
You said that's your way.
You said that's the death you want.
It was all bull crap.
I was blabbering without even living long enough.
So? How do you feel now?
Are you okay? You don't feel anxious?
The funny thing is, seeing Jin Soo, Min Gi, you, and Chief Eun
made me feel better.
I felt reassured.
Yes.
I'm okay.
Because of us? Why?
I'll live long and healthy from now on.
I'll work out every day, too.
I'll get a driver's license, get a car,
and go on a lot of dates, too.
Yes.
It all sounds nice, but...
Jin Hong is the only one you'll have dates with. Right?
You never know.
You're impressive. Truly.
I have a favor to ask.
When I have my funeral,
you'd better not cry.
I think I'll get up in the casket if I hear you cry.
Don't ever cry. Okay?
Go to bed.
I got that and...
Okay.
Bye. See you later.
Are you working out again? Your daughter's leaving, though.
Why would I see you leave? I don't even like you that much.
Don't come out. I don't want to bother.
Here.
What is it?
Backpacking preview by Eun Jae Won.
Whenever I wanted to leave looking at the world map,
I wrote down what I wanted to do in France
and where I wanted to go in Australia.
I've been taking notes like that.
Amazing.
Just go around the globe once. Doing it twice—
I'll miss you.
♫ I don't know where to start ♫
♫ I've been waiting, thinking about that every day ♫
I'll get going.
I'll be waiting.
Of course.
By the way,
can you drive me to the airport shuttle stop, at least?
Okay.
Gosh, amazing.
Do you want me to carry your bag?
It's okay. Do you want to try lifting it?
♫ It's precious to me ♫
♫ You are my dream, my love, everything ♫
♫ I'll protect you forever ♫
♫ I'll embrace you no matter what ♫
♫ I can't help but love you more than myself ♫
♫ I'll always love you the way you were from the beginning ♫
♫ It might be awkward and not be enough since it's the first time ♫
♫ But I'll always love you without changing ♫
♫ You're my dream, my love, everything ♫
♫ I'll protect you forever ♫
♫ Because you're one and only, a precious person to me ♫
♫ I can't help but love you more than myself ♫
♫ I'll always love you the way you were from the beginning ♫
[Family Relation Certificate]
[Daughters: Kim Mi Jeong, Kim Eun Mi, Granddaughter: Kim Jin Hee]
She was my mom...
that I chose.
No matter what people say,
she was my mom.
[Daughters: Kim Mi Jeong, Kim Eun Mi, Granddaughter: Kim Jin Hee]
My grandma, who chose me.
And...
my mom, who chose me.
♫ You kissed my hand ♫
♫ How could I describe it with words? ♫
♫ Like a dream with you, like a dream with you ♫
♫ I'll hold you one more time ♫
♫ I'll stay all night by your side ♫
♫ Good night, good night, good night ♫
♫ How could I describe it with words? ♫
♫ Like a dream with you, like a dream with you ♫
♫ I'll hold you one more time ♫
♫ As if we'll meet tomorrow again ♫
♫ Good night, good night, good night ♫
What brings you here?
Are your shoulders acting up again?
I can't sleep well these days.
I can't digest and my head hurts a lot, too.
Medicine only works temporarily
and I can't keep taking it because I'd develop a tolerance for it.
If so...
you should go see an internist.
Why did you come to an orthopedist?
Pardon?
Should I introduce you to a good internist?
Doctors usually try to help.
But a specialist would be more helpful, no?
Yes, yes. You're right.
I must've been out of my mind.
Gosh, my apologies.
[Passenger Terminal 2]
Final Credits
What?
I'm going on a trip, too. Why?
Mom, I said I'm going alone and even said goodbye. You can't tag along like this.
Who tagged along, exactly?
You're traveling all over the world.
And I'm going on Santiago Pilgrimage.
What are you talking about?
You're supposed to prepare for it several months in advance—
Have you been working out with Ahjussi because—
Do you finally get it?
It has nothing to do with you.
I'm addicted to walking these days.
Wow, look how thorough this woman is.
I don't care.
You're taking care of yourself.
I have my own plans, too—
I have my own plans, too.
Just worry about yourself.
You mean it. Right?
Okay.
Fighting.
Final Credits
Life is like an endless rail.
The things you thought you passed by come back to you.
It's up to you to decide how to confront that moment.
He's my junior in college. I'd like you to treat him.
If you look to the side while running, someone is running at the same speed as you.
Senior?
Let's go to my place.
Even when you want to collapse for a moment,
someone gives you a hand to help you get up.
If you still don't know why,
you're not my daughters.
Sometimes, you experience scary moments that you never thought you'd experience.
You're getting beaten up! You're getting beaten up!
Ms. Kim. Calm down. No...
Sometimes, the genre of your life changes to the one you never thought you'd experience.
But someone in the audience is cheering for you.
What we have to do is...
You're the one who fought with Jin Soo and had him come over to my house all the time?
Even if you have to slow down when you're tired...
You can just ignore it and be on your way.
But run cheerfully when you can with others. Just try to keep running.
♫ You're giving me all the reason in the world ♫
♫ I want to reach your heart a little closer ♫
♫ You make me feel alive ♫
♫ And always make it right ♫
♫ You shine on me like a bright star ♫
Jin Hee asked me to relay this message.
Please tell Aunt Ji Eun that I'll come back from the trip safely.
What a complete joke.
I thought of him as my doctor.
I'll never come back.
♫ You're the only one for me ♫
♫ Many moments I wandered around for getting lost ♫
Gosh, I'm sorry. I...
I ran into your car again.
Geez, what do I do?
♫ So many moments I wandered around ♫
♫ You shine on me like a bright star ♫
♫ You're the beginning and end of my days ♫
♫ Every day and night ♫
♫ You're the only thing I'm sure of in my days full of question marks ♫
♫ I want you to be my last ♫
Final Credits
♫ Want to be free ♫
♫ I want to imagine my life without you ♫
[Not Others]
♫ I want to reimagine my forgotten dreams ♫
♫ Since I met you, because of you, I laughed and cried ♫
♫ Sometimes I think I want to get away from you ♫
[Thank you for enjoying "Not Others"]
[The end]
♫ The connection between you and I can't be broken ♫