[Jeon Hye Jin]
[Choi Soo Young]
[Ahn Jae Wook]
[Park Sung Hoon]
[Not Others]
[This drama is fictitious. The characters, organizations, locales, incidents, and circumstances featured have no relevance to real life.]
♫ I kind of had a feeling ♫
♫ Your face is still sweet and friendly ♫
♫ Your discreet smile ♫
♫ Go ahead and keep trying to hide it ♫
♫ Hey, babe, I see everything ♫
♫ I'm so quick, I know everything ♫
♫ Stand by, my eyes are focused ♫
♫ Your eyes will be on me, just wait a moment ♫
♫ Hey, look at me ♫
♫ Let's get it on and on, baby ♫
♫ Let's get it on ♫
Ice cream! Refreshing ice cream!
♫ Say you love me ♫
♫ It's such a lovely night, baby ♫
♫ What a wonderful night ♫
♫ Before this night is gone ♫
What are you doing? Go play!
No!
Why not?
You'll play with strangers again if I leave.
There's your fried chicken!
Wow, fried chicken!
We paid just now.
Yes, enjoy!
♫ Let's get it on ♫
♫ Your voice is driving me crazy ♫
♫ Please tell me ♫
- Is it good?
- Yeah!
♫ Say you love me! ♫
♫ Such a lovely night, baby ♫
What am I doing with you after coming all the way here?
♫ Kiss me, yeah ♫
♫ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♫
That's my first memory at the beach.
You didn't go in the water with me even once.
What do you want from me?
At least you brought me there.
You tried your best.
Here.
Yes.
I'm proud of you!
Well done.
How about sashimi and soju for Round 2? Yes?
One hundred percent, yes.
Guys, we came all the way here. We should go to the club.
- Which one?
- That's right!
Do you know a good one?
Hey! We should go to the club, too.
Mom, you'll get rejected at the entrance. You can't go in.
- How about a nightclub, then?
- Seriously?
Why would I go to a nightclub with you?
Stop looking! Stop!
[Daughter vs. Mom]
[Episode 1: Mom vs. Daughter]
Hey! You thief!
Help! She's a kidnapper!
Please catch her!
Hey!
Please catch that thief!
Yes, I'm at the Yeyoung High School Bus Stop.
Are you out of your mind?
Please hurry.
I think it's an attempted kidnap. Yes, yes.
How dare you take my daughter?
Please watch her for a moment.
Why would you take my daughter?
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Stop! I called the police.
The girl is safe, too. So stop now.
Hey! Are you out of your mind?
Ma'am! Ma'am!
This isn't good for your case, either.
Stop and watch the girl. Let go of this!
Let go!
Why are you bothering me instead of that bitch?
Are you on her side, too?
How dare you beat my daughter?
Huh?
- Oh, my! My, my...
- Mom! Mom!
Mom, Mom, Mom!
It's because her daughter almost got kidnapped.
What kind of mother punishes the kidnapper without caring for her child?
Don't you care if she's in danger or not?
What kind of mother are you?
What's with you? Why?
- Over here!
- I got her!
Let go! Let go!
She was abused!
You're a total bitch, aren't you?
Stop! You're assaulting her, too, if you do this.
You'll be charged with assault, too!
Come! Come!
- Let go!
- Mom! Mom!
[Woosook Patrol Division]
How does that make sense?
She was reported for abuse multiple times, but they didn't do anything.
Geez! So frustrating.
This is why people hate the police.
- Lieutenant Kim Jin Hee?
- Yes?
Here's your ID.
Thank you.
Why are you blaming them? It's not even their jurisdiction.
What? You were upset with me.
You have to make a fuss so the person in charge hears and takes responsibility.
Should I just have done nothing?
Damn it!
It's sold out everywhere!
Geez, forget about watching a movie.
Let's just go eat.
Mom, how did you know she was abusing her?
Can't you just tell?
She was flipping out without caring for her. It's obvious.
You're right. How come I didn't notice it?
How's gamjatang?
Anyway, that person's so impressive.
Gopchang?
The person who was mistaken as a kidnapper.
Keep it short! I'm starving. Let's get a taxi.
She's just her neighbor! A total stranger!
A total stranger is better than family oftentimes.
You're not family just because you share blood.
Tteokbokki!
- Yes, let's get tteokbokki.
- Deal!
Right? Sharing blood doesn't make one a family.
Call right now. Call a taxi.
Mom, let's eat cleanly without the add-ons.
What do you mean? You need to make fried rice, at least.
No, it's too heavy. Just get more side dishes.
Rice!
Whatever. Let's eat separately, then.
The e-commerce law has restrictions for deceptively luring customers,
but there's no restriction for the seller canceling the order.
The one who saved the victim in the desperate situation
wasn't the police, but a fellow citizen.
- Thank you.
- The police dismissed the victim's request
for special protection twice.
They were unfriendly when I made the request already.
They said I can't because there's no evidence.
They didn't believe me as if I were lying.
The police can't be like that!
I am so scared.
Whose side are the police on, exactly?
It's frustrating whenever we hear news like this.
Let's watch the movie tomorrow instead.
How about 9:00 to be safe?
I have a work dinner tomorrow. I'll be late.
We can watch it later, then. Should I get tickets for 11?
I'll be home at midnight at the earliest. Let's watch it later.
Later when?
How do I know? I have to wait and see.
You're such a meanie.
Watch it with someone else, then.
Do you want me to get the tickets?
Forget it. You think you're the only one busy?
I have plans, too. A lot of them.
I pressed it down. Why are you taking all of it?
I set it up perfectly.
Criticism for the police is growing.
Wolsan Police Station said they're assessing the situation...
You ate all the cheese...
I'm Kim Jang Han from EJC News.
- Please say something about the current incident!
- What do you think about it?
Please say something...
[Wolsan Police Station]
- Jin Hee!
- Oh, good morning.
Stop saying "good morning" today.
Just keep your mouth shut.
I heard the demotion announcement came out already.
Really?
They're so unbelievably quick.
The website bulletin board is exploding, and the reporters are going after us.
They'd better be unbelievably quick.
The dinner tonight is probably canceled. Right?
Of course! We don't want to get yelled at.
Hey! How about a drink afterward, just the two of us?
Who's picking up my Young Hoon, then?
Right. Carry on, then.
See you!
Oh Cheol, you came early.
Hello.
You still look hungover.
I didn't drink that much.
Did the announcement come out?
Yes, it's out.
[Announcements]
Okay, let's see.
Good morning!
Well, Chief Kim.
Yes, did you pull a list of people who are resigning? It's due today.
Yes, but that's not what I'm referring to...
[Lieutenant Kim Jin Hee]
[Conference room]
[Personnel on the waiting list for appointment]
Wow, this is driving me crazy.
[Civil Affairs, Lieutenant Kim Jin Hee]
Why should I be responsible for not responding to the special protection request?
I know the press is pressuring us,
but we can't be doing this!
You know better than anyone that I didn't benefit from nepotism!
I got the highest scores in the efficiency rating and tests.
That's why I reported him!
I didn't know what his father's occupation was, either.
Even if I did, the result would've been the same!
Are you dumb?
Don't you get it?
Why you reported him isn't the point right now!
I didn't do anything wrong!
Why should I be punished, then?
It's simple!
Because your job is to be demoted to satisfy the press!
Don't try to argue anymore.
What if I don't comply since it's an unjust demotion?
Should I get demoted, then?
Sir—
Wow!
I know you didn't do anything wrong.
But you won't be working here for just a year or two.
Suffer just for a year, Jin Hee.
Just for a year.
I mean...
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Should I find a place we can go to late at night?
Apparently, this isn't the place.
There's some detective,
and there's someone else,
but I apparently have to talk to a lawyer.
No, let's hang out some other time.
They said no. What am I supposed to do?
Compensation for losing my precious baby...
I'm about to lose all of it!
Grandmother.
- Grandmother?
- Yes?
Let me help you get free legal help.
Let's hang up for now.
Korea Legal Aid Corporation.
The phone number is 132.
Make an appointment over the phone before you go.
And at your local Community Service Center...
Who's helping whom right now?
You're the one who's in a dire situation.
I wasn't helping. I was just telling her what I knew.
Be quiet!
I saved you from working as a station employee.
You just can't shake your old habit.
I'm telling you this just in case. When you get transferred...
[Im Han Seong, Chief of Security Department]
Don't cause trouble, okay?
[Kim Jeong Min, Chief Accountant]
Don't act cheeky.
You'll be fine as long as you don't.
[Choi Jin Won, Chief of Equipment]
You're like a loose dog in a field.
[Lee Sang Joon, Director of Safety Living Division]
Let's be careful for everyone's peace of mind.
Won't you answer?
Yes, got it.
Please say something, sir!
Can we interview you?
Which department do you work for?
What are your colleagues' reactions toward the nepotism hire?
Do you know them by chance?
I heard the victim's request for special protection didn't go through...
Please say something!
The victim's request for special protection didn't go through...
Get out of here!
Everyone, get out!
You can't take photos. Move!
Move! Move!
Move along.
Get out, get out!
Come this way!
Bye now.
Who would've thought?
This late at night,
a daughter who was demoted from work
who was looking forward to drinking cold beer
would be facing an even greater disaster.
Mom!
Today, I... What?
You said you were coming home late.
Couldn't you call me beforehand?
Have you eaten?
Put some clothes on, at least!
Should we get fried chicken delivered?
Just forget it!
[Mom masturbation]
It's not like I'd get an answer like this.
Tae Gyeong, can I come to your neighborhood right now?
- Welcome!
- Hello!
- I'll have a beer!
- Okay!
Are you okay?
I know! What a joke, right?
They always stressed loyalty so much.
They're so stupid for cutting the tail off when they face a critical moment.
Let's face it. He's the one who put the seal of approval.
You had such a promising future. Why you?
Why did he have to use you like that?
It's okay! Curse them! It's okay!
They deserve to be cursed at!
- Tae Gyeong.
- Yeah.
Have you seen your mom masturbating?
What?
I saw something today that I had never even imagined.
She could just go out and meet a man.
Why does she have to masturbate at home at her age?
Thank you.
And after that, she said, "Should we get fried chicken?"
As if nothing happened.
Isn't it too weird?
I guess she's been acting weird lately.
- Let's go! Round 2! Round 2!
- Let's just go home.
What do you mean, Round 2? This is Round 5 right now!
Good god! I don't care! I'll go home!
Hey! Again?
You go home all the time!
I'm sick of it. I'm not going.
I'm going on a trip.
Don't try to find me.
Hey! You won't even ask where I'm going?
What a bitch.
Sexy.
Guess how many.
Geez! What's that?
♪ Lady, why are you so pretty? ♪
No, no, no. She's always been weird.
This isn't weird. It's...
What would you do if you were me?
Not sure.
Should I get her a vibrator?
She was using her hand.
- Hey!
- I'm sorry. So sorry! Are you okay?
You okay? You got all wet.
It's okay. You're pretty. It's okay.
- Hey, Jin Hee.
- Yes.
Keep your voice down, girl.
So did she go to the hospital?
Yes! She totally overreacted.
She could've beat us. How much could she have gotten hurt?
Geez, he drives like shit.
Hey, let's grab a complaint card when we get off.
Hey, you hit this lady.
I'm sorry.
Let's watch it. Okay?
Hey, let's get off.
What an annoying face.
Just because she hit you? What a bitch.
My mom had me when she was in high school.
Hey.
She was like the No. 1 bully's minion.
♫ I want to imagine my life without you ♫
She had a crush on her friend's brother one day.
She happened to have sex and got pregnant with me.
♫ Since I met you, I laughed because of you ♫
And that bastard transferred to a different school
and the girl was left alone. It's a common story.
♫ I think I want to get away ♫
♫ Don't want to play me, there's no use ♫
The blood sausage is so good!
The liver is better.
What are you saying? Blood sausage is the best.
Since then, I've always been her roommate.
Your younger brother is so cute.
Is that so?
Let's go, Brother.
She never had anyone else but me.
You can't be serious.
Why did you live like that?
What the!
What? Why didn't the alarm go off?
Why haven't you left?
Well...
I-I took the day off.
- All of a sudden?
- Yes.
It just worked out that way.
Hey, hey, hey! Should we hang out in the evening, then?
Let's get food and watch the movie we didn't get to watch.
I have a plan.
With whom?
It's someone you don't know.
Are you going out in the afternoon?
Why?
I wanted to start the washer before I went.
I want you to hang the laundry if you go out late.
Okay.
"Okay."
Seriously.
How strange. Why do my panties keep going missing?
Hey! Did you chew it up?
How strange.
My panties keep going missing.
Mom!
Mom, Mom, Mom! Hold on! Mom...
Did you take out my laundry from yesterday?
Did you do laundry yesterday?
You should've looked first!
Why are you taking it out? Just wash it again.
These are colored, and these are white!
Just wash it and use the lint remover!
You don't care about water and electricity bills, do you?
Forget it. I'll hang them. Go to work.
Come on! I'll do it!
- I said I'll do it!
- I'll do it...
Wait, sir!
Don't look at it and just hang it next to you.
We'll pick it up ourselves!
I'm sorry!
You can just get going, sir!
What's wrong with him?
He looks angry.
- You should go down.
- No, you go.
Why? It's not even my panty!
You go down.
Aigoo, I'm late again. I'm late all the time.
I'll be down there right now!
I'm sorry!
What am I doing so early in the morning?
Goodness, I'm sorry!
Sal—
Salute...
Hello, Sir.
You haven't changed.
Pardon?
I said you haven't changed.
Oh, I see...
Take care!
He can't work in this neighborhood...
You'll be transferred to the closest station to your home.
I'll do that much for you.
Hey! Who was that?
- Huh?
- Do you know him?
Talk later!
- You're saying that again!
- Hey, Tae Gyeong!
It's always later. Later when?
- Geez.
- Hello, good morning!
You said you live nearby. Why are you so late?
My back almost broke while waiting.
You were...
out of hazelnut coffee yesterday. Did you get more?
Of course!
Okay.
Why did you say "haezilnyuk"?
(Sunset in Korean)
Use more beans...
Why are you late if you live nearby?
It's not like you live far away.
The customers were here before you.
When is the director coming?
He'll come when he has an appointment.
So frustrating!
Go inside and call! Ask him when he's coming!
Yes.
Go inside, Unni!
We're here, we're here.
Please, not my neighborhood.
Yes, yes.
No. No. Right? No! Good!
She just doesn't look like a cop type.
Hey, why did you become a cop?
To protect my family and keep them safe.
Wow, seriously? How about the people?
Is it your hobby to insult the police academy?
No, sir!
The taxpayers pay for your training and salary. How dare you say that?
I'm sorry, sir!
Who taught you to answer like a robot?
From the seniors...
Are you serious right now?
It is.
I'm saying she...
only ignores my calls.
She answers everyone else's calls!
Gosh! What a meanie, bitch, and a fox! A nine-tailed fox!
There's one left.
No, I don't want it!
My shoulders are ruined from stress because of that bitch!
I know! That's why you need it.
Forget it! Forget it!
What a bitch.
It hurts, right? Endure a bit more.
Be gentle! Goodness, goodness!
So...
So that young man told me...
Huh?
Didn't you get enough sleep?
What did you do with your husband all night?
Huh?
[Park Sang Goo Orthopedic Clinic]
Was it Patient Kim Ji Young? She has severe back pain.
She said she'd come in today. Should we call her?
[Clean Hands]
Who bought this liquid soap in the bathroom?
I did order it.
I always compliment you. How could you do this?
You told me to get it.
When did I tell you to get liquid soap?
I told you to get a rectangular and solid one.
- The liquid soap...
- Who'd use that stuff? It's gross.
Pardon?
- Pardon?
- What did you just say?
What did I say?
I told you liquid soap runs out fast and wasteful.
I told you to get a rectangular and solid one.
I said that for a reason. Why would you do that...
Same with customer management.
Patients keep coming back if you just listen to them.
It's so important to have regulars in a small neighborhood.
You make them go elsewhere because you won't do that!
What will you do with this?
- Geez!
- Hello.
You came. How are you feeling?
It improved a lot.
I'll have a look in a bit.
Thank you.
Yes, yes. He, he, he...
Geez, that Park Sang Goo...
Anywhere but Woosook Patrol Division, please.
It wasn't easy for me to get you that position!
It's close to your house, too!
You just need to be there for a year. What's the issue?
So I'm asking you to reconsider it since you're already working on it.
I never asked you for any favor!
I always did you favors instead.
Are you serious right now?
There's another one in the neighborhood, too, but...
Which one?
But it's smaller than Woosook Patrol Division and—
It's okay!
Who cares how big it is? I'll be there for just a year, anyway!
You'll regret it.
Not at all!
Never.
What's wrong?
Huh? It's okay to break up...
as long as I can handle it?
You're basically an adultery consultant now.
You could comfort every cheater in the world!
Son of a bitch.
He said he's not impotent.
She couldn't even mention divorce and was frustrated.
Why couldn't he say something?
It was a side-effect of the hair loss pill.
He could've just been honest and quit.
What's the big deal?
So, when I heard what happened...
You have no worries at all.
He told his wife...
My head is about to explode. How come she's like this?
You can't sleep here like this, Ma'am.
But due to the social status of the wife...
I'm not going to.
Why should I care?
It hurts your pride.
They're so pitiful, aren't they?
What? What's wrong? What was that noise? What?
Jin Hee! Jin Hee! Jin Hee! What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do...
Let me see!
What do we do? Well...
Gosh, no!
We need to take it off!
- Don't move!
- I tried, I tried!
But my skin peeled off! It hurts...
Let me try! Let me try!
No! Don't touch me! Don't touch me!
It's because you're doing it yourself!
- It's okay if someone else does it—
- Don't touch!
- My gosh! Geez!
- Don't touch it!
It really hurts! What do I do?
What will you do now?
What do I do? It hurts...
Hold on.
I'm putting it on, okay?
Can you breathe?
How's that? Done.
Gosh, my face...
Hey.
Huh?
Does it feel good to ignore me?
What a bitch.
What's the big deal? Why would you ignore me?
Did I commit some grave sin?
Why don't you go date someone instead?
Instead of doing that at home.
No one wants me anymore.
You don't even know.
Why would you... Why would you say that?
You like doing it?
Why did you come home early when you said you'd be late?
You could've at least called!
How could I've imagined you'd be doing that?
Why can't you? Don't you masturbate?
You do, too!
I'm sorry, but I've never been caught like someone.
What's that face?
What?
Do you really think so?
Think what?
You've never been caught?
Oh, I see...
That's why you acted that way.
Wow, seriously.
Think about it.
You, you, you!
Mom.
Don't go in. Come here.
Let's talk here. Okay?
That's why you did that.
I hate hypocrites more than anything!
Mom? Mom!
Open the door. What are you talking about?
Don't taunt me like that!
[Daughter]
Keep calling. I'll never answer.
Hmph! Chi! Poong-poong! Whatever! Argh!
Okay, bing-bong.
Let's go watch a movie.
Who are you? Do you know me?
Let's go shopping, too.
My card is yours today.
I've never seen you before, but do excuse me.
♫ I want to be somebody special ♫
♫ I know it's too soon, but my heart is yours ♫
Meow! Meow! What is this for?
[For Couples / For Special Dates]
How do you use that?
- Like this?
- Oh!
♫ You're like a gift to me ♫
♫ Everything's about you, you're my only best friend ♫
[Sex Toys / For Couples / For Special Dates]
Would you like to try it? Yes!
Oh my god!
I like this color.
I'll look around.
♫ Somebody like you ♫
♫ It's nice and refreshing, tasty ♫
♫ I have you at the end of a hard day ♫
♫ Somebody like you ♫
♫ You're so dreamy, I need you ♫
♫ I need you, I need you ♫
♫ You need me, my everything ♫
I'm sorry.
About what?
I'm old and gray, yet I come here for a massage all the time
and run my mouth.
It's annoying, isn't it?
Not at all!
No one touches me like this because I'm old.
It doesn't feel like I'm living.
I get to talk when I come here, at least.
No one talks to me at home.
But you're a healer yourself.
Who touches you when you're in pain?
- Me?
- Yes.
I do it myself.
I see.
With the TV on.
TV?
Here we go!
Hey!
[Bulletin Board]
[Police]
"The police are with you."
"The police are warm and trustworthy."
Why did that guy have to throw up?
Hello!
I'm Lieutenant Kim Jin Hee, assigned as a team leader to Safety Patrol Team No. 2
of Namchon Police Station.
Nice to meet you!
Hello.
Here's your desk, Team Leader.
Oh, yes. Thank you.
Please go home if your shift is over.
Thank you.
- Good work.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
- Good work.
Thank you!
I'm Jang Soo Jin, the head of the management team.
Here are your team members of Safety Patrol Team No. 2.
Hello.
I look forward to working with you.
You need to figure out the work routine at the station in three days.
You'll start patrolling and your duty as the team leader afterward—
Hold on. By the way,
are there three people in Team No. 2?
Is there something wrong?
No, it seems we don't have enough team members.
Yes, two of them got fired.
They were transferred outside of Seoul.
Sir.
Captain!
Feel free to ask if you have any questions.
Do you have jurisdiction over the victim
who was denied special protection by chance?
Yes, that's right. It's our jurisdiction.
Were they transferred outside of Seoul because of that...
No.
It was about something entirely different.
Okay.
For not taking appropriate action for the child abuse case,
an officer from the HQ filed a report and sent an anonymous complaint, too.
She ended up stirring up Woosook Patrol Division, which had nothing to do with it.
She even stated their rank and name, too.
Lieutenant Kim Jin Hee.
- Lieutenant Kim Jin Hee?
- Yes?
Here's your ID.
Thank you.
Why are you blaming them? It's not even their jurisdiction.
You have to make a fuss so the person in charge hears about it and takes responsibility.
Should I just have done nothing?
Anywhere but Woosook Patrol Division, please.
But it's smaller than Woosook Patrol Division and—
It's okay!
Who cares how big it is? I'll be there for just a year, anyway!
You'll regret it.
Not at all!
Never!
[Kim Jin Hee, National Police Agency]
Yes, hello!
This is Chief Kim Jin Hee's mom. She won't answer her phone—
Is that so?
Okay.
Is she out of her mind? What does she think of me?
She was acting like a jobless loser for a reason!
Do you think I did it for no reason?
- I didn't just hit him for no reason!
- Hello.
- I had my own reason!
- Okay!
- Okay, okay.
- I'm telling you, we didn't start it!
Let's go in first!
That's enough!
[Tae Gyeong]
Hey, Tae Gyeong! I'll call you later—
You know, Senior Eun Jae Won.
You don't have to look into it. I'll call you later.
Hold on, didn't you say Namchon Police Station?
Senior apparently was sent there.
What the hell are you talking about?
Welcome, Chief!
Hey!
Sal...
Salute!
[Personnel Appointment: Namchon Police Station - Kim Jin Hee]
Do you want to say something to me?
I'll work...
I'll work hard, sir!
Okay, work hard?
How, exactly?
The police that's on the people's side.
The police that's warm and trustworthy...
That's not what I meant.
You know what you're good at.
What am I good at...
I'm good at most things.
You mean being defiant?
Gosh. We're finally talking.
You want me to be defiant while I'm here?
No.
If you do that with me,
you're dead meat.
Ignoring your superior's order and damaging my station's reputation,
or getting my teammates demoted dishonorably.
I'm telling you not to...
be defiant like that.
I'm sorry about the child abuse case, but it's not my fault—
My teammates didn't do anything wrong, either.
You changed a lot, Senior.
Yes, and you're still the same.
You're a naive junior who's only book-smart.
Let's keep it simple!
You'll be here just for a year, Team Leader Kim. Right?
Do you have anything else to say?
No.
Sir, let me make one for you.
No, no, it's okay!
- I wanted one, too.
- Oh, okay!
Anywhere but Woosook Patrol Division, please.
It's okay!
Who cares how big it is? I'll be there for just a year, anyway!
Not at all!
Never!
What? Why is it so dark in here?
Mom...
Do you want to see what I got?
I will... really...
I'll drink and die tonight.
I don't care about tomorrow.
Don't you have anything to tell me?
I do. I have tons.
You have no idea.
Hold on.
You'd better not omit anything.
Where should I start? Oh, wait.
Oh, this is how it started.
There was a commissioner's son at the HQ.
He was being considered for a promotion.
But why should I care if he's the commissioner's son or not?
- Hey.
- Hold on. I'm talking right now.
Do you think I'm a joke?
You think I'm dog shit, don't you?
Watch your language, please.
You think I'm a pushover because I always let it go?
I...
I'm the pushover. How are you a pushover?
What?
Think about it. I'm the pushover between us.
I do anything for you if you tell me to.
You've been so obedient to me?
You've been doing everything the way you wanted!
Forget it. Forget it.
I'm the dumbass for trying to talk to you.
This is your last chance.
Tell me!
Last chance, my foot.
[Epilogue]
♫ Your face is still sweet and friendly ♫
♫ Your discreet smile ♫
♫ Go ahead and keep trying to hide it ♫
♫ Hey, babe, I see everything ♫
♫ I'm so quick, I know everything ♫
♫ I was thinking of listening more, but I can't stand it ♫
♫ I'm crazy, yeah ♫
♫ Stand by, my eyes are focused ♫
♫ Your eyes will be on me, just wait a moment ♫
♫ Hey, look at me ♫
♫ Let's get it on and on, baby ♫
♫ Let's get it on ♫
♫ Your voice is driving me crazy ♫
♫ Please tell me ♫
♫ Say you love me ♫
♫ It's such a lovely night, baby ♫
♫ What a wonderful night ♫
♫ Before this night is gone, kiss me ♫
[Not Others]
♫ My heart was fluttering somehow ♫
♫ I was getting excited a little bit ♫
♫ Your smile feels unfamiliar ♫
♫ Go ahead and keep trying to hide it ♫
♫ Hey, babe, I see everything ♫
♫ I'm so quick, I know everything ♫
♫ Hey, look at me ♫
[Not Others]
Patrolling is a part of learning the job.
Plan the patrol training again.
I don't care who it is.
You thief bastard!
Just panties?
Are you sure only the underwear is missing?
What kind of constable is so young?
He's just being fined because it's a petty crime? How does that make sense?
You're dead. You son of a bitch.
Your hands are so strong.
Hold on, hold on!
You shouldn't have become a police officer.
I'll do my best to be defiant for a year.
I hope you look forward to it.
♫ Yeah, yeah, yeah, we're so crazy ♫