[Jeon Hye Jin]
[Choi Soo Young]
[Ahn Jae Wook]
[Park Sung Hoon]
[Not Others]
[This drama is fictitious. The characters, organizations, locales, incidents, and circumstances featured have no relevance to real life.]
Jin Hee.
Kim Jin Hee, should we order pizza?
Why won't she answer?
What are you doing that you're so quiet?
You were drawing...
Hey! Jin Hee...
This is expensive stuff.
I told you not to play with my makeup!
I don't have a red crayon. What am I supposed to do?
You didn't buy me one.
What?
Kim Jin Hee!
Hey, Kim Jin Hee. Why are you wearing long underwear?
Mom suddenly told me to get out.
Why?
I don't know. I guess she likes her makeup more than me.
Let's go play at the jungle gym.
[Episode 10. Crazy show]
It's snowing.
It is.
Senior.
Thank you.
There are still tons of things to do. And...
why would you? I didn't do it for you.
I'm just saying.
You did a good job, too.
Pardon?
Regarding Senior Cha.
You did a good job.
Yes.
You're home.
Jin Hee, you came.
Stay there, Oppa.
You said you'd come early. What took you so long?
You're here.
Do you want something to eat?
Just tell me. I'll make it for you.
It's okay.
Enjoy, then.
Go rest.
Hold on, hold on.
Success.
[Unnoticeable "Mini hearing aids" released]
[Why it's important to register your hearing aid]
What's going on? Why are you cooking so early?
Why did you wake up so early and...
Well... Uh...
I was going to leave before you guys woke up, but...
You woke up way earlier than I expected...
So you go to work around this time.
I-I'm sorry.
I didn't think it through before I got into this situation.
Well...
I'll leave right now.
Come out and get ready comfortably.
I'll get going.
Wake up.
What time is it?
I said wake up.
What?
Wake me up in an hour.
You're not supposed to bring a man over and sleep in this house.
Wasn't that our golden rule and promise?
So?
You're the one who wanted that rule because we live together.
That's what you taught me.
Okay, okay.
I'm sorry.
Happy?
Don't just try to let it slide.
He drank last night. What were we supposed to do?
Should I have let him drive drunk?
He could've hired a driver.
Because he was worried about me,
he ran to me with bare feet and
without even proper clothes on such a chilly day.
How was I supposed to just let him go?
Yes, I'm thankful for that, too.
But this isn't right.
Didn't you think I'd feel uncomfortable?
Okay.
I'm really sorry that you felt uncomfortable.
Hey.
How about Jin Soo, then?
What about him? Why bring him up?
He's not a man.
Not to you.
Why isn't he a man? Is he a woman, then?
Geez, you want to be this unreasonable?
He was actually just sleeping here.
But he wasn't just sleeping...
He wasn't just sleeping here! Gosh!
What else did he do, then?
We slept and...
Do you mean we did something?
Gosh, Mom!
Are you out of your mind?
Were we supposed to do something else?
I guess we could.
- I—
- Oh, yeah.
Come over here...
What else should we do other than just sleep?
Are you serious about our conversation right now or not?
I get what you mean...
You should've just gone home.
I don't mind taking a bus once in a while.
I could've taken a taxi, too.
It's okay. I kept the heater on.
Jin Hee is seriously flipping out.
I guess she was really surprised.
Why would she be so surprised?
She's not a kid.
Am I her daughter? I'm her mom.
She embarrassed me for no reason.
You didn't sleep comfortably, did you?
No, I slept comfortably.
And I understand why Jin Hee is doing that.
You don't have to worry so much.
It's just us, you know.
What are we exactly, then?
Huh?
What are we?
Well, we're not a family,
but we're not strangers, either.
It's kind of in between those things.
Are you angry?
No.
Why are you taking a joke so seriously, then?
Eun Mi.
Do you...
want to try living together?
I'd like to. With you and Jin Hee.
I don't want to.
I mean...
I know I asked her not to,
but we should at least have our boundaries.
If he just sleeps over like that...
How come no one cares about me feeling uncomfortable?
Seriously...
I didn't think he was like that. He has no manners.
Well... Uh...
Gosh, so embarrassing.
Team Leader, have some coffee.
I'll enjoy it. Thank you.
Sure.
Should we start the morning assembly?
Chief Eun isn't here yet.
He said he'd come later since he had a place to stop by.
A place to stop by?
Where?
Maybe he got summoned to the HQ again.
Again?
Why?
I'll get busy. I'll be away from the station a lot, too.
Fill in my spot for me.
Well, I'm sure he'll come when it's time.
Shall we get started first? Captain Jang.
Well, okay.
This is regarding the complaint we got yesterday.
Well...
Is this the same model as this?
Yes, it is.
This one.
If so, by chance...
can I access the information of a customer using this serial number?
Well, that's personal information. That'd be difficult.
Right.
I'm sorry.
Yes, got it.
[Signal H. Don't agonize over choosing a hearing aid!]
I need an official request for cooperation to release personal information.
- Hey, Jae Won.
- Hey.
I need your help with this.
What is it?
[No. 7]
Are you crazy? Why are you doing this suddenly—
Bye.
Hey, are you becoming dumb like Kim Jin Hee hanging around her?
Hey.
Both the manufacturer and National Health Insurance Service
said they can't release personal information because it's a sensitive matter.
Same with the credit card receipt.
That means we need a warrant, after all.
At least an official request for cooperation.
What were you doing that you're so awkwardly taken aback?
Pardon? Why do you say that?
I got some snacks. Have some.
Yes, we should. Sounds tasty.
You don't even know what it is.
Ttteobokki? Donuts? Hotteok? Hot dogs?
Or bungeoppang?
It is Ms. Lee Na Kyeong's lip balm.
The person the suspect saw in the park might be the culprit.
We don't know for sure yet.
As you said, it might've been either stolen or lost.
What was the hearing aid company called? I wanted to go there.
Do you have a guy you know at the hearing aid company, too?
Or a younger friend?
- Why do you ask?
- It seems like you've led a very proper life.
Everyone volunteers to help if you just mention something.
Was it more than just mentioning something?
Did you threaten?
I need to look for a CCTV, too.
I can do that.
You can count on me.
- Thank you in advance.
- Sure.
Something must be really going on. Right?
Definitely.
They suddenly spend time together
or have private conversations often.
They can't be...
...having an office romance. Right?
No.
Wow, seriously...
I hope they aren't doing something to upset the HQ.
What is the current gossip?
Do you remember Lee Maeng Jin? She quit.
Are you asking because you know Sook Hyeon's pregnant?
A long-distance dad cheated. Guess who?
The park murder suspect changed his testimony.
What about the thing I asked?
Let me ask you something first.
Will you return to the HQ?
Of course.
You're considering coming back, then?
Will my answer change what you'd tell me?
If you are going to come back, create a withdrawal route before you fight.
Don't do anything you'd be held accountable for.
But it has to do with my mom.
Who else should be held accountable other than me?
There's Senior Eun Jae Won.
-Im Tae Gyeong.
- I don't care what you say about me.
I care about you more than Senior Eun.
Wouldn't you feel the same way?
That's why I need to do it properly.
What?
I'll catch the right culprit so no one can be held accountable.
Jin Hee, why are you taking it this far?
If what he said is true,
an innocent person is locked up and the real culprit is out there.
Isn't that good enough?
What sin did I commit in my previous life that I have a nutty friend like you? My gosh!
Hey, don't get the wrong idea. I'm only giving this to you because of Ahjumma.
I don't want you to blame me later because there's an actual culprit out there.
I came up with some other excuse to get this for you.
If anything goes wrong, I'll deny it altogether.
You'd better do this on your own.
Thank you, Tae Gyeong. Thank you so much.
They're videos from CCTVs in the park, the surrounding area, and dashcams at the time of the murder.
How many hours are on these?
- Ten days worth.
- So I need to watch 10 videos that are 24 hours long?
Multiply that by 48.
Help me just once. I beg you, Senior.
I'm looking out for you.
I'm refusing for you, not for myself.
We had a party for catching the culprit,
and we even split the bonus, but you want to ruin it all.
Let's say there's actually a real culprit.
Whether you catch him or not, it comes down to
the fact that if they find out you've been doing this,
you'll be done for.
It'll be game over.
[Park Sang Goo Orthopedic Clinic]
Ms. Kim.
Didn't Ms. Kim Mi Jeong have a morning appointment today?
Is that so?
Yes, she did.
I guess she did.
You're her friend. How could you be so uninterested?
I suppose you're very busy.
Yes, I'll be seeing countless patients right now, too.
Is Dr. Park doing well?
Why do you ask me that?
I know.
You two don't know each other.
I wonder why I asked.
Send me a list of the afternoon appointments.
Yes, I'll send it right away.
I wonder why I asked.
That creepy old man.
Ms. Kim, we're having dinner tonight.
You're going straight home again. Right?
In the black car with the license number 3512?
- Did you see it?
- A few times... Probably more than that.
I see it on the way to work sometimes, but I always see it when we get off work.
How come I'm the only one who didn't know? Who is it?
We don't know because we've never seen his face.
I wonder if he'll come secretly again.
Hey, I'll come to the dinner.
I need to have a social life, too.
- Whoa!
- Are we binge drinking like the old days?
Really? You're treating us tonight, then.
Sounds good.
Ms. Jo Woo Yeon, you can go in.
Don't come today. There's a work dinner tonight.
Team Leader.
- Yes.
- You have a visitor.
What visitor?
Is it someone from the HQ, by chance?
Jin Hee.
Hello.
I heard you know I'm your paternal aunt.
I couldn't just sit back after hearing that.
You must've been surprised.
No. I'm the one who didn't say hello properly.
Don't be silly.
You're in this situation because of us. It's not your fault.
I know it's rude to show up at your work,
but I don't know your address or phone number.
So for that reason...
could you give me your phone number?
Of course. You must feel uncomfortable.
I'd feel uncomfortable, too.
It's okay. Let's just be casual.
You know...
Last time, you said you couldn't accept pocket money because I'm not family. Right?
But I'm your aunt now.
It's okay to get pocket money from family. Right?
No, I—
Gosh, just take it.
That'd make me feel better.
Get something tasty, pretty clothes,
and get your hair done, too.
- Well...
- Goodness.
No, no. Go back in.
Let's have a meal next time. I'm not just saying it.
Go inside.
[Namchon Police]
Go in.
What...
Enjoy.
- Let me pour you a glass.
- Thank you.
Me, too.
Yes.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
- Thanks for the meal.
- Let me get it for you.
So cool. He's so cool.
Get more if it's not enough. Help yourselves.
- Yes, thank you.
- Thank you for the meal.
- Should we raise glasses?
- Sounds good.
- Nice to meet you.
It's a shame that Dr. Park isn't here.
Thanks for the meal.
It melts in your mouth. It's so tasty.
I told you to just drop me off there.
Gosh. Walk slowly.
We're almost on the third floor.
It looked like everyone at the hospital knew.
I told you not to come. Why did you?
Is that a habit, too?
Just like how you drink tea and work out in the morning?
I missed you.
This is no good, Oppa. Hurry up and get a job.
You're such a typical unemployed person.
You're home all day thinking about me. Right?
Eun Mi, by chance, is it because of Jin Hee?
The reason you said no?
Oppa, even if we make a decision and change certain things,
it's between you and me.
I told you before, but stop getting Jin Hee involved.
It has nothing to do with her.
That's how Jin Hee and I've been living.
That won't change because of you, either.
Well, what am I supposed to...
Mom, pack your things.
Where am I supposed to go?
Ahjussi's place.
Of course, I know you mean his place.
Why would I go to his place when I have my own home?
I told you. I won't be home because I'm busy.
I can be on my own.
How could you be on your own?
You need someone to be your underling.
What? Underling?
I-I can do that for you.
What do you mean, you can?
Jin Hee, Mom hates it so much.
What if I just come here—
- No way.
- I don't want that.
Why not?
Because of our promise.
We're not supposed to sleep with a man in this house.
I already broke it. What do you want me to do?
You live in this house with me.
Can't you keep our boundaries even when I'm not around?
Gosh, just the thought of it—
Why would you think about that?
Don't think about it.
Yes, Jin Hee.
I was wrong.
I'll take her to my place immediately.
Eun Mi, let's pack your bag.
I mean, why do I have to leave my home
and stay at someone else's? So uncomfortable.
Wow, you're so selfish.
You don't want to be uncomfortable, but you don't care about my discomfort?
You said you wouldn't be home.
How would I understand your discomfort at home, then?
Well, even if you can't understand, just do it if I ask you to.
You're hiding something. What is it?
What are you plotting to do by making me leave?
What are you talking about? What would I plot, exactly?
Whatever you do, don't do it here and do it at his place. That's what I'm saying.
Was that it?
You think I refused to live with him because of you?
No.
Like you said, why should I care who you live with?
Listen to you.
Hey, why does that not concern you?
You just said so. You said it doesn't concern me.
Well, it doesn't concern you, but it does.
Why? Because it's you.
See? You don't even know what you're saying.
I don't know. Whatever. Just go pack your stuff.
Okay. I'll just pack my stuff.
I will because I can't stand this.
I will.
Jin Hee, your mom and I will be okay.
I'm counting on you.
What? What is it?
What are you doing?
Why are you taking that? Mom.
What's this now?
Why are you being unreasonable now?
Not those. Mom.
You can't take those. I...
Take these instead.
Not these ones. Mom.
I had to wait to get these.
Oppa, I'll use the bed.
How nice.
Do you want a beer or something?
I'll make you drinking snacks.
Deal.
Hey. Let's go in.
There are five hearing-impaired ex-convicts
in their 20s and 30s in the area.
Did you meet with them?
I met two because I didn't have enough time.
They both have clear alibis.
There wasn't anything notable, either.
How about the fingerprint you found?
I'll be meeting Jong Wan tomorrow morning.
I'll look around using that.
What a relief.
Please say hello to Senior Jong Wan for me.
You should at least sleep an hour if you're tired.
We need to stay up all night anyway.
Please wake me up in an hour.
I can't get up if the bed is too comfortable.
Don't worry. I'll make sure to wake you up.
CCTV covers up to there
and he disappeared around here.
Where did he go, anyway?
So she headed to the park afterward?
Yes, it was where the park murder happened, but I didn't notice anything.
We couldn't tell exactly what she was looking for.
- Welcome back.
- Hello.
Welcome back.
Thank you, Team Leader Kim.
Let's talk for a moment.
What is this?
I think you have some explaining to do.
Why didn't you tell us your mother has something to do with the park murder?
So you think the real culprit is out there. Right?
That's why you think your mother is in danger.
Of course, Chief Eun knows about it.
You requested a visit to the jail because of that. Right?
You two were summoned to the HQ because of that, too.
What about us?
Do you guys even consider us as your teammates?
This is...
It's better for you not to know about this for now.
Once things get sorted out—
I'm so disappointed.
I thought we were a team.
Were we mistaken?
It's because it has to do with my mom.
Because of my personal matter—
How is this your personal matter?
That's right. It's our job.
Why are you all doing this?
Do you want the HQ to keep tabs on all of us?
Whatever.
Show us the documents you've been collecting in secret with Chief Eun.
Captain Cha.
That way, we can provide you with what we've been collecting.
What have you been collecting...
Are you crazy?
Ms. Lee Na Kyeong's daily routes and credit card records.
I got it from my classmates.
We analyzed the footage you got from the HQ, too.
Well, what... When did you take those...
Are you saying you did all that work?
That's why you should've told us sooner
instead of struggling between you two.
L-Let me see. What did you do?
Come on, you have to follow the order.
Show us what you and Chief Eun found first.
Chief Eun.
What's this?
Do you live together?
You even changed the passcode, too?
Why did you see my daughter?
Even Oppa doesn't do that without my approval.
You're so strange.
You should celebrate that she has a dad and aunt now. Why be so angry?
Jin Hee and I've been doing fine, just the two of us. What for?
It's because you're not used to it.
Live without a family if you don't want it.
Why would you force that on Jin Hee, too?
What do you mean I don't have a family?
I have a family.
A real, proper family.
Jin Hee was loved by them plenty growing up, too.
You don't share a drop of blood. How's that family?
Does sharing blood make you family?
You and your husband were strangers once, too.
And is it okay to be so rude if you're family?
I see. That's why your parents treat Oppa like this.
You think you can just say whatever?
What do they have to do with this?
Ji Eun! That's enough. Let's go.
And I told you to call before you come.
Why are you so afraid of her all the time?
She's your daughter. Why do you need her permission?
Why is Jin Hee my daughter?
She's Eun Mi's daughter.
She's Eun Mi's daughter, whom she raised by herself.
And why are you acting out when I'm fine with it?
Gosh. You fool.
Does she not have your blood just because you deny it?
If I were strangers to them for 30 years,
you can't be entitled just because you share blood.
When did I act entitled?
Ji Eun.
I'm so happy right now.
I can't ask for more.
Gosh, it's so frustrating. So frustrating.
I'm curious as to what's inside your head.
On the night of the incident, there was a man who was following the victim.
He was spotted in front of the victim's house.
It was confirmed that he went to the park,
but he disappeared with the victim here.
But he hasn't shown up since then.
Meaning he was seen entering but not when he exited.
So we checked the CCTVs at the shops and dashcams in the area.
And this is...
where he was filmed walking downtown by a dashcam of a parked car.
He was filmed?
Did you find him, then?
Yes.
That means he exited the park through a small path.
That's why we looked into it.
It turns out there was a small path.
It's assumed that he exited through here.
So we kept tracking him.
Do you know where he was last seen is connected to?
Where?
The alley with the security light where Team Leader's mom rescued Ms. Lee.
Here.
Wow.
Could you look for more footage?
There's a man the suspect saw at night a few days after the incident.
The culprit always returns to the scene.
You think that's the real culprit?
No, we don't know that yet.
On the contrary, that man was seen leaving the park,
but not when he entered.
How creepy.
I'll look into it further.
Are you sure there's a real culprit in the park murder out there?
Answer me, you bastard.
We're about to enter hell together. I could use reassurance.
Yes, I believe so.
Have you seen a suspicious man in a baseball cap, by chance?
Sir, sir. Excuse me.
Have you seen a suspicious man in a baseball cap,
a hoodie recently, by chance?
I don't think I have.
Yes, got it.
Captain Jang.
I think we need to check this.
This overlapped with the other one.
- Really? I removed the ones that overlapped.
- Really?
Let's have a coffee break, everyone.
Wow, thank you.
Eun Mi.
[Jin Hong]
Ahjumma.
Oh, it's you again.
- Yes.
- You must live around here. I see you often.
Yes, see you next time. Take care.
Okay, see you later.
Oh, right.
I saw Ga Eul walking by.
Ga Eul?
She didn't look so well.
Something she couldn't talk to a man about. You know what I mean?
Where is she?
I saw her deeper inside the alley.
Hello?
We found that man.
You found him? Where?
At the convenience store.
He wasn't just captured passing by.
He stopped by the store and went to the park.
He was captured by a dashcam nearby.
It matches the time the suspect
in jail saw him, too.
But you know what's interesting?
Is there something else?
The place...
where he disappeared last after leaving the park.
Is it the alley with the security light, by chance?
- That's right.
- Yes.
Three people made purchases around that time.
There were two women and one man.
There he is.
Yes, thank you.
[Castle Rock Internet Cafe]
Here you are.
Captain Jang and Officer Jo, please guard the back.
Hello.
Where's the part-timer?
Is something wrong?
He suddenly disappeared. So I was calling him, too. Just a moment.
No one manages a large shop space like he does.
He's nice, attentive, and good with customers.
I even bought him a hearing aid to keep him around.
But why isn't he answering his phone?
Whose cigarettes are they?
They're the part-timer's.
Excuse me.
Whose bag is this?
That's also the part-timer's.
How long has he been gone?
About 20 minutes... No, it's been less than 20 minutes.
[Jin Hee, I can't reach Eun Mi!]
- Jin Hee.
- Ahjussi.
Since when did she not answer your call?
That's when I talked to her last. Hold on.
I got a text message and...
What did she say?
She said something had happened to Ga Eul, and she needed to help her.
Where should I go?
Did she say she's with someone else?
She told me not to worry because she was with someone she knew.
Mom!
Eun Mi!
Hey, is this the right place?
Are you sure?
What are you doing?
Namchon Team 3. Namchon Team 3. We're on our way to assist Team 2.
I've been wanting to kill you so badly.
I finally get to do it.
Thank you, Ahjumma.
If you really want to kill me...
Okay. Kill me. Do it.
I'll die, then.
But at least tell me the reason.
Why me?
You could've just walked by quietly.
Why did you rescue her, anyway?
Do you know how much I suffered because I lost her then?
Well, she ended up dying, anyway.
You son of a bitch!
You!
Son of a bitch!
2 o'clock direction from the intersection.
Seven minutes ago. In front of Jangmi Villa, 19-2, Namchon-dong.
Heading toward 10 o'clock in front of Jangmi Villa.
Mom!
Eun Mi!
It's him!
Stop right there!
Where's my mom? Huh?
Where's my mom?
Eun Mi!
You have the right to remain silent. You have a right to an attorney...
Mom!
Mom.
Mom, are you okay?
What took you so long?
I'm sorry. I didn't know you were here.
Are you okay? Can you get up?
Let's go home now.
Jin Hee, please call the ambulance.
Pardon?
Hello? Someone got injured. We're at...
What the heck! Mom.
Ahjussi, what's going on?
Ahjussi, what's going on? Mom.
Mom.
No, Mom. Mom!
Mom!
♫ The grass is swaying in the breeze ♫
[Operating Center]
♫ A little kid is whistling while standing in the field ♫
♫ The wind carries the sound ♫
♫ It sings to the ears of the birds in the sky ♫
You won't leave?
I said get out, bitch!
Get out! Get out, bitch! Get out!
Let's go to my place.
♫ All over the world ♫
You guys aren't my daughters.
Look at you.
♫ The light pink skirt whirls around in the spring breeze ♫
♫ Once again today, the one who took my jacket ribbon ♫
You're just like me.
Do you know how scared I was whenever you cried?
Because I might abandon you?
♫ Riding the wind, I'm dancing with the spring scent ♫
What?
Gosh...
♫ I'm calling spring ♫
♫ I'm singing to the whole world ♫
Jin Hee!
Where did you go?
Jin Hee! Jin Hee! Jin Hee.
Eun Mi, were you looking for her?
She was playing with Jin Soo. I feel so terrible.
Where were you?
♫ It echoes in the cherry blossoms ♫
Stop crying, Mom.
Are you sad? Being sad makes you look ugly.
♫ In the white sky, I'm picturing spring ♫
♫ Dancing to the sound of the whistle ♫
♫ I'm calling spring in the wind ♫
♫ I try running through it ♫
[Not Others]
My proud teammates got special promotions.
If you get a chance to return to the HQ, leave without looking back.
I should be doing that. I have nothing to do.
Father, how did you know I was here?
I should look into it properly if she's my bloodline.
You didn't expect this would happen when they showed up?
Get out. You don't even know how I feel. How dare you...
I'll do it to prove it for my mom. Give me your hair, Grandpa.
Looks like you never thought I wouldn't marry Jin Hong.
It's fun to watch you.
The way you talk, smile, run...
Do you like me, Senior?