I still miss you
The rainbow falls
The past is hard to forget
Tears fall
And turn into a bitter sea
Fate falls
Love is buried
Love and hate are inextricable
Follow me
Let go
Go away
I won't let go
It's not me
Because you're not me
Old man
You know your own girl's temper
Can I stop her?
And one more thing
I dare not say
Just that Chuan Chuan
I almost killed your girl
What did you say
How do you talk, Gu Bei Xin
Annoy her
You talk too much
My dad, dad, dad
She's talking nonsense
There's no such thing
Don't talk about me first
Talk about you
What's wrong with you
I asked Lu Yan to investigate that missing case
How did you get into it
What missing case
It's Ling Chong's crime
You know Ling Chong
I know it
Ling Chong is still bothering me
Master Yu
Peng Dahai is now identified by Director Bai
The murderer of the missing case
Now locked in the police station
I hope you can
Tell me everything you know
Give Peng Dahai a clear picture
I'll tell my daughter
Go out
Dad
We have to save Dahai
You
Wait
Nothing
Then I'll go out first
No, Lu Yan
Don't be angry
No, Old Yu, he's like this
I'll find you later
Come on, come on, come on
Don't put it in your heart
Not old Yu
You said you were a grown man
Still so willful
Sit down
Let me tell you
Three months ago
The spirit tribe came to me for help
Said someone was lost
At first I didn't care
Then I found out
Ghost city
And the disappearance of Yingdu
More and more
How many people
Less than a hundred people
One day I found out
By Ling Chong
Spirit tribe that was swallowed up
At that time his body
Very fragile
Almost transparent body
I tried my best to learn
I couldn't stop him from being out of energy
There is something in your body
In the West is your energy
I can't help you
Sorry
Ghost
Ghost city
Chang...Changle restaurant
Chang...Changle
I found out
These missing cases
Not kidnapping
But by Ling Chong
The spirit tribe that was swallowed up
So you went to the restaurant to find out
I found out after I went
My spirits
It was sold by the boss of Changle Restaurant
But with his ability
Absolutely not equipped
The ability to feed this bug
So after the purchase method of Mo Qing
I just like to eat mung beans
Go
Husband, have some tea
Is there wine?
Sir, you must be joking.
There is no wine in this tavern.
How can it be called a tavern?
High-quality wine, millet wine,
from the farm to the farm,
you can order whatever you want.
I want the wine from the grass,
not the grass, not the wine.
Go, go, go.
Sir,
people will get drunk with this wine.
It's only sold to the spiritual clan,
not to people.
This is the rule.
Mr. Tian,
it's getting late,
it's time to close.
You can go.
How much do you want?
50.
Five.
Okay.
Okay, sir.
You can walk around,
wait for me to get the goods.
I'll come back in an hour.
I know he doesn't have
so much spiritual graces.
He must go to the Shang family
to get the goods.
So after I came out,
I was staring at him.
The time is up.
Be careful of the fire.
It's been a long time.
The time is up.
Please keep it in mind.
I'll come back.
Bye.
Come again.
I'll go.
Okay.
The light is still on even when the door is closed.
It must be their street code.
It's possible.
It's autumn.
There are so many mosquitoes.
It's itchy.
What's wrong?
On the left,
it's itchy all over.
It has nothing to do with mosquitoes.
It's time to take a bath.
My scalp.
Are you feeling better?
What happened after that?
Who is that man?
Not a lady.
Pearl Effect.
Anything's possible.
Come.
I've agreed.
Anyone?
Ilsipo.
Someone?
Who?
Kimao!
Don't run!
One of them ran away.
I'll go and find him.
Another one.
Do you think I'm jealous?
I think you're right.
That's the way it is.
It's the man in the windbreaker.
It's very likely that
the windbreaker he wears
is the same as the one Lu Yan wore.
He said I was the murderer.
I said he was the murderer.
Dad, don't talk nonsense.
Lu Yan wouldn't do that.
I believe him.
You take a shower first.
I'll go and ask him.
Don't fall for that trickster.
Women are really not allowed to stay.
It's itchy again.
Left, left, left.
Right, right, right.
You should wash it.
Wash it.
Lu Yan.
Are you okay?
Don't be angry.
My dad is a very bad person.
He's actually a good person.
Don't take it to heart.
Let me tell you.
It's okay.
I heard what you said.
Come on, look at this first.
Account book.
I think there are more than one seller.
The old owner said
according to his investigation over the past three months,
there are less than a hundred missing people.
But there are only a dozen of trading information in this account book.
So I think there are other shops in the ghost city
selling spirits.
But there are so many shops in the ghost city.
It's also a big deal to find it like this.
Lighting.
That's right.
If the light is their street sign,
then tonight...
Then tonight we'll go to the ghost city to find a high place.
When you look at the shop at the time of the purple stone,
turn off the light and hang up the lantern.
We can find the upper shelf and clear the sea.
Then we'll set off tonight.
Old fish, you haven't recovered yet.
You can't eat so oily.
Don't eat it.
Come on, have a bowl of porridge.
You're obedient.
What's going on?
If two more pieces of beef and a basket of buns,
you'll recover faster.
Do you need another pot of old Indian food?
That's great.
Chang Yan said there's no wine without meat.
No meat for dogs.
You're serious.
Beixi said you had something to do with me.
Just this?
Let's talk about it later.
I have to go to the case.
I'll bring you some wine.
Wait.
Let me ask you.
How did you know that guy named Lu?
I...
I married him.
I've already married Tang.
He's the legitimate son-in-law of our Qingquan Village.
You're married.
Why are you so beautiful?
Do you know that you're married to a murderer?
What murderer? Who killed him?
Did he want to kill you?
Old fish, don't worry.
Look at me.
I'm fine in front of you.
I'm fine.
I told you.
He said I had a yuan-pellet in my body.
He wanted to kill me to get the money.
Then he said I was a saintess.
He protected me all day.
What saintess?
You're my daughter.
What nonsense are you talking about?
You're so...
Now that it's come to this,
don't hide it from me.
I have something to ask you.
Go ahead.
Am I your daughter?
Of course.
Your mother was pregnant in October.
Your father worked so hard to raise you.
Why isn't he?
Don't listen to him.
What is this?
It's a
treasure.
You're a hunter.
You must know the yuan-pellet of the forest tribe.
Daughter,
this is the kid named Lu who gave it to you.
What you said is true.
I'm from the forest tribe.
Wait.
Now that you've grown up,
I'll tell you everything that happened.
That year...
You and I met
on the edge of the mountain.
We saw you alone on the edge of the mountain.
We took you home
and took care of your mother and I.
So we decided to adopt you.
Since then,
you've been in my arms
and cried when I was gone.
You were happy when I hugged you
and you smiled when I hugged you.
You ate a lot.
I've been hiding it from you
for so many years.
I just wanted...
I just wanted you to be safe.
You can grow up
and be a good family.
I was just saying.
Why am I stronger than others
and more capable than others?
You always say that I'm a hungry, stupid, and wronged child.
Now,
you're strong.
You don't recognize your father anymore.
Who says I don't recognize my father?
Old Yu, don't worry.
No matter what kind of spiritual blessing he is,
or what kind of saint you are,
I'll always be your daughter.
I'll eat you up.
I'll be your wife.
I'll be your brother.
I'll be your sister.
I'll be your mother.
I'll be your father.
Okay, I've made myself clear.
I should go.
I have to go investigate the case.
Daughter,
why don't you let Xing Lu go?
Why are you going?
No way.
He's the second son I married.
He's so handsome.
What if someone kidnaps him?
I have to take him back to Qingquan Village.
Besides,
Peng Dahai is my apprentice.
I have to go save him myself.
Don't worry, Old Yu.
I promised them
that I would save Xiao Yitai.
Didn't you teach me before?
It's hard to pass the test.
I'm leaving.
Go ahead.
Come back soon.
Okay.
Don't be as willful as last time
when you go to the ghost market.
Don't worry.
I'll listen to you this time.
Daqian?
Am I right?
Why is it Daqian?
Daqian.
Let's get ready.
Tell me more about
the weapons and equipment
you found about Bai's Mansion.
40 for the
80 for the
100 for the
300 for the
exponent şöyle
yours is
100 is
100.
Hold on.
He's not a bad guy.
Maybe he can get it wrong.
Right.
Stop it.
Learn from him.
Remember.
Don't always think of
using your brain.
Use your brain.
Understand?
Put on the suit I sewed myself.
Okay.
Be more precise.
Look.
This is good.
This is called brain.
What's this?
I made it myself.
You should be more careful.
You're too careless.
Right.
Sometimes I even want to
cut my own hair.
I'm so talented.
So talented.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
Go.
Brother.
Wait.
Chief.
Why didn't you go in and save you?
Why did you come out?
Right.
Why are you all here?
We're here to save you.
Right.
You didn't send a message to India.
I heard that you were wanted.
Right.
You were wanted in Baifu.
We're here to save you.
I'm fine.
And I'm looking for my father.
Chief.
Where is he?
He's in Baifu now.
But I can't make it clear.
Well.
Father.
Go to Baifu first.
Find someone to report to Gu Beixi.
He's great now.
He's the future son-in-law of Baifu.
He's very handsome.
Really?
The rest of you go back to the village first.
Wait for me to get the money.
Okay.
Don't let me go back.
I'll let you do what you want.
Don't talk so much.
Okay.
You're so disobedient.
We should go now.
Okay.
I have something important to do.
I'll go first.
Be careful, girl.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Chief.
Be careful.
Take care.
Chief.
Be careful.
Don't shout.
What are you shouting?
Don't stand here.
You'll cry.
Go.
Why are you here?
Go back.
Go.
Hurry.
This way.
Go.
Xin.
Has the lantern lit up?
Not yet.
I'm watching.
Our guess
shouldn't be wrong.
Let's wait a little longer.
Xin.
Come back and sit down.
Okay.
Sir.
Master.
Yes?
You two are a perfect match.
I like that.
Tell me more.
Look.
Master is
a gentleman.
a gentle man.
Don't look at his personality.
What are you doing?
Let him say.
Xin.
Three guests.
Sorry.
We're really going to close.
Didn't you say
money can make ghosts go away?
It's the same everywhere.
Let's have another good glass of white wine.
Sir.
We can't.
We've cleaned up here.
We're really leaving.
We'll...
Wait.
Let's go.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Don't be careless.
Maybe it's Yirong.
This bug.
It's not a bug.
It's a bug.
This bug is too cunning.
He used a kid
to do this kind of bad business.
The silver is more valuable than the world.
The deal of this bug
has caused half of the city
to be in a panic.
The only thing that can't be sure
is to light the lamp.
This drug store
is still the place
with the most people.
It even involves the kid.
I feel
this is not a way
he can come up with alone.
After we catch him,
we'll ask him again.
Yes.
I want to see
what they're up to.
In the wild,
we go to the jungle.
The fairy goes to the sky.
If you want to be a fairy,
you can go.
Let the beauty go.
Let's go.
They're still here.
Get ready.
Go.
Where are you going?
How dare you trick me?
Sir.
Where's Lu Yan?
I'm here.
It hurts.
Can you fall down?
Yes.
Was I on organizations?
Your clinic has been dry for a long time.
What did you sell earlier?
Pharm L Vikram medicine.
It's natural.
I can spare your life if you tell me the truth
I... I don't know what you're talking about
You... you are oppressing the people
Is there any law?
You're selling the poison of the dead
You ran away because you're afraid of the ghost
How about this?
We'll tie him up and interrogate him
Sir, Mistress
How about we go back and have a look?
Maybe Lin Chong is still in the pharmacy
It makes sense
Let's go
Come back here
Help!
Sir, let's save him
No need
Take him back to the White House
Help!
Shiqing, it's your birthday today
And your father's case is almost solved
Today is a good day
How about we set up your marriage with Gu Beixi?
No, Dad
It's not urgent
Not urgent
What?
Not urgent?
I heard that Gu Beixi
was always with the people in Xi Yuan
I don't know what he's thinking
Did he leave you alone?
You're unhappy
So you don't want to marry him
I'll call him here
and beat him up
Dad
I'll tell you the truth
Gu Beixi
He has someone in his heart
You're so blind and ignorant
Gu Beixi
You first
I'll go first
Shiqing
We've been engaged since we were kids
But Dengdeng and I grew up together
He's been in my heart for too long
I can't pretend to be someone else
I'm sorry
I've told your father about the marriage
Thank you for helping me
You don't have to thank me
And you have nothing to do with me
You're just like me
You're just struggling in an endless relationship
And I think
it's good to have someone in your heart
I'll leave Bai's Mansion tomorrow
Forget me
and start a new life
What if I can't forget you?
How can you?
You're a rich lady
and I'm a rough man
Time goes by and you'll forget me
Take care
Thank you
Please
Today please
Congratulations
Brother Liu.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
Don't move.
Stay still.
Take him down.
Please come in.
Okay.
Thank you, Director Bai.
Don't move.
Thank you.
Go in first.
Congratulations.
Behave yourself.
No.
Director Bai.
You're a hero.
I'm here
for your birthday party.
All the guests are here.
What do you mean?
What's wrong with you?
A Xin.
What...
What species is it?
It's a chrysanthemum.
We found that
it's related to the business of insects.
It must be related to
the disappearance of the population.
Interesting.
A rabbit is not a rabbit.
A donkey is not a donkey.
It's a good mouth.
Don't move.
I admire you.
You've done a great job this time.
Isn't it, Director Bai?
Today is Miss Bai's birthday party.
And you solved the case.
This is
a good thing for you
to put a peony on the phoenix's head.
Well,
my apprentice, Peng Dahai,
is he...
Let him go.
Don't be so anxious.
Look at this.
Evidence.
Where's the testimony?
You've caught him.
Are you afraid of losing the testimony?
Well,
you caught him.
He pulled you on the street.
I don't believe you.
I'm the one who's empty-handed.
The director is also in there.
I reported to him and he asked.
I was right.
Is it a joke?
Of course it's not.
Since this Chahe is a criminal,
if we want him to speak,
we must interrogate him.
The reason we brought him to Bai's Mansion
is to ask him
to provide us with a place to interrogate.
So we can
know the whole case.
That's right.
Director Bai,
you've been worrying for days.
Finally, you found a witness.
You must ask him.
We caught him.
It's easier to ask.
Don't worry.
We'll try to
send you the witness
and evidence before the birthday party.
You'll be able to
face the guests
in person.
I see.
We're just looking for a place
to interrogate the criminal.
Bai's Mansion is a big place.
You can pick and interrogate him.
And your apprentice, Dahai,
I'll bring him out of the prison
right now
to treat him well.
Don't worry.
As long as you get the evidence,
the director will be over the old man.
And you can put the criminal
on the cart safely.
I'll give you
your apprentice.
Director Bai,
you're
on the right track.
Director Bai.
I'm always on the right track.
We're just looking for...
Director Bai,
the guests are almost here.
The director is sitting down, too.
He's waiting for you to host the party.
Hero.
I'll go over there.
I'll listen to your hero later.
He can do whatever he wants.
Okay?
Okay, director.
See you.
Old Yang.
Is responds correctly.
Zero!
For the last 2 days,
the treasures never came in handy.
That's a shame.
But now I'm Но- people like you
just scoff at you.
Speak out!
Who really
gave the slaughter лет theécофilx the blame?
Erm…
What fish and wideners?
You're still being stubborn, aren't you?
Fine.
I'd like to see
if you're being stubborn
or I'm a whip with chili water.
Say it or not?
Say it!
I'm just
running a pharmacy.
What is it?
I...
I've never heard of it.
You're still not going to say it, aren't you?
Fine.
You're forcing me to be a killer.
Gu Bei Xi!
Coming!
Your ears are so long.
Why did you ask me to be a cop?
You even want this?
Looks like you have a good show to watch.
Here.
What are you doing?
Don't... Don't come here.
Aren't you a good ear?
I told you to be a good ear.
Say it!
You're still not going to say it, aren't you?
Gu Bei Xi!
Coming!
Say it or not?
Say it!
I won't say it!
Stop!
Say it!
I...
I heard about the ghost market.
Someone is doing a spiritual business.
But it has nothing to do with me.
I'm selling drugs seriously.
You...
Did you catch the wrong person?
Sir.
The pharmacy was burned to the ground by the fire.
We don't have any proper evidence.
Could it be that we really caught the wrong person?
The person must not have been caught wrong.
Besides,
we don't have any evidence.
Ling Chong.
The usual pharmacy is full of herbs.
It's important to keep the scale.
The most clear videos of the Yangtze River
such as Danggui, Baishao and Chuan Xiong
are made in the upper level of the scale.
The most important videos
such as Longgu, Muli, Zhenzhu and Mu
are made in the lower level of the scale.
Finally, the videos with a large amount of material
are made in the lowest level.
Such as Tongcao, Sangye and others.
Such a setting is convenient to adjust the time.
In addition to the shelf for the medicine,
it's not easy to find a space
to store a large number of insects.
Just now, in the pharmacy,
I found that the videos of Qingzhi
were made in the lowest level.
So I inferred that someone made the shelf
to be replaced.
He must have transferred something
that was invisible to the upper level.
It made Ling Chong hard to be discovered.
He is indeed the person I like.
He is really amazing.
The evidence is here.
Do you want to play tricks?
I'm just borrowing some kids
to do some business with Ling Chong.
I can't sell
what others buy.
Who is the person behind you?
I...
I'm rich.
I don't need anyone to instruct me.
The pharmacy fire
has already confirmed my guess.
Ling Chong's deal is not done by you alone.
Even if you don't say it,
the person behind you
may not protect you.
Why bother to suffer?
Besides,
it's not good to have Ling Chong's feelings in your body, right?
If you say it,
I can save you.
You... You can't save me.
The... The King of Worms...
It's... It's King of Worms.
King of Worms? What King of Worms?
Continue.
He is our superior.
I only know that
as long as the distance is close enough,
he can manipulate all the Ling Chong
and disturb the host to go east.
The host can't go west.
He is like the master of these worms.
So... So we call him King of Worms.
We are not welcome
to be infected.
Where can we find him?
I don't know.
A few days ago, a subordinate died.
I heard that
it was a crime.
The rules of selling the forest and not selling people
are too high.
We are selling worms.
We are just
a little bit of a burden.
We can't avoid
those people who are so ugly.
We are just a little bit of a burden.
Where did the Ling Chong come from?
Did it come from the sky?
You have a good relationship with the King of Worms.
How can you not have seen him?
Have I seen him or not?
Think about it.
Sir...
Sir... Sir, please forgive me.
I have seen him.
But you shouldn't eat
what you eat.
He only appears when he is delivering goods.
When he comes, he wears a wind coat.
He doesn't look at me.
He only knows
that he makes a strange sound when he walks.
He is weird.
I really don't know anything else.
I think he has said enough.
Why don't we give him to Director Bai
and ask the police to deal with him?
Sir, how do you know
that there are Ling Chong in the Chang'er's clan?
When I first caught him,
I found his neck is wrinkled.
It's the same as the symptoms of the animal's
excretion here.
This King of Worms is too powerful.
He can not only absorb the power of the spirit,
but also control the people who are heavily injured.
Let's save the sea first
and meet him again.
We can't let him hurt others anymore.
Okay.
This matter...
Father.
No problem.
Wait.
Let me see.
Take it.
You are too exaggerated.
You lost weight in a day.
That's not true.
Take it.
I'll tell you a good news.
What good news?
We caught a Ling Chong in the Chang'er's clan.
When we hand him over to Director Bai,
when the sea comes out,
we'll take him to have a good meal
and go to meet him.
Then we'll go back to Qingquan Village.
My father hasn't been back to the village for a long time.
It's time to go back and have a rest.
Our family finally reunited.
It's quite good.
Deng Deng.
You go back to Qingquan Village first.
I'll stay here for a few more days.
When I find out about Ling Chong,
I'll go back to Qingquan Village to find you.
What are you looking for?
Qingquan Village?
You want to go there?
Why do you make him think about you?
Shut up.
What did you say?
You and Deng Deng
are like a fight from the beginning.
You can't even fight back.
If you dare to bully Deng Deng again
and touch him,
I'll kill you.
Father.
I've told you.
It's a misunderstanding.
What misunderstanding?
He wants to kill you with money.
Living with such a person for a lifetime.
That's dangerous.
He's here today.
Come on.
Write the divorce letter to me.
The most beautiful scenery
is all about you
When two hearts are so close
When the whole world is occupied by you
I will call you with all my heart
Until your memory
You are the only one
who walks into the scenery
This city is full of rain and the clouds are scattered
The clouds are about to stop
I have decided to do it for you
with all my heart
I will call you with all my heart
Until your memory
You are the only one
who walks into the scenery
This city is full of rain and the clouds are scattered
I will call you with all my heart
Until your memory
You are the only one
who walks into the scenery
This city is full of rain and the clouds are scattered
The clouds are about to stop
I have decided to do it for you
with all my heart