I won't let go even if you walk away from me
It's not me
You ask you, it's not me
Go
You want
Be careful
Here
After her
Master
Princess
Go
Give me your hand
Hurry up
It's too late
Hurry up!
Jump!
You saved me?
Don't misunderstand.
You're just a human.
I don't want you to die so quickly.
Are your hands okay?
I'm fine.
My lady!
You're lucky today.
Don't say anything to me.
Got it?
Got it.
Gu Bei Xi.
My lady!
I didn't expect
to meet you in this way.
My lady!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
My lady!
The bandit has run away.
Don't chase after him.
Let's go to see the lady.
Okay.
I'm fine.
Is anyone inside?
Something happened.
Let's go down and have a look.
Okay.
No one is here.
Empty?
I should have known
that I wouldn't die so quickly.
No.
Bai Shi Qi
was talking to
the lady inside.
Yes.
A living person
is lost like this.
Lady!
Go and look over there.
Lady is missing.
The bandit and the heroine
are missing.
They appeared so strangely.
They must be together.
Stop talking nonsense.
Lady is missing.
It's not a small matter.
Let's go home
and tell my father.
It's strange.
Why is someone
suddenly missing?
Master,
I'm done for.
I should have come to the library.
I shouldn't have
kidnapped the food.
Don't care about who is missing.
Let's protect ourselves first.
Let's go.
Go.
Master,
something bad happened.
Your lady
was kidnapped
on the way to the upper house.
The bandit
is missing.
Where is Lady?
Lady is fine.
She has gone back to her house.
She is so arrogant
when she is on my head.
Master,
there are two people in the bandit.
Did they do
the previous case?
Stop talking nonsense.
You are smart.
Go to find the painter.
Go to the east of the city.
Hurry up.
Don't be so slow.
It's a girl.
Yes.
How can I recognize her?
You two are watching the scene of the scene.
Oh, no.
She will see
what you look like.
It's these two bastards.
You,
go to the painter.
Yes.
I'm so angry.
Boss,
have you seen
these two people these days?
These two people...
General Yan,
did you see who did it?
No.
But General Yan,
she must be a spirit.
You tell me.
This...
It's Huan Ling.
It's her again.
Recently,
the disappearance case in Yingdu City
is frequent.
Is it related to her?
Although this matter
needs to be investigated,
the disappearance case
is likely to be related to Zhu Rong and others.
Is there any other clue?
No.
Forget it.
You go.
Thank you, General Yan.
Sir,
what should we do next?
Go.
General Yan,
please help me.
Help me,
General Yan.
General Yan,
don't leave me.
please help me.
General Yan,
Don't leave me.
It's you.
It's been three thousand years.
We meet again.
I didn't expect you to be alive.
What you didn't expect
is more than that.
Do you want to get
what you want here?
Sir.
I just took
some memories of the ghost.
But during the process,
she chose to commit suicide.
Suicide?
Sir,
you're hurt.
Her spirit stone
hurt my primordial energy.
It seems that
we can't use this method
to retrieve memories.
I remember.
The book says
that the memory is reflected by the host.
We'll find another way.
You can't do this.
But at least
we got some information
to figure out
what happened
around Deng Deng recently.
By the way,
it's not just the host.
Look.
Gu Bei Xi and others
were arrested
for the missing person case.
Sir,
you are...
Do you know these two people?
Have you packed up?
The police are coming.
So fast.
Go.
These two criminals
live upstairs
with a woman
who was with them.
Go.
Search.
Sir,
no.
Sir, no.
Call the electric shock.
Yes.
You...
You dare to trick me?
How dare I?
I didn't...
I didn't return the room.
Get that woman out.
We'll be in trouble.
Okay.
Come on.
Hurry up.
It's so weird today.
First, we were scared.
Then we lost someone.
What happened?
I really don't know.
Why?
When I opened the door,
there was no one inside.
Only a cat.
Could it be that
Director Bai
wanted to find a scapegoat?
We made a decision.
But we went into his.
The horse that pulled the cart today
has a lot of blood stains.
It looks like it was just scratched.
I have that horse on my back.
Why do you think
there are more marks on it?
Could it be that the Spirit Clan did it?
Could it be Lu Yan?
I haven't seen him for two days.
He must be the ghost in the basement.
I'll ask him about it.
But
no matter where this little ghost is,
he must be in the basement.
Director Bai
will not give up easily.
Now the city is in a terrible state.
The police station will only
check the population of the outside world.
Maybe
my father has already registered.
But
it will be harder
for us to enter the police station
after today.
We don't have to go to the police station.
Director Bai is too stressed
because of the missing case.
He has already
sent people to the Bai family.
I have an idea.
I'll go to the Bai family tomorrow.
I'll go to the Bai family.
If you are here to take a rest,
this is not a smart way.
I don't want to take a rest.
I ask you.
You are the one who
caused the chaos
and disturbed the spirit clan of Golden Horse today.
No.
Who else can it be if it's not you?
The disappearance of the little ghost
and the disappearance of the little ghost
is also related to you.
Of course it's not related.
I tell you.
Don't worry about me in the future.
You help me a lot.
Wait.
It's very dangerous now.
You still have to be very careful.
I'll say it again.
Don't make the decision yourself.
You ruined my good thing.
Otherwise,
I'll kill you.
Miss.
Come in.
It's too hot.
Miss.
Let's have a bowl of mung bean soup.
Thank you.
Miss.
You miss the Lord again?
I miss you.
Number one.
How could others know?
My wife is pregnant.
Okay, okay.
Don't don't.
I'm just ACE.
So what?
Is it considered unique?
Do you want to ask your boss to cook?
Huh?
You said the flower shop
is special.
That man who you called
was poor,
but you won't come here if you really want.
What a receipt.
Take it.
Thanks a lot.
Come on.
Take it.
Give it to me.
Miss has been 18 years old.
They should have married long ago.
But now, there's no movement.
Just beat him up.
Miss, the portrait of the owner of the house
is very similar to the one that kidnapped our bandit.
That bandit was masked.
How could anyone see his face?
We didn't see it clearly.
But someone saw it in the police station.
After you and the bandit were kidnapped,
Master was so angry.
Now, the whole city is in chaos.
Wei Chu, I'll go check.
Yes.
Open the door.
I need to connect to connection.
groundwater
What's wrong?
Yu Yihao.
Why is there no normal picture?
Old Yu.
How much trouble have you made to your daughter?
A yellow hair on her head.
Why are these people so strange?
Be careful.
Don't be rash.
Captain.
Wait.
It's a pity for these two.
I think I've seen them somewhere.
Big Sea, wake up.
The police have found us.
You guys, follow them.
Especially pay attention to that girl.
See where they go.
We're on our way.
The inn is near the backyard.
Don't go to the temple.
I'm afraid they'll meet the Gubei star.
Stop.
Don't run.
It's strange.
Miss, you are...
Come.
Give me some tea.
Miss, this is a cafe.
No tea, only coffee.
No.
What do you mean?
Are you looking down on me?
Old woman.
Come.
Give me a cup of...
What did you say?
Calafie.
Okay, wait a minute.
Go.
Stop.
You want to chase me?
You don't want to see who your grandma is?
It's still early.
It's all my fault.
Huang Yongcai
disappeared from the north of the city.
Li Zhong
What about you all?
report
Corp also said
that tourist
Grandfather
and Subscriber
had decided
to leave Baiattlener
tomorrow.
Mr. Yulong
has already toldawa
of most of them.
Li Zhong.
Er Kui.
What's going on?
Excuse me.
Wake up.
Coming.
Where is that lady?
What lady?
I'm that lady, remember?
Boss, did you see that lady?
That lady?
No.
You!
Where did you hide the lady?
Who hid the lady?
I...
Oh no.
That's the kidnapper!
Call the police!
Boss.
Police!
What?
It's you!
Listen to me.
Go out and talk.
It's you!
Hurry up!
It's him!
I'll kill you!
Okay, okay.
It's him.
Oh no.
Even if you don't kill me,
I'll kill myself this time.
According to the cause,
Da Hai should have woken up long ago.
Why hasn't he come?
Might as well
leave a mark for him
and go straight to the temple to meet.
I wonder
how Lu Yan is doing?
I hope no one knows about it.
Where is he?
Did I say too much yesterday?
No matter what,
it's to save me.
We agreed to meet for two hours.
How long has it been?
No.
I can't wait anymore.
The robbers who killed Yingdu
have been caught.
Look at them.
Let's go.
It's him.
Hit him.
What's going on?
It's him.
Hit him.
Stop.
Take out your pass.
Hurry.
Let them go.
They've been lost.
What's the use of you?
Director.
They're too cunning.
Hey,
where are you going?
You don't look like a local.
Feng Xingzheng.
I forgot to bring it.
Stop playing with me.
Take off your glasses.
My eyes are burning.
What are you looking at?
Why do I see you look familiar?
Kong Jiliang.
Captain.
I've seen you before.
Officer Zhang.
I...
Miss Bai.
Why are you here?
Yingdu City is not peaceful recently.
Why are you here alone?
I'm here to find my friend.
The one in front of you.
He's your friend?
Yes.
I'm a classmate in Shenzhen.
Don't report to my father.
How can I?
Miss.
You look like a wanted criminal.
Officer Zhang.
Do you think I don't even recognize my classmate?
How dare I?
I'm a man of my word.
Here you are.
I'll go first.
Go.
What are you doing?
I'm helping you.
I know.
I'm asking why you're helping me.
Because you saved my life on the mountain road.
I want to repay you.
Is this enough?
Then you're a good man.
You can't tell others about me.
Otherwise I'll...
I know.
You'll come back to me.
Don't worry.
I'm a man of my word.
You're Bai Shiqi, right?
I want to ask you something.
Miss Bai...
Forget it.
You...
I have a question.
You've helped me.
We're even now.
What else do you want to ask?
Why did you come to Yingdu?
And you were going to pick up the car of our Bai family
as a bandit?
It's none of your business.
Can you tell me your name?
Gu Bei Xi.
And...
You can't tell your family about my name.
Got it?
Got it.
Gu Bei Xi.
Da Hai was caught.
I want to borrow some from you.
I know what you're going to do.
You're not allowed to go.
No matter how much I borrow from you today,
I'll pay you 10 times more in the money.
Do you think this is a matter of guns and bullets?
But Peng Da Hai is very timid.
If the police force him to do something,
he'll definitely be unable to take it.
Yu Deng Deng.
That's the police station.
It's not a joke.
You can't stop him.
What do you think we should do?
Don't worry.
I'll go to the police station first.
No.
Even if Xiao Ye doesn't want to die,
I'll help you save Da Hai.
No.
I have to see Da Hai no matter what.
I have to confirm his safety.
I'm afraid that Chief Bai
will blame Da Hai for everything.
He'll be the scapegoat for all the missing cases in the city.
But what's the use?
You're just a scapegoat.
Yes.
If you want to save Da Hai,
I have to turn myself in.
What?
Turn yourself in?
Are you crazy?
Isn't it enough to go in?
Listen to me first.
This is a chance to return the soldiers.
Ying Du is a gathering place of the forest tribe.
There should be a lot of bad things happening.
I said I was a hunter.
I can only bet one.
I bet that Chief Bai
wants to find those missing people
and his little Yitai.
If it doesn't work,
I still have reinforcements.
Lu Yan, Lu Yan.
Can you hear me?
My disciple Peng Da Hai has been arrested.
I need your help now.
If you help me today,
I'll pay you back ten times in the future.
I'll keep my word.
It's disgusting.
Little boy, let me tell you.
I'm very tired.
I'm curious about you. I want to sleep.
Can you tell me where the little Yitai is?
Can you?
I didn't see it.
You didn't see it?
Let me help you think about it.
You didn't see it, right?
You didn't see it.
I didn't see it.
You didn't see it, right?
Say it.
Chief Bai.
Where is the little Yitai?
Chief Bai, listen to me.
Do you remember?
Chief Bai.
Where are those missing people?
I didn't see it.
Where are you?
Say it.
I didn't see it.
You didn't see it, right?
I told you to go away.
Chief Bai.
Did you see it?
Chief Bai, he's really new here.
He's the same as the name of the gate we entered and left.
You idiot.
That name tag won't be wrong.
Look.
Now, for this case,
I'm being watched every day.
I'm so angry.
Isn't this a criminal in the county?
Let me go up there and catch a new one.
Chief, I'm warning you.
Come.
The criminal, Peng Dahai.
I'm here.
Peng Dahai.
I'll give you one last chance.
Say it.
Where are my little Yi Tai and those who were kidnapped?
I'm really innocent.
Write it.
Kill the West Tree.
Throw the stone into the river.
And where are your accomplices?
That guy.
I'm here to turn myself in.
Don't move.
Let your chief Bai come out and see me.
I'm here.
Let's go.
Write it.
Three people are wanted.
Chief.
The accomplice, Yu Dengdeng, has turned himself in.
What's that?
I'm dead.
Chief.
-'Dahai.
Why are you here?
Please leave quickly.
Chief Bai, this has nothing to do with him.
This has nothing to do with him.
Dahai.
It's fine.
They can't do anything to me.
Who knows how to turn himself in?
Explain your own problem first.
I heard that the chief Bai of the capital is a wise man.
But he's not like this today.
He's really a fool.
Chief Bai, I'm not here to turn myself in today.
I'm here to help you.
Help me? Thank you.
Miss Yu Deng Deng, right?
You idiot!
You helped me.
Do you know how much you've committed?
Killing and kidnapping.
That's a headache.
Whether it's a headache or not,
you have to hear me out first.
Say it.
I heard that the capital is the home of the Lin family.
As the official here,
you should have heard about it.
Stop talking nonsense.
We never advocate these
strange and chaotic things.
Why are you nervous?
You should have heard about it.
I believe you've heard and seen
some strange things happen.
To be honest,
the Lin family does exist.
My apprentice and I
are the special scouts of the Lin family.
That day,
we came to the dark cloud
under the capital.
There will be a disaster soon.
And I'm sure that
the disappearance of the Lin family
in the capital is done by the Lin family.
It's true. It's true.
Chief Bai,
I stopped the carriage at your mansion that day
because I knew that
the Lin family would attack your family.
Fortunately, my apprentice and I
arrived in time and conquered the Lin family.
Otherwise,
your family would not only disappear.
I'm afraid that
you're already in trouble.
I'm sorry.