BLACK KNIGHT
Forty years ago,
a comet collided with Earth.
Since then, most continents
have been submerged,
and the Korean Peninsula
has turned into a desert.
Only 1% of the population survived.
The survivors needed
new inventions and a new order.
The polluted air led to the invention
of the gigantic Air Core,
which converts oxyanium into oxygen.
And the scarce resources
led to a division of the population
into General, Special, and Core,
separated by QR codes.
GENERAL DISTRICT
SPECIAL DISTRICT, CORE DISTRICT
However, those who were not chosen
live miserable lives
labeled as refugees.
RELIEF SUPPLIES TRANSPORT VEHICLE
Some refugees, tired of discrimination,
starvation, and lack of oxygen,
become hunters
and start plundering and robbing.
Deliverymen.
We deliver oxygen and necessities
that keep people alive.
We must fight through the sandy desert
and its polluted air,
fend off attacks by brutal hunters,
and arrive at the designated time,
on the dot.
Deliverymen must be tough.
Because they must risk their lives
to protect their trucks
from the attacks of the hunters.
That's why people
dream of becoming deliverymen.
For the refugees with no QR codes
in particular, becoming a deliveryman…
is their only hope.
GANGNAM REFUGEE DISTRICT
There are too many of them.
It might be tough.
Man, those bastards are
a bunch of cowards!
Dummy, Dumb-dumb.
-What?
-Yeah?
We're here just watching the fight,
so aren't we the real cowards?
-Yeah.
-You're right.
I haven't got all day, you punks!
He won.
-Hey!
-Let's go!
Our future deliveryman!
You won again today!
Yoon Sa-wol!
-Look at the oxygen and the masks!
-Good job.
GENERAL DISTRICT
Air purification in progress.
Pollution level five, dangerous.
CARGO CONTROL SYSTEM
District Five, Apartment 862.
CHEONMYEONG GROUP
READING QR CODE
Deliveryman, identity confirmed.
Disinfection complete.
Ah, you're here.
Hello, sir.
AIR QUALITY POOR
OXYGEN LEVEL LOW
COMPRESSED OXYGEN
OXYGEN LEVEL 100%
You cut it close again, sir.
You should order
before the oxygen level falls below 20%.
I guess my time's almost up.
I keep forgetting.
Mr. Lee Yeong-su, recipient confirmed.
It's been a while
since you last ordered food.
Are you eating your meals?
I'm low on coins,
so I only eat one meal a day.
-Sir.
-Stop nagging.
I'm still better off
than the refugees out there.
Sure.
EMERGENCY
Load it quickly before backup arrives
and makes life hard for us.
Okay, all loaded! Let's go, sir!
Wait. Let's take that.
We won't have to worry about starving
until the hand rots.
The gun.
I told you not to touch
anything that breathes.
Aren't you off today?
You waited for my day off to target
a newbie and went for his hand?
We have to make a living too.
Then tough it out as refugees.
Instead of dying as hunters.
Fuck you and your lectures, motherfucker.
You gonna shoot me?
Yes.
-I will shoot!
-Here I come.
Please don't kill me. Please!
Bummer.
Next time, it'll be loaded.
Newbie, are you okay?
PURCHASE OXYGEN
REMAINING OXYGEN 30%
DO YOU WISH TO BUY OXYGEN?
PROCESSING PAYMENT
THROUGH MS. JUNG SEUL-AH'S ACCOUNT
OXYGEN PURCHASE COMPLETE
Ms. Jung Seul-ah has left.
Mr. Yoon Sa-wol.
Can't you at least eat before you run off?
Ms. Park Myeong-hui, you're under arrest
for harboring a refugee
and violating the General District laws.
No, I just felt bad for him.
-Ma'am!
-Let the kid go!
Just take me, not the kid!
Ma'am.
Ma'am!
Okay.
Hands up.
I don't see any progress.
I'm trying!
The two of you wreck the place,
and I'm the one cleaning it up.
Ow, my back.
I warned you
they were cracking down on refugees,
yet you not only wandered outside
but gambled with supplies?
Ow. Ouch!
I mean,
I win, and win again,
and then win yet again.
And now, I can't find
anyone to challenge me.
This is all part of my training--
Challenge? Training?
Is this about becoming a deliveryman?
Seol-ah, I think he's got a chance.
I've seen him fight a few times,
and he's definitely
much stronger than before--
Do you also go
outside the General District?
You were supposed to stop him,
yet you take his side?
Assume the position.
Me?
No, Seol-ah.
Seul-ah didn't do anything. It's my fault.
Rough me up. Just me. Yeah.
Here.
You think anyone can become a deliveryman?
Going around fighting people
won't make you a general citizen.
I told you I'd find a way.
A way?
-What way?
-What?
How on earth are you
going to implant a code here?
A DIC major like you must be terrified
for harboring a refugee alone. Now what?
-Will you buy me someone's hand illegally?
-Sa-wol!
It's been nearly ten years.
I know you're frustrated
because there is no way.
So just stop trying.
I don't want to put you two in danger.
Yeah, I don't want to be in danger either,
so don't fool around.
That's the safest.
Me getting lost would be the safest.
Yoon Sa-wol!
I told you not to talk shit about leaving!
Your future doesn't look bright.
I'm disappointed.
What?
You could end this entire family
before you become a deliveryman.
So, Yoon Sa-wol.
-You're grounded for a week.
-What?
Come on! A week?
Look here, Major Jung Seol-ah,
aren't you being too harsh?
Am I?
-Then 15 days.
-Fifteen days.
Fine, 15 days, starting tomorrow.
I'll lock him up and watch him closely.
Oh, come on!
Make it a week.
It could be a month.
Okay. Fine.
Fifteen days it is.
Air purification in progress.
Pollution level five, dangerous.
Pollution level five, dangerous.
1 TEXT MESSAGE
UNKNOWN SENDER
GATE 8, 1700
REFUGEE DISTRICT
GANGNAM STATION
HANNAM BRIDGE
Entering a known hunter-infested area.
Stay alert.
Humans are such magnificent beings.
They have children and go on living
like that in this environment.
GWANGHWAMUN GATE
We're passing through
the Special District.
We have arrived at the Core District.
CHEONMYEONG GROUP
-Here.
-Yes, sir.
Madam President,
is the situation in the Special District
that serious?
The population is overflowing,
and you can't see the sky or the forests,
so people develop depression
and panic disorders…
It's inevitable.
That's why this relocation plan
is so important to the citizens.
Lots of issues are cropping up everywhere.
I must have botched things
when I was designing the place.
It's been 40 years
since you made this place, Mr. Ryu.
You dug five kilometers below the surface
and built this world
in such a short period.
Once the construction of District A
is complete,
you'll have created
a new environment for us yet again.
Thank you for saying that.
My time must be approaching.
My confidence is gone,
and I'm only awash with regret.
Don't say that.
You're still healthy and strong.
Don't let it bother you.
Just focus on the relocation plan.
It sounds like you're telling me
to die once I finish the plan.
I didn't expect to see you,
Madam President.
Shall I leave you two alone?
No, we've been waiting for you.
I heard the Air Road is complete.
When is the operational test?
I can't give you an exact date yet.
Have you been
to the District A construction site?
Is the schedule being delayed?
I heard the reports to the government
are not being delivered on time.
My priority is to report to you.
The construction is almost complete.
Sharing information promptly is a must.
I apologize.
When can I expect to see it?
I'll visit soon and let you know.
All right.
"Soon."
Why do you antagonize the government?
Father.
This whole world
is Cheonmyeong's creation.
But they wasted a year
meddling in our affairs.
Telling us what to do
doesn't help anything.
You think Cheonmyeong is yours?
No. You are Cheonmyeong itself, Father.
Yes, never forget that, no matter what.
Never.
Yoon Sa-wol.
FIFTEEN DAYS FROM TOMORROW!
He's a lost cause.
You might imprison me
There might be fine dust everywhere
Before my eyes
But I will forge my own path
I will forge my own path
Grandpa!
Useless!
Dummy and Dumb-dumb!
Where are you?
Grandpa!
Jeez, you're so loud!
Hey! You're still alive.
You punk,
I don't plan on dying
until I fix that rude mouth of yours.
Got it?
That hurts!
You know I can't help it
because I'm uneducated!
Sa-wol, you ignoramus,
will you let us study in peace?
Grandpa says studying makes us decent.
Forget it. It's freaking hard
to become a decent person,
so let's go out.
-Go out?
-Where?
I'll be grounded from tomorrow.
Let's make some trouble today.
SLOW
30 KM/H
Air pollution level rising.
Let's go.
30 km/h speed limit zone.
Automatically decelerating.
WARNING
SPEED LIMIT 30 KM/H
Useless! Run faster, hurry!
You go up first.
The kids are going mad
now the world is destroyed.
We're going to crash! Get down!
Farewell.
ELECTRICITY
Your friends all got off.
Are you…
Are you the legendary deliveryman 5-8?
You're rude, aren't you?
You want to know who I am?
My name is Sa-wol. Yoon Sa-wol.
I don't want to know,
and I didn't ask.
Shut up and fight me.
What the heck?
He's freaking strong.
He's got no manners and no fear.
It's coming.
A big one's coming.
DISTRICT A
It looks even more hideous than before.
UNKNOWN SENDER
GATE 8, 1700
Did the mission fail?
Air Core.
It's sooner than I expected.
Has the armed protest been
completely suppressed?
Yes, the guard force
quelled it completely.
I should have called you earlier…
Anyway, thank you
for coming all the way here.
Since I'm here, I'd like to see
the head of the guard force.
Even you can't go in there
without prior authorization, Major.
I understand
it's important to maintain secrecy,
but you can't restrict access
to a major of the DIC.
I've told you time and time again.
Cheonmyeong's in charge
of District A construction.
Please don't take it the wrong way.
I ask for your understanding.
Where are they going?
They are Cheonmyeong's assets,
which means they are not
under your purview either, Major.
It's strange they'd go this far
to stop people from seeing District A.
That's what I wonder the most about too.
That jackass head guard hightails it
whenever I show up,
and that sly Director Oh keeps using
Cheonmyeong as an excuse.
The head guard is over 50 years old.
Calling him a jackass is too…
good, I think.
Damn it!
Idiot, don't you know how to drive?
Sir…
It wasn't my…
All-round defense!
Open the door.
Stop, hands up!
What's going on?
I hate people pointing guns at me.
I'm Major Jung Seol-ah of the DIC.
Is this your vehicle?
Cheonmyeong Group is the owner.
I know that.
Please answer the question.
Yes, I drive this vehicle. Major.
The area near District A is off-limits.
Why is your delivery vehicle off-route?
I got lost because of the tornado
and saw another path.
-Where did you go when you left the truck?
-Does that matter?
I asked you where you went.
I
was
relieving
myself.
Let me check your ID.
IDENTITY CONFIRMED
Please leave immediately.
Get in the car.
She's snippy.
I'm home.
Did you have fun today?
Huh?
Yeah.
Go to your room.
My room?
What could these be?
That should be enough.
Hey!
LOCKED
-Commencing QR code lockdown.
-What are you doing?
Sa-wol, put yourself in my shoes.
You couldn't even stay put for a day.
What else could I do?
Come on.
Something huge happened today.
Just open the door.
I'll tell you everything.
Okay, talk.
I'll listen to everything from here.
Dinner, yeah.
Let's talk about this over dinner.
The delivery box has enough food
to last you for 15 days.
I promise that I won't set foot outside
from tomorrow.
-I swear, seriously.
-You swear?
I've been thinking all day.
Do you know how many times you've kept
a promise over the past ten years?
How many times?
Zero.
Not even once.
Hey!
Still, locking me up is too much.
Listen to Seol-ah and me this once.
Seul-ah! Jung Seul-ah!
You must scan your QR code.
REFUGEE DISTRICT - LABOR MARKET
Are you on your own?
No.
Dad went to get oxygen.
I GAVE MY ALL TO BECOME A DELIVERYMAN
What's that book?
I'm going to become a deliveryman.
Oh, really?
Yes, it's what I really want.
I'll help the refugees,
like 5-8,
and give them oxygen and food.
Anyway, I'll become
a beacon of hope for refugees,
like 5-8.
Hey, mister.
They suppressed
the armed protest at District A,
so we failed to delay the construction.
We can't reach our informant either.
That idiot. Must be dead.
The Air Core's in District A now.
You'll need to go this time.
Okay.
Yeah.
PROCESSED FOOD
It'll be a bit short this time.
We'll be back soon.
Thank you, as always, for showing up
just when we are about to die.
I say this every time,
but split it fairly.
-Okay.
-Here.
Heart rate and blood pressure
are all normal.
I'll come by again before the delivery.
Thank you.
Here.
Challenger knocked out
in 3 minutes 23 seconds.
God, so dang strong.
Are you losing on a full stomach?
If I eat, I have to poop. Would you eat?
-What's with the gross remark?
-It's from a rebellious youth.
Youth, my ass.
A crazy seven-year-old is more like it.
Deliveryman, identity confirmed.
We got a package!
Disinfection complete.
You're not Deliveryman 5-7.
He couldn't be here, so I came instead.
-Ms. Jung Seul-ah, recipient confirmed.
-5-8?
Ah, yes.
Are you the 5-8?
-Yes.
-No way!
Wow.
Wow, could you…
Could you please take a picture with me?
What's going on?
Just one more, please.
5-8?
-Why am I hiding?
-Thank you!
I'll be off, then.
I did nothing wrong.
-Take care.
-Bye.
Bye.
Oh my God!
You looked so thrilled.
"Just one more, please."
"Thank you!"
"Take care."
He's better looking in person.
You're doomed.
You lose in both fighting and looks.
No.
I'm way better looking.
Sure.
Deliveryman, identity confirmed.
What is it?
FRONT GATE OPEN
Who the hell are you? What are you doing?
Inject her quickly!
You must scan your QR code.
Is someone else here?
Go and check.
Seul-ah. Are you okay?
Jung Seul-ah.
Subtitle translation by: Mihee Kim