♪The moon sinks, ripples dance, violet stars awaken♪
♪As time dissolves without a trace♪
♪Frosted memories scatter, silk cannot veil the past♪
♪Fate is drifting in silence♪
♪Let winds and sands accompany the road ahead♪
♪Looking back, joys and sorrows linger, no regrets remain♪
♪Breaking free from the depths of darkness♪
♪Like pearls of tears, we swirl with fate's embrace♪
[Based on the novel The Story of Pearl Girl by Tan Tianyin]
[The Story of Pearl Girl]
[Episode 30]
Shrimp was like a brother to Duanwu.
Loud,
Cao Da, and Wei Yan
were her best friends
after she fled to Hepu.
They were like my family.
But they died because of me.
You took care of their funerals
and comforted their families.
It was not you who killed them.
It was the Black Dragon Bandits.
But they are dead.
Even if I give their family more pensions,
I can't make it up to them.
It has already happened.
It's useless
to indulge in sadness.
I believe Duanwu suffered more pain
than I did.
Time heals all wounds.
Maybe.
I was looking for Supervisor Kang to send it to you.
Take the medicine.
Thank you.
Isn't it hot?
No.
Well...
Thank you for taking care of me these days.
When I'm healed,
I'll leave Clear Mind right away.
Just get better here.
I'll make you noodle soup.
It's delicious.
Thank you.
Have you ever thought
about what would happen to them
if you disappeared in Yangzhou?
What do you mean?
I am willing to be your ally
rather than your enemy.
Do you mean
that I can stay at the Clear Mind?
Just eat it.
♪Life flows like a boat, navigating joys and woes♪
♪Your face glows like lanterns in the night...♪
No one has made you noodles for years.
♪How can we endure the binds of longing?♪
♪Like a grand dream, a lone cup of wine♪
Mr. Zheng.
I invited you here
to explain ourselves to you.
Lady Bai
went to the Governor's Office to admit that she had made false accusations
because she was threatened by Yan Zijing.
How did Yan Zijing
threaten you?
Yan Zijing realized
that Lady Bai and Baicaojing House were working together.
He wanted to discredit me.
Lady Bai had no choice...
Lady Bai, speaking of that,
I must toast you.
Thank you for proving my innocence.
Cheers.
But I'm not interested
in
dealing with your matter.
Mr. Zheng,
Lady Huan is dead.
Lady Bai will definitely win the top beauty title next year.
Baicaojing House will do our best to support her.
Baicaojing House has long since lost its reputation.
Mr. Qin.
Are you not self-aware?
Mr. Zheng, I was an underdog
before I won my first top beauty title.
But I won it.
Baicaojing House is famous in Yangzhou.
We just have to start all over again.
Lady Bai,
I wish you all the best.
Garuda.
I don't like the wine here.
Let's go to another wine shop.
Mr. Zheng.
Walk them out.
What did I say?
We should please him.
But you got on a high horse.
The Zheng family is also a merchant.
Will they give their customers to you?
Maybe he could make a guild director.
Are you qualified, Mu?
I'm satisfied
that we own Baicaojing House
in Yangzhou.
Just take care of the shop.
You saw his attitude.
He looked down
on our Baicaojing House.
It doesn't matter.
It would be nice if he likes you.
Si is dead.
Wu will be the master of the Zheng family.
Niao.
If you marry the Zheng family,
I will be the Zheng family's brother-in-law.
Will Xu Nanying
make you his concubine?
You can't be his concubine.
You're like...
Like what?
Like a whore?
No, that's not what I meant.
Niao.
You have to think for yourself.
I'm doing it for your own good.
Why did you come back so late?
Where is Garuda?
Why isn't he holding you?
He's not holding me.
You'll be happy if I fall to my death.
You're with me
to kill Yan Zijing.
What are you talking about?
Stop drinking.
Leave me alone.
Okay.
Lady Shijiu.
You've endured humiliation
for so long.
You suffered.
I didn't kill Yan Zijing.
You must be disappointed in me.
I'm not the heir of the Zheng family.
I'm useless.
I'm a useless concubine's son.
I'm not good enough for you, Lady Shijiu of the Cui family.
Cui Shijiu.
Let me ask you something.
Do you hate me
for stopping you from going to Chang'an?
There are many dignitaries in Chang'an.
As long as you give yourself to them...
As long as you give yourself to them,
they will kill Yan Zijing for you.
Yeah.
It's too late for you to go to Chang'an now.
The door is right there.
You can leave whenever you want.
I won't stop you.
Zheng Zhiheng.
What do you make of me?
My father is lying to me.
Su Muzhe
is lying to me.
Why are you also lying to me, Cui Shijiu?
Su Muzhe, come out.
[Clear Mind]
Let's talk outside.
The ten-day deadline is up.
We're here to get our money.
It's not easy for us to make money for retirement.
I'm sorry.
You can withdraw your money.
But Clear Mind
has no money right now.
We had a deal.
There has always been a deadline for withdrawal.
You withdrew without warning.
And this is Clear Mind's
most difficult period.
We don't want to talk to you.
Where is Ms. Su?
Call her out.
Su Muzhe, come out.
Let us talk to Ms. Su.
- Su Muzhe, come out. - Keep it down.
Come out.
- Su Muzhe. - Ms. Su, come out.
Shiqi.
I'm sorry.
I know
the deadline is up.
But Clear Mind is out of money.
We have some mother-of-pearl jewelry left.
If you don't mind,
you can take them all.
Here are the IOUs.
Verbal statements are no guarantee.
I'll repay you every three months.
I'll pay you off in six months. The interest is three percent.
I won't let you suffer losses.
If you want the money now,
I'm sorry
I don't have it.
Now that
Clear Mind can't come up with the money,
let's give Ms. Su
some more time.
Ms. Su won't break her words.
Ms. Su.
Show us the withdrawal document and IOUs.
We'll sign it.
There's no other way.
Ms. Su.
Please keep your promise.
I will.
Thank you.
Here's your withdrawal document and IOUs.
[Signature]
Duanwu.
Ms. Su.
The goods are arriving. Come and unload.
- Lady Wu from Guangzhou - The goods have arrived.
lend us a lot of gold and raw stones.
[Clear Mind]
We don't have to worry about it.
Ladies, don't withdraw.
Careful.
Ms. Su, get more people.
There's a lot of goods here.
I can't unload everything myself.
- Yunxiu. - Lady Xue.
Yingtao.
What's going on?
These are all our raw materials.
Look. All these boxes.
There are many in the back.
You won't believe
it's a coincidence.
Ladies,
you've signed IOUs.
It's settled.
I don't know
what will happen to Clear Mind.
From now on,
you don't have to worry about Clear Mind.
We'll repay you on time.
Thank you.
- Wait, Ms. Su... - Stop it.
We wanted to withdraw.
We shouldn't talk about it.
Ms. Su didn't treat us badly.
Come on, Yingtao.
Come on.
Let me.
Let's get out of here.
Yingtao.
Yeah. Let me.
Ms. Su, here's a letter from Lady Wu.
Hurry.
She asked me to bring all the money back.
Duanwu.
I hope this letter finds you well.
I heard Clear Mind is having difficulties.
I'm worried.
Here are gold and raw stones.
I hope this helps you.
As for the money,
don't worry about it.
You said
gold always shines.
[Onyx stones from Sijiao Mountain]
Are you going to make glass?
Yes.
But I didn't find out
the specific process
of making glass,
not to mention the ratios.
If there are no ratios,
I can't make glass.
Take it easy.
If everyone knows how to make it,
it won't be Clear Mind's featured product.
You're right.
I'm rushing.
Look.
I'll copy down the contents
of these books for you.
Don't you have some work to do?
I don't have work to do today.
Then, thank you.
Zhang Jinran.
You're idle as an inspector.
I happened to have no work today.
Duanwu just said the same thing.
What are you doing?
Do you want to make glass?
Clear Mind has no foundation.
Maybe I can gain a foothold by making glass.
You know
the Zheng family is in the glass business.
Are you going against the Zheng family?
I know.
The Zheng family makes Persian glassware.
I want to make Clear Mind glass.
It's different.
What are you drawing?
I'm copying down the contents
of these books for Duanwu.
It's wrong.
It's right.
Master Yan.
I've been drawing since I was three years old.
What's wrong with my painting?
It doesn't matter when you start drawing.
The drawing scale is wrong.
There's a stool there.
Come on.
Get up.
You...
The ratio of a kiln to its entrance is important.
The change in the ratio will affect the heat
and, thus, the finished product.
Today's incense is a little choking.
If I want to make this kiln,
how long will it take?
First...
Are you done? Do you need to see a doctor?
I'm all right.
Go on.
It's not easy
to make a new kiln.
You need to find
some professional craftsmen...
Mr. Zhang, do you need some water?
It's okay.
I'll move it outside.
Where were we?
You can
make a new kiln.
But you need to find some professional craftsmen.
It took your father
a few years
to make the colorful glass.
You have the formula.
But you don't know the ratios, heat,
or a kiln.
And
you need a lot of professional laborers and craftsmen.
You need to do it step by step.
Well.
There was Qin's Glass Workshop in Yangzhou.
I heard that Mr. Qin is still in Yangzhou.
I've sent Yingtao to ask around.
I'll hear from her soon.
It's a good start
if you can find him.
Yes.
Zhang Jinran.
Well.
Are you hungry?
I'm not hungry.
If you're hungry, you can eat first.
I'm busy.
Duanwu hasn't eaten yet.
Why don't you go to the kitchen and cook something?
I want to go.
But I can't cook.
Du Ming usually cooks for me.
That's great.
It's never too late to learn.
You can take this opportunity to learn to cook.
Is there someone in the kitchen?
Kang Ju is there.
Maybe you should go.
You go. I'm busy.
You go.
Go.
I'm talking with Duanwu. You go.
I'll go.
[Zhenlang Pavilion]
[Clear Mind]
Ms. Su, we found him.
Ms. Su,
we found him.
Ten years ago,
a man named Qin
opened Qin's Glass Workshop in Yangzhou.
But they couldn't
sell anything.
They were suppressed by...
The Zhengs.
They were suppressed by the Zheng family.
Qin ended up with a lot of debt,
and his wife was gone. But his children were left.
It's a silver lining.
Did they make their glass
themselves?
Yes.
Mr. Qin studied in Persia for ten years.
Go. Lead the way.
- Okay. - Okay, let's go.
Ms. Su, here we are.
Mr. Qin is cranky.
Mr. Qin.
[Glass vase]
Nice to meet you, Mr. Qin.
I don't have much goods here.
If you want to buy glass,
go to another shop.
Who are you?
She's the owner of Clear Mind,
Su Muzhe.
Ms. Su.
Clear Mind?
Is the shop
going to close?
Mr. Qin.
If you join Clear Mind,
it won't close.
Today,
I'm here
to ask you to work with me.
I want Clear Mind to make glass.
Glass?
Look.
I can't sell
my glass.
Mr. Qin.
We understand you.
It's all because of the Zheng family.
The glass
is their featured product.
They don't allow others to make it.
We understand.
I used to be as arrogant
as you were.
The government closed my shop two days after I opened it.
They framed me for selling toxic glass,
and someone was poisoned by it.
I lost all my money.
They almost beat me to death
before letting me go.
I didn't give up.
I made glass
and sold it from street to street.
You know what?
They smashed my kiln.
I can't hold anything
with this hand.
Mr. Qin.
No matter how dangerous or difficult it is,
I want to give it a try.
If I sell these
for more than half a million mace,
you work with us, okay?
All right.
If you can sell these goods,
I'll work with you.
Mr. Qin.
I'll move these goods.
Thank you, Mr. Qin.
Thank you.
Ms. Su, it's all broken.
How can we sell them?
Miss.
You can take back your words.
Baroque pearls are also pearls.
Broken glass is also glass.
Mr. Qin.
Half a million mace.
It's a deal.
[Zhenlang Pavilion]
Zhenlang Pavilion's people, come out.
Come out.
Sir, what can I do for you?
Are you the owner?
Calm down.
You sold me a fake.
We've always sold the real thing.
We don't sell fakes.
Are you mistaken?
Let's talk inside.
We'll talk here.
Take it.
Is it the mark of Zhenlang Pavilion?
Well...
The mark is real. But this thing...
You admitted it.
Everyone, Zhenlang Pavilion sold fake stuff.
[Zhenlang Pavilion]
They passed gold-plated bronze off as gold.
It's not true.
Stop quibbling.
Come on.
Show everyone the one we burned.
Have a look.
- Ladies and gentlemen. - Zhenlang Pavilion sells fake stuff.
True gold does not fear fire.
Zhenlang Pavilion
deceives people.
They sell fakes.
Fake.
Dishonest.
Listen to me.
- It's not ours. - Dishonest.
- Listen to me. - Dishonest.
- It's not ours. - You sell fakes.
It's not true.
Out of the way.
Back off.
[Zhenlang Pavilion]
Don't make trouble!
Back off.
What's going on?
It's good you're here.
Zhenlang Pavilion sells fakes.
They passed gold-plated bronze off as gold.
Take a look.
They deceived us.
It's not ours.
What do you have to say?
You said
it was a mark of Zhenlang Pavilion.
Everyone here heard it.
Right?
Yes.
- Fraud! - Fraud!
Silence!
Stop arguing.
Seal Zhenlang Pavilion.
You go with me.
Officer.
My master is out.
Could you please make an exception?
When my master comes back
and finds out the truth,
we will explain it to you and this gentleman.
Shut up. Or I'll rough you up.
- Arrest him! - Arrest him!
Mr. Xu.
You may leave.
Mr. Xu, have a seat.
Mr. Xu.
I heard Zhenlang Pavilion sold fakes.
It's under investigation.
The evidence is clear.
Mr. Xu, why don't you give it a push?
We didn't find any other fakes
in Zhenlang Pavilion.
You shouldn't take it seriously.
Zhenlang Pavilion used to belong to the Cui family.
Mr. Xu, please help me.
Zhenlang Pavilion sold fakes.
Yan Zijing is missing.
If you convict him and auction the shop,
maybe Yan Zijing will show up.
Master Yan usually
respects me.
If you auction Zhenlang Pavilion,
I'm willing to give you
all the jewelry in it.
I only want Zhenlang Pavilion.
Zheng Wu, what do you say?
I agree with Lady Shijiu.
Here's to you.
Lady Shijiu, you're generous.
Take the medicine.
Be careful. It's hot.
Thank you.
How do you have time
to study Go?
What?
Is the show over?
Yes.
Zhenlang Pavilion is sealed.
You're the owner.
But you don't seem to care at all.
Are you thinking of setting someone up?
What are you talking about?
Look what the Zheng family did to me.
Can I set someone up?
Don't pretend to be pathetic.
You've always been like that.
You value profits.
You plan ahead every time.
Am I that good?
You don't have to tell me.
I know all the people who are interested
in Zhenlang Pavilion.
Don't forget
that there is one person who is very calm.
Who is it?
What do you think?
Yeah.
Mr. Zhang didn't act.
Tell me.
Who's next?
Xu Nanying
is next.
Collusion between government and businessmen.
Xu Nanying is an official.
The matter in Yangzhou is hard to solve.
You don't want Zhenlang Pavilion.
You might as well burn it
like you burned the Cui's Pearl Farm.
The things that the Cui family get their hands on
are dirty.
I don't understand
why Prince Ying trusted Xu Nanying
and appointed him
as the Governor of Yangzhou.
Xu Nanying was a man of Prince Tan.
Later, he went to Prince Ying.
It's weird.
If Prince Ying wanted money,
he didn't have to trust Xu Nanying.
Maybe...
Maybe Xu Nanying has something on him.
Xu Lin didn't follow Xu Nanying
to Yangzhou.
It's your turn.
You're in a good mood these days.
You're really generous.
If I didn't do it,
Xu Nanying wouldn't have agreed.
Even if you succeed,
you can only get an empty Zhenlang Pavilion.
What's the point of that?
I can change the Black Dragon Bandits' stolen goods
and sell them at Zhenlang Pavilion.
It's also to help the Zheng family.
Have you forgotten
that Zheng Si died on this?
Are you scared?
Zheng Zhixing was stupid.
Lady Huan was noble.
What could they do?
Stop.
[Baicaojing House]
You should learn how to be a woman
instead of a businesswoman.
Zheng Zhiheng and Cui Shijiu went to Xu Nanying.
Xu Nanying intervened in the case of Zhenlang Pavilion.
Steward Zhao pretended to betray.
Zhenlang Pavilion
will soon be auctioned.
The more greedy you are,
the sooner you fail.
Cui Shijiu,
Zhenlang Pavilion
is yours now.
[Contract]
Um...
Wait.
We don't know where Yan Zijing is.
I want to see him alive and dead.
Is he really dead?
Or
he's just hiding.
Wait.
It went so smoothly for me
to get Zhenlang Pavilion back.
He went through a lot to get Zhenlang Pavilion.
Why did he give it up?
Is this a trap?
Are we being deceived?
Shijiu, you care too much about Yan Zijing.
No one in Yangzhou can threaten the Zheng family.
And no one can threaten us.
Be happy.
You got Zhenlang Pavilion back.
Zhenlang Pavilion is one of the important shops of the Cui family.
I took back Zhenlang Pavilion.
I have a chance
to revive the Cui Family.
What are you going to do after that?
Mr. Zheng.
The master asked you to go back as soon as possible.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'll
keep my word.
Tread carefully.
Don't worry.
I've never made a mistake.
I have a favor to ask you.
Qin Mu is unthoughtful.
He wants to depend on the Zheng family.
But the Zheng family won't really help him.
I'm worried he might get into trouble.
Baicaojing House...
Please take care of him.
I'll repay you.
Take whatever you like.
Mr. Qin.
It's all yours.
Mr. Xu.
Niao's boyfriend?
Shut up.
Mr. Qin.
♪Life flows like a boat, navigating joys and woes♪
♪Longing for distant shores♪
♪Aware this moment may tear my heart apart♪
♪Better to roam alone♪
♪Many depart, none return♪
♪How can we resist gazing at each other amid the blooms?♪
♪Your face glows like lanterns in the night♪
♪Love fades on the stone bridge, yet bonds remain♪
♪How can we endure the binds of longing?♪
♪Like a grand dream, a lone cup of wine♪
♪May this world hold♪
♪Both sorrow and warmth♪
♪To hide a broken heart away with laughter and tears♪
♪A debt across time awaits♪
♪A simple tale unfolds♪
♪Nothing compares to soft rice and sweet tea♪
♪May this fate intertwine♪
♪Half in regret, half in longing♪
♪Radiant memories tint your gaze♪
♪The world's bitterness♪
♪Still accompanies my dreams♪
♪Drifting afar on the shore of your life♪
♪Quietly watching over you♪