=The Youth Memories=
=Episode 19=
(Outpatient)
(Dispensary, Nurse Station)
My wound?
It... It's recovering very well.
Yanqiu, let me tell you this.
Now, I can... I can walk and jump.
It's true.
Just some flesh wounds.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not very busy lately.
How about I go and see you?
Yanqiu,
don't do that.
If you come,
who will take care of Dad?
Oh, I forgot that.
Don't worry about me.
Listen, Yanqiu.
In... In a few days,
I'm going back to the army.
I'm serious.
Where's Dad?
Put him on the phone.
I have to tell him the whole story.
He just fell asleep.
Forget it, then.
Let him have a good sleep.
If I wake him up,
he'll scold me.
Xiao Chunsheng, checkup time.
Be right there.
Yanqiu, I have to do the checkup.
I'll hang up.
You take care, too. And take care of Dad.
Bye.
Two pieces of shrapnel
are deep in your body.
The diameter is
between 0.3mm and 5.5mm.
We speculate
the two pieces of shrapnel
are compressing your spine
and nearby nerves
so that you have backache
and leg dysfunction.
Then Doctor,
can I recover?
Can I stand up and return to the army?
It depends on the operation you'll take.
When... When can I have the operation?
Come on, Doctor.
I'm OK with anything you say.
To tell you the truth,
our hospital
can't perform such an operation.
Spinal nerves are complicated.
Even the slightest lapse
can result in irreparable damage.
Is it possible
to have this operation in Beijing?
I've never worked in a hospital there.
But yes, I guess.
After all, medical conditions
in Beijing are much better.
There are many awesome doctors, too.
Would it be better
if he returns to Beijing soon?
If possible,
we certainly encourage
an early operation.
The conservative therapy
can't heal him, after all.
And,
his condition may get worse.
Well,
you think about it.
I'll go check on other patients.
Medical conditions here
are indeed limited.
But don't worry.
Later, I will call
my former colleagues
and ask them to contact an expert
who can give you another checkup.
You will get better.
(Unit One)
Xiaomei said,
he's all right.
Stop worrying, OK?
I can't.
Chunsheng never kept us worried.
He didn't tell us even when he was hurt.
Yunnan is so far away.
How can I know he wasn't lying?
Even if he lied, Xiaomei wouldn't.
Xiaomei always listens to him.
You're just worried about nothing.
That was just a false alarm.
Don't scare yourself.
You're off tomorrow.
How about we go out for a walk
in case you imagine things at home?
Chunsheng.
There you are, Lei.
Come on. Sit.
How do you feel now?
I'm fine. Be careful.
Be careful.
I'm OK. I'm OK.
Here.
Lei, have some fruit.
You know what?
It's from Guohua.
Don't waste it.
Chunsheng,
looks like
I misunderstood Platoon Leader Ye.
You have no idea.
When he and I went back for you,
the enemies were firing fiercely.
He charged forward desperately.
When he heard the explosion
in the minefield,
a man like him
fell to the ground
and wailed for you.
He is
a friend indeed.
Of course, he is.
He and I grew up together.
Come on, Lei.
You used to judge people with prejudice
and underestimate them.
Listen.
After we recover
and return to the army,
you have to cooperate with his work.
OK.
Well, it's also great for Guohua
to have a friend like you.
You don't know yet, huh?
It's quickly spreading.
What's spreading?
About Guohua.
He rushed alone into the enemy camp
and brought back M101 Coordinate.
He's now a big hero.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's great that Guohua became a hero.
Yeah.
But Chunsheng,
I'm confused about something.
Let me ask you.
How did you step on a landmine?
Previously,
we had the demining many times
and you never stepped on one.
I... I just...
I just had an accident.
What?
After I got wounded on the battlefield,
you would still criticize me?
Who would criticize you?
There you are, Guohua.
- Lei.
- Guohua.
Hongling.
Come on.
Your eyes nearly pop out.
Where were you talking about?
We? We talked about you.
I just told Chunsheng
you were a big hero
who brought back M101 Coordinate alone.
Impressive!
Lei,
it's about your checkup time, isn't it?
I...
Oh, that's right.
I... I should go.
You've got a poor memory.
Come on.
Be careful.
I'm OK, I'm OK.
I'll leave you all to chat.
Be careful.
I'm OK.
Lei, let me go with you.
OK.
Hongling.
Come on. Be seated.
What did the doctor say?
You're not doing well, huh?
Can you return to the army?
Don't be silly, girl.
The doctor said,
I'm recovering very well.
It's true.
One minute before you got in,
the doctor just left.
She said I could return after recovery.
You're not lying?
When did I ever lie to you?
Then promise me.
When we give a charity performance
to soldiers involved in the battle,
you have to walk there and watch it.
Why are you crying? Fine.
I promise you.
When you give the charity performance,
I'll walk there, OK?
If you aren't satisfied,
I can even carry you there.
What?
Why more tears?
I'm all right, see?
Don't cry.
Do you know how worried I was?
I even dreamed
that you couldn't come back.
I'm back and alive, aren't I?
But...
No buts.
Hongling,
I just promised you.
When you give the performance,
I will have recovered.
Rest assured.
Look.
You look bad when crying.
Smile.
Lei.
Were you talking to Chunsheng
about M101 Coordinate?
Yes.
Then why did you criticize him?
I didn't.
I'm just curious.
He always got full marks
in the demining training.
And why did he step on a mine there?
So weird.
What did Chunsheng say?
Before he could answer,
you disturbed us.
Look at Hongling.
She finally got some time to visit me,
but she didn't stay for a while.
Count your blessings.
The Art Troupe
has been giving performances everywhere.
It was hard for her
to spare some time
to visit you.
You made sense.
Chunsheng,
I have something to say.
I know what you're going to say.
About the hero thing, right?
Only the two of us know what happened.
Lift your foot.
Chunsheng.
I said lift your foot!
The credit is yours.
The honor belongs to you.
What's more,
you saved my life.
I just want to tell you.
Please don't get me wrong.
I never meant
to claim your credit.
I'm going to tell our superiors
what exactly happened.
Stop.
Sit.
Sit!
Ye Guohua, tell me.
Are we best buddies?
Yes, of course.
We're friends forever.
Then listen to me.
I'm all ears.
About the M101 Coordinate,
only you and I know.
I want no one else to be aware.
Why, Chunsheng?
Don't bother.
I have my own reason.
What reason?
Chunsheng,
take back the credit
and you'll be the hero.
After returning, you can be promoted.
Then you'll have a bright future.
Future?
Guohua, you know what?
Two pieces of shrapnel
are deep in my spine.
The diameter is
between 0.3mm and 5.5mm.
They are compressing
nearby nerves
so that I have backache
and leg dysfunction.
So serious?
Then, can you...
The doctor isn't sure, either.
If I want to recover,
I have to take an operation in Beijing.
I'm familiar with hospitals
and doctors in Beijing.
I'll contact them for you.
The doctor also said,
nerves around the spine are complicated.
Even if a doctor in Beijing
operates on me,
the slightest lapse
can result in irreparable damage.
Guohua,
do you know what it means?
It means
I may not be a soldier anymore.
For the rest of my life,
I may not even stand up.
So,
being the hero
doesn't mean anything to me.
Guohua, listen to me.
The credit for getting the M101 Coordinate
belongs to you alone.
Buddy,
you have to be the hero!
No, Chunsheng.
If I do this,
I'll feel sorry for you
for the rest of my life.
No, I can't do that.
Ye Guohua!
I'm not doing this for you.
Then for what?
For our dreams!
Guohua,
do you remember?
Since childhood, we've dreamed
to be a general.
But now, only you can
realize this dream for me.
So, you have to be the hero.
Only in this way
can we get closer to our dream.
Ye Guohua,
remember.
Go realize our dream
for me!
(Knowing about his poor condition,)
(Xiao Chunsheng gave up being a hero.)
(However, the Party Organization)
(will never deprive a hero)
(who contributes
to his nation and people.)
(The glory belonging to Xiao Chunsheng)
(will get back to him in the near future.)
Chunsheng,
I get your point.
Don't worry.
I'll try my best
to get you back on your feet.
Trust me.
I do.
(Serve the People)
(Develop art activities to consolidate
the socialist ideological front)
Commander,
the violinist
on the first row
is our concertmaster.
Her name is He Hongling.
She plays the best here.
The point is
soldiers like her performance.
How old is she?
21. Perfect age.
The percussion music can last longer.
Get her to me.
- OK.
- Let's try it again later.
Hongling, come over.
Greetings, Commander.
(Outpatient)
Chunsheng.
There you are, Hongling.
Here. Have an orange.
Thanks.
Chunsheng,
I have some good news to tell you.
What is it?
We can celebrate it for you.
This morning, a leader
from the Military Art Troupe
came to us.
He wanted me
to be part of the lecture tour.
Lecture tour?
What is that?
You don't know?
For heroes in the battle,
a lecture tour is arranged.
We'll give charity performances.
By the way,
Guohua also won an honor
and was awarded.
He even got a medal for the hero.
Now, he's a real hero
and he'll be part of the lecture tour.
That's great.
Great, Hongling.
I really feel happy for you and Guohua.
Chunsheng, when I'm on the tour,
I can't visit you for some days.
Rest very well for the recovery
and try to stand up as soon as possible.
I will.
Two pieces of shrapnel
are deep in Chunsheng's spine,
so he has leg dysfunction.
Such an operation can't be done here.
He has to return soon to Beijing
for the operation.
And the operation is risky.
If it doesn't work out very well,
he can't return to the army
or even stand up.
At this moment,
he needs you around him.
You should be early prepared.
(Warmly Welcome Heroes' Lecture Group)
(At his first lecture, Ye Guohua was)
(shy and nervous.)
(When it comes to the demining part,)
(he was on pins and needles.)
Xiaomei,
thank you
for taking me out for a walk.
I want a walk, too.
Xiaomei, don't worry.
I won't be easily defeated like this.
I know.
You're Comrade Xiao Chunsheng.
Come on.
Thank you, sir.
Sir, why did you give me an egg?
You're a hero.
And this is for your wife.
No, thanks.
Sir, she...
She isn't my wife.
Then she must be your girlfriend.
Fine. Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
You fought in the battle to protect us
and got so badly wounded.
Some eggs are no big deal.
Young man, don't lose heart.
In the future,
live with your girlfriend.
I believe
you will get better soon.
Don't worry.
I will recover.
Glad to hear that.
Thank you, sir.
Enjoy your food.
OK.
Here, Dr. Tong.
Chunsheng.
Xiaomei, faster.
But...
Xiaomei, faster. Come on.
Xiaomei.
Guohua.
Hongling?
You're still awake so late?
I can't fall asleep.
Did you call Chunsheng today?
Yes, before I left this morning.
How's he getting?
Do you know
about his condition?
Xiaomei told me a little.
Guohua,
can Xiao Chunsheng
really not stand up again?
Don't worry, Hongling.
I'll contact the best hospital
and the best doctors.
I'll have him cured at any cost!
Hope he can get back on his feet.
He will.
Oh, Guohua,
why were you stammering
when you gave a speech?
You sounded very unconfident.
Chunsheng
asked me not to tell
anyone else about something.
But you're not someone else, right?
I'm dying to say.
I have to tell you about this.
What is it?
That day,
I stepped on a landmine.
It was the enemy's territory
and I was doomed to die.
All I was thinking then was...
Then Chunsheng turned up.
I got my hope immediately.
He wanted to save me.
But how could it be that easy?
I know it's hard. So does he.
Instead of dying together,
I would rather die alone.
I asked him to leave,
but he just didn't.
Then I asked him,
"If we both die,
what will Hongling do?"
He didn't reply
but got down to the ground
to work on the landmine.
Even before I finished talking,
he pressed the spring,
asking me to lift my foot.
He had bloodshot eyes
as if he was crazy.
I didn't know why,
but I just lifted my foot.
Hongling,
I was ready to die, I promise.
I really didn't know
why I lifted my foot.
Now, every day,
I'm regretting it.
I regret not getting wounded
and I regret having my best buddy
suffer so much for me.
Guohua,
don't blame yourself.
I've been thinking recently.
Chunsheng isn't like other guys.
In the face of ideal and reality,
morality and benefit,
in the face of someone else's life
and his own life,
he seems
to always choose the former.
I've been trying to understand him
and I want to choose the same.
But I realize
that I can never be as good as him.
Fundamentally,
he's a hero.
But I am
an ordinary woman.
You're an ordinary man, too.
Hongling,
can you tell me
what I should do now?
Listen to Chunsheng
and go realize your common dream.
That's the biggest reward for him.
Hongling.
Ma'am.
Are you OK?
Yes.
You just visited Platoon Leader Ye, huh?
Yes. He's a very good friend of mine.
How's he now?
Maybe because it was his first speech
and he was too nervous.
I talked to him.
Now that you're friends,
take care of him.
To this lecture tour,
leaders are paying attention.
Get back for some sleep.
And the operation is risky.
If it doesn't work very well,
he can't return to the army
or even stand up.
At this moment,
he needs you around him.
You should be early prepared.
Hongling,
you have to seize this chance.
Regimental Commander Tao
thinks highly of you.
If you do a great job during the tour,
he'll give special permission
to make you the leader of our orchestra.
Then you'll be a cadre.
(Meanwhile,)
(something happened)
(and disturbed Xiao Chunsheng.)
(There was often no reply
back in his home.)
(Questioned many times by him,)
(Xiao Yanqiu confessed)
(that their father was sick
in hospital again.)
(Even though she said it wasn't serious)
(and their father could
leave the hospital soon,)
(Xiao Chunsheng still felt uneasy.)
(Warmly Welcome Heroes' Lecture Group)
When the war just started,
my comrades-in-arms
went to the battlefield,
thinking
we could finally make contributions
to our nation and people.
I wasn't capable enough
to bring back all my comrades-in-arms.
I don't deserve the title
as the combat hero.
(After giving some speeches,)
(Ye Guohua was more familiar.)
(He finally got into it.)
(When excited, he had tears in his eyes
and sounded sonorous.)
(He gave better and better speeches.)
(The applause burst out
and everyone was moved.)
(He Hongling, who sometimes
sat in the auditorium)
(had mixed emotions.)
(Ye Guohua already made his choice.)
(What about her?)
(Outpatient)
Is the man who visited you
Ye Guohua, the combat hero?
Did you take his temperature?
I'll give it to you.
Here.
Yes.
Ye Guohua is my platoon leader.
So, you were also in that battle, right?
Yes.
I was.
Were you wounded then?
Did you make the record?
When he comes again,
may I have his autograph?
(Nurse Station)
Hello, Yanqiu.
Yanqiu.
Yanqiu, tell me the truth.
What happened to Dad?
He passed away.
On the 25th, last month,
our father died.
At dinner,
he... he was all right.
In the middle of the night,
I heard a thump.
When I got into his room,
he was on the ground.
Cerebral hemorrhage.
When he was sent to the hospital,
he couldn't be saved.
He was muttering your name.
Chunsheng,
he was muttering your name.
Commander.
Be seated, please.
How do you feel recently?
For your information, Commander,
I'm doing very well now.
This isn't a visitation.
I came to see if you're doing OK.
As for your recovery,
we have asked the doctor.
If...
I mean if...
If the later treatment works out well,
we'll get you a clerical job.
And if...
If you want to be demobilized,
we'll also solve your problems
as far as we can.
Commander,
if possible,
I still want to return
as a soldier.
I understand your feelings.
But don't push yourself.
Comrade Xiao Chunsheng,
in life, there are many paths.
And every path has different scenery.
Remember.
When you put on this military uniform,
you can never take it off!
I heard about your father's death.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Throughout my father's life,
his only wish
was that I could be a soldier all my life.
But now,
I've failed him.
♪I planted a seed by the sea♪
♪Imagining what it would grow into♪
♪Warm sunshine nursed its sprouting♪
♪Then it glinted and blossomed♪
♪In my dream, I found a bookmark♪
♪Where a blue story was scribbled♪
♪In the story, I saw you and me♪
♪You told the story and I listened♪
♪I wish you a sweet life♪
♪Where you're never bothered♪
♪I wish myself the vast sea♪
♪Where I watch the tide ebb and flow♪
♪May love warm all waiting men♪
♪Telling stories in tears and smiles♪
♪May the world be fantastic as always♪
♪Casting its blue sunshine on the sea♪
♪I wish you a sweet life♪
♪Where you're never bothered♪
♪I wish myself the vast sea♪
♪Where I watch the tide ebb and flow♪
♪May love warm all waiting men♪
♪Telling stories in tears and smiles♪
♪May the world be fantastic as always♪
♪Casting its blue sunshine on the sea♪
♪I planted a seed by the sea♪
♪Imagining what it would grow into♪
♪Warm sunshine nursed its sprouting♪
♪Then it glinted and blossomed♪
♪In my dream, I found a bookmark♪
♪Where a blue story was scribbled♪
♪In the story, I saw you and me♪
♪You told the story and I listened♪