Lovers of the Red Sky
Kim Yoo Jung, Ahn Hyo Seob
Gong Myung, Kwak Si Yang
Lovers of the Red Sky
The characters and settings of this drama are fictional and have no connection to historical facts.
Are you all right? The palanquin is...
S-Scholar Sir?
What is wrong?
Are you unwell?
- I think you should get off now.
- Pardon?
So suddenly?
Man Su, stop the palanquin.
Pardon?
Yes, Supervisor Sir. Stop the palanquin.
Scholar Sir?
Scholar Sir, at least tell me your name.
Hurry, let's go.
- Man Su.
- Y-yes...
Yes, Supervisor Sir.
Supervisor?
Be careful on your way home.
Let's go.
One, two, three!
So suddenly...
Wait, Scholar Sir! Your name!
Sir...
Do I smell of sweat?
Darn.
Episode 3: Ma Wang
Will she be all right alone at night?
The capital is just ahead, but...
Sir?
I mean, how could he just tell me to get off so suddenly?
Is this the right way?
I wonder how Annoying One and Long Face are doing.
Whoa.
What's wrong with these people...
Hold on tightly.
The road is rough here.
The palanquin keeps shaking!
No, wait.
It's shaking too much.
Hold on!
Put down the palanquin!
What are you doing?
S-Sir, are you all right?
Whoa...
Sir?
What is that?
A tiger.
- A tiger!
- No!
It's a monster! A monster!
(Ha Ram Ma: when Ma Wang sealed in Ha Ram's body manifests himself)
Sir!
He's not here.
Dongang Gate
Run!
Hurry!
Get away!
You have made a mistake, Ha Ram.
You have left the palace on the winter solstice, when the yin energy is at its fullest*
(the day with most demonic and ghostly activities)
I found ...
my eyes.
(Changjeong Gate)
(King Seongjo, 4th king of the Dan Dynasty)
Your Majesty.
Are you all right?
Left State Minister, so you must have heard if you have ears.
There is a rumor...
that those owls are begrudging spirits, who had died unfairly at the palace.
The bloodshed by the late king in the palace
returned as begrudging spirits.
One or many...
they are only wild animals.
It is undeniable that every time an owl cries, someone falls ill or dies
It's the owls' nature to cry at night.
(Kim Hong Seo: Left State Minister, Senior 1st Rank)
Please do not concern yourself.
However, the old saying goes that
(Seong Jin Gi: Minister of Personnel, Senior 2nd Rank)
every time an owl cries in the village, a household is bereaved.
Minister of Personnel ...
do not cause worry for His Majesty with such foul words.
Your Majesty, there is no doubt it is an ominous foreshadowing.
Has Supervisor Ha not returned from Inwang Mountain yet?
I must discuss it with him in person.
He is on duty at the astronomical observatory until tomorrow morning.
Why do you seek a man like Supervisor Ha every time something like this happens?
I will ask Supervisor Jang of the Astronomy and Meteorology Bureau to relay to Supervisor Ha to return immediately.
How can a king earn his people's respect
should such strange happenings continue?
Senior Eunuch, tell them to perform the Cleansing Ritual as soon as dawn breaks.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Are you not the attendant who works for Supervisor Ha?
What are you doing here like that?
(Man Su: page belonging to Ha Ram's household)
Supervisor Jang, please find Supervisor Ha!
There has been a disaster in Inwang Mountain.
What...
What disaster? Tell me more.
(Jang Wuk Jin: supervisor of the geography division at the Astronomy and Meteorology Bureau)
We were passing the upper mountains
when we heard the sky rip open
and the palanquin broke
and something like a monster appeared in the sky.
And Supervisor Ha...
Child, where are you going in such haste?
Grandma, what are you doing here?
Come here and get warm.
Oh, the fire.
Thank you for the offer, but I must be going.
It's cold.
You will be very cold.
Oh, my...
Why is it suddenly so cold?
I will stay for only a little while.
This is the payment for your father's painting.
Father's painting...
You should pay me separately for that, Grandma.
This is plenty. Don't speak nonsense.
Nothing is free in this world.
My goodness, you young thing. So stubborn.
Grandma, you shouldn't be in a place like this on the winter solstice.
You should go down with me later...
I smell it for certain.
Is it there?
Please hurry.
W-w-what is that?
- What is that?
- A monster!
A monster!
What?
How long was I here?
Oh, no. I'll get a lecture from Gyeonju Daek again.
I should be going, Grandma.
Wait, it is not time yet.
I have a long way to go.
You should come down soon, Grandma.
- W-wait, hold...
- Come down soon!
Wait, no, no, no, no!
Is it there?
Blast it.
She is making it difficult.
I cannot let her meet Ho Ryeong.
Ho Ryeong?
I am Ho Ryeong, guardian spirit of Inwang Mountain.
This is the land I rule.
Be gone from this mountain!
Foolish divine beast.
Long time no see, Ho Ryeong.
Long time no see, grandmother Sam Shin.
Wait.
It is not time yet.
Are you asking me to let Ma Wang go?
Ma Wang doesn't die.
He is only trapped in that body.
Once that man dies, Ma Wang will be released and free.
Sam Shin...
We must expel Ma Wang from that man's body
and seal him in an eternal vessel.
An eternal vessel?
That child will make it.
Do you truly believe that a defenseless girl can make the vessel that will seal Ma Wang?
When the time comes, she will make it.
She is the child of destiny.
We must protect those two until then.
However, my powers only extend to this mountain and the king's palace.
I cannot guarantee that I will be able to do it.
To protect the humans is to protect the mountain.
When Ma Wang awakens,
blood will be shed again.
Om ahum sabaha.
I was walking just now.
Where am I?
Why am I here?
Ow... my head.
Help me!
Hey, get off...
What?
Hello?
S-Scholar sir?
Sir!
Wait, where did those palanquin bearers go?
Sir! Sir!
Sir! Open your eyes, Sir!
Sir, get up!
I have never in my life been so benevolent.
I cannot do this for nothing in return.
Hello?
Madam Seosan Daek?
Help me!
Have they all gone to find firewood for the winter?
This is where they make paint...
It may smell quite pungent,
but it cannot be helped.
Hold on.
The room is too cold.
Wait right here, Scholar Sir.
I've got it!
♫  My feelings for you?  ♫
♫  I hold onto you like destiny and can't leave you  ♫
♫  I was you and you were me  ♫
♫  I love you, I love you, only you  ♫
What should I do?
♫  So we don't pass each other  ♫
If I don't finish the painting by tonight, the headmaster will have a fit.
♫  I will be here  ♫
Whatever. Let me save him first.
No fever.
Breathing well.
Scholar Sir?
Scholar Sir! Wake up!
- Stop it!
- Ha Ram!
I can't see!
No!
What on earth has happened to him?
Help me!
Help me! You have to help me.
What is it?
They are dead.
They are all dead.
What do you mean all the royal guards died last night?
Are you saying Supervisor Ha also died?
- What of Supervisor Ha?
- Supervisor Ha is nowhere to be found.
We have selected nimble guards to search every corner of Inwang Mountain, Your Majesty.
Senior Eunuch, send a eunuch to Grand Prince Yangmyeong.
He is close to Supervisor Ha, so he will know where he could be.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, forgive me,
but you cannot send His Highness to find a mere supervisor.
Enough!
That is enough.
(Mu Yeong: Il Wol Seong's bodyguard)
Simcheonggak
(Name of the gisaeng house)
Urgent Report: Il Wol Seong disappeared near Imwang Mountain.
Boss, Boss, Boss!
Boss, something's happened! Something big!
- Something big has happened. Elder Il Wol Seong has disappeared.
- Is that true?
What? Sir Il Wol Seong has disappeared?
What? Il Wol Seong has disappeared?
Move!
How does that even make sense?
I told you to catch Hong Cheon Gi and you give me this unbelievable excuse?
It's true...
Did she disappear in the sky or into the ground?
What is taking you so long to catch Baegyu Painting Institute's Hong Cheon Gi just within the marketplace?
I was dragged to the Police Bureau and closed down Wolseongdang because of her.
Get out and bring her here!
Yes, Hyeong-nim!
I hear her mad father is always on the market streets.
Should I bring him instead?
Hey, you should break that wench's hand.
What are we going to do with that crazy man?
What did I tell you when you first came here?
I told you to keep your boundaries even as a thug, no?
Listen carefully!
We... don't mess with the elderly and children.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
Wise words.
Boundaries are meant to be kept, not to be crossed.
- I hear there was an unseemly incident.
- Yes, sir.
There was a minor misunderstanding that we had sold fake paintings.
A minor misunderstanding made you go to jail?
No, not the jail. I was only questioned briefly at the bureau.
- I was released without charges.
- Was it really a misunderstanding?
That you pocketed the money for fake paintings?
That is absolutely untrue! I would never!
This painting must be real.
Your face is pale.
I will deal with you when I get back.
When the master returns, he will make an appropriate judgement.
When he comes back?
Il Wol Seong is really missing?
Master has disappeared.
Soma... let's go.
(Yi Yul, Grand Prince Yangmyeong, third son of Seongjo)
(Han Geon: Master Painter of the Painting Bureau)
As expected, the master of Sansuhwa*,
(landscape painting)
Park Yi deserves his fame.
Observe this mountain drawn like the head of the cloud, and like furled mist.
The clean ink use gives off the effect of dreamy clouds.
The boulders look like moving clouds.
Looking at the mountain, the trees, and the boulders,
I'm in complete awe at the exquisite brush strokes.
It is a true masterpiece with the spirit of nature filling the empty spaces.
You know what you are talking about.
This Sochundo* truly is a divine realm
(small spring scape)
eagerly to be looked upon, visited, and roamed in.
But...
what is this?
Is this not a butterfly?
That is impossible.
Could this be...
It seems to be a counterfeit!
Counterfeit?
Yes.
I hear imitation artists leave secret signatures on their works.
Who would dare make a copy of Park Yi's work?
Is it even possible to copy the aura as well?
Is this truly counterfeit?
I bought this from Wolseongdang.
Jeong Soen Nae.
It must be true that the merchant was taken to the Police Bureau for selling fake paintings.
What a ridiculous new-born puppy!
Your Highness, someone is here from the palace.
Supervisor Ha of the Astronomy and Meteorology Bureau disappeared last night during field work.
What?
That gentle soul, Supervisor Ha has disappeared?
You mean he is missing?
Yes, Your Highness.
All the guards who left to search for him returned as corpses.
Corpses?
What is the meaning of this?
As of now, no one knows what has happened.
The Royal Investigation Bureau has started investigating, so there will be news soon.
But His Majesty asks Your Highness to search for Supervisor Ha personally,
as time is of the utmost importance.
I understand. You may go now.
I shall go at this moment.
This way.
Goodness.
Look, Master Painter Han.
While I look for Supervisor Ha,
find me that cheeky imitation painter.
Yes, Your Highness.
Is it true that Supervisor Ha disappeared and the royal guards died?
- And the culprit?
- They have not caught him yet.
This incident is particularly mysterious.
Mysterious?
Your Highness, it is I, Mi Su.
(Yi Hu, Grand Prince Juhyang, second son of Seongjo)
Have you heard about the tragic ends of the guards?
Yes.
In addition, a parliament of owls cried at the palace last night.
(Mi Su: 4th Head Shaman of Seongjucheong, the Royal Shamanist Bureau)
A parliament of owls?
They say if a parliament of owls cry on the ridge of the palace roof,
calamities occur. Thus we perform the Cleansing Ritual.
On the night of the winter solstice, when the energy of yin is the strongest,
owls cried, and the guards met horrific deaths.
It cannot be a coincidence.
Then...
I must check the corpses of the dead guards.
Goodness, Father!
Goodness!
Aigoo!
The night was cold, and the room was small, so I...
I've shamelessly disrespected you.
Forgive me.
Forgive me, Scholar Sir. Forgive me.
Judging by his clothes,
he seems to be a high-ranking noble.
You are so gorgeous.
After leaving me in such a hurry, you should have arrived at your destination safely.
If I had known that this would happen,
I would have thrown a fit until you told me your name.
Scholar Sir? Are you awake now?
Wait one moment.
Scholar Sir, do you hear me?
Open your eyes.
Scholar Sir!
Who are you?
Speak! Where am I?
This is a pigment studio in Inwang Mountain.
I saw you unconscious
-  Her voice is familiar.
- and it didn't feel right to leave you there.
So I brought you to a place I knew nearby.
It's that woman from yesterday.
I'm the painter that you saved inside the palanquin yesterday.
Are you all right now?
I apologize.
What has happened to me?
That is what I would like to ask you, Sir.
You were lying unconscious by the roadside.
There was no one around?
No. The palanquin bearers were gone
and your clothes were tattered.
Do you not remember anything?
My head feels as if it's splitting open.
I do not remember anything.
You can take your time remembering then.
For now, you must take care of yourself...
Sir?
Sir!
Oh, no...
This won't do. I'll call a trustworthy physician.
So... Man Su, is it?
Yes, Your Highness.
You do not know precisely when Supervisor Ha disappeared?
Would you believe that yourself?
Why did you leave Supervisor Ha by himself to disappear?
Could it be that you did it intentionally?
I would never!
That is absolutely untrue.
The mountain path was dark
and the palanquin exploded suddenly
so I could not take care of the supervisor properly.
This is all my fault, Your Highness.
Who keeps the ledger of the property records of Supervisor Ha, the richest man in Gwanyang?
I... I would not know about that...
I see.
Could it be that you conspired in Supervisor Ha's kidnapping to find that out?
No, Your Highness!
I sensed the presence of a monster.
It could have been a tiger.
Did you have a dream?
A monster in our bright and luminous world? Does that even make sense?
Think about it.
Except for Supervisor Ha, the palanquin carriers and you, all survived.
What could be the reason for that?
Man Su.
It is not difficult.
Only speak of what you know.
Spill the beans while I am telling you nicely.
Before I bring out a cudgel to have you beaten up
This is not fair, Your Highness...
I may only be a palace page,
but I swear to the heavens I have never been disloyal to the supervisor.
How could I...
How could I do that to Supervisor Ha...
I'm desperate to find him.
Enough. Enough.
You are still a child.
Come on. Mum.
Stop crying.
I see you are not lying.
Well, how... How could you even suggest—
Well then. Let's go.
Where to, Your Highness?
The place where Supervisor Ha disappeared.
Gyeonju Daek! Gyeonju Daek!
(Gyeonju Daek: Housekeeper at Baegyu Painting Institute)
Gyeonju Daek is busy.
Come now, Gyeonju Daek.
It is urgent.
Where did a full-grown woman stay out all night?
Can't you even tell me where you're going?
The headmaster didn't sleep a wink, worried sick.
Do you not think of those waiting for you?
Gosh, he blamed me so much, saying it was all my fault.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
But something truly urgent has happened.
Just listen to me this once!
Did you stuff my instructions into the gutter?
Headmaster.
I seem to have let you be too relaxed these days.
What were you thinking-
Did I not tell you that the right hand is a painter's dear life?
Why did you hurt yourself again?
I'm sorry.
Please do not be so angry, headmaster.
There is a scholar who had an accident.
Please help him, headmaster.
A scholar?
I see that you're not remorseful.
Must I punish you to make you come to your senses?
That's not it! He is the man who saved my life.
He is unconscious now, so I have not heard his story,
but he surely had an accident.
Please just help him first and then I'll accept any punishment.
Please, headmaster!
This won't do. Lock her in the shed immediately!
- Yes, Sir!
- No!
Headmaster, you can't!
Please help me, just once!
Headmaster!
Gyeonju Daek!
Gyeonju Daek! Uncle Chun Bok!
Headmaster!
Aigoo. A man is all she could think of.
She failed to think on her feet.
All right, sit.
Your paw.
- Are you sure it doesn't bite?
- No.
- Go Pil.
- Yes, Your Highness.
Aigoo...
I have prepared as you asked,
but among all this chaos, must we bring along search dogs?
Go Pil! This is a matter of great urgency.
Do you think Supervisor Ha went sightseeing or something?
Aigoo. Of course not, Your Highness.
Good. As long as you know.
Man Su.
- You take the lead.
- Yes.
Pardon?
What are you doing?
I shall draw with you.
FInish that sehwa before sundown!
Ah!
I'm coming in.
Aigoo.
Gyeonju Daek, you have to help me.
Gyeonju Daek can't hear you.
I met a handsome man as fair as a fairy in the mountain.
Seriously, I've heard that countless times.
I meant to ask this earlier.
Did you have a dream or something?
If you don't believe me, come with me then.
This isn't the first time I've been tricked by your foolery.
Don't you have any conscience?
Eat up.
How can I eat right now?
I say someone is dying! Isn't everyone being too indifferent?
I'm not eating!
My gosh...
And?
That man dropped straight from the sky and just fainted.
Maiden!
Where are you?
I don't know which family he is from,
but he seems to be highly educated.
He is dressed like a noble scholar.
The man can't even see...
and he fainted again right after he woke.
I couldn't tell where he was injured.
Could it be...
he is being chased because he is part of a group who plotted treason?
Nonsense, my goodness.
In any case, if that is true,
how unfortunate is that...
What should we do?
Maybe we have to call a Chim Ui*?
Yes! That's it!
I came down here to call a physician.
There is no time to waste like this.
We must hurry to the pigment studio in Inwang Mountain.
You like that scholar that much?
What are you talking about?
I owe him my life.
I see.
All right.
Then I must help you.
You mean it? You'll help me?
Yes, I will.
But are you sure he is not married?
Gosh. What in the world are you talking about?
I don't remember anything.
This is the first time after Father passed away.
Last night in the palanquin, I encountered a woman exuding a strong scent of ink.
I thought she headed to town after getting off the palanquin,
but she nursed me...
while I was unconscious.
Could this be a mere coincidence?
My missing memories...
and meeting of a maiden who resembles her...
What on earth... could this all mean?
Take your time.
Careful, careful.
Pull gently. Right.
There is no trace of life left...
It must be the doing of Ma Wang.
As expected.
Is it related to Supervisor Ha's disappearance?
Darn it.
I do not know who you are, but you can't be here.
Leave.
How Insolent!
He is the Grand Prince Juhyang.
Goodness!
We did not recognize you, Your Highness!
He is following his majesty's secret order and covertly searching for the truth behind this case.
You must not speak of the fact that his highness came here.
You must watch your mouth!
Yes, madam.
Secure the corpses of the guards
and be careful of what you say.
I'm sure Mu Yeong must be looking for me.
Seeing as Soma can't get here right away,
I must be deep in the mountains.
Where did that woman go?
Why?
The memories...
of the peach tree field girl ...
keep overlapping with that woman.
My goodness!
Is this the spot?
The site of the guards' murder.
- I do not know who you are, but you can't-
- Insolence!
This is Grand Prince Yangmyeong!
My goodness!
Aigoo!
We did not recognize you, Your Highness.
- Why does this keep happening today?
- I don't know.
There is no quality of living beings in these bodies.
It is truly bizarre.
So, what seems to be the cause of their death?
It is truly mysterious.
They are not normal cut wounds caused by swords and spears,
but strange tears and partial burns on the skin.
Judging by the external appearance, it does not seem to be done by a human being.
Not done by a human being?
This leaf here...
I sensed the presence of a monster.
It could have been a tiger.
Are there any survivors?
Supervisor Jang Wuk Jin of the Astronomy and Meteorology Bureau was the sole survivor.
Is that so?
Listen up. We must find Supervisor Ha before sundown.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, sir!
Chase them.
Gyeonju Daek! I didn't realize you are so fast, like a flying squirrel.
You say he is a nobleman.
I'm dying here.
Slimming down while working.
We're killing two birds with one stone! Exert yourself a bit more!
Cheon Gi!
What?
Oh, no. Scholar Sir!
Sir!
- Darn it.
- Your Highness!
My goodness! Are you all right?
Dear me!
This is expensive.
Over here! Come help me!
Yes, sir.
Aigoo. Here.
You must be cold.
Agh, Go Pil!
This smell is too...
This is all because I work hard for you.
The dogs seem to have caught a scent.
- Go follow them.
- Yes, Your Highness.
Follow the dogs!
Follow the dogs! Let's go.
Soma, you're here.
- I've looked everywhere for you.
- You're here.
What has happened?
I don't remember at all.
- How did you find me here?
- I followed Soma.
Grand Prince Yangmyeong is looking for you himself.
Why did even the grand prince get involved?
I hear misfortune has befallen the royal guards who were sent to look for you in Inwang Mountain.
I also saw Grand Prince Yangmyeong's group on my way here.
They had search dogs with them, so it is a matter of time before they get here.
Then I must wait here.
Yes, sir.
Someone is coming.
Scholar Sir! You are awake.
I was worried sick about you.
Are you feeling better?
- It is you.
- Yes, it's me.
Did someone come by already?
No.
Where have you been?
I thought you were in urgent need of care so I left to bring a physician.
You're not well.
Please go inside. The wind is cold.
I feel better now.
Well... If it's not discourteous,
I would like to know your name.
My name?
Hong...
- Hong...
- Hong Hong Hong?
Is your name truly Hong Hong Hong?
I mean... No, that's not it.
It's Hong Cheon Gi.
Hong Cheon Gi?
The peach tree field... from 19 years ago.
She has the same name as that girl.
♫  Whichever way the wind blows  ♫
♫  Wherever my feet lead me  ♫
♫  I can walk without a moment's rest  ♫
♫  Wherever you are, I ask you to stay  ♫
♫  Even on sunny days filled with the most radiant sunshine  ♫
♫  Only you could blind me  ♫
♫  I don't think I can live without you  ♫
♫  I miss you no matter what I do  ♫
♫  Is it me who lives in your heart?  ♫
♫  The one you miss endlessly?  ♫
♫  I may not be, you may hate me  ♫
♫  I'll stay by your side like destiny.  ♫
Lovers of the Red Sky
Preview
You and I are acquaintances now.
- Is anyone here?
- Who are you?
Insolence! Do you know who I am?
Do people like us... not have the right to protect our homes if Your Highness comes in?
Maejukheon Painting Contest.
If you get first place, His Highness will grant whatever you wish.
Must you do it at Maejukheon?
This is the beginning.
Do you truly not intend to send me to the painting contest?
Never.
Because you think I'll go mad like Father while painting?
I'm from the Baegyu Painting Institute.
That woman...
Her voice is familiar. Could she be ...?
♫  Is it me who lives in your heart?  ♫
♫  The one you miss endlessly?  ♫
Lovers of the Red Sky