Lovers of the Red Sky
Kim Yoo Jung, Ahn Hyo Seob
Gong Myung, Kwak Si Yang
Lovers of the Red Sky
The characters and settings of this drama are fictional and have no connection to historical facts.
If it's not discourteous, I would like to know your name.
My name?
It's Hong Cheon Gi.
What is your father like?
My father?
He is a painter...
who paints on the market streets everyday.
Is it truly her?
I see.
I will repay you for your kindness.
I shall remember your name.
There's no need.
You saved me first.
But why are you out here?
You should be lying down.
No one was here, so I came out to seek a way for myself.
- I just met you and caused so much trouble.
- Not at all.
You and I are acquaintances now.
I'm afraid you will catch a cold.
You should go inside until the physician comes.
I will help you.
All right.
Are you really better?
Isn't that the missing Supervisor Ha of the Astronomy and Meteorology Bureau?
(Seomungwan: a government office in charge of astronomy, weather, and making almanacs)
Pardon?
That man?
That is the son of Ha Seong Jin,
that divine child from back then.
As expected, Ma Wang entered that child's body on the day of the Rain Ritual.
Your Highness.
We should move after observing a little longer.
(Yi Hu, Grand Prince Juhyang, second son of Seongjo)
Thank you.
Well then. Rest here for a while.
Episode 4: Red String of Fate
(Yi Yul, Grand Prince Yangmyeong, third son of Seongjo)
Is anyone here?
Who are you?
I'm looking for someone.
Have you seen a man in an Astronomy Bureau uniform last night, by any chance?
Astronomy Bureau uniform?
Was that an Astronomy Bureau uniform?
I should pretend not to know for now.
No, I haven't seen any.
- I must check.
- Wait!
What are you doing barging into someone's house?
There is a man who is ill here.
-You cannot barge in without the owner's consent.
- You!
How dare you get in my way!
Insolence!
Do you know who I am?
You!
How should I know that?
This will not do.
I am a man of good looks,
called the Man of Three Skills
for my excellence in poetry, literature, and painting.
I am the grand prince of this nation,
Yangmyeong.
I truly meant to show you my utmost respect.
If you are the Grand Prince Yangmyeong,
I am...
the Grand Princess Consort* of that Grand Prince Yangmyeong!
(Title of a Grand Prince's wife)
You are quite bold.
I may be wearing smelly clothes now, but—
Gutsy?
All right.
Let us pretend you are the Grand Prince.
Then do people like us
not have the right to protect our homes if Your Highness comes in?
What law is that?
Is the name Grand Prince Yangmyeong a pass?
I have never experienced something like this in my life.
This is quite awkward.
I was born as a grand prince and lived as a grand prince.
Thus, I only know how to speak like a grand prince.
One would think you really were the Grand Prince.
But that won't work with me.
You cannot ever go inside.
You must hurry and go back.
I say I am the Grand Prince.
- Let me just—
- Go back!
- I only want to see the ins—
Maiden.
What is it?
Is someone here?
Supervisor Ha!
Scholar Sir!
You were alive! You survived!
Is it not Grand Prince Yangmyeong?
Yes.
Are you all right?
- You are not injured anywhere?
- No.
I'm not gravely injured.
My, that is a relief.
Do you know how worried I was?
My apologies, Your Highness.
Milord Grand Prince Yangayeong!
Supervisor Sir!
- Supervisor Sir!
- Milord Grand Prince!
Yes, Man Su.
Are you all right?
- Are you really all right?
- I'm all right.
Did you walk all the way here all night?
I was on my way to the Inwang Mountain observatory last night
and fainted inside the palanquin.
I do not remember anything after that.
When I woke up, I was here.
Gosh. What a mystifying incident.
Anyhow, I am glad you are safe.
Come.
- Let us go back.
- Yes, Your Highness.
Let's go down.
- Yes, Your Highness!
Wait, stop!
Go Pil.
Where did that gutsy woman go?
A woman? I did not see her.
She was about this tall and wearing a red skirt.
That woman.
I'm not sure...
Your Highness, there was a lady who cared for me through the night.
Perhaps you are looking for her.
I see...
Perhaps she was trying to protect you.
Where did she go?
I do not know.
She hid somewhere like a stray cat.
I cannot see her all of a sudden.
Well then. We shall go back down with Supervisor Ha.
- Let's go!
- Yes, Your Highness.
One moment, Your Highness.
- Are you finished?
- Yes.
All right, let us go.
Let's go.
Supervisor Ha and Yangmyeong.
Are they just friends? Or...
As expected, Supervisor Ha is suspicious, Your Highness.
Why were there no signs all these years?
We will find out once we investigate.
Gosh, I'm dying here.
Cheon Gi.
Where is he?
There no trace of life left in those bodies...  It must be the doing of Ma Wang.
It was a m-monster.
It does not make sense if it was not a monster!
I fainted inside the palanquin. I do not remember anything.
Supervisor Ha is suspicious, Your Highness.
Wounds like these do not heal on their own.
You must encounter the being that first gave you this wound.
It was Ma Wang.
It was Ma Wang who came into my body and gave me this incurable wound.
I must find him.
Without fail.
What?
Did something inhuman kill the royal guards?
Yes. I have never seen corpses like those.
They looked like sword wounds, but they are black as if burnt
and their life force seems to have been sucked dry.
I see.
Yul.
How are the preparations for Maejukheon Painting Contest* coming along?
(lit: Painting Gathering at Plum Blossom and Bamboo Manor)
The preparations are underway as planned.
I must ask you a favor in regard to the contest.
Please order me to do anything, Royal Father.
Your Majesty, Supervisor Ha of the Astronomy Bureau is here.
You realize what you have done wrong.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You did not take care of yourself and protect yourself.
That is your wrongdoing.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
I shall forgive you if you can give a clear explanation
of something ominous that happened while you were away.
- Ask, Your Majesty.
- A parliament of owls cried at Eunjeongjeon last night.
Every time owls cry, people say that they are begrudging spirits of this nation.
Your Majesty, owls represent wealth.
It is because after acquiring food, they stock them.
It could be read as wealth and authority for the throne.
Additionally, owls are animals of wisdom that brighten up the darkness.
That such sacred animals sat on the roof of Eunjeongjeon...
You mean this is a good omen?
But the royal guards have lost their precious lives.
Is all this only coincidence?
Your Majesty, I may speak out of turn, but
is it truly the owls that cause you unease?
I cannot deceive you.
Sit comfortably.
A month later, the envoys from Yeon Empire will arrive.
The Emperor's brother, Yu Si Hong, will be a part of the envoy.
The Crown Prince is inexperienced and won't be able to deal with them.
I shall take care of this and then abdicate, making the Crown Prince ascend the throne.
So, find me an auspicious day for the abdication.
Do you mean...
Yes.
It is time for me to step down.
My health is declining rapidly.
I cannot help but worry for the country.
However, Your Majesty,
I hear an unknown disease is spreading in the Crown Prince's body.
Yes.
I heard from the royal physician.
He will gradually recover from his sickness.
Your Majesty, I put my life on the line to say a word.
We cannot disregard the possibility of the Grand Prince Juhyang
with his great spirit, or the Grand Prince Yangmyeong who's highly respected by the court, ascending the throne.
Abdicating hastily and giving the throne to the ill Crown Prince in the midst of such a state of affairs—
You must know...
that neither my father nor I were the eldest, thus the rightful heir.
Every time there was drought and famine, the people would criticize me,
saying that the heavens do not approve of me.
Your Majesty, how could you say such things?
You do not understand the animosity of the people when the rightful eldest doesn't ascend the throne.
Thus, the Crown Prince must ascend the throne as soon as possible and have his legitimacy acknowledged.
No matter what happens after that.
♫  Can you see my feelings for you?  ♫
I wonder if he made it back safely.
♫  I hold onto you like destiny and can't leave you  ♫
I wonder if she made it back safely.
♫  I am still like this  ♫
Ilhwaekseong.*
(the spirit of the artist shown at the moment the brush touches the paper)
It means you end with a single brush stroke.
It also means you cannot undo a stroke.
Only when you can contain vitality, meaning, and virtue into a single brushstroke,
you can express the vividness and liveliness of a painting.
♫  I love you, I love you, only you  ♫
♫  So we don't pass each other like the passing breeze,  ♫
♫  I will be here  ♫
True, how could I have hoped for such a thing?
It's impossible for me to have such a relationship.
(Gyeonju Daek: Baegyu Painting Institute's housekeeper)
What are you muttering about?
Are you still thinking about that scholar or that "divine being" at the paint-making house?
Fine.
I did something good, and now I should forget.
Forget about it.
Cheon Gi, what are you doing?
- Come see this.
- What?
Come on.
Come.
What is it?
Ah! It has happened, finally. Finally, it's happening.
The anticipated and longed-for Maejukheon Painting Contest.
The Grand Prince Yangmyeong, skilled in painting and literature
has prepared this contest for the sake of daubers like us.
It has been so many years since the last one.
If you are the Grand Prince Yangmyeong,
I am the Grand Princess Consort of that Grand Prince Yangmyeong!
- This is the opportunity of a lifetime.
- Goodness!
Don't shove your face everywhere.
Cheon Gi, the headmaster is looking for you.
(Kang Chun Bok: Chief Steward at Baegyu Painting Institute)
(Choi Won Ho, Headmaster of Baegyu Painting Institute)
Do you know why I called you?
You don't want me to attend the Maejukheon Painting Contest.
No.
You can attend the contest.
- Do you really mean it?
- Of course.
Once you finish the commissioned sehwas
and finish the hwajohwa folding screen for Lord Choi—
You're just telling me not to go.
I only mean you should finish your work before you go.
I never said you couldn't go.
Fine.
If I finish them on the appointed date,
you will put my name on the contest participant list.
Don't go back on your word.
That, that...
What if she really finishes them?
Why would you promise her such a thing?
It would take all the painters working together a week to finish it.
By the appointed date? Never. Impossible.
♫  I prayed earnestly and searched the darkness  ♫
♫  The moon once covered by clouds shines upon us  ♫
♫  Even though my heart is torn and tears blur my vision  ♫
♫  I cannot hold your hands for you  ♫
♫  Our love hurt so and our love was earnest  ♫
♫  I won't let go anymore  ♫
♫  I will protect you by your side  ♫
The fifth star in the constellation is shining.
The 27th constellation is two degrees to the right.
♫  My heart is full of your scent  ♫
♫  Deep within it, there is only you  ♫
Gather, everyone.
Here is the list of attendees for the Maejukheon Painting Contest.
- I'm there!
- My name is there.
Me, too!
Headmaster!
Have you really excluded my name?
First bring me the paintings you promised to finish by today.
Hey.
What are you...
- What are you doing?
- I'll add my name to the list.
No. If the headmaster finds out, he will have my head.
Give that back.
Since when did you obey the headmaster?
I wonder if the headmaster knows that you meet Gangho Daek in the neighboring town every day.
- Gangho Daek!
- How did you..? That's a secret!
- Hush! Promise me.
All right.
(Hong Cheon Gi)
There.
Here you go.
Cheon Gi, deliver this list yourself.
- What?
- I'm too nervous to take it.
I don't know anything about this. Nothing, nothing!
All right, I'll take care of it!
Wait. I need to go to Maejukheon to deliver the list.
And there...
Grand Prince Yangmyeong?
What should I do?
He wouldn't recognize me like this, right?
This is too stuffy.
Cheon Gi, you cannot sully these clothes.
You must make sure to return them to me by tomorrow.
Well. I'll just be careful and return quickly.
Scholar Sir...
how was your day today?
Maejuk...
Is it here?
How grand.
I wonder if you have recovered.
There are carps.
If we meet again like that day by chance,
I would like to paint your face then.
Who...
goes there?
I see the wine pot of Gao Wen Ji
I asked who you are.
He wouldn't remember even if I told him.
I'm here to deliver the attendee list from Baegyu Painting Institute.
It's that woman from the paint-making house.
Grand Prince Yangmyeong is not in at the moment.
Then, I shall leave the list here and go.
- Well then.
- Wait.
Could it be...
What are you doing?
Your voice is familiar.
Are you not Hong Cheon Gi from the paint-making house?
Pardon?
Have I offended you so much that you will not greet me?
No!
No.
That's not it...
The truth is, I've been disrespectful to the Grand Prince—
What, did you confess your feelings for him?
The Grand Prince looked for you as we left the paint-making house.
I was wondering what had happened.
Well...
That day at the paint-making house, I said to the Grand Prince Yangmyeong...
"If you are the Grand Prince Yangmyeong, I am...
the Grand Princess Consort of that Grand Prince Yangmyeong!"
I said that aloud.
Don't laugh like that.
I knew you would not understand
how serious this is.
So...
what are we doing here?
You would not understand even if I told you.
So why did you come all the way to Maejukheon, risking to be seen by Grand Prince Yangmyeong?
I had to deliver the list of attendees to the painting contest.
Give that to me and go on your way.
I shall relay it to him.
- You would do that?
- Of course.
I will work out your misunderstanding, as it was my fault.
Apologies- I mean,
you have graced me with your kindness!
Then, I shall leave the list with you and get going.
One moment.
Supervisor Ha, you're here.
Your Highness.
Hold on.
Who are you?
That woman is...
the stray cat from the paint-making house.
Your Highness.
You!
Wait.
I was looking for you.
I don't know what you mean.
I think you have mistaken me for someone else.
Is that so?
I will know if you face me.
(Baegyu Painting Institute)
What are you doing?
Forgive me!
(Baegyu Painting Institute)
Baegyu Painting Institute.
I know Headmaster Choi well.
Are you from Baegyu Painting Institute?
No, I'm...
I shall take this list.
Oh, no.
I will send it again more officially.
Give that to me.
No, no.
Come now.
I will send it again!
Are you all right?
Yes.
Geez! What were you thinking?
Let us go inside, Your Highness.
Maiden.
So, why did you run?
When I found out that you, whom I saw in Inwang Mountain,
are indeed the Grand Prince Yangmyeong,
I did not have the courage to face you.
And if you saw the list that I gave you,
how could I not be at a disadvantage?
I am a Grand Prince of this nation.
I would not use a mere painter list to get revenge.
"Mere painter list?"
You indeed only know how to speak as a grand prince as you have only lived as one.
You were right.
To a high-born grand prince like yourself,
it may just be a mere painter list.
But, this list, at the very least, has...
my friends' lives and the honor of Baegyu Painting Institute,
and my life's hope written in it.
So who told you to act so boldly at the paint-making house?
This would not have happened had you not said such shameless things.
But that is...
I just...
How could I have known you were truly Grand Prince Yangmyeong?
Come on.
Are you talking back to me?
All right, it is clear now.
Maiden Hong was trying to protect me
and made a mistake, not knowing who you are.
Forgive her for not recognizing Your Highness
with your generosity as vast as the ocean.
I have already forgiven her.
You may not have recognized him, but he is still this nation's Grand Prince.
You, too, must beg for proper forgiveness for your rude actions.
Grand Prince Yangmyeong, I deserve to die.
I cannot hear you.
That day, with my benighted vision,
I did not recognize Your Highness and committed a sin deserving of death.
Louder!
I deserve to die!
Of course, those who disrespect a royal deserve to die.
But that is enough.
I did not realize you were a painter either.
I take back what I said about a mere painter list.
Besides, if I kill you, I would become a widower.
Pardon?
You said you were my grand princess consort.
No, that's...
I even forgave you for swinging at me earlier because you are my grand princess consort.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
I have disrespected you as I am blind.
That is all right.
It was a mistake, after all.
Sit up now.
If you are finished talking, you should leave.
Yes.
I shall be going now.
You should take your leave.
How is your recovery?
Thanks to you, I feel much better.
I came to thank you.
I was about to call you as I have something for you.
Here.
What is this?
It is an invitation to the Maejukheon Painting Contest.
This time, the first place will be chosen by an auction,
so you, the richest man in Gwanyang, should attend
and grace the contest.
I have been already wondering about the Maejukheon Painting Contest.
We were thinking along the same lines.
Notice
This isn't your usual yearly painting competition!
The eldest son of Old Man Kang Son Ju, from whose household hails the prior first place winner,
the godly brushstroke, Gang Hi Yeon!
They say this man wields his brush with astonishing adroitness.
The Painting Bureau's consummate brushstroke, Choi Jeong!
Jeolla Province's most talented,
Monk Man Yu!
Gyeongsang Provinces's spellbinding brush lines,
the magical Sim Sat Gat*
(His name means "conical straw hat") !
Now, everyone, wager on the first place winner of your guess!
The so-called life's all-in game!
Maejukheon's gamble for the first place winner!
Have you prepared the painting supplies?
Yes, Your Highness.
Go Pil.
Make absolutely certain you mark every drawing paper.
Do not worry, Your Highness.
Deok Soe.
Yes, Your Highness?
The location of this incense altar is...
You seem busy with preparation for the competition late into the night.
(Han Geon: Master Painter of the Painting Bureau)
Master Painter Han, you're here.
I am almost finished.
The marketplace's gallery lane and painting institutes
are all hustling and bustling at the long-awaited painting competition.
I am most excited to see which painter
will surprise me this year.
Oh, yes.
Have you looked into that cheeky imitation painter?
Yes. I tried, but...
Wolseongdang is closed now
and it is difficult to find out right away.
If you could give me more time...
Blast.
Is that so.
There is a chance that the guy could compete at this contest, too.
With his talent, he absolutely could.
I would like to see that man's face.
Your Highness.
What? A divine painter?
You mean we must find a divine painter
to recreate the predecessor King's portrait?
Yes, Your Highness.
From generation to generation, the predecessor king's portrait could be drawn only by a painter with divine powers
or that painter's descendants.
So, we must find such a divine painter from this contest.
Yes, Your Highness.
But is there a method to recognize such a painter?
Father!
Father! Father!
Father! Please help me!
Help me! Father!
It is too late.
I'm sorry?
What do you mean by that?
If he has another fit of madness in the future,
he will continue to live semi-unconscious and die soon after.
What?
What do you mean die?
Please save him, physician!
My father has had to live his whole life alone in a feeble state of mind.
Please, save him this once! Please, I beg you!
There is one medicine I can prescribe.
But I'm not sure if it would work.
What is it?
Cheongsimwon.*
(medicine made of Calculus Bovis and Dioscoreae Rhizoma among other components)
It is the best medicine known to remedy lunacy.
Perhaps royals could get it.
We cannot get it here.
A precious medicine only used in the palace.
How am I to obtain it?
Hey.
Why are you making that face? Did you cry?
Is it because of your father?
- Is he unwell?
- How can he not be?
(Cha Yeong Uk, Baegyu Institute Painter)
He is always sitting out in the market streets.
(Choi Jeong, Painter at the Painter Bureau)
It is incredible that he hasn't fallen ill already.
Hey! Cheon Gi!
Hey, Cheon Gi.
Hey...  Aigoo...
Are you all right?
Maejukheon drawing contest.
All the nation's rich and powerful, magnates and nobles gather at Grand Prince Yangmyeong's Maejukheon painting contest.
The monetary award is enormous.
If you were to win the first place,
you would have enough to buy the medicine.
I heard His Highness even granted the wish of the previous winner.
But I hear all the great paint slingers of the eight provinces of the nation who are worth their name will gather there.
Won't it be hard just to pass the first round?
- Is that true?
- Of course, Cheon Gi.
You don't know how wide the world is,
- but there are plenty of hidden teachers—
- Not that.
Is it true that Grand Prince Yangmyeong will grant your wish if you win first place?
Y... yes, of course.
Cheon Gi!
Where have you been to show your face only now?
The neighboring town's Lord Kim ordered as his sehwas a Seonyeodo  (drawing of fairy)  and a Sanshindo  (drawing of mountain god) .
The munbaes  (door painting to repel evil spirits)   for Sajikdong's Scholar Seo—
Do you truly have no intention to send me to the painting contest?
Men and women each have their place, and the rules of social class are strict.
So instead of going to the contest, I should just do what I'm told. Is that it?
I never said that.
I said I would let you go if you finished all your work.
Headmaster, are you afraid that I would sully Baegyu Painting Institute's honor at the drawing competition?
J-j-just listen to the way you talk.
How dare you spew out such a thing to me?
Forget the painting competition. You are not to leave this place for the time being.
I don't want to.
You dare defy my words?
Why?
Because you think I'll go mad like Father while painting?
That...
Cheon Gi, that's not it...
It's no use even if you say that to me!
You have no idea...
You, you...
Geez, my head...
Father...
What should I do?
Maejukheon Painting Contest. The award money is enormous.
Grand Prince Yangmyeong is hosting it.
He is this nation's most skilled painter, calligrapher and a man of letters, favored by His Majesty.
Yes. If you get first place, His Highness will grant whatever you wish.
All right.
Let's do it.
Please wait a little while, Father.
Simcheonggak
I was so shocked when I heard you had disappeared.
(Mae Hyang: Head gisaeng of Simcheonggak)
How is your health?
Your job is not to worry about me.
What about the task I gave you?
As you ordered, I obtained the property records of the Supreme General.
Good work.
Grand Prince Juhyang is here.
I'm coming.
I shall be going.
Be particularly careful with your actions.
He is full of suspicion.
Yes, I will.
You're here.
This is the beginning.
Yes, Sir.
But, must you do it at Maejukheon?
(Mu Yeong: Il Wol Seong's bodyguard)
I worry your identity will be revealed.
I understand your concern.
But...
now that His Majesty has revealed his thoughts
is the right time to get my revenge.
Yes, Sir. And I investigated the woman from the paint-making house as you asked.
And?
Hong Cheon Gi is her real name.
She lost her mother at a young age.
She is an ordinary painter who paints to support her father.
Her father was once a painter at the Painting Bureau,
but now he is mentally ill ...
and works on the market streets.
It is her.
It has to be her.
What is it?
What happened to her eyes?
What do you mean?
How is she able to see now?
Was she blind before?
My revenge is just within my reach.
Now of all the times ...
- Sir?
- It is nothing.
Let's go.
I heard that His Majesty will abdicate the throne
(Seong Jin Gi: Minister of Personnel)
(Ahn Yeong Hoe: Grand Prince Juhyang's strategist)
in favor of the crown prince after the visit of the envoy from the Yeon Dynasty.
The Crown Prince?
I hear none of the myriad medicines the Royal Physician's Office used has any effect on the crown prince.
(Seo Gi Jeong: Advisor at the Office of Special Advisors)
His Majesty ordered the Astronomy Bureau to find an auspicious date. So it is for certain.
What we expected has only been moved up.
Your Highness.
Is this what you expected?
Forgive me, Your Highness.
Because of his illness, I hear...
Hyeong-nim has trouble falling asleep.
Gifting him with a deeper slumber would be another way to cure him, wouldn't it?
But it is too soon.
- Too soon?
- Yes.
Even if we succeed in the coup,
we need the support of the ministers and officers of the court.
In the court, we still lack those who trust and follow Your Highness.
We must turn Grand Prince Yangmyeong to our side.
- Yul?
- Yes, Your Highness.
How about attending Maejukheon Painting Contest this year?
It is a good opportunity to test Grand Prince Yangmyeong's willingness.
I will be attending the contest as a judge.
Should Your Highness attend, I shall attend to you closely.
Your Highness, it is Mae Hyang.
Mae Hyang?
Enter.
My name is Yeon Ji.
My name is Myeong Wol.
You made a promise to me last time.
When you returned to Simcheonggak, you promised to call on me.
My heart has been tied to this one place ever since that day.
What man would open his heart to such
pickup lines often heard in a courtesan house?
When it comes to men...
all is good, but they are all tediously the same.
They feign aloofness, pretend to be a righteous scholar,
but they become a little child in my lap.
I cannot hide my affection for Your Highness tonight.
I summoned you to this room today as a gesture of good will toward your interest in me.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Do you understand?
Yes, Your Highness.
Should you try to test me again,
I shall not laugh it over.
I will keep that in mind.
Well, then. Let us drink.
Yes, let us.
Have another.
Then, shall I trust you and bet a large sum at the Maejukheon painting contest?
I am honored, Your Highness.
Why is it so hard to find the outhouse?
Starting tomorrow, we shall open Wolseongdang again.
Yes, sir.
What shall I do with the deputy leader, Jeong Soen Nae?
Make sure he does not set foot into Gwanyang* again.
(Fictional capital of the fictional Dan Dynasty]
Yes, sir.
- Il Wol Seong?
- He's talking about you, isn't he?
Geez! Are you deaf?
Let's go to Wolseongdang.
(Jeong Soen Nae : Deputy Chief of Wolseongdang)
What? Hyeong-nim, now?
(Long Teng: Years of Rainwater)
Get everything worth the money.
Yes, Hyeong-nim.
My life is ruined because of that dirty wench.
Hong Cheon Gi.
Wait until I catch you.
I will break you.
Since she's a painter, she must be busy preparing for the painting contest herself.
Of course.
The prize money is enormous.
Wait.
Prize money?
What did you do with the attendee list?
By chance, did you write down
your name on the list?
Yes.
You don't heed my words, do you?
At first, I wrote it because I was angry.
But now, I have an important reason to participate in the contest.
- Please give me a chance.
- Shut it!
- Chun Bok.
- Yes, Headmaster?
Send her to the Shed of Truth.
- Yes.
- Headmaster!
Wait, Uncle!
Uncle, wait!
- Come on, let's go.
- That's not it!
Please don't do this, Headmaster!
Headmaster!
- Reflect on your actions and finish your paintings.
- Please open the door!
Please!
Headmaster!
Headmaster, Father is-
Father...
No. Headmaster won't have any good answer either.
The only way is to win in the painting contest.
(Morning of Maejukheon Painting Contest)
All paintings...
begin with a line and end with a line.
Do not forget.
You must put all your painterly strength into a single brush stroke.
- Understood?
- Yes, Headmaster!
(Maejukheon) (= Plum Blossom and Bamboo Manor)
(Maejukheon Painting Contest)
Goodness.
Painters, get in line!
What are you doing?
Welcome, Lord Park!
Come inside.
- Good morning, Headmaster.
- Yes...
- Do not be so nervous.
- Yes.
Take out your contestant identification sticks in advance!
Yes.
Welcome, Grand Prince Juhyang.
You are hard at work. Where Is Yangmyeong?
He is greeting guests inside.
What a circus.
Headmaster!
You said your lifework is to teach the ways of painting
and not block the paths of the painters,
but you lock me up like this.
I don't know anymore.
I'm here to collect my painting.
(Hwacha: a goblin that lives by absorbing energy from paintings)
Aigoo. You scared me to death.
Yes, Sir. Of course. One moment.
But the painting is not yet...
Not yet ready?
Where is the painter I designated?
No, you can't!
It is locked.
He is a client, client.
What?
I am here to receive my painting.
Pardon?
What painting?
Munbae and Sehwa.
(Munbae: a painting put on the front door to prevent bad luck)
(Sehwa: a painting to celebrate the new year)
Oh, the Munbae and Sehwa...
Oh, here is a Sehwa I painted.
How is this, sir?
I like it.
Wonderful! I'm glad you like it.
One moment.
Cheon Gi, Cheon Gi!
Cheon Gi!
Father, I will win first place.
- Go inside.
- All right.
Painter Hong Cheon Gi of Baegyu Painting Institute.
Painter Hong Cheon Gi of Baegyu Painting Institute...
Well, look who this is.
Our Painter Hong!
We should finish our business first.
How dare you harass a woman in broad daylight?
What a disgrace!
- What is that man doing?
- Disgraceful!
Quiet down!
You don't know anything!
Hey, hey.
Let go.
Are you truly a painter?
Where is your contestant identification?
Oh, yes.
I seem to have left it at home.
I am from Baegyu Painting Institute.
I'm a painter. Please let me in.
Aigoo. A woman painter?
A dog walking down the street would laugh.
If you don't have a contestant's identification stick, you cannot go inside. So there.
Next, next. Hurry up and wrap it up.
- Wait...
- Hurry, hurry.
Let's go while I'm being polite. Let's not waste energy.
Wait, hold on!
What is going on here?
Let go of that hand right now.
Palanquin?
Sir Scholar.
I see.
So, you two are in that kind of relationship, huh?
Watch your mouth!
- This is-
- Man Su.
Yes, Sir.
I will take her with me.
Who says? Come here!
♫  I was you and you were me  ♫
♫  I love you, I love you, only you  ♫
♫  So we don't pass each other like the passing breeze  ♫
♫  I will be here  ♫
♫  I'm afraid it will all be a dream when I open my eyes  ♫
♫  Is this the love you speak of?  ♫
♫  You can try to deny it  ♫
Lovers of the Red Sky