Teacher P'Sun, I'm very exited.
This is my first time.
Is it difficult for you?
Being my boyfriend, you have to be patient
I can't stand it.
Just to have you next to me,
I'm happy.
You're really cute, Nuea.
Will I meet someone as cute as you again?
You exaggerate too
much.
Are you tired, uncle?
No.
I'm sorry for making it hard for you.
Why did you hit me?
Uncle, don't say like that.
We're in relationship now.
If one is happy, it is shared.
If one is suffering, it is shared too.
Are you achy, Uncle?
A little.
Let me give you a massage.
Okay.
Feeling better, uncle?
Much better.
Oh, I've made some noodles for you.
- Noodles
- Umm.
My favorite.
This is Nong Nuea's noodle recipe.
Try it.
Is it delicious, Uncle?
Yes.
I can make noodles now.
Do you want to go to a concert?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Here are the concert tickets.
Concert.
- Umm.
Save Sunday concert.
Yes.
Huh, Save Sunday concert.
Save Sunday!
Is this real?
It's real.
Save Sunday! Save Sunday!
Save Sunday!
Can I give you a kiss?
One more time?
Thank you very much.
Wait.
Did you forget something?
The reason that this Prince will ask his Beloved Smile to go out today is...
One, he hasn't been out to see his friends for a long time, a total of three months.
So the Prince would like your permission.
Second, Kaeng, my friend, has always invited me to hang out.
And I want to hang out with him.
Part three...
If we are apart some times, it might make us miss each other more.
Fourth, my Smile is the cutest in the world, right?
Fifth, The Prince loves his Smile only.
The Prince promised that he would never look at anyone again.
Sounds good.
But the Smile still doesn't see any benefit that both of us will get.
The benefit that you will get is
you can read a book and sleep without any one bothering.
For the Prince's benefit,
he get to go out to relax with his friends.
Permission granted?
Relax?
So when the Prince is with Smile, you're stressed?
Not like that, Smile. I used the wrong word.
I mean..
The Prince get to hang out with his friends.
The Prince's Project isn't very sharp.
And, didn't you think that your outfit
was too good looking and seductive.
My outfit? This outfit is pretty normal.
But if you want me to change, I will.
Permission granted?
The Prince will go now.
- Hello.
Wait.
Yes?
Completed your duties yet?
Laundry, mopping and packed up for you, all done.
Very good, then you can go.
But come back no later than 10PM.
10 PM?
But it's already 8:30 PM.
I couldn't be back in time for 10 PM.
Can I extend the time?
So, 10:15.
May I extend to 11PM?
No go.
So it's 10:15. I will hurry back.
Wait.
Yes?
Did you forget something?
Bye.
OK.
Bro?
P'Team hasn't arrived yet.
So late.
Too late for him.
Kaeng?
What is this outfit about?
-Oh...P'Team!
-My best friend, Team!
Why?
This is normal?
I thought you're the uncle that come to pick up his nephew home.
Not cool for our gang.
Shut up. Just that I can get out is a blessing.
Team, look. The table over there squinted at you.
Nope, I already have a boyfriend.
Ah, go, go, drink.
Oh, I'm sorry, he already has a boyfriend.
Come here.
I'll make one for you.
I'll take water.
- What?
- I'll take water.
Kaeng.
- Come here.
- Cheers!
Been so long!
- Nuea. What time is it?
- Huh?
I have to go back.
What time is it?
The Prince came back at 10:14.
A minute, earlier.
And the Smile is still not sleeping?
I can't sleep.
Without a Prince, it's weird.
Let the Prince make his Smile fall asleep?
No need, I will.
Coach Tue, I'm your boyfriend.
Lost again?
It was full of loopholes.
The moodier, the more out of focus.
Oy.
Coach Tue,
I'm your boyfriend.
Just pretend to lose for me.
You don't have to be serious all the time.
It's different.
In a match, you can't pretend to lose.
It will give the opponent the advantage.
Do you understand?
Come here.
OK.
So one more round?
Come, Coach Tue.
Oy.
What is it?
I got dizzy...
My head hurts.
What's wrong?
How are you?
Is this a foul play?
Oy.
It hurts.
No more practice.
- Okay.
- Oh, does it hurt?
You already had good mitts.
And you're complaining?
You can put my mitten on then.
Help me put them on.
Nicely.
Calm down.
What are you playing at?
Crazy ass coach.
Do you like it?
I might like it.
Might?
I'm so sad.
So... I might not like it
but like it very much
and would have liked it better if someone put them on for me.
I love you.
what?
I said
I love you.
Crazy ass coach.
It hurts.
Oh, sorry.
Coach Tue.
What?
Want to kiss?
Everyone else will see us.
Should we go back to my room?
Fast.
Papa loves Daddy the most in the world.
Baby Seven.
So cute.
Are you hungry?
Papi?
Yes?
Why are you begging?
What you want?
Acting suspicious.
Nope.
Who dares to take anything from you?
Yes, right?
Tell me.
What's up?
Can Papi ask Daddy to go out tonight?
With whom and where?
With Team and Nuea.
We talked in the group chat.
Please?
I promise to behave nicely.
Will you let me?
Here's the permission granter.
Don't use the baby kiss.
So you allowed?
Umm... go.
Really?
But
you have a boyfriend, and he is very jealous.
Babe, you gotta let me wear this for real?
If you don't want to wear it, take it off.
But I don't want you to go.
Not that I don't want you to wear.
I can wear it.
Don't forget to pick up my call.
If you don't accept it, there'll be a problem.
I will be there myself.
Yes.
I know!
Give me some money.
Here it is! A nerve asking for them.
Please.
Wait.
A hundred.
Umm.
Daddy?
What?
Almost not enough for the car.
Almost doesn't mean not enough.
You told me that you'd sit and talk. Why are you going to share the drink fees?
So go or no go?
A hundred is fine.
Go now.
Have a safe trip.
Don't be stubborn like the kids.
- OK, bye bye.
- Bye bye.
Bye.
Go!
Nowadays your skill is getting worse, Nuea.
Asking me about my shirt but then what are you wearing?
If I don't wear it, he won't let me go.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
Talked about him, and he calls right away.
Hello, babe.
Not in bed yet?
Nope, still waiting.
I'll drink a bit more and I'll back.
- Hurry back.
- Brother Kaeng, Brother Kaeng?
I'd like to talk to P'Puth, please.
Go on.
P'Puth, I'll take care of P'Kaeng myself. Don't worry.
Okay, so have fun.
That's all.
Bye bye.
What are you laughing at?
Nope.
Excuse me, cheer to you.
OK.
Who?
- This is a cute shirt.
- Thank you.
Excuse me, cheers to you?
Yes.
You're cute. Put on your boyfriend's shirt.
If it's me, I will love to death.
Thank you.
Kaeng, since you wear this shirt, so many people approaching.
My boyfriend's name is Puth.
- See.
- Oh.
My boyfriend's name is Puth.
Bro, don't laugh.
Good for you.
Should we wear too, P'Team?
He calls again?
Papi is coming.
Have you waited a long time, Daddy?
Papi loves Daddy.
Let's take a photo together.
Smile a little.
Looking at camera, hon.
Papi loves Daddy the most in the world.
Are you tired, Thurs?
With you besides me, I'm not tired.
After that...
a child ran down to hide in the basement.
Shortly after he was hidden,
a foot appeared.
A foot in ancient shoe swayed.
The boy, when he saw it, his eyes widened.
Then it rained with the sound of thunder.
What will happen with them in this abandoned house?
What they found was only in their thoughts,
a set up, or really
the ghost of the abandoned house?
Welcome to Haunted Days, Dorm Nights.
For tonight, goodbye everyone.
Haha... Done.
- Are you tired, Thurs?
- With you by my side, I can't be.
By the way, are you tired or bored
to help me do something like this?
You think too much!
Not tired, not bored at all.
It's a form of creativity. It's fun!
Just you don't do medium, I'm very happy.
But medium makes a lot better money.
- A comment?
- Umm...
Can I see?
I'm tired of you. Always told from other's stories.
Yes, I'd like to hear from other people.
I want to see you invite others to co-tell.
Well, at this point, I'm out of content.
What I experienced, I already told them.
And I don't know who could host the show.
Umm... How about this! Try to think. Maybe ask your friends or the fans.
There might be someone who wants to co host the show with you.
The fans?
I don't want anyone to come host the show.
And my friends... they all have boyfriends.
Who's going to be free?
- Boyfriend...
- Umm!
- So you? Come host the show with me.
- No, I can't host and I don't speak clearly.
It's okay. Just come as a guest?
- You don't have to be good at talking.
- No!
If I host the show, who's going to handle the sound?
I can let Khao Niao and Waat do that.
Host the show with me? Please...
If my boyfriend wouldn't help me, who would?
- Please.
- Well, ok!
Really? Yes! You're the best.
- I'll prepare the script for you.
- OK.
OK...
Hello everyone!
Welcome to the scariest show of the night
with the Haunted Days, Dorm Nights.
Meet Thurs, Chairman of the Mysterious Club
Today, I'm not the only one here.
We have a special guest, which is Khun Pae.
And we have a personal story to share.
It's something that just happened recently.
It's a story between man and ghost.
I'm not sure too that
if it's faith or destiny.
We want everyone to listen carefully.
- Because of this is both scary and cute
- Yes.
The story goes... there is a 1st year boy.
Cute with six senses, and love mysteries
and a little indifference.
Oh, it's a cute type of indifference.
One day, that first year boy
met a ghost, great looks, cute personality.
But that ghost can't remember anything,
like a ghost with amnesia.
That boy named that ghost as Pao,
name of the dog next door that he loves.
That Pao ghost...
helped the boy, stay with the boy.
Both when sleeping and awaken.
And the boy fell in love with Pao.
Because the cuteness was overwhelmed.
Pao, I know that Pao is here.
I come this time, it's the last time.
I don't want you to go.
Can you trust me? That we will meet again.
You and him are meant to be, there's always a reason to meet.
After that,
destiny made the two see each other again.
Though Pao didn't immediately recognize Thurs,
but their bond made them remember each other easily.
When they knew each other, they became boyfriends,
and they have been in a relationship to today.
The story of the first year boy and Pao Ghost,
ended with this, everyone.
Thank you very much for staying with us until the end of the program.
Goodbye and Good night.
Done!
The story we've been telling, will it be a happy ending?
A very, very happy ending.
- Really happy.
- I'm happy too.
Thank you for hosting this birthday party for me.
Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to Tir
Thank you for hosting a birthday party for Tir.
I told you, the thing you have, they are yours.
Don't worry, I'm happy to.
Masuk, try the food. Is it alright?
Thank you, Hia.
What's going on, Masuk? Food not good?
It's delicious but it's hot.
Here...
Food that you spooned for me
is the most delicious.
If you like, I'll do another spoon.
Hia...
Hmm...
You're very tired today.
I'll wash the dishes for you.
You go take a break.
Huh!
I'm not tired.
I'm glad.
Masuk?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Can we go on third base?
Are you crazy!
Tir might see us.
Tir won't know.
See? Tir is happy at his birthday party in heaven.
You talking nonsense.
Sat, have you been waiting long?
Not that long, Choke.
- What are you looking at? I'm embarrassed.
- We lovers. I've seen you all. Come in!
Be quite, the others can hear us.
Let them hear everything.
You look very mature in these swimming trunks.
Why? Is it daddy's trunks?
- No.. It just looks...
- Stop! You pervert! I know what you're going to say.
Sat!
Or you want me to kiss you?
- You crazy! I'm gonna swim.
- Choke, wait for me.
Choke!
- Sat!
Sat! Sat!
Sat!
What's wrong with you. Don't play like this!
I was worried about you.
Choke, are you mad?
Sorry, I just wanna play with you.
Let's go back. I want to go back.
Choke, Choke, wait!
Choke! Choke!
Choke! Choke! Choke!
Choke, I just want to kiss you.
But you won't let me.
So I...
So you set it up?
You know you've done wrong.
People who make mistakes must be punished.
What's the punishment?
Choke, what are you doing?
Do what you want me to do.
Finally, this semester we have boyfriends.
They're not here yet. Assholes.
It's not time yet. Why in such a hurry?
Today we'll have fun. Just leave it for a day.
Friends will start arriving.
I understand.
Are you feeling hot?
Tue, Ake, we are here.
- Hello.
- Hi!
Ahem... You look so bright, Masuk.
- We're here.
- Good morning.
- Hello.
Six of you are late. Prepare to be our slaves the whole trip.
P'Puth! You woke up late again.
I told you to wake up early. If I don't wake you, will you even be here?
Team, you look at your boyfriend. He's a big deal now.
So grumpy, I don't know why. I hardly slept.
You deserve it. No discipline.
- Papi...
- Oh...
But I think it's definitely not me that's a slave.
Did you forget...
- Sun and Nuea aren't here yet!
- Well, yeah...
- Ahem, I'm sorry. Give way.
- Here they are.
Oh! Oy! What are you guys on about?
Bro!
- I think we will toe the slave this trip.
- Well, I want to use him!
- I was always the slave. Let him be this time!
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- Do you mind?
- Oh.
Well, be careful what's inside.
- This too.
- Take care of it well, P'Sun.
Thank you P'Sun.
- Mind them for me, P'Sun.
- Yes, yes.
- Thank you, P'Sun.
- Yes.
- I'm fine.
- Huh, what!
Take care of it.
Yes, Nong Nuea.
Again?
Consider it a production thing.
Bro, hey.
- Ooh... Oh...
- So beautiful.
Everyone, I have reserved rooms for you.
If there is no prob then let's go in.
Well, see you in the evening.
Do whatever you need to but spare you energy.
You are the strongest...
- So beautiful.
- See you soon.
Go...
Can I ride on your back? Faster!
- Wow... that's extra.
Ohhh... Will there be glue on it?
- Nong Nuea, let's go.
- Sun!
- You forget something?
- Yes!
What?
That you are a slave this trip.
Oh... a slave?
Leaving it to you. Let's go, Papi.
Like I was a hanging rial.
Do it quickly, Teacher P'Sun.
I'll wait in the room.
Nuea, wait for me.
Hello everyone, you're with this same old Mon again.
I'm at Khao Yai with my friends and bros.
And, of course, the Prince.
- Will be right back. I'll find someone.
- Okay.
This is this guy, my friend Thurs.
- What is this?!
- And who was that? Introducing yourself.
Hello, I'm Pae.
- My very boyfriend.
- Ooh, the very boyfriend.
You can follow us at "Haunting Days, Dorm Nights"
With me, Thurs and Pae.
OMG... so cute.
It's better not to bother them, let's go find someone else.
Hello Masuk, who are you with?
- Hello, this is Jia.
- He looks very nice.
What?
- I'm glad to see you Smile.
- Go somewhere else.
- OK, I don't want to bother lovers. Bye.
Ooh, Brother Puth, Brother Kaeng, oh...
Love birds everywhere, dorm, uni, and here!
- Let us be, we're newly met.
- Ummm...
- Don't look newly at all!
- Well, something is new.
Which is?
- Go away, go.
- Okay, won't bother now.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Mon...
P'Tiw! Who is this person?
My wife...
Brother... are you a wife?
Who's your wife, Tiw? I just did that to you just now....
Better not say...
Teacher P'Sun, are you tired?
Just that you're here, I'm not tired...
They are so sweet.
- I help you grill.
I took the barbecue, now I'm gone.
Mon! What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- It's for P'Team.
Aren't you in a sweetheart?
So cute! A kiss too...
I won't give up. I'll go find my baby.
Bye-bye. What's up with him?
To hit drum, we have to stand in this pose too?
- Huh!
- You'll make mistakes.
What mistakes, the drums or...? - Oh, juicy.
And who's that guy?
My Boyfriend...
- Boyfriend means lover...
- Go away. Go.
I'm back, the Prince. Brought you a barbecue.
- Let's go eat?
- I'll tell them.
- Let's go, everyone, let's eat.
- We're gonna eat n,cw. Bye-bye.
Slave, hurry up.
- To our love.
- Cheers... woo...
Cheers!
Guys, did you thank my wife?
- Oh... Thank you.
- It's okay, you're fine.
What are you on about?
THE END
Finally, this semester, we have boyfriends.
Yes!
Our babies are so cute.
Look for a new one next semester!
-Yeah...
Don't find a new one.
- Following Sun..
- What? I said I love my boyfriend very much.
So cute.
I have something I want to say.
- What is it, bro, so serious?
I really have to thank fate
that made me born to be Sun
and made me meet Nuea...
and also you guys.
This term!
We've been through a lot and we got through.
Can you make a promise with me
that we won't leave each other?
- Can you make a promise?
- A promise it is. Yes!
- Promise me, Nong Nuea.
- Oh, they won't stop!
Love us like you do him!
Can we just be serious for 1 minute?
I would like to thank P'Team...
P’Kaeng...
who always advise me
when I need help.
And I would like to thank Teacher P'Sun
That makes me understand that...
All that I've put in, it's not for money
but it's love.
Thank you for being the cutest lover for me.
So... how are the others? What do you want to say bro?
Oh!
Don't be in a hurry, calm down.
Uh...
I want to thank myself first for being a boxer.
That made me meet you.
And I want to thank you
that came to be an obstacle,
it makes me know that...
Obstacles can turn into love.
I want to thank myself too.
that I change myself for someone.
And I thank you.
Who taught me that...
I don't always have to win.
Wow...so cute...
Puth! What about yours?
Thank you Kaeng
that makes me know...
how much Papi loves me.
Thank you Papi.
Yes...
So do you have something to tell everyone?
Me...
- Papi would like to thank Daddy.
- Umm...
that chosen me
And I want to thank Mon
who advises me about Puth
made I was willing to change myself for him.
And then...
I want to thank you, Team, and Nuea for always being there for me
on days that I have no one.
I would like to thank all of you very much.
Especially Kaeng, Nuea
who are always beside me.
And...
I would like to thank Mon
for being my happiness,
making my life better!
Thank you for making me know true love.
I also...
thank you P'Team as well.
Thank you for making me know that
the true love I believe in is real.
Thank you for bringing happiness to me.
I had never been this happy before.
Thank you all, brothers.
All my friends too.
- Especially you, Thurs, P'Puth too.
- Well...
Thank you for being with me all the time.
Even when I'm sad
or when we are happy together.
I want to see everyone happy like this forever.
Thank you very much everyone.
- Umm...
Go, Pae.
- Oh!
- Skipping you.
What?
Oh...
Thank you, Thurs for everything.
If it weren't for you, I'd be in a bad shape.
Well, speaking like we know who Pao is.
- It's him.
But I won't take it anymore, Pao!
Thank you Pao for keeping the promise.
And thank you very much, Mon and P'Puth
who was always by my side.
And the most important thing is...
thank you, Pae
for...
- being my cute boyfriend. Thank you.
- Umm...
Next one...
Well...
Me then. I want to thank Masuk for being such a good code bro.
Thank you for being my friend.
But most importantly!
I want to thank you...
Choke!
Thank you for growing up together.
Thank you for staying with me.
Thank you for being my friend.
Thank you for taking care of me.
Thank you for loving me.
For me, well...
Thank you very much Sat for...
making me, this fat kid knows what love is.
You make me Choke as in today.
And thank you everyone, especially P'Masuk
who was always by Sat's side.
Thank you for being my best friend and my boyfriend.
Huh! so sweet
- I'll be everything and anything for you.
- Oh, that's enough.
Oh, it's you and Hia Jia.
Me?
What is it?
Nothing.
I want to thank you all
for being by my side as always
to this day
especially Sat.
Thank you for...
always being worried about me...
Staying with me
when I was
alone, there will be Sat keep coming in...
Thank
myself for moving on.
Thank you for being able to
live happily
Just like Tir had asked for...
Thank you Tir...
Thank you for...
always by my side
no matter where he is.
I know you are always with me here...
Thank you for...
taking care of me
even if it's a short time.
I was really happy.
Thank you Hia...
Thank you for...
agreeing to love a friend like me.
I thank you Masuk's friends
especially Sat
Who has always been talking to Masuk.
I thank Masuk
for opening up his heart to let me in
though inside, there is still Tir there.
Yes, Hia.
I thank Tir..
Thank you
for giving me a chance to love Masuk
and save my nephew from the fire.
Tir is a good person and the bravest.
Thank you very much, Tir.
Thank you, Tir.
Hia...
Thank you for taking care of Masuk.
Thank you for...
accepting him,
bear with him
and don't let go of him.
Take care of Masuk.
I thank myself
for helping Masuk live a happy life
and help him open up
to find new love.
Masuk!
I really thank you
for never forgetting me
for loving me...
I love you.
Being an ordinary person day by day
Waking up to the same life with more loneliness
I envy that everyone had someone beside him
Everyone looks at me, I seem fine
Deep inside, I can't stand it, my heart calls for
someone who will change the lives of the ordinary
to become meaningful