[The Best Day of My Life]
[Episode 2]
Wait for me.
I'll change the medicine.
Why?
I was too anxious to check it.
Patients with allergies
should use it with caution.
When I was in high school,
I fainted due to allergies.
It was serious.
I guess I can't take it.
I'll change it.
Don't go.
Patients with allergies
refer to those people
who easily have an allergic reaction.
You fainted in high school
simply because
you were allergic to peanuts.
You wouldn't have fainted
if you hadn't eaten too many.
Hey, you...
No more pretending, huh?
Had enough fun, Director Jiang?
In the barbecue restaurant,
you said you couldn't recognize me.
Oh, Xie Shi.
This is ancient history.
I don't even remember
what he looks like.
Even if he stands in front of me,
I may not recognize him.
I just blurted it out.
Just because of that,
you fooled me for a couple of days.
How could you be so revengeful?
It depends.
You're as sharp-tongued as before.
You haven't changed at all.
Go have dinner
before you take the medicine.
I won't.
Drive me home.
Won't you be hungry?
I won't.
Not at all.
Wait here.
I'll bring my car around.
[Shuanghuanglian Capsules]
XY is 0.
X or Y should be 0.
We shared a desk for a long time
and I looked at your face
a million times.
I should have recognized you
at first sight
so that you couldn't fool me.
Good for you.
You reflect on yourself.
You have a good appetite.
You didn't have that in high school.
You got good sleep, though.
In high school,
I studied, ate, and slept every day.
But now, I'm busy working.
And my clients are tough.
Oh, no.
I don't mean you.
I mean someone else.
Hey.
Reach out when you can't argue?
Try to hurt your deskmate?
Hey.
Remember to tell Mr. Liao
that I can work.
I can take care of the project, too.
No need.
Why?
Because I tricked you.
What a man!
I'll go pay the bill.
I caught a cold during work.
Instead of comforting me,
Mr. Liao made me buy Xie Shi a present.
It doesn't make sense at all.
With this excuse,
you'll give the client a present
to bond with him.
Why do I feel
you're like a princess
to be married for politics?
Don't make fun of me.
Think about what present I should buy.
Let me think about it.
Belt.
Lighter.
In the worst case,
give him an Ultraman
and ask him if he believes in light.
Song Niannian.
Just kidding.
Oh.
What about a tie?
The day you met him,
he was wearing a suit, right?
It goes well with his suit.
Tie...
Is it appropriate?
Will it be too intimate?
It's not the underwear
and it has no special meaning.
Why is it inappropriate?
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Which tie is good
for a man about 27 or 28 years old?
Are you picking one for your boyfriend?
Umm, no.
So, your future boyfriend?
No, no.
Just my client.
Don't say that.
It's just a couple thing.
Even if you ask him
to order you as a client,
he would not dare.
Am I right?
Yes.
How about you start to recommend?
OK. Let me see.
What about this one?
OK.
I'll take this.
Pack it.
OK.
Write a card for me.
Just write,
"To Jiang Zhou".
OK.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Zhou.
It's really you.
I thought I got the wrong guy.
Chen Xi?
Yes, it's me.
Zhou,
I just came back a few days ago.
Last night, I asked my mother
when I could see you again.
And now, we meet.
Xie Shi?
Big romance.
Don't you miss me?
It's not a very long time.
Wait.
Looks like
Xie Shi is pestered.
Mu.
I have something to do
and I need to see my editor.
Remember to take the tie.
I will.
And...
Tell me if there's some gossip.
Don't think of the gossip.
Just go.
I should go.
Will you, Zhou?
Walk around with me.
We seldom meet, anyway.
Xu Mu.
Oh?
Director Jiang.
What a coincidence.
Watched enough, huh?
Zhou,
why did you walk so fast?
I couldn't catch up.
Where have you been?
Didn't you say
you had something
to tell me this afternoon?
Help me.
I don't want to get involved.
Director Jiang,
I think you remember it wrong.
I don't think
we have anything to talk about.
You...
Think harder.
Zhou,
is she your colleague?
Why don't you introduce her?
Hello.
Call me Xi.
Hi.
We...
We aren't colleagues.
He's just my client.
A normal client.
I have things to do.
I should go.
Director Jiang,
how about
you walk around
with your friend Xi?
Bye-bye.
Have a nice day.
Enjoy yourselves.
Miss,
your boyfriend's tie is packed.
The card is in it, too.
To Jiang Zhou.
Let me tell you some experience.
When you give him this present,
put on some perfume.
Not to mention Jiang Zhou,
you can get any other man.
Madam.
Madam, go back to work.
Don't let me hold you up.
We're in no relationship,
seriously.
In the company, we...
We're...
We're just...
Help me.
I don't want to get involved.
You go back.
My girlfriend is getting angry.
Hey.
You're on purpose, huh?
I just said that for your sake.
Because you said
I was your boyfriend.
Aren't you going to explain this?
Here's the thing.
Mr. Liao asked me to...
You'll explain it here?
Then tell me.
Where do you want to go?
A normal restaurant will do.
Mm.
Do you know how expensive
that restaurant is?
One single dish
costs over a hundred.
He didn't make you pay anyway.
I was clever enough to skip out.
The result is good, anyway.
Don't bother about the restaurant.
Tell me.
After I left, did anything exciting happen
between Xie Shi and that girl?
Don't tell me
you're calling just for gossip.
I'm not that kind of person.
So,
any gossip?
Song Niannian.
Come on.
I'm just curious.
You know me.
Let me tell you something happy.
This afternoon, my editor called me away,
saying a film and television company
would buy my novel.
Again?
Good for you.
Which company?
Its name is...
Dazzle.
Dazzle?
I get you in my company
to make you focus
and work hard.
If you aren't fired in three months,
I'll release your cards.
And...
I can't reveal my identity.
I know that.
And your car...
The new guy?
Yes.
Hello.
Oh,
what's your name again?
Shen Yi.
Shen Yi?
Is my name so funny?
You have no idea, bro.
There's a very popular novel
named Limited Romance.
There's a supervillain in it.
His name is Shen Yi.
If you don't believe it,
come and check.
Shen Yi galloped on the grassland.
[Limited Romance]
Arrows came out of nowhere
and shot him like rain.
Shen Yi was shot.
Shot like a sieve,
he was lying there, bleeding.
What on earth is this?
I won't read this kind of book.
Who wrote it?
[Song Jinxin,
Writer of Tingjiang Literature]
Song Jinxin?
Hey.
Who are you?
Why did you sweep
the rubbish over to our region?
You swept it over first.
I just returned it.
You don't even concentrate on sweeping.
You're arguing just to argue.
It's you who swept the rubbish over.
Which class are you in?
What is your name?
I'll tell your teacher about it.
Why would I tell you?
Which class are you in?
Hi, director.
Give it back to me.
Song Jinxin?
Not a good name.
It truly is a small world.
[A Week]
Mm.
I've seen the person in charge.
I'm going home now.
I'm sorry.
Oh, he's a fan.
Don't you think
I look familiar?
Aren't you...?
Right.
I'm your idol,
Song Jinxin.
Who's your...?
Oh, I recognize you.
I just saw you reading my novel.
Tell me.
Which novel do you like best?
Since when were you fascinated with me?
With my novel.
Maybe
when I was in high school.
When you were in high school?
I just started writing at that time.
Mm.
So,
you're a hardcore fan.
Which character do you like best?
I love all the characters.
Especially
some villains.
I think you depicted them perfectly.
How shall I put it?
You depicted them
with great thoughts.
Thanks for that.
We're meant to meet.
I'll give an autograph to you.
Thank you, then.
Write down what I say.
Shen.
Yi.
[Shen]
He's really Shen Yi?
Shen Yi in our high school?
Yes.
Who else could be so annoying?
This morning, I found
I was dead in a novel.
And at noon, I met the writer.
Could I be even unluckier?
It's hard to tell.
When I picked up his phone,
he was reading my novel.
She thought I was her hardcore fan
and gave me an autograph.
But I really didn't expect that.
Shen Yi has totally changed.
He looks...
She's prettier than before.
But her personality is really...
Awful!
You're meant to meet.
We're enemies!
We're not enemies.
But since she was in high school,
she has been despising me.
I don't know how I offended her.
She tricked me all the time.
How's the cafe going?
Really good.
Maybe in a couple of years,
our cafe will be open
all over the world.
Why is there such a big decline?
Who made this?
Who?
Oh.
They're off work.
Hey, check this.
No losses. It's balanced.
If you're too busy, I can get a helper.
Don't bother about the cafe.
Keep using the room on the second floor.
It's your investment, then.
When I work out the AI Guide Dog,
I'll make some money and have dividends.
You'll have some.
But I have to say,
The room on the second floor
is perfect for my research work.
First,
my father can't find me.
Second,
it's free of charge.
In case my father says
I do nothing serious.
I can't make him understand.
He's not to blame, though.
I haven't worked out anything successful.
It takes time.
I can wait.
But Nicole can't.
It's just like a bottomless pit.
My little money...
Oops.
It's long gone.
Now, I have no money at all.
Forget it.
I'll just play it by ear.
Shall I take you up to my son's room?
Come on.
Everybody,
let me introduce him.
This is
Mr. Xie.
He offers us this room.
Thank you, Mr. Xie.
Not at all.
You guys work.
I just look around.
You haven't gone back home again?
Look at your hair.
And you...
Look at your shirt.
When did you change last time?
You just go back home for some rest.
Let's go.
We'll wash up before we return.
Fine.
We should go.
How does this room look?
Better than I imagined.
When you work it out someday,
your father will be proud of you.
My investment.
Take it.
All right. You go back.
Text me when you get home.
OK.
At work, Xie Shi upsets me.
At home, my roommate upsets me.
I'll have a nervous breakdown someday.
Then why don't you
move in with me?
Keep me company, then.
I always stay at home alone.
Pitiful, aren't I?
I want to live with you.
But you live far away from my company.
Is that a hint?
Get in the car.
Let's go see a flat near your company.
If you pick one,
I'll pay the deposit immediately.
Don't squander your money.
Just go home.
Fine.
Good night.
Mm. Good night.
Off you go.
You'll have a blind date this weekend.
I saw his photo.
A conscientious young man.
I like him.
You're no longer young.
Don't always ignore me.
When no man wants you,
you'll cry.
Xu Mu.
Still keeping it secret?
Deskmate.
High school.
We all know that.
Now, everyone in our company
knows about the two of you.
So...
What did Director Jiang
look like in high school?
Any big difference?
Come.
Director Jiang hasn't changed at all.
He was so indifferent
that even a dog stayed far away.
What I suffered from him in high school
is even more than my savings.
Oh.
Director Jiang.
Morning.
What were you saying about me?
We were saying
Director Jiang...
You work really hard.
Yes.
And you're kind.
Very easygoing.
Yes.
Nothing else.
Xu Mu,
come check something with me.
Xu Mu.
Be right there.
Mu is pitiful.
She suffered in high school
and she suffers now.
They're like a wolf and a rabbit.
You acted really poorly.
Speaking of this,
you're the best actor.
Come on,
Director Jiang.
Xu Mu may not really suffer.
For now,
they are actually
an old fox and a little fox.
♪We're almost there♪
♪Be very careful♪
♪Don't let him get it,
though I also want it♪
♪Maybe you knew how much I loved you♪
♪The pink bubble rain keeps falling♪
♪Playing a film in my universe♪
Ouch, Director Jiang.
Are you OK?
You must be burned.
♪Revolving heart is acting♪
♪You seem to have
a universal attraction♪
♪Gradually getting us closer♪
♪How I wish this isn't just a dream♪
[Oneday]
Mu,
where shall I put the flowers?
Over there.
At the end?
Yes.
At the end.
Over there.
That's right.
Move it left.
[Sign-desk]
Hello. Hello.
You can photograph
everything in the homestay.
Have a nice day.
How's it going?
More than half
of the invitations are valid.
And they are
satisfied with the homestay routes.
This time, most of them
are female bloggers.
Many flowers and scented candles
are put in the lobby.
They can also serve as souvenirs.
When they leave, they can take some.
That is the dessert table.
This is where they'll dine.
Oh, and this.
Come this way.
This is
a small garden we've decorated.
They can check in here and take photos.
What do you think, Director Jiang?
Good.
Stingy.
As stingy as before.
Nothing.
I'm done introducing this.
I'll go back to work.
Director Jiang,
there's some dessert.
Low in sugar.
Would you like some?
No, thanks.
Hey, who did this?
Who turned off the lights?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Maybe it's someone's birthday.
Little surprise, you know.
I just asked.
The voltage is too high
and this building is too old.
So, the fuses are blown.
Have them fixed.
They can be fixed, but...
The repair
will take one and a half hours.
One...
Let's do this.
Go buy a cake immediately.
If someone asks,
tell them it's your birthday.
OK?
Where's Xu Mu?
Mu...
I just saw her...
Call her now.
Sorry to have scared you.
Let me apologize first.
This idea...
I had this idea when one day
I came back home very late from work.
I suddenly thought
my pain life kept repeating.
Nothing was new.
I could tell how it would end up.
At that time, I was thinking.
If only every day,
someone would give me a surprise.
So,
here in Like,
I want everyone to get his or her surprise.
Everything you've never imagined
may appear today.
Music.
Candle.
Aurora.
The moment the lights went off
was when the surprise was being prepared.
♪Just a little bit closer to the moon♪
♪I worry you'll miss the fact
that I miss you♪
♪Before I feel your tenderness♪
♪I'm sleepless all alone
in the universe♪
♪I want you to tell me
about the world in your eyes♪
♪You've led me by your side
for the sealed ten years♪
♪My bravery may come late♪
The fuses are being fixed.
But it will take a while.
Luckily, in our tool cart,
there are projectors and candles
from the last activity.
Xu, without you,
what could we do?
Mr. Liao,
you flatter me.
Go explain this to Director Jiang.
OK.
Umm...
Cancel the cake.
But it's being delivered.
I'll claim it, anyway.
That was close.
Good solution.
Thank you, Director Jiang.
♪I want you to miss me
and my heart beats a million times♪
Excuse me.
Can you take a photo of me?
No problem.
♪Love becomes more clear
and you get to know me♪
♪There's no reason I don't kiss you
the day we meet again♪
Done.
Thank you.
♪On the night when meteors
soar across the sky♪
♪I have no wishes
but to look at you without blinks♪
Don't just look.
This is something worth recording.
Let's take a photo.
♪When I'm overwhelmed by memories,
I'm glad I remember your face♪
♪Only the moon is a little brighter♪
Smile.
♪And there are more stars today♪
[Weibo Hotspot]
Everybody,
I have some exciting news.
The discussion on Like's homestay
has been heated.
What's more,
Like released an official video.
Have a wild guess
There you go, Yusi.
Five million.
A wild guess, OK?
Such a coward.
Come on.
Xiaoke,
you guess.
Ten million.
Xu, you guess.
Can it be
thirty million?
3.5 million!
Mr. Liao, buy us dinner.
- Mr. Liao,
- buy us dinner.
Mr. Liao, buy us dinner!
OK. Tonight.
Let's have dinner!
Come on. Cheers.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Very good.
Let me give a brief talk.
Recently, you've had hard work.
Our first publicity was successful.
Like is very satisfied with us.
Applaud!
Especially Xu...
She had hard days.
Every day, she worked overtime
and took care of the project.
So, I announce
we'll give Xu
a kebab.
Here.
Enjoy yourselves, everybody.
For the stage,
we'll keep working hard.
OK.
Mr. Liao is right.
I think you're thinner from hard work.
You should eat more.
I can't complete this project by myself.
Everybody should eat more.
We will.
Come on.
Hey, Mr. Liao.
Why isn't Director Jiang here
for our celebration party?
Mr. He informed him.
I guess he's arriving soon.
Come on.
Let's drink. Cheers.
Thanks for your hard work.
What's up?
Nothing.
I just fear you may forget
you have a celebration party to attend.
I remember.
I'm on my way.
Fine, then.
I'm also arriving.
I'll wait for you at the door.
OK.
- Truth!
Fine.
Just do it, then.
Ask me some harsh questions.
Oh, wait.
I'll keep some evidence.
OK. Go ahead.
Mr. Liao, have you given
a nickname to any superior?
Yes!
What nickname?
What is it?
TOSB.
The King of Sock Blood.
TOSB for short.
Oh, that's good.
I made a video.
Go ahead.
No problem at all.
Whose turn is it?
Let me see.
Xu Mu.
You should play truth or dare in turn.
No one can drink all night
instead of playing.
Yeah.
Do it.
- Do it!
Then, I'll pick...
Dare.
Oh, Xu Mu.
You think big now.
Suddenly, Xu
become so generous.
Xu Mu.
Play something exciting, then.
Later,
you'll go hug the first person
who gets in here, OK?
Exciting!
Let's see who'll come in.
Mm.
Oh.
Xu Mu, Xu Mu.
It's good for you.
Too good.
Director Jiang.
Director Jiang, here.
What's wrong?
Sit down first.
Explain this.
We were playing Truth or Dare.
It was Xu Mu's turn.
She was punished to hug
the first person who got in.
You're the second.
That's a pity.
Why are there two Director Jiang?
Which one shall I hug?
This one.
♪Just a little bit closer to the moon♪
♪I worry you'll miss the fact
that I miss you♪
♪Before I feel your tenderness♪
♪I'm sleepless all alone
in the universe♪
♪Want to tell you
how fascinated I am with you♪
♪I think of you all the time♪
♪If I were a star in the universe♪
♪My trajectory would deviate for you♪
♪Want to tell you everything about you♪
♪Is recorded in my heart♪
♪Want to travel with you
from summer to winter♪
♪So, you're everything in my dream♪
♪So, I always sneak closer♪
♪I realized I'm a little bit obsessed♪
♪I'm waiting for your reply♪
♪If you can be by my side♪
♪And spend every year with me♪
♪Regardless of uneasiness and anxiety♪
♪I'll enjoy the sunset
and tides with you♪
♪If you sense my feelings♪
♪Can you get closer instead of fleeing?♪
♪Listen carefully to how we breathe now♪
♪My heart beats so fast just for you♪