Why haven't you left yet?
I won't leave.
I want to stay by your side.
I have nowhere to go anyway.
Rather than staying in the deep woods
and worrying about being caught every day,
it's better to stay down here
and live a carefree life for a few days.
Stop messing around.
Cultivation, cultivation.
All you know is cultivation.
Every day you're either doing good deeds
or cultivating.
Hey.
Do you have any joy in life at all?
Cultivating the Dao,
doing good deeds,
cultivating the mind,
and bringing peace to the world.
This is what we cultivators pursue.
How could there be no joy in it?
Then...
What about having fun?
I am no longer a child.
I have no desire to play.
If you are bored,
just take a walk around the mountain.
Stinky Daoist!
How dare you call me childish?
I'm telling you,
even if you beg me in the future,
I won't play with you.
My Silver Lotus Grass tastes better.
The way you humans eat
is much more cruel than us demons.
Not only do you kill them,
but you also boil them.
And
it doesn't taste good at all.
It's not as useful
as me absorbing
the moonlight essence at night.
Although you eat them raw without cooking,
the ultimate goal
is to sustain or elevate yourselves with other species' lives.
In this regard,
there is no difference between our two races.
You are clearly a Taoist,
not a monk.
Why are you so wordy?
Silver Lotus Grass,
are you going to eat it or not?
Such a good thing,
how could I not eat it?
I see you
practicing under the moonlight at night.
But it seems you don't practice any spells for fighting enemies.
I don't want to practice any killing spells.
We flower demons
are not born to fight with humans.
I just want
to be beautiful
and smell good
every day.
But the world is tough.
You still need the ability to protect yourself.
So you mean
I can attack humans?
That's not what I meant.
If I want to become lethal,
watering with blood is the fastest way.
No way.
You say no to everything.
What exactly do you want?
Learn some self-defense spells from me.
I don't want to learn.
It's difficult and tiring,
and boring.
I won't learn.
Let's go.
Cultivate.
Daoist Master,
I'm here to bother you again.
You...
A demon!
Cultivator, why
are you here?
I...
My purpose here is no longer important.
Daoist,
is that a demon hiding behind you?
She is a demon.
But it has nothing to do with you.
Daoist Yuren,
why are you protecting a demon?
She has never harmed anyone.
You cannot treat her like this.
Demons are demons.
Humans are humans.
Demons and humans walk different paths.
Those not of our kind
are sure to have different hearts.
They must be eradicated.
I beg this cultivator
to let her go.
Daoist.
How many of our people have the demon and monster tribes killed?
My parents died at their hands.
These evil demons
must be eliminated.
Little flower demon,
run away!
Don't even think about escaping.
Miss,
are you in some kind of trouble?
The world is ruthless.
Demonic cultivation is difficult.
Leave after your injuries heal.
No.
Taoist Master,
are there any demons around here?
Around here,
there are no harmful demons.
Little flower demon,
run away!
No!
I see that at night,
you cultivate under the moonlight.
But it seems I haven't practiced any offensive spells.
If I want to become lethal,
watering with blood is the fastest way.
Such similar soul fluctuations.
Such a similar feeling.
But,
you are not him.
It's been thirty years.
You have never opened your eyes.
I originally thought
you might have already reincarnated.
But the moment I saw him,
I really thought you had come back to life.
Although you two are so similar,
I know
that person is not you.
Since that's the case,
then I will refine his soul.
It will definitely wake you up.
This is
the flower demon's memory.