Consciousness.
I think
I saw the Demon King's memories.
You...
Yes.
When his blood
dripped onto my hand,
I suddenly saw them.
And last time,
when I touched the wound on my neck,
I saw them too.
It seems that
whenever I touch someone's blood,
I can see their memories.
This ability...
Xiaoxue,
are you okay?
Danyu.
Danyu,
are you okay?
I was so scared.
You saved me again.
I'm glad you're fine.
Danyu,
are you hurt?
And Shishi,
how about you?
Danyu,
you were too reckless just now.
If it wasn't for Brother Li, you would have...
Brother Li,
your hand is bleeding.
Xiaoxue!
The Power of Heaven!
This is a refining material comparable to Origin Blood.
Xiaoxue,
you suffered internal injuries.
Is it serious?
Miss Mu,
your injury...
Xiaoxue,
is it because of the aftershock just now?
It's all my fault.
I failed to protect you.
Wuzhou,
don't panic.
My injury is not serious.
I can still hold on.
Brother Li,
how are your injuries?
It really is the classic cliché of the second male lead falling for the female lead.
But,
Demon Lord, oh, Demon Lord.
You two will never be happy.
In this small world,
the female lead belongs to the male lead.
If you actually fall in love with the female lead...
But you...
Borrow it for a moment.
You...
Hey.
What are you doing?
Healing.
Let me go.
I'm here again.
Consciousness.
He said I have
the purest Source Blood in the world.
Likong.
The Likong clan
has naturally special blood.
The energy within it
is a supreme medicine for the Nether Demons.
Although it has no effect on humans,
it provides a multiplied boost to
sacrifices, seals, and talisman drawing.
So,
they used their blood as an exchange
to seek the protection of the Tiandao Palace.
Tiandao Palace?
If you have
the purest Source Blood,
you would definitely be heavily protected.
At least ten Foundation Establishment disciples of Tiandao Palace
would stay by your side at all times.
How could you grow up outside?
I know this.
It should be her mother
who took her out of
that palace you mentioned.
Ran away?
I don't have the extra energy to trace this history for now.
We can only wait for a chance in the future
to find out the reason.
Now, remember this.
Before, the demon lord used himself as a foundation to sacrifice the Daughter of the World,
unleashing supreme power,
and ultimately destroying the world directly.
The Daughter of the World is suitable for the heavenly sacrifice
because of her special soul.
And you,
possessing the purest Source Blood,
are even more suitable than her.
So I'm also suitable for this heavenly sacrifice.
What a sad reality.
From another perspective,
it's also a good thing.
At least,
he probably won't want to kill you in the near future.
That seems to make sense.
The world's trajectory
has completely shifted now.
I don't know how it will develop later.
But having changes
is a good thing after all.
It's just that
I can't stay awake all the time.
You can only rely on yourself for now.
You're going to sleep again?
Little Yiyi?
Goodbye.
I've finished chatting.
Why isn't he done yet?
Hurry up.
Are you done?
I'm about to become anemic.
Was I talking too loud just now?
Anyway,
he's like this now
because he saved us.
Um...
Thank you.
Thank you for saving us.
Aren't you afraid of me?
That's a different matter.
You saved us,
so you are our benefactor.
Thanking you is the least we can do.
Is that so?
Then remember this.
Your life now
belongs to me.
This is supposed to be a bossy CEO speech,
so why does it sound so cringeworthy?
Danyu.
Brother Li.
Where did you take Danyu?
Ask her.
Danyu,
your injuries are all healed?
Went to treat my injuries.
You went to
treat injuries?
Danyu,
are you
really healed?
Yes.
My injuries are all healed.
Just a little anemic.
Brother Li,
your injuries
look a bit serious.
I can hold on for now.
Xiaoxue,
are you feeling better?
It's fine now.
Since
everyone is here,
let's go.
Wuzhou,
although there are no demons in this village,
demonic energy still lingers.
Remember
to notify a sect that can clear it
to deal with the aftermath.
Don't worry.
Later,
I will notify the cultivators of Tiandao Palace
to handle it.
Let's go.
Danyu,
let me sleep with you tonight.
I can stay up all night to take care of you.
No need, no need.
Look, my injuries are all healed.
Then,
how about
I give you a massage?
After fighting all night,
you must be tired.
No thanks.
I'm sleepy.
Let's just go to bed early.
Then how about
we go back and take a bath together to relax?
I'd rather not.
She has to serve me when we get back.
I don't have time to play house with you.
Let's begin.
Chunyi.
We only have five
blood talismans left.
How many do you plan to use
in this village?
Use them all.
All of them?
This...
The Likong clan is scarce now,
and the supply of blood talismans is decreasing every year.
We should use them sparingly.
You're right.
We should save them.
But...
The demonic aura in this village is too heavy.
If we don't use them all,
I'm afraid we can't settle this.
Alright.
When we get back,
I must apply for a subsidy from the sect.
But Chunyi,
this Likong clan is
too weak, isn't it?
Our Heavenly Dao Palace
raises them with the best resources,
and gives them priority for all the good stuff.
We disciples
don't even get our turn.
Yet the people of their clan
are actually decreasing every year.
Is it really that hard
just to provide some blood talismans?