Xiaoxue,
are you sure
you want to go in with me?
This could be a point of no return.
Why are you being so chatty today?
I,
I am just worried.
Worried.
You risked your life to save me,
why can't I
give up my future
and take a gamble with you?
Xiaoxue.
Let's go.
Everyone.
Tiandao Palace acts perversely
and disregards human relations.
We can't let them continue like this.
We should unite
and seek justice for the Likong Clan.
If it's just about seeking justice,
you can go by yourself.
Why drag us into it?
Besides,
I don't even know anyone from Likong.
Leader Zhang,
you can't say that.
The Likong Clan has been imprisoned and oppressed for years.
They have already...
It's just exploiting the Likong Clan.
It shouldn't be that serious.
Exactly.
We don't have deep ties with the Likong Clan.
It hasn't come to this, has it?
Leader Xu,
Leader Gao,
they sacrificed a whole clan.
They're almost wiped out.
Is that not serious?
Anyway, Tiandao Palace didn't sacrifice me.
They are the strongest human force.
Even if you gather all the sects,
do you think
you can beat them?
Sect leaders,
we are not trying to start a war with Tiandao Palace right now.
We just want to ask
why they did this.
By uniting all sects,
we can put pressure on them.
In the end,
they just want to seek justice for the Likong Clan.
If we're just going for a discussion,
I
am willing to go with
Young Master Wei.
If the Likong Clan really made such a huge sacrifice,
it's only right that we
go and ask.
But what if
our questioning
leads to a fight?
Tell me,
what should we do?
Fighting the Tiandao Palace for the Likong Clan
or getting beaten at the Tiandao Palace
is not worth it.
Everyone,
I just want to say one more thing.
If one day
we
are confined and raised like the Likong Clan
because of our own uniqueness,
then what
should we do?
Just obediently deliver ourselves to them?
That's right.
Yeah.
I'm almost fully recovered.
Let's go.
I'll take you to find Wei Wuzhou.
Okay.
If...
I mean, if...
After I get my revenge
and stop,
will you stay with me?
Is he...
confessing his feelings?
He's asking me to stay.
I...
If the deal is done,
you don't need to stay in this world.
That's a bad idea.
Lu Danyu,
we should find a way to seal him permanently.
Do we still need to do that now?
Yiyi,
I feel
he won't harm this world.
Also,
don't worry.
I won't say yes to him.
Mom and Dad
are still waiting for me at home.
No need to hesitate.
After I get my revenge,
I will stop.
This way.
Sneaking up from behind,
we have a better chance of winning.
Sneaking in like this,
are we sure it's okay?
If we don't sneak in like this,
do you want to attack from the front?
I...
Just tell me if you can beat them.
All right.
Stop arguing.
Aren't you afraid of drawing the attention of Tiandao Palace?
We're already here.
Are we still afraid of being discovered?
You can't put it that way.
Something's up.
Taishu Yi.
Why is he here?
That is the question I should be asking you all.
Although this place is hundreds of miles away from Tiandao Palace,
it is still Tiandao Palace's territory.
Why are you all here?
This...
Well...
We...
You all
couldn't possibly be here just for a visit.
Palace Master Taishu.
We came today
because we have a question for you.
Why did you sacrifice the Likong Clan
to bring success to your Tiandao Palace?
You mean them?
What do you mean by sacrifice?
Everything they did
was for the stability of the entire human race.
That's called contribution.
I, Taishu Yi, gave them this opportunity.
They should be grateful.
What a great honor this is!
But before this,
I didn't even know of their existence.
Your so-called honor
is just the honor of your Tiandao Palace.
Your Tiandao Palace,
although becoming the leader of the human race,
has hands
covered in the blood of humans.
Those who achieve great things
all have blood on their hands.
But at least their names
will remain in the history books of the human race,
for future generations
to sing their praises.
Palace Master Taishu.
Your words,
aren't they a bit too high-sounding?
Just a phrase of singing praises
wipes out the fact that the Likong people are nearly extinct.
Could it be that over the years,
what your Tiandao Palace did to them
never happened?
Their Tiandao Palace has always been like this.
Hypocritical,
and two-faced.
Lanqi Moyuan.