♪In such an unexpected way♪
♪I came across you♪
♪It was a romantic opportunity♪
♪When we exchanged faith♪
♪In the name of you and me♪
♪Youth starts quietly♪
♪Then you and I are together♪
♪Tired but excited we run along♪
♪Destiny is a mystery But I’m fearless♪
♪Because of you I never shrink back♪
♪In my hands hides my life♪
♪Keep it for me forever♪
♪Let’s be gentle to each other♪
♪My love Everything is precious♪
♪The world is noisy
But the future is promising♪
♪Because of you I expect more♪
♪Of a far-away world♪
=You Are My Hero=
=Episode 21=
I’m, I’m home now.
I still have five minutes.
How about we sit for a while?
OK.
Uh…
Last time you said
I chose sunflowers on purpose
because your face is big.
So I…
I specially picked
baby’s breath
for you.
Is…
Is this one OK?
They have really small “faces”..
Thank you.
Is this
the alarm clock ringing?
Time
is
up.
You may go back now.
You’re holding my hand. I can’t get off.
I… I… I…
I let go of it.
It’s you. You didn’t loosen your hand.
I…
I’m getting off now.
OK.
I’m leaving.
I…
I’m going home now.
♪Give you my missing♪
♪It’s easy to bear♪
♪I recall your words in my mind♪
♪It’s difficult to understand♪
♪The sky is more blue♪
♪The moon is more beautiful♪
♪I’m so insensible to feel it♪
♪I don’t understand your love♪
♪I will persist with smile♪
♪Change the result♪
♪Exchange our minds♪
♪Love can be ignited♪
♪Like messy palette♪
♪Various colors♪
♪Describes the appearance of♪
♪Happiness♪
♪Suddenly clear persist♪
♪Change the result♪
♪Exchange our minds♪
♪Love can be ignited♪
♪Like messy palette♪
♪Various colors♪
♪Describes the appearance of♪
♪Happiness♪
(Nurse Station)
Dr. Mi.
Chen Feifei went for Mr. Shao.
She agreed to have an operation.
Really?
What did you say to her?
I didn’t say anything.
Maybe she figured it out herself.
You’ve been looking good recently.
Is it for me?
Or else?
You treated me last time.
It’s a return.
Thank you, Mr. Shao.
-Mr. Shao.
-Yanshan.
Chen Feifei’s operation
is difficult.
Come and help with Mi Ka.
-OK.
Feifei.
You have to do several check-ups
to prepare for the surgery.
Could you let me finish this?
This was
our reporting performance.
You can’t see me in the pictures.
I was just a supporting actor.
Have you ever watched a Yue opera?
So I made a right choice
of changing my career.
Modern people have a rapid pace of life.
Things that can catch on
bring stimulation
to senses.
This kind of local opera
can’t be understood by modern people.
I don’t think so.
If someone can let me
watch that earlier,
I think I will like it.
Let’s go.
Let’s do check-ups.
(Xing Kelei: It’s getting cold.)
(Wear more clothes.)
Boyfriend?
The man you take a fancy to
should be an excellent man.
There used to be a man
treating me like this before.
How about now?
He’s left.
After I fell ill.
It’s weird.
We used to
be together all the time before.
One day I suddenly found
that I’ve never
seen him clearly.
You may get lucky.
I have a boyfriend.
Let me bring you good luck in love.
How can we cut a bit more
without destroying
the nerve?
Absolutely impossible.
The spinal cord
is full of nerves
while astrocytoma
has infiltrative growth.
There is no way to cut it clearly.
Don’t think of anything now.
Just adhere to one principle.
Cut as much as you can
within the warning range of nerves.
Moreover, Mi Ka,
don’t overthink
before the operation.
Remember three words.
Try your best.
OK.
Let’s start now.
Scalpel.
Monopolar electrosurgery.
Milling cutter.
Micro-scissors.
I’m cutting off the emergency membrane
to find out the tumor location.
Tumor is found.
Microstripper.
Tumor pliers.
Sample is found.
Send it for rapid diagnosis.
Bipolar.
Tweezers.
We are doing the operation and waiting
for the outcome at the same time.
Hello.
We have the laboratory report.
It’s malignant astrocytoma.
OK.
We got the result.
It means
the tumor can’t be fully resected.
Go on.
Try to cut more
while remaining the function.
Yanshan.
Watch the SEP.
Once the indicator drops
below 50%,
tell it to me.
Otherwise,
it will cause irreversible influence
on the patient’s spinal cord.
OK.
It’s to 45%.
No more cutting.
Ready for suture.
Chen Feifei is awake.
How is she?
She asked me to give you
this letter.
She was smiling
while giving me this letter.
You should imagine her smile
on reading this letter.
OK.
Dr. Mi.
When you are reading this letter,
I know it must be because
the operation result isn’t as our wish.
Please forgive me for using
the way of writing a letter to tell you
my decision of giving up the
follow-up treatment.
Please allow me to leave
this world decently
with my beauty.
I’m very grateful
to meet you
at the end of my life.
You told me to fight back against fate.
Yes.
It wants to torture me
and make me suffer.
I won’t.
I will try to pursue joy
in the rest of time.
No matter it’s a month or a day.
I will make it worthwhile.
Thank you, Dr. Mi.
What’s wrong?
I quit.
I’m tired.
Hey.
You just quit without sweating.
You asked me to come.
I asked you to come
with Xia.
It’s boring for me to practice with you.
I’ve told you many times
that the one she likes is Shu Wenbo.
Do you mean you are better
friend with Shu Wenbo?
I’m his friend too.
We are competing fairly.
It’s not a problem.
Fine.
Except for sending me
the wedding invitation card,
don’t ask me for anything
between Mi Ka and you.
You just need to give the whip-round.
Seems everything
is going well.
That’s fine.
It’s time to enter the next step.
Next?
What is it?
You don’t need to ask me.
Seems you need a spanking.
What are you doing?
Can we talk
about something without injury?
The next step for example.
Say it.
Have a trip.
Trip?
Yes.
Only trip can bring you an opportunity.
What are you thinking about?
I’m saying only trip
can bring you an opportunity
to know each other better and see
if you can mutually make a compromise.
What are you thinking about?
Go to a home stay nearby.
Keep away from the hustle and bustle.
It can purify
your dirty spirit
and also help you understand life.
Right.
It’ll be Mi Ka’s birthday.
That’s just a perfect time.
I know a place
that is fit for birthday trip.
At the top of the mountains,
making a solemn pledge of love.
That’s wonderful.
You went with your ex-girlfriend?
No, ex-ex-girlfriend.
It also has honeymoon suites.
Order one-room or two?
It’s up to you.
Inviting is not as good as encountering.
How about
we invited Xia to go together?
What?
No way.
You are kicking down the ladder.
Mi Ka.
-Mr. Yi.
-Come here.
You are here for Mr. Shao?
No.
One of my friend
has a cardiac surgery in Renxin.
I’m here to see him.
I’ve been too busy recently.
I don’t have time
to study in your party.
We didn’t have a party lately.
Why?
You know
how busy you are.
And Xing Keyao
takes Shao Yuhan’s time
for advice on medical devices.
So he really doesn’t have any time.
Mr. Shao pays great attention
to Keyao’s business.
Of course.
They used to be lovers.
Oh, no.
You didn’t know
their relationship before?
I don’t know it.
Don’t let others know
I told you this.
Here is the thing
between them.
In my opinion,
maybe they’ve never
given up each other.
Or maybe it’s because they fell in love
with each other after meeting again.
They’d rather keep silent
than speaking it out.
They just think of it
without telling each other.
We are all very anxious about it.
I really want to push him forward.
(Xing Kelei)
You have a three-day holiday.
I’m also on the annual vacation.
Let’s go have a trip.
Mr. Yi.
Can you do me a favor?
And the honeymoon room.
One room or two?
Decide it yourself.
For two people,
two bedrooms
seem to be a bit extravagant.
If we order a one-bedroom house,
I can sleep on the sofa.
However, if it’s a one-bedroom house,
maybe she will
misunderstand me. Will she?
(Mi Ka: I booked a big house.)
(You don’t need to
book the accommodation.)
(Xing Kelei)
Why a big house for only two of us?
(Mi Ka: Someone else will go, too.)
Someone else?
(Xing Kelei)
Who is that?
(Mr. Shao)
Dr. Mi.
Patient of bed No. 3 isn’t good.
You’d better go take a look.
OK. Coming.
(Mi Ka: Mr. Shao)
Can you stop laughing?
Sorry.
I don’t mean it.
But it’s really funny.
Is Mr. Shao her family head
or her pet?
Why does she
always take him?
Can you tell me why?
We are dating.
But she takes Shao Yuhan with her.
I…
I don’t know. You can ask her.
I dare not.
It appears that I’m a stingy person.
You are not a generous man.
You said it yourself.
Two people should be frank
on being together.
You are unsatisfied with
her behaviors today, aren’t you?
Yes.
Send her the text and tell her.
Send it.
Timid?
Fine.
Why did you
decide to invite
unrelated people
without my permission?
Uh…
I still can’t.
Forget it.
What?
It’s sent.
You…
I’ve sent it.
Don’t send it. I…
Uh…
It can’t be withdrawn.
I’m screwed.
Restrain your grief.
Here you are.
Take a haw to steady nerves.
Are you tired?
Give it to me.
When girls get mad,
firstly,
she acts as if nothing were on her mind.
But she gives you the cold shoulder.
She must have been getting angry.
What do you want to eat tonight?
You make the arrangement.
It’s all OK for me.
Second,
she keeps silent.
When a girl gets mad,
she says nothing.
Pretending to be a dumb.
There is a symbolic action of girls
when they are extremely angry.
She will turn away
with her back to you.
It’s a serious problem.
It means she refuses to communicate.
Then what should I do?
Make an apology.
When a woman
gets mad,
it’s utterly unjustifiable.
You only need to apologize.
I didn’t mean
to blame.
I just want to ask
why you
invited Mr. Shao.
It’s we two…
Can I
take a nap?
I’m sleepy.
Silly girl!
She sleeps every time she takes my car.
Is she that relieved on being with me?
Right.
I’m her “uncle special police”.
I fell asleep again.
Every time when I am in your car,
it’s easy for me to fall asleep.
It means I am at ease
when I’m with you.
What’s the time?
10:30 p.m.
I’m too tired.
I had four operations today.
Why didn’t you awake me?
We agreed to watch the film together.
I think looking at you like this
is more interesting than watching film.
I didn’t check my phone
in the afternoon.
All…
The whole afternoon?
No.
Don’t check it.
No way.
What if I miss
-something important?
-No.
(Xing Kelei: Why did you decide)
(to invite unrelated people)
(without my permission?)
I… I didn’t mean that.
I was just…
I was just asking for it.
No blame on you.
I’m sorry.
I shouldn’t have made my own decision
of inviting so many people
to go with us.
Love is about two people.
I should have discussed with you.
The… So I…
You won’t get mad, will you?
No.
But it’s true that
there is a special reason.
Mr. Shao
must go with us.
Why?
It’s partly because of you.
Me?
Shao Yuhan is my sister’s ex-boyfriend.
See?
You don’t know it, either.
I just know she
used to date someone.
But…
I know why she didn’t date others.
So she still loves Mr. Shao.
According to Mr. Yi Qian,
I suppose
they both love each other.
Neither of them has forgotten the other.
It’s really a pity, right?
Then what to do?
I have the same vacation
with Mr. Shao.
I intend to ask Mr. Shao out.
You may ask your sister out by lying.
Then she will definitely
rip my skin out.
Don’t worry. I will sew it on for you.
Thank you.
I will also ask Xia to go with us.
We will have more people.
It won’t be that embarrassing.
It’s like a coincidence.
What’s your opinion?
Well.
I will sacrifice.
What for?
You are rubbing my sister the right way
for not being bullied
after we get married, right?
What will you do to bully me?
Not me.
But my sister.
Of course I won’t bully you.
If your sister bullies me,
won’t you help me?
That’s the problem?
-Answer it.
-No.
Answer me.
What are you thinking?
Give it to me.
Peel it.
Reporter Xia.
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you, too!
I’ve finished the video
for the earthquake rescue last time.
I took it to Captain Hao.
Thank you for your hard work.
Do we have to be
so polite?
You refused me lately
when I asked you out.
Very busy with work?
Yes, I’ve been busy.
But I think
you are avoiding me on purpose.
I am not.
The…
It’s Mi Ka’s birthday this weekend.
Xing Kelei asked us to go on holiday
with Mi Ka in a home stay.
Will you go?
I…
I asked Xing Kelei for it.
He said you have time.
If you don’t go,
it means you are avoiding me.
Why need I
avoid you?
Right,
why do you have to
avoid me on purpose?
Do you mean I’m
different in your eyes?
You are afraid of seeing me.
I’m not.
Then go there.
Remember it.
I will pick you up at the weekend.
If you don’t come,
I will misunderstand that
I’m different from others
for you.
One, two, three, four.
-One, two, three, four.
-Xia.
Here you are.
Get on the car.
What?
Safety belt.
Thank you.
Here you are.
What’s it?
Open it and take a look.
It’s not salty this time.
I’ve tasted it.
You are allergic to eggs.
You remember it?
It’s OK. Please don’t worry.
I just tasted a very little
with my tongue.
Your mother taught me about it.
My mom called you again?
What did she say?
A lot.
I will tell you in the future.
Thank you.
How did you persuade Keyao
to go with us
for the trip?
I told her that
you want to marry me very much
and will make a proposal.
So she agreed.
How can you
flatter yourself
in such a good way?
Shameless.
It’s only for you.
Laugh.
Why are you laughing?
How could you speak out that words?
(Chen Tao)
I heard it’s your birthday,
Happy birthday.
Don’t take me as being disloyal.
I have a secret.
Captain Xing asked me
to sign a package
valuing thousands yuan for him.
I guess it’s for you.
There must be a surprise
for your romantic journey.
Pay some attention to it.
What?
You really want to make a proposal?
Here they are.
Xia.
Let me help.
I will park my car here.
Drive your car.
OK.
How did he
finally make the decision?
It’s hard at beginning, right?
I won’t tell you.
No.
It’s a meeting
for you
in the name of my birthday.
Changed your mind?
What are you saying?
You know what I’m saying.
Look, you are laughing.
Why should I laugh?
Look how happy you are.
Let’s go. Get on the car.
Will you sit here?
It’s for you.
What brings you here?
Yi Qian
said he ordered a holiday house
for me to have a trip.
Just now he called and said
he couldn’t come for his enteritis.
How about you? What brings you here?
For holiday.
Holiday?
Where are you living?
This house.
How about you?
Yi Qian told me
it’s over against here.
They are coming.
They asked you to come?
What a coincidence!
Mr. Shao, you…
What brings you here?
Yi Qian asked me to come.
Then where is he?
You don’t know?
I don’t know.
He isn’t feeling well.
He doesn’t feel well?
Mr. Yi said he would
come here for holiday with us.
And we ordered
a whole house.
You are so familiar with Yi Qian?
You even invited him for your birthday.
No. He heard it on that day.
And we agreed to come together.
It’s lively with more people.
It’s coincidence.
Xing Kelei, don’t hit me.
It’s really a coincidence.
It’s fate, right?
Yes. It’s fate.
Fate.
-Look the hair of you two.
-Fate.
It’s fate.
Let’s go take the suitcases.
You may get in first.
It’s OK. We can wait.
It’s really nice.
It’s large and bright.
Look.
It looks nice.
Yes.
We can fish here.
There are four rooms.
One for Wenbo and I.
One for Mi Ka and Xia.
I’ll take it.
And you…
One for each?
I don’t care.
OK.
Thank you.
You don’t care?
Go anywhere at will in the afternoon.
I will make you dishes tonight.
OK. Keyao?
OK. You never cook at home.
There are many interesting things here.
There are bicycles built for two,
and also a land for vegetable growing.
-For two?
-What land?
There are also manors here.
You may walk around.
OK.
I will take the things back.
Let me help.
For two. Four legs.
I feel I’m destined
with your brother.
(Wenbo’s Mom)
Hello, Mrs. Shu.
How is it?
Did he agree?
I’ve told you.
My silly son
is a riddle.
He needs to be reminded
before he knows what to do.
If he likes you,
I can tell by having a look at it.
It won’t lie.
Qingxia.
Remember it.
He always ran
everywhere in our village
since his childhood.
Hit on what he likes
to force him to accept.
OK.
I see, Mrs. Shu.
I really like you.
You are the one.
I’m waiting for you to call me mother.
I see.
See you, Mrs. Shu.
Are you ready?
Xia.
Where
are your purple high-heeled shoes?
I’m going hiking.
The air here is nice.
Go hiking?
It’s a big sunny day.
Aren’t you afraid of being tanned?
No.
I like to go hiking.
Do you
need someone to accompany you?
Will you go?
OK. I will take something for it.
I’m waiting here.
OK.
Nice.
You turned the corner.
What’s wrong?
Are you tired?
No.
I often go hiking.
For going hiking,
shoes are very important.
Yours are a bit tough.
It will rub the feet.
It’s best to wear hiking shoes.
It will make you comfortable
on walking.
I don’t think my shoes are bad.
You shoes…
Quickly.
Your shoes don’t have a problem.
Let’s go.
Don’t tell me it’s a coincidence.
That’s a coincidence.
Do you have a lot of free time?
What is it in your mind?
Sunset glow.
Late-life love.
It’s no big deal. Just have a try.
That’s not sunset glow.
Mi Ka.
Mr. Shao.
Let’s go buy something.
There are a lot. Do we still need more?
We have a lot here.
But you didn’t buy anything
I want to eat.
What…
What’s it?
I forgot the sea-ear.
Answer me.
How’s your enteritis?
It’s Yi Qian.
There are so many things here.
Let me help you.
Yes. Put it here.
OK.
What did I say just now?
Buy some sea-ear.
God.
Only the sea food and poultry now.
Oh my God!
Is it too obvious?
Yes.
But we are creating
opportunities for them.
What will we do?
Take some pictures.
Do you have the phone with you?
No.
Then…
Let’s go for a drive.
No key to car too.
Why are we so pitiful?
Just
take a walk.
♪My future is a fantasy♪
♪Where there is a sea of stars♪
♪And I will see you
Walking towards me♪
♪I feel lonely in the crowd♪
♪Watching the stories of others♪
♪And wondering
Who will conquer my heart♪
♪Because of an incident♪
♪My life has changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I won’t harm anyone♪
♪I won’t have any regrets♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I am the one
You can count on♪
♪I didn’t expect I would
Come across you♪
♪And thus my life changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I know what is hope♪
♪I’m afraid that I may hurt you♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I’m the one you can count on
Do you think the same as me♪
♪Love by accident
Yet it’s more than an accident♪
♪Love indeed exists♪
♪I think you’re free to love♪
♪Until I know it’s me
That can’t be separated from you♪
♪I rely on you too much♪
♪You’re bound to be my dearest♪