♪In such an unexpected way♪
♪I came across you♪
♪It was a romantic opportunity♪
♪When we exchanged faith♪
♪In the name of you and me♪
♪Youth starts quietly♪
♪Then you and I are together♪
♪Tired but excited we run along♪
♪Destiny is a mystery But I’m fearless♪
♪Because of you I never shrink back♪
♪In my hands hides my life♪
♪Keep it for me forever♪
♪Let’s be gentle to each other♪
♪My love Everything is precious♪
♪The world is noisy
But the future is promising♪
♪Because of you I expect more♪
♪Of a far-away world♪
=You Are My Hero=
=Episode 26=
What are you looking at?
A video of intracranial abscess surgery.
Xu Yanshan’s mother
is having surgery tomorrow.
I will be Dr. Wang’s assistant.
Is she okay with that?
It’s the basic quality
of every doctor
to treat patients equally.
She should at least
have some faith in me.
Your hand...
How did you injure your hand again?
I cut myself during training.
It’s just a minor injury.
A minor injury again?
You call every injury a minor injury.
But it has never been a minor one.
Worry about me?
I worry about you.
You are the captain
of the Tiger Assault Team.
Your health
concerns everyone’s safety.
It’s not that serious.
It is that serious.
Think about it.
When I was holding a grenade in my hand,
you were the only person
I can trust.
I basically
entrusted my life to you.
Captain Xing.
You have a great responsibility.
For those who might
entrust their lives to you
just like I did,
you have to protect yourself.
Don’t get hurt again.
What’s more,
when you told me
you are a cop,
I didn’t
feel that scared anymore.
And I thought
you are really handsome.
It’s a compliment.
I am handsome.
All right.
It’s cold outside. Just stay inside.
Well,
let me know when you
get back to the dorm.
Good luck with
your surgery tomorrow.
I’m leaving.
Good night.
Captain Hao, it’s me.
Something goes wrong with my body.
I don’t think
I can join the combat.
Do you have time tomorrow afternoon?
I want to talk to you.
Okay.
Mom, don’t be afraid.
Just get a sleep
and you will be all right.
I think you are more nervous than I’m.
-I’m not.
-Dr. Xu.
We are going to take the patient inside
for anesthesia.
Okay.
I’ll leave my mother to you.
Rest assured.
Auntie will be all right.
I...
How about
we go to the popular cafe
when you have time?
Okay.
(Neurosurgery)
(Medical Image)
Xiaoxiao. Xiaoxiao.
Dr. Wang asked you to go there.
Okay.
(Xing Kelei: Do you have time
this noon?)
(I have something to tell you.)
(I’ll wait for you in the lobby
of the hospital.)
(Mi Ka: I have an operation
this morning.)
(It might take some time.
Is 2:00 PM okay?)
Mi Ka.
I just met Captain Xing.
He is at Neurosurgery Outpatient.
Does any of his
team members feel uncomfortable again
and he accompanies him to see a doctor?
He didn’t mention it.
Okay.
I’ll go to send this first.
(Visitor Waiting Area)
The patient has been anesthetized.
Vital signs are normal.
Okay, let’s start.
Mi Ka, you’ll perform the operation.
I’ll supervise you.
Okay.
The patient has two abscess cavities
that are at some distance
from each other.
So let’s try to
remove these two lesions
with a bone window.
Use the milling cutter
to mill her bone flap first.
Milling cutter.
Attention.
Seal the border of the skull base
and endocranium with bone wax.
Open it after hanging the endocranium.
Be careful to protect the brain tissue.
Move! Move!
What’s the situation?
A three-vehicle collision.
What are the body temperature
and the blood pressure?
The body temperature is 36.
The blood pressure is 90 and 60.
It’s kind of serious.
Take the patient to the Emergency Room.
Okay, hurry up.
Move!
(Neurosurgery Operating Room)
Dr. Wang.
There is a victim of a car accident
in the Emergency Room who suffers
severe cerebral hemorrhage.
They need you to take a look there.
I’ll go to check it.
Mi Ka, go on.
Okay.
Jia Li, supervise her.
Notify me immediately
if there is any problem.
Yes.
The bleeding is increasing.
There is too much bleeding.
I can’t find the bleeding point.
Stay calm.
Watch carefully and suck the blood.
Use one more suction apparatus.
The patient’s blood pressure
begins to drop.
Her cerebellum is a little swollen.
It might affect the brain stem.
It’s dangerous.
Try to enlarge the bone window
to reduce pressure
and reveal the bleeding point
at the same time.
I found the bleeding point.
The gap is too big.
Electrocoagulation can’t stop it.
The blood pressure dropped to 70.
Give me a temporary aneurysm clip.
What’s the patient’s blood pressure now?
The blood pressure is 90.
Mi Ka.
You did a good job just now.
The most important thing is not to panic
when you encountered danger
during the operation.
The patient can be saved
only when the doctor doesn’t panic.
Yes.
But it’s mainly
because of Mr. Jia’s guidance.
Not at all.
I have said no more than
three sentences in total.
Well,
I have something else to do.
I should leave.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Don’t worry,
the operation was successful.
Thank you, Dr. Wang.
You should thank
Mi Ka and Dr. Jia.
They handled
the crisis with calm.
Where’s Mi Ka?
She got something to do and she left.
I just finished the operation.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It’s okay.
Whose medical history is that?
Didn’t I tell you
that my friend gets
an adenoma of the pituitary gland?
Actually,
it’s me.
What’s your plan now?
I just made an appointment
with an expert this afternoon.
I want to see the doctor first.
Why haven’t you told me till now?
I also need some time
to accept it.
If you tell me,
we can take it together
and figure it out together.
You are already stressed.
I don’t want to cause you any trouble.
I am your girlfriend.
We’ve been through
so many things together.
Why didn’t you tell me
such an important thing?
No matter how strong
and how powerful you are out there,
I don’t care that much.
I want you to be totally real
in front of me.
Even it’s your most vulnerable side,
I can accept it.
I’m willing to be there for you.
Alright?
You also said
it’s not a big problem.
Whether it’s a big problem or not,
you are the one who gets it.
Did you tell Keyao?
Not yet.
I haven’t figured out
how to tell her about it.
I also think
you need a craniotomy
as soon as possible.
How long will it take
for him to recover?
It depends on the individual situation.
This kind of surgery
is not difficult for us.
But a craniotomy is always risky,
especially considering
the job of Captain Xing.
What about the minimally
invasive surgery?
Didn’t many patients
have minimally invasive surgery
in such cases?
The location of his tumor is not good.
The tumor is relatively large.
The difficulty of a minimally
invasive surgery
is much bigger than a craniotomy.
And it’s hard to cut the tumor clean.
Yes,
it takes less time to recover from
a minimally invasive surgery.
But if anything goes wrong
during the operation,
it would be the opposite to
what you want.
Well,
I’ll do the craniotomy.
How soon can we do it?
Let me see.
Next week.
Okay, next week is fine.
Have you really decided?
My physical condition
has totally affected my work.
Besides,
what’s more important than my health
is my responsibility.
I should be responsible to my teammates
and to the people.
I can’t work
no matter what.
I’d better face it.
No matter what happens,
I’m here with you.
If you are not here with me,
where else do you want to do?
Here.
It’s delicious.
Sorry.
It’s okay, put it down.
I’ll go to the restroom
and clean it.
Sit down.
Have a seat.
I mean,
if someone else stains his clothes,
would he still be that calm?
It must be a torment
for a neat person like him.
Why don’t you try it next time?
No need.
I have an unquenchable thirst for life.
Your breakfast.
Here is your breakfast.
Thank you.
You know what,
I’ve always had a question.
But I don’t know if I should ask it.
If I say you shouldn’t,
will you not ask it?
No.
That’s it.
I mean,
how did you get Shao Yuhan?
Who told you that I was
the one who chased him?
That’s what everyone said in school.
They said
that you chased him
to the elevator.
Wait!
Shao!
I...
I want to tell you
about changing
the surgical records.
Are you talking to me?
Change what?
Rena.
How are you doing?
A lot of work. Exhausted.
What are you doing today?
I’m not sure.
These stuffs.
Maybe grab a cup of coffee later.
Okay then, call me.
-Okay.
-Okay. Rena.
Okay.
-Bye.
What did you just say
about changing something?
The hematoma range
and the description of
the bleeding point I recorded
are not very clear.
I want to change it.
That’s why you got yourself
panting like this?
Just to tell me about that?
Although it is a
simulated surgical drape,
I still want to be precise.
And also,
it was my fault
that I accidentally
spilled coffee on you.
But you can’t
stop me from changing it
for that reason.
What’s your name?
Tracy.
Xing Keyao.
Put it on my desk on time
tomorrow morning.
And also,
you spilled coffee on me.
Remember to buy another one for me.
What’s wrong?
It seems that this question
is difficult to answer.
What question is difficult to answer?
A question that doesn’t
need to be answered.
Got it.
Refusing to answer means
a guilty conscience.
A guilty conscience means a tacit yes.
What were you two talking about?
-Nothing.
By the way,
there is an activity
of visiting the organic farm
this afternoon.
Do you want to go together?
This afternoon...
Come on, what’s the silence about?
Are you going or not?
Anything is okay.
I’m up for anything.
Anything is okay for you.
And you are up for anything.
So you are going.
Just keep it simple
and tell me you can go.
You two can really drag your feet.
Let’s meet this afternoon
in front of the hotel.
Okay.
Have the porridge.
How are you doing now?
It’s okay.
You asked for a leave
last time because of
the tumor in your brain?
Yes.
I’m here today
to tell you about it.
I want to quit the combat
and do logistics.
Have you figured it out?
The disease I have
will affect my vision.
I can’t affect the whole team
just because of me.
Who do you think
is suitable
to take your place?
Wenbo and Wenjing
work well together.
I think they are perfectly qualified
for the sniper project.
As for the new off-road motorcycle,
Wenbo has been practicing it
for a long time.
If it’s a manhunt in complex terrain,
Luo Ting is the best for it.
Okay.
I’ll do it as you said.
Wenjing will start to get trained
for the shooting project
you joined before
as your substitute.
Substitute?
Captain Hao, I...
Kelei.
You are the best
trainee I’ve ever coached.
I know
you would never give up
until the last moment.
Me too.
As for whether to replace you or not,
we will make a decision
based on your physical condition
after the operation.
Okay.
Captain Xing.
You are off today.
Why are you here to get trained?
Captain Xing.
We will stay with you today.
We will practice as long as you do.
We all know
your condition.
We all want to be with you.
We don’t know what to do
except to stay with you.
Captain Xing.
What are we going to practice next?
You are finally off.
Have some rest.
We...
We can stay...
This is an order.
Everyone, stand up.
Never mind, let’s leave him alone
for a while.
Left turn!
Lockstep marching!
Hello, Mi Ka.
What’s the matter?
Xing Kelei has a pituitary adenoma
in his brain
which is pressing against
his optic nerve.
The doctor recommended
surgery as soon as possible.
I see.
Dr. Shao.
How are you going to thank me?
Why should I thank you?
You know why.
If I didn’t bring up with the activity,
how could you ask her out?
Mind your own business first
and find a girlfriend.
You are...
Really...
She is here.
Well...
What’s wrong?
Mi Ka called me
and said that they found
a pituitary adenoma in Kelei’s brain.
We can’t make it clear over the phone.
I’m not going with you this afternoon.
I’ve booked
the latest flight to go back.
I have an important meeting
tomorrow.
I can’t go back with you.
Well, don’t worry.
Send me all his
examination results and reports
when you get back.
I’ll take a look.
Thank you.
Go up and pack your stuff.
I’ll wait for you in the lobby
and take you to the airport.
Okay.
Well...
Forget about me.
Go ahead and do what you need to do.
I’ll take care of myself.
No one is worried about you.
Bye.
Goodbye.
This is the menu.
Well, are you stalking me?
I’ve known you for years.
Do I need to stalk you?
You would come here
when you feel down.
-Two bowls of beef noodles!
Okay.
I remember it was Lu Feng
who found this restaurant.
We used to come here to have noodles
every time we got punished
during training
when we were young.
We were naughty at that time
and we did need some lessons.
I remember it was
Captain Shen who coached us.
Yeah.
What’s that look?
Why do I think you need a lesson?
What’s wrong with my...
Don’t implicate me if you feel itchy.
I...
-I...
-Don’t mess with Captain Hao.
Do I have a problem?
We will be brothers
for a lifetime.
Here are your noodles.
Thank you.
Madam, another bowl of
beef noodles here.
Okay.
I’m starved.
Speak of the devil.
Aren’t you supposed to be in Thailand?
Don’t you know there is
a means of transportation called plane?
It takes only a few hours to come back.
I bought a ticket tonight
to fly back.
Just for a bowl of noodles?
How expensive the noodles are?
It’s because of you.
I was wondering why you were
weird that day.
Why didn’t you tell us?
You can’t carry it on your own,
can’t the three of us
carry it together?
Your noodles.
Do you remember
that whoever lost during the training
would pay the meal?
I never paid for it anyway.
I remember it was you all the time.
He also paid before.
I was having a fever.
Otherwise how could I lose to you
with short legs?
Whose legs are short?
Don’t you insult me.
When I first
entered the police academy,
the leader said
that my image is suitable for
undercover work.
Like Chen Yongren in Infernal Affairs.
Who is calling me?
It’s obviously calling me.
You are Liu Jianming.
Here is your song.
It’s obviously your
shower song.
What...
♪Wind and rain come and go♪
Go on.
♪Another round of spring and autumn♪
Stop it, there are many people here.
Keep going.
Stop it.
♪Golden shield♪
Sit down. Sit down.
Sit down.
Why are you
like a ghost?
You should tell me
that you would come back.
Are you going to tell me
when you are
in the ICU?
I see.
It’s not a serious illness.
It’s not a big deal.
So I didn’t tell you.
What’s serious?
Is it serious when they ask me
to collect your body?
Can’t you wish me well?
Let me ask you,
if our parents know it,
what should I tell them?
I’m your sister,
but I don’t know anything.
I know you are a tough guy.
You want to handle
everything on your own.
But you are my younger brother.
You will only
make me worry more in this way.
Do you know it?
I know.
Well, it’s just
I have a pituitary adenoma
in my brain.
I do think you have a tumor
in your brain!
You studied medicine.
You know
it’s not a big deal.
So,
don’t worry.
It’s okay.
It’s not a big deal.
I’m not worried.
I’m just angry.
I studied neurosurgery.
Don’t I know it?
Isn’t it just a tumor
in your brain?
It’s a simple surgical procedure.
A really simple one.
Well, are you hungry?
Do you want egg noodles?
Less oil for the luncheon meat.
All right.
Are you all right?
I’m fine.
I’ve heard about
Xing Kelei.
A pituitary adenoma
is not a major operation.
Don’t worry too much about it.
I know it as a doctor.
But as his girlfriend,
it seems impossible not to worry.
But I believe
you can adjust yourself
and accompany him through
this difficult time.
Thank you.
I should thank you
for what you did for my mom
in the operating room.
It’s my duty.
Do you remember
the patient with thoracic trauma
when we got stuck in the elevator?
I couldn’t be as brave
as you.
But if you were like me,
maybe my mother
would still be
in the ICU.
Thank you for your understanding.
Mi Ka.
I used to take you as my friend
because I think you were inferior to me.
Later I found out
that Dr. Shao thinks highly of you
and it made me really jealous.
Perhaps
that was when
I got on the wrong road.
Yanshan.
You have always been
a quick learner
and also
a professional doctor in my mind.
Mi Ka.
I’m sorry.
I accept your apology.
We are still friends
just like before.
I told you that you don’t
need to pick me up.
Well,
you start to dislike me now?
No.
It’s my duty
to serve you well.
But the driver
can’t drive today.
How about we take a taxi?
Let’s take a bus.
There should be empty seats
right now. Okay?
Okay.
Let’s go.
Let me do it.
Don’t move.
Stay there
and wait for the food.
It’s rare to
have my sister’s cooking.
Well,
have I ever treated you badly?
When you were young
and no higher than the cooking bench,
wasn’t I cooking for you?
Really?
Thank you.
Let’s eat.
You are really my sister.
No meat at all.
You should have more vitamins.
Okay.
Have a taste of my sister’s
excellent scrambled egg with tomatoes.
She is never stingy with eggs.
There are a lot of eggs.
That’s it.
Are you off these days?
I need to go back
and finish the handover.
Hurry up and finish it.
Then take a rest for a few days.
It’s not like that the earth won’t turn
without you.
I haven’t had surgery yet.
Why should I rest?
I think Keyao
is totally right.
You can’t be too tired before surgery.
I happen to have two days off.
Why don’t you
begin your
days off earlier?
It has been a long time since we
went out together last time.
We can go shopping
and watch movies together.
Aren’t you going to
take the year-end assessment?
How do you have any day off?
I’m all ready.
Well,
I’m going to ski in Canada this winter.
Take Mi Ka to the mall
and buy me the latest
ski suit.
Okay.
You have a room of ski suits
and you haven’t worn them many times.
Are you going to buy more?
I want the latest one.
Come on, can you two act normally?
You are making me more nervous.
It’s like something serious
is going to happen.
Don’t talk nonsense.
If you really want to
make me feel better,
you
prepare for the exam.
You
wash your ski suit
and keep wearing it.
Come on, let’s eat.
Have more.
I mean,
I’m being treated too well
-for my illness.
-Have vitamins.
Eat.
Shrimps.
It is too much.
I’m like a lord now.
Come on, massage my legs.
Are your legs uncomfortable?
Come on.
Where else?
Here, and here...
-Your shoulders are uncomfortable?
-Yes.
-Come on.
-All right.
-Let me give you a massage.
Are you feeling better now?
Are you showing me how tender you are?
Harder. Come on.
I did.
Let me wash the dishes.
No need, go to watch TV.
Let me do it.
Where’s Keyao?
She is out.
She wants to give you a chance to show
the virtuous and diligent side of you.
♪Because of an incident♪
♪My life has changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I won’t harm anyone♪
♪I won’t have any regrets♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I am the one
You can count on♪
In fact,
I think he
cares about it a lot.
He just won’t tell me
and won’t express his feelings.
He feels upset inside.
Sometimes
the person who gets sick
is not the one who suffers the most.
The one who suffers the most
is the person who cares about him.
I really hope
I can help him with it
and do something for him.
But later I found out
there is nothing I can do.
Nothing will work.
You can do it.
Didn’t I lose all my hope
at first?
You are the one
who made me stick to it.
You made me believe
that there are miracles.
Whatever you want to do,
you will make it.
(Intradural operation)
Thank you.
Dr. Shao?
Aren’t you attending
the academic conference?
Yeah.
But
I can also choose to come back early.
I heard about Xing Kelei.
It’s not
a big operation.
It’s just...
You worry that he can’t
go back to the front line
after the surgery, right?
Because
if he has the craniotomy,
it’s very likely that he can’t
do a lot of actions during training.
So you want to
look for more information
and see if he can have
transsphenoidal microsurgery?
Dr. Wang said
that his tumor is big
and its location is not good.
It’s very difficult to do
the transsphenoidal microsurgery
and totally remove the tumor.
But I think I can do it.
Although this operation
is risky and difficult,
I’ve read all his reports.
I can try it.
Thank you, Dr. Shao.
I am a doctor.
What’s wrong?
We have talked about it
and figured out a plan.
Dr. Shao said he can do
the transsphenoidal microsurgery
for you.
It would take less time
to recover from it
and the incision would be smaller.
Maybe you can still join
the combat.
That’s why you want to see me so late?
Yes.
I know you care about it.
You just pretend not to care.
Your tumor is big
and its location is not good.
Actually, there is
a certain risk
of having the
transsphenoidal microsurgery.
But Dr. Shao said
he has confidence in
minimizing the risk.
A craniotomy is safer.
But it takes less time
to recover from microsurgery.
I’ll let you
decide
on your own.
I’ll support you
no matter what you choose.
♪My future is a fantasy♪
♪Where there is a sea of stars♪
♪And I will see you
Walking towards me♪
♪I feel lonely in the crowd♪
♪Watching the stories of others♪
♪And wondering
Who will conquer my heart♪
♪Because of an incident♪
♪My life has changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I won’t harm anyone♪
♪I won’t have any regrets♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I am the one
You can count on♪
♪I didn’t expect I would
Come across you♪
♪And thus my life changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I know what is hope♪
♪I’m afraid that I may hurt you♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I’m the one you can count on
Do you think the same as me♪
♪Love by accident
Yet it’s more than an accident♪
♪Love indeed exists♪
♪I think you’re free to love♪
♪Until I know it’s me
That can’t be separated from you♪
♪I rely on you too much♪
♪You’re bound to be my dearest♪