♪In such an unexpected way♪
♪I came across you♪
♪It was a romantic opportunity♪
♪When we exchanged faith♪
♪In the name of you and me♪
♪Youth starts quietly♪
♪Then you and I are together♪
♪Tired but excited we run along♪
♪Destiny is a mystery But I’m fearless♪
♪Because of you I never shrink back♪
♪In my hands hides my life♪
♪Keep it for me forever♪
♪Let’s be gentle to each other♪
♪My love Everything is precious♪
♪The world is noisy
But the future is promising♪
♪Because of you I expect more♪
♪Of a far-away world♪
=You Are My Hero=
=Episode 17=
Captain Xing!
Dr. Mi!
-Dr. Mi!
-Captain Xing!
Dr. Mi!
Captain Xing!
-Dr. Mi!
-Captain Xing!
Dr. Mi!
Xing Kelei.
Xing Kelei!
Xing Kelei! Xing Kelei!
Mi Ka!
Don’t waste your time.
Stay with me for a while.
Okay.
Xing Kelei.
Oxygen.
I don’t need it.
I have something to say to you.
In the lavender garden last time,
my notebook
was found by you.
Actually, I have another notebook.
I expected to read it to you.
But now I suddenly find
I…
I can even recite it.
Mi Ka.
Colon.
I want to solemnly and warmly
invite you.
We two…
Listen.
I beg you, listen to me.
I know I am not perfect.
But I wish to
build
an impregnable city for you.
Regardless of the rainstorms outside,
I hope to bring you
sunny days
so that you can bask in the sunshine
and live happily without worry
in flowers.
If you also love me a little bit,
please promise me
to be strong this time
and leave here.
Mi Ka, you must leave here.
Sorry,
I’m not sure I could.
Xing Kelei!
You must leave here.
Captain Xing.
You wake up, Captain Xing.
Where is Dr. Mi?
The doctor…
The doctor said your right hand is okay.
Where is Dr. Mi?
Oxygen was severely undersupplied
in the gallery then
and she put the oxygen mask on you.
And then...
What happened then?
Tell me what happened then!
Then she…
Say something.
I am here.
You spoke so loudly.
It seems you have recovered well.
What a moron!
Captain Xing, I must tell you.
Captain Shu immediately
rushed over without hesitation
once he knew you were
injured and unconscious.
You don’t know how anxious he was!
You should have made it more clear.
No.
You were too anxious then.
You hung up
before I finished my words.
Yes.
But it was
very dangerous then.
You…
If we had arrived a little later,
you wouldn’t have been here
after you fainted away.
Stop it!
Dr. Mi and Captain Xing
are people of great fortunes.
You seem idle.
Go out.
We… we are just worried about you.
Zhuo Wenjing is back in Jiangning now.
She just called and asked
about your conditions.
Over?
No… you…
Get out. Hurry up!
I want to be with you.
I don’t need you. Just get out.
I still have something to say to you.
That is enough.
Don’t keep talking about it.
Shu Wenbo.
Are you silly?
You three!
Get out of here right away.
Crazy guys.
Sit down.
Put on the clothes.
Thanks.
You are welcome.
How are you?
Are you hurt?
I am okay.
Does what you said
still count now?
What did I say?
I seemed to hear
someone saying she loved me,
and she had loved me for long.
Weren’t you in a coma then?
I could still hear the words
that I wanted to hear.
Er…
How about what you said?
I…
I love you.
Can you be my girlfriend?
Anyway, if you…
if you refuse to accept me,
I presume
it is hard for you to get married.
Can you cooperate?
I can’t date
myself anyway.
Can you be my girlfriend?
Yes.
Wish a good cooperation with you.
I will
give my girlfriend a present.
A present.
Distinguished Mr. Special Police,
first of all, please accept
my highest salute.
Thank you for
protecting us with your life
in the rescue action
of the jewelry shop.
Although it seems to be a nightmare,
I feel I am very lucky.
I wish to
say thank-you again here.
Mi Ka.
I saved you once
and you saved me once, too.
It is a return for your favor.
♪My future is a fantasy♪
♪Where there is a sea of stars♪
♪And I will see you
Walking towards me♪
♪I feel lonely in the crowd♪
♪Watching the stories of others♪
♪And wondering
Who will conquer my heart♪
I am here
and you will be okay.
♪And thus my life changed♪
You should have told me earlier.
I don’t want you to love me
out of gratitude,
but the way I am.
The one I love is Xing Kelei.
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Until I know it’s me♪
♪That can’t be separated from you♪
♪I rely on you too much♪
♪You’re bound to be my dearest♪
Very soon our medical team
will go back to Jiangning tomorrow.
I am really reluctant to leave here.
Dr. Chen,
you are welcome
to stay here.
Just forget it.
Doesn’t Captain Shu
wish to stay here
and participate in the reconstruction?
But some people
are really reluctant to leave.
You also know about it?
I am Mr. Know-it-all
of the Emergency Department.
What do you know?
You don’t know it?
I don’t know.
After Xing Kelei was injured,
Dr. Mi
checked his ward eight times a day
and took his temperature all the time.
They look at
each other differently
now.
In what way is it different?
There is something more in it.
What is that?
Love.
Love in their eyes.
My goodness!
What a joke of love
you have made!
I am leaving tomorrow.
The station notified me to return.
Take care of yourself on the way.
I will drive you to the airport
so you don’t have to make a transfer.
Won’t you go back?
I will participate
in the reconstruction.
I have contacted the project team
and I must wait for them.
I didn’t expect you were reliable
when you were serious.
I still have many more merits.
Just find them patiently.
Don’t be carried away
by flattery.
What are you doing?
You caught a cold immediately
after I took away your scarf?
How is that possible?
I… I am so strong.
You are just eye candy.
Drink it. Just drink it.
I am afraid you keep complaining
about me as the cause of your cold.
For me?
Don’t beat around the bush.
I know you do care about me.
You are nothing more than a chatterbox.
Will you drink it or not?
It doesn’t matter if you won’t drink.
I’ll drink.
It’s hot.
I got my ankle sprained some days ago
and it feels painful when I am seated.
Xia!
Captain Shu.
Madam.
Sir and Madam.
They say you will leave tomorrow.
I have woven two pairs of gloves.
Please accept them as a gift.
Take it.
Madam.
Don’t mention it.
It is just our job.
You don’t have to say thank-you.
The gloves look so nice.
Just accept them.
They were woven personally
as a return to our help.
Yes, just accept them.
Okay.
Thanks, madam.
You are welcome.
Madam.
I am reluctant to leave you.
You must
take good care of yourself.
I will come back to visit you.
I am
reluctant to let you go, too.
You two are really kind-hearted.
You two must stay together.
Okay.
We have to leave now.
Madam,
let’s take a photo together.
Okay.
-Come on.
Come on, come here.
Just help us take a photo.
Go and take the photo.
Come on, madam, stand in the middle.
Okay.
Come on, be ready.
Three, two, one.
Cheese!
How is it?
Let me check it.
Great.
Good job.
A good photograph indeed.
Is it
a new merit of mine?
Be modest.
Don’t feel conceited upon flattery.
Madam,
let’s be WeChat friends.
Okay.
I will export the photo
and send it to you.
Okay, thanks!
Okay.
We have to go now.
Bye!
Let me see you off, madam.
Okay.
Go.
Bye!
Bye, madam.
I thought
Xia was just an ordinary girl
in the city
who loves good food and taking selfies.
.
But she really
impressed me this time.
She was sparkling all over
when she was
in a hurry to offer a hand.
Do you know what I was
thinking at that moment?
What?
I must be her boyfriend.
You already refused her.
Are you okay with me courting her?
I am not qualified to comment on it.
Just go and ask Xia personally.
I believe we will make a good couple.
We match each other in many ways.
We both love
eating, playing and having fun.
We look out of tune normally,
but we are reliable at critical moments.
I believe she must
be interested in me too,
although she may not recognize it.
Otherwise she wouldn’t
have been a constant dissident of me.
Do you agree?
How can I know
what is going on between you?
What a dummy!
(Medical Rest Room)
Er…
you take care.
I have to go now.
You too.
Take care on the way.
Let’s go.
I have to go now.
Bye.
Drive carefully on the way.
Okay.
Shu Wenbo,
call me when you are back in Jiangning.
I have something to tell you.
Let me do it, Dr. Shao.
Thanks.
Let me do it.
Let me do it. Put it here.
Remember to change the medicine.
-Never have the wound…
-Never have the wound infected again.
I see.
Bye!
Wait until I’m home.
Okay. Take care.
♪The spring sunshine♪
♪The call of summer cicadas on a branch♪
♪The flowers dance in gentle breezes♪
♪Until the autumn rains arrive♪
Let’s go together.
Don’t get separated.
♪This beautiful world♪
♪At each moment♪
♪Tell you privately♪
If you also love me a little bit,
please promise me
to be strong this time
and leave here.
I love you.
I don’t want you to love me
out of gratitude,
but the way I am.
♪Wait permanently♪
♪The spring sunshine♪
♪The call of summer cicadas on a branch♪
♪The flowers dance in gentle breezes♪
♪Until the autumn rains arrive♪
♪The world calms down
after winter snowfalls♪
♪This beautiful world♪
♪At each moment♪
♪Tell you privately♪
Why isn’t there any signal
at this place?
♪Just miss you♪
♪Even if I can’t be by your side♪
♪I will never forget♪
(Xing Kelei: Are you home?)
♪I am still here♪
♪The sound of missing♪
♪is a perennial agreement♪
♪I will cherish with deep yearnings♪
(Xing Kelei: Are you home?)
(Mi Ka: Yes, I am home.)
Captain Xing.
Don’t move
your right hand freely.
Otherwise, it won’t recover well.
I think I have almost recovered.
Can I take it off?
It feels very uncomfortable.
You can.
Let’s consult Dr. Mi.
We don’t have to.
Bye!
I just received a notice.
We will return to Jiangning next Monday.
We will possibly arrive in the evening.
The signals aren’t very good here.
It must be envying us.
What are you doing?
Nothing. I am doing exercises.
(Schedule of Emergency Surgery)
Dr. Mi Ka is on a leave tomorrow.
Mi Ka, Mi Ka!
Can I change the shift
with you tomorrow?
I bought a concert ticket
three months ago.
No, I have plans tomorrow.
It doesn't matter when you bought the ticket.
What matters is that her boyfriend is back.
You knew it all.
I am a forecaster.
Chen Tao, do you have a crystal ball?
I know something about divination.
You are also a gourmet.
You enjoy your meals the best
every day.
People would think
the dishes of our dining hall
are delicious
by watching you eat.
Emergency treatment is a hard job
and I must have enough food for it.
How about
a Yakult after the meal?
It helps you digest.
Chen Xiaoyan,
you finally sound reasonable this time.
Can you…
Don’t even think about it.
I have to go to the airport tomorrow.
With Xu Yanshan?
You have courted her since college days.
You are both a driver
and an errand boy for her.
When will you become her boyfriend?
Does it have anything to do with you?
I don’t care so long as I am pleased.
Can’t find someone to change shift?
Just watch the live broadcast.
Go buy one for yourself if you like it.
What did he say to you?
Who?
Dr. Mi,
it is him who is dating you.
What will he say to me?
Haven’t you two
conspired to
move something to my home?
Do you like it?
Yes.
That is enough.
He hasn’t said anything to you?
Do you want to know it?
Go and ask him yourself.
What a moron!
Go to hell.
Do you think
I should prepare something
for Xing Kelei before he comes back?
For instance,
reserve seats at a restaurant
or make something for him,
or pick him up at the bus terminal?
What are you doing?
Silence.
You are done for.
You are terminally ill.
To put it simply,
you’re worn out after you fall in love.
I am okay. You are ill.
I am serious.
You can treat patients
but you can’t treat yourself.
But
you are lucky enough to have me.
I can cure you.
Thanks!
Do you want to know the diagnosis?
Go... go ahead.
Are you looking for signals?
Don’t waste your time. It’s useless.
There were signals just now.
Buddy,
it is in the mountains.
Normally a man
must be in a hurry
to call his would-be wife
instead of his mother.
What are you talking about?
My advice is that if you make
too many calls,
you will lose her in the end.
Man,
I still have some more advice for you.
My principle is that
you can be active before dating
but never after dating.
Why?
Do you start up a business
before you maintain your business?
She must be waiting for your actions.
So you must take actions voluntarily
and tell her that you
can’t go.
Am I out of my mind?
Man,
surprise, okay?
You must pretend you don’t care
and he will give you
a pleasant surprise.
If you act like you care too much,
you will just startle him.
Why?
It is Xia’s Law.
Normally,
a woman is dissatisfied
with a man
for his indifference.
But normally a man…
Oh, no, it is for a woman.
Normally a man would
feel very satisfied
with a woman,
do you know why?
For her indifference to him.
To put it simply,
it is kind of insanity.
If I tell you
you have a billion dollars,
do you feel very happy?
But if I tell you
you have lost a billion dollars
and get a billion dollars again,
do you feel even happier?
What nonsense!
It is not nonsense.
It is Lu Feng’s Law.
Listen.
I have no fewer experiences with girls
than you.
Yes.
But it is a pity that
such experiences
aren’t dating experiences.
Have you ever held the hand of a girl?
You were just saying it.
I know
the truth is normally
unacceptable.
It’s your first time in a relationship,
trust Xia and it will pay off.
Put down your cell phone.
Don’t contact him voluntarily.
If you show too much care
about him,
he won’t care about you.
What you have to do now
is only one thing.
What is that?
On the first few dates
after you become lovers,
make yourself stunning
and make him feel that
he still owes you much
whatever he may give you.
I don’t believe you.
I think you are out of your mind
because you look as if
you are
acting as a lunatic.
Love is just a play.
If you are too active,
it will just become a solo
and you will get bored with it alone.
Trust me,
be cold before you show your care.
She will be deeply moved
and run into your arms.
You should consider it carefully
if you want to be an ignorant girl.
Sew your grapes.
(Xing Kelei)
If you show
too much care about him,
he won’t care about you anymore.
Hello?
Hello.
Have you woken up?
Have you arrived?
Yes, I have.
Okay.
If I tell you
you have a billion dollars,
do you feel very happy?
But if I tell you
you have lost a billion dollars
and get a billion dollars again,
do you feel even happier?
But I have something to do at work
and can’t go back home.
Will she be very disappointed?
I will also work a night shift today.
So I am also busy tonight.
So
let’s just focus on our work.
Yes.
Don’t disturb each other.
Er… You…
Take care of yourself.
You…
You take care, too.
Okay, that is it.
What did I say?
Why did you cheat Dr. Mi?
Moreover,
Captain Hao said
your shoulder was injured.
Just rest for a few more days.
What?
I remember Chen Tao told me
she wasn’t on duty today.
What happened?
She must have said so purposefully
to exempt my uneasiness.
How can you get so much information
from just a single sentence?
Is it so surprising to you?
It seems I must
be well prepared for it.
You’re amazing.
Xiaoyan,
have you found anyone
to take your shift?
I am available tonight.
I can change shift with you.
Not bad.
(Emergency)
Two patients of cerebral hemorrhage
were received last night
and they’re under observation now.
Two other patients suffered
from traumas.
One was drunk.
He fell downstairs and got bruised.
The other is a delivery man
who drove too fast
and fell off his bike.
His leg received three stitches
but no entorrhagia was found.
They have gone back.
If the patients of cerebral hemorrhage
are okay, transfer them to neurosurgery.
Okay.
You are dismissed.
Mi Ka,
please stay.
Director He.
Mi Ka.
Considering your specialty,
we’ve decided to transfer you back
to neurosurgery department.
I’m just keeping you informed
to inquire about your opinions.
I…
Why are you looking at me?
Your opinions are needed.
It is not easy to have you
at neurosurgery.
Considering your specialty,
we certainly hope
your knowledge can be fully utilized.
Director Shao has communicated with
the leaders about your performances
at the earthquake rescue.
We all appreciate your efforts.
I am certainly very happy I can be back.
So I will handle
all the other issues.
Director He.
We are so busy here.
How can you take away
my people at this moment?
Haven’t I been helping
with the shortage of staff
at the Emergency Department?
Come on,
you must find a substitute for me.
Somebody like her
who works twice
as efficiently as others.
Okay,
Director Wei.
I will manage and find a solution.
Bye!
Bye, Director He!
Director Wei.
What?
It is good to return to Neurosurgery.
It was a pity to quit halfway.
Do your best.
It’s not yet declared.
Go to receive patients there.
Okay.
It is on me.
Why?
Director Shao must have helped me
greatly for my transfer
back to neurosurgery.
I really don’t understand
why telling the truth
can earn a cup of coffee.
Thanks!
You can choose not to tell the truth,
right?
So I owe you my thanks.
Give me a cup of Vanilla latte.
Vanilla latte?
Only milk and sugar.
It’s not healthy.
But I feel good with it.
What are you drinking?
Black coffee.
I feel good with it, too.
Very special.
Good to see you so happy.
Do your best when you are back.
Okay.
Thanks.
What is most important for a gourmet
is to choose the right beef.
Kobe Wagyu
is famous for its tender meat
with evenly distributed marble textures.
You don’t need any cooking skills
and you can even eat it in a raw state.
Side dishes,
carrot,
onion and potato are a must.
Appetizers are also very important.
Salmon and butter
with lemon juice.
Avocado and crab
together with Spanish ham.
Which one is better?
The same.
You’ve bought a lot.
Of course.
I must fill my stomach.
I have ordered a bottle of wine for you.
It will be delivered
to your home tonight.
Take it easy.
Cash on delivery.
Although I am very rich,
I will feel happier
if you can pay the bill.
Okay.
Next time.
It will be on me next time.
Next time?
Didn’t you say you would cook for me
so you asked for my advice?
Who said that?
Thank you for your time
as my aide.
You asked her out?
I said be cold before showing your care.
You don’t have to be in such a hurry.
I don’t want to follow your advice.
It is too late.
Bye!
I didn’t drive.
You shall at least take me back.
It hurts.
I haven’t started.
Doctor,
I am afraid I can’t stand it.
Can you use anesthetic on me?
Just two stitches.
Be a man.
Frankly,
it will be even more painful
to use anesthetics.
You need several injections and
it’ll be even more painful.
It is up to you.
I see.
Go... go ahead.
How were you hurt?
My goodness!
You can’t tell?
It is a chop in a fighting.
A smart guy never
resorts to physical violence.
Why?
As a philosopher says,
if you engage in a battle against
an adversary
who is more powerful,
it shows you are so silly.
If your adversary is weaker
but dares to fight with you,
it shows he is tougher than you.
You will suffer in both cases.
What you said
sounds reasonable.
Who is that philosopher?
A philosopher called Mi.
A philosopher called Mi?
Yes.
Okay.
It is wrapped up.
Never allow your wound to touch water
and take anti-inflammatory drugs for
three days.
Thanks, doctor.
Mi Ka.
Can I add your WeChat,
doctor?
When do you go back home at night?
I…
He wants to add my WeChat.
What?
Add her WeChat?
She has a boyfriend.
Her boyfriend is a policeman.
So what? Just a police…
Policeman?
Sorry.
Good job, Dr. Mi.
You are almost a showgirl
in our department.
Thank you!
You didn’t wash your hair?
Your hair is too oily.
Does it have anything to do with you?
It is a night shift.
I don’t have to wash my hair.
I will wash it tomorrow morning
to save some shampoo.
Aren’t you on the day shift today?
I will do it again for Chen Xiaoyan.
How could
Chen Xiaoyan do that!
Xing Kelei will come back today.
So what?
Do I need to
welcome him with wide open arms?
He didn’t say he wanted to see me.
♪My future is a fantasy♪
♪Where there is a sea of stars♪
♪And I will see you
Walking towards me♪
♪I feel lonely in the crowd♪
♪Watching the stories of others♪
♪And wondering
Who will conquer my heart♪
♪Because of an incident♪
♪My life has changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I won’t harm anyone♪
♪I won’t have any regrets♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I am the one
You can count on♪
♪I didn’t expect I would
Come across you♪
♪And thus my life changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I know what is hope♪
♪I’m afraid that I may hurt you♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I’m the one you can count on
Do you think the same as me♪
♪Love by accident
Yet it’s more than an accident♪
♪Love indeed exists♪
♪I think you’re free to love♪
♪Until I know it’s me
That can’t be separated from you♪
♪I rely on you too much♪
♪You’re bound to be my dearest♪