♪In such an unexpected way♪
♪I came across you♪
♪It was a romantic opportunity♪
♪When we exchanged faith♪
♪In the name of you and me♪
♪Youth starts quietly♪
♪Then you and I are together♪
♪Tired but excited we run along♪
♪Destiny is a mystery But I’m fearless♪
♪Because of you I never shrink back♪
♪In my hands hides my life♪
♪Keep it for me forever♪
♪Let’s be gentle to each other♪
♪My love Everything is precious♪
♪The world is noisy
But the future is promising♪
♪Because of you I expect more♪
♪Of a far-away world♪
=You Are My Hero=
=Episode 12=
How can you drive that way?
It’s unsafe.
-Do you know…
-I will use the parking space.
Just go away.
What?
How could you speak that way?
You almost hit my car.
The space…
I saw the space first.
How could you be like that?
You saw it first?
Call it. Will it answer you?
Don’t touch me.
What’re you doing?
What?
Don’t hit him.
Can you be reasonable?
Go to hell!
What? Stop hitting!
Stop!
Hello, 110.
Stop hitting! Dear!
110. Someone is hitting my husband.
Please come quickly.
Stop!
Don’t hit him.
Go on. Hit him.
-Stop!
-Go on.
Stop!
What do you want?
Someone is hitting my husband.
Please come quickly.
Stop!
Mind your own business.
Don’t move.
She’s cool!
It’s a restricted knife.
Please call the police.
I already called the police.
Thank you.
They don’t need us now.
Dear!
Get up!
Come on.
Are you alright?
Baby!
Dad.
Don’t cry. I’m here.
What’s going on?
Hi, I called the police.
They hit my husband.
The lady
-helped us just now.
-Dad.
Dear.
Are you alright?
Give me your hand.
Dad.
Dear. It’s OK, baby.
-Hello. Miss.
-Hello.
The thing is,
the two people
keep restricted knives
and I subdued them.
Thank you for helping.
But we still need you
to go to the police station with us
to take a statement.
No problem.
This way, please.
You two,
come with me, too.
OK. Thank you.
-Be careful.
-Dad.
Dad.
It’s OK. I’m here.
Mum.
The girl
looks gentle and quiet.
But she’s agile.
She must be a peer
with very professional skills.
(I was expecting to search data
for the paper.)
(But the computer is down.)
One. Two. Three. Four.
(I was expecting to search data
for the paper.)
(But the computer is down.)
One. Two. Three.
Kelei.
Captain Hao.
OK. Come with me.
I’d talk to you. Come on.
The running target
you designed
is good for the training.
The branch came for exchange
and also tried that
after they went back.
After hearing that, their captain
asked if
we still have
similar special equipment
to share with them.
They can’t
just ask for me about that.
They are my secret weapons.
Secret weapons?
The improvement of
combat capability
is a good thing
for the whole police force.
You can’t hide them privately.
I was just kidding.
Please don’t take it seriously.
Here is the way.
Make a document about
the training equipment we developed
and the training ways.
We will arrange a lesson
for you to share it.
Got it.
Who is it?
Coming.
Mi Ka.
What brings you here?
Keyao.
I bought too many cherries.
So I got some for you.
Thank you.
Kelei is in special training.
I don’t think he’ll be back
in over ten days.
I know. He told me that.
You still want to see if he is in,
right?
No.
I’m just taking you the cherries.
Thank you.
Then I’m leaving.
Mi Ka.
I want to talk to you.
Let’s go to your place.
Come in.
He didn’t allow me
to get in before.
Come in.
How is it?
Do you think
Xing Kelei is childish?
He even plays toys as an adult.
Somewhat.
All these
are his soldiers.
He always leads his soldiers
to simulate here
the scene of robbery
and sand-table exercise.
It can be played in that way?
There are many ways.
Is your computer down?
You can use this one.
The password is
ielekgnix.
How do you know my computer is down?
Kelei told me that.
He said you need
to search data for your paper.
Then…
How did he know that?
About that,
you’d better ask him.
He’s straight.
But he can also be
extremely meticulous,
especially for people
or things he cares about.
Well. Go ahead.
I’d leave now.
Thank you, Keyao.
Do not touch
his soldiers.
He will ask for compensation
if you break any of them.
Those are like his lifeblood.
OK.
My mistake.
I didn’t mean to hit it.
OK. Help me with that.
And remember to put him on a drip.
Pay attention to her body temperature.
OK.
Come on. Team One. Ready.
Go!
(To Xing Kelei
Are you sleeping?)
Let’s suppose the victim is here.
We observe him from here
and go down from here.
Then these two can rappel.
He can be seen
from both points here.
Why are you
eating the hot pot again?
Why not eat
celebrity food in the canteen?
You are not here.
It’s none of your business.
It’s you.
Are you used to my computer?
Mi Ka.
What’s wrong?
Seems your spirit has freed.
Xiaoman.
Do you know anything about Lego?
How to play it?
It’s so hard for me.
Dr. Mi. See you tomorrow.
See you.
Mi Ka.
Director Shao.
Get on.
What’s wrong?
What’s the matter?
Tell me.
Maybe I can help.
No. I’m just a bit tired.
Tired?
Working in emergency makes you tired?
Right?
No.
The weather is bad recently.
It’s always cloudy.
I’ve been on multiple shifts.
It’s hard for me to see the sun.
And my computer is down.
A lot of important information is lost.
I only finished half of the paper,
but it gets stuck.
What’s your paper about?
It’s about the study on distribution
of CSF pathogenic bacteria and treatment
effect of severe intracranial infection
after cranial operation.
I can’t help in the weather.
But about the paper,
I can give you some
effective advice.
Thank you, Director Shao.
Here we are.
Be careful.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Bye-bye.
The website I just sent
to you
has many data
and papers.
You can have a try
if you need.
OK?
♪I have a Living Buddha♪
Oh.
During the day off
after your training,
let’s go to the suburbs.
Prepare some beer and barbecue.
We can have a picnic.
You’ve changed your hobby?
Don’t say that.
Xia, you know her, right?
Xia?
What’s up?
Last time you asked me
to pick Dr. Mi up.
Xia was with her.
We met.
And then?
Nothing special.
I like her. So I want to chase her.
Xia…
I know.
She’s chasing Wenbo.
But according to her words,
she chases Wenbo
for she never met such a man
who ignores her like Wenbo.
She is unwilling to submit.
It’s kind of betting.
How about you, Wenbo?
Do you like her?
If not,
I will chase her.
I have nothing to do with her.
(It’s OK. The fever is gone.)
(That’s fine.)
(Go to the school)
(and pick up Niannian.)
(Why?)
(It’s her birthday today.)
(So what?)
(It’s none of my business.)
(Do you forget it)
(or you never remember it?)
What they said in the play
does make some sense.
(Pay more attention to your girlfriend.)
(You know what?)
(It’s me who helped you)
(during the new year holiday.)
Here. Eat more.
It’s so delicious.
You are here alone
and don’t know
how to take care of yourself.
The dishes I made are delicious, right?
Yes.
Here you are.
Well.
You finished?
Yes.
I have to go back to the base.
Did you buy the cinema tickets
I asked you to buy?
Yes.
Why do you suddenly
want to watch a film?
Mum.
It’s boring for me
to stay at home alone.
You don’t accompany me often.
It’s weekend.
So I want you to watch a film with me.
Give me the ticket.
Why?
I will pick you up.
Right?
Don’t bother.
I need to
buy things
for my friends on Saturday.
You go there by yourself.
What if you get lost?
What are you talking about?
I didn’t get lost
when I came here.
It’s really a long way.
But you were lost last time
when you bought vegetables.
I just arrived here at that time.
I was unfamiliar with it.
Give me the ticket. Quickly.
Don’t get it lost.
OK. I see.
Well, I’m leaving. Mum.
See you.
Xia.
She hasn’t arrived yet.
Hello, mum.
It will start soon.
Where are you now?
I get in first?
Do you know how to get in?
Well, please calm down.
I will get in first.
OK.
See you.
Excuse me. Thank you.
Thank you.
Xia?
Shu Wenbo?
Why are you here?
I see.
Your mum arranged it for us.
My mum is officious.
Take it as
falling in with her wishes
and accompanying me to watch the film.
I’m not a spider woman.
I won’t do anything bad to you
in the cinema.
Which one would you like?
No, thanks.
-Thank you.
-Pick one.
No. Thank you.
Thank you.
What’s wrong with you today?
Why are you like a cold fish?
If my mum
bothers you again with such things,
just ignore her.
I don’t think she bothered me.
I feel it’s great.
Xia. I think…
I know what you want to say.
You will surely say,
Xia,
I don’t think we are well-matched.
I don’t want to listen.
Whether we’re matched or not,
it’s up to me.
No. I…
Think it over.
It starts.
Take it.
Why me?
You take it, and then
it’ll be nice for me to eat.
Just put it here.
Put it here and you can have it.
(Meng Dongxing VS Luwei Weiwei)
Take one.
Eat it.
No. Thanks.
I’d say it frankly.
My mum misunderstood
my intention.
It makes you misunderstand.
I’m sorry for that.
What are you saying?
Xia.
I know city girls like you
always like new things
and seek for exciting things.
That’s why you pursue me.
You are actually very clear
men with my conditions
are not your liking.
You haven’t met
the man you can’t reach.
So you are persistent.
Actually, I don’t fit you
-very well.
-Lower…
What’s wrong with you?
That’s what you think about me?
I’m a slattern
in love
in your eyes?
No, Xia.
-I want to say I…
-Say no more.
I see.
Yes.
I am that kind of person.
I won’t keep after you anymore.
Bye-bye.
Xia.
A letter of thanks from the other force.
Take a look.
We write this letter
to express our sincere gratitude.
Since we’ve got a letter of thanks,
it means
I finished the task well.
It’s fine.
Can I ask for
a paid leave?
Shu Wenbo has a holiday now.
You still want to leave?
It’s because Shu Wenbo
didn’t go home during the new year.
His mum seldom came here.
So he needs to accompany her.
Exactly.
You said you’d substitute, right?
I don’t mean
a real vacation.
I mean
we don’t have tasks
these nights.
Can I go out for dinner to satisfy
an appetite for good food?
It’s OK for dinner
if you are not on duty.
Come back after that.
OK.
By the way,
some newbies
will come for trial
tomorrow.
We want to keep several.
Go pick the better ones
and leave them.
OK. No problem.
Mr. Lu. You haven’t come for long.
So I’m here today.
So,
this evening…?
Excuse me, Miss.
Let’s cancel it.
Xia.
What’s wrong?
Can you hear me?
Crossed in love.
That’s
what’s going on.
It’s my fault.
We played basketball last time.
I misunderstood Shu Wenbo.
I said the words to him.
Forget it.
It’s a sore point for him,
like a mine.
If it weren’t for you,
there would be some other fuse
igniting it.
What will you do then?
What can I do?
It almost kills me.
Should I
go for him?
It’s impossible.
I didn’t expect
you are so frank and generous.
It’s different from what I expected.
What do you think of me?
We are not that familiar.
I’d like to invite you to dinner
and be familiar with you quickly.
OK.
I don’t want to
have dinner alone.
Stand at ease.
Attention.
Salute.
After salute.
Xiaochao was transferred
to a civil position.
So
we will select some
new members.
Let me introduce you
the new ones for the trial.
Cui Zhihao.
Yes!
Xu Ning
Zhuo Wenjing.
Yes!
Zhuo Wenjing
is the only female special police
among the newbies this time.
She’s excellent.
Wenjing.
Introduce yourself.
Hello, everyone.
I’m Zhuo Wenjing.
Graduated from Beijing Sport University.
I was a shooter before.
I was specially recruited
to the police force.
For rifle,
my score for basic shooting is,
rifle, prone position, 200m,
100 shots, 1,000 rings.
Rifle, standing position…
Captain Xing.
200m.
-I remember you were
-50 shots.
-the shooting champion.
-500 rings.
She will catch up with you.
It’s said our team
-are full of undiscovered talents.
-You forgot Captain Shu.
Hope we can have an opportunity
-Wenbo.
-to learn from each other.
We have an opponent in the trial.
Words are nothing but wind.
We will see
after competing.
No problem.
Captain Shu performs better
than he used to do.
There won’t be a problem.
So amazing.
Halt!
Turn left.
I’m announcing the result of the match.
First,
Zhuo Wenjing.
Second,
Shu Wenbo.
Third, Xu Ning.
Fourth, Song Huaxia.
Fifth, Cui Zhihao.
Sixth, Li Yongning.
Uh…
How is it possible?
Zhuo Wenjing and Shu Wenbo
finished the match accurately
at the same time.
But Zhuo Wenjing still accurately hit
on the target at last
when the third target fell off.
So the winner of today’s match
is Zhuo Wenjing.
Amazing!
You are in good state today.
Anyway, Zhuo Wenjing
is really amazing.
Yes.
She still could accurately hit
on the target at last
when the third target fell off.
It’s really cool.
If it were me,
maybe I couldn’t
do a better job.
She is just a lady.
But she defeated me.
Captain, I’m sorry.
I lost face of the old members.
You know,
she must have made greater efforts
for such achievements.
Losing out to people like her
doesn’t mean losing face.
(Arms Room)
Captain Xing.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Wenbo is one of the best
in our team.
But you defeated him as a newbie.
You are really awesome.
Winning him is not that great.
The one who can win you
is the real best.
We are not athletes.
We do team work.
Anyhow, if you want to compete,
you can tell me at any time.
Except for today.
Welcome to Tiger.
These are typical cases.
They’re not universal.
But be sure you will
read them carefully.
They will be helpful in operation.
OK?
-OK.
-You can take them.
-Thank you, Dr. Shao.
-It’s OK.
Director Shao.
Thank you.
The website is really useful.
Of course.
Or I wouldn’t share it with you.
How is your paper going?
I haven’t been in Neurosurgery recently.
So there are not enough cases.
I’m in Neurosurgery.
I just have
some related cases.
You can use the data
for reference.
If it’s OK,
you can come with me and take them.
(Xing Kelei)
It’s OK.
Answer the phone.
Send your paper to me later.
I will check if the cases
fit your paper.
-Keep in touch.
-OK.
Thank you, Director Shao.
I’m leaving then.
Go ahead.
Hello, Xing Sir.
Dr. Mi.
Are you on duty today?
No.
Let me treat you to dinner.
You are in special training, aren’t you?
It’s OK to have dinner outside.
I can go back to the base after dinner.
Find a place
near the base.
It’s convenient for you.
Thank you.
Tell me what you want.
Then I will make a reservation.
OK. Deal.
See you later.
♪Give you my missing♪
♪It’s easy to bear♪
♪I recall your words in my mind♪
♪It’s difficult to understand♪
♪The sky is more blue♪
Captain.
Let’s have dinner together today.
♪I’m so insensible to feel it♪
♪I don’t understand your love♪
♪I will persist with smile♪
Sir,
please
stop ahead.
I will walk there.
OK.
♪Love can be ignited♪
♪Like messy palette♪
♪Various colors♪
♪Describes the appearance of♪
♪Happiness♪
I’m sorry.
The traffic is too heavy.
I got off on the way
and ran here for 2 km.
Do we still have time?
When will you go back?
Take it easy. We have time.
I intended to eat with you alone.
But…
Let’s get in first.
It’s really cool.
You gave ground to me.
Lucky for me.
No, it’s not like that.
This is Mi Ka, Dr. Mi.
-Nice to meet you.
Sit down.
Finally you are here.
-We are starved.
-OK.
Everyone is here. Let’s start.
OK. Let’s eat.
Eat.
Pass on the water.
I intended
to eat with you alone.
As it happens,
three new colleagues
are dining together.
-I’m sorry.
-It’s OK.
It’s alright.
Zhuo Wenjing.
You defeated Captain Shu
once you came.
Will you
drink with Captain Shu?
I will propose.
For her skills,
she’s the top
in our team,
let alone policewoman.
Come on. A toast to you.
Thank you.
You two newbies
should drink together, right?
-Yes.
-Cheers.
-Drink together.
-What are you doing?
Cheers.
What are you laughing about?
No.
Nothing. It’s just…
They drink water like it’s alcohol.
They still need to work at night.
So they can’t
drink alcohol.
Every time I want to eat with you alone,
things became like this.
I’m sorry.
It’s OK.
Well,
for the meal you should treat me,
I’ve forgotten it.
Just focus on your own business.
Captain Xing.
On behalf of the newbies,
it’s a toast to you.
I’ve heard a lot about you.
Champion of three contests
of public security system.
One first-class merit.
Three second-class merits.
The Tiger Assault Team led by you
is the example
of special police nationwide,
no matter in practice
or in training.
It’s a great honor for us
to work with you.
I hope you will help me in work.
OK.
I will propose a toast, too.
-Together.
-Cheers.
OK.
Tiger Assault Team.
The brave fears nothing.
Cheers.
Dr. Mi.
I’m Zhuo Wenjing.
I’d toast you.
You are
Captain Xing’s girlfriend, right?
No.
He used to be my instructor.
OK.
Uh…
Dr. Mi is our
good friends.
We are quite familiar.
In the case
the fan kidnapped the star,
Dr. Mi helped us
a lot.
Right?
Yes.
Come on. Let’s eat.
Eat.
The crabs are great.
Come on. Each of you, take one.
It’s male.
I mean it.
All are male.
Every time Captain Xing treats us,
we can have very delicious food.
We’d better have the crabs
when it’s hot.
Dr. Mi.
Why don’t you eat?
I’m not used to
eating crabs like this.
Let me do it.
To do what?
To shell the crab.
No, thanks. Just eat.
Cheers.
Peach flavor.
Rose flavor.
Matcha flavor.
Which one do you like on earth?
Bixin.
Your heart.
My heart.
Of the same mind.
Heart beats as one.
Damn Shu Wenbo.
Why
can’t you understand my mind?
(Xing Kelei)
(Lu Feng)
Do you have a target tonight?
What?
I don’t want one anymore.
Change your hobby?
Shut up!
What are you talking?
Watch your mouth.
I only have one girl in my heart now.
Horrible.
Do you meet your true love?
Sir.
The lady near the counter
has drunk for three rounds.
She’s been crying while drinking.
They are worrying
so will you please go and take a look?
What can I do for you?
-Pour the wine.
-Sir.
That’s her.
Pour wine for me.
Go on with your work. I will handle it.
Give her
a glass of honey lemonade.
Warm.
Hey, you.
What’s wrong?
What’s the trouble?
Tell me about it.
There is no trouble.
Because of Shu Wenbo?
For him?
Do I need to?
Shu Wenbo,
dumb blockhead!
Miss!
Don’t be like that.
You are kind of famous.
We’ll be dead ducks if we’re shot
with videos uploaded to the website.
Dead duck?
Who is a dead duck?
Shu Wenbo, you scoundrel!
He’s the dead duck.
Here you are. Drink it.
You will feel better tomorrow.
I don’t drink honey water.
-I’m not a underage girl.
-No.
-I don’t drink it.
-It’s not honey water.
Whisky with honey.
Hot.
Nice.
What’s wrong?
It has no taste of spirit.
Even the alcohol is bullying me.
Shu Wenbo, you scoundrel!
He bullied me.
♪My future is a fantasy♪
♪Where there is a sea of stars♪
♪And I will see you
Walking towards me♪
♪I feel lonely in the crowd♪
♪Watching the stories of others♪
♪And wondering
Who will conquer my heart♪
♪Because of an incident♪
♪My life has changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I won’t harm anyone♪
♪I won’t have any regrets♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I am the one
You can count on♪
♪I didn’t expect I would
Come across you♪
♪And thus my life changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I know what is hope♪
♪I’m afraid that I may hurt you♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I’m the one you can count on
Do you think the same as me♪
♪Love by accident
Yet it’s more than an accident♪
♪Love indeed exists♪
♪I think you’re free to love♪
♪Until I know it’s me
That can’t be separated from you♪
♪I rely on you too much♪
♪You’re bound to be my dearest♪