The Fiery Priest Season 2
All characters, locations,
events, organizations,
and religious backgrounds in this drama
are fictitious.
Child actors and animals
were safely filmed
under supervision
and in compliance with guidelines.
- They're here!
- The car's here.
They're here. They're here.
I'm very disappointed, Chairman Kim.
How could you let things get this bad?
This is nothing.
All you have to do is stick to the script.
Still, this thing is being broadcast
to the whole nation.
How embarrassing.
Oh, come now.
Prosecutor Nam, you know how this goes.
A hearing is just a performance.
You just need to put on a good show.
He's right.
The outcome's already decided.
Even so,
if the other side lands a good punch,
I'll get bruised.
If I get bruised,
the two of you will be bloodied.
Prosecutor Nam, I'm Kwon Namcheol.
I know how to get things done.
Really? Is that why you thought
to set fire to Gudam Temple?
Is it?
Make no mistakes.
None.
I'm off.
How dare that dog
talk to a veteran Chairman that way?
Leave him be.
He's a dog with his teeth
around our throats.
Departmental Chief Prosecutor Nam Duhun
Hello.
-Father Kim. Just ignore him.
-Hey, he just--
- Order in the assembly.
- Take a seat.
The Special
Investigative Committee's hearing
on investigating allegations
of collusion with a drug cartel
and reduction of drug crime charges
for children of high-ranking officials
will now begin.
Chairman Yeom!
You better apologize now!
Apologize? For what?
We've just started.
What do I have to apologize for?
The color of your necktie
clearly indicates party ties.
Are you really making a big deal
about color?
Apologize now!
My daughter said
that real men wear neon green.
Don't take it the wrong way.
"Men wear neon green"?
Are you trying to emphasize
the gender divide?
My personal color is winter cool.
Personal color?
So now you're just blatantly showing
your true colors, aren't you?
Apologize now!
Damn it.
Witness, please take the oath.
"The oath."
"I solemnly swear
that I will tell the truth
in the National Assembly's investigation
on Prosecutor Nam Duhun's
alleged collusion with a drug cartel
and reducing drug crime charges
for children of high-ranking--"
Hold on. Prosecutor Nam?
Aren't you taking the oath?
Ah…
Unfortunately, I will not be able
to take the oath at this time.
What are you saying?
Are you kidding me right now?
Who do you think you are?
It's not that.
In specific situations,
like taking an oath
or swearing on something,
I faint due to the stress under pressure.
We'll wake you up if you faint.
Stand up and take the oath.
I'm sorry, but this isn't a joke.
Once I wake up after fainting,
I'll spend two to three days
in a panic state
and will be completely unable to testify.
Cut the crap.
Who in the world has those symptoms?
You're making this up.
Father Kim.
That little…
I'll show you my doctor's diagnosis
regarding my symptoms.
"Reflex mediated syncope."
"Situational syncope"?
Aren't you sick and tired
of always having to show up
to these hearings in a wheelchair
or with some kind of doctor's diagnosis?
- This is nonsense!
- Excuse me!
Will you quiet down?
-I…
-Apologize now!
Why are you so obsessed with apologizing?
And I'm not the one to apologize.
The one who hasn't taken the oath should!
How dare you talk back to us?
-Be quiet.
-Watch your mouth!
Let's all settle down.
Father, please be quiet.
You can talk when you take the stand.
Okay.
Chairman Yeom, will you allow him
to get away with such brazen behavior?
What's brazen about it?
It's his right to refuse the oath.
Apologize now!
Order, order.
If a witness's reason
for not taking an oath
is deemed invalid in the future,
there will be a penalty
for refusing to take it.
Of course. I completely agree.
Wow, he's really something.
Let us continue the oath
without Prosecutor Nam Duhun.
"…and will accept the penalty of perjury."
"Witness Park Kyungsun."
On what grounds are you indicting
Prosecutor Nam Duhun?
I've submitted
over 300 pages worth of documents.
But aren't they all
just one-sided allegations?
There's no solid proof.
Isn't that why we're holding this hearing?
How dare you run your mouth like that?
Apologize now!
In order to help you all understand,
I've prepared a video.
What sort of video is it?
It's titled, "Go to hell, Nam Duhun."
Witness!
Are you joking right now?
This is a serious hearing!
Apologize now!
I'm sick of you telling me to apologize.
When you watch this video,
you'll see that Nam Duhun is total trash…
…that he is a bad person.
Start the video!
- Is that true?
- Yes.
Prosecutor Nam…
threw soju
over Chief Prosecutor Park's frozen body.
How could someone do such a thing?
There's something in this honey jar.
Take a look.
"What's behind this honey jar?"
"Tails of Tales
Go to hell, Nam Duhun"
What is this?
A photo
of Chief Prosecutor Park's frozen corpse.
This is fake, right?
It's not real, is it?
I know it's hard to believe,
but it's real.
An undercover detective
who was investigating the drug cartel
secretly took that photo.
How could such a terrible photo
only just come to light?
This isn't all.
The way they got rid of the body
is so cruel,
it's hard to even put into words.
They disposed of it at a sturgeon farm.
A sturgeon farm? Then…
"Chief Prosecutor Park's body
was disposed of at a sturgeon farm"
I can't hear any more of this.
Then we'll look at the rest of his crimes
through this video.
Please hit play.
"Go to hell, Nam Duhun"
♪ Behind that white smile ♪
♪ Are black lies ♪
♪ Inside this dead heart ♪
♪ I can't let go of this thread of hope ♪
♪ This fire inside me burns like crazy ♪
♪ It reawakens me from this calm ♪
♪ There's no use ♪
♪ But scream and run away ♪
♪ All secrets will be revealed
In the end ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ He turned a blind eye ♪
♪ To the kids of higher-ups using drugs ♪
♪ He used this as leverage over them ♪
♪ And built up his honey jar ♪
♪ Go ahead, make my day ♪
♪ He's numb to sin ♪
♪ We'll dig this up ♪
♪ He's besties with the drug dealers ♪
♪ Sharing both crimes and friendship ♪
♪ You've ruined Busan's Uma-gu ♪
♪ You paved the way for drug dealers ♪
♪ You sent
The righteous Chief Prosecutor Park ♪
♪ To an unfair death ♪
♪ Always complaining
About your smoothies ♪
♪ You're a rude guy everyone hates ♪
♪ Now you're on the express lane to hell ♪
♪ Nam Duhun might be a disaster ♪
♪ He only cares about
Filling up his honey jar ♪
♪ The secrets
Hidden inside the honey jar ♪
♪ You're screwed as soon as it's opened ♪
♪ This fire inside me
Burns like crazy ♪
♪ It reawakens me from this calm ♪
♪ There's no use ♪
♪ But scream and run away ♪
♪ You'll receive a fiery judgment
In the end ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
All right, all right.
So what was that?
As I said earlier,
"Go to hell, Nam Duhun."
Go to hell, you bastard.
Live broadcast
of Prosecutor Nam Duhun's hearing
It's nice to finally see your face.
How's security?
It'll be hard for our vehicle
to even get close.
Security is tight in this country.
It'll be worse
when we get to the main building.
There's no way
to avoid the metal detectors.
All we have to do is get in.
Then we can go all out.
It's what we've always done.
It doesn't matter
if there are 100 of them.
We can take them all.
Prosecutor Nam Duhun.
Why are you being suspected
of colluding with a drug cartel?
The Uma Police Violent Crimes Team and I
were undercover,
investigating a drug ring.
I approached the head, Kim Hongsik,
to take him and all his suppliers
in Southeast Asia down.
The real undercover work was done by me,
Team Leader Gu Jayoung, and Bing Sangu.
In that process,
we found out about the relationship
between Nam and Kim Hongsik.
So for the purposes of your investigation,
you pretended to be
a rotten, corrupt prosecutor.
Wow, that is just brilliant.
Brilliant? As if.
It's not an act.
He really is rotten!
Look at him.
He's more than rotten,
he's basically fermented.
Don't you see how moldy he is?
- He's covered in it!
- Witness.
Raise your voice again,
and you'll be required
to take a 10-minute break.
All right.
I was also undercover at the Busan
Southern District Prosecutors' Office,
and I can confirm
Nam and Kim's relationship.
Prosecutor Nam even tried
to set me up with Kim.
Does it look like I'm on a dating show?
Prosecutor Nam threatened me
by the seaside.
He said if I kept looking into him,
he'd retaliate.
I was taken aback
by how natural it was for him.
It was as if he'd taken a course
on threatening people.
Please refrain
from any statements unrelated to the case.
Is it true that he threatened you?
Why would I be standing here
if I were going to lie?
I found the location
where the honey jar files
were kept and sent from.
Where were the files sent?
We're in the middle of confirming.
But the transmission range isn't far,
so we're searching the area.
So there's no way to prove
whether the honey jar files
are real or not?
-What do you mean?
-She said they're in the jar!
Then show them to us!
- Goodness.
- My gosh.
I understand you were undercover,
but you never received money or valuables
from the drug cartel, did you?
I know I was undercover,
but I'd rather die
than take money from a criminal.
I did not accept a single thing.
You held onto your integrity
throughout all that.
You're truly admirable.
A public official without integrity
is nothing but a corpse.
Please call the cops.
A corpse has been found at a hearing.
Wow, look at that corpse.
Integrity?
Don't be ridiculous.
Conspiring to murder
Chief Prosecutor Park Byeongil
of the Busan District Prosecutors' Office.
Explain yourself.
Did you really take his body…
…and feed it to sturgeons?
That is absolute fabrication and slander!
Chief Prosecutor Park
is currently missing.
Even at this very moment,
his wife and family
are desperately hoping
for his safe return.
Chief Prosecutor Park
was an irreplaceable colleague
and someone
who I deeply respected and looked up to.
Stop squeezing out tears!
Chairman Yeom, don't fall for it.
His nickname is Faucet.
He even cries when he eats a good meal.
He's not an orange.
He's not squeezing anything out!
He's an emotionally sensitive person.
He's feeling his feelings!
Again, if you raise your voice,
it's a 10-minute break.
Will you even listen if she speaks softly?
And we're telling the truth.
Why should we take a break?
Oh, stress.
I should've taken
herbal meds for my nerves.
According to the accuser,
you have "honey jar" files
with compromising information
on high-ranking officials.
Is it true? They exist, don't they?
I swear on my parents and my honor.
They absolutely do not exist.
You bastard.
How could you sell out your parents,
no matter how ignorant you are?
If you were in my family,
we'd have you excavated
right out of the family register.
You can't call him a bastard!
It's not a crime to be ignorant.
What are you, a heavy equipment operator?
He called a bastard a bastard.
What should he have called him?
An ass turd?
Also, it's not a crime to be ignorant,
but it is a crime to be evil!
-He's right!
-Listen to yourself.
How many minutes are left?
Seven minutes.
It's only a two-minute penalty
in handball.
Any way we can play by handball rules?
Then what about ice hockey? Five minutes?
He's certainly quiet.
Why'd you have to call him a bastard?
Well, he's not wrong.
If that bastard had a bastard son,
he'd sell him out too, that bastard.
Why does it feel like
nothing we say is getting through to them?
It felt weird from the start.
They were oddly warm and friendly
with each other, like heaven.
Well, we'll just have to push
until we get through, won't we?
Yes!
Prosecutor Nam Duhun
threatened me multiple times
to remove myself
from the drug investigation.
What kind of prosecutor conducts
an undercover investigation on his own
without any police involvement?
He cut off my legs
and threatened to do the same
to my son and my grandchild.
How much do you know
about the relationship
between Prosecutor Nam and Kim Hongsik?
I don't know much
about their relationship,
but Prosecutor Nam said
that if I didn't cooperate,
he'd accuse me
of tax evasion and smuggling…
S-Sucheol…
My grandson.
Let me clarify.
Kim Hongsik is the bad guy.
Prosecutor Nam has nothing to do with him.
Mr. Yong? Speak the truth.
I am speaking the truth.
Mr. Yong, why are you
suddenly acting like this?
Lee Eungsu from customs,
please say a word.
I have nothing.
You said you'd testify
on the bribes made to the upper officials
and Nam Duhun's threats.
What are you talking about?
I came here to say
that I don't know anything.
Please speak the truth.
The comfort of a lie is merely temporary.
Mr. Lee.
Mr. Yong.
We'll conclude the hearing
as the last witness has taken the stand.
We'll resume tomorrow.
We're already in a tough spot.
Who knew Mr. Yong would pull that move?
When did his family
come back from America?
Did Mr. Lee back out because of Mr. Yong?
We weren't thorough enough.
We should've thought to protect
his family as well.
The hearing's not easy, is it?
So why'd you start a game
you can't even win?
You seem pretty easy to play.
It's fun for us.
Hey, bastard.
How long do you think you'll hold out?
I wouldn't have gone to such lengths
if I didn't think
I could make it all the way.
How can you live
without the slightest bit
of fear or a conscience?
Oh, please.
Look here.
That's the problem with you believers.
You have too much blind faith
in history and conscience.
"History will judge you."
"Future generations
will be ashamed of you."
That kind of talk doesn't work on me.
The hell does that matter?
This is the most obnoxious
I've ever seen you act.
Dear ladies and gentlemen
of the traveling theater troupe.
Do you think the people out there
who are even worse than me
care about history or future generations?
Even if they were posthumously executed,
they wouldn't bat an eye.
"I've lived a life of fame and fortune."
"Who cares
if they chop off my bones or head?"
"So what?"
"It's over when you're dead."
That's what they think.
Can someone like him be redeemed
according to God's will?
I'm not sure. Let me ask, hold on.
Hold on, hold on!
Wait!
God said you can keep living
the way you are.
Wow, does the Lord have a cell phone?
That was quick.
Does God give up on any of his children?
Yeah, he says this one had his fingers
in the cookie jar.
We can ditch him.
Oh, now I get it.
That explains everything.
Perfectly.
See you tomorrow, cookie fingers.
Seems like God doesn't care about
what my fingers get up to.
What's that?
Just thinking about Nam Duhun
makes my blood boil.
How's he so shameless?
Tell me about it.
Why is this so good?
The flavor is timeless.
Really?
Mmm!
This even cures hangovers.
That's why it's so good.
This is relieving the stress of today.
This is absurd.
You gave them police reports,
witness testimonies,
and evidence material.
But why won't they believe you?
Isn't that plenty of evidence
to have Nam Duhun locked up by now?
It honestly seemed like
they were protecting him.
Prosecutor Park, is it always like this?
I'm so mad
that I can't sit through the hearing.
I'd say it's fairly common.
The lies of the powerful become the truth,
and by contrast,
the truth of the weak becomes lies.
How can that be?
Then who protects the truth of the weak?
That's what we're trying to do.
She's right. And we have
someone powerful backing us up.
I get that we have him,
but how will we get through tomorrow?
I'm getting a call.
Oh, it's my aunt.
Hey, Auntie.
Are you serious?
Where's my chauffeur?
You're handsome in person.
Let's go for a drive.
How dare you…
Second day of the hearing
I'm watching you.
Is this a new watch?
Is Assemblyman Lee Hongok still not here?
Yes, he's running late
because he's stuck in traffic.
Tell him to apologize when he arrives.
We will begin for now.
As party chairman,
I wanted to testify voluntarily
so that I could clear up
this whole situation.
As you well know,
the government and our party
have worked tirelessly
to eradicate drugs in this country.
The government, the Prosecutors' Office,
and the New Era Unification Party
joined forces to create
an undercover investigation operation.
And the head of command
was none other than Prosecutor Nam Duhun.
Chairman Kim.
Then what are these charges
against your son, Kim Inseok,
regarding drug use?
Was this part of
the undercover operation as well?
That's exactly right.
Drug cartels target
the children of people like us.
My son bravely sacrificed himself
to lay out a trap for the drug ring.
A trap for the drug ring?
More like for the nation's citizens.
Who would believe this?
I'm sure it's hard for you to believe.
But these are the facts.
- "The facts…"
- Prosecutor Nam
was the one
who crafted this extraordinary plan.
So really,
we should be giving him an award.
What are we doing right now?
This is slander and entrapment.
Chairman Kim,
this is absolutely ridiculous.
Do you believe
our citizens are no smarter than animals?
It's worse than that.
They see them as complete idiots.
You're being totally…
Witnesses, you're out of line.
Any further disruptions and all of you
will be removed from the hearing.
I mean, we just…
Jeez.
National Assembly Building
You're late, Assemblyman Lee.
There were some reckless drivers
on the road.
Who's that next to you?
You don't know?
This is the eldest son of the Babel Group.
He came to observe the hearing.
I apologize, sir. Go on ahead.
Witnesses, listen carefully.
The nation's sense of justice
and morality in this new era
is all thanks to our upright government.
If you leave your laptop in a café,
no one steals it.
No one touches your delivery packages
left in the hallway.
There's no other nation like us.
You're right.
There's no other nation
where people like you
try to suppress the truth.
Father Kim.
This National Assembly
is just as holy as the church.
Watch your language.
A holy National Assembly?
A holy National Assembly…
If no one steals a laptop or a package,
does that mean it's a safe country?
A truly safe country…
is one that guarantees the truth.
It's not just people
that can be slaughtered.
This nation is slaughtering the truth,
justice, and history,
and blameless citizens
are the ones paying the price.
Do you understand?
He's right.
The truth alone
is the greatest safety and stronghold.
Exactly, so please stop
telling these lies. It's frustrating!
Witnesses, particularly Father Kim.
I've been
watching you closely since yesterday,
and your intentions are suspicious.
You seem politically motivated.
Who's backing you--
Chairman Kim!
Does caring about society
make me "politically motivated"?
Do the citizens who care about our country
have forces backing them?
Explain yourself.
Is that what you're implying?
Thank you for your statements.
You're dismissed. Please leave the hall.
Wait!
To end our hearing with a bang,
we'll now commence
the honey jar opening ceremony.
You all put on quite a show
until the very end.
Hey, take those with you.
Come on out.
Hey, hey.
Come on.
Are you bluffing?
Are you just messing around
without any evidence?
Please don't mess around.
Hurry up and go to hell, Nam Duhun.
Cue!
Don't worry, Chairman Kim.
I'll make sure to get a reduced sentence
for your son.
I'd be very grateful.
By the way, what drugs had he taken?
Well, he seems to like a wide variety.
Hepanyl, kasanin, the works.
That damn bastard.
I'm so sorry, Prosecutor Nam.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Of course not.
Your trust is what matters to me.
About Prosecutor Park.
Don't you need to take action?
It's already taken care of.
He'll be reborn as caviar.
"Phone call recording
between Nam and Chairman Kim"
Take a good look, everyone.
These are the honey jar files
we've been talking about.
What's happening?
Guess the honey jar
wasn't sealed tightly enough.
Starting today, Kim Mancheon
is gonna be shaking in his boots
every time he sees me.
I've caught a big one.
What a fishy smell!
So fishy.
Chairman Kim.
What is the source
of these honey jar files?
The source?
They were at his house.
What's that?
We'll head out.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Is there anything more?
I think this is from next door.
Next door?
This is a familiar scene.
Team Leader Gu,
this isn't a company residence.
It's privately owned.
The owner is Nam Duhun.
I knew it.
Honey jar!
We've finally found it!
We've got him. Let's go!
Yeah!
Nam Duhun, you bastard.
The files were sent to this room.
It wasn't even 100 meters away
from where he was transmitting.
Wow, seriously?
The heavens helped us.
How did you find it at this moment?
There are
about 50 to 60 high-ranking officials
listed in this document.
Will this information
turn the nation upside down, Auntie?
It won't just be turned upside down.
It'll be doing
a double airborne somersault.
People who colluded with Nam
Park Gitae, Kim Inyong, Kwon Namcheol,
Kang Ikja, Mu Jinhae…
Chairman Yeom
and respectable citizens of this nation,
this is all fabricated.
Those were AI-generated deepfakes!
So your fingerprints
found on the storage devices
were also deepfakes?
They must've gotten my fingerprints
from a mug or something.
You've watched too many movies.
Your imagination's running wild.
Just fess up and admit that you did it.
You total conmen.
The whole nation is watching.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Even if I get a hole in my head,
I'll never admit to anything.
I apologize…
Everyone, be quiet.
Sit in your seats.
Isn't that the guy we know?
Well, he came out of nowhere.
Sit down.
Remain calm and you won't get hurt.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm here to collect a debt.
Is there a creditor here?
Who is it? Hurry up and pay--
I said be quiet.
What don't you understand about that?
Okay.
Hey, Kim Hongsik.
Your face is being broadcast
to the whole nation.
I know, and that's why I'm putting on
a good show for them.
Don't do anything stupid.
If you try to pull anything,
you'll all get killed.
The guards will be here in 60 seconds.
59, 58, 57…
Then I'll finish this in six seconds.
Including you three.
Chairman Kim.
You better think carefully.
The whole nation is watching.
If you kill me right now,
you're a heinous murderer
whose actions are unforgivable.
"Chairman Kim"?
Don't give me that bullshit.
You need to repay the debt
for my brothers.
What happened to them
was because of an airplane door, not me.
But I can't shoot an airplane door, can I?
Dear citizens.
This drug cartel is pure evil!
Who is he talking to?
-The camera's not even on.
-Is he an idiot?
He's a smart idiot.
Go to hell.
What's going on?
My goodness.
I really thought
I'd get a hole in my head.
The first bullet was live
and the rest are fake?
Did you buy that
from Dogbowl from Incheon?
Please reach out to us again.
We're always happy to assist.
Who's Dogbowl?
They sell fake weapons in Incheon.
Only the first bullet is live,
but it's so realistic
that even experts get fooled.
- They all get fooled.
- Poor Hongsik.
You really got had by a Korean scammer
in this critical moment.
Goodness gracious.
Huh?
This is all being broadcast,
as Prosecutor Nam said.
Let's just go quietly, Hongsik.
If I go quietly,
that's a global embarrassment.
You and Nam Duhun both committed crimes.
Isn't it only right
to be globally embarrassed?
Live footage of witness
and infiltrated drug lord face-off
- What's going on?
- What's that?
He's the drug lord.
Hearing turns into an octagon ring
You bastards.
Trying to start a fight here?
You're nothing but thugs.
The nation is watching--
You talk way too much.
- Jeez.
- Where you running off to, you little rat?
-I'm no rat.
-What?
I don't even have whiskers.
- What?
- Shut that damn mouth of yours.
This hearing is legendary.
It'll go down in history!
Father Kim!
Yeah!
-Yeah!
-You did it!
- Wow, that was crazy.
- No way.
- That was amazing.
- Drug lords are nothing.
- That was so good.
- He's done for.
Great job!
Freeze!
Don't move.
Freeze.
Kim Hongsik.
Korea's not easy, is it?
Hey, Kim Hongsik.
At least you didn't end up
getting stabbed.
Be content with that.
Over here! There's one here too.
You're right.
- Come with us.
- Let go of me!
How dare you touch me?
Pompous till the very end.
Stop it, stop it!
How can you be applauding right now?
Who do you think caused this mess?
They're just clear and empty-headed.
Really? They look as thick as makgeolli.
You mean rice wine?
At least that's rich and tasty.
- And sweet.
- Right.
Anyway, how many times have I told you
not to overdo it?
-You're killing me.
-I took my meds today.
Still, great work today.
There you go!
Well, thank you
for the live survival reality show.
It was a blast.
It was very entertaining.
Bye!
All right,
let's get out of here.
-Here, take this.
-Thank you.
We will now adjourn the Special
Investigative Committee hearing.
In what could've ended
in a fruitless stalemate,
we witnessed a rare display
of bipartisan cooperation
to refer all involved
in the corruption scandal
-to the Ethics Committee…
-There he is again.
Someone ought to teach him a lesson.
All involved in the corruption will be…
Ki Deokgi!
Read forward, it's Ki Deokgi.
Read backward, it's Ki Deokgi.
-Wow.
Now that I think about it,
Polka Dot was returning the favor.
You two found her body
and allowed her to rest in peace.
Does this make sense
from a Catholic viewpoint?
Right?
It's more like we were in a horror story.
The Lord brought desperate people together
and helped us achieve our goals.
We desperately sought out the truth,
and she desperately wanted
to join the Lord in heaven.
Hearing it put that way
is saddening yet heartwarming.
The Lord always watches over us,
regardless of the situation.
Exactly.
I won't fall asleep at Mass anymore.
I don't need to watch Animal Farm.
Don't kid yourself.
-Are you being for real?
-For real.
- There they are!
- There!
Prosecutor Park,
a word on how you're feeling?
I'm hyped!
Phoenix Sun!
Let's get it!
Gosh, I'm tired.
-Great work, Father Kim.
-Great work, all of you.
Shall we go for some raw yellowtail?
Sounds great.
I agree.
Raw foods help generate new flesh.
Is there someone among us
who needs new flesh?
It's me.
- Why?
- Wait.
Hey, the fautores!
It is.
What perfect timing.
- Great timing.
- We…
- Why are you only getting here now?
- We… just…
- Huh?
There was crazy traffic
on the way to Yeouido.
We didn't want to ride the subway
wearing these outfits.
- What's wrong?
- Father Han, are you okay?
Fast and Furious.
I'm sorry about that.
You didn't have to drive so recklessly.
Furious, I see.
Is it over?
Yes, as you can see.
What?
Then I'll take this off.
It's making me really sweaty.
I will as well.
Let's all go eat raw yellowtail together.
We haven't even done anything today.
There is one thing
that I was hoping you two could do.
What is it?
What's your affiliation?
Who's your immediate superior?
Talk to me.
You think I'll be in there for long?
Life is all about one shot.
You better think--
Oh, jeez. What the…
What is this?
What's this throbbing pain I'm feeling?
A hwatu card?
Those traveling theater troupe bastards.
Where are you?
Where are you hiding?
- Come out, you bastard!
- He's over here!
Come at me!
-Just hurry up.
-Take me to the hospital first.
I need treatment!
Let's just go.
Do I not have rights?
-Come on.
-You imbeciles!
It's a case that Gen Z
would describe as "completely cooked."
Honey Jar-gate.
A case involving a drug cartel,
a corrupt prosecutor,
and the hidden crimes
of high-level officials.
Although both parties
acknowledge mutual fault
and are trying to gloss over this
without consequence,
the nation's citizens seem unsatisfied.
The most important fact
is that this huge scandal was uncovered
by a priest, a prosecutor,
and a detective.
How long will South Korea continue
to place the burden of justice
on those without power?
100 billion?
"Transfer the amount
to the national treasury"
Thank you.
I hope you become rich,
but only in your dreams.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Do you want it that badly?
Where are you going?
-He does want it badly.
-What's wrong with him?
Control yourself.
Get back here!
Goodness.
-Goodbye!
-Now it's really over.
We gave Hong Cheolbeom's money
to the government five years ago.
Now it's the same
for Kim Hongsik's money.
Why does it all have to go
to the government?
Can't we just take a teensy bit of it?
Where would you use it all?
It's not about having somewhere to use it.
It's more like a commission.
If we're going to work,
we have to get paid, don't we?
You're right. We've been spending
our own money all this time.
Now that I think about it,
I've taken out all my savings.
Me too. I even made an overdraft account
for Night Guy activities.
Stop it!
Stealing candles to read the Bible
doesn't make it right. Got that?
-Come on.
-He's so uptight.
We could skim off just 1%.
Or even just 0.5%.
Or what about right in between? 0.75%?
- Let's go!
- For a commission fee,
- that's minuscule!
- Totally!
- No way!
- Father Kim!
We have faced many threats
from the forces of evil
and came close to suffering greatly
at their hands.
There were even times
when we were on the verge of death.
But the Lord reminds us
not to be afraid.
He sent us help…
…and showed us how to deal with evil…
"The Lord's tools that blocked Satan"
This is footage
from a police officer's bodycam
from last month's drug ring crackdown
in Busan.
These students from Busan Major Seminary
risked their lives to help the police
and played an essential role
- in taking down the vicious drug ring.
- Guts!
Let's go, Chae Dou!
The seminary's dean fought
tooth and nail alongside these students.
Their noble resistance
and sacrifice against injustice
have deeply moved not only Catholics
but the entire world.
2025 New Student Application Overview
Competition rate: 5.8:1
Dear God, please send me
a less fervent angel next time.
Oh, right. Don't forget.
Make sure to choose another taekwondo lead
before your ordination.
I probably won't be ordained
as a priest because I'll be kicked out.
You won't be kicked out.
You're a warrior of the Lord.
And that's a badge from God
for fighting against evil.
This is from Rockfish, not God.
And bruises fade.
If it fades,
fight again and make some new ones.
A badge isn't something
that's one and done.
You're right, but…
Why am I so angry?
-At me?
-No.
Here. Put this on your desk.
What is it?
A small gift from me
to activate
the fighting spirit of a warrior of God.
My fighting spirit sure is burning,
Father Kim.
Neck slice!
Let's go, Chae Dou!
Let's go!
"Congratulations Gu Daeyoung
and Gu Jayoung on the Commissioner Award"
Why'd they do all this?
My goodness.
It sure has been a long time.
Mm!
The smell of home.
This is so uncomfortable.
It makes the elders proud
when we come all dressed up.
What is there to be proud of?
There's a lot.
The youngest-ever leader
of the Uma Police Narcotics Team,
Gu Jayoung.
Oh, come on. It's not that big of a deal.
Okay, follow me, little Daeyoung.
Why are you suddenly
talking to me like that?
What?
We're back with family.
Respect the age hierarchy!
Follow me.
I'll carry that for you, Auntie.
That's a good boy.
You called for me,
Chief Prosecutor?
From the looks of it,
you don't seem to regret it one bit.
Not even 0.0000001%.
You know that you've got
a target on your back now, right?
I'm well aware, sir.
I've caused an uproar
in Sejong, Seocho, Yeouido, and Yongsan.
Who wouldn't want to shoot me dead?
It'd be better if that were possible.
That's why you're such a pain!
If you have a lot of kids,
you're bound to have one joker.
Don't you realize
how immature you're being?
Acting mature
only makes you overly cautious.
Prosecutor Park.
Once you get older,
you start to see things.
Are you talking about those polyps
they remove during a colonoscopy?
I got one removed recently.
Prosecutor Park!
I knew you'd act this way.
That's why I've brought this.
My resignation letter.
Goodbye, everyone!
God, that was refreshing!
Ow!
I feel amazing!
I just quit.
Jealous, aren't you?
You guys should quit too. Give it up!
Follow me!
Oh, my knees.
They're so stiff every morning.
- Sister Kim.
- Yes?
-You forgot to take this, didn't you?
-Oh, you're right.
I'll get one for you.
Thank you.
I forgot to take one.
Here you go.
-Thank you.
-And one for me.
Shall we take it?
You won't be able to continue
your fautor duties at this rate.
No way.
I'm going to keep taking care of my body
and be a fautor
until well into my sixties.
Don't you worry.
Hurry, come quick!
They're here!
Already?
Let's hurry up and go out to greet them.
- Goodness. Out of my way!
- Sorry!
She'll definitely be a fautor
for a long time. Wait for me!
"The bellator Kim Haeil
and his faithful comites
have fulfilled their mission
of making the world brighter
and have once again
widely spread the Lord's will.
Thus, I, Francesco,
another servant of God,
extend my heartfelt gratitude
to my friends
and offer a token of friendship."
Thank you. Thank you.
- Come on.
- Hey now.
Don't be like that.
- Let's look at it together.
- Come on.
- Hold on.
- Let's look at it all together.
-Come here quickly.
-Come on.
-Sit down.
-Take a seat.
-Stay there.
-No… My coat…
-Come on.
-Sit down, sit down.
There we go.
-Watch out, I got my hair done!
-Stop pushing!
-I just got it done.
-Yohan, don't push!
I was just breathing!
- Hey, copy me.
- Move over.
Good. Now hold your breath
for five minutes.
Five minutes?
You're basically telling him to die.
-How about just three minutes?
-Hey! Scoot over.
Three minutes? I hate that.
My goodness. Stress!
-I told you I didn't want to do this!
-We're ready!
-Here we go.
-Jeez.
- I'll take the photo now.
- He's taking it.
One, two, three!
Comes!
Together forever
Let's do it.
Let's stay together forever.
You didn't have to put me in there…
"Insi…" What does this say?
Is this a curse word?
- Cheers, everyone!
- Cheers!
-That's refreshing.
-Nice.
-Gudam-gu is most beautiful at night.
-You're right.
We've finally reached
a true oasis of peace…
Don't jinx it!
-Watch your mouth.
-Right. I take it back.
Father Kim,
how long will you be gone to the Pope?
Just two weeks.
The food doesn't sit well with my stomach.
Since I quit, should I go with you?
I've never been to the Vatican.
Oh, I'm unemployed too. Take me with you.
Unemployed?
Why are you unemployed?
I got fired over text 10 minutes ago.
-How?
-You just got an award.
-What happened?
-Seriously.
They can't resist the pressure
from the higher-ups. I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Darn it…
Then that's perfect.
-Let's go. Let's all go.
-Let's. Let's go.
Hold on.
You have your mortgage
and your car payments.
I don't need them.
I'm letting go of all material wants.
If that's what you wanted,
you should've become a monk.
Want me to introduce you to
the Gudam Temple abbot? He's a good guy.
No way. I can't live without meat.
Should I open up my own firm?
I'm a total celebrity now.
Oh! Then I'll be your first employee.
-Deal!
-That law firm won't do too well.
You'll only take cases
that don't make money.
You're right about that.
What will I do for a living?
What will you do?
Yes. That.
-That, that!
-What?
What about working to fight
for justice and the weak?
-I do work.
-Not that.
What, you want me to join
the National Assembly?
-Yeah, yeah, that!
-Yeah!
Why are you suggesting the impossible?
It's possible.
With your fighting spirit
and us supporting you,
-we got this.
-We got this.
What the heck are you talking about?
Why are you trying to butter me
into doing something?
Sounds like it worked.
We're not buttering you up. We're serious.
-Jeez.
-It fits your current public image.
People think of you as a fighter!
You'll have a second term, a third term,
and eventually become a minister.
And after that…
You always put the cart before the horse.
I can hit you both.
I don't care, I'll still say it.
This is your fate.
- Your God-given fate!
- He's right.
The Lord has nominated you
to work for him.
-Exactly. Send Park Kyungsun…
-To the National Assembly!
Cut it out, you two!
Why would I do that? Sounds like a pain.
I'm not doing it.
I'll ne…
ver do that. Never.
Number five!
♪ Park Kyungsun's the one for the job ♪
♪ She'll make Gudam-gu happy ♪
I'm not afraid of any external pressure!
"Park Kyungsun protects Gudam-gu"
We're done with political stress.
I'm Park Kyungsun, candidate five,
and I can do it!
-She can do it!
-Yay!
A clean, honest government.
Let's go!
Park Kyungsun for Gudam!
With the general election just a day away,
there are
many highly competitive districts.
In particular, in Seoul's Gudam-gu,
the New Era Unification Party's
newly redistricted
three-term candidate Lee Hongok,
and independent candidate Park Kyungsun
have approval ratings
of 39.1% and 38.9%, respectively.
It's a close battle.
Park Kyungsun is a fiery prosecutor
who exposed Honey Jar-gate
to the world.
After more or less
being fired from her job,
she received widespread support
after announcing her campaign,
shaking up the political world.
Have a refreshing day!
Why is the time crawling by?
Should we pray
before they announce the results?
No, we can't.
If we beg for things outright,
he won't listen to us.
-You know?
-Right?
Oh!
My goodness.
I just remembered that this morning…
I prayed for the election.
Father Han…
- Goodness me.
- One minute left. Just one minute.
"We will soon share the results
that will change the nation"
We'll begin the 60-second countdown
until the exit polling results.
I didn't think I'd get nervous,
but I'm shaking from head to toe.
Let's try to relax as we wait.
You look the most nervous
out of all of us.
I'm nervous. I'm going to the restroom.
Hold it in.
Or just keep drying it little by little
like me.
That's disgusting!
Yohan…
- We'll announce the exit poll results…
- All right, get ready!
…in 10 seconds.
Ten, nine, eight…
Seven, six…
Five, four, three…
two…
- What's going on?
- What?
-Yohan!
-Damn it, Yohan!
You damn pig!
Looking back on everything,
it wasn't miracles
that made the impossible possible.
When injustice becomes law,
justice becomes obligatory.
The real miracle was
regular people refusing to remain silent
and willingly taking on
the responsibility.
Every moment we spent together
was a miracle.
We took responsibility through action,
and though we fell, we always got back up.
In the end,
the true miracles came to those
who regarded every moment of a life
that respects justice as a blessing.
Our faith and courage
continue to stay with us
and remain the calling of the fiery people
who have the will and hope
to change the world.
Today, I continue to pray
that morality and justice
will forever shine like the stars.
Dear God…
thank you for always giving us
the strength to fight.
- Please let me go.
- It's okay.
- It'll be over soon.
- Good, good.
Hold still!
- Hold onto her!
- Come on!
- Can't you do it right?
- Please!
- I want to go!
- You're fine.
-What was that?
-What?
-Did we hire an actor?
-No.
Hey!
Are you the ones
making sexually exploitative videos?
-Who the hell is he?
-You called him, didn't you?
-Dude.
-Just hold on a sec, I'll save you.
- You little bastards.
- Damn it.
Why, you little…
- Damn it…
- Please help me!
-Hey, lock the doors.
-Hey.
- Help me!
- Lock them.
Hey, lock the doors!
Get ready to get on
the express lane to hell.
Uh…
Scoot back. A bit more.
Not you guys.
You'll be out in no time.
I used to pack
quite a punch back in the day.
The Fiery Priest Season 2
Thanks to Park Jiil
for his special appearance
Sweeper Gang
- One, two, three!
- Again?
Comes!
The Pope is asking
for you, Father Michael.
As always, you and your comites
have made a significant contribution
to bringing light to the world.
But there are still many places
that are waiting for you, Bellator.
Your help is needed.
With that being said,
you need to go to the Vatican.
To the Vatican?
Yes, that's right.
Translated by June Hong