The Fiery Priest Season 2
All characters, locations,
events, organizations,
and religious backgrounds in this drama
are fictitious.
Child actors and animals
were safely filmed
under supervision
and in compliance with guidelines.
Ta-da.
- You're all dead meat.
- You're done for.
Episode 10
Blessings Start Rough
Where did she go?
She's not even picking up.
Where's Prosecutor Park?
She left saying
she had an urgent matter to attend to.
An urgent matter? I wonder what it is.
You can get back to work.
Darn it.
She's all over the place, isn't she?
What now?
There's something urgent
I need to tell you.
What isn't urgent?
I bet the emergency center
doesn't even get this many calls.
This is actually urgent.
It's about Father Kim Haeil.
I had Detective Cho
stay at the hospital
in case there might be trouble if he died.
But guess what?
An unexpected person showed up.
An unexpected person?
What, did Son Heungmin show up?
I followed her tracks
to see who she came to visit…
and it was Father Kim Haeil.
Caught you. Say cheese.
She's also a world-class traitor, huh?
Man, my blood pressure's going up.
This is a strange new feeling.
Kim Hongsik
Hold on a second.
I need to deal with this first.
You didn't ask to meet
to deliver bad news, right?
No, sir.
The thing is…
Hmm?
Why don't you guys tell him?
The amount of kasanin leaves coming in
has increased dramatically.
What's wrong with that?
That's more for you guys to mooch off of.
It's too risky
if it increases more than this.
And it's beyond our capacity to handle it.
Listen.
Customs rats.
Then find a way to gather more rats.
We'll give you more food.
That's easier said than done.
I don't know
how things were back where you lived,
but things are different here in Korea.
This bastard's got
far too much national pride.
No one bends the rules like Korea does.
Answer me.
Yes, sir.
I'll…
I'll give you however much you want…
…so please let Fire Eel go to heaven.
I'd appreciate it if you could
squeeze Jellyfish in as a BOGO deal.
We don't do buy-one-get-one deals,
but this one's on the house.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Shaman!
May you be blessed.
Will that be okay, sister?
Does the shaman in the velvet outfit
not know how to talk?
What did you say?
My sister
has sacrificed her voice to the spirits
to gain spiritual power.
You little.
No, I just…
As for the male shaman,
it'd be nice
if we could see your face a little bit.
You know,
just for security reasons.
My goodness! What's going on with her?
Jeez, what's going on?
What's wrong with her?
-I don't know!
-What's wrong with her?
She must've felt something outside.
There must be something there.
-I'll go check.
-Go. Hurry!
What's going on?
Show me around every corner of the ship.
Wait.
Instead of looking around the ship,
shouldn't you relieve
Fire Eel's resentment first?
Fire Eel's spirit
is wandering around this ship.
We have to find him first!
Fire Eel!
Why are you wandering around?
You don't even know your way around here.
Stay in one place, will you?
-All right, let's go.
-Let's go.
Wait, it's better this way.
-Let's go that way then.
-Let's get moving.
Spirits!
That was great.
Did you go to acting school?
You could easily win the Grand Prize.
True acting
isn't defined by chasing awards.
Where is it? Hurry.
It's this way. Follow me.
This way.
"Catholic Diocese of Busan"
Nothing like this has ever happened here.
Better yet, this has never happened
anywhere in the world.
How can a seminary be involved
in a conflict with a gang?
And what is this about the instructor
and student who initiated the conflict?
How have you been managing
the seminary and the students?
The archbishop is having a hard time
understanding the situation.
You will have to
get to the bottom of this incident
and provide a clear explanation.
I don't want to give an explanation.
What…
We only owe an explanation
if we've done something wrong.
Father Lee.
How could you say that in this situation?
You said this has never happened
anywhere in the world before.
That's not true.
It's happened everywhere.
There have been priests
who have fought against injustice
and violence by risking everything.
Spirits, help me find Fire Eel.
Spirits.
Please help me find Fire Eel.
Help me, spirits.
- Let's find him.
- Boss Park.
Doesn't this sound a lot like Roo'ra's
The Angel Who Lost Wings?
It's our Fire Eel who lost his wings.
He can't fly even if he has wings
because he's heavy.
You're heavy too!
Spirits.
This is it.
- Hold that.
- What?
Who are you?
Black Velvet.
Seokhui!
Seokhui.
Damn it, I knew it.
I guess even the Grim Reaper
is a woman these days.
Come to your senses.
It's Haeil.
Did you… become a nun?
Are any of your bones broken?
Can you walk?
Judging by how I'm annoyed seeing you,
I think I can walk.
I'm so sorry.
I shouldn't have gotten you involved.
It's better this way.
Now I have a reason to cut you off.
All right, you can cut me off.
But you can do that
after we get out of here.
Try walking.
-Careful.
-Oh, my God.
Who is he?
He's an undercover cop
from the Drug Investigation Unit
who's been here for four years.
Hello, I'm Detective Bing Sangu.
Oh, hello.
It must've been tough all alone.
Hostage obtained.
What am I, a game item?
You know what I mean.
The elderly are in the lab, right?
Yes, they're working right now.
Disguise Seokhui as one of them
and bring everyone to Uma Police Station.
No, it's okay.
I'm going with you.
I'm going to beat those bastards up.
You'll slow us down.
Just get to the agency's hospital.
- But--
- Wear this.
Take her and come to the station.
-Okay.
-Hey!
Be careful!
Come this way.
Help me…
Get out immediately.
Mm.
Boss Park.
Did you find him?
You have to manage your mood swings, okay?
Mood swings?
Run to the entrance!
Get them! Get them!
What are we, wanted criminals?
Why are they blasting the siren so loud?
Why is the entrance so far away?
It feels far when you're running away.
It's so far.
There's a way out over here!
I memorized the way!
Hurry up and open it!
-Hurry, hurry!
Come on!
- Go, go, go!
- Go, go, go, go, go!
Come here!
You're dead meat!
I'm going to kill you!
Where the hell did they go?
Did they leave?
Maksan, that bastard.
He sure does live recklessly!
Go, go, go!
Wait.
I thought it was the way out.
This is the lab.
I had it memorized.
Left, right, left, right.
No, it's left, right, left, left, right.
No, it's left, right, left, right,
left, left, right.
It's right, left, right, left,
right, left, left.
Left, right, left, right.
What are you doing, Prosecutor Park?
I almost joined.
This is the lab, so there must be
a secret way out. Let's look for it.
Let's attack.
It's finally time.
I underwent
harsh training in Denmark
for this very moment.
For two weeks!
"Justice"
- Is that a guy or a girl?
- Damn it.
I swear, Park Kyungsun.
This dress is too… Wait, is this not it?
So that's where they were.
This room looks ridiculous.
I don't think
you're in a place to say that.
You bastard!
It's finally time.
Here goes the pig's transformation!
What's wrong with him?
What's he doing?
The power I got from the monster rabbit!
Fast charging complete!
Who said you're a budget superhero?
Pikachu!
Go, Yohan!
Stay still.
Yohan, electrocute him! Come on!
Is that person from the past?
What are they wearing?
I get that you're a drug dealer,
but isn't kidnapping and torturing a woman
a bit much?
-You guys were on the same team?
-No, we're family.
You should've told me sooner
that she was one of yours.
I guess Nam Duhun didn't tell you…
that I used to be one of them.
You guys must be really close
to share such intimate information.
I wonder why he didn't tell you.
Perhaps he wanted to toughen you up.
I'm already as tough as I can get.
How dare you hit a woman?
Hurts, doesn't it?
How dare you?
God damn it, pantyhose.
What are they, zombies?
Why aren't they staying down?
We have to get out, or we'll die.
Damn it.
Hey, priest.
Let's end things.
I don't think those guys down there
will last another minute.
Father Kim.
Where's the way out?
-I remember now!
-Me too!
Left, left, left, left, left, left, left.
Oh, come on!
How could you mess that up?
Go, hurry!
They're getting away.
Get them!
-No wonder things were going well.
-Damn it.
We can each take a guy.
- I call the hairy guy.
- What?
You pork belly!
Electronic power!
You all talk too much!
Let's go!
Get in! Hurry!
- Get in! Hurry!
- Get in! Hurry up!
Let's go! Come on!
Go get them!
-Yes, sir!
-Yes, sir! Get them!
Hurry up and get in!
Get in the car!
Drive carefully, will you?
How can I, in this situation?
Everyone, hold on!
There's nothing to hold on to!
- Step on it!
- Sister Kim!
TQ Logistics
Hey.
-Hey.
"Safe Uma, happy citizens"
Come in slowly.
Watch your step.
Don't worry.
Good work.
Ma'am.
We only did what they told us to do.
- I swear.
- It's true.
-That's right.
-Indeed.
I understand.
If you all just answer
our questions honestly,
we'll factor that in
as a mitigating circumstance.
Okay.
Please escort them.
Yes, ma'am. Please follow me.
- Okay.
- Don't worry.
Get up, get up.
-Get up.
-Sir.
-I said get up.
Get up.
Please forgive me.
Sir…
Bring me a knife.
Now!
You've made too many mistakes.
Actually, no.
Let's make a cemetery tomorrow.
We should've done it sooner.
We've been exposed. It's too risky now.
They know about the gas and the bomb,
so they won't make any rash moves.
Even so, we should leave
before it's too late.
Just say the word,
and we'll have everything prepared.
Get the cash ready,
and get ready to move to Albuera.
-Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Need a hand?
-What? What do you want?
-What…
It's been a while
since I swung my sword around.
My forearm is killing me.
Why are you taking pictures?
Judging by how things went today,
I thought it'd be best to have
your funeral portraits ready in advance.
You little…
You'll see our double chins
if you take it from that angle.
You have a triple chin
even when you're standing, you pig.
I'm sorry.
Take another one of me.
I'll smile this time.
Sure.
Make a peace sign. Good.
My knees.
My joints are all worn out.
Is the hospital
your colleague went to safe?
Yeah, it's affiliated with the agency,
so it's safe.
What's the deal with Fire Eel?
Fire Eel?
What do you mean?
He was resurrected.
It's cold.
I'm going to freeze to death.
Please let me out of here.
Is anyone out there?
What happened?
- Huh?
- How are you alive?
I've been sensitive to cold
since I was young,
so even a little chill
would make me tense up.
It was so cold in the mortuary chamber
that I tensed up.
This is unbelievable.
It's a miracle.
Since you've experienced a miracle,
live a good life from now on.
Okay, I'll live
the rest of my life atoning.
But didn't the doctor say
there was fluid in his stomach?
I guess he was wrong.
It must naturally be like this.
I thought it was fluid too.
-Are you okay? Does it hurt?
-The eel is pregnant.
It's thanks to the power of your prayers.
You prayed for him when he died.
-Of course.
-That was nothing.
I did what was expected of a priest.
I swear your prayers
have mega, ultra, super strong powers.
The best.
What am I, a superhero with superpowers?
Wait a second.
Detective Bing,
what are you doing there alone?
- Come join us.
- Come on.
- Join us. You're family now.
- Come here.
- Come join us.
Come on.
- You're family.
- Okay.
- Lie down here.
- There's a lot of room. Lie down.
-Hey, scoot over.
-You had to pick the tightest spot, huh?
It's always tight next to Yohan.
Jeez, it's so crowded.
Good work, Detective Bing.
Father Kim will have you reinstated.
Oh, Father Kim
was the Aladdin you were talking about?
Yes. If you rub his arm three times,
he'll grant your wish.
I'm too exhausted
to come out of the lamp right now.
You should've taken
better care of yourself!
- Right.
You should've at least told me
if you were in such a serious condition!
I know we only just met, but that's not
something you should keep to yourself.
How does it make sense that the comites
don't know about the bellator's health?
I don't want to attend your funeral.
Is he ill?
I don't know.
It seems we're the odd ones out.
I feel so left out.
It's only been five years
since Father Lee Yeongjun passed away.
I can't say goodbye to you too.
Actually, I won't.
Will you give me a chance…
to confess to you, my friends?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you…
about my illness.
I'd like to apologize to you all.
But from now on,
I promise I'll share
every little pain and secret
with you guys.
There's a saying I've overlooked…
because I was so focused
on fulfilling my duty.
"If you want to go fast, go alone.
But if you want to go far, go together."
Just as that saying goes,
I'll make sure…
-The food must be here.
-…to stay with you for a long…
- When did you order?
- Food!
Did you order noodles too?
Soju, soju, soju.
I don't even have the energy
to yell anymore.
I'm so tired.
Today, the Busan Uma
Police Chief's press conference
caused quite a stir.
Let's take a look.
Starting today,
the Uma Police Station will declare war,
no, a dogfight, against the drug cartel
operating in the Uma district of Busan.
Narcotics Team Leader Ma Jungno,
please say a word.
Hello,
I'm Team Leader Ma Jungno
of the Narcotics Team.
Our team will hunt down the drug cartel
to the ends of the earth
and utterly destroy them.
I'm sorry, but you'll have to be
utterly destroyed first.
Good luck!
What is this, some sort of school play?
Hey, Chief Go.
Why don't you dispose
of that Team Leader Ma or whatever
and slap some sense into yourself?
I've never been
as clear-headed as I am right now.
Ms. Chief.
If you keep this up
thinking the priest's got your back,
you'll also end up in heaven.
So quit your bullshit
and just lounge around in your office!
Lounging around all day is rather boring.
One second.
Team Leader Ma says
he'd like to say a word.
This is Team Leader Ma Jungno.
There are three things I dislike.
First, oppression of human rights.
Second, excessive use of force.
And lastly, external pressure.
Hello? Hello…
I guess you won't be
leaving this world peacefully either.
Well done,
Team Leader Ma.
High five!
What a sight.
Put the bed all the way down.
No, stop it. Just stop it.
-You'll get bedsores.
-Leave me alone.
Hello.
-Hey, you came.
-Goodness gracious.
Hey.
You okay, friend?
It hurts.
Goodness, he mashed you up
like a potato salad.
I'm sorry for showing you
such an ugly sight, my friend.
It's okay.
Things like this happen
when you do business.
Then shall we… postpone our plan?
Our what?
Oh, a placard?
There's no need to do that for me.
This won't work.
Sir, don't worry.
I'll make sure to thoroughly prepare it.
All right. It's best to stick to the plan.
We'll make it quick and sweet.
Kim Hongsik, that asshole.
It's finally time.
I'll…
make sure to burn him to ashes.
-Are you okay?
-What's wrong with him?
Nurse!
Someone's calling me. I'm getting a call.
-Oh, I see.
-Can you put it next to my ear?
Sure.
Just go.
Just go already!
I got it. I'm sorry.
Hello?
Oh, Prosecutor Nam.
Do a small job for me.
Actually, make that two.
Two?
All right.
This is very important.
We have to finish everything by today.
Are you sure we can end things?
I guess you don't know our strength yet.
Tell him.
Somehow getting the impossible done!
He's right. We always somehow get it done.
All right, we'll show you
the power of half-assing!
I love the passion in you guys.
I deeply trust you all.
I'll be counting on you. All right.
- Dismissed!
- Let's go.
- It's this one, Songsak.
-It's this one, you idiot.
-Back off.
Yohan and Songsak, you guys take this one.
Team Leader Gu, Detective Gu,
and Detective Bing are in this one.
So it's two and three…
Is it really that difficult to split up?
I knew he didn't trust us.
- You said you trusted us.
- I'm sick of this.
He doesn't trust us.
It's not that I don't trust you. I just…
He doesn't.
Who's driving? Is the van driving itself?
We don't have a driver's license.
I'll drive for you.
Team Leader Gu, you drive this one.
Jeez, I've never been so overworked.
We can raid
the honey jar storage room tomorrow.
If there is a tomorrow for me that is.
Come in.
When did you get here?
Oh.
I just got here.
I heard there was an urgent matter.
My brother got into trouble,
so I had to go help him out.
I didn't know you had a brother.
I thought you were an only child
from the way you acted.
He's got a nasty temper,
so he gets into trouble a lot.
Those who can't control their temper
are a lost cause.
Did you take care of it?
Yes, I did.
That's all that matters then.
Considering how messed up
the world is these days,
I was just worried.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
From now on,
let me know if something happens.
I'm an expert at solving problems,
you know?
I will. Thank you.
It's no big deal.
You can go home now.
I'll see you bright and early tomorrow.
Yes, sir. Have a good day.
I have to go meet the chief prosecutor.
I kissed his ass that one time,
and he won't stop calling me.
I hope it's not too bad today.
Salute!
See you tomorrow.
Welcome.
You've come a long way.
I've heard a lot about you from Gozaev.
You're from NASA, right?
Please help us out. This way.
It's slippery,
so please watch your step.
NASA is in the States, right?
Busan King Karaoke
Who the hell are you guys?
Are you okay?
Ms. Kim?
I'm fine, thanks to you.
Wait, are you the one
who zapped me last time?
Yonggwang Fisheries and Shipping
does two things.
They distribute the drugs
in Southeast Asia, and…
Bring in the kasanin leaves.
Yes, that's right.
I get they have
their way of shipping it out,
but they need to pass customs
to bring them in.
Prosecutor Nam has two men
working for him in customs.
-It's only one now though.
-Why?
One of them pissed Chairman Kim off
and died on the spot.
They became food for the sturgeons.
You know who the other one is, right?
Yeah, his name is Lee.
He's a corrupt piece of shit.
If we take down this place,
we'll be shutting down Kim Hongsik's
production and distribution, right?
Yes, completely shutting it down.
The drugs are obviously an issue,
but we also have to take down
the rotten customs guys too.
Things are easier
now that we can just toss these bastards
to Chief Go.
Come back.
I said come back.
What's your real affiliation?
Busan District Prosecutors' Office's
Internal Investigations Team.
Were you investigating
Prosecutor Nam Duhun?
Yes.
Who do you report to?
I was sent here under
Chief Prosecutor Park Byeongil's orders.
I see, it was Chief Prosecutor Park.
Where did you work
before being dispatched here?
You'll find out soon enough.
How did you know I was dispatched?
A spy recognizes a fellow spy.
Do you know
what the purpose of the go house is?
It's a honey jar storage room
where Prosecutor Nam
hides his secret files.
I knew about it long before you did.
How'd you know I'd go there?
I tailed you the day you were questioning
Vice Minister Park's son.
Why did you stop me from going in?
Why did you zap me?
The thing is…
there's a security camera
inside that room.
Oh.
What's this?
I noticed that
he was watching the room on his phone.
You would've been caught
if you had gone in.
Then how'd you know about tonight?
I look through his laptop
whenever he's out of the office.
Specifically, deleted files.
I was looking through it earlier,
and there was CCTV footage of you
visiting Father Kim Haeil at the hospital.
Oh, so he saw that.
Wait, so he knew everything
and still said,
"I'll see you bright and early tomorrow"?
How sly.
These guys are Boss Park's guys.
I'm certain
that Prosecutor Nam was behind this.
These assholes.
This is really pissing me off.
How dare they play around with my life?
Why are you so tense?
Where's the person
who was using two stun guns?
The thing is…
There's something I didn't tell you
about this house.
What is it? Wait, one second.
Okay.
Tell me.
To be honest…
I'm going to the bathroom.
It's number two.
Is he singing or just being a clown?
That was just pure yelling.
My ears are ringing.
This relieves your fatigue and stress.
It's really amazing.
You should give it a go.
What the hell?
Is she not dead yet?
Pawn Park
Where are you?
What are you doing?
Zapped?
Double pistols?
Cut the crap, you idiot.
This complicates things.
What's taking him so long?
Sir.
Don't say too much.
Then I'll die.
Hey, friends.
What took you so long?
Are you okay?
-Damn it, it hurts!
-Oh, dear.
Shouldn't you stay at the hospital?
Jeez, an important bladder…
I mean, an important matter has come up.
I can't just stay in the hospital, can I?
Good point.
Is the work done?
Done, and there are no issues.
Chairman Kim…
didn't catch on, did he?
If he did,
we'd be crippled or dead by now.
Actually, we'd be blocks of ice.
All right.
We just need to get our hands on the cash.
Make sure to divide it evenly.
Don't worry about that.
Boss Park may not be good at subtraction,
but he's an expert
when it comes to division.
Damn right I am.
Great!
Come in.
Oh, Father Kim.
- Come in and take a seat.
- All right.
So, are you feeling better?
Yes, I'm much better now.
I heard you went to the Diocesan Office.
I did.
I went to see the bishop.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
You sure know…
how to apologize quickly.
You must be really upset with me.
That's not true.
You're a…
You're a bellator.
I know you don't agree…
with a bellator's duty.
But in all honesty, you were a bellator
far before I became one.
May I ask why you deny ever being one?
That's not true, I was never a bellator.
To be more precise,
you've undergone a much tougher battle
than that of a bellator.
Noah found this
while organizing some old newspapers.
He fought in the 2004 demolition protests
in Yongcheon-gu, Seoul,
with the priests in the diocese.
I didn't expect him
to throw Molotov cocktails.
I've never even used those before.
It's all in the past.
It may be in the past,
but that doesn't make it go away.
I had no choice back then.
Fighting… was the only way.
Then what about now?
It's not a matter of past versus present.
I just think…
that lives matter more.
At the time,
I encouraged my closest friend
to join me,
and he died at the scene.
Francesco Jang Deokjun.
We attended seminary together.
Fighting against injustice…
only led to his death.
I might've considered it an honor
if it had been my death.
But because
it was that of my closest friend,
it felt like…
I had lost everything.
When I saw you fall to the ground
covered in blood that day…
…I was reminded of Deokjun.
That's why…
it was all the more heartbreaking
and painful.
Father Lee.
I've overcome death countless times
to fulfill my missions and duties.
There's something
that always crossed my mind
when I was on the verge of death.
I hoped that everything
could be resolved with my death.
And if it couldn't,
I hoped someone else would carry on…
and finish it on my behalf.
It turns out
that risking your life to fulfill a duty…
gives you… quite a dopamine rush.
And about the late Father Francesco.
I'm sure he's telling God every day
about his heroic exploits of that day…
all the while
sympathizing with your guilt.
It's an honor to have met a priest…
who has fought before me.
Nam Duhun, that bastard.
That absolute asshole. That shithead.
Kim Hongsik
Why is he calling?
Hello?
I'm sorry for calling so late.
"Late"? You realize it's 2 a.m., right?
Can we meet at the church?
The church?
All right.
Have some kimchi too.
You've had it rough the past two days.
Will this be enough?
What's wrong with ramyeon?
Whoever invented this should be rewarded.
It's so delicious.
-Father Kim.
-Stop talking to me while I'm eating!
We'll win this battle, won't we?
It's what the Lord wants, right?
Nothing is free in this world.
We have to be ready to make sacrifices.
Why does the Lord lead us
to a happy ending the hard way?
That's how he's always been.
His blessings always start rough.
That's the only way
we'll know their value.
Got it?
Mmm!
This is delicious.
Does it taste better when you don't share?
Yeah.
I can never eat in peace.
- Darn it!
- Where are you going?
I'm going to finish this!
Why did you want to see me
on such short notice?
I'm going on a business trip tomorrow.
I see this bastard's fleeing the country.
That's not something you need to tell me.
Can you come with me?
Why would I?
I have to deal with legal matters,
so I thought I could use some help.
Don't you have an attorney?
My attorney lacks resolve.
I'd appreciate your advice.
I can't. I'm a public official.
I never get involved
in personal company matters.
I'll talk to Prosecutor Nam,
so please consider it.
I won't no matter what he says.
A no is a no.
What do I do now?
I need you.
Do I have to kidnap you?
Oh my, listen to this guy.
If you are,
make sure to give me a delicious meal.
I like jokbal.
More specifically, jokbaengi.
-Jokbaengi?
-Ever heard of it?
Jokbal and golbaengi, jokbaengi.
Pig trotters and whelk. Got it?
I'm craving it now.
I don't know if it's appropriate
to say this, but I'm going to miss you.
I guess I'll miss you too.
Miss seeing you as a free man that is.
I don't think Kim Hongsik knows about me.
I guess Nam Duhun didn't tell him.
If that's the case,
then it seems he's trying to cut him off.
What do you mean?
It can only mean one thing
when he's keeping a double agent a secret.
He's trying to screw him over.
You're right.
Then again, an alliance
between two corrupt guys can't last.
Have you been to the honey jar room again?
Oh, right.
That's not what's important right now.
There's something more serious than that.
What's more important than the honey jar?
Well…
Polka Dot.
Polka Dot?
There's something I didn't tell you
about this house.
The previous tenants of this house
weren't chefs.
Do you know about
Oh Cheolgwang's case from last year?
I do.
The crazy bastard
who killed three of his girlfriends.
He committed suicide in prison.
This is where Oh Cheolgwang used to live.
You're lying.
I'm serious.
The splatters on the wall
aren't from sauce.
They're bloodstains.
Oh, come on!
I'm sorry.
Everyone knew it was a murderer's house,
so it didn't sell.
So the Busan Southern District
Prosecutors' Office bought it
and turned it into company housing,
and you were the first to use the place.
Why me? Why was I the first to live here?
Anyway, what exactly happened?
He killed three women in this house.
Two of the bodies were found in the river.
The remaining body hasn't been found yet.
As for Oh Cheolgwang,
he never revealed the location
of where he disposed of the body
and committed suicide in prison.
Do you have a picture of the woman
whose body wasn't found?
They've been looking for her body
for a year,
but it's highly unlikely they will.
That ghost is a murder victim.
Wait.
Do you have… a picture of the victim?
I saved it just in case,
but I can't look at it. One second.
-Can I open my eyes?
-Yeah, go ahead.
Come on, stop overreacting.
It's not that…
Things are really going downhill,
aren't they?
This is driving me crazy.
What is this, the year of misfortune?
Screw this.
Oh.
Taxi. Over here.
Young Beach Tower.
Oh, jeez. What the heck?
What the hell?
Do you not sleep?
Would you be able to sleep
after being humiliated
by the priest like that?
They can go about
doing whatever the hell they want,
but no one will ever know,
and your livelihood
won't be affected in any way.
Sure, whatever.
There's something I want to ask.
Why didn't you tell me
he was a former NIS agent?
Oh, that.
Well…
Well, I did some thinking…
…and thought
it wasn't worth telling you about.
Wasn't worth it?
It seemed pretty worth it to me.
Did you not tell me on purpose
to get me and the priest to duke it out?
What are you talking about?
What good would that do me?
You know,
weakening your partner
for you to become stronger.
You've watched way too many movies.
You seem pretty delusional at times.
I've developed a habit
of not trusting people over the years.
Goodness, Kim.
You really don't have
a keen eye for people, do you?
There's someone else
you shouldn't trust, not me.
What do you mean?
Prosecutor Park Kyungsun.
She's not who you think she is.
Ms. Park Kyungsun
is one of Father Kim Haeil's people.
What are you gonna do?
Can't trust anyone, can you?
♪ It's always fun ♪
♪ The little penguin Pororo ♪
All right, get ready!
Let's go! Extend your arms!
More! Extend them!
Make sure you do each move!
That's it!
Get ready for the kick!
There you go!
Pump it up!
All right, I want more energy!
Come on!
-Father Lee.
-Oh, hello.
Ah.
I thought you'd be busy,
so I had Chae Dou take the lead.
But you banned this exercise.
I realized that at times,
you need guts and strength.
That's it.
All together!
Bravo! Bravo!
- Guts and strength.
- Well done.
Hey, guys, have you heard?
I heard Kim Hongsik will be doomed
if we take down this place.
Wow, Kim Hongsik will be doomed
if we take this place down!
You know, he's not nearly as meticulous
as I thought he'd be.
He puts on a good show,
but he's sloppy in reality.
Go get your weapons.
Hey, let's get ours.
Our weapon…
is love.
We love you.
We love you. We love you!
Let go. Let go of me.
You can't just leave like this.
I don't know anything.
We know Kim Hongsik threatened you.
Just come with us and testify.
Go where? I'm not going anywhere.
I'd rather just die here right now.
Is it because of your family?
The police will protect them.
No one here trusts the police!
There are a few you can trust,
so please give them a chance.
How can I trust you?
Here.
We'll protect you and your family
with our lives.
Goodness, Mr. Lee.
You're the traitor.
That's a bit harsh, isn't it?
Don't run away.
It's better that you surrender to me.
Jeez, I told you so.
I was going to kick him.
I'm not just taking down a mere criminal.
I'm cutting out the rotten core
of South Korea's corrupt officials.
You hear me?
That's enough, Detective Gu!
You're going to kill him!
I thought this was
finally feeling like our home turf,
but it seems
we're more suited for away games.
Should we blow up this place?
You mean this entire 87-story building?
Yes, sir.
We're not terrorists.
Let's consider it a donation
and just leave.
Everything's ready.
Bye, Busan seagulls.
Goodness gracious.
I'm exhausted.
This is torture like no other.
Kim.
How does it feel to face reality?
That's the feeling of betrayal.
The phone is turned off…
"Good evening."
That's for nighttime.
Chairman Kim and his underlings' phones
are all turned off.
-Yeah?
-Yes.
I wonder why.
Did they run away?
-Did they?
-Probably.
-Probably?
-Are you kidding me?
Probably. Oh.
Come here.
-Are you out of your mind?
-I'm sorry.
You think you can joke around with me?
-Know your place.
-Yes, sir.
Stomach.
Get lost.
Should we start the countdown?
No.
Let's make it special this time.
Okay.
I'll get in touch
after I measure the distance.
How many kilometers is it from here?
It's 23.4 km.
We're clear of the blast radius.
You've never set off the bomb yourself.
This time…
I want to do it.
- It worked.
- It didn't go off!
Be quiet.
Why? Why?
Sound might cause it to go off.
Be quiet.
Thank God it didn't go off.
Stay still. Don't move.
Uma Gas Station
Sit. Sit for me.
What's going on?
There seems to be an issue.
Should we set it off manually?
I should've blown up
that 87-story building.
Angela the Geezer
Geezer Park!
Have you had breakfast?
It didn't seem like it to me.
Kim Hongsik.
Good work.
You got rid of my backup.
Where's Prosecutor Park Kyungsun?
She's not
Prosecutor Park Kyungsun anymore.
She's my new backup.
I wonder where she is.
Perhaps on the verge of meeting God?
What was that?
Father Han, Sister Kim.
-What happened?
-Go to the church.
- The church?
- Hurry!
Go ahead. Hurry.
Father Kim.
Don't move and stay where you are.
I'll go to you.
That chair
doesn't suit the church, does it?
Let me tell you its purpose.
I turn police or prosecutors
who don't listen to me
into drug addicts
and execute them on that chair.
It's my first time using it here in Korea.
Both syringes are filled with kasanin
at 100 times the usual concentration.
The second she's injected,
she'll suffer an excruciating death,
right around the time you call 911
and give them the address.
Hey, Kim Hongsik.
Do you have to be so clingy?
I have the right to be.
I even removed puffed rice from your face.
You're the one who fell for it.
You're right.
I honestly can't believe
how badly I fell for it.
Why are you doing this?
What do you want?
Look next to you.
Kill yourself.
Then Prosecutor Park will live.
You asshole.
Stop pissing me off and just kill me.
Suicide is forbidden in Catholicism.
Will you go against the Lord
and save Park Kyungsun,
or follow his ways and leave her to die?
You have only two choices.
Don't play any games.
If you do, she'll be injected right away.
You asshole, just kill me!
I hate playing the damsel in distress.
You have one bullet.
Aim properly.
Father Kim.
Put the gun down and get out of here.
You only live once anyway.
I've lived once and my time's up.
That's all it is.
If you were me…
would you be able to leave?
Then aim for one of the syringes.
I'll slip away when there's space.
I'm more likely to hit your face
than the syringe.
Just forget it. Stop. Forget it.
Okay.
It's decision time.
I'm starting the countdown.
You have three minutes.
Why only three minutes?
You could've given us more time.
It takes three minutes
to cook instant noodles,
the time it takes to think clearly.
Show us, Father Kim Haeil,
your faith or your sacrifice.
Don't do it, Father Kim. Please.
Don't do it.
-Father Kim!
-Stay back, it's dangerous!
Stand back.
Looks like he'll save Prosecutor Park
but not make it into heaven.
I don't want to live my life
feeling like I owe someone something.
Don't do it. I'm serious, Kim Haeil.
That feeling…
will go away with time.
Don't do it. I'll feel the same way.
Father Kim!
Don't do it, Father Kim.
Thank you…
for everything.
Father Kim…
Thanks to Shin Eunjung
for her special appearance
Translated by Jully Ryee