♫  Just tell me you can get up, so, so  ♫
♫  Just tell me you can do anything  ♫
♫  Right now  ♫
Welcome.
We've booked a couple's massage.
- It's under Lee Ru Da.
- Yes.
You made a reservation to meet Hee Jin and Yu Ri.
Please, wait a minute.
The customer has arrived.
They'll be here soon.
Hello.
My shoulder muscles are tight, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
Ugh, I knew they would be.
It gets like this all the time after I go on a date with my boyfriend.
Why?
Because my boyfriend doesn't let me sleep at night.
Others have eel or octopus
or even those herbal drinks.
I'm afraid my boyfriend will get a taste of those things.
It's already too much for me to handle.
His stamina is very good.
Unni, you're bragging, right?
Is that so?
Well, it is something to brag about if
a man isn't tired of dating one woman.
That's right. My friend says she feels unsatisfied with sleeping with her boyfriend.
She's wondering if she should break up with him.
Ah, I don't understand the girls who blame the guys for sleeping.
How is that just the boyfriend's fault?
If she is very attractive then the boyfriend can't stop himself, even if he wants to.
Isn't that so? Right?
Oppa, you haven't slept, have you?
How is it? It's refreshing, right?
It's nice, right?
It's nice.
Do Yong Shik's style is that?
I feel so refreshed.
Good.
I did so well.
It's been a while.
Have you been well?
I didn't know you worked here.
You looked good.
It seems like you're doing well with your girlfriend too.
Anyway, congratulations on your new relationship.
Hee Jin.
Thank you for everything.
What?
A guy like me...
For liking me for a long time.
For such a long time,
you stayed by my side so I feel so thankful.
Not being able to tell you this after we broke up,
weighed on my mind.
I told you I was sorry so many times,
but no thank you.
Truthfully, there were more times where I felt thankful towards you.
If you weren't by my side then...
I would've broken down even earlier.
I only endured it since you were there.
Thank you very much.
What are you doing?
Why did you say that?
Your erectile dysfunction started with that woman.
The words she said caused you trauma.
Even if it's a treatment for trauma, I don't think this is the right way.
You've hurt Hee Jin.
Is her pain more important to you right now?
You don't remember the horrible things she said to you?
You don't even want to get revenge?
I don't want to.
You guys broke up a while ago. Do you still have feelings for her?
She was once a person I loved.
Even though we broke up, she's a person I once truly loved.
Hurting someone I loved in order to erase my scars?
What kind of person could do that?
I feel thankful that you're thinking of me,
but I think you crossed the line.
If this is the method for treatment
then I don't need it.
Hurting someone I loved in order to erase my scars?
What kind of person could do that?
Do I still look like I'm childishly playing a game with you?
Yeah, you look like that even though you're not fit to be in that position.
Why aren't you getting out? You're leaving work.
I... I forgot something.
What about you?
I need to study something.
I guess the treatment for that friend isn't going too well?
That's what I'm saying. You're now feeling it, right? You've done something unnecessary.
That's not pride. It's just you acting rashly.
Ji Hyuk.
Yeah?
During the one and half year we dated,
did we love each other?
Someone said,
that they couldn't hurt someone they loved in order to get rid of their own scars.
But I feel like we always did that.
If I thought I took a blow, I would deliver a blow to my opponent to restore my pride.
I hurt you a lot by doing that.
But, was that love?
I'm questioning if it was.
Are you okay? Don't move your hand.
Show me your hand.
Does it hurt?
I think it's a fracture.
Forget it and please call 119.
I already called them. While waiting we should at least do some emergency treatment.
Wait a minute.
Hold it like this.
Are you a medical student?
Yes, a freshman.
Oh, you must've learned this.
I'm a medical student so you can rest assured. I'm doing this after learning how to do so.
Okay.
It's done.
Until the ambulance arrives, raise your arm higher than where your heart is.
I don't think we have to go that far.
You don't even know, so just listen to the future doctor.
I will help you.
Like this?
- What? Have you fallen for me?
- No way.
Okay then.
Is that better?
Hey, it's been three hours. Aren't you tired?
Just leave me be. This is the best thing to do when I'm stressed.
Why are you so sad for breaking up with a guy like that?
I'm angry that I got dumped.
Still, relieving stress by overexerting your body is foolish.
Why don't you spend time doing something more productive?
If it's like this
Would you like to date me?
I feel thankful that you're thinking of me, but I think you crossed the line.
Still...
Do Yong Shik is still the same.
Wow!
Aigoo, you guys are all Chunsam's kiddos.
There are too many!
What did you feed him to get him so productive?
Chunsam, you're really amazing.
Don't look.
Don't look at it.
Hey!
I'm even getting looked down on by a dog.
It was all a dream.
You are paying with a credit card when it's not even 2,000₩.
No.
Sorry.
Let's pay the bill together.
It may be more burdensome for you to take credit cards, but you do know it's illegal to refuse them, don't you?
Thank you.
Today the weather is really nice, right?
It said the fine dust level today is bad.
Very bad.
Why are you in our neighborhood this morning?
Do you have to be so straightforward?
Sorry.
Yesterday, I didn't think things through.
I was so focused on treating you that I hurt both you and Hee Jin.
Sorry for crossing the line.
I was sensitive too.
Then will you continue to get treated by me?
Even if I treat your trauma, it won't be in such a disrespectful way as last time.
I will study and do more research on it.
- Lee Ru Da.
- Yeah?
Thank you for putting so much effort.
Even though we have a history as classmates, you could've just ignored me.
Helping like this... not everybody will act like this, right?
I will try hard too so that your effort isn't wasted.
You came to work late today too.
I told you that I would come in whenever if I didn't have any appointments.
What if Lee Ru Da actually wins?
What?
You've been so hooked on treating your erectile dysfunction patient.
But that's because you made a bet with Ji Hyuk?
So, are there any improvements with that friend?
It's none of your business.
Why?
Are things looking worse than you expected?
I told you.
There's only one sure way to treat erectile dysfunction.
A new woman.
Really, Sunbae.
Wait a minute.
He met a new woman.
Who?
- You.
- What?
Yes, you.
You said you were the patient's first love.
Although he's been going around with you,
he hasn't changed much?
- Sunbae.
- That's weird.
Guys usually have that fantasy of their first loves
that lasts forever.
How ridiculous.
But now that I think about it...
Why hasn't Do Yong Shik changed even one bit since he met me?
The more I think about it, the more it hurts my pride.
Aish.
Do I have to use that method?
A $200 course meal?
Some people are cutting $200 worth steak
and here I am eating 70 cent ramen.
Ru Da.
Your lamp went out?
You're here.
Come in.
I was going to just leave,
but my younger sister won't be back until tomorrow
and I'm scared to be alone so I can't just do that.
Right here.
Wait.
Here.
You can stand here.
Okay.
When the light is off, suddenly It feels so hot.
Want me to hold you?
N-No w-wait.
Why?
Something came up, I think I need to go.
Sorry.
Yes!
It's hot in here.
Want me to hold you?
No need it's all done.
It's done.
Okay?
Why did you fix it so quickly?
In the military, I handled all the maintenance.
Maintenance?
Do you need to fix anything else?
No.
What a shame.
Good job.
Okay.
You can go.
Are you okay?
You said you were in charge of maintenance?
What was this?
I'm sorry.
I'm okay, you can let go of me.
Ru Da.
I said I'm okay. You can let go of me.
You make me embarrassed.
What is this?
I couldn't let go and talk to you.
Stay still I'll take it out.
I can't see. Wait just wait a minute.
I'm sorry, please wait.
Let's go to my room and take it out.
W-Wait.
Room? Stand up.
One, two.
Why? Why?
Why? Why? I'm sorry.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Sorry.
You stupid.
- Wait.
- Here. It's right here.
I know but—
Right foot, left foot.
I was so scared.
I almost cut my hair.
You know, right? I'm not suitable for short hair.
I said it suits you.
Like Matilda.
Matilda?
You're really going abroad to the US?
Yes.
When will you come back?
Don't know.
♫  I've walked around  ♫
I see.
♫  I arrived at where we used to go before.  ♫
Why is your hair like that?
My father got mad at me so he cut it.
What?
He found out I watched The Chaser on the day we got into an accident.
♫  It hurts  ♫
I look like Choi Young Rak, right?
No you don't.
You look like Matilda for me.
Like the heroine in the movie "Matilda."
Really?
♫  In your heart  ♫
♫  I really want to save you  ♫
♫  Wanna be with you  ♫
Even being abroad I will contact you.
Don't change your mail address.
Of course.
You must contact me.
Ru Da.
Lee Ru Da.
♫  My cold hand  ♫
♫  In your warm hand  ♫
♫  My frozen heart  ♫
♫  In your heart  ♫
♫  I really want to see you  ♫
♫  Wanna be with you  ♫
♫  There was no word we   ♫
♫  Just  ♫
♫  hurt  ♫
♫  Hold me in your heart  ♫
I wanted to contact you...
but I lost the note that had your email address.
After that, I was busy with many things.
That's life, I guess.
But sometimes I was curious
how you changed and what person you had become.
You must really be disappointed with me.
I was a little disappointed...
but you are still cool.
What?
When I saw you yesterday, I thought you still seemed like the same person you were back then.
Even though that person was someone you loved, protecting that person even if they hurt you and left you
is not an easy thing.
Humans, after all, put their hurt first.
♫  The bird with bent wings  ♫
Well.
♫  In the dark room  ♫
You were so cool.
And once again, I'm sorry.
♫  Tears fall down endlessly   ♫
♫  Leaning on the wall today it also closes its eyes  ♫
It's the perfect weather to have a cup of coffee.
Isn't it?
♫  A dream about flying  ♫
♫  Far, far, to far away  ♫
It is nice.
♫  Dream of flying high to reach the sky  ♫
♫  You quietly came to me  ♫
♫  Without a word, you stay next to me  ♫
You are so cool.
♫  Has passed again  ♫
♫  I close my eyes   ♫
She just happened to say that stuff.
♫   I am dreaming   ♫
♫   Just you and me   ♫
♫   Far, far, to far away   ♫
Are you okay?
♫  A dream with you and me  ♫
It hurts.
♫  Far, far...  ♫
Let's sleep.
♫   A dream that reaches space   ♫
The car key is on the kitchen table, take it.
Today's the 10th day.
Hey, Lee Ru Ri.
Do I look pretty?
Are you crazy?
Why is she like that?
It's like she's got a new man.
Hello.
- You came by.
- Yes.
Want me to give you the usual?
No, today... make them more beautiful.
Is it a special day?
Nothing like that.
Just to look good in front of my girlfriend.
Yes, please wait for some time.
Are you okay, Ru Da?
Let's get up.
Ji Hyuk, are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
The fracture isn't too deep so he just needs to have a cast on for three weeks.
Then.
Thank you.
It could have been really bad. Do you know how surprised I was?
Do you still think that I don't like you after this?
What?
Ru Da.
When you chose urology, the seniors all tried to stop you.
With such good academic grades, they were wondering why you chose such a bad major.
Suddenly why?
At that time you said this:
"Must I stay off a path just because everyone tells me to avoid it?
Why can't I pave the way by going there first?"
You were so brave back then.
And I thought it was so cool because it was something I lacked.
I might have even
had some kind of inferiority complex
towards you.
What do you mean with this so out of the blue?
That's why I thought you were cool,
and I also pushed you down
in order to raise my own pride.
Ji Hyuk.
You were asking if there was love while we were dating.
I really regret the way we spent our time together, too.
So... Let's start over again.
♫  I miss you everyday  ♫
How do you want me to cut it?
J-Just to look neat and likable.
Are you going on a blind date?
No.
Then you are meeting someone you like?
♫  I want to get closer to you slowly  ♫
♫  So that I don't make you uncomfortable   ♫
♫  Now I even talk the way you do  ♫
♫  I make it obvious like a fool  ♫
Let's go drink some coffee.
I already have plans.
Who? With Do Yong Shik?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
That person's treatment... let's hand it over to Jang Sunbae.
Let's not talk about your pride or whatsoever.
Even though you can't treat that person, I will not look down on you.
Perhaps are you worried because he's your first love?
No. There's no way.
Maybe it was like that in the past, but what can I do with a guy like that?
So...
let's wrap this bet and focus only on us.
That's what it was.
A bet between the two of you.
Yong Shik, that's not it.
You can do it, Yong Shik.
I will help you.
What should I do?
Perhaps you're worried because he's your first love?
No, it's not like that.
Maybe in the past,
but what can I do with a guy like that?
Do Yong Shik.
You didn't even know it was like that.
Lee Ru Da.
Yeah?
Thanks.
For caring this much.
You were cool.
♫  Holding on to the time  ♫
How do you want me to cut it?
Just to look neat
and likable.
Then you are meeting someone you like?
♫  and said please stop for a moment  ♫
♫  Your warm touch,  ♫
♫  your warmth for me in the past.  ♫
♫  I still can’t forget it  ♫
♫  I can’t do anything  ♫
♫  In a world like this  ♫
♫  In a world without you,  ♫
♫  I can’t do anything  ♫
♫  Even when I close my eyes for a moment  ♫
♫  I can still clearly remember you  ♫
♫  vivid memories of you.  ♫
♫  Like that day when we promised  ♫
♫  Can’t you show me more of our memories?  ♫
♫  I need to forget you but  ♫
♫  without even knowing, I’m thinking of you  ♫
♫   Those words  ♫
♫  So I lowered my head and closed my eyes  ♫
♫  I can’t do anything  ♫
♫  In a world like this  ♫
♫  In a world without you, I can’t do anything  ♫
♫  Even when I close my eyes for a moment  ♫
You.
You said you can treat me, right?
♫  I can still clearly remember you  ♫
You said you can fix me.
You said you can't watch me break down.
You said that, with your help,
I could do it too.
♫  Only tears fall because I couldn’t be better to you  ♫
I hate the fool that I am too, so
♫  I really can’t do anything  ♫
please, fix me!
♫  I don't want to  ♫
♫  I don’t want to let you go, please don’t leave me  ♫
♫  Even if I lose you for a moment,  ♫
♫  thoughts of you  ♫
♫  still remain with me,  ♫
♫  and so I  ♫
♫  so I can’t do anything now  ♫
♫  anymore.  ♫