Nuev verdrect
The Lastert of the gang
Get off!
During the dark night, it got in line Just like you, mix light to bright
Breaking free from darkness, you gave me strength
And unfortunately, I find my pain
Drawing on the hope that you'll render me
In this long journey, I run, I will not leave
Oh, Qiao Qingyu
I remember you right away
The first two days, I saw Ming Sheng
Bring a girl down from the bus
That little girl is you
Qingyu disappeared for two days
Is it because of Ming Sheng's grandfather?
Are they two good friends?
Don't talk nonsense
Those two days, she lived in our distant relative's house
It's none of your business from now on
Don't talk nonsense
I didn't say anything
I remember clearly what clothes she wore that day
Really? You're back
Let's go home
Let's go
Why are you back?
Give me a glass of water
Don't bring a pair of shoes
The teacher insisted that I didn't go to class
I had to come back
You're so annoying
Think about it again
What else did you forget?
Don't run around
You're wasting time
I'll leave the key here
I have to go back to the noodle house
Remember to lock the door
I know, mom
Send me the key
Okay
Qingyu
What?
Do me a favor
I'm going out
Why are you going out?
Mom won't forgive me
I want to see Ming Sheng
Sister
What's going on between you and Ming Sheng?
The little girl downstairs is not here
She's not here
The little girl downstairs
The owner of the shop is annoying
I heard she came to the store for noodles
for the first time in three days
She caught mom and told her
the idle talk between you and Ming Sheng
Ignore her
If she comes again, you'll drive her away
If I make her angry
she'll say bad things about our family
Mom said
The noodle house and the house
have been rented for a year
We'll move in until September
Then, when you graduate next year
you'll go to college abroad
I'll stay in Huanzhou
to study
Dad and she will go back to Shunyun
so the economic pressure will be less
Sister
What happened between you and Ming Sheng?
Nothing
Then how did you get to her house?
I can't say it clearly
but I have to see her today
I won't have any relationship with her
anymore
Then
you always have me to blame this time
For the reason that
I didn't ask you to help me
in the last draw
you didn't mind me
I helped you
But you have to remind me
to see Ming Sheng
I have to tell her in advance
I have to return the key to mom
The time of our work
is only two hours
Enough
I'll send her a message first
She'll come if you send her a message
I hope so
I'll see you in the summer
Now
Give me a tree
This is not yours
This tree is mine
This big tree can talk
It's saying
I shouldn't have been angry at you yesterday
I'm sorry
I heard that your mom is very strict with you
I didn't expect you to come out so soon
My mom said if you harass me again
she will set your family on fire
She is not joking
I really find it funny
I have a feeling that I am not in the right place
But if it wasn't for your mom
I didn't know
that I was so important to you
Don't talk nonsense
I didn't talk nonsense
Since you read the note
and asked me out
should you explain
why you left without saying goodbye
Why do you think
I would choose you between family and you?
Actually you want to leave home more than me
Recently he said it was just a game
Yes, I want to bet on the future
and bet on everything
I asked you out today
because I think it's better to say it in person
I am very grateful that you have done so much for me
But nothing has happened between us
Nothing in the past
Nothing now
It won't happen in the future
I don't understand
There is no future between us
What do you mean?
After graduation from high school
you will go abroad and I will stay in China
Our life is two ways
We shouldn't have any contact
You have your future
I can't ruin it
When I was abroad
I didn't help you
You were in the train station during the New Year
You had a fever. I took you home
I can decide my own future
But I am different from you
I lost the moment I was caught
I can't hurt my family again
I can't leave home again
You are like last semester
You can treat me as a stranger
or a person you hate
I am not a stranger to you
I don't hate you either
But without you, my life would be much easier
You are my burden
I hate you from the beginning
You are so arrogant and arrogant
You are so arrogant
We are not on the same side
Qiao Qingyu
I didn't want to hurt you
I am sorry
It's okay if you don't accept my apology
But can you not hate me?
I hate you
Qiao Qingyu
I always thought you and I were alike
But I was wrong
What will you do?
I will choose freedom
If people don't have freedom
why would they live?
Qiao Qingyu
Are we still friends?
Yes
It's okay
I didn't say anything
I am still grateful for what you have done for me
It's okay
It's all nonsense
Let's go
Every choice in life is like a battle between yourself and yourself
The most painful thing is not that others deny you
but self-doubt
My mental world suddenly collapsed
I feel like I have never really touched this world
There is chaos around
I feel like I am standing in a big fog
My body grows like a dark cloud
But my soul is lost
I am still grateful for what you have done for me
Guan Lang
I only got one point worse than you
You were only one rank lower than me
You got 20 rank lower than me
I finally understand what you mean
What does one point difference mean?
Come here
Zilin, why are you so anxious?
You never have any suspense when you are in the shop
Can I help our Ah Sen?
Sure
14 seconds
Full of physical and physical
You are so excited
You can't do it, you have to do it in a row
It's called hard work
Do you understand?
Qiao Qingyu got 13 seconds
Isn't this a life-long test?
Ah Sen
Is it funny?
Isn't it funny?
Half
Qingyu
Teacher Sun
Your composition
Teacher Pan told me
I didn't expect
You look calm
But you hide something so big in your heart
Actually
I have experienced this
I suddenly found
These common values
Life principles
It's not quite right
I was also depressed at that time
Because I didn't know if it was my fault
Or the whole world was in trouble
But then I slowly found out
These standards are not always the same
You have to look at it specifically
For example
Hiding
It may not be wrong
I think
The best growth
Is to face life gently and calmly
The world that once made you sad
It will go with the flow of time
It doesn't matter anymore
We are experiencing a lot of things every day
Meet different people
Unpredictable and uncontrolled
Instead of persistent struggle
It's better to smile
These two days
The school invited a doctor from the province
To give psychological counseling to the classmates
If you have any ideas, you can talk to him
He is a professional
In short, the school and the teacher
Hope you can open your heart
Sorry
It's okay, classmate
Come to me at any time when you are ready
I can't talk to Le Fan
I have too many worries
I can't see the sun
Actually I have been insomnia for a long time
Is it because your parents quarreled?
I don't know
How long do I have to live in this world?
Mom, after you pass the college entrance exam
And leave home
You will get better
Then
What about my mom?
Yes
I did leave home
But I will always be their child.
They will always be my parents.
I can live without them.
But the relationship between us will last forever.
We will never be able to break free.
So, Qingyu,
I envy you.
You can endure it.
You can live on.
Because in your heart,
there is light.
So you have no fear of the dark.
No, Nanny.
The light in my heart is going to go out.
It's good that you're here.
You saved me.
This is the evaluation that everyone has for me.
Warm, kind,
and considerate.
Don't you like it?
It's not about whether I like it or not.
I feel that the road ahead of me
is very dark. I can't find the light.
So, Qingyu,
I envy your courage.
At least you can do what you want to do.
There will be light.
《The
Life of a
Coward》
Morning, Mr. Caterpillar.
Where are you going to play?
Sheng is not here.
Deng Meixi said that he had a physical exam.
He went to the library with Deng Meixi for a lecture.
Library lecture?
He really has a good reputation.
Let's go.
Next time.
Pack up your things.
Sheng said he's going to sing in the afternoon.
Yi Zhong and Xiao Hua?
Let's go.
I have a friend who I've asked to meet several times,
but he didn't show up.
Sheng and Yi Zhong and Xiao Hua.
Is this a strong alliance?
Is this a history of competition?
Let's go.
There aren't many books to write.
Hurry up.
Are you okay?
Give me a hand.
Your dad is also
so stingy for this 20 or 30 yuan.
Have some tea.
Isn't that the pretty girl on TV a few days ago?
Yes, yes, yes.
The heroine who made a scene
on the TV.
She's pretty.
Look at her.
Isn't she the sister of the most beautiful girl in Shunyun?
Yes.
You've got the wrong person.
How could I have the wrong person, auntie?
You're the owner of the Qiao family noodle house.
We often go there to eat.
What are you doing there?
Let the pretty girl eat with us.
Song, what are you doing?
Isn't that Qiao Qingyu?
Aunt,
what are you doing?
let's make friends with the young people.
Let's go.
You're leaving?
What's wrong with you?
Didn't you say you were going to meet Yi Zhong, Xiaohua and K?
When are we going?
I'll give you a headache.
Thank you.
You didn't make an appointment?
Then why did you invite us here?
To eat instant noodles and enjoy the scenery with you?
I told my dad that we were going to have a bowl of porridge today.
The difference is too big.
I'll eat yours.
Song,
why did you pretend to be a man when you saw Qiao Qingyu?
You like to be unfair and drag her down.
What's wrong with you?
Did you have a fight with Qiao Qingyu?
I see.
You're called
to win the heart and to win the heart.
Winning the heart and winning the heart.
Right?
I'll eat yours.
You can't avoid eating what you have.
Eat.
Have a bite.
Qiao Qingyu?
The online celebrity Qiao Qingyu
is very handsome and has a very good look.
I'm sorry.
You want to see the original picture or the real me?
What do you mean?
Hurry up.
Oh my gosh.
Is it that bad?
Did they find out about it?
Is this Qiao Qingyu's clothes?
Did something really happen to her?
Sheng.
Is a picture enough?
Is it that person?
Sheng, calm down.
Sheng.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
It's not her.
How many more are there in the row?
Let's calm down first.
Calm down.
You hit her.
You hit her and you came here.
You scared me.
What's wrong?
Talk to me.
Did you send the picture of Qiao Qingyu?
It's none of your business.
I mean the picture.
Will you talk to me?
Say it again.
What's wrong?
Come on.
Oh my gosh.
The picture is her fart.
How can it be so smelly?
It's not good to look at it.
Qiao Qingyu's hair is in the news.
The hair is pasted on the back.
The background is also fixed.
Ye Zilin.
It's me.
Can you blame me?
I didn't even touch the picture.
You just went out.
Enough.
The truth is out.
You didn't touch Qiao Qingyu.
So Qiao Qingyu's mother
was scared.
Only aunt beat her.
I understand why Qiao Qingyu
was so scared of her mother.
She is a cruel person.
Luckily, the police came soon.
Otherwise, I can't stand
so many people fighting.
Because a picture is so impulsive.
It's not like you, Sheng.
Childish.
Enough.
Have you said enough?
Anyway,
we three have to fight.
I'm sorry.
I'm in big trouble.
The school will know.
I can talk to her.
I'll think about how to deal with your father.
There is no infection.
It's just a case of
keeping people from eating all day long.
I'm so annoyed.
Qingyu.
Come to the hospital with me tomorrow morning.
Take a blood test.
Qingyu has a math test tomorrow.
It won't affect the college if you don't take the test.
The school has a medical examination every semester.
It's useless.
You don't understand me.
Take a blood test to make everyone feel relieved.
You can't let people say
what they want to say.
They have the strength to say it.
It's up to the person.
Don't you know how bad they say?
They say your whole family is sick.
If you go to the hospital and let people see it,
isn't that more idle talk?
Or you go too.
Mom, I'll go.
Isn't it just a blood test?
It's quick.
I'll go to class after the blood test.
The school has a medical examination every semester.
Dad is asleep.
What's wrong with mom?
She's insomnia.
She can't sleep if she's asleep.
She's old. She's like this.
I'll sleep here tonight.
I don't want to wake her up.
I thought this would pass.
But it turned out to be true.
I don't want to argue with your mom.
You're going to take the college entrance exam soon.
Think about it.
We were pretty close.
When we got married,
they were all my friends.
I was your friend.
Your mom and I
were in a free love.
But
I don't know how
I can live my life like this.
Stop drinking.
I'm sorry.
Jingyu,
I'm not afraid of your jokes.
I'm a man.
I'm the pillar of the family.
But I often
can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
You're really good.
Give me a kiss.
You didn't plan to let Qiao Xin know
about what happened yesterday.
It's okay to avoid her.
Ah Che, your dad is here.
He's in Mr. Sun's office.
Your dad is here.
I thought...
The situation is a bit serious.
Why did Mr. Sun
make your dad so mad?
Mr. Sun made your dad so mad.
Your dad will definitely make you mad tonight.
You're done, Ah Che.
Ah Che.
I see you.
Hello.
How is it?
Is the signal over there okay?
It's okay.
It doesn't seem to be lagging.
The show is over.
It's very good.
It's very successful.
When I was envious for the last time,
the applause lasted
four or five minutes.
Do you know how excited I was?
Oh, right.
This is from Yuemi.
Mom,
congratulations.
Good luck.
Thank you.
How are you?
I'm fine.
I learned half of the words
from the school president.
It's a small achievement.
Ah Che.
Mom, you don't have to persuade me.
I just want to remember.
I won't do
what he wants me to do.
You're an adult now.
We can talk like adults.
Can you listen to me?
I really don't want
your relationship with your father
to be so different.
I know very well
how he feels about you.
He's not good at growing up.
You can also
talk like us.
You can be honest with each other.
This is good for you.
Okay?
Wait a minute.
There's something
that's been hidden
in my heart for more than ten years.
I want to tell you.
Back then,
I left your father
on my own.
Your father
put all his energy
into his work.
We were a family.
I thought that
it would be a bad thing
for us.
So I insisted on leaving.
I was very willful
and impulsive.
I didn't want to leave
because I didn't want to
be a burden to my family.
I didn't want to leave
because I didn't want to
be impulsive.
I insisted on leaving with you.
Your grandfather disagreed.
He was right.
I was alone in France.
I had no shelter.
I ate too much
and didn't get enough sleep.
How could I give you
a normal life?
He said
he wanted to keep you
and leave on his own.
I was selfish.
Because of my selfishness,
I made you and your father
become like this.
Because of my selfishness,
you became so rebellious.
I didn't want you to forgive me.
I just wanted to let you know the truth.
I'm sorry.
Yanqiu.
Dr. Chen's dog.
You've raised it well.
You don't know.
It's been a mess
since I came here.
These days
are just as important as before.
I brought some fruit.
Thank you.
It's windy today.
Really?
How is your family?
They're doing well.
The deceased patient's family
has applied for medical confirmation.
The Medical Regulation Committee
has also joined.
The results will be out in a few days.
Everyone has to face
the death of a patient.
If they're sick
or hospitalized,
if they don't cure the disease,
it's all the doctor's responsibility.
But doctors are not gods.
Doctors are just the excuses.
They've suffered so much
and they still have to suffer.
This is probably
the greatness
and the sacredness
of our profession.
Everyone
has his own
perspective and position.
Everyone is willing
to look at the problem
from his own perspective.
I've been thinking
about it for a long time.
The knot in life
that can't be untied.
I started to stand
at the patient's point of view.
I even stood at the point
of my son, Sheng.
At this time,
I suddenly understood
why they could be so powerful.
I was so angry.
When I really started
to understand them,
the knot in my heart
was untied at any time.
No matter what the result is,
I believe in you.
Don't...
Don't say that.
It's not that bad.
Even if I can't
do the surgery anymore,
I still
have other things to do.
I still believe
in fairness and justice.
I believe in you.
Don't talk about me.
Talk about you.
How are you recently?
I...
That nurse
didn't ask you to go on a blind date, did she?
I think
she's quite like you.
She's like me.
We're both pretty good.
You're not going to answer me, are you?
If you have any questions,
you can ask me.
I'm your father.
You're a high-ranking police officer.
This is a community.
Don't play with me.
I'm your father.
I'm your mother.
You're so strong.
Don't talk to me like that.
Okay, okay.
I'll go to the car.
I'm warning you.
You bastard.
You're not going to answer me.
I'm so angry.
I'm going to die.
I'm warning you.
You're not going to answer me.
Momo.
I called the police yesterday.
I called them.
They said
they were going to call me.
I told them
that I'm going to go to the police station.
I called them.
I want to help mom.
Be brave like you.
Do something.
The police came
to ask mom if she wanted to take responsibility for her father.
Mom refused without thinking.
After the police left,
dad was even angrier.
He beat up a Greek in the house.
Mom said I was not sensible.
How could I send my father
to the police station?
He didn't sleep all night.
It's so obvious that it's right and wrong.
Is there no place to talk about it?
The police said
if this happens again,
you must not be indifferent
and call the police immediately
and apply for legal aid.
I hate my dad.
I hate him
for not doing anything
and only hurting me and my mom.
But now,
I hate myself even more.
I'm sorry.