Please come in.
Hello, I'm looking for that…
Old place.
Thank you.
Come in.
- Dr. Tian, I'm back.
- Come on, sit.
This is for you.
Why are you alone again?
Where's your husband?
Dr. Tian, the prescription you gave me last time really worked.
It was quite effective.
I told you last time the patient himself needs to come.
My husband's illness mainly involves…
Sometimes, he gets back pain and his legs feel sore.
Are you… joping for a child?
No.
Since you don't want one, then why are you so eager to see a doctor?
Look at those male patients outside.
Which one of them has his wife come to see the doctor for him?
It's male pride.
Dr. Tian, please understand.
How about this? You give your husband a call.
At least, I need to understand what exactly your husband's situation is.
All right.
He's usually very busy with work, and when I call him,
he can't answer during work, so, he might not be able to answer.
Look. He's busy.
Can't even answer.
Give me his number.
Here, I'll call him.
Doctor, well…
- It won't make any difference.
- Let me try.
He's busy.
Hello?
Hello. Hello.
Are you Mrs. Liu's husband?
Here's the situation.
Mrs. Liu came to our traditional Chinese medicine hospital to get medicine for you.
But look, Chinese medicine requires inspection, auscultation, inquiry, and palpation, but I have not seen you in person.
She came to get medicine today, but I don't know what your situation is.
Honey, you're back.
Honey, when did you come back?
Why did you drink so much? What was the occasion?
Have some water.
Are you feeling unwell?
I just had a little drink with colleagues.
All right, I got it.
- A little bit.
- It's okay.
Are you uncomfortable?
Don't sit here.
Don't keep sitting here.
Shall we go to bed?
Quick, get up.
I'll help you, go slow.
One, two, three.
Lie down properly.
Are you feeling unwell?
My wife is the best in the world.
The best, the best, the best.
You should drink less in the future. Do you hear me?
Drinking like this is bad for your health?
What can I do?
I didn't drink much.
- I only drank a little.
- Fine, you didn't drink.
Take off your shirt.
Forget it, don't take it off. Cover up and go to bed.
Forget it. Time to sleep.
Jelly Bean,
don't go away.
[WeChat: Red Jelly Beans❤️, Yingying Jelly Beans, Pink Jelly Beans, Yellow Jelly Beans❤️, Green Jelly Beans❤️, Black Jelly Beans❤️]
[Red Jelly Beans❤️]
[Pink Jelly Beans❤️]
[Baby, I haven't seen you for 37 hours]
[I miss you so much what should I do?]
[Today, my wife and I...]
[Already miss you my Jelly Bean]
[Are you thinking of me? You must me.]
[Okay, are you taking a shower? I'm going home.]
Jelly Bean.
[Fake It Till You Make It]
[Episode 7]
Sorry, I'll be there soon, I'm sorry.
[Liujianlian North Village]
[No.18 of 24: The estimated waiting time is 40 minutes, and maybe longer during peak hours.]
I'm sorry.
- I'll do it.
- No problem, I'll do it.
Are you-Are you okay?
I'm really sorry. Where are you hurt?
Hand or foot?
It's okay.
- I'm really sorry.
- Sorry. Sorry.
Where are you heading? We can give you a ride.
I didn't see you. I'm sorry.
Wait! Are you okay? Do you need to go to the hospital?
No need, I'm fine.
Where are you going? I'll take you there. Let's go.
No need.
It's fine. Where are you headed?
I'm heading to the WFC. It's in Guomao. Is that convenient?
- Convenient, get in.
- I'm indeed in a hurry.
Thanks.
You haven't slept all night until now?
Impressive.
When are you leaving?
Tomorrow.
You have to personally run a due diligence in Anbei District.
How things change.
That's the truth of our industry. Winners get it all.
Bullshit.
Just because the Walrus case didn't work, they're giving you a hard time.
Look at your dark circles.
It hurts me to see them.
Do you remember when we just started our careers?
We did an M&A case, and hardly slept in a month.
No time to sleep or to eat.
Both sides' lawyers were competing to stay up.
It's only been seven or eight years.
Why do I feel like I can't keep up anymore?
What you lack is someone who cares about you.
You have a meeting with a client at 10:00 in the morning, and you wake up at 9:50 a.m.
Shouldn't you be taken down a peg or two?
I was really anxious this morning.
I was afraid I would be late, and I was in a hurry.
Didn't I send you a message?
And then, in that instant…
When the business card was handed over…
I took a look and instantly calmed down.
- You're Mr. Ma from Wanguo?
- Yes.
I felt like, at that moment, he was glowing.
I must have been the chosen one.
What a rare and golden opportunity this is.
I could get close to the client.
He took a liking to you.
Impossible.
Mr. Ma. Ms. Xin. I will send the meeting minutes to your email.
If there are any updates on the project, I will keep you updated in time.
All right, thank you.
Thank you all.
- Mr. Ma, I'll go back and get it done first.
- Okay.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
Sure, let me scan your QR code.
I'll scan yours.
We just added each other on WeChat. How normal is that?
The higher-ups tend to be more straightforward.
So when they spot a target, they strike quickly.
If they only saw you as a minion, why would they add you on WeChat?
Tang Ying, let's have dinner together this weekend.
I told you.
What-What should I do?
When I said he was glowing, it was purely for the project.
What if he really likes me...
and I don't handle it well?
Wouldn't it harm our case?
But what if you handle it well?
As a worker in the workplace, you should learn to leverage all the resources around you.
If you're smart enough, there might be a cleverer solution to this.
Having choices is a luxury.
So you're very lucky.
The opportunity is right in front of you.
If you handle this well, it will mean a promotion and raise.
Of course, there are also certain risks.
In general, it depends on your personal will.
I choose to do a good job on the project.
I believe in you, and I will protect you well.
By the way, Geer Group asked for a new legal specialist.
Liu Meiling quit.
When did this happen?
Before you came. Mr. Zheng said it just now.
[Friend hasn't posted in their circle of friends in the last 3 days]
[Tang Ying, have dinner this weekend?]
[Sure.]
[Set up notes and tags, friend permission, circle of friends, more information]
[General friends can only see the circle of friends in the last half year.
[MA: It's not a pity to stain clothes, but nothing can be done to make wishes.]
Look.
He's also trying to be mysterious in his Moments.
What would you like to eat?
I can eat anything.
There's a very authentic mutton soup place near my house.
Would you like to try it?
Be careful.
This box is so big.
- The benefits are really good.
- So good.
The company treats us really well.
No need to give it to Xu Ziquan.
He'll be gone in a few days.
- Boss-Boss, do you need help?
- No.
Where are Jin Hao and Dou?
They have been visiting Miss Ada frequently recently.
By the way, keep an eye on a recent project for me.
- I'll send the specifics to your phone.
- Okay.
Before I get back, don't tell anyone which company I've been in touch with.
Don't worry, Boss.
Boss…
Eat your mangoes.
Hello, Mrs. Meiling.
You're in Beijing.
Sure, no problem.
I'll come to you.
Okay, see you later.
[DO Original Saloon]
Tang Ying.
Mrs. Meiling.
You changed your hairstyle.
Do you like it?
It looks nice. A different style.
Here, have some water.
How's it going? Are you getting along well with the legal specialist at our company?
Pretty good.
Actually, I wanted to invite you to dinner just to say thank you.
Thank me?
I got a divorce.
After seeing countless jelly beans on his phone,
Mrs. Meiling started to doubt
whether everything she had built till now had any meaning at all.
Her marriage, her life, these facades,
were they deceiving others, or just fooling herself?
But looking at everything she already possessed, she hesitated.
Until that day, when her flight landed ahead of schedule.
Hurry, she's back.
Get dressed now.
Forget it, just go.
You…
Why didn't you tell me you would be back so I could pick you up?
I always thought you were ill.
Turns out you were spending your time with someone else.
Jelly Bean, I was drunk, you know?
I don't even know how I got back.
Jelly Bean.
When you touched my hand, it made me feel utterly nauseated.
And stop calling me "Jelly Bean".
It's also disgusting.
I'll send you the divorce papers. Sign them quickly.
- Stop it, will you?
- Let go.
- Will you stop?
Let go.
You're really terrible at sex.
I thought I'd keep living like this, deceiving myself.
It seemed all right. But then I realized I couldn't.
Mainly because Zhang Yiwen appeared.
Yes, I feel like he reminded me
of who I used to be.
[Gore]
What brings you here?
A business trip.
Well, I was passing by.
I happened to be in the area, so I came.
This area of yours is large.
You've come to Shanghai.
Yes.
I've come to Shanghai.
I got a divorce.
I know.
I'm doing pretty well. You-You're doing well too, right?
When are you leaving?
I haven't bought my ticket yet.
Are you free later?
Let's go and have a meal.
Tang, if it weren't for you,
I might have missed him for the rest of my life.
So, thank you.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Miss Tang, your meeting minutes were very detailed.
I look forward to cooperating with you.
Perfect.
For the Matsuba crab, we should mainly eat its meat.
The hairy crab is more popular with us normally,
and it's about the roe.
When Autumn comes, I'll take you all to Shanghai
to taste the authentic Yangcheng Lake hairy crab.
All right, that sounds like a plan.
So, for our team building, we're going to Shanghai,
and you'll treat us to freshly on-season crabs.
For hairy crabs, we have to wait until they're in season,
and then wait another two to three weeks,
that's when they're the fattiest.
We have a saying, "Nine females and ten males." Have you heard of it?
No, we haven't.
The nine and ten here refer to the months in our lunar calendar.
But, Mr. Hu, don't just keep talking.
Look. You haven't eaten the crab meat on your plate, and it's about to overflow.
It's true.
I have this problem that I love to peel but not eat.
Here! Let's share it and eat together.
Here, Xinzi, let me give you some.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Isn't it a bit too much?
- No, it's not too much at all.
Help me divide it. Eat more.
You know, your habit of loving to peel crabs
but not eating them is just fantastic.
In the future, if anyone becomes your girlfriend,
she will be so lucky.
Who can argue with that?
Xinzi's boyfriend is just like that,
treating her with complete compliance. Not to mention peeling crabs,
he could even skin a spider for her.
Xinzi has a boyfriend? It makes sense.
You see, if such a beautiful girl like you were truly single, I would find it a bit strange.
Hurry up and dig in.
I'll continue peeling for you, come on.
Xinzi, I want to buy a gift for a girl I like,
and I'd like to ask for your advice.
I don't have good taste. Should we ask others to help you choose?
Your taste is indeed not good.
So you should ask others for help.
Xinzi, you didn't misunderstand
and think the girl I like is you, did you?
How could I possibly think it was me?
After all, I have a boyfriend. Right?
Yes.
You know I am still your leader right now, but it's so hard to ask you for a favor.
And do you think I am the kind of person
who'd eagerly steal someone from others?
It makes sense.
How about this? Tell me your budget, taboos,
and any special meanings, and I'll help you choose.
Okay, there are no special meanings,
no taboos, and no expected price range.
Let's just choose the expensive one.
- That's so perfunctory.
- No, it's not.
It's because I trust your taste.
You just said my taste was not good.
I meant your taste in picking men.
Xinzi, I didn't mean that. I'm sorry.
I know you're my leader, but I still have to say this.
I don't want to hear anyone talk badly about my boyfriend in front of me,
especially when you don't know much about him.
Mr. Xu, Richard specifically told me to accompany you and give you a hand.
As for the hotel, it's not that I'm not attentive,
there just aren't any good hotels.
When you get there, please don't be angry.
No problem, as long as there's a bed to sleep in.
Over here, Mr. Xu.
Where is dinner arranged?
They said it's the best restaurant in the local area,
and they just sent me the location.
Let's go.
Wait for me, sorry.
Mr. Ma.
I just went for a bike ride.
You changed your car.
- They haven't arrived yet.
- I'll go to the restroom.
To be honest, when you sent me this address yesterday,
I was a bit surprised.
I thought we would go for mutton soup.
I really do like mutton soup,
but it's nice to change up the flavors now and then.
This place seems like the food should be good.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Besides mutton soup, what else do you like?
Actually, I like drinking tea.
Not many young people like tea these days, huh?
Because I think when I'm drinking tea, it allows me to slow down.
And actually, tea tasting is quite interesting.
For example, look at this menu here.
The Phoenix Dan Cong and Rock tea,
even though they're both part of the oolong tea family,
and they're both semi-fermented teas, there's a big difference.
Rock tea is a northern Fujian oolong,
and Phoenix Dan Cong is a Guangdong oolong.
Which one do you like?
Actually, they both have their own merits,
and their aromas are also different.
Rock tea is mainly characterized by its high boiling point,
its fruity and woody aroma, and it has a rather long-lasting fragrance.
It tastes solid when you drink it.
Phoenix Dan Cong is mainly characterized by its low boiling point and floral aroma.
The fragrance doesn't last long, so it tastes a bit frivolous when you drink it.
But it's lively.
So, it mainly depends on what you want to drink.
After dinner, let's have a solid cup.
Sounds good.
Young man, your face is all red.
This kid is stubborn, isn't he?
- Can you still drink?
- You're bluffing.
Mr. Xu. Factory Manager, this is Mr. Xu.
Cheers.
Mr. Xu, a talented individual indeed.
Come on, take a seat.
Squeeze in, squeeze in.
Okay, quiet down, guys.
Mr. Xu, please sit.
This is our guest of honor today. Mr. Xu.
Everyone, a round of applause.
Good, good.
A little introduction. These are our friends today.
You could say, in this place,
they are somewhat important figures. Right?
The cultural group.
All the performances will be well arranged by us.
For loan-related issues, you can come to me, no problem.
The young man is really good-looking.
- Later, Old Bai will set you up with someone.
- Hello, hello.
If you need steel, talk to me.
I'll give you the good ones.
Cheers.
- Let's introduce this person, it's our…
- Do we even need to say?
You've heard of the Tomson Revival. Right?
It was built by him.
He's an entrepreneur; the big boss.
Brother Shan, isn't it?
Yes, right.
Brother Shan, his reputation is high.
Well, everyone, please have a seat.
Let's sit.
Why be so polite?
Sit, sit.
- Look, your face is all red.
- You've introduced us,
but you didn't say what Mr. Xu does for a living.
Haven't I told you before?
Well, he is with that Xin…
Jintou Xintai.
Never mind what it is.
It's about taking companies public,
resource integration and transformation, and revitalizing our Anbei market.
By him?
Can this young man do it?
Though the weight is small, it can weigh a thousand pounds. Right?
I like that.
Let's not talk about it, let's…
How about a toast to Mr. Xu?
- Good idea. Come on, let's toast.
- Wait a minute.
According to our rules in Anbei, we must drink Chinese wine. Right?
- I'll pour for you.
- Thank you.
Of course, it must be Chinese wine.
Come on, fill it up.
A full glass is a sincere heart.
Unfortunately, the weather is not so good today.
During Autumn in Beijing, the bike view along Chang'an Street is particularly beautiful.
You also like riding bikes.
I also like riding bikes.
Have you read "Spring Evening" by Yu Dafu?
Spring Evening?
On A Night Drunk with the Spring Breeze.
Every time I ride a bike along Chang'an Street, I would think of this piece.
Because the scenery is really too beautiful.
The last time I rode a bike along Chang'an Street was when I was in college.
Unfortunately, my cycling skills are not good.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have bumped into you last time.
I'm really sorry.
You didn't have any after-effects, did you?
No, no.
I'm very tough. I can't be hurt.
See you next time.
Phoenix Dan Cong, solid.
Rock tea.
Frivolous?
You got it backward.
Just drinking tea, can you really tell the difference?
Are you messing with me?
How could it be?
Before I went there, I studied here all night at the teahouse.
I asked them a lot of questions.
You worked so hard.
You put in the effort you would for a background check.
If you don't succeed, who will?
I'm even worried if I tried too hard.
You had a meal with Mr. Ma.
How do you feel about him?
He's not like the rich man I imagined.
Maybe because he is a first-generation entrepreneur. He's very down-to-earth.
Do you like him?
I can't say I like him. At most, I don't dislike him.
So I suggest, for this matter, we should focus on landing this project.
First, try to figure out what he sees in you.
And then you just take this strength and maximize it.
I don't know what he sees in me.
It certainly can't be my looks.
So the first time you met, he was interested in you, a little lawyer.
It certainly can't be for any practical value.
Could it be that I provided emotional value for him?
Maybe he finds me interesting and fun
and wants to ask me out for a chat over dinner.
Anyway, I suggest that the next time you see him,
show more of your professional woman's aura.
Don't let him look down on you.
You're right.
After leaving it has gotten quite lonely here, hasn't it?
You call this lonely? This is called tranquility.
How are things with you and Xu Jiabai?
To be honest, he takes care of me in every possible way.
Every morning when I wake up, I can see a full breakfast he prepared for me.
It's nothing like when I lived with you.
Every day all I ate was some junk food.
What kind of junk food?
So, you are showing off your love
and rubbing it in my face, huh?
Honestly, I feel he's a bit overly attentive to me.
It makes me a bit uncomfortable.
Men in love are like this, anxious and insecure.
But you have no idea.
Every day when I go out, he is always fussing over my clothes.
Walking on the street, he thinks there are men staring at me.
He's totally fallen for me.
He's just nervous about you.
This bath oil of yours is very expensive.
If you take it and lose it, what will you do then?
Just keep it at home for your own use.
I bought it to use it.
We should learn to enjoy things.
It hasn't been opened yet. I opened it specifically for you.
See how good I am to you.
Wait! We're going to the bathhouse
just to eat the buffet, to scrub off the dirt, and to gossip while lying down?
Why are you trying to be so fancy?
What dirt to scrub off? I am very clean.
I don't need to scrub off anything.
Have you forgotten how you got scrubbed by Aunt as a child
when you were covered in dirt, the floor was all muddy, and even the drain was blocked?
- Don't slander me.
- You need to scrub off the dirt.
You still need to scrub it off, huh?
Thank you.
- Hello.
- How may I help you?
Could you arrange two scrubs for us?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Brother Shan.
- Why did it take you so long to undress?
You came, Brother Shan.
Okay.
Brother Shan.
Brother Shan! Brother Shan!
We've been waiting for you. We don't need to spend any money.
- Brother Shan.
This is the feeling.
- Just enjoy it.
- Good.
- How about it, Brother Shan?
- Brother Shan, remember to go upstairs later.
Is it comfortable?
Do you still remember
that time you competed with me in the sauna to see who would faint first?
Don't talk. You're affecting my performance.
How did my aunt describe you?
Stubborn and competitive, not taking the easy way.
Every time my mom calls your mom, these are the two words she uses.
Do you know what kind of a pipe dream your aunt is having now?
She wants to come to Beijing to buy me a house.
Did my aunt become rich overnight?
She's not thinking clearly.
She doesn't understand the housing prices in Beijing at all.
How could we, as workers, possibly afford it?
I agree.
They can't imagine the situation in Beijing at all from our hometown.
Look at our monthly salary. It's so little.
If we talk about down payments,
we could only buy those old, worn-out second-hand houses,
tiny and crowded, with no elevator,
and definitely not in the school district.
How's it going between you and Xu Ziquan?
Pure friendship.
Who would believe that?
You're not deceived by his rubbish talk, are you?
Let's go and get something to eat.
There's also buffet food.
Have you stayed enough?
It's okay. Let me tell you.
Go take a sauna.
What's up with you?
Didn't you use to take baths at home?
Mr. Xu is shy.
Rarely.
I actually have something to tell you.
What is it?
Do you remember that guy from Palm Bay?
The one who invited you for mutton soup?
I know, yeah.
He later became your client, didn't he?
He asked me out.
On a date?
Do you mind?
Do you like him?
I don't like him.
But on the one hand, he is my client.
I have a professional relationship with him, so I can't refuse him.
On the other hand, I think
there's nothing wrong with getting to know him.
I see it as a kind of exercise.
If you want to deal with him, go ahead.
I just feel that he might be a little bit rustic.
No, to be precise, he is a bit too down-to-earth.
So he is really rich?
Super rich.
Super rich?
I was wondering why you suddenly asked me to take a bath.
Then let's have a toast.
No worries.
Who doesn't slack off a bit at work?
- Here's the information on the Wanguo M&A case.
- Look carefully.
Okay.
The world is quite cruel, isn't it?
You have to work and deal with interpersonal relationships.
No one cares whether you have enough time.
They only care if you're doing well enough.
Not giving up on either side is what a worker does.
I read the report you sent me yesterday. It's very professional.
I was impressed.
Thank you.
Why are you blushing?
Hasn't anyone praised you before?
When Wang was here,
all she said was "no, not right, not possible."
Everything started with a 'no'.
- I know it's her personality, but…
- I see, a lack of affirmation.
No worries.
I'm here now, and I'll praise you in the future.
By the way, the afternoon meeting, Mr. Ma changed it to 7:00 p.m.
and it's at the golf course.
I see you've got a good grip on this case. So I won't go.
You can report to him.
Am I going alone?
Why are you getting nervous? Didn't I just say how great you are?
Okay.
Be tough in tactics and soft in demeanor.
You are the best.
Keep it up.
Mr. Ma.
- Mr. Ma.
- You're here.
It's okay. Take your time. I'll just wait here for you.
That's impressive.
Come on, you have a go.
No, I can't.
And I've never understood the pleasure of playing golf.
Because this sport seems too static.
In golf, you can imagine that each hole is
one of the many goals in our lives.
Every time you swing,
perhaps it's not about how to get the ball into the hole,
but to achieve each and every goal you set for yourself.
Is that true for every golfer?
Not necessarily. Because everyone interprets things differently.
Hearing you say that,
I've become a bit interested.
Well then, give it a try.
Your shoulder, waist, and hip, should be in a straight line.
Come on.
Not bad, you hit it. Another one.
Hitting it counts as good?
You've got to start somewhere.
Look. The difference
between golf and other sports is
your only enemy is always yourself.
So, it's a sport where you can make a mistake at any time,
just like in our daily life.
If you want to let go and not be entangled,
you have to immediately and quickly adjust your mindset, and start over.
Come on! Find the feeling and try again.
- Starting over.
- Start over.
Not bad, the line is straight. The line is straight.
No, I'm not good at this,
and I don't have any talent for it.
Mr. Ma, I'd better report to you about my work.
You haven't even tried and you're already negating yourself.
I've read your report. It's crystal clear at a glance.
Actually, I don't have any questions.
But you asked us to have a meeting.
Originally, it was because...
I saw you work hard, and I wanted to let you relax a bit.
However, I made you feel a bit tangled, huh?
No, I'm very happy. Thank you, Mr. Ma.
My friend's daughter is going to have an art exhibition, and the opening is the day after tomorrow.
Are you interested in attending with me?
Me?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Meng, impressive.
Come again.
- Can I sit here?
- Come on, Mr. Li.
Can I sit here?
Are you all right?
Cute guy, did you come by yourself?
- What?
- Did you come by yourself?
With my assistant.
Aren't you with Brother Shan?
Yes, I came from out of town
to talk business with Brother Shan.
Then, will you have a drink with me?
Let's add each other on WeChat.
Let's ask Brother Shan to create a group. Okay?
Brother Shan, your friend is too boring.
What's wrong, Quan? Not happy?
Sit down.
Going out is about having fun.
- I'm happy, happy.
- Right.
I want to tell you we really don't do real estate.
How about this? After I go back to Beijing,
I'll organize some information and then send it to you.
You can see if there's anything you're interested in.
If there is, we can talk further.
- All right?
- Okay, no problem.
You've come a long way, so I should take good care of you. Right?
Brother Shan, how about this?
You guys have a good time.
I'm a bit tired today, and I'll go back first.
What are you saying? You can't leave.
You're our guest of honor. What will we do if you leave?
I'm telling you! You can't leave, right?
Brother, can I take a call?
I won't leave. My clothes are here.
Fine, you can take the call.
Come back soon.
Mu.
Boss, the Universal Conjecture case is done.
Okay, got it.
Brother Shan.
I won't leave, okay?
I'll stay in Anbei for a few more days.
Let's drink. Okay?
Come on, come here.
Bottoms up. Okay?
Come on!
- Mr. Xu, look. This is our storage tank.
- Okay.
Yes, we also have different grades.
Take pictures.
They are mass-produced.
This side is our fermentation tank.
Right. They might look the same on the outside…
How is it?
The taste is not bad.
Try it.
- A warm welcome.
- Bottoms up.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir. Our plane is about to take off.
Please confirm that your phone is in airplane mode and then turn it off. Thank you
Okay, thank you.
Hair.
Miss Wang.
Come on, let me see. Are you ready?
Not really.
When does Ma Qiyuan want to meet you? Tomorrow?
Tomorrow. His friend's daughter is having an art exhibition in their courtyard house.
And he's inviting many friends.
Art gallery celebration.
There must be many young girls at the scene.
Plus, with Ma Qiyuan's status as a wealthy bachelor,
many girls would be interested in him.
The relationship between the interviewer and the interviewee has turned from one-on-one to one-to-many.
If you don't stand out,
you will be drowned out.
By that time, this admission notice will be out of your reach.
I understand.
So this second interview is a group interview.
So, I should dress to attract attention.
The flashier and more brilliant, the better?
As long as I catch the eye of my interviewer,
won't I be the shining star of the whole scene?
You're wrong.
Ma Qiyuan is looking for a colleague
through a group interview, not a girl group member.
In comparison, gentleness and wisdom are much more appealing than aggression.
So on that day, I have to be a woman
who understands art and has a low profile.
The weather is quite nice today.
But it's a bit too sunny.
I'm telling you! I really want to meet him.
I'm quite nervous.
Who isn't?
But I don't see him.
Their style is quite unified.
Why are you here?
A friend invited me.
Always telling me you're busy,
but you're here messing around.
Aren't you messing around here, too?
You seem to have a good eye.
Accompany me to buy some stuff. Okay?
Let's go, hurry up.
Hurry up, quickly.
You're doubting me, huh?
I remember there should be some small shops around here.
What kind of shops?
Clothing shops.
You'll know in a bit.
This looks good. Let's give it a try.
Are you planning to change your style?
Didn't you notice the girls just now?
They're all dressed similarly to me.
How would I stand out?
Is it a bit too exaggerated?
Could you help me find a coat? I always feel this coat doesn't match well.
This coat is too plain.
The color scheme I'm wearing matches better.
Indeed, it's not bad.
However, cute girls only wear small sizes.
Thank you.
Please help me look carefully.
You're not changing clothes just because you wore
the same style as everyone, are you?
Of course.
Do you not know it?
Sometimes, clothes are not just clothes.
They are battle armor.
Battle armor?
For which spoils of war?
Of course, it's for someone very important.
The total is 3,420.
Okay.
Does it look good?
Fantastic.
That's good. Fantastic?
Awesome, thank you.
Actually, you'd look good in anything. No need to deliberately dress up like this.
I'll contact you later.
Goodbye, see you, we'll talk next time.
Mr. Ma.
Ziquan.
Was that your friend? Not going in together?
No, we just said hello.
Let's hurry in then. It's almost time.
Wait a moment.
Can you accompany me to buy something?
Is it appropriate?
[Dialogue Art Exhibition]
My mom's friend also has a courtyard house like this.
It's just a bit smaller.
Guess how much?
How much?
About the market value of a small listed company.
That's Beijing.
Filled with hidden talents.
Do you see that uncle?
He's the owner of the courtyard, Old Zhang.
I heard he has a deep background, a second generation.
The person talking to him should be the chairman of Wanguo, Ma Qiyuan.
The one wearing the off-shoulder shirt on the side...
should be his new girlfriend.
At such a young age, she's attached herself to an uncle.
Quite vain.
Xu Ziquan.
You look quite handsome today.
I thought you were only interested in contemporary art.
Look at these flowers and birds. How vividly drawn.
I'm just looking around.
These flowers and birds are all part of Old Zhang's collection.
Who is Old Zhang?
That one.
Look. He has vision, luck, and energy.
- Not at all.
- So impressive.
I didn't see them at the auction.
Tang Ying, look.
The paintings here at Mr. Zhang's, each and every one is a masterpiece.
Very rare.
Miss Tang, are you also interested in calligraphy and painting?
Whose paintings do you like?
Well, I'm just a novice.
I dare not speak, afraid you'll laugh at me.
Let's go in and take a look.
Wait a moment, no rush.
Then I'll say it.
Actually, I think these painters have all been influenced by the landscape of the Sui and Tang dynasties.
Admiration and impact from one generation to the next are all passed down one by one.
We can't jump out of the entire era
to evaluate any of them individually.
Mr. Zhang, you mentioned Master Lin just now.
Actually, I quite like him.
Look at the bird painted by Master Lin.
Its belly is round and plump, very cute.
But if you look closely,
I feel a bit of sadness.
Surely, it has a beautiful name.
Sleeping with the Wind.
Very romantic.
Let's go.
I didn't expect Miss Tang to have such a high level of artistic accomplishment.
Mr. Ma, what a coincidence.
Long time no see.
Xu Ziquan from Jintou Xintai. Nice to meet you.
We had a project together before.
- Hello, hello.
Mr. Ma's girlfriend is really beautiful.
No, she's my legal advisor, a lawyer, Tang Ying.
I'm sorry, I assumed.
I won't bother you any longer.
I'll just look around.
I'll give you Master Lin's bird.
This off-shoulder girl is quite impressive.
I originally thought she was just Ma Qiyuan's dessert after dinner
or a small strawberry on the dessert.
I didn't expect her to not only be articulate, brave, and meticulous,
but also earnestly represent Ma's business.
It seems that tonight will be fruitful.
"Moment of Peace" - Saji
♫ They walk... the streets where thoughts were lost ♫
♫ Wondering if they will ♫
♫ ever be caught by their own lies ♫
♫ In the quiet of night ♫
♫ as wonder if we right ♫
♫ Just another day this was the trace ♫
♫ And this the noise a rush cry for rush ♫
♫ I need the peace for a moment, it's my time I need to feel alive ♫
♫ to feel alive ♫
♫ The hearts align their heartbeat ♫
♫ Where the dreams are, the dreams are so close yet so ♫
♫ Yet so far to grasp ♫
♫ All these doubts will leave but still will find a way ♫
♫ Will find a way to feel alive ♫
♫ Will take a guess I wonder ♫
♫ If we're really, truly blessed in our life, I want to feel alive ♫
♫ If your hopes, they make you blind, will find a way ♫
♫ I'll find a way ♫
♫ I will find a way ♫