Let's go this way.
Sure.
[Caution]
But...
there's a restaurant in this area?
Well...
Is it one of those hidden tasty restaurants without a sign?
Restaurant?
There's no such thing.
What? It's you, right?
From the BABting app last time.
It was...
Nameless!
Now you recognize me.
I was actually going to buy you a meal
because I left so suddenly last time.
Don't you think it's too late for amends
when you left so rudely and looked down on me?
[8 missed calls from Cha Min Ho]
The number you have dialed is currently busy. Please leave a message after the beep—
Where is she?
[BABting app...]
The number you have dialed is currently busy. Please leave a message after the beep—
Joo Ah.
Are you okay?
Sunbae.
Do you...
like Ha Neul?
What?
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
I'm so taken aback right now.
On what grounds are you asking me this?
I don't want to bring up every little thing that bothers me,
but I still feel the need to confirm things.
The fact that you took Ha Neul's picture during class,
and saved his name as Maneul on your phone.
Isn't that all because you have feelings for him?
During class,
I already explained I did that to get a good grade.
And his name on my phone holds no meaning.
I just saved it as his nickname.
I save lots of my friends by their nicknames.
It's ridiculous that I have to explain myself to you.
Then what about this?
What about it?
- It's just scenery.
- It's a picture of the sky.
(T/N: the word 'haneul' means sky in Korean)
Hey, Seo Ji Min!
You're so full of it.
I know that you really like Ha Neul,
but aren't you being too sensitive right now?
You're the one who asked me to take care of him since we're in the same major.
All I did was be nice to him since he's your boyfriend.
[Sang Gu: See you tomorrow]
You saw the guy I was with just now, right?
That's the computer science Sunbae I told you I liked last time.
Things are going pretty well with him.
I was at a café, doing my assignment with him until I got your call and came here.
But you...
I even told you my secret
that there's someone I like.
How could you corner me like this?
I mean...
I thought it would be better to talk to you than continue to suspect you.
I'm really sorry.
- I guess I've been too sensitive lately.
- Forget it.
I can see what you thought of me all along.
- No, Ro Sa, it's not like that—
- If it bothers you that much,
I'll just stop hanging out with Ha Neul.
I'll go now.
Holding something warm should calm you down.
Thank you, Sunbae.
Let's go to the police once you've calmed down a bit.
I already reported what happened,
but I think it would be best if you went yourself.
Hey, Cha Min Ho!
Why don't you pick up your phone?
D-Do you know how scared I was?
Tak Moo Yeong, this guy.
He has several previous convictions of stalking and residential invasion.
You could've been in serious trouble.
Thank goodness this student called it in right away,
so nearby patrol officers caught the perpetrator.
That son of a b***ch.
Cha Min Ho.
Just stay here.
It's a relief
that nothing happened, and you even found your phone.
It's thanks to you.
I'm really grateful.
It's nothing.
I'm more thankful that you're safe.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I shouldn't have made this weird app.
It's all my fault.
No, it's not.
He's the weirdo.
I'm going to get rid of this app.
What?
Hey, you worked really hard on this app. Why would you get rid of it?
And didn't you say you would start a business with it?
You can use this opportunity to check on risky aspects
and tighten the security.
I don't even want to look at the app right now. I'm going to delete it.
No, it wouldn't make sense for you to just quit everything over this.
I can just make something else. I'll do business with that.
I'm sorry I found you too late and
for making you go through this because of me.
Hey,
I still survived, thanks to you.
This.
Today, I'm going to win that Polaroid for sure.
You said you were good.
We spent over 30,000 won ($30) on this already.
We could just buy a Polaroid with this money.
No.
I have a good feeling today.
Please, please, please, please.
Of course...
Pepper spray?
How could you grab the most useless-looking thing in there?
Wow. I never thought I would use it for this.
You really sprayed this on that bastard?
Are you out of your mind?
What if you had aggravated him even more?
Why? I ran away just fine.
I didn't think I had the courage.
When he got to about 50cm close to me,
I sprayed this straight in his eye—
Please don't make me worry anymore.
Call me whenever you walk into dark alleys from now on.
Okay?
I'll pick up right away from now on.
Y-Yeah.
You must have been really scared.
I was scared, too.
All right.
You're overreacting.
I guess I am your only best friend. No wonder you're so worried.
I'm almost touched.
Let's go now.
[Lee Chi Yeong Sunbae]
- You're here?
- Yes.
What about Joo Ah?
- She's not here?
- Yeah.
Something came up, so she didn't come to work.
What did you talk about with Ro Sa?
Just about Cheer Squad stuff.
Why?
Is something going on with the Cheer Squad?
No.
We just talked about random things.
Hey, stop glossing over things ambiguously.
Speak your mind, huh?
How am I supposed to know if you don't tell me?
Hey!
I don't want to talk!
What's your problem?
I'm on a café date with you because you wanted it so much.
And every day I let you eat your 15,000 won ($15) souffle pancake that's just a piece of bread!
Hey. I followed you to the Internet Café.
And I even learned how to play games for you.
Did I ask you to?
I honestly don't want to play games with you, either.
- Wow.
- Oh, my.
Fine. You won't even watch one romance drama with your girlfriend.
Why am I wasting my time talking to you?
You said it was fine!
You said you're fine watching it alone.
Did you think I was really okay?
Wow, look at your sense of empathy. Are you showing off that you're a science major?
Aigoo. Then what about you?
Do you talk in circles because you're studying liberal arts?
Forget it. Why are we even dating?
- Let's just break up.
- You bring up a good point.
You took the words out of my mouth.
This is why they say not to be a campus couple.
That couple from earlier was really funny, huh?
Do all couples fight like that?
We wouldn't know since we've never fought.
I know.
But isn't the guy right?
She should tell him so he knows what's going on.
But we don't know that couple's situation.
There could be a reason she didn't want to say anything.
Like something she didn't want him to know.
Or...
the boyfriend could've been unreliable, to begin with.
Oppa, would you like to eat lunch with me tomorrow?
[Ro Sa: Oppa, would you like to eat lunch with me tomorrow?]
Would be great. What time should we meet?
Dongsaengdeul, it means she's interested if she asked me out to eat, right?
You're the one studying psychology.
How could you not know the psychology behind dating?
Dating is all about the data and experience,
but Mok Jin Hyung has never been in a relationship before.
How would he know without any data?
You little punks are spewing painful truth right in front of me!
What is this? Is this real?
BABting will be closed for the safety of all users.
Thank you for using BABting until now.
No wonder I couldn't open the app today.
Joo Ah, are you okay?
You must've been really scared.
It could've ended terrible.
I'm glad nothing happened.
I've had it rough, too,
but Cha Min Ho really worked hard to make that app.
But if I were Min Ho, I would close the app, too.
You, above everyone else, could've gotten hurt.
Min Ho must be suffering, too
and feeling sorry toward you, too.
He even had to shut down the app he had worked hard on.
But he'll overcome it soon.
He'll make another app in the blink of an eye, too.
I know Cha Min Ho.
There could be a reason she didn't want to say anything.
The boyfriend could've been unreliable, to begin with.
Hyung, that doesn't look like an assignment.
What are you doing?
I've been working on a game in my free time.
I really want to complete a game this semester.
Please show me when you're done.
Sure.
Are you pulling an all-nighter, too?
Yes. You, too, right?
Let's do it with a fighting spirit.
Fighting.
[SAT 08:19]
[SAT 08:20]
Excuse me, Ro Sa...
Hey, you came.
Are you up?
Why are you calling me so early in the morning?
I want to start working out starting today.
I'm at the gym. Do you want to come, too?
Why are you doing something you've never done?
Running yesterday made me realize that my stamina isn't the same as before.
I want to increase my stamina and I might as well go on a diet, too.
You're really not going to come?
No. I'm hanging up.
Joo Ah is working out?
Yes. She's going to the gym in the dorms.
Really?
It reeks of sweat in there.
I went there once and thought it was for men only.
There are only guys there.
Okay.
Is this your first time?
Yes.
Why don't you get off for a second?
Look, you shouldn't go all out from the beginning.
Okay.
So you lie down like this.
Grab it like this and just push up.
Breathe out here.
Bring it all the way down and hold your breath.
Understand? Here.
Have a seat.
Give it a try.
That's right. Grab it like that.
Grab it.
Good. Now push all the way up.
As you're pushing up, breathe out.
Breathe in and then push up again.
Good. All the way.
Wow, you're good. That's it.
Thank you.
Are you in physical education?
Oh, I'm in Early Childhood Education.
I'm an Early Childhood Education teaching assistant.
Good. You did well.
Lower it a little and breathe in.
That's right.
Push it all the way up. Good, you're doing great.
Lower it slowly.
Right, and push all the way up.
Hey, Ma Joo Ah.
What? I thought you weren't coming.
My body felt a little stiff after we hung up,
so I thought I should loosen myself up.
- I'll see you next time.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Hey. He's really good at teaching exercise.
I think he would do really well if he opened a gym.
Sunbae!
You guys come to the gym, too?
Yes. You, too?
Yes. I come out every morning if I can.
That's great. Let's work out together.
I would love to.
Excuse me.
Hey. Aren't you overexerting yourself?
What are you talking about?
I always do this much.
Wow. What's that?
You have abs, too?
Hey, this is just in the morning.
Later in the day, they speak up for themselves, and it's worth a good look.
If you say so.
Min Ho Dongsaeng, are you okay?
- Yes.
- That's why you shouldn't overdo it suddenly.
But, Dongsaengdeul, what are you going to do about the scenery assignment?
Oh, right. We need to do that, too.
I'm going down to Tongyeong soon.
Do you guys want to come with me?
Did I tell you my family runs a guest villa?
Oh, really?
I'll offer free bed and breakfast.
We can go and take pictures, hang out, and relieve stress.
I think it might be hard for me because I have an assignment.
I need to create a new app, so I'll pass, too.
Fine. Don't go. Don't go.
You think I don't have any other friends besides you guys?
I have other friends who'll go with me!
We met Mok Jin Oppa in front of the dorms earlier.
He asked if we wanted to go to Tongyeong with him.
He said he had other friends. That was you guys?
Yeong Unni and Joo Ah said they wanted to vacation and do the assignment, too.
You probably can't because of your assignment, right?
I guess we can go together next time.
You want to go, too?
What?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
I was just wondering what you were going to do about the assignment.
Let's go.
I don't have assignments for a while.
- Really?
- Yeah.
We should go.
I honestly thought that we couldn't go anywhere for your birthday
since you're so busy with the switch in majors.
I'm so glad.
It's my first time going to Tongyeong.
Hyung, I'll go to Tongyeong with you.
We're just saying it's for an assignment, but it's going to be a total retreat!
You're really not going?
I don't have time. I need to make a new app.
Oh, right.
Don't worry. I'll have double the fun on your behalf.
Don't be tacky and take a suitcase to Tongyeong.
Like that time during the orientation.
That was because I was a freshman, and I didn't know.
I'm not like that anymore.
Do you happen to know what Mok Jin Oppa likes?
Hyung? Why all of a sudden?
Nothing. I just have a favor to ask of him.
But, why did you suddenly ask me to eat lunch with you?
Oh, well...
I just wanted to get closer to you.
I don't know that many people at school
because I came back from the exchange program.
I also did think that we would get along
when I met you in the game room for the first time.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Oppa, you seem to be really close with Ha Neul.
You're roommates, and you even went to an escape room together.
Yes.
Ha Neul seems apathetic at first,
but he's a good guy the more you get to know him.
That's because you're a good guy, and you see him that way.
Someone once said,
that it's instinctual to see the bad traits in someone,
but seeing the good traits in someone is a talent.
Gosh, you didn't have to say that.
Ha Neul has a lot of good traits.
He's good to his mom and responsible,
and he doesn't get mad easily.
He relieves his stress by gaming.
Oh, he must really like gaming.
There's a game that'll be released soon called "Last Youth."
He's totally excited waiting for that to release.
Oh, really?
And it's Ha Neul's birthday soon.
October 1st,
so I'm planning a party.
Oppa, you're so attentive!
You even take care of your roommate's birthday.
Gosh, this is nothing.
I would take great care of my girlfriend's birthday if I had one...
Excuse me?
Oh, it's nothing. Nothing.
What are you planning to do about the scenery assignment?
My family runs a guest villa in Tongyeong.
So I'm planning to gather some people, including Ha Neul and Ji Min
to take a visit to the guest villa for the assignment.
Do you want to come with us?
Yes. I would love to! I want to go, too.
Really? That's great.
The more, the merrier.
And it's good if we do the assignment together.
Ro Sa.
Are you still angry with me?
It's just hard to face you right now.
I know. Of course.
I'm really sorry.
I know it's an excuse,
but it's my first time seeing Ha Neul grow close to someone so quickly.
I guess it felt so unfamiliar to me.
I still shouldn't have accused you like that.
I'm so ashamed of myself, and I feel bad toward you.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
Actually, I went home and thought about it, too.
I think I would've been worried if I were you, too.
Thanks for asking me right away, though.
Or else, I would still be under your suspicion.
I don't want us to keep being awkward with each other either.
Really?
You won't misunderstand me again, will you?
Of course not.
Thanks.
I met Mok Jin Oppa earlier, and he asked me to go to Tongyeong together.
Can I go, too?
Yes! Of course, you can.
Oh, that's great.
Then can the app that we're developing also be utilized in aircraft?
Joo Ah!
Why did you call me?
Oppa, please drink this.
Thank you.
Do you know that sunbae in the sweater?
We take the same class.
Yes, I do. I've seen him around.
Can he come with us to your guest villa?
I don't know him that well, though.
And I don't think we'll have enough space in the car.
A cleaning product organizing kit?
I had this added to my cart.
If that sunbae comes with us, I'll give you that.
Okay. You can bring him.
We just need to rent a bigger car.
Wow, how handy.
The study group ended earlier than I expected.
What are you doing now?
I'm going to meet Ji Min and the others at Re-Feel later.
You must be really close with your roommates.
Yeah.
I heard you ate lunch with Mok Jin Hyung earlier.
Yes.
I had something to ask him.
Hey, Hoobaes!
Hoobae, is our assignment coming along?
Yes. You know.
You two look really close now.
I always see you two together.
Is that SeoRab post true?
That something is going on between you two?
- Flirting?
- No.
If not, fine.
I'll be off now.
If you want any food or snacks while working on the assignment,
just let me know what kind of food you crave.
I'm done with my shift!
Good work, Joo Ah.
- Good work.
- Good job.
Let's eat.
Joo Ah, thanks.
I was able to stay comfortably until this late.
No worries.
You can come to our café for your study group whenever you want.
I'm close with the boss.
Okay.
Everyone's from our class.
Hello.
Oh, these are my roommates and Cha Min Ho's roommates.
Sunbae, you should join us for a drink if you have time.
Please do.
Yes, join us.
Yeah. Have a beer. Let's go back to the dorm together.
Then, shall I?
Sit here.
Thanks.
Then everyone here is going to Tongyeong, right?
- Except Min Ho?
- Yes!
Retreats are fun with more people.
Is there anyone else who wants to go?
Are you guys going on a retreat?
Oh, we're going to Tongyeong for our Photography and Appreciation assignment.
Sunbae, would you like to join us if you're free?
What?
That's right. You're in the class, too.
I'm fine with you joining us.
Can I?
We rented a big car, so we have extra space, too.
- Let's go together.
- Yes, let's go together.
Yeah?
Then I'll drive.
If it's all right with you guys, then let me join.
I'm a good driver.
That's great.
Sunbae, would you like more beer?
No, it's fine.
Huh? What is this?
There is a new post from Maple Latte.
Why didn't I see this earlier?
"I drew this picture because I saw a blooming flower as I walked down the street
and it reminded me of my first love."
But what is this?
Isn't this an insult?
Is it a man or a woman?
Is it even a human?
The floral background is pretty, though.
I think they did a good job.
This?
Yes.
It's like modern art.
I also think it's nice.
It's like Picasso's style.
Perhaps, did one of you draw this?
Really. Is that it?
It's one of you, isn't it?
You're both suspicious.
And they had one more glass.
Wow! Thank you.
- Thank you!
- Amazing.
It seemed like you liked this one.
Thank you, Sunbae.
Something's going on between them, right?
The air between Joon Hyung and Joo Ah is sweet.
Something's going on between them.
They do look good together.
What's going on, Min Ho?
Is something wrong?
Or are you mad at me?
No.
My keyboard is usually loud.
Oh, yeah?
I think I see the back of your heads more often than your faces.
I'm lonely.
Gosh, I want to have a sweet romance, too.
Sweet...
Sweet romance.
I don't know if I ever can.
You're staying up all night to finish your assignment to go on the trip with Ji Min Noona.
Hang in there.
Ji Min Noona should know how considerate you are for her.
Don't worry about me and worry about yourself.
What?
Are you really going to be okay?
Sending Joo Ah and Joon Hyung on the retreat?
What about it?
Judging by today, it seems like you should step it up.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Why are you acting ignorant?
You're aware of it.
That you like Joo Ah.
Joo Ah Dongsaeng, are you moving?
She took out a few things this morning, and it's still like that.
I thought I would need everything.
Okay.
Min Ho. Over here.
Min Ho's coming, too?
What?
- You said you're not coming.
- I know, but...
I changed my mind.
Shall we go?
Yes!
- Off we go!
- Let's go.
Not there.
Sit next to me.
Why are you doing this?
I'm going to sit in the front.
You're going to fall asleep for sure.
What will Joon Hyung think when he sees you sleeping with your eyes and mouth hanging open?
What are you saying? You think I would fall asleep next to Joon Sunbae?
Joo Ah fell asleep.
She always falls asleep when we travel for over two hours.
Min Ho.
Are you really closing down BABting?
Yes.
You probably worked really hard on it.
What a shame.
There are a couple of other apps that I thought of,
so I'm working on a new one.
Yeah?
As expected of a talented one.
Ro Sa, what's your MBTI?
INFJ.
You were an INFJ?
I'm an ENFP!
Did you know that INFJ and ENFP are a match made in heaven?
Huh? I'm also an INFJ.
Then are we also a match made in heaven?
What?
There's no way that's possible.
That should never be.
It's going to be so much fun!
It's the ocean!
The weather's so nice.
What a bunch of tacky city people.
Where are you going?
We need to work on the assignment!
I took a lot.
What do I do? I just slept the whole ride.
I should have helped navigate and such.
You don't think Sunbae is disappointed in me, do you?
You should've listened to me when I told you to sit in the back.
Did I sleep with my eyes open again? How was I?
You were a mess, but Sunbae didn't witness any of it.
What a relief.
Joo Ah. Can I borrow your lip balm?
- Sure! Of course.
- Hold on.
My lips keep getting chapped.
Thanks.
Was the car dry?
They keep getting chapped.
This is the famous Dongpirang Mural Village.
There are a lot of places that are photo-worthy, so take a good look.
This all changes periodically.
So it's a little different every time you come.
And it also depends on who you walk with.
I think I've seen it in movies, too.
That's right! In "Ha Ha Ha!"
It came out in that movie.
And you can see sugarcanes here.
The view here is really nice,
but if you go all the way up, there are even better views.
In Tongyeong, there's what's called Dongpirang and Seopirang...
I'm going to take a good one.
Were you taking photos of me?
Look at this.
- You're so good.
- They look so good together.
I could also take great pictures of my girlfriend.
Let's go together.
♫ Our relationship is getting sweeter ♫
♫ Oh, babe ♫
♫ Maple latte, smoothly ♫
♫ It remains around my lips ♫
♫ I hope you feel the same way as I do ♫
What are you doing?
Move it!
Gosh, seriously.
It doesn't suit you.
I just tried it on.
Get lost!
Come quickly!
Quickly, quickly.
Noona. Hyung.
What are we doing?
- Did everyone take their photos?
- Yes, it's so nice here.
Now, it's time for the highlight.
Are you all prepared to be cursed out?
Let's go! Let's go get cursed out.
Let's go.
I can still go.
This is Tongyeong's specialty, Profanity Latte.
[No future for you, b**ch]
[Buttery city hick]
[Tongyeong country hick who acts like a city hick]
[Your mind is tacky]
[A b**ch with a sucky personality]
[You lucky b**ch]
[Boyfriend of that lucky b**ch]
[Something's off, you b**ch]
[City hicks were here]
Hello.
Come here.
Aigoo, my son!
Aigoo. Aigoo. Really.
How come you're so skinny?
Not again!
It must've been a rough ride for all of you.
It's okay.
We prepared food and everything!
Go unpack and come back out.
Okay!
The women's room is on the first floor, and the men's room is on the second floor.
Let's quickly move.
Go in, all of you.
Take your bags.
Aigoo, everyone is so good-looking.
Whose bag is this?
Mother, Father, please take this.
I couldn't prepare much because we came last minute.
Thank you for inviting us.
You shouldn't have prepared this.
You really shouldn't have!
Please take it.
Take it. Her hands will fall off.
Did anyone bring a foam cleanser?
- Me!
- As expected.
Do you have a portable charger?
Of course.
Here.
And type C? 5 pins? 8 pins? I have everything.
I have a dryer,
straightening iron...
We don't pack anything because of people like Joo Ah.
Joo Ah, you know we don't need to bring shampoo to retreats, right?
But you'll need this and this.
There's no time to wash the next day from my experience
and no one wants to wash.
As expected of you.
[Recipe for Gochujang Stew]
Isn't your perfume "From Purple"?
Right.
How did you know?
This is the same perfume that Ha Neul gifted me for our 100-day anniversary.
Oh, really?
I also got it as a gift.
Is this popular?
Isn't the scent really nice?
Yes, it's really good.
- I'll head out first.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Is it good?
- Yeah.
Here comes the meat.
- Great.
- I'll grill now.
No, it's okay. I only eat the meat I grill.
- Sit down.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thanks!
Enjoy your meal!
- So good.
- It's so good.
The stew.
It looks so good.
Is this gochujang stew?
Ha Neul likes gochujang stew the best.
Oh, really?
You're good at cooking, too?
My ideal type is a woman who can cook.
Ha Neul, have a bite. It's your favorite gochujang stew.
It's really good!
- Really?
- Yes.
What a relief.
Gochujang Stew Restaurant that Ha Neul likes.
- It's delicious.
- Right?
- Bon appetite.
- Enjoy.
It's really good.
The app that you made disappeared.
- What happened?
- Well...
I saw a limit to its growth.
I'm preparing a new app.
You never stick to one thing for long.
Make something long-term this time.
Yes, that's what I'm planning.
Oh, and I'm an advisor for an app development competition.
It's pretty large-scale.
If you're going to make a new app, you should participate.
What?
Dad, I'm not interested in any competitio—
Everyone in the field knows about the competition.
Do your best.
Shall I prepare some penalty drinks?
I'm not going to lose.
Unni, you shouldn't drink.
It's okay. I'm good at drinking games.
If you lose, I'll drink for you.
Sure.
Okay then, for the first game,
why don't we start lightly
- with "3, 6, 9"?
- Deal!
But with binary numbers.
What?
Are you showing off that you're from computer science?
Who wants to play with binary numbers?
This is...
Okay, majority rules. We'll play with binary numbers.
- 3, 6, 9. 3, 6, 9.
One.
One, zero.
One... one...
You lose!
♪ Hwang Bo Yeong, drink up! Hwang! Bo! ♪
There's Black Rose, right?
(T/N: When a female drinks in someone's stead)
I'll drink it.
♪ Seo Ji Min drank a shot ♪
♪ Ji, Min ♪
♪ One shot ♪
Ji Min, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine. Honestly, I just wanted a drink.
Ji Min has pretty good tolerance.
M, J.
Problem!
(T/N: Words that have the sounds M and J)
- Holidays.
- Invincibility.
Moon Joon!
Hey. Disqualified. Disqualified.
No names.
Why not? Names work, too.
Names are disqualified!
Come on.
Ch, C!
- Choco!
- Czech.
Chucky.
- Chicken.
- Choke.
We got you!
H, H!
- Leave of Absence.
- Regret.
- Sheer.
- Chemistry.
- Painting.
- Mussels.
- No!
- Drink! Drink!
Drink!
- W, W.
- Milk.
- Cucumber.
- Wine.
- Valid.
- Nutrition.
He's good.
Use the Black Rose.
It's okay.
Use Black Rose next time, okay?
M, N.
- Ma Neul!
- She's it!
- Couple shot!
Couple shot.
♪ We had some drinks, shall we play "Like" game? ♪
I like Ro Sa.
Spit.
I like Ji Min.
I like you, too.
Like! Like!
I like Ha Neul.
I like you, too.
Like! Like!
I like Ji Min.
You couples, stop.
Spit.
I like Min Ho.
I don't like you.
Then who?
I like Joo Ah.
Spit.
♪ Drink! Drink! ♪
♪ The alcohol is going in. Down, down ♪
♪ Look at my shoulder ♪
♪ It's been dislocated ♪
♪ We had some drinks, shall we play "Like" game? ♪
I like Joo Ah.
I don't like you.
Then who?
I like Moon Joon.
I like you, too.
How much?
A lot.
What exactly?
Oppa, you need to respond with detail.
That's right.
Well...
When she smiles like a baby, she's cute.
And...
her laugh is so cheery,
so I end up laughing right next to her, too.
What is this?
Shall we play another game?
♪ Let's go. Let's go ♪
♪ Let's go. Let's go. Let's go ♪
♪ I like Mok Jin ♪
They're having a blast.
Then who?
I like everyone.
♪ Let's go. Let's go ♪
♪ Let's go. Let's go. Let's go ♪
Ro Sa.
We drank quite a lot.
Do you want to go out for some air?
Sure. Let's go.
The air is so refreshing.
It's so nice.
Look at how clear the water is.
It's so clear.
I know, huh?
How are you so good at drinking?
You look totally fine.
I even outlasted all the sunbaes at the orientation.
How amazing.
Ro Sa.
Thank you for accepting my apology.
I'm not sure if it's because I repeated a year,
but it wasn't easy to make any friends in college.
Other people didn't seem to mind me,
but I just avoided them because I didn't want to make them uncomfortable.
And then I joined the Cheer Squad and even on SeoRab...
a lot of gossip formed about me.
It got even harder to make friends.
That's because you're really popular.
It's not.
But after you returned and we went everywhere together,
I feel like we're back in high school.
Me, too.
I was so glad that you were there when I returned.
That's why the day felt so long while we weren't talking to each other.
Okay, okay. Story of your life.
I understand you.
Hey.
Let's stop here. It's embarrassing.
It's chilly at night, right?
Yeah.
The room is pretty close, so I'll go and get some outerwear.
Stay here for a second.
Okay.
Wait.
Could you please get me a hair tie, too?
My hair keeps getting in the way.
Sure.
Then use this for now.
- Just clip it up?
- Yeah.
Should I do it for you?
- Can you?
- Okay.
This is the hairstyle that you do every day.
That's right.
Where were you?
I just went for a walk.
Are you okay?
Yeah, well...
Hyung, you drank quite a lot.
Right. I'm going to stop now.
I'll die if I drink any more.
Hyung, where's Ji Min?
She went out for some air with Ro Sa.
I see.
One meat dumpling.
One galbi dumpling.
Tteokbokki for one person. To go!
What in the world?
Hyung, hide your face.
This dumpling has been steamed well!
How delicate. Delicate dumpling skin!
Get up. Get up.
Let's go.
Why does this tteokbokki look rotten?
It's rotten.
- What's wrong with her?
- She worked for too long at her mom's restaurant.
- Tteokbokki?
- Yeah, yeah. It's over.
- I'm not done...
- Yes, you are. You're done.
- Sit.
- Hey!
That's not water! It's soju.
You couldn't taste the alcohol?
He must be really drunk.
- He can't even taste the alcohol.
- Seriously.
Wait...
You didn't even drink. Why are you cleaning up everything?
Whoever can clean should clean.
This picture style looks so familiar.
From where?
That's right. That confession post.
Confession post? Hold on.
That's it.
Who drew this again?
This was drawn by Joon Hyung earlier.
Two.
Three.
[App development competition]
There's a dumpling here, too.
This dumpling's pretty...
and the tteokbokki is pretty, too.
Dumpling, listen up.
I'm...
in the middle of a one-sided love these days.
But...
are one-sided loves usually like this?
It's like
every day
you're getting a package delivery.
My heart pounds.
And I feel like I'm floating.
And I get excited.
But that package
is so precious and beautiful,
so I can't open it.
I'm afraid that...
the answer I want won't be in the box,
so I'll be disappointed.
What if it's not mine?
That's why I just keep it stacked next to me
and I just watch over it.
Do you know what that feels like?
You don't, right?
Dumpling!
But you look like that.
Moon Joon.
My first love, Moon Joon.
Wait...
Are you really Moon Joon?
You are.
Moon Joon.
Sunbae.
Can I kiss you just once?
Why isn't she picking up?
Magnet.
I looked all over for you.
You put on the perfume I bought you.
It's so nice.
Sunbae.
Can I kiss you just once?
Just once.
♫ The reason why my heart longs for you is all out of my greed ♫
♫ I end up with your photo clutched in my hand ♫
♫ The reason my heart tries to push you away is that it doesn't want to regret it ♫
♫ All the useless thoughts just grow in my mind ♫
♫ There's not one day or even one hour ♫
[Dear.M]
♫ Even the moments when we cried and laughed together ♫
♫ I can't hang onto you, call on you, or see you ♫
~ Preview ~
Joon Oppa is going on a group blind date with another department today.
Was he playing with me?
You should go to Hyung. You know you want to.
Can I?
- I honestly didn't have the time to—
- Are you sure it wasn't because your heart desired it?
You're honestly afraid, aren't you? That I might steal Ha Neul from you?
Whatever you do, Ha Neul won't fall for you.
Aren't you curious, too?
If Ha Neul likes you as much as you think he does.
I don't think we're going to work out.
♫ Turn around and take a look at me ♫