ALL NAMES, GROUPS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND EVENTS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
When AlphaGo was first introduced,
speculations arose
that AI might replace some jobs.
The age of AI judges may be drawing near.
The Supreme Court is considering
the introduction of AI judges
to civil cases such as damages…
Here is your beef bone soup.
-Here.
-Thank you.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
-How many?
-Three people.
-Are there any tables left?
-Take your pick over there.
There are so many people here.
Let's sit over there.
Excuse me.
Aren't all news broadcasts live?
Yes.
But that man…
You don't know about the AI news anchor?
The anchor's face and voice
are replicated using a computer.
Replicated?
Oh, my. What a strange world
we're living in.
-Jeez. Enjoy your food.
-Thank you.
Goodness, what should I eat?
What?
Are you eating alone?
I came to update the software today.
I see.
Thanks to you,
I get to eat at noon during the news.
You could end up on the streets.
Sorry?
If you can't prove
that you're better than the AI,
it could happen.
You're full of confidence.
If you're that confident,
why don't you make an appearance
on Nine O'Clock News
and explain Silver Lining's blueprint?
-Why should I?
-It's a special invite.
I have that much power.
Do you know how many followers
Silver Lining has on social media?
The account's influence
is greater than your program.
So why should I?
You chose to respond
to my goodwill with rudeness.
You must enjoy making a lot of enemies.
I enjoy stating the facts.
So…
not only was Mr. Kim Seon-ju attacked,
but his soul is also trapped
inside a phone?
And you picked up that phone.
How are you seeing and talking right now?
The camera is my eyes,
and the speaker is my mouth.
Is that so?
Technology these days is so great.
Then explain this.
Can you see this?
Someone as famous as you were attacked.
But there isn't a single article about it.
If they were able to attack me,
they would also be able to cover it up.
Gosh. You seem like a trickster.
If you think it's fake, bail out.
You're not the only one
who needs a billion won.
Is the 100 million won real money?
You can check for yourself.
Jeez. Do you think I won't be able to?
It's so easy to spend money.
Okay. I'm going to hop on
the wireless earbuds trend.
SALE PRICE: 350,000 WON
BUY NOW
It better not be fake money.
ORDER COMPLETE
What? It went through?
TRANSACTION APPROVED
Goodness.
What do I do now?
It's hot.
It's so hot.
This…
How is this happening to me?
Don't tell me…
Could this be…
The Truman Show?
THE PARK IN-SEONG SHOW
A person trapped inside a phone?
He believed that?
Is he stupid or what?
-Wouldn't you fall for a billion won too?
-I would.
This is hilarious.
Goodness.
-Mr. Park. Congratulations.
-Hyeon-ho.
This is strange.
Don't you think it's weird
that I became a CEO?
What do you mean?
Who says you can't become
the CEO of Silver Lining,
a subsidiary of Bumyoung, the largest
Korean company by market capitalization?
What the…
What is with this bib?
What's with your hair? Are you Superman?
A congratulatory gift.
MIRACULOUS LIGHT! LED
This LED mask meets the safety regulations
of the Korean government.
The light from 220 LED chips
will penetrate the skin
and make it supple and clear.
What are you doing?
Hyeon-ho, what are you doing?
Hyeon-ho.
Darn it!
Stay cool and just think about the facts.
Park In-seong.
Think rationally.
This is a dream.
This is reality.
A dream.
Reality.
In-seong, come and eat.
All right.
I've just been cast for the role of a CEO.
Park In-seong.
Show off your acting skills!
I think I've given you enough time.
I made up my mind.
To sign the contract,
register your fingerprint on the screen.
I will send the signed contract
to your email.
In-seong, let's eat.
There's one last thing I'd like to ask.
This will be your last question.
Because from now on,
you just have to do what I tell you to do.
I thought long and hard about this,
but I still don't understand.
If you're really Kim Seon-ju…
What I'm saying is,
if you're really the CEO of Silver Lining,
why did you choose…
Why did you choose me of all people?
I never wanted our relationship
-To last this short
-There he goes again.
I thought our son was here to lend a hand.
It's my fault for getting my hopes up.
That's not it.
I was practicing for the talent show.
What?
I got a job…
at Silver Lining.
What?
-Silver… What's that?
-Silver…
I've never heard of that company.
Are you sure it's a company?
Silver Lining is an IT corporation
and a pioneer of future technology.
For four consecutive years, job seekers
rated it as the most attractive company.
Even if you're a yokel,
you should take note
of this global enterprise.
"Yokel"?
Your phone sounds like it's agitated.
Then…
did you get a job at a conglomerate?
In-seong.
You worked so hard. Thank you.
Thank you, In-seong. I feel so proud.
Thank you.
I DIDN'T FIND ANYTHING.
PULL OUT.
I heard magpies crying at dawn.
Something good must be
waiting for you in Seoul.
Indeed.
He'll wear his phone out
at the rate he's fondling it.
I'm so proud of you.
All right.
PARK IN-SEONG
AMOUNT SENT: 50 MILLION WON
What? Fifty million?
I was just sending you money.
Where did you get this money?
I decided to end my lease.
She returned it this quickly?
Your landlady is as quick as lightning.
Where are you going to stay?
My company is providing housing.
It is a conglomerate after all.
I'm not sure if we can take it.
I'm sorry I haven't been a good son.
Use the money to cover
any urgent stuff first.
And build a huge greenhouse
for your Shine Muscats as well.
Jeez.
What is he saying?
Will he be okay? Should I follow him?
Leave him be. He's going
to the village head to brag.
Goodness.
I'm so proud of you.
Right. You can do practically
everything with a phone.
What is to stop a person
from being trapped in one?
Are you sleeping?
I never take naps.
I don't live my life half-heartedly.
Anyway…
Even if
you sent out an email,
will the employees believe I'm their boss?
They won't believe you.
But if it's my orders,
they will follow them.
I have the authority and their trust.
You don't need to do anything.
I'll make you the CEO.
We need to make a stop before that.
How can a pair of pants cost 530,000 won?
Sir, that is the price of the belt.
The jacket and pants
will cost 5.3 million won.
Pardon?
Where are you going?
It's too expensive.
-I'll just find something--
-Buy it.
Sorry?
Pay with this.
It looks good on you.
You look amazing.
Very nice.
Buy that too.
Get oversized sunglasses
because they're more stylish.
Mr. Park.
Mr. Park, you can stop now.
Stop.
No social media.
Check the contract.
NO SOCIAL MEDIA
What's over here?
This is so nice.
But do the bubbles always
disappear this quickly?
It's different from the movies.
Gosh, I should've brought
an exfoliating towel.
"I WISH I COULD UNSEE THAT"
Gosh, this is great.
I'll pay with this.
Room service orders
are paid upon checkout.
Oh, right.
I remember.
That's how it worked in Las Vegas too.
I had all this delicious food by myself.
Are you not hungry?
Will you feel full if I charge you?
-Where is the--
-I have never felt hungry inside here.
I see. Then…
What about sleep? Can you sleep?
I don't have time for sleep.
There's a lot of work to do.
What?
I need to find out
what happened in the mountains that day.
But I can't remember anything
that happened a week before the accident.
Is it memory loss
associated with
post-traumatic stress disorder?
That is why I had Baro check my schedule.
That day, I had a golf meeting
with the Bumyoung family,
and I was on my way
to a campsite to see my daughter.
I'm sorry I'm late, my little princess.
The GPS data of my phone
matches my schedule.
Then how did you--
This is where it starts getting strange.
It's a mountain route.
In order to end up on the spot
where you picked up the phone,
I should've hiked up from this point.
It's not even a hiking trail.
What happened to your car?
I've been searching for the same model
and color, but I found none.
They probably scrapped it.
I am looking for more clues,
but I can't do much inside a phone.
So this is what I need to help you with.
Was I even at the golf course that day?
Why did I suddenly get out of my car?
And why did I have to go up the mountain?
I need to find out the truth
to know how I ended up like this.
That is how
I'll return to my position
as a CEO and dad.
All right.
Everything's okay.
Is this your head?
Mr. Sim.
What happened to Mr. Kim?
You still can't reach him?
Haven't you known him since he was a baby?
-Is there no one you can contact?
-He has a lot of irons in the fire.
He could be on an overseas business trip.
Or…
he could be on a vacation.
He's not the type
to go on a spontaneous trip.
We never get to rest because of that.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
Why are you leaving the phone here?
Doesn't everyone leave their phone
next to them when they go to bed?
So you're saying two men
should lie on the same bed?
Why would you say it like that?
Gosh.
Should I turn the phone off
so you can rest?
Just leave it on.
I don't know what'll happen to me
once you turn the device off.
Before I go to work,
I want a definitive answer.
Why me?
You said Silver Lining
rejected you, right?
That proves that you have no connections
within my company.
I had no connections…
but now I do.
And it's the CEO.
Get some rest.
Things won't be easy starting tomorrow.
Hold on.
-Yes?
-Take off the case.
If you have my phone,
people will suspect you.
There are some things you need
to know before your first day.
Hello.
Executive Director Oh Mi-ran of Bumyoung.
Her father, Chairman Oh Bum-geun,
the founder of the group,
suddenly fainted last year,
making her the de-facto chairwoman.
The international development
of the self-driving car…
She's the largest shareholder
of Bumyoung Motor Group
and plans to use its success
with self-driving cars as the foothold
to beat her uncle
and become the chairwoman officially.
That is our goal. Thank you.
Then she needs all the help
she can get from Silver Lining
for the critical technologies.
Mr. Oh is not going to
just stand by and watch.
He even lived behind bars
in his brother's place.
His determination knows no bounds
and neither does his loyalty to Bumyoung.
He won't be satisfied
with his position as Vice Chairman.
So a shrimp got caught
in a fight between whales.
SIGNING CEREMONY
Silver Lining is not a shrimp.
It's a kingmaker
that can get on top of either whale.
Mr. Kwak will be waiting for you.
He is a typical bully
who turns weak in front of the strong.
He's one of Mr. Oh's people,
a recruit from Bumyoung Electronics,
and a plant to keep me in check.
Today is the first day
of our newly appointed CEO.
Let us greet him respectfully
and sincerely. All right?
-Yes, sir!
-Okay. Stay calm.
Button your suits.
Is it always like this?
They never did it for me.
With a new boss,
they chose the old-fashioned way.
-Mr. Park. Hello.
-Hello.
Just act casual.
What are you doing? Hurry!
That's right. Don't get intimidated.
I was in the 27th class,
the best of Evergreen Theater.
There's no role I haven't played.
I did my best in every role.
This is my stage
and from this point on, I am the CEO.
Three, two, one.
What are you doing right now?
Aren't you supposed to be working?
I detest formalities such as this.
Don't ever do this again.
I see.
Yes, sir.
Get back to work.
Did you have a pleasant drive
on your way here?
The Pyeongyang cold noodles guy?
Hello, I am Jung Se-yeon,
your personal assistant.
-What?
-I only have good things ahead--
You're the shirt lady.
Right this way, sir.
Okay.
Do you know Ms. Jung?
I bumped into her once.
-The other day--
-There's no need to explain
how a job seeker became a CEO
overnight.
-This way, sir.
-Okay.
CEO PARK IN-SEONG
I did the best I could
in a short amount of time.
Is there anything else you need?
This is enough.
It is interesting
seeing you again like this.
Indeed.
It turns out I wasn't the interviewer.
You were there to interview me.
No wonder I got the inkling
that you were an extraordinary applicant.
Did you?
It is amazing how you made
a thorough inspection in advance.
I apologize if I was too insolent.
Mr. Kim's email explained
the circumstances to me.
Yes, I see.
Do you mind if I ask
what your relationship is with Mr. Kim?
Neither your age, educational background,
hometown, nor face…
seem to overlap with those of Mr. Kim.
We're close. I'll just leave it at that.
If you don't mind my asking,
what do you mean by "close"?
Well…
Everything's okay.
I touch, and…
Sorry?
We're…
touchy-feely, very open, and honest about
giving each other pointers and such.
Got it?
But the thing is,
I don't have experience as a CEO.
Goodness. No one is born a CEO.
You learn as you go.
Even so, I just don't have
any experience whatsoever.
So you should be given the chance
to display your abilities
and prove your real worth.
You're very different
from when I first met you.
You see, I may not have much hair up here,
but I promise
I won't ever get in your hair.
What are you going to do
about your personal assistant?
-Sorry?
-Ms. Jung.
When CEOs move around,
they bring in their personal assistants
as a general rule.
What should I do about the assistant?
Ms. Jung has worked for me
for a long time.
She knows how to keep a secret
and hide her feelings.
Then she can stay.
If you think about it differently,
she's hard to read.
And because she knows me well,
she is likely to find out about us.
Then I'll find someone else.
She knows my official
and personal schedules
like the back of her hand.
She probably accompanied me
on my last golf meeting.
Se-yeon might be able
to lead us to some clues.
Ms. Jung can be your most reliable friend…
as well as your worst enemy.
What should I do now?
Go to my office
and connect my phone to the computer.
Why do you want me--
Darn it.
Lady!
-I'm sorry.
-Are you insane?
I told you not to leave your supplies
in front of the bathroom.
-Look.
-I was mopping the floor.
Someone tripped.
-I'm sorry.
-How many times do I have to tell you?
Do you want to get fired?
-I'm sorry.
-Excuse me, it's my fault.
I was staring at my phone.
-Clean up the mess.
-Just leave.
Clean it up!
I wasn't going to say this,
but that's why
you're cleaning bathrooms at your age.
I wasn't going to say this,
but that’s why you’re still
working part-time at your age!
This is my stage.
And I'm the boss.
Don't do anything that attracts attention.
-Clean it up!
-Are you the only one who works here?
You're pissing me off.
Do you want to get fired?
Who are you?
I wasn't going to say this,
but that's why you're on a power trip
at your age.
How does that
make you feel?
How dare you?
Do you know who you're talking to?
Hey!
I'm a team leader in the sales department.
Which department are you in?
CEO PARK IN-SEONG
He is the newly appointed CEO,
Mr. Park In-seong.
Shall we, sir?
Thank you.
What you did just now
is a breach of contract.
Three strikes and you're out.
You currently have one.
I'm sorry.
I've always wanted to
go on a power trip.
It's already so hectic.
Right. You want me to
connect your phone to the computer?
Yes.
I need to check if anyone attempted
to hack Baro Version 4.0.
It's a beta version.
Is it still being developed?
It needs to go through more tests.
There's Son Heung-min.
He's the model for Silver Lining.
Your voice can also be reproduced
after an hour-long recording session.
It's like listening
to the late Kim Kwang-seok
singing the songs of today.
I just took the technology a step further.
Baro, what should I wear today?
The temperature outside is 18 degrees.
I recommend wearing a dress
that suits the spring breeze.
A dress.
Baro, what should I wear today?
The temperature outside is 18 degrees.
I recommend wearing a dress
that suits the spring breeze.
Darn it, you fool.
The current design has AI assistants
respond uniformly to a given question.
However, Silver Lining is developing
a personalized AI assistant
that uses deep learning
to tailor to each individual.
Our AI assistant won't be a humdrum one
glorified by words such as versatility.
It will be an AI assistant
that thinks, decides, and talks
like Son Heung-min, your mom, or me.
That is what Version 4.0 will become.
Is that why you became a model as well?
No more questions.
-But I'm the CEO. I should at least know--
-The reason why I can trust you
is because you know nothing.
The more you know,
the more difficult it'll be
for me to trust you.
This is Kim Seon-ju,
the CEO of Silver Lining.
OH BUM-GEUN
Due to personal health reasons,
I would like to take some time to rest.
I am sending this email to request
approval for my replacement.
-You can't do this, sir.
-Move!
Please step away.
-Get out of my way!
-Please step away.
Move!
Mr. Oh, sir!
-Sir, please.
-Move out of the way!
What game are you playing?
Compose yourself, Mr. Oh.
This is the office of the chairman
of Bumyoung Group.
That's right. Such principles were kept
when my brother held office.
But a sabbatical
at an important time like this?
Perhaps something unavoidable
happened to him
at an important time like this.
On top of that,
the new CEO is wet behind the ears.
The board of directors
will not tolerate this.
I, the largest shareholder
of Bumyoung, allowed it.
Who isn't going to tolerate what?
Let's see how he fares.
If he's gold, he'll shine.
If he's iron, he'll rust.
Bumyoung…
Electronics…
has Young-geun.
And…
Bumyoung Motor Group…
has Mi-ran.
So the bigger the spike
in Silver Lining's share price,
the greater the decrease
in value for Bumyoung Electronics?
You're picking things up quicker
than I thought.
By nature, Silver Lining and Mr. Oh
can never be on good terms.
Who is it?
This is a list of assistants
picked out by Mr. Kwak.
All four of them can start working
as soon as tomorrow.
There must be a misunderstanding.
I have yet to request…
CEO PARK IN-SEONG
Are you acting out again?
Mr. Park, I warned you.
Our deal was to make me CEO,
not for you to control my every move.
Mr. Park.
Mr. Park In-seong.
What a good hair day.
Let me do this side too.
Goodness. What brings you
to such a lowly place?
You should've just called for me.
This.
Did you already finish
looking over the candidates?
Would you like to see your replacements
for yourself?
Pardon?
Why did you hand the list
of candidates to Ms. Jung?
Because it's her job.
Was it necessary
to make her deliver the list herself?
That's how we've been doing--
Then make the necessary changes
starting now.
At least for the duration of my tenure,
I'm not going to allow anyone,
regardless of their position,
to be stabbed in the back
or under their nose.
JUNIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR KWAK SAM-SU
Someone is causing a scene.
-What are you doing?
-Let me go.
Let go!
Jeez. What's wrong with you?
Hey.
I told you I know her.
I told you not to come to my workplace.
And I told you I only trust money.
Are we good now?
Where's this money from?
Why does it matter? I paid you.
You won't take it if it's dirty?
Write me a receipt.
For payment in full.
Give me a receipt before you go.
What are you saying?
You have 50 million left.
Do you think I'm running a charity?
You need to pay interest.
You should've paid it sooner,
don't you think?
See you again.
Se-yeon is a good person,
so I'm going to work with her.
You only saw her
for 6 hours and 48 minutes.
How do you know for sure?
I think Se-yeon
will become a reliable friend.
Why?
Do you have anything to back it up?
My shirt.
What?
This is a woman's size.
Gosh.
My stocks won't rise,
but you're making my hackles rise.
It's always the quiet ones.
It's not what you think it is.
What am I thinking? Tell me.
Is she pretty?
She has a kind heart.
She offered to help
even when she didn't need to.
Is it the lady who gave you her shirt?
-Yes.
-I see.
She's a good person.
"A good person."
Why is your face turning red?
Listen here.
We should get one of her friends
to join us on a double date.
I can act as a social lubricant.
You don't have to do anything.
I bet she's pretty.
Your shirt?
Cut it out and show me the exact numbers
or convince me with irrefutable logic.
This is a matter of life and death to me.
Is it even possible
to describe a person with numbers?
Humans are not AI machines.
You're wrong.
The reliability of anyone
that Mr. Kwak recommends is zero.
On the other hand,
Ms. Jung is fifty-fifty.
Ms. Jung is the better option.
This is how you should convince me.
So you agree with me.
Nevertheless, you stormed into
Mr. Kwak's office.
You have one strike left.
He is a novice.
He's a greenhorn
who can't control his emotions.
You may rest assured.
Yes, sir.
Well, of course.
Where did he find such a lowly punk?
I'll have the board discuss his dismissal.
What's the point of removing a cub?
Pardon?
Just wait.
Let's wait for him to mess up on his own.
That way we can get rid of Silver Lining
and my niece all at once.
Yes, sir.
Right. How is that going, by the way?
I'm looking into it.
All right. Keep looking into it.
I can't believe
I get to live in a place like this.
I didn't expect
to live inside my phone either.
Figures.
You should be living
in a 67-pyeong house in Pyeongchang-dong.
But you're living
in a 6.7-inch display instead.
-What?
-What is it? Is something wrong?
It's already 6 p.m.
If I'm the boss, that means
I can leave work on the dot, right?
You don't seem that self-conscious anyway.
I just got goosebumps.
I hear that often.
We must have gotten pretty close.
Ms. Jung, aren't you clocking out?
It's already 5 minutes past 6 p.m.
Here's the handover document.
Throw it away.
Ms. Jung.
See you tomorrow.
Is this it?
That two-storied house is mine.
-With the billion won, I should--
-You can't.
Sorry?
That would only cover the master bedroom.
I'll forever be stuck in a studio.
Is she even coming though?
Min-a loves buying chocolate snacks
from the grocery store.
This is around the time
she usually gets back home.
I guess she knows.
What?
Spending brings happiness.
Your kid is capitalistic.
She's coming.
Right. She doesn't know who I am.
Is that her?
She's so cute.
Are you okay?
You waited so long
just to see her for a minute.
Let's leave now.
What?
He's coming back out.
Is he going home?
No. They're both live-in employees.
I see.
He's a rough driver.
Tail him.
-What?
-Chase after him!
Why? We came all the way over here--
Chase after him!
Jeez.
I'm still technically alive,
which means things didn't go
exactly as they had planned.
They will likely try to
get a grasp on my situation.
That would make Mr. Sim
their number one target.
I HAVE ARRIVED
Or…
he may already be on their side.
Check who he is meeting.
Welcome.
Who is it?
What?
Why is Se-yeon there?
Take a look at this.
Head straight to my house.
-Sorry?
-Now!
Hurry!
Bring out a document envelope
from my study.
I'll unlock the door.
You can go in now.
Ms. Jung should be
in her room cross-stitching
after putting Min-a to bed.
You should have about an hour.
What do I do now?
I don't think I can go in
through the main entrance.
Head to the right.
Now to the left.
No, not yet.
Turn left here.
Your house is huge.
Go in through the pool entrance.
Don't worry about the security cameras.
I'll handle it.
You said you'd make me a CEO,
not a thief.
Did you think it'd be easy
to earn a billion won?
Take off your shoes.
I can't erase your shoeprints for you.
The study is located
at the very end of the second floor.
Gosh, there's a person.
It's a suit of armor.
There's nothing inside.
There's no time. Hurry.
Ms. Jung went downstairs.
There's a car.
It's expensive. Be careful.
So where's the document envelope?
Up the stairs, in the safe by the desk.
Go up those stairs.
It's too dark to see.
Why don't we come back
when there's no one home?
You saw what was happening.
They're starting to move.
We have to hurry.
This isn't a study.
It's bigger than my house.
There's a safe next to the desk.
There's a passcode.
It's 0630.
There's nothing here.
Are you sure?
There's no document envelope?
There's nothing.
Let me see.
There's no way.
Are you sure you left it here?
You could've been mistaken.
No, I always left it there.
What's inside the envelope anyway?
I need to know what I'm looking for.
Hold on. The hallway lights came on.
Stay calm and hide yourself.
What now?
Don't panic.
Just to be safe, why don't we--
Ms. Jung is headed in this direction.
Hurry!
What now, Mr. Kim?
If she--
-My goodness!
-What's the matter?
I heard a sound coming from this room.
That's absurd.
Mr. Kim isn't even here.
UNKNOWN
Did you hear that?
I did. It sounds like a phone.
Oh, my. It was my phone.
It's Mr. Kim.
What?
What did he say?
He's giving me a raise.
Goodness. It was my phone.
That was close.
You really are from Silicon Valley.
How did you think of sending her a text?
You can count on me from now on.
You're amazing.
UNKNOWN
What?
"Unknown"?
WHY WON'T YOU PICK UP?
I'M THE OWNER OF THAT PHONE
What is this person saying?
This is Kim Seon-ju's phone.
GIVE ME BACK MY PHONE!
Kim Seon-ju.
Who are you?
Are you really Kim Seon-ju?
Do you know what's really unfair?
Daring to take that seat.
You want me to live in your house?
Se-yeon is probably confused too.
Looking back,
I went through endless days of pain.
You can get in touch with Mr. Kim?
The CEO of Silver Lining
put his money where his mouth is.
Watch out!
There's no road!