ALL NAMES, GROUPS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND EVENTS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
1 YEAR AGO
You didn't go to bed yet?
Mr. Kim will be home late.
Let's go upstairs and sleep.
Dad might come in late,
but he always makes time for my birthday.
All right then.
Min-a!
It's not midnight yet, right?
You almost didn't make it.
Goodness. I tried to come early,
but a software bug suddenly showed up.
I know you have to update
Baro Version 4.0 every Monday.
There we go.
Are you forgiving me, Min-a?
There's no time, so let's skip the song
and blow out the candles.
Okay.
-What was your wish?
-It's a secret.
You're not even going to tell me?
I wished you'd come home early
for my birthday next year.
Here.
This is the doll you wanted.
Give me Mom's gift first.
That's what I thought. Mom's gift.
Here.
Here you go.
HAPPY SIXTH BIRTHDAY
ON YOUR FIRST DAY OF ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
HAVE FUN ON YOUR FIELD TRIP
WHEN YOU GET A JOB
YOUR 13TH BIRTHDAY
HAPPY SIXTH BIRTHDAY
In-seong.
If Min-a's mom were alive,
Min-a would've had more happy memories.
BASED ON WEBTOON UNLOCK THE BOSS
(UNLOCK MY BOSS) BY PARK SEONG-HYUN
Don't feel small.
It's really not like you.
We can just
catch the culprit.
And then you'll be able to
create more memories for Min-a.
Will catching the culprit
bring me back to Min-a?
Dad?
What?
It's you, right?
Dad, where are you?
Why aren't you here? It's my birthday.
Min-a.
When you go on a business trip,
you usually tell me
when you'll be back.
But this time, you told me nothing
and have not come back.
Do you know how scared I was?
I'm sorry.
I was going to call you, but…
I thought you abandoned me
because I kept nagging you to read for me.
-That's not it.
-I thought you left me.
I would never leave you alone, Min-a.
You promised.
Yes, I promise.
Don't hang up.
Dad!
Don't cry, Min-a.
-Min-a.
-Dad…
-Min-a, don't cry.
-Don't cry. It's okay.
-Dad…
It's okay.
Dad…
I just found…
another reason
why we must catch the culprit.
Thank you for your time.
Even though I sent you an email,
I didn't expect you to agree
to do an interview for a school newspaper.
Gosh, college students chose me
as the most respected entrepreneur.
This is the least I can do.
What do you think made you
number one for three consecutive years?
To be honest,
whenever I see such articles,
I can't help but feel sorry.
You all have to
hit a three-base hit yourselves,
while I was born on the third base.
So in order to feel less ashamed,
I ran for all I was worth to home plate.
I heard you were
put in charge of a subsidiary
as soon as you graduated college.
That's right.
Back then,
I had a lot of courage like you guys.
After I returned to Korea,
I told my father
that I wanted to lead the company.
And what did he say?
He handed me a business card.
A business card?
Yes.
My first ever business card.
CEO OH MI-RAN
Manage the baseball team.
Next up is an update on Bumyoung Group.
Bumyoung has decided
how they will be using
the third Chungbuk redevelopment site
which is 280,000 pyeong.
Figuring out the purpose of
the redevelopment site was a long process.
Mr. Nam's corporate card
transaction records aren't of much help.
What about his social media?
I'm looking through
the employees' accounts,
but there are so many.
Plus, if his account is private,
we're at a dead end.
Looking at the security camera footage,
he was usually alone
whether it be in the lounge or cafeteria.
By the way,
Silver Lining has a lot of clubs.
It's in my management philosophy.
Every employee is part of a club.
I even take care of their welfare.
Isn't it a bit strange?
What is?
A voluntary loner
is part of the alpine club?
It's just for form's sake.
It doesn't mean anything.
Is that so?
Then did you also
join a club?
Sorry?
Yes.
Which club?
Start-up? English?
Or…
a movie club?
Comedy.
That is…
The comedy club provided the most funds.
Then do you have any skills
you can show off?
No.
-Show me.
-I don't have any.
Show us. Mr. Kim.
-Show us!
"All right. Bamboo helicopter."
It was just…
to put my name in the records.
Yes. That's what I was thinking.
Hold on.
Mr. Nam didn't join the club
as a formality.
What?
SILVER LINING ALPINE CLUB, TURTLE SHIP
This is the sole footprint
that the ghost left.
Who is the president of the club?
It's time for you to leave, sir.
Yes, just a minute.
We should hurry
if we want to make it in time.
There he is.
I've never seen him before.
Right.
I forgot to introduce you two.
I hired him as my bodyguard and driver.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
If you had let me know, I would've hired
a more suitable person!
Hey, you bastard. Are you in a rush?
Do you want to die that much?
Where did Ms. Jung go?
I sent her on an errand.
-Hold on tight.
-Okay.
Yes, I know Mr. Nam
from the sales department.
He came out every once in a while.
SILVER LINING ALPINE CLUB, TURTLE SHIP
Did he ever talk to anyone or--
Never.
He always kept silent
and never joined our get-togethers.
I thought, "He must love the mountains."
I see.
Why do you ask?
Did something happen to Mr. Nam?
I heard he doesn't come to work either.
That's not true.
The sun is so bright here.
I guess Korea is a large country.
You look pleased.
I know, right?
It was always so depressing
getting older each year.
For the first time, I'm desperate
for the next year to come.
Are you talking about
the end-of-year shareholder meeting?
Congratulations in advance.
Please.
Today, I proclaim
that the largest domed stadium
in Korea will be built here.
I am not seeking profit.
I am seeking to provide a better life
for Korea, just like Bumyoung's values.
These are the teachings left by my father.
I mean…
An enterprise should make money.
Does a domed stadium make sense?
Let her be.
This will be the mistake
that will lead to her fall.
Today, I would like to reveal
another one of my father's teachings.
Mr. Park.
Please step up for a moment.
The level four self-driving car
that Bumyoung Motor Group
and Silver Lining collaborated on
will be launched
on National Foundation Day, October 3rd.
I couldn't tell you in advance
due to security reasons.
My apologies.
It's not ready--
Just have it launched by October 3rd.
I'll take care of the rest.
This time it was a two-month gap.
And sometimes he appeared
after three months.
Just looking at this,
it's hard to tell
why Mr. Nam joined the alpine club.
No.
There's something about those dates.
It looks like Ms. Oh is trying to
launch the self-driving car
before the shareholder meeting,
so she can have the upper--
Do you think I don't know that?
I'm sorry, sir.
They can prepare Baro Version 4.0
even without the presence of Kim Seon-ju?
I don't think so.
SILVER LINING ALPINE CLUB DIRECTORY
So what is it?
He was only present during the weeks
when the beta test results
of Baro Version 4.0 were released.
Feigning hiking,
he delivered the results to someone?
It's just a hypothesis,
but the club must have been
a cover story for them.
Mountains don't have cameras after all.
Who could he have been meeting?
Thank you for coming.
Whether it was someone
longing for Baro Version 4.0
or someone who wanted to
stop Baro Version 4.0,
everyone would've coveted the data.
Thank you for setting up
the shareholder meeting.
It looks like I'll become the chairwoman.
Mr. Kim.
Look at this.
Did you find something?
Whenever Mr. Nam was present,
Mr. Kwak was always there too.
Mr. Kwak.
Do you want cold noodles?
I just realized I didn't ask
what you wanted to eat.
It's all right.
I like Pyeongyang cold noodles too.
Doesn't it taste too bland?
Do you want some vinegar?
No, I'm okay.
-Come on.
-It's okay.
I should've had a meal with you sooner.
I was being dense
when you work day and night
to pick great people of talent.
That is my job.
So…
do you know where Mr. Nam is right now?
Who?
Mr. Nam from the sales department.
He's been absent without notice
for the past few days.
Is this all you have?
You need to earn your keep!
It's not like Silver Lining
is a small business.
I have no way of knowing
where every employee is.
No, you must have a way of knowing it.
You were in the alpine club together.
Didn't I tell you
that I live apart from my family?
I only attended a few times
whenever I got lonely during the weekends.
But you see,
is it a coincidence
that Mr. Nam was only present
whenever you were?
I'm not sure.
I don't even remember
the times that I showed up.
Try to remember.
I did hear something from Mr. Nam.
I don't know who told you what,
but it is a bit unpleasant
to see you accusing me
without any evidence.
All right. Enjoy your food.
Min-ju,
are you out on a date with your mom?
Yes, we're shopping. It's Dad.
I told you to cook your meals
even if it's troublesome.
I usually do. Today was an exception.
Why are you calling at this hour?
What do you mean?
I just called because I missed you.
Dad, can I buy tickets to the BTS concert?
They're coming to New York,
but the tickets are a bit pricey.
Of course you can. Don't you worry.
I'm a board member of Bumyoung.
You can do everything you want
and see everything you--
Dad, I'm sorry.
I'm getting a call from my friend.
-I'll call you again.
-Min-ju…
My goodness.
Gosh, I'm always put on the back burner.
When will they move back to Korea?
Mr. Kwak acted like
he didn't know anything about it.
We need something irrefutable.
Are you guys detectives?
Why are you trying to look for evidence?
We can just hang him.
I'll get him to confess.
That's your way of doing things.
How do you call yourself human?
What did you say?
If we make a rash move,
we'll just end up in jail.
Watch out!
Gosh, I've been so out of it.
There's something I forgot.
We're a team now,
so we should have a team dinner.
Here.
-The food will be out soon.
-Okay. Thank you.
Cheers.
If you're a bodyguard,
you should abstain from drinking.
Shouldn't you know that?
Come on.
-We're not working right now, so--
-We're not?
Then I guess I can leave.
-Se-yeon.
-That was nice.
Se-yeon.
You're lucky you're so kind-hearted.
You easily forgive and make peace.
I'm sorry, but I'm not like you.
Hey.
Mr. Kim, I can't do this anymore.
You should've prepared yourself
when you decided to hire a man like him.
You know, the most difficult aspect
of life is people.
You're right.
But the person who can resolve
such a difficult matter is not me.
It's you.
That is true.
Could I…
take these to-go?
They'll get soggy.
Right? I thought so.
This is quite the feast.
Thank you.
All of a sudden?
What do you mean?
You were a lot of help that day.
But why did you order so much?
It looks enough for three people.
No. It's just…
I wanted you to eat a lot.
In-seong, you have gotten generous
after becoming a CEO.
Right. What happened
to that industrial spy?
What?
We're still searching.
It must be a pain in the neck.
That's not the only thing.
Being a CEO
doesn't give you peace of mind.
The real CEO keeps pushing me
while my employees keep arguing.
Hey.
I mean…
Why would you work hard to earn money?
Bumyoung Motor Group's stocks are rising.
Just quit everything and invest in stocks.
Should I?
Yes, just call it quits.
All right. I'm going to quit this darn…
What?
Hyeon-ho…
What's wrong?
What is it?
What's the matter?
What is this?
What in the world is this?
I think it's my salary.
The salary of a CEO is on another level.
Right?
We used to get paid with virtual currency.
You can get paid with crypto?
No.
I'm saying the money disappeared
from our accounts almost instantly.
You're right.
It would disappear in a flash,
which was a shocker.
Darn it. Why won't it come in?
It's today, right?
We waited for a month.
Just wait patiently.
It's because I'm so excited.
Hey, what are you going to do
with your first paycheck?
-Me?
-Yes.
PREMIUM KOREAN BEEF
I should buy my parents a beef set.
What do you think?
That sounds like a good idea.
-Right?
-Yes.
Yes, we can also be good sons.
Yes, we can!
It's finally here.
We're rich.
We're rich now!
Hello. This is premium Korean beef.
Can I have the 140,000 won set?
No. I'll get the 150,000 won set.
-This?
-Yes, give us two, please.
Okay.
Thank you.
MONTHLY RENT: 600,000 WON
STUDENT LOAN: 450,000 WON
PHONE BILL: 40,000 WON
TRANSPORTATION CARD: 72,000 WON
UTILITIES: 25,000 WON
INSURANCE: 45,000 WON
INSTALLMENT SAVINGS: 100,000 WON
BALANCE: 50,000 WON
BALANCE: 49,510 WON
PREMIUM KOREAN BEEF GIFT SET
-We forgot our wallets.
-We did.
Sorry.
Are you crying?
No.
At least you took home a tuna set.
I bought a toothpaste set.
But…
my parents were still so happy,
which made me feel worse.
Tell me about it.
Parenthood isn't worth it.
That does it.
It's the department store next time.
All right.
After 29 years,
I'm going to be a decent son for once!
Let's do it!
-My bus is here.
-Right.
-Bye.
WITHDRAWAL
BUMYOUNG HOSPITAL: 1,320,000 WON
NURSING FEE: 2,800,000 WON
Hey.
About my monthly pay…
I deposited it. You can check.
I already did.
I was just wondering
if you could increase the amount.
You are getting off.
Hold on. I need to get off.
Coming through. Sorry.
-I'll get going then.
-Okay.
BALANCE: 232,350 WON
What…
I'm sorry.
I want to apologize
for doing everything my own way.
After you left,
I repented.
I also have someone…
that I don't want to
reconcile with or forgive.
You do?
Yes.
It was rude
and hypocritical of me.
Even your apologies
are like you.
Your mother…
has such pretty hands.
Her hands were at work her whole life.
She only stopped working
after being hospitalized.
I wanted to become a hotelier.
I got an offer!
I did it!
MOM
My goodness.
Mom, I got an…
OPERATION IN PROGRESS
She collapsed due to hemiplegia
caused by an acute stroke.
And in the process,
she suffered severe head trauma.
She is alive,
but she is minimally conscious.
You should prepare yourself
for a long journey.
RECRUITMENTS
HIGHEST-PAYING
ANNUAL SALARY:
40 MILLION TO 70 MILLION WON
PERSONAL ASSISTANT TO SILVER LINING CEO
I wanted to have her enjoy a luxury hotel,
sleeping in a bed with a magnificent view.
But in reality,
she is stuck in a hospital bed.
Se-yeon.
I wanted to give you an answer.
When we were camping,
you asked me what my dream was.
Though it was for a short moment,
your question brought back memories
and made my heart flutter.
The situation isn't great.
At the news
of the self-driving car's release date,
Bumyoung Motor Group's stocks
are rapidly rising.
At this rate, the shareholder meeting
will make my niece the chairwoman.
What should we do?
It can't be helped.
I need to meet Mr. Park.
Thank you.
Goodness. Thank you.
Hyeon-ho, I'll pay.
Goodness. No, thanks.
Why would you pay for my parents' gift?
Come on. I owe you a lot.
And I got my first paycheck.
Hey, my Bumyoung Motor Group stocks
skyrocketed too.
Fine, but I'm paying for our meal.
We should also gift nice outfits
to replace their baggy pants.
Good idea!
We may not be cool, but we're not poor.
We're cool too.
Yes!
Welcome. What can I help you with?
Give me everything from here to there!
Thank you, sir.
Babe, let's go!
Love?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'll buy it with money.
How much will it cost? Answer me.
What's wrong with you?
What made your face turn red?
Something's fishy.
It's nothing. Let's go.
In-seong.
I think someone's following us.
Who?
Four o'clock, in a suit.
Don't look. Act casual.
He's my bodyguard.
I see.
It's a bit small.
It's meant for your wrist.
I can't keep saying "Excuse me"
or "Hey" whenever I call you.
What should I call you?
There's no need to discuss that.
They call him Mafi.
Mafi?
Are you in a mafia?
The legendary fist
that broke his opponent's mouthguard.
Mafi, for mouthguard fighter.
You were a rising boxer
in the national youth team,
but now you're a loan shark
with three previous convictions.
Why did you do a background check
if you're going to say that to my face?
I needed to perform a fact check.
If you run your mouth like that,
you'll see me get convicted again.
That's the fact.
He blew a bubble.
How did you do it?
You look so brutal.
If you stare at her like that,
she'll get scared.
Can't you smile?
How can you be so antagonistic?
My goodness.
Come over here.
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
He doesn't scare me.
He's like a friend of mine named Ha-seung.
He always messes with me
and steals my snacks.
But my teacher told me
it's because he likes me.
-Here.
-What is this?
It's a shirt for you.
Why would you give me…
By any chance…
Did you throw away my shirt?
Sorry?
You didn't have to buy me a new one.
I threw away your shirt too,
thinking I wouldn't meet you again.
I see.
Ms. Jung, what time
is the VR seminar again?
It is at 2 p.m. at Daejeon Expo Plaza.
Mr. Park, can you go there in my stead?
If it's in Daejeon,
can I visit my parents after?
Sure.
Since you came all the way here,
let's go in together.
No thanks.
While buying gifts, Mafi…
Anyway, I bought something for you too.
It's a watch.
I saw you that day, and you seemed
to use the watch in various ways.
I bought one that's durable.
I hope you like it.
My goodness.
It's a purple dress. My favorite color.
You always wear the same clothes.
-I like it.
-And…
Since you like beef…
You must have money to burn.
If you squander your money like this,
you'll become a beggar.
-It's his first time getting paid.
-That's what I'm saying.
That's nonsense. Since you started late,
you should pinch pennies to save up.
What? Why do you
keep comparing him to others?
Would you like it
if I compared Cho Yong-pil and Lee Yong?
Go ahead! I'm confident.
-Goodness.
-Father.
-Here.
-What is that?
Glasses?
Are you trying to warn me
to keep my eyes wide open?
Jeez. It's nothing like that.
Here. Try them on.
-Forget it.
-Come on. Don't turn it down.
-Why would I…
-Stay still.
-They'll look good on you.
-I don't need…
What?
Honey, what's--
Baro, play Cho Yong-pil's "Mona Lisa."
What the…
My goodness. Honey.
Sir…
What?
Sir.
Goodness.
Honey!
My goodness.
Honey, what's gotten into you?
Sir, I love you!
-Sir!
-Jae-chun.
-Are you okay?
-Look.
-What's going on?
Cho Yong-pil is right there.
-Have you gone mad? What's wrong with you?
-You're crazy.
Snap out of it.
-What's with you?
-Village Head.
Close your eyes.
-Why?
-I said close your eyes!
-Don't freak out.
-Okay.
Okay. Open your eyes.
-My goodness, sir.
-What?
-Isn't that Cho Yong-pil?
Your father will stand tall
in front of the village head for a while.
I knew he would like those
more than the beef.
But how is it that you can see
Cho Yong-pil with those glasses?
They're called AR glasses.
My company made them.
Yes. Well…
Do you remember
when we video-called each other?
Isn't it cool?
What is that?
Do you remember
how I put effects on my face
like a flower and a dog?
I remember laughing so hard.
Those glasses are the same.
They put visual effects like Cho Yong-pil
on top of the world that you see.
I see.
So you're saying
the Cho Yong-pil that he's seeing is fake?
Gosh, it looks so real.
-Sir.
-Goodness.
-Goodness, sir.
-I'm getting a call.
-All right.
-Sir!
-This is amazing.
-Goodness.
I'm sorry. I took a while, didn't I?
How did you think of
getting your parents AR glasses?
-Sorry?
-You did great.
Did I do something praiseworthy?
Of course.
Thanks to you, I struck upon an idea
to corner Mr. Kwak.
CEO PARK IN-SEONG
Will it work?
It's technically perfect.
There won't be a problem
if we have good teamwork.
KIM SEON-JU
We have to wait
for when Mr. Kwak is asleep.
Thank you.
-Mr. Kwak.
-Yes?
Goodness. Thank you
for the delicious meal.
I'm sorry for cornering you
without any evidence that day.
Enough with the apologies.
I'm glad we resolved the misunderstanding.
I'm starting to fall into a food coma.
Let's grab some coffee.
It'll be on me.
No. The coffee will be my treat as well.
How strange.
Is this the place?
Yes. The sky lounge
has an incredible view.
I see.
Why are all the elevators
under maintenance?
Where are the employees?
Why don't we take the stairs
to walk off our lunch?
To the sky lounge?
Yes. Let's go.
Goodness.
ELEVATORS UNDER MAINTENANCE
Take your time.
The coffee will taste amazing.
Don't you think so?
Mr. Park.
Don't you think
they would've fixed the elevators by now?
Come on. We're almost there.
Just consider it as exercise.
We still have 15 more floors to go.
We'll be there in no time.
Let's go.
We're almost there.
The 36th floor…
What?
It's locked.
Is that so?
Well, there's always next time.
Pardon?
What are you doing?
Lunchtime is almost over.
Let's go back to work.
Heading back down.
Goodness.
Buckle up.
All right.
Ms. Jung, it looks like
Mr. Kwak is fatigued.
Can you turn on the massage function?
Goodness.
It worked. He's asleep.
-Ms. Jung.
-Yes?
Can you…
turn on some music?
Yes, sir.
Gosh, this song is amazing.
Right, Mr. Kwak?
Goodness, Ms. Jung.
You should've woken me up if we arrived.
Ms. Jung?
Mr. Kim.
You can't possibly be here.
Why did you do that
at the golf course that day?
Why did you do that to me?
I had no choice.
I was given orders.
Did you have a good dream?
Don't get me wrong.
It's too late to make excuses.
You can't possibly be here.
VOICE RECORDING
I had no choice.
I was given orders.
I know you're not the mastermind
behind everything.
It's not in your nature
and you don't have the guts.
Who has your back?
Sorry?
I'm afraid I don't follow.
I don't know
the extent of your involvement.
But I know you're aware of one thing.
Mr. Kim was attacked.
What do you mean by that?
Isn't he on a sabbatical
due to health reasons?
You can continue to play innocent.
But I wonder what will happen
to the tail that's been cut off.
Right.
Do you think
they'll continue to protect you?
Or…
will they feign ignorance,
the way you're doing right now?
How did you handle the situation?
That novice sounded
like he knew everything.
No.
I can't trust you guys.
I'm going to go myself.
Will Mr. Kwak move according to our plan?
His own safety
is the most important to him.
When push comes to shove,
he'd be more than willing to
switch sides to survive.
It's human nature
to react to something unfair.
To avoid being the fall guy,
he'll come clean.
I'm certain
we'll hear from him soon.
VICE CHAIRMAN OH YOUNG-GEUN
What did I tell you?
Hello?
Yes, Mr. Oh.
The apples were very tasty.
I understand your taking pride
in your parents' orchard.
I heard it's extremely difficult
to grow apple trees. Is it true?
They're high-maintenance.
I figured.
The sweeter the fruit,
the more susceptible it'll be to pests.
Why did you want to see me?
Just as your parents
grew apple trees,
I spent my whole life
building up Bumyoung.
But the thing is,
a pest appeared out of the blue,
and it keeps making holes in the trees.
What is usually done in such a situation?
If it's serious,
the tree is cut down or incinerated
to prevent further damage.
I like that approach.
The same goes for business management.
My antsy niece
announced that she would release
the self-driving car.
Don't you know?
She's just manipulating the media.
Why do you think that?
Because
Mr. Kim is not in a situation
to release the car.
Isn't that right?
You were sleeping?
I'm sorry.
What about Min-ju?
No, I was just wondering
if everything was okay.
Yes, I called for no particular reason.
Go back to sleep.
I'll hang up.
IMPYEONG MENTAL HOSPITAL
NAM ****-WON, MALE
Do you know what apple blossoms symbolize?
Temptation, wisdom,
and success.
Once you leave, think wisely
about whose side you'll stand by.
I will not stand by anyone.
It's great to be young.
But you know what?
If you don't stand by my side,
I can't guarantee your safety.
Are you threatening me right now?
No, I would never.
Just think of it as a boomer's words
said out of concern for you.
Mr. Oh said that?
Yes.
Does he know something
or was he just fishing for something?
I just can't figure it out.
Hello?
This is Kwak Sam-su.
Yes, Mr. Kwak.
Let's meet.
I have something to give you.
-Me?
-I will tell you the truth
about that night.
Come out alone.
Mr. Kwak, stay with me.
Mr. Kwak!
If you don't stand by my side,
I can't guarantee your safety.
Mr. Kwak.
Mr. Kwak, stay with me.
Help!
Can you call an ambulance?
Excuse me, Mr. Kwak.
Move.
There's no way.
He called me and asked to meet.
He didn't commit suicide.
Yes, I see.
That's what I think too. Grab him.
Anything you say from now on
can be used against you in a court of law.
So if you're scared…
you should use your right
to remain silent.
Take him away.
What should we do?
What else can you do?
You must throw it away.
-Did you hear from Mr. Park?
-No.
Since it's complicated,
let's think simply.
I traced the number,
and its location is around Yeongbo Park.
What are you doing?
If they know you were with me,
it'll make things worse.
He left the base,
so he should've run with all his might.
If he was going to hesitate,
he should've just stayed on the base.
Bring me the next base in here.