This week again,
we're together with Loco and CODE KUNST.
(Loco, singer)
It's the fifth day in Japan.
Last week, we had Seung Yong who cleverly started shaking...
his ex's heart.
Min Kyung, Yoo Sik's ex,
has also started to move along with Seung Yong.
- That's right.
- I don't know how it'll turn out...
in the last episode,
but will this be the trigger...
that brings Min Kyung and her ex back together...
as CODE KUNST said?
- It has started.
- Right. It has started.
- Also,
the fact that Yoo Sik hid his stomach pain...
is evidence of love.
(A cloudy and rainy morning)
(Blue Room: Won Kyu and Yoo Sik's room)
(He starts writing something as soon as he gets up.)
(After writing for a long time, )
(he gets ready to go out.)
- A letter? A note?
- I don't think it's a letter.
That's right.
- It's a poem.
- That's right.
- A poem?
- He wrote it down.
It starts with "you."
Wouldn't he give it to Ji Hyeon?
He might give it to Ji Yeon.
(Ji Yeon is eating alone.)
Hi.
I keep meeting you whenever I come here to eat.
It's delicious.
- Is it good?
- It is.
You know,
I share a room with Hyeon Ji.
But...
she also knows about the T-shirt.
- Hyeon Ji?
- Yes. So,
that came into my mind then,
so I thought about it again.
Ji Hyeon put an apron on me that day because I was wearing white.
Do you remember that? I was cleaning the dishes.
When she asked me, "Is that Won Kyu's?"
and even when you were sitting next to me,
I think I made some jokes saying,
"I shouldn't get food on this."
- "It's a cute T-shirt." - Right.
Right?
I think I said...
so many things I shouldn't have.
But that's...
my fault.
"Why did I do that?"
(Woo Jin came to the communal area.)
That thought kept popping up.
I see.
(He quietly walks past them.)
Right.
I see.
- Hi, Woo Jin.
- Hi.
Hi, Woo Jin.
I think I hurt many people...
without my intention.
(Woo Jin leaves the area.)
But you really didn't intend to do that.
Are you concerned about Ji Hyeon?
I wasn't concerned about her at all,
but after knowing who she was,
there are things that add up.
As far as I could tell,
Ji Hyeon was really considerate of me.
Weren't you concerned about Woo Jin when he just came?
When Woo Jin came?
Woo Jin didn't look happy.
He always has a bad expression.
He's like that even when he's with me.
He really seems upset today.
He's always like that. I don't know.
Normally,
he would have greeted us first.
I think he left because he didn't want to disturb us.
I don't know what Hong Ji Yeon is thinking.
Goodness.
I think she wants to get back with you.
- What?
- I think...
she wants to get back with you.
Does she still have feelings for Won Kyu?
I felt bad because I saw them...
as soon as I woke up.
That's why I just drank some water and came out...
without greeting them.
Am I taking things the wrong way?
(Won Kyu came back to his room after eating with Ji Yeon.)
- You were here.
- Yes.
When did you get up?
Me? Around 11am.
Where are you going?
- Where am I going?
- Yes.
I'll go see Ji Hyeon...
I'll get going.
(He takes something with the paper he wrote in the morning.)
(He even puts on some perfume and leaves the room.)
- Who is it?
- It's me.
Are you okay?
- What's okay?
- Your condition.
I was wondering if you're okay.
- What is this?
- It's a gift for you.
- Really?
- Really.
Open it later.
What is it? It's a perfume.
Yes. It's the one I use.
What? When did you buy it?
Some time back.
When?
- When you got the hoodie?
- No.
Why did you get it?
To give it to you.
Her expression was like,
"Why is he giving this to me now?"
It felt like she was trying to keep some distance.
So I was a bit disappointed.
It looked like she was glad.
I guess he wanted her to react more.
I think she looked glad.
"Really? This is amazing." Something like that.
- Right.
- He shouldn't expect that.
- That's what I wanted to say.
(Sung Baek Hyun)
(Choi Yun Nyeong)
(Lee Jae Hyeong)
(Park Ji Hyeon)
(Cho Yoo Sik)
(Park Hyeon Ji)
(Kim Woo Jin)
(Kwak Min Kyung)
(Jung Won Kyu)
(Hong Ji Yeon)
(Shin Seung Yong)
(EXchange 4)
(Episode 18: A Sleepless Night with Rain)
Right.
(Hyeon Ji and Yoo Sik's casual date)
(Yoo Sik will be driving today.)
Are you comfortable with driving?
- Here?
- Yes.
It's the same.
- It's the same?
- Yes.
- That's interesting.
- Why?
I think it would be difficult and confusing.
(Exclaiming)
Why?
It's just fascinating.
It's my first time moving by car in Japan.
I don't know why,
but I found Yoo Sik driving really cute.
It...
It was just...
Maybe it's because he's younger than me.
It's like an amusement park ride.
He seemed cute.
The magic that makes him start to look...
- like a baby?
- I know, right?
After hearing the practical things?
- No way.
- Suddenly?
Please don't do that.
Come to think of it,
I don't think she finds him cute in a bad way...
because of what Seung Yong said.
I think he would seem cuter in a good way...
and more attractive.
But when you think a man is cute, it can't be helped.
Right. I guess she really finds him cute.
It's nice.
We're going to have pastries.
- Pastries?
- A cafe with pastries.
Pastries? That's nice.
Is it because I said...
- I wanted to have pastries?
- Yes.
(Yoo Sik prepared the course for Hyeon Ji.)
- I guess it's this place.
- Yes.
It's a high-end bakery.
Is there anything you want?
There is.
Should I have this? One of the two.
- Shall we have this?
- Yes.
I want one canele.
Here?
It's so nice.
It's so nice. Amazing.
It's so...
It's so open.
Right.
(They came to a cafe with an open view of the forest.)
It's so pretty.
It feels so relaxing here...
because it's open.
Why?
- It's too uniform.
- Too uniform?
- It's...
- I wanted to make it like this.
How did I make it? Let me see.
I didn't want to make it look like dots.
I wanted them to be big like this.
It's because my fingers are thick.
You said they would get wider.
But they didn't.
Isn't this the widened version?
It's certainly wider.
Here you go.
Oh, it was French toast.
You talked a lot yesterday.
With who?
With Seung Yong.
We talked during the day.
- I wanted to make it clear to him.
- Your hair.
I said I was going on a date with you today.
I didn't think he'd tell her.
I don't really mind people knowing.
Be it Seung Yong or Baek Hyun...
or others.
But...
I'm quite concerned because it's Min Kyung.
Me or you?
I'm concerned because you might be concerned.
Min Kyung seemed to really want to get back with him,
and he's been talking to Min Kyung...
a lot lately.
I think his heart could be shaken a little.
I thought it was possible.
You've met for a long time,
and if you kept talking,
your heart might change. I thought that was possible.
I'm not saying that's weird.
Honestly, I can't say...
I'm not at all bothered...
by her struggles,
but I have feelings for someone else now.
I keep telling her that,
but she becomes emotional.
No matter what she thinks, what happens after that...
has to be left to her choice and freedom.
(He expressed how he feels to Hyeon Ji.)
Go on and eat now. Eat while they're warm.
It's already dark.
I wish it wouldn't get dark.
You said...
you feel at ease recently.
- Me?
- Yes.
But you don't seem comfortable these days.
When did I say I felt comfortable?
I have to meet many people...
when I get home.
- This?
- Yes.
Here.
(They go for a drive to have some peaceful time together.)
I should go slowly.
What's that?
Isn't that an amusement ride?
- It looks fun.
- But I...
- I thought I saw it wrong.
- Me too.
(They're captivated by the interesting monorail.)
- Amazing.
- I wonder what they're thinking.
It's so fascinating.
It's raining a lot.
Right.
Would we be able to walk by the sea?
Have you been to the sea?
I didn't go to the sea per se.
What?
I did have a view of the sea.
Where?
I don't know where it was.
When?
The day before yesterday.
Why are you saying that so softly?
(He didn't do anything wrong, but he feels like he did.)
So you had brunch at a place with a view of the sea.
You ate at a nice place.
You went to the aquarium.
Yes.
I just saw the water. I didn't see the sea creatures.
(She received jealousy for jealousy.)
We'll see the sea now.
So this is the seaside.
It's raining now, right?
No.
- There's a sea here?
- Over there.
It really is open.
I'm starting to feel relaxed.
That's what I'm saying.
Didn't you say that you like to watch the sea?
Yes, I like to watch the sea.
Hold on.
It's raining.
It must have been nicer if the weather had been fine.
We had excellent weather yesterday.
- That's true.
- Yesterday in the afternoon.
- Where is the rain coming from?
- Aren't you in the rain?
- I'm fine. Where is it coming from?
- I'll stay here.
- Okay.
- I won't be in the rain here.
- Are you in the rain?
- Do you want me to be?
Come here, to the right.
The rain is coming from here.
My shoulder is wet here, though.
- What? It's fine.
- It's wet here.
- You got so wet!
- Well...
The rain hit me from the side.
- I covered myself, though.
- Seriously.
We get to see the sea properly while we're in Japan.
They say we'd stay near the sea,
but we might not have seen the sea...
- and left.
- I know.
Watch out.
- Oh, no. You got too wet.
- Sorry?
- You're too wet.
- I'm fine.
Not here?
No, you're all wet.
It's because of how it rained.
I'd have gotten wet anyway.
One of his arms was soaked in rain.
I didn't know he was that wet.
I felt thankful.
(On the way back)
- Do you feel cold?
- No, I'm fine.
Did your clothes dry off?
It's getting dry.
Yes, that's nice.
That's nice.
Both of them are trying to go home as late as possible.
It just looks like a real date between lovers.
- I know.
- It looks like a date...
between people who have already become lovers.
That's dangerous.
(CODE KUNST supports Min Kyung, so he feels a sense of crisis.)
Since they came to Japan, the first one to apply a casual date...
- is Yoo Sik.
- Right.
That shows his feelings for Hyeon Ji are growing.
I don't feel that his heart wavers because of Min Kyung.
I don't think Yoo Sik's heart would waver.
- What do you think?
- What do you think about that?
Shall I change my mind now?
(Kamakura House)
Did you see the gift?
It seems to have a letter inside. Am I right?
I don't know.
What is it? Tell me.
You can just look at it yourself.
I seriously went back to when we broke up and thought about it.
I couldn't help but think that you have every reason...
to hate me.
When did such a thought come to you?
Just while we were talking about what happened so far,
when I really took the time to look back on that moment.
You know I was at my part-time job when you told me it was over, right?
I was at work too.
At that time, I thought I should stop dating someone...
in a way that I sincerely love him...
and think about marrying him.
I was a fool to believe in love.
I think you must have felt so.
So, although you came here and showed...
an attitude that you want to get back together,
if I accept that instantly,
I'd feel so sorry for my past self.
Back then, I was...
not solid as a person.
Since I was like that,
I feel that I wanted that quality even more from the one I dated.
Then how do you feel now?
It's only been a year. Are you more solid now?
I'd feel ashamed to say that I'm more solid,
so I can't say so.
But about why you behaved so at that time,
although I didn't like that,
and why you couldn't help behaving so,
I think now I can understand.
Actually, you're not doing anything wrong.
But since I think you're doing wrong,
I got to tell you it was over, after all.
Thinking back now, you didn't do anything wrong.
It was the first time for you, so it was hard for you.
You didn't know it well, and you were in the process.
But I only thought from my own standard...
and thought that you were just different from me.
I considered being different to be wrong,
and I thought so about too many things.
I told her I had the wrong idea about her when we broke up.
I told her she was different, not wrong.
I just told her about what I felt.
(That's how their conversation ended.)
(Ji Hyeon comes back to her room and takes out Won Kyu's gift.)
There were song lyrics written like a poem.
When we were dating,
we used to listen to the song together since we liked the meaning.
The memory about the song...
and the thoughts we had back then...
flooded in at once.
(You become my little world)
(You make me dream a dream I've never dreamed of)
(Even if this is my illusion)
(Hold me in your arms just for today)
(My little heart came to you)
(I want to travel that long road with you)
(Even if this is my illusion)
(Hold me in your arms just for today)
When I first started dating him,
I kept asking him to write me a poem.
Back then, he said he could never write a poem...
and wrote me a letter instead.
However, all of a sudden,
he writes something for me himself...
and says he bought a perfume thinking about me.
He's trying to express more...
and is changing, I thought.
I remember the scene...
of listening to the song together.
We were just lying, looking at the ceiling,
and talking to each other with music on.
Back then, singing along with the song felt very funny.
I remember we were singing as we laughed.
What?
It's very nice.
(You said you'd believe in me)
(That's a deep love)
(Their little world, made of only two of them, disappeared.)
(Nothing but longing remains in that place.)
I held so much yearning for the song.
However, you can't just get back together by yearning.
I felt both happy and anxious.
I had such ambivalent feelings.
(You become my little world)
(You make me dream a dream I've never dreamed of)
(Even if this is my illusion)
(Hold me in your arms just for today)
Won Kyu is good.
Won Kyu is trying to swallow his pride and give in.
It's nice to see that he admits.
It seems that he actually realized things.
- Right. I agree.
- Yes. He realized.
Just that little effort can open her heart that wide.
- Right.
- It just melts her heart.
He did a good job.
- I support Won Kyu and Ji Hyeon.
- It was the right timing.
It wasn't too late.
Handwriting expresses his sincerity.
Right. He wrote the song lyrics they liked together.
Their conversation and the lyrics in the gift...
- Right.
- connect really well.
And sitting on the couch earlier and talking to Ji Hyeon,
all of those...
made her cold heart melt away.
He used to think that she was wrong,
but he began to admit that they are different.
Then I see a hope that they won't fight.
How about you? Have two of you, like Won Kyu,
prepared a romantic event before?
Those who create music...
- can do it.
- We write lyrics.
- We all did it at least once.
- I record the song...
and let her listen, you know.
- Do you do that?
- Yes, I did.
- Surprising.
- Amazing.
The song is not to be released.
- I write it for one person...
- Only for one.
And give it.
- Seriously.
- Right.
- I mean it.
- Come inside.
- Isn't the rain splashing inside?
- No.
- It's raining a lot.
- Are you okay sitting there?
I'm fine.
You can turn your chair a bit like this.
- Why aren't they coming back?
- What?
- Why aren't they coming, you asked?
(Min Kyung is bothered that Yoo Sik hasn't come back.)
I guess there's a traffic jam because of the rain.
What am I supposed to do if I get vicious?
- You didn't yet?
- No.
I mean, not very seriously.
You can. It's going to be okay.
But I don't want to.
Right. Yoo Sik doesn't like it when people get emotional.
- He doesn't.
- Because Yoo Sik...
doesn't like it when people get emotional?
This is really beautiful. This one.
Come here.
I wanted it to look neat,
so I ripped it all apart.
(Baek Hyun puts the bracelet on Yun Nyeong.)
I added the silver color too.
- It looks good on you.
- I like it.
I'm returning it.
- I'll give it to you later.
- Okay.
Wait. What is this?
Did you say the rain isn't splashing in?
It is. It's splashing in a bit now.
- Bring it inside.
- What's wrong with the rain?
- Shall we go inside?
- Can we?
I'll get inside with Yun Nyeong.
- Get inside.
- Okay.
Three of you can get some rain here.
Yes, we can get some rain.
Let's get inside.
It feels comfortable, even before I lie down.
- Where?
- Here.
- Is this your bed?
- Yes.
You look even more beautiful looking up from below.
Since I have single eyelids,
I look better when looked up, rather than when looked down.
So photos taken from below are all the better.
Then I saw it correctly, right?
Yes, that's right.
Don't you feel sleepy now? Why do I, all of a sudden?
You can sleep.
I'm not going to because someone might tell me I got puffy.
Yun Nyeong, you already slept earlier.
What are you saying, seriously?
- Didn't you sleep?
- I slept for only a bit.
- For a bit?
- Yes.
For a bit, but you slept.
- About ten minutes.
- Ten minutes?
Yes.
(A brief moment shared just between the two of them)
Didn't you just feel like it was ten minutes?
- I really slept for ten minutes.
- All right.
It took 40 minutes to go, so...
- So you slept in the car?
- Right.
- Then you didn't sleep.
- No.
- Who is it?
- It's me.
- Kim Woo Jin?
- Yes.
- I was putting on makeup.
- What are you doing?
There's no one else.
- Can I come in?
- Yes.
- Are you transforming?
I had something to tell you, actually.
What is it?
Have a seat and wait. I'll tell you a bit later.
I'll tell you what I was going to.
Okay.
This morning, I was in the front yard with Won Kyu.
Yes.
But you didn't even greet us.
I felt that you weren't feeling good for some reason.
I could see that.
I guess Won Kyu saw that too.
He said, "Woo Jin looks so upset."
From your perspective, you didn't want to disturb us,
so you avoided us intentionally and gave us some space.
But when other people saw you,
they might not think the same way,
even when you're not that kind of person.
- Right.
- I'm not criticizing you.
I'm telling you this because I'm worried.
You think that I'm being very rude...
to Won Kyu.
I didn't say that you are rude.
- Yes, but...
- I mean, it shows.
And I hope it doesn't.
Here, it's supposed to be like that.
- You know what I mean?
- Yes.
Okay.
(Woo Jin left, and Min Kyung has come to Ji Yeon.)
Ji Yeon.
- May I come in...
- Who is it?
- It's me. May I come inside?
- Sure.
I'm coming in.
Have a seat here.
- Okay.
- Whose is this?
- I was so troubled.
- Why?
(Sighing)
Yoo Sik hasn't come back yet.
- What?
- Yoo Sik isn't back yet.
Is he on a date?
I'm so angry about his not getting back.
(Hyeon Ji and Yoo Sik are back from their date.)
- You're back.
- Hi.
- Where are you going? You're back.
Is everyone downstairs?
No. Did you bring something tasty?
- We've been to a convenience store.
- A convenience store? Sounds good.
Nothing special happened. There were not so many people.
- Really?
- Do you want to go to the room?
Who is it?
He's back. I'm leaving.
Hi, Hyeon Ji.
We were having a talk.
I'm tired. I'm sleepy.
I'm going to leave.
- See you later.
- Okay.
- Are you going to go downstairs?
- Yes.
(Blue Room: Won Kyu and Yoo Sik's room)
You must be tired.
- Me?
- Yes.
(Min Kyung visits Yoo Sik.)
Yes?
I don't think someone should enter right now.
- Because of Yoo Sik?
- Yes.
Yoo Sik is changing right now.
May I enter?
- He's changing.
- I'll wait here.
Okay.
Shall we head out?
- Shall we do that?
- Yes.
It's okay.
What? It's okay.
Won Kyu and I were going to head out anyway.
It's okay.
We can talk at the doorway.
Talk comfortably in the room.
Won Kyu and I were going to head out anyway.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be.
- It's intense.
- I know.
What are they going to do?
(My goodness)
Where have you been?
To a cafe.
My feelings...
Why are you crying?
Why did you come back so late?
Why did you wait?
Yoo Sik, you went out on a date.
I knew with whom you went. You didn't come back until late.
Of course, it got on my nerves.
You know, I...
I just came back.
How did you know that I was here?
I was with Ji Yeon.
- Ji Hyeon?
- Ji Yeon.
And?
I left the room since Hyeon Ji came back.
Min Kyung, you're being too much.
Why?
You stayed in Hyeon Ji's room. When Hyeon Ji returned,
you came straight to this room...
and drove out two people to talk to me.
- For goodness' sake.
- You had it all planned out.
I'm Type J.
I mean...
Hold on.
- Hold on.
- Stop with that MBTI!
- You know, that's...
- How cute.
- "I'm Type J." - "I'm Type J."
That shouldn't be cute, but...
- Seriously.
- MBTI is something else.
- It can explain everything.
- My goodness.
I can't believe she used MBTI in that situation.
But it made us speechless.
- Seriously.
- I see.
Even Yoo Sik found it cute.
- Of course.
- I know.
It was cute and funny.
You stayed in Hyeon Ji's room. When Hyeon Ji returned,
you came straight to this room...
and drove out two people to talk to me.
- For goodness' sake.
- You had it all planned out.
I'm Type J.
I mean...
Right now, this is the only thing I can do.
Hanging around in front of you is the only thing I can do.
Talking to Won Kyu is the only thing I can do.
What did you say to Won Kyu?
I told Won Kyu...
I'm the most relaxed around Won Kyu.
There's a big age gap. Why do you feel that way?
He's practically your uncle.
I'm the most relaxed around Uncle Won Kyu.
Won Kyu is a good man.
In any case, I don't want to talk about Won Kyu.
Can I ask you what you've done?
- We went to a cafe.
- What did you guys do?
We had a brunch with bread...
and drank coffee.
For five hours?
We went somewhere far in a car.
Did you drive?
Was I supposed to make Hyeon Ji drive?
Why do you call her "Hyeon Ji?" She's older than you.
Was I supposed to make Big Sister Hyeon Ji drive?
You must be happy about becoming an official couple.
The two of you were the only ones who weren't home today.
Does it look like I'm being egotistical?
No.
Then what?
You can be egotistical or not.
I want to be honest with my feelings.
I want to get back together with you.
I want you to come back.
Having someone who expresses her interest in an honest way...
helped me open up.
I have feelings for her.
To be honest, I lean more toward her than you right now.
Did you erase me?
I didn't say that.
Give me hope.
It'll be harder for you if I give you hope.
Don't you think about how hurtful those words are?
Let's say...
I don't have much interest in getting back together with you.
Let's say I'm interested in someone new.
Do you still want me to get back together with you?
Wouldn't that be more hurtful?
I feel so betrayed.
Why does this make you feel betrayed?
Just how terrible do you want to make me look?
Honestly speaking... Do you want me to lie?
Have I ever told you the words you wanted to hear...
or white lies?
Even if it was a bit hurtful, I always spoke honestly.
Do you think they'll change?
I'm talking about your feelings.
Right now, I don't know.
What do I need to do?
When can you tell me for sure?
- What?
- When will you make up your mind?
Not much time remains.
Okay.
If you get another chance to go on a date,
will you choose Hyeon Ji?
What's the percentage?
I can't express it in numbers.
Do you think you'll be happy if you date Hyeon Ji?
Just as you said,
I'm being honest with my feelings.
You're about to open your heart to someone else,
and I'm asking you to come back.
If my plea doesn't work,
there's nothing I can do.
I just think I should be honest with my feelings.
During the remaining time,
you'll definitely get a chance to go on a date.
If you go on another date with her, your heart will open up even more.
I never said that you weren't on my mind whatsoever.
Then go on a date with me.
Then can you not go on a date...
with someone else?
I won't.
Don't avoid me. Even if you do, I'll hang around in front of you.
Can I take this?
Take it.
(Sighing)
(Thoughts rain down.)
Let's have a meal.
- Let's eat.
Meat on a rainy day?
It fits the mood.
The mood.
I feel lucky.
Shall we eat beef first?
Shall we eat pork first?
Shall we start grilling meat?
Not everyone is here.
Start grilling.
- Start grilling.
- Shall we start grilling?
- Yes.
- Start grilling.
All right.
Shall we put all the meat on the grill?
- That way...
- But not everyone is here.
- Here? Everyone is here.
- Everyone is here.
- Is everyone here?
- Yes.
The meat...
Not everyone is here.
- Really?
- Yes.
You put oil on the grill on purpose...
so that meat wouldn't stick.
Doesn't this one work?
(Hyeon Ji joins the group.)
Everyone has gathered around already.
Yun Nyeong, we're wondering if we should pour in water.
Ramyeon? What is it?
- It's really tasty.
- Isn't it mala hot pot?
It's incredibly tasty ramyeon. I love it the most.
I'm curious.
- We bought so many ramyeon bags.
- That's right.
At what time did you come back today?
Just a moment ago.
Right before this.
You have something on your lips.
You should look in the mirror.
What did you do today?
Today? We just went to a cafe.
What did we do? We just enjoyed the drive.
(I see.)
(Glancing over)
It smells good.
(Min Kyung and Yoo Sik are in her line of sight.)
- Have you tried it?
- Not yet.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
- She saw it.
- She really saw it.
She saw it, right?
It does look strange.
She's watching them with Seung Yong.
I know. Are they watching a show or something?
- It's weird.
- What's up with the two of them?
- Is it tasty?
- Yes.
Did something happen to put you in a bad mood?
- Why?
- You look down.
No, it isn't like that.
Shall I grill it?
No.
Oh, instead of me?
Yes. I'll do it.
Is it hot?
(Uncle Won Kyu reads the room and gives them space.)
- It isn't hot, right?
- Beef doesn't disappoint.
- Beef is tasty. Yes.
Min Kyung, hand them over...
- and help the others inside.
- Why? I...
Don't stay near the fire.
I have tongs.
Where should I put these tongs?
Just give them to Baek Hyun.
(The liquor of the day is soju.)
Ji Yeon, will you drink soju?
We brought out soju.
- Somaek sounds good too.
- Ji Yeon.
- Yes?
- Drink with me today.
That sounds good.
Big sisters, let me join.
- Okay. Everyone can join.
- Big sisters, let me join.
Why does it feel so awkward to call them "Big sisters?"
Jae Hyeong, you should start using the polite tone.
- Call me, "Big sister." - Jae Hyeong.
- Don't be like that.
- It feels so awkward.
Jae Hyeong, call me "Big Sister Ji Hyeon."
You know,
I need to... I'll tell you later.
- What?
- I need to buy you a meal.
- I need to buy you a meal?
- Why?
- Stop.
We went to that restaurant together.
I didn't know...
that you had paid for the date.
It doesn't matter.
Still, I'll buy you something tasty.
Still, thank you.
(The two of them make a secret appointment.)
Are we done grilling meat?
Yes. Let's move it to a plate.
Let's stop here.
It looks tasty.
- Thank you for the food.
- Let's have a drink together.
- Okay.
- Cheers.
DFO!
- What was that?
- DFO.
It comes back endlessly.
DFO.
Drink your fill without overdoing it.
I learned it...
about two days before joining the show.
- It's tasty, Ji Hyeon.
- I know.
You're eating rice with gusto.
- You didn't eat at all, right?
- That's right.
It looks nice.
- It's so nice.
- Jae Hyeong is on a mono diet.
You lost a lot of weight.
- I realized that from here.
- Really?
- You lost a lot of weight.
- He lost a lot of weight.
- He gets skinnier by the day.
- Woo Jin...
gets handsomer by the day.
This is a therapeutic day.
- I know.
- Really?
- Why?
- Ji Yeon.
That was a loaded question.
(Her two exes are sitting across from her.)
You eat with gusto.
What?
Hold on. What's up with our socks today?
That's insane. What's this?
What's up with this man?
- Seriously. What's this?
- What's up with this man?
What's up with this man?
- It's like a parallel universe.
- I know.
(The two of them make a fuss about wearing the same socks.)
(Sighing)
For goodness' sake.
I bet it feels strange to see them like that.
- I'm glad that they get along.
- I see.
Don't you drink soju?
- I usually drink soju more often.
- I see.
- I bet you can hold your liquor.
- But...
it has been a while since I drank soju.
You said you could drink two bottles of soju.
- What are you saying?
- You told me that.
You told me that you could drink two bottles of soju.
- I did?
- Yes.
You told me that you could drink 1 to 2 bottles of soju.
That doesn't equal two bottles.
Hyeon Ji? She can drink more than me.
- That's right.
- Hyeon Ji can drink two bottles.
That's right.
Seeing the two of them say it is so...
- They're sitting together too.
- It's so funny.
You should sit in the middle.
(Glaring)
I can't hold my liquor these days.
It has been a while since I drank.
Really?
There's a season when I drink and one when I don't.
It's like we're at someone's birthday party.
At like Popeyes?
- Popeyes.
- Delicious.
Pizza Hut.
(The doorbell suddenly rang.)
That scared me.
I'll get it.
(The sound made everyone nervous.)
I'm scared.
I'm opening it.
"Tomorrow is a mutual date."
"Only the matched partners will go on a date."
"Send a text at this moment..."
"with the name of the person you want to go on a date with,"
"excluding your ex."
(Tomorrow is a mutual date.)
(Only the matched partners will go on a date.)
(Send a text at this moment with the name of the person...)
(you want to go on a date with, excluding your ex.)
The partners must match,
- It's a must, right?
- excluding the exes.
- Excluding the exes?
- Then...
- Hyeon Ji and Yoo Sik.
- Yoo Sik.
Would that include whether he keeps his word...
to Min Kyung or not?
- No.
- You're right.
- But that's an official date.
- It's an official date.
- The thing is...
- He said he wouldn't pick her,
- didn't he?
- Min Kyung...
- He did, right?
- But that was for unofficial dates.
Hyeon Ji and Yoo Sik will pick each other for sure.
Right now?
Excluding my ex?
"Only the matched partners will go on a date."
"I'm going to text Baek Hyun's name."
"We'll go on a fun date tomorrow."
That had already crossed my mind.
I'll go on a date with Yun Nyeong. I need to spend time with her.
I got my hopes up.
I had a feeling Yoo Sik would choose me too.
All I thought was, "Yoo Sik and Hyeon Ji will go on a date again."
I didn't give it a second thought.
(Choi Yun Nyeong)
(Sung Baek Hyun)
(Kwak Min Kyung)
(Kim Woo Jin)
Woo Jin and I talked about...
getting something really delicious...
on a date before.
I recalled that and chose Woo Jin.
If we were to go on a date,
I thought he'd choose me as well.
If not, I'd be at home.
That was all I thought.
(Choi Yun Nyeong)
If my ex saw me go on a date with someone else,
she might think,
"Is he not being serious about me?"
(He chose a partner so as not to go on a date.)
So if we don't match, there's no date?
No.
(Cho Yoo Sik)
(Everyone has sent a text with the name of the mutual date partner.)
What do you want to do tomorrow?
I've already done everything I wanted to do tomorrow.
- Really?
- Yes.
I want to go to a theme park.
I really wanted to go to one.
Universal Studios.
I went there.
- You did?
- Really?
But the theme park was inside the Tokyo Dome.
It wasn't like Disneyland.
- Really?
- I went with Seung Yong.
I heard you went to the haunted house.
The haunted house was the real deal.
It was odd.
- Is that so?
- Odd and scary.
I hope everyone gets a chance to go there.
- It's that bad.
- I hate the thought of it.
I'd just walk in and out of the place.
Bluffing.
What? What did she just say?
- "Bluffing." - And she didn't continue.
I bet you'd close your eyes.
Totally.
(Who made your heart flutter today?)
(Let them know via text.)
(Your text will be delivered with your name.)
(The time has come once again, even today.)
(Dear feelings they only send to one person)
(Everyone has sent their text.)
You're sitting in the best seat.
So it happened.
Did he just say, "So what?"
- So it happened.
- "So it happened."
"So it happened."
Why would I say "So what?"
- I was taken aback.
- Like I would.
I thought you said, "So what?"
Where's my phone?
(Baek Hyun)
(It'd be nice if we could go on a date tomorrow. From Yun Nyeong)
How nice it would be if we could...
- work out together.
- Right?
(Yun Nyeong)
I want to go home.
(Nyeong, let's talk about what to wear tomorrow. From Baek Hyun)
The match result wasn't even out,
but he wanted to talk about our outfits for tomorrow.
It was hilarious.
How could he be so certain?
Even before getting the mutual date text,
that was what I sent.
(Their feelings have connected even today.)
What do you carry around?
Wait. It's mine.
- Mink?
- Mint.
(Thanks for looking out for my behaviior.)
I was wondering why everyone carried one around.
I know, right? Same here.
(Your ex picked you.)
"Thanks for coming."
"What a relief that he took it well." That was what I thought.
- Are you opening the wine?
- No.
How come?
For real?
(Woo Jin)
(There aren't many days left now.)
(Your ex picked you.)
"Because we don't have much time..."
"or things to talk about now,"
"let's do our best." Wasn't that what it meant?
(The two sent each other texts just like yesterday.)
I have the room to myself.
- Right now?
- Right.
- It's comfortable.
- I heard you wanted to be alone.
Listen. It's comfortable,
but now, I want a roommate.
Come to our room.
- Yes.
- Yours is next to mine.
- Next to mine?
- No, it's not next to hers.
- What?
- Are you two next door?
(Your ex picked you.)
- What's our room number?
- You two are next door.
- Aren't we in room 204?
- Yes.
Sending me that text...
might mean that she is expressing her feelings for me.
But the text itself...
wasn't all about positive feelings.
Her feelings aren't deep enough...
to go all in on me.
The thing is, I'm not sure how to further express...
my feelings.
I've already conveyed everything...
I possibly could to her.
What a secretive flirtation.
(Ji Hyeon)
(I hope you don't stress out too much. Don't get sick.)
We were roommates.
(Your ex picked you.)
He's the main source of my stress.
We're constantly stressing each other out.
What was that?
(They passed on their complex feelings to each other.)
I don't shave. My beard doesn't grow much.
(Hyeon Ji)
(I didn't get to see you all day. Let's hang out for long today.)
(From Jae Hyeong)
(Let's talk again later with ice cream. From Seung Yong)
I got laser treatment twice.
What I felt after receiving the texts was different.
To Jae Hyeong, I felt grateful.
To Seung Yong...
Should I say I was bothered?
Yoo Sik, are you drinking?
- Drinking?
- Yes.
I'm drinking buckets.
- Is that so?
- Yes, why?
- Just asking.
- Do you want some?
I'm already drinking.
I didn't empty it alone.
(Yoo Sik)
(I had fun thanks to you today. The sweater looks good on you.)
(From Hyeon Ji)
- Got it.
- Digital complex.
No, please.
- Guro Digital Complex?
- Digital.
(Hyeon Ji)
(It would've been really pretty had it not rained. From Yoo Sik)
Of course, it made me happy.
(The two shared their feelings with each other today as well.)
(Yoo Sik)
(Our Japan trip was fun. I miss it.)
- Got it.
- No, please.
Digital.
(Your ex picked you.)
(He received a text from Min Kyung in 4 days.)
"I still have lingering feelings for you."
"I like you."
I wanted to convey my feelings to him.
How strong.
- People might be blown away.
- Exactly.
At this rate, Ji Yeon and Min Kyung might get blown away.
I know, right?
The lightest two girls.
(Your ex picked Park Hyeon Ji.)
I clearly knew that he went on a date...
with Hyeon Ji that day.
I also knew that Yoo Sik's feelings...
for Hyeon Ji were quite big.
So the text that said he picked Hyeon Ji...
didn't really shake me up.
(Your ex picked Cho Yoo Sik.)
The fact that my ex...
keeps choosing Yoo Sik...
is telling me the two are set in stone.
It breaks my heart.
(Their different feelings have been passed on.)
Keep trying.
- I hope he keeps trying.
- It's not over yet.
If Seung Yong keeps trying...
- Yes.
- in his own way,
- Right?
- he might...
I don't know. Things are too certain...
- between Hyeon Ji and Yoo Sik.
- Yes.
There's no chance with Yoo Sik.
But Hyeon Ji has some openings.
- Really?
- You mean Hyeon Ji?
- Is that so?
- So Seung Yong...
could try to sway her.
Attack her with reality.
Yes, attacking with reality.
- It won't work.
- Reality?
My thoughts are the opposite.
I think there's an opening with Yoo Sik.
- Really?
- Not with Hyeon Ji.
- Same here. He doesn't...
- With Yoo Sik?
Make things certain.
- Like doubts?
- I can feel it.
It seems like Yoo Sik...
can't act all cruel toward the person...
who was with him for a long time.
Watching Yoo Sik so far,
he's the type who can't say...
- anything mean.
- Totally.
I was like him back when I was young.
I really couldn't say it.
I only realized it after being severely scolded by someone.
I can tell who it was.
(Blue Room: Won Kyu and Yoo Sik's room)
What do you two talk about?
- Well...
- We don't have a set topic.
- We just...
- When we feel like it,
- We talk.
- we drink in our room.
Like back then?
- Yes.
- Like when we drank in your room?
About that mutual date text.
Did you get the result via text?
- No.
- Me neither.
I asked, wondering if I didn't get the mutual date.
- I didn't get it.
- Same here.
I might not have been matched.
(Everyone wants to know the result.)
Won't we get the text regardless of the result?
Is it our room?
- Yes.
- Yes?
Can I come in?
- What?
- Why?
Weren't you talking with Hyeon Ji?
She disappeared.
You're going to drink, right?
Yes.
Have you talked about that with your ex?
The girls made unexpected choices for the pick-a-date by the ex.
I did. My date was with Min Kyung.
- Yoo Sik's date was unexpected too.
- Mine was...
- with Yun Nyeong.
- Exactly.
It was my first ever date with Yun Nyeong.
Yun Nyeong has a great personality.
- How do you feel, Yoo Sik?
- About what?
About Min Kyung.
Min Kyung?
Why did you two break up, Yoo Sik?
Our priorities in our current realistic situation...
and the future we imagined were different.
The future you two imagined.
Was it something serious, like marriage?
Marriage was one of the few.
- Really?
- Yes.
If two have totally different perspectives,
it's hard to be together.
You can't picture the future together.
Were your thoughts about it that different?
Personality-wise, I'm someone...
who can't say anything...
- that I don't mean.
- I see.
Min Kyung always brought it up.
Even when she did as a joke or in a playful way,
I told her not to in a serious tone.
- About marriage?
- Yes.
Like, "Let's get married?"
She was like, "We should get married."
But every time she said that,
I treated the situation seriously.
How?
"Don't say things like that."
- Really?
- Yes.
Nice.
He brought it up first.
- What a way to ask secretly.
- Seung Yong...
- For real.
- He's a strategist.
That's great information.
He's figuring out his enemy.
Hold on.
- Yes?
- May I come in?
(Another person has come.)
- It's Woo Jin.
- What are you doing?
- Hi.
- Chatting.
Have you seen Hyeon Ji?
Hyeon Ji? No.
- May I join?
- Of course.
In the end, everyone has gathered.
We were asking about Yoo Sik's life.
I took a shower. I was dying to wash up.
Say that Min Kyung...
is understanding of it now.
Would your feelings change?
- If Min Kyung were to understand...
- Yes.
- my situation?
- Correct.
She'll accept the situation...
- and even go along...
- Work together.
With the direction you're going.
Min Kyung might say that...
she'll understand my situation right now.
But you can't trust her.
Right. "Will she really?"
No. Beyond that,
at the end...
of a long-term relationship is marriage.
But I'm not sure if I want to get married yet.
- Right, you're too young.
- You're young.
(New dilemmas pile up as the time to choose nears.)
That talk just now was...
- Right?
- I know.
Seung Yong is smart.
- Come on.
- No wonder he's a doctor.
He set up a trap, and Yoo Sik fell for it.
- He fell for the trap.
- Imagine how Seung Yong...
will pass that on to Hyeon Ji.
- Right?
- Exactly.
Imagine how he'll exaggerate it.
- Exaggerate it a little...
- Add a bit to it and...
- Just a tad bit.
- It only needs a tiny bit.
He'd win an award right away.
- Award?
- An award?
Exaggeration is all it needs.
(Purple Room: Min Kyung and Yun Nyeong's room)
Who did you choose today?
I chose Won Kyu.
- What about you, Min Kyung?
- How honest.
Last time I talked with Woo Jin,
I said, "If we go on another date, let's eat something really good."
- So I picked Woo Jin.
- You picked Woo Jin?
- Right.
- It was the last time.
I don't think Woo Jin chose...
To be considerate of you, he wouldn't have chosen me.
- You mean, Woo Jin?
- Yes.
- Because it has to be reciprocal?
- That's possible.
Yes, it has to be reciprocal.
But I've told him once.
"Let's eat something really good."
You get to go out only when it's reciprocal.
- When will the result be out?
- Your date is confirmed.
I talked to him a moment ago.
- Did you talk to Yoo Sik?
- Yes, I did.
I think his interest in her grows the more he sees her.
- I see.
- So...
the date with your ex remains.
We still have a chance to go on a date with someone else.
I asked him, "After our date,"
"if you go on a date with Hyeon Ji again,"
"will you fall for her even more?"
The more he sees her, his interest in her grows.
Yoo Sik answered,
"Then I won't go on a date with her."
He must still have feelings for you.
- He's not completely over you.
- Based on his answer.
The fact that they went out today affected me a lot.
- Right.
- It couldn't be helped.
Everyone else was home.
- Everyone else was home.
- Only the two of them went out.
Right. It felt like...
they went on an official date.
It affected me very much.
I haven't expressed my feelings...
to someone else.
I don't know how the mutual date will turn out.
- Right, the mutual date...
- It'd have a huge impact.
If he doesn't go on the mutual date...
Hyeon Ji definitely picked Yoo Sik.
I think so too.
- I don't know whom Yoo Sik picked.
- Yoo Sik's choice...
Exactly.
Based on what he told me,
I don't think he picked her.
Later,
everyone could get together...
and take a look at the results.
If you find out that Yoo Sik is...
going out on a date with Hyeon Ji...
Yoo Sik that I know wouldn't have done that.
Right.
He said that he wouldn't.
You should've picked Baek Hyun instead.
Then you could have stayed at home with Yoo Sik.
I won't get to go out with Woo Jin.
- You never know.
- You don't know that.
- Woo Jin has no one to choose.
- You suggested him something.
You should've picked Baek Hyun instead.
I should've done that.
Until now,
I sent a text to someone different every day.
Really?
I never sent one to Yoo Sik ever since we came here.
You should send him a text if you want to get back with him.
I told her to forget about her sense of pride.
She needs to forget about her sense of pride.
I sent a text to him today.
(Today, she sent a text to Yoo Sik.)
Forget about your sense of pride if you want to get back together.
What if I have to go out with Woo Jin?
It'd be ridiculous if you went out...
- while Yoo Sik stayed home.
- Right.
What if you go out while Yoo Sik stays home?
- Are you crying?
- No, I'm not crying. Wait.
That didn't cross my mind.
- Goodness.
- What is it?
- My goodness.
- After brushing my teeth...
We got a message.
Is it about who failed to be matched?
- Did people get matched?
- No.
- Hey.
- The ones who are going out...
Who are they? Tell me.
- What is it?
- Lee Jae Hyeong, Park Ji Hyeon.
Sung Baek Hyun, Choi Yun Nyeong. Jung Won Kyu, Hong Ji Yeon.
Cho Yoo Sik, Park Hyeon Ji.
(The mutual date result)
(Yoo Sik will go on a date with Hyeon Ji.)
My gosh.
He told me that he wouldn't go out.
- Oh, no.
- Yoo Sik and Hyeon Ji?
- Wait a minute.
- Goodness.
- I knew he'd cause trouble.
- Oh, no.
I thought so too.
- He misunderstood.
- My goodness.
The words were so confusing that...
- we almost asked them to replay.
- It's a misunderstanding.
- Gosh.
- Oh, no.
Both Ji Yeon and Yun Nyeong look shocked.
- I know.
- This is real.
Oh, no. Even I'm walking on eggshells.
Goodness.
Once, I've gone around to enter.
- Did you go around here?
- Yes.
(The mutual date result)
(Park Ji Hyeon and Lee Jae Hyeong, Hong Ji Yeon and Jung Won Kyu, )
(Choi Yun Nyeong and Sung Baek Hyun, Park Hyeon Ji and Cho Yoo Sik)
(Four couples have been matched for the date.)
(The match result was also delivered to the men.)
- What is it?
- No way.
- What?
- They sent this via text?
- Gosh.
- Isn't it so cruel?
So other people weren't matched?
Still, there are four couples.
Who are the remaining people?
Woo Jin and...
- Min Kyung.
- And Seung Yong?
(Min Kyung, Woo Jin, and Seung Yong will remain.)
Gosh.
He told me that he wouldn't go out.
Gosh, I will be back.
Okay.
Isn't he out of his mind?
It's so windy. Do you see the palm trees moving?
- Let's have a drink.
- Shall we have a drink?
- Aren't you drinking?
- Wait.
Let me check something with Hyeon Ji.
Here's a thought I had...
right after receiving the text.
I can't be interested in multiple people.
Okay.
I couldn't think of anyone I wanted to go out on a date with,
so I picked Yun Nyeong.
- She wouldn't pick me anyway.
- Right.
But everyone else got matched.
Do you want to go out on a date when you want to get back together?
I really want to know. It's not because I'm upset.
- Can I respond first?
- Yes.
You and I have talked the most.
It's not that I don't want to get back with her.
Yes?
Is Yoo Sik here?
Yoo Sik.
You said that you wouldn't go out.
- Right.
- You said that you wouldn't go out.
I told them that I wouldn't go out.
When I told you that I was worried, you said you wouldn't go out.
You said that you'd think about it instead of going out,
but why are you going out?
Are you happy to make a fool out of me?
You won't go out on a date?
Did I apply to go out?
You're really awful.
You never think about me.
You never did.
Are you happy to make a fool out of me?
How did I make a fool out of you?
- You keep making a fool out of me.
- What do you mean?
You promised not to go out.
Do we have to go this far?
Is that our relationship?
What is it that you don't understand?
Did I treat you so badly?
During our preliminary meeting, did I complain to you?
You've been treating me this way because you're going with the flow.
I wasn't going with the flow.
You thought that I had no feelings for you anymore.
- You had no feelings for me.
- How would that be possible?
What did you say during the interview?
- That I wanted to meet someone new.
- Right!
Anyone can say that at first.
Yes, I understand that anyone can say that at first.
You're really terrible.
Is this why you came on the show?
To abandon me like this.
To see me get ruined.
Then why did you come on the show?
Obviously, I wanted to meet someone new.
It was also to be with you.
If we ended things badly, I wouldn't be here.
Did I ever say that I don't care about you at all?
But that's how you behave!
You keep telling me that you have feelings for me.
- When did I say that?
- You said I wasn't nothing to you.
Right, how can I not care about you?
Exactly. I mean something to you.
Then what are you doing with Hyeon Ji?
Should I have picked you instead?
It said that it wasn't allowed.
There's something you told me a while ago.
Is that why you didn't respond until the last moment?
What do you mean?
What did I not respond to?
You kept giving me hope.
Hope for what?
You said that you might want to get back with me.
I can't ignore you completely.
Then go out with Hyeon Ji.
If those nine years were nothing, go out with her.
- You've always been like this.
- What about you?
As those nine years were nothing to you,
did you want to meet someone new?
Is that why you said during the interview...
that you wanted to meet someone who treats you better than me?
As those nine years were nothing to you, you got over me?
Think about what you said before.
That's funny.
Who made me break up with you?
Do you want me to give up everything and be with you again?
What would you give up?
Do you want me to stop everything including work?
Did I ask you to give up your work?
Then what should I give up?
- Did I ask you to give up?
- What do I do other than work?
- Then what?
All I asked was to care about me a little more.
- Wasn't it because...
- All you had to do was apologize.
Wasn't it because we weren't spending enough time together?
You could've said, "I'm sorry,"
"I'll take better care of you."
Is this what you want?
Stay in the same situation and get back together...
while you get hurt by me? Is that what you want?
I've told you many times that I don't want to lose you.
Exactly.
You've gotten hurt by me a lot.
That's why we broke up.
Do you want us to be together under the same circumstances?
So you have no intention to make things better?
- For us to get back together, - You don't want to be with me.
What do I have to give up?
I just need you to care about me a little more.
Did I not care about you when we were in a relationship?
I worked hard and cared about you,
but we couldn't spend much time together.
Do you want us to spend more time together?
Then shouldn't I give up my work?
- I didn't ask you that.
- Then what?
I just want you to care more about me.
How can I care more about you?
Isn't it spending more time with each other?
Even when I went on dates with other people,
I didn't forget about our time together.
- And I forgot?
- You already forgot.
- I already told Hyeon Ji about it.
- You forgot about it.
- I told Hyeon Ji about it.
- Yoo Sik, you forgot about it.
A period of nine years isn't short.
I can't say that I don't care about Min Kyung.
It's not short?
- It's half of your life.
- It's long.
It's long.
It's long for me too.
You're precious to me too.
- But...
- I didn't say...
that I didn't care about you.
Come back here.
Come back. You're getting wet from the rain.
Let me go.
I don't want to talk here.
(Yoo Sik comes back with some tissue.)
Wipe off your tears.
Once I leave here, I'll never see you again.
I refuse to see you.
Will that be okay?
What did I do so wrong?
Come here and talk.
I didn't say that you did something wrong.
What did I do so wrong...
- that you fall for someone easily?
- That's not what I'm saying.
When did I fall for someone easily?
It seems that way to me.
It seems like you fell for someone easily.
That's what you think, but it's not true.
That's how I see it.
Just say no.
- "I don't like you." - Why would you say that?
"I don't like you anymore. Go away."
Say that to me instead.
We were together for nine years. Do you think...
that I can say that so easily?
You say that to me every day.
Hyeon Ji wants to get married.
What do you think about marriage?
You said that it's impossible with me.
Have you guys talked about that?
Am I here to get married?
That's part of the reason why we broke up.
Have you ever imagined a future with me?
- I have.
- Like what?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why should I tell you about a future...
that I'm not sure about?
What if things don't turn out the way I imagine?
What if you get hurt later?
I've already been hurt.
I've been hurt too.
How did I hurt you?
Tell me what I did so wrong.
I really want to know.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Then?
It's my fault.
(The knot gets tangled up even more.)
My lips are getting dry.
Why isn't their conversation going anywhere?
Why aren't things working out for them?
I think he still has feelings for her.
- Do you mean Yoo Sik?
- Yes.
Even if it isn't love, he might feel confused.
Is it love...
or is he just attached to her?
- Or lingering feelings.
- Right.
I don't think...
he's able to say easily how he feels.
There must be a world between them that we don't know about.
They've been together for a long time.
They're learning how to break up...
- on the show.
- I think so too.
Neither of them know how to break up.
- Let me start.
- Okay.
(The three of them are still talking.)
At first, I thought about who to pick for a long time.
I couldn't pick my ex.
Then there was Ji Hyeon.
Before sending the text,
she said that she was grateful to me and wanted to buy me a meal.
We talked about eating together, so I picked her.
I see.
- What about you?
- Me?
Isn't the question really for me?
- Is that not it?
- I'm wondering if I'm strange.
- Really?
- I wanted to know about you too.
- I...
- Okay.
First of all, she and I...
hardly got to talk lately.
- But you did. Like yesterday.
- Who?
- Well, we talked a bit.
- Didn't you guys talk today?
But it wasn't a proper conversation.
She just happened to be there when I went down for some food.
- That's it.
- Are you talking about Ji Hyeon?
- No, Ji Yeon. My ex.
- Ji Yeon.
The vibe I'm getting from her now...
is different from before.
And I'm getting close to making up my mind.
But I didn't get to have...
a serious conversation with her about that yet.
- I absolutely think you should.
- Yes. I must.
I'm not telling you this because I'm mad at you or anything.
I was just questioning myself.
I'm just seeking advice.
- I...
- I'm not upset or anything.
- I thought I should talk to her.
- I see.
You guys haven't talked about it yet.
- I...
- I thought you already did.
You have to understand that I saw you two talk yesterday...
and today.
- Hi.
- What's going on?
- Do you want to come in?
- Can I join you guys?
- Sure. Come in.
Who's here?
- It's the three of us.
- It's us. It's Jae Hyeong and me.
Oh, thanks.
There are only men here. You don't mind if I join you guys?
- It doesn't matter.
- Sure.
Anyway, so that's where you stand.
Yes, that's where I stand.
- Where do you stand?
- I thought I was the weird one.
I cleared everything with her.
So that explains my thinking process.
- Actually...
- I thought I was being weird.
You're more interested in getting back with your ex.
That's why you could do that.
- Is that so?
- That's why.
Isn't it weird how they revealed the matching results in a text?
- Right?
- Yes.
At this point,
- there are no secrets.
- Right. It doesn't matter.
- What? About our feelings?
- So it's out in the open.
No. I mean, yes. That too.
- I'm talking about messages too.
- Right.
No one's hiding their feelings now.
- Everything...
I've never shared my feelings.
You've never shared your feelings. I have no idea how you feel.
I'm sorry.
My goodness. I should go...
- and talk to my ex too.
- I'm sorry. Don't leave.
My gosh.
I'll step out for a moment.
(Everyone is confused by the news of their ex's date.)
(He feels awkward around his ex and her date.)
Pretend I'm not here. You guys can just talk.
- What? No.
- That's unnecessary.
I'm going on a date with Jae Hyeong tomorrow.
Right.
You guys can talk. I'll leave.
- Why don't you leave?
- Okay.
- Why are you really leaving?
- I'm serious. Go on and talk.
By the way, whose room is this?
It's mine.
Hold on. Is Baek Hyun talking...
to Yun Nyeong?
- Probably. You have no place to go.
- Right?
And Woo Jin went to talk to her.
(Even if he leaves, he has no place to go.)
I have no place to go.
But once Jae Hyeong and I start talking,
you'll find out about our secret.
- What?
- If you listen to our conversation,
you will hear...
about what happened between us before coming here.
- What happened between you two?
- Yes.
- What happened between us?
- Well, it doesn't matter.
- We...
It doesn't matter? My gosh. You must be so open-minded.
You don't mind hearing about Ji Yeon and me, right?
- Actually, I don't want to hear it.
- Really?
I'm very jealous.
I get jealous too.
Okay. So I get it. Where should I go now?
I don't know. I'll go and wander around. Go on.
(Won Kyu steps out while leaving them in the room.)
Cheers.
I wasn't...
interested in getting back with my ex when I moved in.
Right.
I was hoping that they wouldn't be so focused on their ex.
Same here.
But I'm getting the feeling that they're a lot more focused...
on getting their ex back than I anticipated.
I see.
You should've moved in early, actually.
What about you? Where do you stand on getting back with your ex now?
Cheers.
No comment?
Getting back together with my ex...
is tough.
Of course.
Getting back together with my ex means...
considering a lot more things than starting a new relationship.
When I first moved in,
- I expressed my interest in you.
- Yes.
We talked and went on a date.
Afterward, I thought I should take more initiative.
Then that's when they informed us that we were going to Japan.
I see. But for my date, I chose...
You chose Seung Yong.
- Right.
- When that happened,
I was disappointed.
That was all.
This is why timing is important.
Totally.
It's been a while since Ji Hyeon and I talked.
I will have to talk to her more and go on more dates with her...
to see if I can develop more romantic feelings for her.
But despite that, she's special to me.
I thought things might change if she and I talked one more time.
And I hoped that it would.
(They carefully try to align their missed connections.)
(Won Kyu braves through the storm and comes out.)
(He's visiting Baek Hyun and Yun Nyeong.)
(Can I come in?)
Come on in.
(He gets permission to enter.)
Right. Appearance draws attraction.
I was drawn to you.
Really?
- If you say I'm not your...
- I'm not sure if I can join you.
- Come on in. Please sit.
- Sure.
(They warmly welcome Won Kyu who has no place to go.)
I was drawn to you.
But you said I wasn't your ideal type.
When I told you my ideal type, I was just really detailed.
I don't think I should sit next to you guys.
(He shamelessly sits next to the happy couple.)
Who were you with until now?
It was the three of us. Jae Hyeong, Ji Hyeon, and me.
You thought you shouldn't be there, so you left to join another group.
Yes. I just left the room.
Why? You left Ji Hyeon and Jae Hyeong alone?
- Yes. I just...
- Ji Hyeon...
Ji Hyeon...
Exactly.
(At the same time, Woo Jin came to Ji Yeon's room.)
It's hard to understand everyone's feelings.
Then why did you pick Won Kyu...
when you texted me?
On tomorrow's date, I'm going to tell Won Kyu...
that I want to focus my time and energy on figuring out...
whether I can or even want to get back together with you.
You guys still haven't had that talk yet?
- No.
- I see.
I'm going to stay here.
Isn't it raining outside? Isn't it humid there?
Do you want to sit here? So you're comfortable?
So you're going on a date tomorrow to have that talk?
I wouldn't say that's the only reason.
Okay.
- Won Kyu was the only one...
- I...
I could pick other than you.
But you texted me yesterday...
- and today.
- Yes.
You've been spending time with me.
So I assumed...
you would either get back together with me...
- or not date anyone else.
- I see.
- But I wanted...
- You...
to go on a date with him, so I could end everything.
- So I find that ridiculous.
- I wanted to say goodbye.
I can't understand that.
Ji Yeon, when you told me that I wanted to talk to Min Kyung,
you said I didn't need to go on a date to do that.
You said I could easily talk to her.
- You...
- You told me...
you were certain that you wanted to get back together with me.
- Yes.
- Right.
Aren't you going to have that talk because you're certain too?
I'm certain now, so I'm going to talk to him.
Right. Then do you have to go on a date to have that talk?
Let's say you're certain about me and want to tell him how you feel.
It doesn't have to be a date.
You can even tell him tonight...
or tomorrow morning. There are many ways to go about it.
I didn't think that far.
- I... Yes.
- That's what you told me.
But your actions tell a different story.
I thought you wouldn't go on a date.
But you went on the date too.
Right. So I told you I didn't think it through.
I apologized to you.
I thought going on a date with her...
I mean, I told you that because it didn't cross my mind.
But going back to what happened today,
if you seriously wanted to consider getting back together with me,
you should spend more time with me.
Isn't that the way to find out if this is what you want?
- I understand your point.
- Yes.
I get it. But that didn't occur to me.
- I've been telling you that.
- Okay.
So in my opinion, you have double standards.
- Yes. I think I was wrong.
- Yes.
- I do have double standards.
- Are you mad that I brought it up?
- No, I'm not mad.
It sounded like you were mad.
Part of me thought that...
she might be going on a date to have that talk.
But she could've done that in the house.
Was going on a date necessary?
(Woo Jin comes out alone to the communal area.)
All the tough moments I had to deal with alone...
since moving into the house in Pyeongchang-dong came over me.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
Gosh, this is so annoying.
Come on.
Go away, please.
Could you leave me alone, Ji Yeon?
I'll stay next to you.
But I won't look at you.
(It's not easy to calm his emotions.)
(And the conversation between Yoo Sik and Min Kyung isn't over.)
Just tell me why you wanted...
to go on a date with her after the conversation we had.
You said you wouldn't go on a date. Why did you pick her?
I naturally thought that you wouldn't pick her.
Okay. I'm sorry about that.
Why did you do that?
- I just did.
- So why?
I just thought I should since it said I couldn't pick you.
But let me be honest with you.
If I could pick you for the date, I would have picked you.
You didn't think that I would be bothered by it?
Don't you remember our conversation?
Yes? Yoo Sik.
When we were having that conversation earlier,
if you said no...
and you would do what you wanted,
I wouldn't have said anything to you now.
But you said you wouldn't.
You wouldn't have said anything?
Even if I said no,
you wouldn't have moved until you got the answer you wanted.
You always say this to every decision I make.
"Had you done that, I would've done this."
That's what you always say.
If I told you not to intervene with my decisions,
you would've let me?
You would've been okay with that?
That's not you.
After what you promised me earlier,
you should follow through on your promise.
You said you wouldn't go on a date, but why did you pick her?
Why did you do that?
You knew I would find out.
- Yes.
- Why did you do that?
I told you earlier.
You clearly expressed how you felt.
And I clearly told you where I stood.
But we keep talking about the same thing over and over again.
So I asked you to give me some time to think it over more seriously.
But you're going on a date tomorrow. Will you have time to think?
I will.
I'm curious about why you chose to go on a date with Hyeon Ji...
after everything you told me earlier.
Why did you pick Hyeon Ji?
(The two of them are getting tired of repeating the same conversation.)
When are you leaving tomorrow?
At 9am.
Good for you. You have time to go on a date.
Min Kyung, stop it.
Stop what?
I feel so sorry for myself.
That's why I can't help but ask you repeatedly...
what I did so wrong.
You didn't do anything wrong.
What have I done so wrong that...
- You didn't do anything wrong.
- you're pushing me away?
You really didn't do anything wrong.
Tell me.
I'll wait until you give me an answer.
An answer about what?
About what you want to tell me.
I told you earlier. I needed time to think about this.
I kept your side for all these years.
But you met her only a week ago.
So think about if it even makes sense to compare me to her.
I told you I would seriously think about that.
Besides, this act of dedication wasn't one-sided.
- What?
- I also kept your side too.
- I'm grateful for that.
- This was our relationship.
- Thank you for that.
- This relationship of nine years...
- wasn't one-sided.
- I told you I was grateful for it.
Because I'm very grateful to you,
I can't move on from you.
I get it. You told me about your feelings...
over the past few days now. So I get it.
If you let go of my hand,
it really is over.
All that time we spent together will go in vain.
I want you to be sorry for the rest of your life.
Let's end it.
(Just like that, their conversation ended.)
Why did you tell Min Kyung that I was going on a date yesterday?
Right.
- Well... I can't?
- Don't tell anyone.
I was only telling her...
Just do your best and mind your own business.
Why would you tell Min Kyung?
- "They're going out." - That will upset her.
I only said, "I heard they were going out."
- Is Jae Hyeong outside?
- Yes.
Where did Jae Hyeong go?
- He's in another room.
- What?
He's in a different room.
(Green Room: Seung Yong and Jae Hyeong's room)
So? How do you feel?
You didn't look so happy earlier.
Why can't I hide that I'm upset?
Why? Something happened?
- Then why?
- Nothing happened.
I just have a lot on my mind.
What's bothering you? Can you tell me?
- Seriously.
- What?
You want to choose Yoo Sik,
but he won't give you reassurance?
So I'm pretty bothered.
- Like what?
- The things you said.
- The practical matters?
- He's not open enough...
to talk about them.
So I can't talk to him about it.
You should've talked to him indirectly.
Talk to him about what indirectly?
About the details. Like...
Whatever's on your heart.
For example, "When do you plan to get married?"
Even if I say that indirectly...
Why?
You do have a point though.
But...
the problem is solved if you get married late.
I like someone who gives me reassurance.
It's hard.
So I'm making myself clear.
But I don't like it when you put it like that.
- Like what?
- Like now.
- The way you talk.
- As if I'm showing off?
No, the way you talk.
What's wrong with the way I talk?
You're not soft.
I'll talk softly.
It wasn't...
exactly what I expected.
I can tell that you thought about it a lot.
Okay.
But I'm not sure if you'd change.
I'm different from who I used to be.
I wonder if that's possible...
I think it is.
How long is that going to last?
If I give you a hard time, you might change again.
This is what I think.
You admit...
that I'm an endeavoring romanticist.
But can you do that?
Why not? It's simple.
I couldn't do it. But if you think about it,
it can be resolved.
Will you look me in the eyes?
It's true that I didn't express myself enough.
If I expressed myself...
and embraced you,
this wouldn't have happened.
That's what I said.
Why didn't you express it when it didn't cost money or time?
At the time, I wasn't aware...
of the essence of the issue.
From your perspective,
I might be late.
But you're capable of endeavoring?
I told you.
One can change.
I can still afford to make an effort.
I'm sorry, but let me use the restroom.
- Of course.
- Go ahead.
Let's talk outside.
- No, I'm going out. One second.
- Okay.
You can stay.
(Hyeon Ji and Seung Yong move to the 1st floor.)
- Do you want to talk here?
- Let's talk here.
This roll cake is really good.
There's one more. Do you want more?
There's one more?
(The endeavoring romanticist gets up immediately.)
(Ji Yeon and Woo Jin are still in the lounge.)
(He quickly covers his tears when he hears someone walking.)
(Rushing himself as it seems serious)
(Escaping quickly)
What's the blanket for? Are you cold?
No, I grabbed it from the room.
In case you were cold.
- Okay.
- I'm not cold.
(Showing her what he learned)
Is that the one?
- Look.
- You were this witty?
What?
This is unbelievable.
I thought about what I could do for you.
Then I came up with this.
(The born romanticist appears.)
Are you going to tell Yoo Sik again?
Why are you down all of a sudden?
What?
Is Yoo Sik bothering you? Do you want to go up?
Why go up?
- To the room.
- Why?
Why would I go up when he's bothering me?
To show him that you stopped talking to me.
I'm going to talk to him.
To Yoo Sik?
When he sees this, he'll be bothered.
I wouldn't be bothered.
He looked bothered.
So...
Let's go. Let's see what time we have to leave tomorrow.
Is Jae Hyeong sleeping?
- It's hot.
- Gosh, that's too much.
Seung Yong is doing his best.
- He's trying everything he can.
- Yes.
He admits what he lacks.
- That's a new type.
- I know. That's new.
- On EXchange.
- He sticks to his plan.
But is Hyeon Ji swayed?
If there is more time and composure,
I'd say she'll definitely be swayed.
I think it's the perfect timing.
- I know.
- She saw Yoo Sik...
- feeding Min Kyung meat.
- Right.
- Yes.
- She saw it.
The wit and kind act...
- Is her standard too low?
- Hyeon Ji mentioned...
He can overcome that hurdle with effort easily.
But it's hard to stick to the basics.
Unless you're aware of it,
you don't know you have to do that.
- Right. Because you don't know.
- That's why it's hard.
- Hyeon Ji, is that you?
- Yes, but I'm leaving again soon.
To do what?
What?
You don't need to leave.
- What are you going to do?
- I want to go out.
- If you're wandering around...
- I want to talk to Yoo Sik.
Sure. Then I'll let you leave.
- What are you doing here anyway?
- What?
Are you still talking?
He's feeble-minded right now.
I think I'm drunk.
I think Seung Yong saw you.
- He didn't.
- He did.
What could he see when I didn't do anything?
You were covering your face with a pillow.
- Me?
- You...
Anyway, what did he see?
- What?
- I'm drunk.
- Did you kiss?
- Are you crazy?
- What?
- That's crazy.
I'm suddenly getting a runny nose.
- What have you done?
- Hey.
I suddenly had a runny nose.
- What...
- That's ridiculous.
- What were you doing?
- Hyeon Ji.
You're pretty funny.
- I had no idea.
- Is it that funny?
What are you saying?
Gosh, you're funny.
That's hilarious.
I'll let you talk.
"Kissed?"
I didn't see that coming.
You said you made a mistake.
It wasn't a mistake.
I'll let you talk. I might...
- come back soon.
- Okay.
Or late.
It's okay to be back soon.
(Hyeon Ji visits Yoo Sik's room.)
(The room is quiet.)
(Won Kyu and Yoo Sik are already sleeping.)
Please.
Seriously?
- Seung Yong. What?
- What?
Where's Jae Hyeong?
I don't know. Isn't he in the other room?
I think it's empty.
Really? I'm not sure.
(Yoo Sik got changed.)
Why didn't you come out when you were in the room?
Why didn't you come out?
- Were you sleeping?
- No, I was just lying down.
- You were lying down?
- Didn't you ring the bell...
only once?
- Yes.
- I came out right away.
- What?
- I came out after getting changed.
- Did you?
- Yes.
I went to ask where you were.
We were just lying down.
- What? This?
- Yes.
- For you.
- You don't need it tomorrow?
Tomorrow? I'm not sure. Keep it for now.
You can keep it. I don't need it.
- No?
- Tomorrow morning...
- Did you cry?
- I didn't.
- What?
- I didn't cry.
(What did you do?)
What?
Why are you still up?
I'll go to bed soon.
I saw you walking back and forth a lot.
- Me?
- Yes.
Back and forth? On the first floor?
Yes, and you were talking a lot.
Didn't you...
talk more?
What are you saying?
Woo Jin and Ji Yeon are talking in my room.
Now?
Really?
What are you going to do?
(Clacking)
- Are you drinking?
- We're sleeping.
Won Kyu is sleeping.
Really? Goodnight.
Where did Jae Hyeong go?
Jae Hyeong is with Baek Hyun.
- Okay.
- All right.
Why?
Come here.
See you tomorrow.
What time are you going to be up?
Seven?
Seven.
(Hyeon Ji shows the ring on her finger.)
I wondered what it was.
Because I couldn't see.
Behind you...
Never mind. It's hair.
What?
I can't see. Don't look at me.
- Were you in your pajamas?
- Me?
You should get some sleep.
Later...
Sorry.
(EXchange 4)
- Min Kyung.
- Yes?
- I have a question.
- Okay.
Seung Yong wants to get back with me.
He was talking about getting married to change my mind.
And...
you said you broke up for practical reasons.
What are they exactly?
(Staying single.)
(Staying single?)
(And)
(The night of the truth begins.)
What if...
(If your ex tried to sway you with her sincerity, )
(would you have been swayed?)
He didn't seem certain.
It can be changed.
Let me ask Yoo Sik.
If I'm pouring my heart out to Hyeon Ji,
are you still going to keep going?
Baek Hyun's bothered a lot.
The answer didn't choose either one.
(The situation might change.)