♪Standing in their eagerly sought trap♪
♪Learning to deduce meticulously
like Sherlock Holmes♪
♪Traces at the scene♪
♪Pointing to the elusive phantoms♪
♪The heart consumed♪
♪Leaving only ripples
before disappearing♪
♪You see that ambition
begins to take shape♪
♪The body can only surrender♪
♪Numbness in the feet
initiates a mutation♪
♪Waiting for time♪
♪To reveal the truth♪
[Undercover Affair]
[Adapted from "You Are My Only Star"
by Zong Gong Da Ren]
[Episode 18]
Don't
flatter yourself.
You have absolutely no use
to me anymore.
No.
I...
Tai,
she's not completely worthless.
This girl is quite attractive.
Why don't you
keep her for yourself?
After all, she's Sen's woman.
You want me to eat Sen's leftovers?
You keep the leftovers
for yourself.
Thank you, Tai.
Tai, please reconsider it.
Now,
you're mine.
Don't touch me.
Sen.
It's alright.
It's alright now.
Let's go.
Sen.
Where are you going?
Tai.
So many people, huh?
There's no need
to be so ruthless, right?
I'm being ruthless?
You two have been acting in front of me
from start to finish.
And you say that I'm being ruthless?
I...
Stop posing here, attack them!
Tai!
Stop!
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Lingyi,
listen to me now, alright?
You go home immediately,
don't go anywhere else,
and don't ask anything.
If the police come looking for you,
don't be afraid,
just cooperate with them, okay?
Okay.
Lingyi,
I voted for Elena but it doesn't mean
that I don't care about you.
I know.
Didn't I say it already?
You need to do the right thing.
And
I really appreciate
you coming to rescue me today.
Alright,
go now.
Wait for me to come back.
Mm.
What are you doing?
Sen,
you're finally back.
I'm glad you're okay.
What do you mean 'okay'?
Of course, I'm fine.
I can't figure out
how Tai got caught.
What's so hard to understand?
Scar got caught,
and he ratted Tai out to the cops.
It's pretty straightforward.
Plus, he gets a chance to plea bargain.
Could you two please come with us?
We need your cooperation
for an investigation.
Tai got away.
Scar ratted him out, right?
Yes.
Scar confessed that he and Tai
conspired to assassinate Kun.
We were trying to get in touch with you
while we were chasing Tai,
but we couldn't reach you.
Tell me,
what's the next step of the plan?
We've already sent people
to apprehend him
and conducted a search of his house.
And we did find something of value.
But...
But what? Tell me.
But we found out
that a large portion
of the cases
related to the Kuntai Group
were not orchestrated by Kun and Tai.
So...
So who could it be?
Elena.
She destroyed the evidence
before you arrived.
Dang it.
Sen,
it looks like you'll have to go back
and continue searching for evidence
against her.
We'll definitely assist you
in any way we can.
However, she must be very cautious now,
so there probably won't be
any new transactions for a while.
If you need anything,
we'll definitely...
Kun is already dead,
and Tai has run away.
As for me,
have you ever considered my life?
Get me a cigarette!
We are not allowed to smoke here.
I can at least have some gum, right?
After these years
of living on the edge,
your tastes have become refined, huh?
Once you finish your mission,
let's see how you can return
to a life of simplicity.
Here.
Come on.
Leave it to me.
Hey,
but honestly,
I quite enjoy living this simple life.
I don't really want
that kind of wealth and luxury.
If...
if we could swap our lives,
would you be willing to do it?
I'm off to solve the case.
Sen,
stay safe.
I didn't expect this opportunity
to come so soon.
Tai ran away,
and I've pinned everything
I could on him.
Let's go.
Here,
have some water.
Thanks.
You can leave
after completing the formalities.
Leave?
Yes, I'll leave.
You've worked hard
taking care of Sen recently.
Actually, I didn't do anything.
And I almost became a liability to him
several times.
What makes you say that?
Sen has always praised
how clever you are to me.
But now that Tai is on the run,
if we don't catch him,
none of us will be safe.
I'll be careful too.
Mm.
♪Standing in their eagerly sought trap♪
♪Learning to deduce meticulously
like Sherlock Holmes♪
♪Traces at the scene♪
♪Pointing to the elusive phantoms♪
♪The heart consumed♪
♪Leaving only ripples
before disappearing♪
♪No one can evade
the murky grasp of desire♪
♪The more I resist,
the more entangled I become♪
♪Walking into the mist,
the sight gradually becomes unclear♪
♪Is that your silhouette?♪
♪Or my reflection
on the water's surface♪
♪You see that ambition
begins to take shape♪
♪The body can only surrender♪
♪Both feet slowly leave the ground♪
♪Catching up
with the boiling rebellious soul♪
♪You hear thoughts clamor incessantly♪
♪Can only cover the eyes instinctively♪
This is a Sad Frog.
Anyone who owns it
will have their sadness
and worries taken away by it.
♪Waiting for time♪
♪To reveal the truth♪
Miss,
why are you still sitting out here
on such a cold day?
♪Catching up
with the boiling rebellious soul♪
Thank you.
♪You hear thoughts clamor incessantly♪
♪Can only cover the eyes instinctively♪
Let's go.
♪Nature has already begun to mutate♪
♪Waiting for time♪
♪To reveal the truth♪
♪Trap♪
♪Ambition begins to take shape♪
♪Can only surrender♪
♪Slowly leave♪
♪Rebellious soul♪
♪Thoughts clamor incessantly♪
♪Can only cover the eyes♪
♪Already mutated♪
♪Time reveals the truth♪