I have no reason to go
unless it's a top performance at a top stage.
Make that happen if you want me to go.
Have you not gotten over it yet?
Almighty Cha, it's okay.
Just do what we did at the rehearsal.
It's okay, Cha Yoo Jin!
You were wrong.
These are the friends
who made me feel like the best
when I wasn't the best.
You were wrong again.
Showing my heart was not a weakness.
It returned with another heart.
There are so many of them.
You called me here
with an excuse of Seol Nae Il
but the reason is Dr. Kim?
I heard Cha Dong Woo came by
to see your concert yesterday.
He'll flip
Sun Young's heart upside down again
with your problem.
He's been doing that all along.
I'm sorry.
It's been a while
since you went to Dr. Kim, right?
Will you just waste time?
Try as hard as you can,
but when things don't work out,
you should learn to give up.
Raise your left arm
as high as your shoulder.
It should feel heavy
as if you're holding a dictionary.
Now, we're going back
to when you were 10 years old.
Cha Yoo Jin, you're on a plane.
What happened?
Gymnopedie. I like this music, too.
This was when Sunbae was little, right?
He looks exactly the same as now.
But I guess he wasn't afraid of water then.
Do you know about that?
Pardon?
I guess...
Well, this is the first time
Yoo Jin brought his girlfriend.
I didn't know he'd really bring you here
just because I told him.
If you're that close,
I guess you should know.
About what?
About Yoo Jin's accident.
The plane accident.
Uncle!
What are you doing right now?
I...
can't go study abroad.
I can't get on a plane or a ship.
Isn't it funny?
You can mock me.
Why?
Trauma from the plane accident.
I was dropped to the sea wearing a life vest.
Since then, I can't get on a plane or a ship.
Does that mean you can't go study abroad?
It's not that you are not going.
You can't go?
You wanted to go study abroad.
Why are you about to cry? I didn't even cry.
I wasn't going to cry.
Why would you cry over this?
It's no big deal.
Bye.
Sunbae.
You don't just want to go home, do you?
Gymnopedie.
The music taught me
that simplicity can be plentiful.
Is this from the composer's wish,
for the audience
to soak to the music comfortably.
You're working hard
to comfort me, Seol Nae Il.
Your event for me
was playing the piano for me?
You like it when I play the piano.
And I heard
your grandfather liked this music, too.
It's Professor's watch.
When did you receive this?
Before Milch was dragged to Germany.
No wonder he was calling you "Baby, Baby".
He really likes you.
I like it
because it feels warmer than new ones.
Have you tried hypnotherapy?
I tried everything.
I heard it could last a lifetime...
and it's true.
I saw it on TV, too.
Using this to induce hypnosis.
It's about focus.
Maybe it's a scam.
When someone said,
"You're falling asleep, asleep,"
and they really fell asleep.
Yes, I heard hypnosis is easy
if the person trusts the partner.
Maybe it's because I can't trust people?
You are sleepy, you are sleepy.
Sunbae, are you asleep?
Sunbae.
You didn't fall asleep for real, did you?
Wake up.
You were asleep.
What do you mean?
I've been awake the whole time.
I'm thirsty.
Do I really have to get rid of this?
What's so scary about this fan?
You didn't know?
A lot of students are scared of it.
They are all just lazy.
This is the symbol of my education.
I taught many students with this fan
and sent them off to competitions.
Our school students are really nice.
Even elementary students these days
upload a video of getting flicked
and report the incident.
What?
How about this?
We had a bet
over Cha Yoo Jin's duet performance, right?
I haven't told you the condition
from that bet yet.
That was ages ago.
I'll tell you now.
Hide your fan for a while, please.
She needs compliments more than the fan.
What do I do?
♪ I woke up this morning
and went to the bathroom ♪
♪ If I push hard,
I'll get a good bowl movement ♪
Would you like some cookies?
I received the score yesterday.
I mean, the Fart Song.
I was surprised. It has its charm.
It flows with the player's emotions
and it has a good structure, too.
How about completing the Fart Song with me?
The Fart Song?
Can you come closer?
One step.
One step closer.
See? I don't have the fan.
I've wanted to tell you this for a long time.
Yes?
It's not the 'Fart' Song.
It's the 'Gas' Song.
Gas?
Fart' has a murky smell,
but 'Gas' has a cheerful smell.
Fart or Gas, they both smell!
I see. It is really a cheerful smell.
Should we play the Fart...
I mean, the Gas Song?
Here, have a seat.
It's so hard.
- You should give in this time.
- No.
I've been giving in many times,
so you should give in this time.
I said no!
Mini Min Hee!
Do they actually like you
or are they just competitive?
They spend more time fighting with each other
than following you around.
Make your decision soon.
I don't like either of them.
I already told them.
And they're still like that?
- No!
- You give in!
Shouldn't we go and stop them?
They're okay.
I guess they just don't have anything to do.
My Shi Won is wearing a skirt.
Be careful when you're wearing a skirt.
She's wearing it in a million years,
so what would she know?
Be careful. You're ruining my eyes.
I wouldn't be wearing this,
unless I'm seeing my grandpa.
If you feel uncomfortable, cover with this.
Okay, thank you.
Don't mention it. Hello? What's up?
Hello? What's going on?
Did you see him answering the phone?
Yoo Il Lak has a peculiar style.
He's still like that
even knowing the real Jung Shi Won?
Leave him alone.
He's willing to sacrifice himself
for all the male in the world.
Hey!
I'm so stupid.
I don't want
to suggest a drug treatment to you.
Let's think about other options.
By the way,
do you really want to get it treated?
When I saw you for hypnotherapy,
you seem content with your current state.
It's Yoon Hoo!
- Is it Yoon Hoo?
- Yes.
Is it a group text?
A group text is all we get?
What's the attached file?
There are so many pretty noonas here.
I believe everyone is doing well?
I miss you.
Where is he?
It looks like Juilliard, right?
Maybe he won't come to Han Eum anymore.
He wouldn't leave without a word like this.
I'm disappointed.
Pretty noonas?
I'm so jealous. He is really in Heaven.
Yoon Hoo! Thanks for the snack.
Thank you! Just tell me anytime, noona.
What brought you here?
You came to visit me, by any chance?
No, it's a coincidence. Not a very happy one.
By the way,
since when was I on your friends' list?
Were you the one
who called on the day of surgery?
What?
"A friend I don't know the name of."
So this is you.
Why do you have to hide about that hand?
You're doing a good job of hiding it, too.
I don't need to go around tell them.
Me too.
I don't want
my friends to look at me and feel despair.
I only want to show them
the bright side of me.
Carrying it alone wasn't that great.
It's up to you since it's your choice.
You're surprisingly nosy.
Still, thank you for stopping me
from performing the duet.
We paid back each other's debt with this.
A clean relationship without debt issues.
I didn't have anything
I owed or wanted from you in the first place.
Bye.
I know.
I didn't want any debt
in a mediocre friendship.
So that's great.
- Orabang!
- Almighty Cha!
- Yoo Jin!
It's my fault.
Lak, what did I tell you?
Professor, now I added chords
as you told me to,
it feels much more urgent.
Let's go.
Sforzando!
Yes, the big event ended just now.
Of course. After that, 'tempo rubato.'
Shouldn't we go with a free style?
That's a great idea!
Professor, you finally grasped
the essence of gas.
It's nothing.
Should we go back to the beginning?
Go!
It really is a good song.
The structure is great, too.
Professor Ahn, this is indeed
like a treasure.
But what about the ending I helped?
The final stop of the long Fart Song.
The majestic spectacle
that meets with a powerful bowl movement!
Bravo!
Professor.
Good job.
Thank you.
It's been a long time
since I had a fun lesson.
I had forgotten about all this fun
for a while.
Let's work on "Fluffy Fluffy" starting tomorrow.
I'll prepare...
Professor, hold on.
Why? You don't want to?
I heard you prepared it with Professor Ahn.
Professor, until when
will you just play around?
Shouldn't we get ready for the competition?
What?
We should get ready
for the Baek Geon Soo Competition.
I'm requesting lessons
to prepare
for the competition starting tomorrow.
Competition?
Bravo!
Dean.
Yoo Jin!
What is it about?
I have a really good news.
Oh, you don't like being in the media.
But I'd like you to appear this time
since the conductor is the main focus.
Is it really necessary?
Think about it.
It's a chance to let people know
that Rising Star is
the official Han Eum Orchestra.
To the melody of classical music.
I'd like to request
that Rising Star members participate
in the filming.
Dean Song Mi Na.
Oh, filming?
All the TV station cameras
were swarming last time,
and they're coming this week!
We're finally national!
My father would pass out
if he knew I'd be on TV!
He'll be really happy.
Being on TV what's so great
about showing your face on TV?
It'll be great promotion for us.
Then so many people will be there for us.
That's awesome!
This program is known to connect performers
with major label and recording studios.
Son Soo Ji got a contract
through this program, too.
Really?
She got a contract with Lusa
after this program.
Lusa? Really?
Then our soloist albums
will be possible, too.
That's where my idol oboe soloist
had his contract, too.
What if they attack us to get a contract?
It'll be a big success for all of us!
It's my dad!
Me too! Me too!
Sorry.
It would be nice if I could participate.
But I have to go to Europe right away.
You're an idol of classical music,
so you're busy.
You'll get there soon.
"Move aside, idols.
Conductor-idol is coming.
The conductor
who plays the biggest instrument,
an orchestra."
That will be a frame used for you.
That's horrifying.
How long will you stay here?
Do you really plan to stay here
until RS is settled?
I started it.
It's just strange.
There are a lot of instruments in the world
that you want to play.
Don't you want to play those instruments?
The real orchestras in the world.
Are we close enough
to talk about this kind of stuff?
You're being so formal.
Think about it.
A lot of orchestras are interested in you.
Sunbae!
Why are you here?
I heard you went abroad for your concerts.
Looking at you,
I don't want to leave anymore.
Should I just stay here?
What? Why?
If you can't see me, will you leave?
I'm going to hide!
I'm hiding!
Why are you so cute?
Do you want to come with me?
No.
Aren't you leaving? You said you were busy.
Why are you on alert?
See you next year. I'll stop by.
Sunbae.
There are a lot of instruments in the world
that you want to play.
Don't you want to play those instruments?
Hey! Seol Nae Il!
Hurry up! We're having a meeting.
Sunbae, let's hurry.
The real orchestras in the world.
Let's go with Trumpet Concerto by Haydn.
I can do it.
No, we should go with a violin concerto.
What about a contrabass concerto?
Let's just go with a oboe concerto.
I can do it, too.
There is a timpani concerto, too.
You're getting too greedy for the TV program.
A performance as a soloist at the S level?
It will just be a big humiliation
at the concert and on the program.
Who's S and who is A? We're all Rising Star.
Yes, all of us are good now.
That's only when you piggyback on our sound.
- What?
- That's all you can say?
You're too mean.
Did I say something wrong?
That's enough.
Let's have the meeting at another time.
Sunbae!
Sunbae, you have such charisma!
You ended it in one swing.
A and S seemed to get along,
but there they go again.
They'll stop soon. Don't worry about it.
I think it'll be pretty bad this time.
Everyone has high expectations
for the TV program.
I guess their future depends on it.
What?
You're like a dad worried about his children.
Dad?
And I'm a mom.
The mom who is not worried
about the children,
but who is preparing for a competition.
Staying as the mascot is...
Competition?
You decided to go for the competition??
Yes. Pat me on the back.
Isn't it too soon?
Just think about what you'll get me
when I win the competition.
Seol Nae Il is getting ahead
of herself again.
It's not that easy.
S kids don't know their place.
Who made the RS concert a success?
There isn't anyone good enough
to be a soloist over there.
They are just being greedy.
We performed with Son Soo Ji.
A soloist among those losers?
Our level is dropping.
Besides, it's filming for a TV program.
It is a good chance
to get your name out there as a soloist.
You can't pick that one.
A kids are talking behind our back.
- These punks...
- We don't care about A anymore.
They keep looking down on us.
If a soloist is picked from one of us,
they'd rather leave.
What the heck is this?
They lost rationality
over the thought of soloist.
Nerds!
Should we break it off?
Should we?
Seriously...
That shouldn't happen.
Stop, everyone.
Let's decide on the soloist first.
That's right.
Don't be stubborn about your own parts.
Let's consider the skills first.
That's of course us.
The visual part is also important
since it'll be on TV.
This face will work on TV.
Yes, that's right.
If you go on TV with those faces,
you'll gain a million anti-fans in no time.
S is for the visual.
Stop it! I don't even want to be soloist.
Yes, let's at least respect each other.
Forget it.
I don't even like sharing the practice room
with them.
If you don't like it, then leave!
That's right.
"We popped champagne too early"?
What do you mean, Franz?
About the orchestra members.
It's not necessarily good
that we got the official approval.
We needed the approval to get support.
Don't worry.
They even had a taste of fame
from the RS concert.
They'll do a good job on their own now.
If a baby who just started taking steps
tries to run,
of course he will fall.
If he is fascinated by small successes,
he misses obvious things.
I believe this is the most dangerous time.
What do you mean?
Where are you now, Dan Ya?
- Lak!
- Dan Ya!
What do I do?
Let's go.
Mini Min Hee! Hurry!
- Wait for me, Lak!
- Wait for me!
Hurry! Hurry!
- Open the door!
- They locked it.
- Is it locked?
- Yes it is.
- Hey, open the door!
- What is it?
- What's going on?
They locked the door!
They locked the door? You're not kids.
Hey, let's talk it out.
Weren't you the one
who punched in the first place?
- I don't want to share the practice room.
- Me neither.
Right?
Punch?
He was really on my nerve,
so just a little...
It was really a light one though.
Yes, I'm a witness.
A light one?
Let's block them too.
Let's do that!
Push! Push!
One, two! One, two!
Are you okay?
We have two solutions.
Choose one of the them.
First, the cause of this trouble is soloist.
We'll go with music without a soloist.
What are you saying? That's nonsense.
- No way.
- That's not right.
- Yeah.
- Second...
an open audition.
After that, pick your own soloist by voting.
There are about equal numbers of A and S,
so it won't be a problem.
Write down the names
who are good as soloists from the other team.
Then we write down the names from A members.
And we write the S loser...
We write one of their names?
We can't do that!
We can't play with those people!
If you don't want to...
we'll go with music without a soloist.
I have the right to choose the music.
If you don't like it, do whatever you want.
Don't you want to play those instruments?
The real orchestras in the world.
You picked Haydn?
Have you played it before?
No, but I was attracted to it
from the homework.
How should I say it?
It's something like a desire
to date someone with a different style
than my usual type?
Date someone within your type.
We don't even have time,
so why do you want
to pretend to act like a playgirl?
No, I want to play this one.
I don't know much about other music anyway.
And I stayed up all night to practice it.
You practiced it?
Okay, then try it.
Look at the score!
Don't get drunk in your own emotions
and make whatever sound you want!
You should cut that off!
Transfer the score onto the piano exactly!
If you go with your feeling
in the preliminary round,
you will be eliminated.
Are you saying
that there is a problem with Seol Nae Il?
All geniuses have their own timing.
If they don't know what they are born with
and don't have any opportunities
they have no choice
but to live an ordinary life.
What do you mean?
I feel like I'm forcing her into a box.
Pardon?
Seol Nae Il doesn't like playing it
the way it's in the score.
She can't forget
how she used to follow her feeling.
It may work in the final round,
but she won't be accepted
in the preliminary round.
If she can't pass the preliminary round,
what's the use of the final round?
I'm worried
that I discovered Seol Nae Il too late.
Come to my house.
What are these?
Things you need to do after your practice.
Make sure to wear the gloves.
It'll help you
if you soak your hands in warm water
before the practice.
Don't use your hands except for the piano.
No sewing machine.
You'll hurt your hands
trying to sew your own stage costume.
But, Sunbae, you heard from Professor Do.
I'm not saying
that I'm not entering the competition.
I just need to practice for a few more days.
I'm not used to following the score yet.
It's the performance completely fitted
for the judges' taste.
Can you memorize it?
Professor Do doesn't know you that well yet.
He only saw a part of your talent
and now he's in despair.
Of course he wouldn't know that it's faster
for you to hear the music than read it.
Follow the frame just for a while.
Once the world gets to know you,
then play however you want.
You played this, right?
I had free time.
You would have been be busy
preparing for the orchestra music.
I have free time in between.
Oh, my God.
Imagine that you're dating Haydn.
Then you'll want to hit each note perfectly.
It's your own style again!
The essence of music is enjoyment?
You can only enjoy as much as you know.
Don't play by your feeling. Follow the score.
It's more difficult
to follow the standard way.
Isn't that Yoon Hoo?
Lee Yoon Hoo!
- Lee Yoon Hoo!
- It's you!
- Where have you been?
- Il Lak!
When did you come back to Korea?
Are you just stopping by?
Just to say goodbye and leave?
No way.
Mini Min Hee, it's been a while.
You're still cute.
And you're still the same.
What happened?
You disappeared without a word.
Yes, you canceled the duet and disappeared.
And Nae Il didn't say anything.
The dean had a hard time handling it.
My mom also said
she was busy submitting statements.
What happened? Did you get hurt?
It's a light fracture.
I'm just being careful. It's no big deal.
It must hurt.
Are you okay? Still, it looks bad.
Are you all worried about me?
That makes me happy.
By the way, is My Nae Il busy preparing
for the competition?
- Why isn't she around?
- Yes, she's busy...
"My Nae Il"?
Yoon Hoo!
You got prettier, Nae Il.
Didn't you miss me?
I did miss you.
Still, you shouldn't do this.
I have a boyfriend.
I already know that.
By the way, you look a little different.
I heard people change when they get sick.
Are you really sick?
What happened? You said it was no big deal.
To be honest, I was really in pain then.
I'm joking.
It wasn't anything serious then.
I got a slight injury after that.
I'm just being careful, so I got a cast.
I'm happy that Nae Il is worried about me.
Now I feel like I'm back.
You've changed a lot Yoon Hoo...
[Open Audition]
Is she playing the viola or seducing a man?
Why? I like it.
Yoo Il Lak is pretty good.
But he chose Tchaikovsky
knowing that Shi Won picked
that music, right?
I guess Yoo Il Lak truly isn't interested
in being a soloist.
Yoo Il Lak, did you choose that music
knowing that Si Won picked the same one?
That way, we'll be compared.
My bandmaster is really good.
- You're such an idiot.
- Such an idiot.
We had a concert with Son Soo Ji.
There must be a lot of interest.
It should be Shi Won
with her talented skill as a RS soloist.
It's true, but I just can't stand A members.
Let's pick the soloist next week.
Everyone will need time to think.
We've roughly made the decision on the music.
With a common sense,
the result will be obvious.
Yes, the result will be obvious.
- It's a bit hot here.
- Is it?
They didn't say anything, did they?
Of course not!
All of us know our own skill level.
If we have a fair vote, it'll be the end.
All the issues will be resolved.
At this rate, which name would
the S members write down?
Who knows.
It'll be Shi Won following common sense,
but would S members pick Shi Won?
Then we can't give our votes
to one person easily.
What do you plan to do?
Shi Won is really good.
If all the votes go to her,
A will have a soloist.
- But that can't happen.
- Of course not.
I'd miss the filming
rather than handing over a soloist to A.
Then what do we do now?
Let's decide on someone who can't do well
or someone who'll give up on his own.
You don't want a soloist
from A members, do you?
Then there is only one way.
Hey.
We didn't do anything wrong,
so why are we shooting a spy movie?
You never know.
Everyone's so sensitive right now.
If we told them
that we were discussing together.
They'd call us traitors.
I thought only good things were happening,
but what's this lightening on a clear sky?
What do we do now?
That's why we should unite...
What?
- The smell.
- Huh?
Do I smell?
I brushed my teeth and I washed up.
Your hair smells nice.
I didn't wash my hair for you.
Are you coming on to me right now?
What's with that pickup line?
What pickup line?
It's not like that.
It's a bad habit to flirt with any girl.
I don't flirt with any girl. It's just you!
Because I like you,
that's why I'm flirting with you.
She's about this tall.
Or is she shorter?
Her body is about this big.
What's her size?
Is that the dress?
The dress that Nae Il will wear
to the competition.
No, not yet.
I'm not sure if Nae Il will like...
So it's the type of dress
that Nae Il might like.
Hey! Hey!
I'll get this dress.
I'll come back for a fitting.
I picked this dress first.
I said I would buy it first.
You saw that I picked it first.
You saw me there from earlier.
The one who says first has the priority.
Don't you think you went too far
by snatching the one I picked?
Your hesitation is the problem.
Snatching is not a problem?
Then, you can have it.
I can have that dress custom-made, right?
Of course.
I've been trying to say that.
No, I'll give it to him this time.
Continue to stay alarmed.
That butter boy,
why do I feel like he got stronger?
Come out to the door.
Sunbae, what's up...
I saw something pass by just now.
It's a dress!
Sunbae, this is mine?
This is for my competition?
Then would that be mine?
My goodness!
Shopping is tough.
So you made up your mind?
Yes. There is nothing to decide.
I'm transferring
to von Stresemann's conducting major.
I didn't think you'd come to Han Eum.
I'm a bit surprised.
I'll keep surprising you more.
I look forward to it.
I'll get going now.
It's Nae Il's preliminary round today.
I heard Nae Il was entering the competition.
Is it today?
That's why Cha Yoo Jin ignored my call
and left.
I'm late, too.
I might miss my Nae Il's preliminary round.
Off you go.
"My Nae Il"?
Professor, isn't this pretty?
Yoo Jin got me this dress as a gift.
Bravo!
You're talking about the dress now?
Aren't you nervous?
Remember this.
Do not get excited.
Don't follow your feeling.
You have to follow the score.
Yes.
Just follow the score. Follow the standard.
That's how Haydn becomes Haydn!
Participant No. 25, please be ready.
Yes.
- Let's go!
Why am I so nervous?
It's a rare occasion!
For you to come to the preliminary round.
Yes, I was asked by someone.
Whoever it is, he must be a big shot
to ask you to come here.
That student's name is Seol Nae Il, right?
Do you know her?
Yes, I know her well.
She ran out of my master class
on the first day.
- Really?
- I see.
Yes, just like that.
You're doing well.
Show the world now...
the pianist...
Seol Nae Il.