How about we go somewhere on Sunday?
Oh,
of course, you don't have to
if you don't want to,
and you might not be convenient.
Seriously? I'm in!
Natsukawa, lower your voice.
Oh, sorry, I got too excited.
I didn't expect you to be so happy.
Of course I'm happy,
I'll come up with a few plans!
Am I getting too carried away?
Well,
honestly, I thought you might say no.
I'm happy.
(Episode 5)
Oh!
Not many people know about this place.
Yeah, it's really nice here,
but it's empty.
Oh, no,
I wasn't looking for an empty place.
I was actually looking for a spot,
and it happened to be like this.
I know that, thank you for checking.
Alright, so first, the tent?
Yeah.
Have you ever been camping?
Never, what about you?
Me neither.
But I did extensive research for today,
This camping trip will be perfect.
Just leave it to me.
Oh!
Huh? Wait a second... I can't do it.
Is it this side?
You're right.
Okay, okay.
Ready, set, go!
Wait!
Huh? It's so hard.
Let me try.
Done.
Huh? Why is it unstable?
Maybe it's supposed to go here.
Done.
Alright.
Wow!
Huh? This is food?
- Just leave it to me!
- Yeah.
Since it's camping...
ta-da! Let's use this.
Oh, this feels so professional!
Right?
Get ready for some delicious food.
(Living With Him)
Sorry,
I couldn't get the fire going,
and I forgot to bring a lighter.
I couldn't do it either. It's fine.
- What about here?
- Sounds good.
Nice weather.
They might have a lighter.
Let me ask them real quick.
No, I'll go.
Excuse me,
do you happen to have a lighter?
- Would it be okay if we borrow it?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
- Wait,
are you from Koshien by any chance?
Ah, yes.
- Wow, it's really him!
- No wonder he seems familiar.
I've always watched you!
Thank you very much.
- Feel free to come and chat.
- We always welcome you.
- Thank you. I'll borrow it.
- Sure.
- Wow, so handsome!
- So cool!
Let's set up a tent.
Here, I borrowed it.
Thank you.
Sounds exciting.
- Huh?
- I mean, those people.
Oh, looks like someone remembers me
Koshien really is something, huh...
So?
They know you and that's it?
Oh, yeah.
I see.
Well, they were just being polite
and invited we over for a meal.
I see. And?
So I said I wanted to eat with you.
Wow!
It's ignited.
Or do you want to
eat together with them?
No, I also preferred just the two of us.
- I'll go return it.
- Wait.
I'll go.
- Natsukawa.
- Hmm?
How much should I peel?
Peel until the brown disappears.
Oh, got it.
Oops, I get nervous when
someone watches me cut.
It's fine.
Oh no.
Where should I start?
- Where should I start peeling?
- Right there.
The meat we got
this time is really good.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah, it's definitely
tastier than our usual!
- You're right!
- Right?
- Hot!
- Careful!
Hot!
It's hot!
Delicious.
Hey, can I take a picture of you eating?
Tasty, Absolutely delicious.
Let me try this.
Seafood.
I'm taking picture, smile.
Bon appétit.
Mmm, delicious.
Here.
Huh?
Huh? Seriously?
Could it be, finally,
finally,
finally...
Did I lose?
Woo!
Is this my first victory
in how many years?
As usual,
you are no good with this kind of thing.
Yeah.
For Kazuhito-kun the scaredy-cat...
Ta-da!
With these, even if ghosts show up,
you won't be scared.
You gotta have these
coming to such place.
- Right.
- Yeah.
But we don't have fire.
Ah.
Looks like they left.
Well, maybe next time.
It's like we didn't get a proper finale.
What's that supposed to mean?
Let's play one more round.
- Another round?
- Another round.
- I won't let you win this time.
- Dream on.
I want this moment to last forever.
I find myself keep thinking
about such things,
I...
By the way,
how about doing that thing tonight?
That park across from
the family restaurant
- supposedly allows fireworks.
- Sorry.
I have a drinking party
that I mentioned tonight.
- Oh, right, sorry, I forgot.
- No, it's fine.
What time do you think you'll be back?
I'm not sure,
but I'll try to come back
as soon as possible.
No, it's okay, have fun.
What are you going to do?
Maybe I'll make some pasta and relax.
I see.
Well, I'll try to come back early.
- I told you...
- If I can make it,
let's play with the fireworks.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
But don't push yourself for me.
Yeah, understood.
Hey,
Haruna calls you 'Ryota, ' right?"
Yeah.
Should I call you that too?
Ah.
You've always called me
'Kazuhito, ' right?"
Well, either one is fine.
I see.
Want to try calling me that?
- Huh, your name?
- Yeah.
Ryota.
Sorry, let's stick with
Natsukawa for now!
Yeah, that's probably for the best!
Oh, I have to go!
- I'll take care of it.
- Thanks.
- I'll quickly return.
- Take care.
Now I know my heart clearly.
Thank you, everyone.
Let's have a drink tonight,
cheers!
- Cheers!
- To all of you, thank you very much.
- Likewise.
Thank you very much. Drink up.
- Thank you, drink up!
- Thank you, manager!
Tanaka-kun, mind if I sit next to you?
- Umm, well...
- Please, go ahead.
- Thanks, Yoshi Eri-chan.
- No problem.
Wait.
So, what are you going to eat?
I don't know.
By the way,
what do you usually eat?
You live alone, right?
No, I live with someone.
Oh, a girlfriend?
No, it's my childhood friend
from elementary school.
Is that so?
Then you probably cook
bachelor-style meals.
Actually, he cooks most of the time,
but it's quite decent, you know...
And it's quite delicious.
Not two.
Just one.
I wonder if he's having fun.
You take leave quite often.
It's for personal business.
Where did you go?
Saitama.
- Saitama?
- That's so close.
Saitama?
Um, manager, I should...
- Let's have a chat first.
- There you are,
finally found my Tanaka-kun.
Wow.
But seriously,
you're so handsome and cool.
Thank you very much.
Hey, you don't have a girlfriend, right?
- No, I don't.
- I see.
Teshigawara-san.
Please give up on him.
Huh, why? He's single.
I won't let him go.
- I'd go for it.
- Oh!
Umm, sorry,
actually, there's someone I like.
Oh, really?
That's the first time
I've heard that from you.
I've kept it a secret.
Well, it was pretty obvious.
- Huh?
- So, it's a one-sided crush?
I don't have much hope,
but I'm waiting for an answer.
What? Tanaka? Unbelievable!
Isn't he just being led on conveniently?
I don't know.
I'm sorry,
but I think it's time for me to...
Let me teach you how to win them over,
shall I?
- Hello.
- Brother.
The girls in class want to see
the latest pics of Kazuhito-kun,
Can you send them over?
Take a great picture, okay?
There's none.
What?
You don't have one in your stock?
Some good-looking ones?
Fine, I'll find something.
Thanks.
So rush.
He's probably popular even
at the drinking party.
How slow.
Listen, someone like Tanaka-kun
has to surround himself with girls.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Yeah, you need to play around a bit,
make them feel a little jealous,
ignite the flames of envy.
Flames of envy?
Just imagine,
they're burning up
with jealousy for you.
Sounds good.
See? See?
That's why
we're gonna party until morning!
- Karaoke!
- Yay!
- Morning ramen!
- Exactly!
But I'll pass on that.
Umm...
I want them to be jealous.
But I don't want to test them
or make them worry.
I'll patiently wait.
Please marry me!
Yeah, that was definitely
an excellent response.
Hey, are you sure
he's not just being fooled?
- No, I don't think so.
- Yeah.
Alright, alright,
Kazuhito is leaving.
- Let him go.
- Don't go yet.
- Stop, don't touch him.
- I haven't touched him.
- Kazuhito.
- Please stay.
- Try keeping him here.
- Do your best!
- See you later.
Bye-bye!
Thanks for helping.
It's nothing.
But are you sure you'll be okay?
Totally. If things get rough,
I'll just leave you behind.
I see.
Hey, Kazuhito.
I'm not going to pry into
who you're interested in or anything,
but I'm rooting for you.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Bye.
Wait.
There's a weather alert.
A weather alert?
Rain.
The weather forecast was way off.
Looks like he'll return in the morning.
I see.
(An all-nighter, huh?)
(Take care of Kazuhito for me)
There's no need to care.
Hello.
Huh, Kazuhito hasn't come back yet?
Wasn't it an all-nighter?
No, the photo from earlier
was taken a while ago.
Kazuhito already left.
I thought he was already home by now.
Sorry, goodbye.
The number you have dialed
is currently switched off...
What? Kazuhito? Huh?
Sorry for being late,
I wanted to let you know,
but my phone died.
What about your umbrella?
They were all sold out.
Just get in already!
The train stopped because of the rain,
so I ran.
No need to speak, wait here for a sec.
Here!
If rains that bad, you should've
gone back to the store.
But...
You're freezing!
Take off your clothes!
Yeah.
Cover yourself.
Sorry for the trouble.
Dummy!
It's moments like these
when you should rely on me.
Learn to lean on me properly.
I'll go run the bath.
Come on, hurry up, water! Heat up!
Wait a moment, it's almost ready.
- Kazuhito.
- So warm.
Huh? Kazuhito, Kazuhito, Kazuhito.
(Next episode)
Natsukawa.
When you entered middle school,
are you going to join the baseball club?
I intended to.
You got in because you are
a youth baseball superstar.
If you don't mind, let's be date.
Natsukawa.
What should we do if we feel like
we've lost ourselves?