[English subtitles are available]
[We Are Young]
[Episode 42]
I've no idea what's wrong with Mr Duan.
He exposed it all for you
and ended up losing his job.
Mr Wu, Cloud Live is still
a large ship.
Small setbacks are only tiny bumps.
It's not causing much loss.
This ship will not capsized.
Why don't we practice yoga together?
Yoga mat is over there.
If you don't know, I'll teach you.
[Cloud Live]
Jia Yun.
[How was the brand discussion today?]
It's not worth mentioning.
I like how the old saying put it.
Everybody bullies the defeated one.
You've worked hard today.
Cloud Live,
in the world of live streaming,
is still a very famous company.
Everyone seemed courteous
when things were good.
After the decline,
people seem to think
as if it has never existed before.
[Chen Lang,]
Cloud Live is your child.
It's your hard work.
However, as for as the brands
are concerned,
it's just a name.
What they care about
is the return on investment
Cloud Live could provide,
and helping them to
accomplish online sales tasks.
If it doesn't work,
then collaboration is impossible.
Yes, this is the reality.
I understand.
[You once said,]
the world of business is cruel.
Sometimes you can even say
it's cold and merciless.
[I got it.]
I will not concede.
You don't have to be pessimistic anyway.
I just read and predicted your future.
I believe your good luck
will come soon.
What good luck?
Let me see.
There should be a divine assistance.
Tell me the detail of this assistance.
This is the divine secret,
I can't reveal too much.
For specific details...
Guess it yourself.
Hello.
Divine assistance.
Pour into a bowl.
Sugar.
Milk.
Stir well.
Medium heat above 150 degrees.
Put it in the oven for 20 minutes.
Okay,
Come in.
Ms Ouyang.
Mr Ding.
You have been working overtime recently.
So, I bought you some protein powder.
It can enhance your immunity.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
However, what you just said
is what I should do.
Since you are here,
I have something to discuss with you.
Please go ahead.
Speaking of the OEM matter,
I want Xi Xi help me to deal with it.
Let Xi Xi
manage OEM?
OEM is such an important thing,
I don't think she is the right person.
She's only suited to be a broadcaster.
I think no one
is better than her for this role.
Speaking of Qian Xi Xi and Duan Ran,
the reason why I hire them
is not because they are capable.
I hire them
because we are childhood friends.
-She herself...
-Mr Ding.
Listen.
When I joined the company,
it was agreed that
I have independent administrative power.
I've decided to appoint Qian Xi Xi, okay?
Sure.
If you really want her, just go ahead.
Of course I don't agree with it.
I just respect your authority.
Thank you.
If you really want to thank me,
Have you eaten? Let's have a dinner later.
Ouyang.
So,
I thought we want to lose weight together?
What should I do if you go for dinner?
Yes, lose weight.
Can we have a talk outside?
I have to excuse myself first.
Mr Ding,
make yourself comfortable.
Sure.
Coffee is here, let's have a drink.
Speaking of Ding Ding,
obviously he is against me.
Duan Ran has left the company.
We should help each other more.
Look out for each other, right?
To safeguard our territory.
Now is the darkest period for the company.
We should really let go of our feud
to confront our common enemy.
To put it simply, I guess
we both share similar aestheticism.
We like the same style.
This is not even a feud at all.
No problem with that.
If Shen Ding Ding
harasses or bullies
you again, let me know.
This is his habit.
He loves to play with
beautiful girls since young.
Speaking of this,
don't worry.
For those who love idle talk in office,
I have my ways to deal with it.
If you didn't come in just now,
I would have punched him.
You saved him.
Come on.
You are gentle and elegant,
there is no way you could behave violent.
No one will buy it.
Violence against violence
is the way to curb him.
Why talk nonsense if we can attack.
It's simple, direct and violent.
New skills learned.
There's nothing wrong with it.
Uncle Duan.
Aunt Zhou.
Xi Xi is back.
Xi Xi.
We're saved.
Why did you buy so many egg tarts?
Bought?
Duan Ran made them?
Duan Ran.
Why are you making so many egg tarts?
Are you opening an egg tart shop?
Don't ask so much.
Since you are here,
just try it out.
This is already the fifth tray.
How are you going to finish them?
Who will eat it?
Don't ask or say anything.
Just give a try.
It's hot, quickly.
-It's hot!
-Wait!
Wait! Let it go!
I forgot to add blueberry sauce.
Where did I put the sauce?
Where's my sauce?
Uncle Duan.
How is your health?
I'm good. I go fishing occasionally.
It's good to exercise
more during recovery.
Does this make a difference?
Just taste it.
Xi Xi.
-Please talk to him soon.
-What's wrong with him?
He has been like this for two days.
Working on egg tarts everyday.
Trying out all flavours.
We have to try all this mess.
We are really sick of it.
Please talk to him.
Oh my God, there he goes again.
Do you want barbecue flavour?
I'll add some cumin for you.
After adding blueberry sauce,
it doesn't taste that good.
I'll try canned apricot later,
or add some apple sauce.
Have you tried cucumber egg tart before?
What happened?
Let me cuddle for a while.
Duan Ran.
You really want to stay at home
and be idle just like this?
I'm not being idle,
don't listen to my mother's nonsense.
I'm quite busy these days.
I get up every day
to make egg tarts and desserts.
I have to work out every day too.
By the way, I bought a drum set
and it will arrive in two days.
I am going to do all the things
I had wanted to do.
You are doing all these
just to make yourself look fulfilled.
Actually you are an escapist.
You are overthinking.
I'm just taking time to relax
and to get some rest.
To feel what real life is all about.
What about me?
Am I within your plan?
Of course.
You are my girlfriend.
How could it be possible without you?
Of course you are in my plan.
What about Rui?
Oh, Rui.
As for Rui, I think
by leaving it behind,
I'm getting closer to life,
making life easier
and be comfortable.
Duan Ran.
I don't mean to persuade
you to go back Rui.
Because I know I can't
persuade you at all.
But have you ever thought that
Rui is not the only place
to realize our dreams.
There is still Cloud Live.
Cloud Live?
You can join Cloud Live and
be the pioneer with Chen Lang.
Jia Yun has resigned from Rui Live.
She's helping Chen Lang.
It's possible that
Cloud Live will be our new starting point.
You are too naive.
First of all, Shen Ding Ding
probably won't agree to it.
After joining Cloud Live,
aren't we doing the same things again?
The so-called restart
is to start these ideals,
ambitions and desires
and the pain
all over again.
In the end,
it would just reconfirm my failure.
Why bother?
Isn't life like this?
Think about your ambition
and your talents and aspirations.
They are neither assumption nor fantasy.
All you need is to do it step by step,
one at a time and finally realize it.
Xi Xi.
I may not be as good as you think.
I think you are too good
and way better than I thought.
Duan Ran, we both grew up together.
We've been through
so many things together,
so many difficulties.
I know you.
I don't even know myself.
But I know you.
Believe me, you truly are the best.
Don't doubt yourself.
Okay, Xi Xi.
I need a rest,
let me relax.
Don't be like that.
Why are you still awake?
My worries have finally come true.
[Go Younger]
I'm really looking forward.
Let me see.
How is it?
One piece dress!
Are you satisfied, Mr Five?
-Do you like it?
-It looks good!
Look at this one,
do I look kind of intellectual?
It's too intellectual.
You are the most intellectual one.
I once worried as this is
only for the niche market.
People might not like it.
I like it. I'm keeping one for myself.
You are the first to buy.
In fact, niche market is not a concern.
Because the main concept of Vine
is to lead the fashion trend.
Xi Xi, what do you think of this?
This is the more satisfactory one
among my design.
It's perfect!
You have to go live for this dress.
It's so cool.
Okay, all sizes and styles
for all dresses have arrived.
The first thing is to inform our fans
so they won't bother our
customer service. It's been crazy.
I can't wait to go live now.
Hurry up.
Take care of those two and
you take care of these three.
-I'll take these two boxes.
-OK.
[Baking Bible]
Let's chat for a while.
Stop reading.
You're already a master.
Put your book down.
Chat with me.
Go ahead.
I know you are taking a break
during this period.
it can be quite boring to be alone.
I'm thinking...
How about getting you a girlfriend?
Speaking of blind dates.
It happens mostly among the single,
desperate and older
leftover men and women.
This doesn't suit me at all.
Just meet her once for my sake, will you?
Cute boy.
That girl is very pretty.
It's so embarrassing.
Please! Just be there for once.
She looks prettier than me.
Try my newest egg tart.
Marble pattern.
Cinnamon.
For both the taste and sweetness,
I have made some adjustments.
[Hello everyone, I'm Mr Five.]
[I'm streaming on time today.]
[Today, I'm bringing everyone]
[some good news.]
[These are Vine's new
products for second season.]
[They have all arrived.]
[Vine]
For those who have pre-ordered,
you will receive your clothes soon.
[Today I will introduce to everyone]
[this pleated skirt I designed.]
[Chat with the host]
As you know the main elements
of Vine series are denim
and our pleated designs.
We're still using
the re-utilization of denim fabric...
re-utilizing this...
Su Su.
I request to end this
streaming session in advance.
Yang Yang, do you have time now?
If you do, come to Rui.
I want to discuss something with you.
I have emphasized in advance that
I need double welt
seam for pleated fabric.
None of this batch of clothes have it.
When I went live,
I saw that this has ripped.
[Qian Xi Xi.]
[You are in charge of the
factory. What have you done?]
Mr Ding, I've just appointed
Xi Xi two days ago.
I suppose this batch of clothes was
completed three days ago.
What should we do now?
The pre-sale is already live.
There are already thousands of orders.
Fans are discussing this batch of clothes.
If it is not shipped out on time,
fans will complain.
Why not we ship them first
and then recall the products.
No way.
We can't sell like this.
Exactly, isn't it deceiving consumers?
Besides, our brand
always strive for excellence.
Many fans are here because of me.
Isn't this digging your own grave?
What is your opinion?
Redo everything?
[What did the factory say?]
As for the factory,
Xi Xi contacted the new OEM.
The boss has transferred some machines,
but still they can't make it.
Listen to me.
[Destroy this batch of products.]
Destroy?
[The quality of an independent
brand must not go wrong.]
Mr Ding.
Ouyang, Yang Yang.
Every piece of clothes from Vine
is all our hard work.
Since there are problems with the clothes,
I think they should not be destroyed.
We should try to salvage them
based on current conditions.
This matter...
is my responsibility.
Mr Ding, I hope you can give me a chance.
I'll monitor it personally.
I'll monitor the factory personally
for processing this batch of clothes.
I'm responsible entirely.
I back you up.
Me too.
[Okay, I'll give you another chance.]
[If you can't handle this batch properly,]
[you don't have to work here any more.]
[Look at all of you.]
[I've just been away for a few days.]
[Look at what trouble you all caused.]
[What's the matter with you all?]
Why are you still holding it?
That's really obedient.
Where are they? Why is it dark?
The information of all garment
OEMs in Xiamen is here.
Contact details and so on,
the scale information are all listed here.
Take a look.
Thanks.
I'm doing something else to do tonight,
I won't be working overtime with you all.
Don't worry, just leave it to me.
[Your father was forced to leave QE.]
[You also left Rui Live.]
I'm actually worried about our future.
I need to think for you both.
[Don't say no in such a hurry.]
[Just meet her once, okay?]
[Qian Xi Xi]
Just call one by one.
Hello.
Hello, I'm from Rui Live.
There happened to be
a designer's collection
that are ready to be
made into apparel products.
We want to add on...
Add on production.
Hello, is this Xiamen Big
Forest Service Market?
Yes this is urgent.
Can I talk to your manager?
You can't accept it, is that so?
We have a batch...
Is this Yongji garment factory?
Why.
Ouyang.
Why are you here?
I'm here on a blind date.
Look what happened to us.
My mum forced me
to come for a date too.
You are expecting me?
We're hoping to cooperate with you.
I have cut a deal.
-Great!
-but it's too costly.
Our core business is live commerce.
Then we can meet up to
talk about some details.
Is that okay?
Xin Si Le is off.
Why?
The clothes in their own factory
has already piled up.
-I won't call Xin Si Le then.
-Forget them.
I was about to call them.
Sorry,
there has been a delay in update.
I thought you were still around.
Hello, this is Rui Live.
You don't need to call them.
They don’t make clothes any more.
Yu Shi, be careful.
Mainly about live streaming e-commerce.
It's fine.
Stop calling Sicheng Garment.
Which one? Sicheng Garment?
Yes, they're no longer making clothes.
Take a look.
Now Chenghui, Huali and Xin Jia Le
all think our quantity is too big.
They are not able to commit.
These are the few reliable OEMs left.
We talked to some more in the morning.
Let's call and communicate once again.
By putting together
our Vine design concept,
the outcome we want,
our requested amount,
including their price,
let’s communicate again.
Aren't there three companies
that have agreed
to let us visit tomorrow?
In case we go tomorrow
and find that it’s unreliable,
what should we do then?
We have to call again.
I need to take a call.
-Yu Shi
-This Hu Li Enterprise...
Dad.
[Why did you video call me?]
[What can I do for you?]
Nothing much.
I just wanted to chat
since it's been a while.
What are you doing now?
[Nothing much, just busy at office.]
Busy?
[You don't look good. What's wrong?]
Is it?
I'm fine. Everything's good.
Perhaps it is caused by
the lighting of this office.
I'm fine, don't worry about it.
Bad lighting?
You think I'm stupid?
I knew about Uncle Duan.
He is no longer the chairman.
You're not the CEO any more.
Who told you this?
There's no way to hide
such a big matter from me.
[Dad, listen to me.]
I'm fine.
Doesn't matter if I'm the CEO
of Rui or not.
I will do my best to protect it.
How could my mother
arranged this blind date?
She is such a fool.
Why would we need such a blind date?
Isn't it good enough to
have a wine session?
Aunty talked to me yesterday.
She told me that you've almost
turned into a patisserie at home.
She asked me to come and meet you.
My mother is still worried about me.
She is such a cautious person,
always careful and
attentive to everything.
Something happened at home recently,
I think my mother should be
the one to be worried about.
I should be the one worrying.
When she asked me about this yesterday,
I was reluctant at first.
But I still came today.
Firstly, I really want to
comfort and talk to you.
But more importantly,  It's for myself.
You do know why I
went to Rui Live earlier.
I know you do.
At that time,
the streaming cancellation
happened again in Rui Live.
So I thought
I could help you out
more or less over there,
to overcome the challenge.
I also hoped that you could see my
good intentions.
You know how strong my self-esteem is.
For words that I have no confidence,
and things that I'm unsure,
I won't do it, and I won't say it.
But when it comes to you,
my self-esteem is thrown out the window.
So I decided,
whether or not
you know what I'm going to say,
or if I'm going to get
an unfavourable reply today,
I still have to say this.
I still love you.
Come and stay with me for a while.
Relax.
[You want me to go abroad?]
You'll know when you come.
It is scarcely populated over here.
Although there's nothing else here,
but there is time for you to be alone.
Dad, I am a mature adult.
I can take responsibility for my own life.
Just mind your own business.
Silly girl, you're reluctant
to hurt this one,
and you need to protect that one.
[I'm thinking of the consequences.]
[In the end...]
[In the end, you suffer alone.]
[You end up getting hurt.]
What are you trying to imply
through this late-night call?
In fact, I'm too far away from you.
I can't reach you. I'm anxious, you know?
[I don't know how to help you either.]
I wish I could be like
how you protect Rui Live,
to protect you by your side.
Thanks, Dad.
Ouyang.
Qian Xi Xi is my lover now.
It's impossible for us to be together.
Xi Xi and I grew up together.
Over the years,
our feelings for each other...
We lived under the
same roof since young.
We shared everything
from food to personal belongings.
I even let her drive my precious car
for so long
yet I don't mind at all.
Then Jiang Zhe Yang appeared suddenly.
After his appearance,
I began to notice that
if Xi Xi and Jiang Zhe Yang...
were getting too close,
I would be unhappy about it.
Sometimes the way they interact,
the way they talk, made me furious.
Fact is, I was jealous.
I'm jealous of the relationship
between Qian Xi Xi and Jiang Zhe Yang,
but I couldn't say it out loud.
I dare not face my relationship at first.
After that I learned
there is no way to escape from it.
Actually it's not that scary after all
to hear it from your own mouth.
It's not so scary after all.
We have known each other for so long.
We should know each other's
temperament very well.
Although I'm telling you straight up
but it will hurt you still.
But I think I still have to tell you,
I want to tell you. I think telling you
is far better than
saying nothing at all
and pretend to be a fool.
I would be a bad guy to behave such a way.
The consequence from that is in fact
the most hurtful thing to you.
That's good.
There's no need for you to apologize.
What you said today is really good.
It's really sincere,
It's simply Duan Ran.
Go directly to the fourth floor.
It's inconvenient for me to move around.
I won't meet you downstairs then.
I wait for you at the lift.
It's easy to spot me
as I'm on a walking stick.
Yes, I'll wait by the lift.
Okay.
Are you Mr Duan's mother?
Yes, I am.
Mr Duan is not here.
Is Xi Xi here? I'm looking for her.
Yes, she is.
Before I came today,
I had no expectations.
As for my mission at Rui,
I think it's done.
So I plan to leave.
I understand.
Still I want to thank you.
Thank you for being here to help out
during the the most difficult time.
Thank you as you've done
so much for Rui Live and for me.
I sincerely do.
You don't have to thank me.
I volunteered myself.
Speaking of Vine.
This independent brand
is doing well now.
Although some problems crept up,
but I can see that
Shen Jiang Tao really values ​​it.
Since I'm leaving,
why don't you take over?
Forget it.
I'm no longer with Rui Live.
I don't have a company either.
There's neither resources nor people.
To take over it is to damage it.
Don’t you realize it's a bargaining chip
to serve as a good
opportunity for you to go back?
If that's the case,
just do me another favour.
Let Xi Xi do it.
[Duan Ran]
Aunt Zhou.
What brings you here today
and why such a hurry?
You even come to the office personally.
I just want to ask you out alone.
Let's have a talk.
Your phone.
[Duan Ran]
Why don't you answer Duan Ran's call?
There's nothing important about his call.
I will call him later.
I want to listen to you first.
Xi Xi.
You stayed in our home for years.
How are Uncle Duan and I treating you?
Both of you have been very nice to me.
All these years you both
raised me like your own daughter.
You have been very
accepting, understanding.
You took care of me since I was young,
You gave me a carefree life
and showed me the warmth of a family.
I'm contented.
This...
The feeling of being lovers,
is it different from being siblings?
Aunt Zhou.
Leave Duan Ran.
I can't accept you two being together.
Why?
There's something
in my heart
which I've kept hidden for 13 years.
Xi Xi.
Your mother's death had
something to do with me.
I made an unforgivable mistake.
That's impossible.
My mother died in a car accident.
It was me.
What happened?
Why are you drinking so much again?
Come and take off your clothes.
Can't you drink a little less?
You've been like day everyday.
[Those days]
[were the darkest period in my life.]
[Uncle Duan has just started his career.]
[He was drinking and
socializing so often.]
[We are running late.
Let me stop by for a while.
-I'll be back right away.
-[Every day, after attending to Duan Sr,]
[I had to take care of Duan Jr.]
[It was never ending.]
[I couldn't seem to see the end
of such a life.]
[During that period of time,]
[I often dragged your
mother along for a drink.]
[She had something to do that night.]
[I insisted her to go to the bar.]
[We were having a good time.]
Are you happy?
Of course.
But you tricked me just now.
-I did not.
-Yes, you did.
-No.
-I told you best two out of three.
I beat you twice.
-You said you didn't lose.
-But one more game is left.
Fine.
Let's do it one more round.
This final game decides the winner.
Ready.
Open!
Nothing.
You...
-You tricked me again.
-Alright.
-I won't tease you any more.
-The last game.
Rock paper scissors.
I lost.
I won so you go to buy some alcohol.
-Two bottles?
-No, four bottles.
Okay, four bottles.
-Go quick, I'll wait for you.
-Okay.
Isn't it just four bottles?
Someone got hit by a car.
-Someone got hit.
-Let's go and see.
After your mother passed away,
we failed to reach your father.
Out of guilt and self-blame...
And of course
responsibility,
I must raise you up on
behalf of your mother.
I want you to grow up healthy and happy.
Guilt.
Self-blame.
Aunt Zhou, do you know?
For all these years,
the way you look at me at home,
I always thought it was somehow weird.
As if I've said something wrong
or I did something wrong again.
I upset you and you were angry.
So it's all because of this incident.
In that case, why didn't
you tell me earlier?
Xi Xi.
Every time I see you,
I wanted to tell you.
But I can't seem to utter the words.
I'm afraid you won't forgive me.
I wanted to raise you up first.
When you are capable,
you can be independent then.
However,
now you're in love with Duan Ran.
This is something I can't face, you know?
I...
I don't want to see you again every day.
I don't want to live in
such a shadow any more.
Because of your self-blame,
you want to atone for it.
You chose to keep me by your side.
Raised me up.
And because you think I won't forgive you,
you chose not to tell me and
concealed it from me.
Now because of you again,
because you don't want to face me
any more,
you forbid Duan Ran and I to be together.
It's all about what you want,
how you like it to be.
Have you ever considered me
when you did all these?