[English subtitles are available]
[We Are Young]
[Episode 39]
Anti-fans, double agents,
imitation products, account suspension,
and now, stealing Mr Five's designs?
Aren't you despicable?
I met her once before this.
Actually, she longs for this very much.
I once mentioned to you
and urged you on.
It's a pity that it didn't materialise.
Now I want to make up for it.
I was hoping you'd
be excited to hear this.
Looks like
it's hopeless now.
I don't mind.
You can be angry, too.
It's simply ridiculous.
I'd never have expected you
to steal someone's ideas
and use it to justify yourself.
My work here is done.
[Moe Tea]
[I have conclusive evidence]
[that you sent us the imitation products
on Singles' Day.]
[I'd never have expected you]
[to steal someone's ideas...]
[Hello.]
[Hello, please speak up.]
Hello, I want to report
on an unfair competition.
The company involved
is Cloud Live.
[B2]
[It's such a white shirt skirt.]
[And,]
[it has a nice bow-knot design.]
Its cuffs are hollow.
Just take a look.
[Even...]
[Cloud Live,
Live streaming account is suspended]
What's going on?
Go check it out.
What happened?
I have no idea.
It's suspended.
Is it suspended?
It suddenly happened.
Yes, indeed.
Everyone, gather around.
Just calm yourselves down.
Listen to me.
It was unexpected.
I just knew about it.
There's something more serious.
Double 12 is coming up.
Then there's the Lantern Festival,
and a series of promotional
events afterward.
We mustn't rest on our laurels.
I'll get us a temporary platform.
I believe the suspension won't be long.
I heard such suspensions usually last
at least three months.
Are we going to be fine?
Wen Wen, you're scaring everyone.
Listen.
When we first started,
didn't I fulfill all my promises
that I made to you all?
Now we're having a little trouble,
we can't just back out from it, right?
We can't know for sure
what's going to happen next.
Three months isn't too long.
And we'll keep on
waiting during this time.
Waiting without salary
for three month is
unacceptable.
During this time,
you'll still get your salary.
[Shapowei Art Zone]
Can't you two just talk it over?
Just talk to him.
Mao.
Well,
Mr Five wants to talk to you.
You two should just talk it over.
Start talking to each other.
I have something urgent in hand.
I'm very busy.
-Go ahead.
-Xi XI.
Just go.
Well,
I'm going to do a live stream
with Jiang Zhe Yang.
Project Vine is back on track.
Are you angry with me?
I'm sorry.
I was too engrossed in my work
that I neglected your feelings.
I was foolish
and careless, too.
Just let it out on me.
Don't be angry.
It's passed.
I'm sorry.
It's simply impossible to do that.
[Resignation Letter]
I've something urgent in
hand. Call you later.
Xiao Xiao.
Why the resignation at this time?
You're my head broadcaster.
Our 40 percent of viewership
comes from you. If you go now,
what will happen to
the rest of the company?
Mr Chen.
The suspension is serious.
We won't be unsuspended for quite a while.
No jobs in three month,
do you know how much I'll lose?
Xiao Xiao, since you mention this,
let's talk about it.
[File pocket]
Look at these.
All these papers have the records
of the company giving
you the full resources
in order for you to become
the head broadcaster.
Now you want to leave us,
what's that supposed to mean?
Mr Chen.
I wish I could ride out
the storm with you.
I have my son to think about.
There're endless expenses.
My subsidised salary
is hardly enough to feed my kid.
I've signed quite a few
baby product contracts.
If we stop for three months,
the termination fee will be astronomical.
I could bring over my contracts
in a new company.
It'll lessen your burden this way.
Since you disregard our work relationship,
then let's talk about your
contract termination fee.
How do you plan to pay me the fee?
Rest assured,
the legal person from my
new company will talk to you.
Are you kidding me?
[Jiang Zhe Yang Private Label
Concept Release Special]
[Vine]
Hello, everyone. It's been a long time.
Today Mr Five and I have an announcement.
Mr Five.
Hello, everyone. I'm Mr Five.
We had some problems
during our last program.
Today we're making a clarification.
This is the patent
for the Vine Series that's awarded
by the government.
[We didn't copy from anyone else.]
[The Vine Series]
[was built on Mr Five's]
[previous work that includes]
[the denim elements.]
[Right, Mr Five?]
[That's right, just as she said...]
Timing's perfect this time.
Our dear fans
can pay attention
to Mr Five's work.
Let's take a look at
what I'm wearing today.
It's one of the designs
from the Vine Series.
It's a sweatshirt and
I feel comfortable wearing it.
[And it's made of cotton linen.]
[Is this the latest style?]
Luckily, we manage to do
this just before the New Year.
Thank goodness.
We have to thank Jia Yun for this.
I wonder whether it was his conscience
or gratitude that made Chen Lang
give us the patent.
I just hope Chen Lang
can get Cloud Live
back on the right path.
I heard Xiao Xiao is
going to leave Cloud Live.
Many of them, too.
Not sure if he's able
to weather the storm.
Anyway, this is business.
When things are fine, we're galloping.
When things are going south,
we'll see a stampede within the company.
Don't just look at the negative side.
This incident may be a nuisance,
but it has put our company
in the spotlight.
The key is pre-sales strategy.
First, we must act fast.
We should go all out for sale while
we're still hot from the incident.
Second, we must focus
on our target market.
After every sale,
we need to do a data collection
and analysis on the customers.
We must get our after-sale services right.
I agree.
[Rui Live]
I haven't got time to tidy up.
I'm sorry.
Feel free to sit.
Didn't expect you could
become like this, Mr Chen.
Now you're living in the office.
It's good living here.
It's better than living on a farm
with the animals.
When I was a kid,
I had to live above a pigsty.
Both floors were connected.
Bet you haven't seen it.
Didn't expect you were that poor.
No wonder you are overcautious.
Mr Duan Jr is more daring instead.
Am I as you said?
If that's the case, then you're a snob.
I used to hear that whenever
you encountered difficulties,
Mr Duan Sr was always there for you.
And that was what he got for helping you.
Do you know what you've
done to Duan Ran and Xi Xi?
I owe them nothing.
It was Duan Sheng Yun who started it.
Why am I telling you this?
But you.
Little Duckling is
your close friend, right?
Didn't you use her as well?
I think you're the most wicked.
I just couldn't help it.
I had a bad role model
and made a wrong decision.
There's no turning back for me.
Who doesn't make a mistake?
If you don't owe Duan Sheng Yun,
then I don't owe you either.
We've reached a consensus on this.
You're free to leave if you want.
You can see it.
Nevertheless,
I hope you can still bear with me, Cola.
But now Cloud isn't
as good as it once was.
Even so,
I hope you can trust me as you once were.
Trust me this time.
Sure.
Well,
just tidy up your place.
You'll feel better this way.
Mr Chen.
Nobody could have expected
things would turn out like this.
They threatened me with
the company. I was scared.
I'm to be blamed.
It's my fault.
Enough.
It was not entirely your doing.
Jia Yun was right to scold me.
Look what I've done
to get to where I am.
[Rolling in it]
[Blessing]
Babes,
Su Su seems to be in a good mood today.
Get ready, everyone.
Roger.
I'll get prepared right away.
Hello dear.
We need to put up the "blessing" sticker.
Can you help us?
-Sure.
-Not done yet.
Thanks.
Why are you so superstitious now?
Let's create a new
atmosphere for the New Year.
You think it's going to bring world peace
or fulfill our wishes?
Look at these red packets.
[Yu Shi loves Su Su]
Jia Yun.
There're so many red packets.
Su Su.
Well,
you're early today.
I'm the best at
handing out red packets.
Of course.
Su Su.
Actually, I've always
wanted to ask you a question.
Well,
your mum arranged so
many blind dates for you.
Have you ever wondered
the kind of person you would
like to spend your life with?
When I was meeting the guys,
there'd inevitably be many rules.
Personally,
I don't demand much.
When two people get together,
what matters is mutual affection.
And they're comfortable
in each other's company.
This kind of love
often comes naturally
without you noticing it.
Do you think so?
I hope so.
Jia Yun said Su Su is in good spirits.
But it doesn't serve us if
only she alone is feeling good.
It's taking so much time.
There's nothing I can do about it.
-I'll speed it up then.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
-Take a seat.
-My alarm clock didn't go off.
I don't know what's wrong with that.
What are you doing?
Makeup?
Please don't, Mr Five.
This is just a concealer.
Will I look fragile?
-No.
-I don't want it.
Here.
Really have to do this?
-Which is better?
-The one on the left.
I like this better.
No.
Black or white?
I look old.
-Forget it, Mr Five.
-What's with you?
I look too serious with this on me.
And I'm sweaty now.
It makes him nervous.
-Fine.
-You might look good in glasses.
Put on some perfume.
Are you serious? One, two.
One, two, quick.
♫ Spin and jump ♫
You remember the
confession procedure, right?
They've sent the speech
to me via WeChat.
Okay.
I've memorised it.
-Let me rehearse.
-Sure.
There's still time, right?
Leave me alone. I'm trying to memorise.
We'll print out the lookbook
for Vine right after New Year.
You'll be the first one to get it.
Sure.
I'm ending this call, bye.
Hurry up, Mr Duan. Otherwise,
Su Su is going to discover it.
I'm coming.
Didn't you see I have a handful?
Ms Ouyang left for a holiday
and passed me her work.
She usually has a lot of work.
They don't call her
a workaholic for nothing.
Where's Xi Xi?
She went to a shop that's
all the rage on the internet
to get something for the Weiya Festival.
She won't be long.
Jia Yun.
Is he ready for his mission?
Don't mention it.
He's almost ready and wants to be alone.
And now he's nowhere to be seen.
Most likely he's hiding
somewhere, rehearsing his speech.
Just received his message.
What's it about?
[Mr Duan.]
[I need your help.]
[I couldn't unlock
the door in the toilet.]
Yu Shi.
Mr Duan.
Are you in there?
Luckily, you came to my help.
Help me unlock the door.
How could this happen?
I'm just curious.
Stop kidding, Mr Duan.
I have no idea.
Step aside. I'm trying to open it.
Sure.
It appears to be stuck.
I'll need to call the locksmith.
Hold it, Mr Duan.
-Don't do that.
-Why?
If you do that,
everyone will know about it.
I'll be a laughing stock then.
I don't want Su Su to see me
locked in the toilet.
It's so embarrassing.
What's there to be embarrassed about?
It's not your fault that you're
locked inside.
It's the toilet's fault.
I just feel embarrassed.
Great things don't come easy, you know.
This is no time for jokes.
I'm about to confess to Su Su.
I finally mustered my courage,
and now I'm stuck in the toilet.
Why am I so unlucky?
Why don't you confess
through the door?
Mr Duan.
I don't think today
is a good time for this.
Today is the best day for this.
You can forget about doing it,
if you miss it today.
I've checked the lunar calendar.
You sure will succeed if you do it today.
-Okay.
-I'm locked in the toilet.
Today can't be a good day.
What are you doing, Mr Duan?
-Yu Shi, calm down.
-I'm listening.
-Okay.
-It's time to open your heart.
Come on.
Duan Ran.
Why is he locked inside?
The men's room?
Can't unlock it?
You can try.
I'll do it. Step aside.
Is that you, Ms Qian?
I'm here to save you, Yu Shi.
Ms Qian.
Even Mr Duan couldn't unlock it.
Are you all right?
I'm not at all.
I'm giving up.
Just calm down.
Any idea, Duan Ran?
I would have already
unlocked it if I could.
Just calm down.
We'll come up with something.
What's going on?
Su Su is here.
You need to queue up.
I'm queuing up.
This is the men's room.
I'm keeping him company.
Stop hiding from me. I already know it.
I saw the light sign this morning.
We wanted to give you a
surprise, but never expect
this mishap could happen.
Let me talk to him.
Go ahead.
Yu Shi.
Su Su.
Is that you?
-Yes.
-Getting emotional.
You're here, too.
I'm going to die of embarrassment.
I'm sorry.
Are you feeling sorry for not
having the guts to confess to me,
or being so stupid to
lock yourself in the toilet?
You already knew it.
I'm truly sorry.
I wanted to give you a surprise.
I just couldn't figure it out
why the toilet locked me inside.
It's so embarrassing.
I'm sorry, Su Su.
It was my fault.
I've prepared a speech.
I've included something
good about you in it.
And everyone else helped
me with famous quotes
which they downloaded from the internet.
But I can't remember a word now.
Su Su.
I really
like you, Su Su.
I like you, Su Su.
I know.
In my current situation,
I don't meet
the criteria you've set for me.
But I'll work hard, Su Su.
I'll do my best.
I'll turn myself into the man
you want me to be.
What?
Will you be my girlfriend?
He did it.
Think about it.
Listen, Yu Shi.
You may be timid
and kind of dumb.
And possess many undesirable traits.
However,
I'm willing to be your girlfriend.
It's done.
What did you say?
I said I'm willing to be your girlfriend.
Are you just kidding with me?
Even if you're just kidding,
I'm more than willing to accept it.
-Love.
-It's successful.
This is love.
He actually confessed through a toilet.
-This is the power of love.
-It's done without facing each other.
So romantic.
Let's get him out quickly,
so he can see her.
I'm happy even if
you lock me here forever.
-I'll go look for help.
-Are you fool?
Calm down, Yu Shi.
Help is on the way.
I'll just wait.
I'm cool.
I'm fine.
Ms Zhang.
You're Chen Lang's assistant, right?
That's right.
What do you want?
I've something to tell you.
I've kept this for long.
There's something I want to clarify.
He didn't mix the leftover
stock with imitation goods.
It was me who did it,
on the order of my secret boss.
Chen Lang asked you to come?
He didn't know I came here.
He's very bad lately.
He's in a bad mood and
locks himself in his office.
He's completely isolated
from everyone else.
I've been with him for so many years.
I'm really worried about him.
Can you visit him if you’re free?
It’s almost the New Year
and everyone's busy.
I really don't have time.
It was all my fault. Don't blame Mr Chen.
I'm sorry.
Ms Zhang.
Today
is a happy day
and a day we should celebrate.
First of all,
today is our company's annual
Weiya Red Packet Event.
Do you know what these are?
Red packets.
These are the clinking red packets.
Everyone will get one of these.
There's another thing we should celebrate.
The two of them.
Yes, we're talking about you both.
Today we celebrate Yu Shi's
successful confession!
Let's congratulate them on
their sweet and long-lasting love.
Let's wish them a sweet
and long-lasting love.
And I also appreciate their
contribution to the company.
Thanks, Ms Qian.
For you, Su Su.
You really worked hard, Su Su.
-Thanks.
-It's my job.
-It isn't easy for you.
-It's okay.
Keep up the good work.
-For you.
-Thanks, Ms Qian.
You'll get one, too, Mr Five.
Here's yours.
Thanks, Xi Xi.
You did well this year. Keep it up.
-Boss.
-What's it?
Aren't you from the same family?
Each family shall
only have a red packet.
I want a red packet.
Hey.
Thanks for your generosity, boss.
Don't be smug.
We must use the money wisely.
Save it for your mum's medical expenses.
Then you shall keep it.
Okay.
Keep it up for next year.
You're awesome this year.
Thanks, boss.
-Thanks, boss.
-Wait for your turn.
Where's Jia Yun?
-Jia Yun.
-No idea.
-She left after answering a call.
Doesn't she want this?
Just give it to me.
-I'll keep it for her.
-You're the boss.
-I appreciate your hard work.
-Thanks.
Everyone else gets one.
-So many.
-Aren't these for me?
-Not for you.
-I just want it all.
-These are for everyone.
-Stop being bossy.
-Return them to me.
-They're mine.
Stop it.
He's taken all of them.
Watch him, Yu Shi.
Don't try to run away.
[B2, Live for You, Cloud Live]
Chen Lang.
You're still sleeping during the day.
Never expect you would come.
Help me carry these.
What are those?
They're heavy.
What have you brought?
My hands are now red.
Are you all right?
What are these?
Bamboo shoots?
You just came back from hometown?
Last time I went back,
didn't you refuse to
give your mum your address?
So she got mine instead
and sent me lots of delicious goodies.
She's wanted you to have a share, too.
That's why I never
give my mum this address.
Didn't expect she'd send them to you.
Thanks.
It's nothing.
The bamboo shoots
are best for hot pot.
I also bought lots of meat and vegetables.
Let's have hot pot today.
Oh my.
Sure.
The door was open when I came in.
What if the thieves sneaked in?
What's there to steal?
I have nothing now.
Except for my body, if they want it.
Not bad, you still could joke.
I didn't bring a pot.
Do you have one?
I may have one in the kitchen.
Okay.
Make yourself at home.
Why do you think
we left our depressing hometowns
for the big city?
It's to make money
and make our folks
and ourselves proud.
And to retire in style.
No wonder you'd rather stay here
during the festival
than to go back.
I wish to be back, too.
See what I've done to my company.
It's now ruined beyond repair.
I won't be able to face them.
On the contrary.
Your family is still proud
of you no matter what.
That's even a more valid
reason for me not to do so.
I think you're totally wrong.
You were able to pull yourself up
by your bootstraps.
That's already an amazing feat.
After visiting your home,
I'm now able to find out
who you really are.
I saw your childhood and
your track of growing up.
I had the very first attempt to understand
your desire for success.
You're carrying too many
missions on your shoulders.
That's why
your pressure got increasingly huge.
How's your grad school application?
So-so, I guess.
Anyway, the processes are complicated.
We'll see.
No rush.
Here.
Your mum wants you to have this.
My mum dug this bamboo
shoot with her own hands.
And you put it in my bowl.
This is so delicious.
So
you should visit her more often.
Anyway, the old folks won't
have much material needs.
What about you?
You hardly go back to hometown, too.
Tell me.
Just tell me honestly.
You love me all along, don't you?
That's why you're here.
Stop being smug.
I'm only here to deliver
your mum's bamboo shoots.
Like I said, they go bad quickly.
I see.
You usually make acquaintance
with the rich and powerful.
You'd never visit a small fry like me,
especially now that I've hit rock bottom.
I'm not that kind of person.
I only make friends with people
that deserve my friendship.
I must thank my mum.
Otherwise, I won't get
to have this hot pot today.
I think
your folks haven't had an easy life.
They'll surely miss you.
Just give them a call when you're free.
Why do you think I strive so hard?
I just want a better life.
I'm building a foundation
for my future family.
And to give my folks a comfortable life.
Our industry.
The e-commerce industry.
Today we may have the edge.
Who knows
what will happen tomorrow?
As a new wave rises, an old wave falls,
crashing on the beach.
I'm like the old wave, dying in the sand.
I think this is the
best thing about mankind.
You see, one wave succeeds another.
Each generation has its innovations.
We continue to advance
and evolve this way.
For me,
I believe the best always survives.
It's all about the
survival of the fittest.
I think it's the opposite.
I wonder why humankind is
divided into different classes?
That's why
there are so many wars and disasters.
Why can't we all
get along and prosper together?
Do you agree?
I like your kindness
but it's too idealistic.
People like us are beaten up by life.
I shudder to think about it.
Actually, I didn't say this.
I heard this from a friend.
And he said it better than me.
Really? What did he say?
This is what he said.
In this world,
everyone is like a rabbit.
Some are black while the others are white.
However, when the black rabbit
runs, the white rabbit must run, too.
We're using our gifts
to make it in our lives.
So there's no such thing as
the survival of the fittest.
I like this statement.
This person should be quite interesting.
Then do you want to see him?
Today?
Sure.
I suggest
-we have a toast.
-Sure.
I'm drinking water instead of wine today.
Only water for you.
I wish you all in the new year,
health and good luck.
Work harder for a successful career.
-Thanks Uncle Duan.
-Here's to it.
Happy new year.
-Xi Xi.
-Happy new year, Aunt Zhou.
-Happy new year.
-Happy new year, Duan Ran.
Shen.
Thanks for everything.
I know you like fish.
So I specially ordered a fish for you.
Aren't you too kind to me, Sister Zhou?
Xi Xi and Ran Ran absolutely
had a challenging time previously.
Please help yourselves.
It's okay.
Don't worry. We'll take care of ourselves.
He usually eats a lot.
He'll have rice and noodles.
He likes rice so much.
Just don't worry about us.
Xi Xi.
You've only been CEO for a year,
and you've gotten so thin.
I got thinner?
-I think so.
-Really?
No, Dad.
She was never fat.
I think she's malnourished.
My figure is perfect, okay?
Young people these days have it tough.
I've seen it all.
By the way, the rascal
has lost weight. You'll see.
-He's back?
-Ding Ding is back?
He suffers
from jet lag.
He couldn't wait to see Ran Ran and Xi Xi.
Looks like he's now a changed person.
Didn't expect he'd take
the initiative to meet us.
Ding Ding.
You've become thinner.
Hello, everyone.
-Dad.
-You look handsome.
Your hairstyle is really nice.
Help yourself, Ding Ding.
Shouldn't you inform us
that you're back?
Well,
you should have at least
informed us, right?
What? Are we not important enough?
I think so.
That must be it.
Look at Ding Ding.
Now he's just like Ran Ran
when he returned from overseas then.
You like the local food better, right?
I don't think he's become thinner.
Mind your words.
You two always bullied Ding Ding
when you were kids.
Now you've grown up and yet
you're still doing the same thing.
No, we didn't. Have some more.
Don't mind them, Ding Ding. Eat up.
I'm done.
Are you kidding?
Eat some more.
You could use more weight.
That's enough.
Say,
Chubby Ding.
You've been a finance guy in the UK
for quite a while now.
You must've made a lot of money.
You should have visited
the Chinese restaurants
in Chinatown more often.
His little deals are nothing
compared to Duan Ran's business.
and Xi Xi.
You're too humble.
I heard
Ding Ding set up an
investment company overseas.
How can we even compare?
Meanwhile, we have to work so hard
to solicit funding
unlike this genius.
Is that so?
Don't you have QE Group to back you?
Why do you need to solicit funding?
So dishonest.
Who'd invest in you?
Xi Xi is trying to be modest.
Can't you tell?
He still lacks experience.
Where are you taking me?
Who are we seeing?
You'll know when we reach.
Just trust me.
I've always trusted you.
What kind of setup is this?
Why are there four sets of tableware?
How many of them?
The couple is having a meal here.
I've invited them to
come after their meal.
A couple?
It's unexpected.
Jia Yun.
You're here.
-We're late.
-It's okay.
We've some snacks and tea here.
-Jia Yun.
-Please take a seat.
-Chen Lang.
-Mr Duan.
-Long time no see.
Take a seat.
Jia Yun has arranged today's meeting,
I thought I'm going to see Duan Ran.
I didn't expect it to be you two.
Why?
Is seeing me making you uncomfortable?
Not at all.
I'm flattered.
I'm just flattered.
Well, I actually have an
appointment with a couple of friends
next door.
I'm going over to meet them.
Please excuse me.
Let me walk you to the door.
No, I'm fine.
Bye.
-Thanks for coming.
-Bye, Jia Yun.
Okay.
What's going on with you?
You should have informed me
when you invited Mr Duan Sr.
I feel guilty meeting them.
It's so embarrassing.
No matter what, we're already here.
Stop muttering in front of me.
Let's sit down and chat.
Mr Duan, I heard
that you fainted during the negotiation.
How are you now?
It's just an old bug.
I'm quite used to it.
Chen Lang.
If I'm right,
after the Sanya incident,
this is our second meeting, right?
Mr Duan,
actually I don't deserve to meet you.
I understand.
I've done some pretty bad things.
I'm a real jerk.
It takes time
to become a jerk, and it takes time
to turn over a new leaf.
Even if I'm remorseful,
I can't redeem myself.
Don't be so hasty to draw conclusions.
In this world,
there's always a chance for redemption.
First of all,
let me dispel your
misunderstanding about us.
You, Ran Ran and Xi Xi.
To me, you three
are like my children.