♫  Everything is different from the sea to the sky  ♫
♫  The person I used to be has disappeared without a trace  ♫
♫  I no longer believe one person can redeem another  ♫
♫  Until when you broke into my world  ♫
♫  Even if the world exploded into darkness  ♫
♫  We bloom in the dark  ♫
♫  The knight and the king  ♫
♫  Sail at night with white sails to navigate
and protect the vast ocean  ♫
♫  I can see a clear direction  ♫
♫  In which a touch of golden color flickers
at the end of the wheat field  ♫
♫  Even if I am the king  ♫
♫  With supreme glory everything would be meaningless without you  ♫
♫  Going through fire and water is to make you remember  ♫
♫  The way everything was at the beginning  ♫
♫  If I am the king  ♫
♫  Who is as arrogant as the fierce wind and wild grass  ♫
♫  I only want you to be at my side, whatever it takes  ♫
♫  And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning  ♫
- I'll have a cup of Americano.
- Okay. Just a moment.
- Thank you.
- Please visit us again.
He's quite handsome.
But I wonder if you can handle him.
He's coming. He's coming.
Li Xun.
I'm Chen Minmin from School of Foreign Languages.
Would you like to dine with me later?
No.
Are you going back to your dorm later?
If you need anything, just let me know.
No need.
What a poser!
Is it fun?
I'm not stalking you.
I'm here on a mission.
Really?
Here's the thing.
The department has recently checked the attendance of morning self-study.
Well, we're freshmen and we just started school, so the department keeps a close eye on us.
Are you in primary school or kindergarten?
Do you think it's useful to study in the morning?
No matter whether it's useful or not, that's the rule of the school.
- We should observe...
- Here.
Press the space button.
A game?
Move the character around to avoid the ball coming down from above and across the river.
Three chances.
If you make it, I'll attend the morning self-study.
Keep your word.
You called that a ball coming down from above?
It clearly smashes down.
How many balls are there?
Two balls for three chances.
I already know where the first one is going to land.
I'm going to find out where the next one will fall next, and pass it at the third chance.
That's simple.
This ball is going way too fast.
I've pressed the keyboard as fast as I can.
Are you throwing in the towel?
Isn't there another chance?
Game over.
What's going on?
Editor.
[// if we have only one player, we restart the level, if (Player.Count &lt; 2)
- This if statement means…
- The player is dead when crossing the river.
If the player gets hit by a ball, he dies.
- If he crosses the river, he dies too. You must have got it wrong.
- No.
- I'll die anyway.
- Yeah.
- So this is a game to lose.
Why did you want me to play it?
I don't like you.
What?
Because I don't like you.
Why?
You are so fake.
You lose. Don't come to me for morning self-study again.
And this is my place.
You are not allowed to come up without my permission.
Why couldn't you just cross the river?
I did.
So what?
He designed that program.
I died anyway.
Didn't he just make fun of you?
In fact, his little game was quite simple.
Although I still don't understand the meaning of that function,
the logic of the code was very simple.
Although I don't know how the rich become rich,
I think the logic is very simple.
Fang Shumiao, for whom did I suffer such humiliation?
Another four points will be deducted tomorrow.
Four points after four points.
How many four points are left?
What's the point of reading now? You lost.
He said I was so fake. I think he just has a problem with me.
Is it great to know how to program?
- What's wrong?
- Look at this.
Isn't it the same game?
It's said that he was the top scorer.
But he just used an example from the textbook.
Are you still reading? Stop staying up and go to bed.
Did Li Xun irritate you so much?
Yes, he really did.
You!
- Zhu Yun.
- Morning.
You must be possessed.
No. It's lights-out time. Where do you get the electricity?
Beware of electric shock.
I managed to get it from the water room.
Are you waiting for me?
Shall we play a ball game in the afternoon?
How about yesterday?
Sure.
Why are we sitting this far in the front?
People tend to be sleepy when the computer is hot.
I won't doze off in the front.
Looks like you're really in a fight with Li Xun.
It's not a big deal.
We lost another four points this morning.
It is a big deal.
The professor is surnamed Lin.
The seniors said they all call him Old Lin privately,
and he is a big shot in the circle.
Nine out of ten coders are bald and one is with sparse hair.
It's no exaggeration at all.
He hasn't come yet.
He doesn't even show up for the first class.
How can he be that arrogant?
Well, this computer is broken and can't be started.
- Broken?
- Yes.
- You can find another spot.
- Here.
So warm-hearted.
No, no, no.
What a fatal attraction!
Boys and girls, do any of you
know about C language
or have tried to write some small programs in C language before?
We all know that it's an information society now.
The computer develops very fast,
and so does the programming language.
Compared with the emerging programming languages,
C language is like me standing in front of you.
What does that mean?
It's getting old.
As the old saying goes, "Older and wiser."
Age has many advantages.
The older it gets,
the richer and more rigorous it is.
No matter whether you go on studying algorithms,
compilations, databases, or operating systems,
the C language skills you're going to learn
will be the foundation for all of your future programming.
Kungfu is all about skill.
Don't make mistakes that good students usually like to make.
Be a fight-to-the-death book.
At the mention of C language, the first thing we need to know is what C language is.
So who can tell me what C language is?
Raise your hand!
- You studied so long last night.
- The nail that sticks up will be hammered down.
Lend it to me.
Lend it to me. Lend it to me.
What are you two talking about?
Are you reading other books?
Notes.
How detailed these notes are.
Can you answer my question?
C language is a process-oriented abstract programming language,
which is widely used in low-level development.
C language can be compiled in a simple way to deal with low-level memory.
It's a high-level programming language
that produces only a small amount of machine language
and does not require any runtime support to run.
Despite its many low-level features,
it remains cross-platform
and can be compiled on many computer platforms,
including embedded processors and supercomputers.
Good job.
Let's give her a big hand.
Take your seat.
Your game is no big deal.
What a fight-to-the-death book.
- What's your name, classmate?
- I'm Zhu Yun.
Zhu Yun.
It's easy to remember and it sounds good.
You'll be my class rep.
I can't, sir.
You can.
Why can't you?
It seems you are not only shy but also modest.
It's a done deal.
You've got to stop being modest.
Let's move on.
Game over.
Mr. Lin, as for the class rep, you'd better find someone else.
Why? Are you afraid it will take too much of your time?
Not really.
It's just a bit of a hassle.
What's the difference?
Don't make a decision. Go back and think about it.
We have a class tomorrow.
Can you answer me then?
I have to go to the canteen.
My wife will be mad at me if I fail to buy red-cooked pork.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
It's good to be a class rep.
You're so lucky.
He is a big shot in the circle and going to give us several specialized courses.
You can't do any harm by cottoning up to him.
Come on, I'll wait for you.
From primary school to junior high school, I have been the class rep
of Chinese, math, English, biology, chemistry, and geography.
If I was serious, my classmates would be annoyed with me.
If I didn't take it seriously, the teacher scolded me.
I was dog-tired every day, but couldn't please either side.
I didn't want to to be a class rep again after I made it to college.
Are you afraid he'll get you in trouble if you're the class rep?
He's part of the reason.
Aren't you the perfect example?
Some people think the college entrance examination is the end.
This is absolutely wrong.
College is where you're really taught how to live.
So the college entrance examination isn't the destination
or even an intermediate station.
You can't take it easy in college.
Is it time to choose class leaders?
Were you in?
No.
What about the class rep?
Class reps have the most contact with teachers and are very important.
There is one.
Which class?
C Language. It was settled today.
That's great.
Then do your best and show your teacher what you can do.
I didn't say yes.
Why?
Do you dislike the class or the teacher?
You can't always be so headstrong.
It's supposed to be tough and tiring to study or work.
Mom, I really don't want to be a class rep anymore.
No way. You have to listen to me.
I've worked in education all my life.
I can tell you responsibly that being a class rep will only do you good and no harm.
- But…
- Enough.
When is the next C Language class?
Tomorrow.
Okay. Then tell the teacher in class tomorrow that you want to be the class rep.
You hear me?
- Mom!
- Just do as I say.
I have a meeting soon.
I have to go. Do as you're told.
Are you going to do the laundry?
Yes.
That's a very good idea.
You can't be a good programmer without breaking a few keyboards.
Class rep, come here.
Distribute these copies to everyone.
Sir, I haven't decided yet.
Come here.
Is Director Liu your mom?
Yes.
Your mom spoke to me through one of the school leaders about your concerns.
You don't have anything to worry about, do you?
The fact that I asked you to be the class rep means
I have every confidence in your ability, doesn't it?
My mom said I agreed, right?
Yes.
Why? Is there a problem?
No.
Jianhong is organizing a programming interest group.
You should join it, too!
- Why me?
- Sure.
All the teachers of my professional class have participated.
How can you, the class rep, not join it?
Mr. Lin has agreed to be the instructor of the interest group,
and even said that he would apply for a place for us to do activities.
Join in.
So not only do you have to join it
but you also have to be in charge together with Jianhong.
Well, I finally got you back.
I tried to make a small program in C language, but it never executes correctly.
Can you help me out? I've been working on it all day.
I declare the pointer first.
Next, all I have to do is allocate space to the graph and then I can manipulate the nodes directly.
- Why?
- Because there are nodes in the space of the graph.
I have to allocate memory space to the nodes when I apply for a graph.
Why can't it be executed correctly?
Because I didn't give a graph memory address to the pointer.
Why are you asking me when you know the answer?
Li Xun, Old Lin has agreed to tutor our interest group
and apply for a space for our activities.
I'm not in.
I'm in.
So?
I wanted to try out Li Xun's C language level,
but he set me up and I solved the problem by myself.
I think Li Xun is a master.
He deliberately led you to the answer.
It means he knew the answer.
I also feel that.
Li Xun is writing code in the dorm every day.
I can't read what he wrote anyway.
I don't think so.
Some people are just bluffing and actually don't understand anything.
How could he be a top scorer?
Someone is blinded by hate.
Someone helps others and can't tell the good from the bad.
Zhu Yun has a point.
Actions speak louder than words.
If you want to know how good Li Xun is, you have to look at what he writes.
Anyway we can make the game he did last time after a few classes.
That's the basic function. It doesn't look good to me.
Indeed.
This is a place Old Lin applied for us.
This is going to be the home of our programming interest group.
This is the place where we can do our activities.
What do you think? Pretty big.
It's so spacious.
It's a little dirty.
It'll be nice and tidy if we clean it up.
We'll have to do a deep clean.
You can.
Old Gao, why are you so interested in Li Xun's programming skills?
I just want to know how big the gap between us and the top scorer is.
You're not convinced, huh?
Everyone wants to be the top scorer, right?
Zhu Yun, are you convinced?
I may be convinced by other top scorers, but him…
See?
I think I'm just fine being normal.
It is extraordinary that you can be admitted to Nanhu University.
Has Li Xun handed in the homework assigned by Old Lin in the last class?
Everyone in the class turned it in except him.
I'm worried about how to explain to Old Lin.
- Well, hurry him up then.
- Hurry him up.
I can't even avoid him.
Aren't you afraid Old Lin will yell at you?
Whatever. I'll endure.
Li Xun is always so arrogant and looks down upon others.
Don't you guys wonder what his level really is?
It's so windy here that you can catch cold.
Didn't I tell you not to come up without my permission?
Everyone in the class turned in the homework for C Language except you.
I won't. I didn't do it.
- If you don't turn it in, your usual grade will be deducted.
- I don't care.
Are you afraid to hand it in?
Afraid?
Yeah. You appear to be a programming expert who types codes on your computer every day.
What if you hand in your homework with codes full of mistakes?
Wouldn't that be a shame?
So the best thing to do is not to hand it in, right?
Yeah.
Are you so interested in my programming skills?
What if you're just a pretty face?
What is our homework?
Find the maximum of three numbers.
So long. How come I finished it in less than ten lines?
Flash drive.
It suits you.
Coming. Coming.
Got his homework?
I'm pretty sure he's nothing but just a pretty face.
Why?
Isn't the logic of the homework very simple?
It can be done in ten lines of code.
He managed to write a hundred lines.
What is the most important thing about writing code?
It is to be simple.
He made such a simple logic so complicated.
He's just making a mystery out of it. Isn't he just a pretty face?
This seems to be a virus.
You have an i7 processor and 16 gigabytes of RAM.
Girl, you are a computer science student. Right?
You can even tell that? You're so experienced.
How can the average student use such a high-configuration computer?
You must have spent a lot of money on it.
Do you think it can be fixed?
Fool, don't bother me...
Isn't it just a little virus?
No sweat. Five minutes.
- I'll have it fixed in five minutes.
- Okay.
Girl, is Old Lin still the head of our department?
Are you my senior?
I was admitted in 2001.
You must be a freshman.
Well, don't worry.
The Computer Science Department of our college is famous,
so it'll be very easy for you to find a job later.
I used to work for a tech giant.
Then, why don't you work there anymore?
Well, it sounds nice.
To put it bluntly, I was still like a migrant worker on the internet.
That job consumed youth, hair, and waist.
Those in their thirties there looked like they were in their fifties,
and they were either in the office or in the ER.
Those who don't want to die young should change careers.
Well, who did this to you?
One of my classmates.
- Who?
- One of my classmates.
One of your classmates?
No way. How many classes have you freshmen taken in C language?
How is it possible to make it?
Wait a minute.
I have a virus here. Yeah, I can't handle it with my flash drive.
Change it. Change it. Change it. Take it easy.
Change it. Change it. Change it.
- Yes.
- It works. It works.
It works. It works. It works.
It works.
I think maybe we should reinstall the system in this case.
- Why did you call me here in such a hurry?
- Secretary Zhang, quick. Come on. Come here.
Your turn. Change it with yours.
Here. Come here.
Use your secret skill. Here. Be quick.
-  Have you done it the usual way?
- Yes. It didn't work.
That's it. That's where it changes.
- Here, it's going to pop out.
-  Was it made by the guy who created the panda joss-stick virus?
Her classmate.
Which year is her classmate in?
First year.
It's impossible. This is absolutely impossible.
Indeed. If… none of us can solve it.
If her classmate could do that, what else is he going to college for?
Am I right? That's very professional. It's way beyond our level.
Try again. Try again. Try again.
Why not ask him to meet us?
Okay, okay, okay.
Girl.
You done?
Not yet.
Would you introduce your classmate to us?
Yeah, introduce him to us.
Let's communicate with him. Get him here, so we can talk.
Yeah. We want to make friends with him.
Isn't it fixed?
Old Gao, here's your chance to practice.
Oh, no. It totally turned into a brick.
Zhu Yun, why don't you bring Li Xun over to tell us how to remove this virus?
I won't ask him for help even if it turns into a brick.
I'm going to the library to look things up.
It's just one virus. I just don't buy it.
Give it up.
Li Xun is really a genius.
He deserves to be the top scorer.
Fang Shumiao, do you have a conscience?
If someone has no character, no matter how high his IQ is,
he won't succeed.
Yun, what about your homework?
Oh, no. Old Lin is still waiting for me in the office.
You didn't write a virus
to keep from turning in your homework, did you?
Don't make an excuse.
Let me see what kind of virus it is.
Who wrote it?
Li Xun.
Li Xun,
you wrote it yourself?
You brat.
Hurry up.
Hurry up. Take a seat.
Take a seat.
Li Xun, tell me how you wrote it in detail.
It's just a worm.
Worm?
Are you fooling me?
Don't hide it from me.
I've just patched and fixed the zero-day.
(is a broad term that describes recently discovered security vulnerabilities that hackers can use to attack systems.)
What else should I do?
You can't solve it by reinstalling the system either.
I planted a virus in every disk.
Every disk?
Go on.
I just want to try to make something like the panda joss-stick virus
that can infect exe, com, pif, src, html, and asp files,
terminate the anti-virus software and delete the backup files of the backup restore tool
so that the system can't be reinstalled.
You're terrible.
Do you want to bring down all the computers in our college?
But the panda joss-stick virus was still too low-tech and not subtle.
The more insidious the virus, the better.
What exactly are you planning to do?
Sir, in fact, now a virus is to obtain user information,
hijack the browser to install some programs, or take it as a botnet.
But a single computer is not worth much as a botnet.
What is there to steal from the average computer user?
That isn't worth attacking.
But the average person also has a lot of things on their computer that they don't want to lose;
such as, graduation papers, family photos, designs, and company documents.
All of these can generate exchange value.
For example, the 2008 Conficker is actually the same thing.
(A computer worm targeting the Microsoft Windows operating system.)
It's just that it spread on the internet.
The firewalls are getting smarter,
less vulnerable and harder to attack.
But the Automator virus is still very efficient.
Exactly.
So I made this computer a source of infection.
She'll get different people working on the virus.
Every time the system is reinstalled, it'll be connected to a different hard drive
and the virus will have direct access to the information.
Sir, did you just reinstall her system with your hard drive, too?
I was set up by you.
Don't worry, I only wrote the hack, not the extract.
Li Xun, tell me all about it.
I heard the worm has mutated.
Indeed.
Now, Windows XP operating system still has vulnerabilities.
Put this formula here. Go over here again.
Then add another line.
Then repeat…
Sir, your phone is ringing.
- If…
- Your call.
Hello.
Old Lin, what time is it and you still haven't come back?
I forgot my house key. Come back now.
Why did you forget the key again?
Fine. All right, all right.
I… I'll be right back. I'll be right back.
Sorry, it's my wife.
Here about this? I'll talk to you some other time.
Okay.
Class rep, why are you still here?
Sir, that virus.
Sorry. Sorry.
Li Xun, solve it now.
Okay.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Goodbye. Goodbye.
Li Xun.
You've arrived.
Are you going to solve it or not?
What time is it?
Stop pulling him. Let him go, girl.
Go back. Go back.
Let me go, girl.
Mr. Lin asked you to help me.
I just made it very clear in the office.
- You can't even remember that?
- I can't understand it even if I remembered it.
You don't understand it, do you?
I thought every class rep was excellent.
It seems that your interest group didn't teach you anything, either.
Will you do it or not?
What if I say no?
Are you still going to tell the teacher?
Li Xun, I admit I'm not as good as you.
I sincerely seek your help.
Will you help me to fix it? Okay?
Zhu Yun, you should study hard as you're worse than me.
What scum!
What happened?
It's just a virus. I don't believe I can't solve it.
Yun, get up.
- I'm not going.
- How can you not go?
- You're trying to kill me.
- I can't get up. I don't have the strength to get up.
- Hurry up.
- I'm not going.
Yun, the teacher will call the roll.
Come on up.
I don't want to go.
What am I supposed to do without you? The credits will be deducted.
Get up. I'll wash your face.
Get up and I'll wash your face.
What's wrong?
Is it that simple?
Old Gao is awesome. He really figured it out
Go and wash yourself.
There is no end to learning.
The library will be closed soon.
Welcome to Nanhu University Library again.
The lamb kebabs from Adao are tasty.
I just want to say thank you. I solved the virus.
You talked to Mr. Lin about the virus.
Old Gao and I looked into it and really solved it.
Although the virus was also thanks to you, we learned something at least. Thanks.
Li Xun, you get good grades and know how to program.
In fact, morning self-study is a time for us to communicate with each other.
Would you like to come and tutor your classmates?
I have no time.
The scholarship the school paid me isn't for tutoring my classmates.
But you're always absent from it.
It is a hot potato for Fang Shumiao, the monitor.
Do you know that the counselor has talked to her several times because of it?
If this goes on, our class won't be awarded merit
and Fang Shumiao won't get extra marks for the postgraduate recommendation.
She may be unhappy for the next four years because you don't go to the morning self-study.
I know you don't care if your marks are deducted,
but we are a group.
You still have to think about others. Right?
I knew you weren't so cold-blooded.
Well, many students slack off once they get to college
and waste four years of college.
- In fact, it is important to study in the morning.
- Are you done?
Yes.
So you said yes?
Yes to what?
Do I have to give my heart to you after eating ten of your lamb kebabs?
Are you unwilling to leave?
That's all right. I don't have to go back to the dorm.
I… I didn't take my phone.
Open the door.
As a man, you don't follow school rules and make others suffer the consequences.
Do you have any sense of responsibility?
Open the door and give me my phone.
Open it.
You!
Don't answer my phone.
Stop.
- Hello.
- Hello, Yun.
Is Shumiao with you?
Sorry.
Zhu Yun is busy right now.
I am sorry to interrupt.
Will you open the door?
I will drag you to the morning self-study.
Don't play any tricks on me.
You can't keep it closed forever.
I'm going to wait for you to open it.
What a fool.
♫  I have passed through the world  ♫
You don't have to keep an eye on me.
We can be together in the open.
You really gave yourself up?
He'll do anything to play tricks on me.
You clarified the fact?
Did his golden hair fade?
He didn't really dye his hair black for you, did he?
♫  It's the intuition of the dream  ♫
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I am leaning on your shoulder  ♫
♫  We will not separate  ♫
♫  Avoid the hustle and bustle by staying with me  ♫
♫  It's the center crease of your palm  ♫
♫  That holds me up by giving me the courage to move forward  ♫
♫  Just like a burning flame in the night  ♫
♫  'Cause I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  It's the intuition of the dream  ♫
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I also want to stand by your side  ♫
♫  As long as I am brave enough  ♫
♫  Every dream that I have  ♫
♫  Will not, will not, will not lose to time anymore  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫