♫  Everything is different from the sea to the sky  ♫
♫  The person I used to be has disappeared without a trace  ♫
♫  I no longer believe one person can redeem another  ♫
♫  Until when you broke into my world  ♫
♫  Even if the world exploded into darkness  ♫
♫  We bloom in the dark  ♫
♫  The knight and the king  ♫
♫  Sail at night with white sails to navigate
and protect the vast ocean  ♫
♫  I can see a clear direction  ♫
♫  In which a touch of golden color flickers
at the end of the wheat field  ♫
♫  Even if I am the king  ♫
♫  With supreme glory everything would be meaningless without you  ♫
♫  Going through fire and water is to make you remember  ♫
♫  The way everything was at the beginning  ♫
♫  If I am the king  ♫
♫  Who is as arrogant as the fierce wind and wild grass  ♫
♫  I only want you to be at my side, whatever it takes  ♫
♫  And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning  ♫
Lina, we have arrived. Are you at school?
Old Gao.
This is for you.
You bought it?
Last time you treated me to dinner, so just take it as a return gift.
You are so polite. Thank you.
I don't understand. I chose one that I thought was good.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
Don't you want to open it?
I like everything you give me.
Okay.
Old Gao, only you came?
Where's Li Xun? Has he come yet?
Yes.
Where is he?
In the room.
We changed our project as he said. I was just looking for him.
Let's go upstairs.
He's sleeping.
He sleeps at this point?
Is he an old man?
He's been irritated recently. Don't bother him.
He scolds people mercilessly.
Really?
Fine. Then I'll go shopping.
Let me go with you.
I'm free and want to take a walk.
All right.
This is so cute.
Yeah.
This Macchiato is too sweet. I'll get fat.
Then give it to me. I'll buy you a new one later.
This. Thank you for coming.
Welcome to the comprehensive oral care brand.
May I help you?
I want to buy a toothbrush for my friend.
- Would you recommend some?
- Okay.
Then you can take this marble electric toothbrush. It sells well.
- It can clean teeth effectively.
- Really?
There are twelve modes for you to adjust the intensity by yourself.
Is this for lovers?
Yes, it's for lovers.
It's pretty. Then I'd like to take a pair.
Okay. Will that be cash or charge?
Cash.
- Okay.
- Wait.
I'll buy it myself.  Card.
Okay.
You are back.
Yeah.
I bought some fruit. Have a bite.
Okay.
How was the discussion today?
- Pretty good.
- That's good.
Why did you come back so late?
I was stopped on my way back.
Go for the competition.
You are always No.1 in my heart.
You smile every day.
Xu Lina.
Let's go to the restaurant we ordered from last night.
Several groups eat together.
- How many of you are there?
- Zhu Yun?
You go first.
Bye-bye.
I remember when you graduated from high school,  you changed your phone number?
It suddenly occurred to me that I forgot to ask for your mobile number the last time I saw you.
You also came to the competition?
The last time I asked you, you didn't tell me.
I didn't see your name on the list.
Come on. Does you need to hide so deeply?
I'll have a group meeting later.
It'll end at about 7:00. Then let's have a meal.
No thanks.
We are old classmates. I haven't seen you for so long.
How about having a meal and talking about the past?
Our group has an appointment to have dinner together.
Is Li Xun also coming?
Of course.
You can keep your own trump deep.
I really want to see how capable he is.
Then I'll go first. I'll be late.
Wait. Tell me your phone number. Let me make a note.
I didn't bring my cell phone with me. I can't remember the number.
That's amazing. Next time.
Bye, old schoolmate.
Have you submitted it?
Deadline is 12:00. It's 11:40 now.
What are you doing?
Click submit.
Test it again?
No need. You've packed it.
Test it again.
How many times have you tested it?
What if there is a problem with this platform?
There are only three competition platforms.
Windows, Linux, and Unix.
Even pupils won't make any mistakes.
But I'm afraid.
Isn't it over?
That's it?
What a rabbit.
- Hello. Hello. Hello.
- Here.
Okay.
Hello. Hello.
I'm so sorry.
It doesn't matter. I just arrived.
Is that so? Well, I'd like to leave for a while.
Order me a macchiato.
- Okay.
Waiter.
- Hello.
- A macchiato, not too sweet.
Okay.
Thank you, Brother Feng.
How is it? Isn't this a good place?
You should have avoided suspicion at this time.
But you asked me out alone.
I've invited you to such a far place.
- It has avoided suspicion enough.
- Fang Zhijing.
What on earth happened?
Isn't that the sponsor of the competition?
Brother Feng, I heard that Nanhu University has recently had a pretty good project.
The judges loved it.
You heard about it?
Have you seen their project? How did you like it?
What's wrong? Are you scared?
Scared? Not at all.
Anyway, you can't be more careful.
By the way, Brother Feng, can you discuss this with Mr. Chen
and ask him to apply for a star prize with the organizing committee?
There is no such award. It won't work.
Brother Feng, listen to me first.
Think about it. Haven't we made an agreement?
The contract is ready, waiting only for the signature.
Mr. Chen also needs to enhance his performance this year. Right?
If something goes wrong here, the company must treat him as a joke.
How should I persuade Mr. Chen?
How about this? I can give in three more percent in the patent transfer fee.
Brother Feng, later, for the annual patent transfer fee, you will take 30% and me, 70%.
Okay. I'll give it a try.
Great. Thank you, Brother Feng.
I have a meeting this afternoon. I have to go.
Let me walk you out.
Wait, Brother Feng, take an umbrella.
Thank you for that.
Discuss it with Mr. Chen.
Fang Zhijing?
Isn't that person beside Fang Zhijing from our competition's sponsor?
You know him?
He was also present at the forum.
What is Fang Zhijing doing with him?
What are you up to?
He must be trying to do something.
During the competition, meeting with sponsors privately is against the rules.
Don't be so impulsive.
I'm going to report them to the organizing committee.
Do you have any evidence?
We saw it with our own eyes.
So what?
Did you hear what they said?
It's against the rules to meet privately.
But at most, they will get a notice of criticism.
Can it help?
What a coincidence. We even came across him.
I didn't expect Fang Zhijing to make such a move.
What happened to Fang Zhijing?
When we had coffee this afternoon, we met Fang Zhijing.
I've never met any mean person like him.
We saw him with someone from the organizing committee.
What happened?
Sorry. I'll answer the phone first.
The competition will start soon.
He met the sponsor in secret at a far away place.
They wouldn't have a normal chat only.
I think they are simply negotiating to directly decide the award-winning final winner.
They have determined the result of the finals?
What finals? They are cheating fools like us.
- Why is it so cold?
- Has the taxi arrived?
Not yet, but soon.
What would you like for dinner?
Some people are really mean.
They can do anything for an award.
Being able to sell patents are a kind of ability.
Instead of gossiping here,
some people would be better to go back and improve their level.
What level should I improve?
The level of playing tricks and pulling strings?
What bullshit are you talking about?
Whether it's bullshit is clear to everyone.
Xu Lina,
what right do you have to slander me about "playing tricks and pulling strings"?
You are just a gifted student of folk dance
who got in by adding points.
Aren't you clear about your programming level?
Have you no shame to say this?
Make it clear.
You are clearer than me about how many people you asked for help
to make your shabby system.
You alone will never be able to enter the finals in your life.
But I've improved it at least three times.
Right, Li Xun?
Miss Xu.
Next time, before you criticize someone,
consider whether you have this ability first.
You.
Here, let's go.
How can there be such a person?
Fang Zhijing.
Is what Xu Lina said true?
Zhu Yun, why are you so naive now?
Can you ask this directly?
I asked you if it was true.
You participate in this competition
because you really want to compete with me?
What a pity.
I'd love to compete with your God Li.
But there's no chance.
Maybe next time.
It's all cut and dried.
You are so scared about Li Xun attending?
You're using such unscrupulous means.
The judges think my stuff is good. So is it called means?
People like Xu Lina only play tricks. You saw it too.
They have their resources.
I have my way.
Don't just say anyone.
And I don't even care.
Do you know the essential difference between them and me?
They can choose to talk nonsense or not.
I can also choose to listen or not.
But whether they talk nonsense or not, my result will not be changed.
If I choose to listen, at most, I will be annoyed for a while.
If I choose not to listen,
then I'm the winner.
You're so smart.
You should understand who is better.
In this world, heroes are always judged by success.
People always worship the strong.
Believe it or not.
As long as I keep succeeding,
everyone will forget today's criticism
and become my fanatical followers and admirers.
Okay, I'm done.
I have to go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I squeezed so much time out,
not to see you like this.
I'm sorry.
Do you hate Fang Zhijing?
I see.
Aren't you going to ask why?
No.
What if the reason doesn't convince you?
It doesn't matter if there's no reason.
Everyone can make decisions based on their emotions.
Do you have a way?
No.
Do not overdo it.
Some things have no result originally.
To stop loss in time,
waste less time.
I'm tired. You can leave.
Hello.
How are you feeling now? Are you nervous?
Let me tell you.
On the day of the competition,
the group leader will go to the stage to explain first
and the judges will score on the spot.
You have only ten minutes to explain.
Then it's the work demonstration.
Zhu Yun.
Class rep.
Mr. Lin.
I mean, you need to demonstrate it first.
In a short time, show clearly the work's creativity, technology roadmap, and application prospect
to the judges and audience.
This is important.
Got it?
Yeah.
Mr. Li,
that USB encryption project of the Information Technology University will be awarded anyway?
Miss Zhang told me about this. I also inquired about it indirectly.
There is definitely a rumor
saying that a star prize will be set up.
Don't think so much about it. This is beyond our control.
Just mind your business.
We learn for ourselves, right?
I see.
I have other lessons. I'm waiting for your good news.
- Bye-bye.
- All right, goodbye, Mr. Lin.
Goodbye, Mr. Lin.
Didn't you listen to Mr. Lin?
They gave them a star prize.
This is good for us.
The biggest competitor is left.
It will do us no harm.
We have a better chance.
No chance.
He will still stand on the stage like a success,
saying those acceptance speeches proudly.
No one knows how dirty he is.
No one can tear off his hypocritical mask either.
In this world, there is no absolute fairness.
Moreover, there are countless roads to victory.
Even if one way is blocked by you,
there are still countless ways for him to take.
Where's Li Xun? Where is he?
He hasn't been back for days.
He didn't answer any calls or WeChat massages.
I can't tell if he came for the competition or travel.
I'm tired. I'd like to go back to get some rest.
By the way, Brother Feng, can you discuss this with Mr. Chen and ask him to apply for a star prize with the organizing committee?
Do you really think no one can defeat you?
Li Xun,
even if you block one of his ways,
there are countless other ways he can take.
Do you really think you can do anything?
I think we have no problem.
Princess, have a look again.
Stop that. Where's Li Xun?
I don't know.
Congratulations.
You know what?
You won the first prize this time.
- Really?
- And what about you?
I can't compete with you.
I got a star prize.
You don't even have a chance to compete with me.
Are you disappointed?
Where's Li Xun? He is absent again?
He's busy.
He is really mysterious.
He doesn't leave any chance for others to worship him.
You can get this result in your freshman year. That's great.
Let's have a chat later.
Bye.
He is really bold-faced.
Next, we are going to issue the first prize in this competition.
Nanhu University. LAN ARP Protocol Attack Defense System Based on Switch.
Winners are Gao Jianhong, Zhu Yun, and Li Xun.
- Let's go together.
- You go.
Thank you.
Great!
Next is our most important link.
We have a work that stood out at the competition stage
and got the opportunity to sign the contract in advance.
The purpose of this competition is to promote exchange and cooperation
between enterprises and universities.
This work has taken the first step for us.
So we set up a star prize.
The winner is the Information Technology University's
USB intelligent encryption interface.
Participants are Fang Zhijing, Wang Yujun, and Zhang Shuo.
Well, we also invite the sponsor of this competition,
leader of Huake Technology Co., Ltd to present the award to them on stage.
Thank you.
I'll call Mr. Lin.
- Yes, sure.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Fang Zhijing.
Right here.
First of all, I would like to thank the organizing committee for giving us this star prize.
Secondly, I want to thank all of you here.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you.
Get down!
I know there have been a lot of rumors in the school recently,
saying that I cheated or I stole another's work.
Originally, a clean hand wants no washing.
As I have never done it, I don't need to explain too much.
But for the rest of my team, this is quite unfair.
So right here, I solemnly clarify to everyone that, I, Fang Zhijing,
have never done anything that violated the rules of the competition.
Those irresponsible remarks, slander, or false accusations,
will damage the reputation of this information contest,
and a great insult to the fairness and impartiality of this contest.
It's an insult to the fairness of the competition...
that you can win a star prize for this shabby project.
Is it Li Xun?
Who is this?
Li Xun.
What's up?
You have been disappearing for days.
Where have you been these days?
I went to do something bad.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean,
your so-called encryption interface is totally vulnerable...
and doesn't deserve this prize.
Li Xun, you should be responsible for your remarks.
Am I afraid of responsibility or are you afraid of responsibility?
Yeah. Are you afraid of responsibility?
Yeah. Yeah.
You are afraid?
Afraid?
Okay.
If he can crack my encrypted USB disk,
I can give up this patent transfer fee to him.
But if...
you can't break it,
you...
need to apologize to me.
Okay.
It's a deal.
For the sake of fairness, I'd better use the computer of the organizing committee.
Help yourself.
This competition will be wonderful.
I have confidence in Fang Zhijing.
What are they doing?
Li Xun is cracking Fang Zhijing's encryption USB disk.
I've seen your plan introduction. Good concept.
Of course.
Or I couldn't take it.
Within a minute, I have three ways to crack it.
Okay.
This USB disk contains my personal privacy.
If he can crack it, I'll show it to you all.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
Go ahead.
You're very considerate.
To prevent forgetting the password, while the USB disk is encrypted,
usually a key is generated.
Indeed.
Our patent considers that many people forget their passwords.
But you are not skilled enough.
What is generated is a local static key.
This key can be found as long as your computer is hacked.
The letter "e" here represents the drive letter to be unlocked.
This is the local static key you saved.
Great.
Let me see.
There's no privacy.
You hid them all?
Oh my god.
His girlfriend is there.
You didn't hide such private things well?
From the source of the document, you have another WeChat account.
Does your girlfriend know about it?
That's not good.
It's not over yet.
Do you want to see it?
Yes.
Let's continue.
The second way.
Empty disk copying.
Now, I am about to use Ghost to copy the disk.
But I have to say your encryption software is quite secure.
Even in DOS, it also prohibits the use of Ghost.
Once Ghost is activated, the USB disk will pop up automatically.
Even if you plug it back in, it cannot be seen in Ghost.
Therefore, I used DiskGenius,
software for direct operation of the hard disk.
Insert two USB drives to copy directly and decrypt successfully.
Because this encryption software is associated with the serial number of the USB disk,
if it enters a new USB disk, the file will be automatically released.
Great!
You can't delete the file cleanly.
You need to improve your safety awareness.
You don't deserve the star prize in the Information Security Network Competition.
Well done, Li Xun!
So cool!
Great! Well done!
This is too outrageous.
Chairman Peng, you can't let him do this anymore.
Don't worry.
Isn't he testing your product?
This is not in accordance with the rules of the competition.
It's not appropriate here.
I'll ask you again later.
You just leave in this way?
If you run away, your patent can't be sold.
Here is a chance for you. Put a patch.
Only five seconds left.
Li Xun, there are only five seconds left.
Can you?
Let's get started.
Li Xun! There are three seconds left.
Chairman Peng, look at him.
What do you mean? You can't afford to play?
Who can't afford to play?
You can't afford to play?
Look at him.
He can't afford to play.
How is it?
Admit failure?
Do you still need me to explain this to you?
The third method is the physical method.
As long as the flash granule or the main control chip is replaced,
the original software encryption will be automatically invalidated.
I don't need to explain such a simple truth to you, right?
Sorry. I just delayed you a minute.
But then, I have to delay you for a bit longer.
This is the surveillance video of last Saturday afternoon from a cafe on Nanchang Road.
What does that mean?
Tian Feng is really my senior. I admit we should avoid suspicion before the competition.
But I haven't seen him for a long time. We just met and had coffee.
What's wrong?
Any problems? Any problems?
Really?
By the way, Brother Feng, can you discuss this with Mr. Chen
and ask him to apply for a star prize with the organizing committee?
Think about it. Haven't we made an agreement?
This is the cafe I went to that day. The day I saw him.
Mr. Chen also needs to enhance his performance this year. Right?
If something goes wrong in the end, the company must treat him as a joke.
How should I persuade Mr. Chen?
How about this? I can give in three more percent in the patent transfer fee.
Later, for the annual patent transfer fee, you will take 30% and me, 70%.
Okay. I'll give it a try.
Look what you've done?
Mr. Chen. Mr. Chen!
Mr. Chen, listen to me.
Li Xun, I'll remember you.
This student, I feel like you're kind of breaching the rules of the competition.
This will also affect your performance.
I see.
Then can you tell me why you did this?
Because of love.
♫  Everything is different from the sea to the sky  ♫
♫  The person I used to be has disappeared without a trace  ♫
♫  I no longer believe one person can redeem another  ♫
♫  Until when you broke into my world  ♫
♫  Even if the world exploded into darkness  ♫
♫  We bloom in the dark  ♫
Li Xun, I love you! You are so cool!
♫  The knight and the king  ♫
♫  Wherever I go, I just want to wander with you  ♫
♫  My princess will never be sad again  ♫
♫  If I am the king  ♫
♫  Who is as arrogant as the fierce wind and wild grass  ♫
♫  And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning  ♫
You beat us, the jury's face today.
That's good.
You finally supervised the fairness and justice of our competition.
We will revoke this star prize.
But you have to be punished.
I know.
By the way, I have a project in Sanya this summer vacation.
It's still a secret stage.
Would you like to go with me?
Let me think it over.
You are putting on airs.
All right, see you later.
Let's go.
Fang Zhijing,
in fact, you are smart in some ways.
Some of your ideas are also correct.
In this world, it's true to judge heroes by success.
But it's a pity.
You got the end time wrong.
There's still a long way to go.
It is not over yet.
Okay.
I'm waiting for it.
Let's go.
Are you happy?
Then give me a smile.
Silly girl.
Are you so happy?
Yeah. I've never been so happy.
That's good.
Otherwise, I would lose a lot.
Where did you go the other day?
Did you really think I could decode Fang Zhijing's encrypted USB within one minute?
I've been working for several days. I'm so exhausted.
Li Xun.
What kind of person do you think can be called a princess?
Princess.
First,
must have a pair of lofty eyes.
In addition, she must have an innocent and fragile heart.
Yes, of course.
If she has dash of risk-taking adventure,
that would be better.
You think he and I...
Perfect match.
Slow down.
Li Xun.
I want to start a business with you, starting from L&amp;P.
Do whatever you want.
I'm your confidence.
Xun!
I came to see you.
Why are you here?
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I am leaning on your shoulder  ♫
♫  We will not separate  ♫
♫  Avoid the hustle and bustle by staying with me  ♫
♫  It's the center crease of your palm  ♫
♫  That holds me up by giving me the courage to move forward  ♫
♫  Just like a burning flame in the night  ♫
♫  'Cause I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  It's the intuition of the dream  ♫
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I also want to stand by your side  ♫
♫  As long as I am brave enough  ♫
♫  Every dream that I have  ♫
♫  Will not, will not, will not lose to time anymore  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫