♫  Everything is different from the sea to the sky  ♫
♫  The person I used to be has disappeared without a trace  ♫
♫  I no longer believe one person can redeem another  ♫
♫  Until when you broke into my world  ♫
♫  Even if the world exploded into darkness  ♫
♫  We bloom in the dark  ♫
♫  The knight and the king  ♫
♫  Sail at night with white sails to navigate
and protect the vast ocean  ♫
♫  I can see a clear direction  ♫
♫  In which a touch of golden color flickers
at the end of the wheat field  ♫
♫  Even if I am the king  ♫
♫  With supreme glory everything would be meaningless without you  ♫
♫  Going through fire and water is to make you remember  ♫
♫  The way everything was at the beginning  ♫
♫  If I am the king  ♫
♫  Who is as arrogant as the fierce wind and wild grass  ♫
♫  I only want you to be at my side, whatever it takes  ♫
♫  And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning  ♫
Unexpectedly, this store is still open here.
I know just a few stores.
Yes. Back then you seldom took me to restaurants like this.
That was a favor to you.
You remember it very clearly.
What is this?
Chronology of events.
You didn't have time, right?
How long did it take you to write this?
What you wrote is just ordinary.
They are historical events accessible to all.
But this kind of game needs a sense of curiosity.
It requires more details.
I've compiled several e-books and posts on forums,
including some unofficial history records.
Unofficial history?
Those are my favorites.
I made it for you to study,
not for your curiosity.
You don't usually play games.
The last time I played a game is...
Are telling me the last game you played was the one I designed for you?
A game?
Three chances.
If you make it, I'll attend the morning self-study.
I also found several games similar to Invincible Generals.
The installation package is on the flash drive.
Tomorrow is the weekend. Don't go to the company.
Take time to play and feel it.
You stood up on impulsion.
Think about your capability before doing that.
Can't you say something nice?
So are you going to fight with Gao Jianhong?
Yes.
Invincible General will be our first bullet.
Be serious.
I see.
Boss!
I'll have a bottle of Erguotou.
Wait.
- Are you going to drink?
Yes. I want to celebrate.
- Okay.
- Wait.
We don't need alcohol.
Why? Mind your own business.
Don't drink.
None of your business.
Don't serve the alcohol. I won't pay for it.
I will. Serve it.
Well. Excuse me.
Who should I listen to?
Me.
I'm the group leader.
Serve it, Boss. Thanks.
Can't I celebrate?
You don't need to walk me back.
I'm not drunk.
When I was abroad...
You learned to drink abroad.
It has nothing to do with that.
You misguided me.
I learned to drink from you.
I drank for the first time.
I played games for the first time.
The first bullet Invincible General.
I work desperately for the first time.
Great.
How were you doing abroad?
Great, except that I had to speak English
and the food was terrible.
But I was happy as I could do and learn what I liked.
Won't you go abroad again?
Are you going to give up?
We'll miss many things in our life.
I know what I want,
so every step I take is in that direction.
I'll never regret.
That's what you told me.
Don't say that I corrupted you.
Are you sober now?
Yes.
My room is up there.
Thank you for sending me back.
See you.
See you tomorrow.
What do you want to eat today?
Whatever.
Then eat nothing.
Who it it?
Who are you?
I want to meet Li Xun.
She wants to meet you.
Long time no see.
What can I do for you?
May I come in?
Do you have time?
Let's go out for dinner.
No.
He is cooking.
Okay. Let's dine at home.
I didn't prepare food for you.
Never mind. I'll prepare it.
The dishes are ready.
Please enjoy your meal.
Send Mr. Wang back.
Enjoy it. Help yourself.
Okay.
Do you really work in the Flying Company?
Ask Old Gao and you'll know.
He keeps watch on us every day.
How about Zhu Yun?
If you're curious about her,
ask her directly.
I knew she'd go to work there with you.
But don't you think it's a bit shabby to start like this?
I'll leave the key here.
Drive my car.
My dad has a vacant apartment.
You can live there to make use of it.
It's cramped here.
You're here to poach him?
You want to keep me as a boy toy?
Have you ever thought that if we were together,
everything would be different now?
Can we make it up now?
I can't.
No.
I feel a little sick.
Li Xun,
you never regreted it?
Xu Lina,
you especially came to this rented house and reminded me.
Thank you.
If there is one thing I don't regret,
it's that I refused you.
You will never be able...
to compare to Zhu Yun.
I won't see you out.
Old Gao has been on a business trip for just a few days.
I have to tell him about this.
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
Get to know my enemy.
What else can you do except playing dirty like this?
Playing dirty?
Old Gao thought of this.
It has nothing to do with me.
You're contemptible.
Good-for-nothing;
You look furious.
What did he do to you?
You make me sick.
Xu Lina, don't forget that Old Gao provides everything for you.
- Go.
- Yes.
- He bought the car for you.
Mom, it's time to eat.
Xiuzhu's painting is so imposing.
I like it very much.
Thank you, Aunt.
Come on. Please taste this tomato beef soup I made.
Thank you for making so many dishes for us.
What are you doing here this time?
I can accompany for the next two days.
You don't need to accompany me.
I came to see what Zhu Yun was doing.
She has been helping me with the painting exhibition these days.
I'm going to ask her to go back in a few days.
You just rent this place.
I can help you with guest coordination and site layout.
When will your exhibition start?
- Next week.
- Next month.
It'll start next week and end next month.
Okay.
At that time, I will definitely come to join you.
Then Zhu Yun can stay here to help with your exhibition preparation.
Here. I wish you a successful exhibition.
Thank you.
Mom, I'll make a phone call.
Xiuzhu,
is everything all right with Yun recently?
She has been helping me with my exhibition recently.
What's wrong?
To tell the truth,
although that young man is in prison,
Zhu Yun overthinks too much.
I fear that she'll go and meet him without telling us.
Keep an eye on her.
Don't worry.
I'll report to you as soon as possible if anything goes wrong.
Okay.
I'm relieved to have you here.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Okay.
You said the exhibition will start next week.
What if my mom comes next week?
Taste this tomato beef soup.
Tell me. How does it fare to your liking?
I didn't expect that you could draw and cook now.
Sorry, Auntie. I'll answer the phone.
Hello, Mom.
Brother Xiuzhu, you're sending our enemy a bomb.
You said the exhibition would start next week and end next month.
My mom can come anytime.
What if she comes suddenly?
Don't worry. I can deal with it.
I'm having dinner with Zhu Yun and Aunt Liu.
It's almost midnight there, right?
Convince her.
I have to go back to work this afternoon.
Let's just say we're going to meet the guests of the art exhibition.
Don't let it slip.
Okay. No problem.
Your mom?
Mom, Aunt Liu is here with me.
Do you want to talk to her?
Okay.
Hello, Jiang.
I...
Hello?
-  Hello?
- I'll check it.
The phone hung up.
The infrastructure abroad is unreliable.
The connection is broken.
- How about calling back?
- Okay.
Don't bother her. It's time to sleep.
How do you know that?
Uncle goes fishing and Aunt goes running every morning.
Now it's midnight there.
You remember it better than I do.
Of course. The lake near your house connects to a private lawn.
It would be wonderful to hold a wedding ceremony
in such a beautiful place.
By the way, Aunt, well,
I'll meet a professor of the School of Art of Nanhu University.
I'm afraid I can't keep you and Zhu Yun company.
You're familiar with Nanhu University.
Yes, I am. I'll go with you.
Right.
Then-Then I'll go with her.
No problem. You can go together.
- Leave the room card to me.
- Okay.
I'll go back first.
- Taste this shrimp, Aunt.
- Okay.
Great. We're safe.
So I covered you to let you go to your company to play games?
It's important to the fate of three people and Flying Network.
Why are you staring at me?
Zhu Yun, you've changed.
You aren't who you were abroad.
You just finished your work mechanically abroad.
But now when you talk about your game,
you sound so proud and your eyes are shining.
After all, this is the first work I'll complete as an independent group leader.
Okay. I'll walk you upstairs.
No need. I can go up by myself.
Well, let me have a look at the birthplace of the rising stars of the Chinese game industry.
We're a small company.
This elevator is old.
Wait.
Sir, wait.
You looked familiar when getting off the car downstairs.
It's you.
- Your friend?
- Yes.
You work with Zhu Yun?
Hello. Tian Xiuzhu.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, are you painter Tian Xiuzhu?
Yes.
You're my idol.
I have two idols in my life.
One is Xu Kaiyang, my university senior.
The other is you. I like you so much.
- It's an honor for our company.
- He is seeing his idol.
In addition to its appearance,
talents matter a lot to the strength of a company.
Zhu Yun and our company chose each other.
We're a powerful combination.
In recent years, startups in China start from scratch
and develop step by step.
Li Xun. Li Xun, let me introduce you.
This is Zhu's friend.
Tian Xiuzhu, a well-known painter. He is very famous.
I know him.
Mr. Tian, that's how he is.
- He is indifferent.
- Never mind.
- Taste this.
- Okay.
If you don't like it, I'll add some milk for you.
Thanks. All stages are cleared.
No wonder you have time to do other things.
Xiuzhu, we're going to work.
Would you go back first?
Okay. When should I come to pick you up?
No need.
You came out with me.
Your mom is waiting for us.
- You're right. Come at 5:00.
- Okay.
- See you.
- I'm leaving.
- See you, Mr. Tian.
Taste this, okay?
No, thanks for the offer.
Thank you. I'm leaving.
Are you leaving now?
Let-Let me see you out.
Zhu Yun, see him out. Go.
Take care, Mr. Tian.
Come here when you have time.
Take care.
- I'll go say hello to Aunt.
- No need.
Mom.
Aunt.
Perfect timing.
Come out with me.
Yun, I rented a room for you.
Mom, you should have asked me before renting it.
It would be too late.
So many people wanted to rent the room.
Fortunately, I immediately signed the contract and paid the money this afternoon.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be us who are looking at the house now.
I don't even have the right to live where I want to now.
You can choose, and Aunt will decide.
Xiuzhu, what do you think about this room?
Great. Very great, Aunt.
The environment is beautiful here.
And it's secure here.
I think the most important thing is that coincidentally,
it's just one kilometer away from my studio.
We can walk here.
- Really?
- Coincidence?
Mom, you planned this with Xiuzhu?
No. No. No.
It has nothing to do with him.
I rented this room for you on my own.
How much is the monthly rent for this room?
Don't worry about it.
I paid for three months.
You can pay me back if you have money.
I have no money.
Never mind.
Well, I think I need two domestic workers,
one for cleaning and the other for cooking.
I want them to do housekeeping. You'll pay them.
Aunt, how about this?
Zhu Yun led a frugal life abroad.
Now let's make her life easy.
Tomorrow, I'll find a domestic worker to do the cleaning for her.
I'll pay.
If Zhu Yun wants to eat, come to my studio.
I can cook for her anytime.
Great.
Xiuzhu, please take care of her.
Aunt, don't mention that.
Please, Aunt.
Please take care of her.
I will.
- See you.
You cooperated well with my mom.
Come in.
Go ahead. Because of your girlfriend?
Her name is Zhu Yun.
Just as I thought. I guessed it.
Well, you met the painter.
Don't mention him.
Okay. I won't.
Would you forget it if I didn't mention it?
I'm warning you.
Don't give me a lecture.
You look affected.
You don't need my help in terms of career.
As to relations,
to tell you the truth,
you're too naive.
At the time, it was you who drove away Sister-in-law.
You hurt her feelings severely.
How do you know she can't be by your side?
You drove her away at your own will.
Did you ask her what she thought?
You're sulking here alone.
Why don't you ask her if she is dating the painter?
Ask her?
You want me to ask her these questions?
How?
You're too paranoid.
The only thing I'll never learn from you since we met is
how you treat girls.
They're the most precious flowers in the world.
A sign of disturbance
will ruin their luster and fragrance.
That's why they turn old more easily than men.
You're disgusting.
Stop dancing.
You know what, you didn't give others a chance back then.
You chose for yourself.
So you don't know how they got through.
I don't know if she still loves you.
But what I know is that
if you want to achieve any goals now,
she will be the most able person to help you at any cost in the world.
Don't treat feelings like a computer.
They are't binary.
You should be mature.
Computers are binary.
They accept only two types of inputs,
because digital circuits can only accept 0 and 1.
That's because nonlinear electronic components
have only two nonlinear regions.
Stop.
I won't think about this again...
until this matter is completely solved.
Won't she think about it?
She's different from you.
She's prone to hitting dead ends, especially when it comes to the two of you.
If it's impossible, don't let her misunderstand.
Don't let her miss her own chance.
You know what? Your tenderness is a double-edged sword to her.
Once she feels that you can't move on,
she won't move on.
I can move on.
Then why bother coming here?
I think you are jealous.
Get out.
You're obviously flirting under the guise of work.
Group Leader Zhu and Li.
Wasn't this just a change of identity at the base back then?
She is right. A secret office romance play.
The PUA battle between female boss and male subordinate.
What you say sounds filthy.
Come on. We're obviously praising your innocence.
- Yes.
- He just fixed the computer for you
and you just had midnight snacks somewhere that you two had visited together.
Isn't this flirting?
We did these for work.
But listen, we'll start making weapon effects next week. And...
We're not curious about that.
You're annoying.
Anyway, I'm energetic after drinking coffee.
If you say nothing interesting, we won't let you go.
Tell us. What you are thinking?
What do you mean?
We agreed that we would be ordinary colleagues.
She is exposing herself when trying to hide.
Let me ask you. Are you happy?
Yes. I can do what I like without feeling tired.
Just as you did at the base.
Honestly, I've known you for so many years.
But only when you're with Li Xun, can you be passionate,
impulsive, and brave to go forward
as if nothing would frighten you.
He did change me.
If I hadn't joined the base back then, I wouldn't have found that I liked programming.
But it's history. It's all over.
Now I have to consider my tone when I speak to him.
I hope that we can talk normally.
You're worried because you care about him so much.
I'm worried about the both of you.
It has been so many years.
Why can't you make up your mind?
Get together if you like each other and separate if you don't.
Is it difficult?
Why don't you just change?
Pick one of my boyfriends.
You can try to get along with them.
Okay?
Or pick one of my clients.
Get out.
Drink it.
The deadline for uploading past.
Click it now.
I'll test it again.
Come on. It's time.
Do you want the client to scold you?
It'll be ready soon.
When?
I'll upload it soon.
♫  If love remains warm  ♫
Quite simple.
♫  This dream will automatically abort  ♫
♫  When you wake up, please stay  ♫
♫  Don't go, fate is not a journey  ♫
♫  Hold onto me, don't get lost  ♫
♫  It's the depth of one's soul  ♫
♫  You're my everything  ♫
♫  Take one step back and try to understand  ♫
♫  I care so much about you  ♫
Thank you.
Never mind.
It's just a closed beta.
It can't be perfect.
I think there is enough content.
We can add more gradually after it's launched.
Keep in mind that this company hasn't launched any products.
Invincible General is our only bullet now.
If we screw things up,
we have to pay for it this year and next.
Am I too indecisive?
Group Leader Zhu,
now you don't need anyone's affirmation.
You should have confidence in yourself.
I think Senior is right.
We have to trust ourselves.
If not, how should we trust others and build a family?
- Get out.
- Okay.
I tried to play the closed beta of our game.
It's really interesting.
Playing the closed beta,
clients think that our game is great.
Great.
But with its downloads after the official launch,
we'll know whether the game is great.
Zhang Fang.
Do a good promotion before the game goes online.
Don't worry about money.
You must get it done at any cost.
Don't be a drag on us.
Listen!  If you do anything wrong, you'll be seriously punished.
Did I make myself clear?
- Yes, but...
- Dismissed.
Do we have money?
- Do we-Do we have money for promotion?
- We have.
I saw the promotion fee on the statement.
Yes, but you and he used it as salaries.
Don't mix that with promotion.
Without promotion, our efforts in the early stage will be in vain.
I...
How much do we have?
- 50,000 yuan?
- 5,000 yuan.
Are you kidding me?
I know we should do promotion,
but we have no money.
Is that my fault?
Yes.
You're CFO.
Right. Right.
Don't worry.
Focus on the posters first.
We'll find a way later.
These are my masterpieces. What do you think?
Great. You're reliable this time.
I think they're great.
I don't think so.
- Why?
- They're ordinary.
Ordinary?
Is this a problem?
It isn't spectacular enough.
Is it too late to change?
I-I've tried my best.
I know that, but the concept poster is a facade.
It's the users' first impression.
We must make it impressive.
What should I do?
Redo it?
I guessed that.
Come on. It's too late.
- I think this is not bad.
- Even so, we have to change.
I don't mean to offend you.
But this is his superior limit.
That's what he can do. He's not a great painter.
Even if you give him more time, he can't draw what you want.
That makes sense.
Next.
Wait.
What do you want to do? Are you going to work as a painter?
People specialize in different subjects.
An-An artist should design it. Why should we bother?
Shut up.
Sorry, sir. I found that Miss Zhu Yun checked out a few days ago
and never checked in again.
What's wrong?
Please help me find out if there is any rental information of Zhu Yun.
Send me the address when you find it.
Now?
I have no way to find it for you now.
It's your business.
Come on. You always tell me what to do.
Are you...
He even hung up.
Hello, it's me.
Go ahead.
Call Ren Di and ask her where Zhu Yun is.
Buddy, you could have asked her directly.
Please ask for me.
Okay.
Thanks.
Ask me for help directly if you want.
How do you know?
You've been staring at the posters the whole night.
Okay. I'll design it for you.
Do you have time?
It's easy for me.
Moreover, you asked me for help.
It's easy.
But as a startup,
our company is short of money.
No payment?
Yes. We'll pay you.
Well, how much should we pay?
Book me first.
For such a huge favor, there are no thank yous.
No, no, no. Thank yous are a definite.
When you have enough money, pay me a big sum.
Okay.
When do you want it?
At your convenience.
How about tomorrow?
Do you see me as a convenience?
Tomorrow night will be fine. The sooner the better.
What are you going to do?
I'll clean up and go to work in the studio.
I'll go with you and help you.
To supervise me, right?
Who is it?
Brother Xiuzhu, open the door for me.
Coming.
Who is it?
Nobody.
I liked you. So what?
Go to ask anyone out there if he remembers the one who he liked at 18.
Do you still like her?
No.
It's strange.
Now that you don't like her, why do you care about her staying with the painter?
Is he Li Xun?
Yes, it's him.
Shall I call him in?
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I am leaning on your shoulder  ♫
♫  We will not separate  ♫
♫  Avoid the hustle and bustle by staying with me  ♫
♫  It's the center crease of your palm  ♫
♫  That holds me up by giving me the courage to move forward  ♫
♫  Just like a burning flame in the night  ♫
♫  'Cause I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  It's the intuition of the dream  ♫
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I also want to stand by your side  ♫
♫  As long as I am brave enough  ♫
♫  Every dream that I have  ♫
♫  Will not, will not, will not lose to time anymore  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫