♫  Everything is different from the sea to the sky  ♫
♫  The person I used to be has disappeared without a trace  ♫
♫  I no longer believe one person can redeem another  ♫
♫  Until when you broke into my world  ♫
♫  Even if the world exploded into darkness  ♫
♫  We bloom in the dark  ♫
♫  The knight and the king  ♫
♫  Sail at night with white sails to navigate
and protect the vast ocean  ♫
♫  I can see a clear direction  ♫
♫  In which a touch of golden color flickers
at the end of the wheat field  ♫
♫  Even if I am the king  ♫
♫  With supreme glory everything would be meaningless without you  ♫
♫  Going through fire and water is to make you remember  ♫
♫  The way everything was at the beginning  ♫
♫  If I am the king  ♫
♫  Who is as arrogant as the fierce wind and wild grass  ♫
♫  I only want you to be at my side, whatever it takes  ♫
♫  And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning  ♫
Are you sure you won't use me anymore?
Why don't we have something in the canteen?
You're back.
- Hello.
Is he the ordinary student you mentioned?
This is Li Xun, my classmate.
This is Tian Xiuzhu.
I won't have the meal with you in your canteen.
Invite me to dinner next time.
No problem. I'll go first.
Li Xun, wait for me.
Well.
What?
What's the project you just received about?
The integration system of the godown entries and outbound delivery orders of an automobile parts company.
Is it difficult?
Forget it.
Why did you come back so early?
I had nothing to do at home, so I just came back to work.
You just paid me, so I should work harder.
Who was that man I saw?
My driver.
Driver?
Princess, do you need any help?
No, thanks. My luggage is not heavy, and it's near my—
Don't dawdle. After putting away your luggage, come to the base.
I should have kept Xiuzhu so that he could help me.
I said I didn't need your help,
but you actually ignored me.
Hello.
What are you doing in the dormitory? Come to work now.
Am I mad? Why did I come back voluntarily to suffer his maltreatment?
Come here to copy the documents and codes.
You look exhausted after coming back from putting away your luggage in the dormitory.
How delicate you are.
You are the boss. As long as you pay me, I dare not argue back.
Then come to work now.
I finally have a helper.
But we should observe the base rules.
It's not time to start school yet.
You have no reason to ask me to work for you.
This is malicious overtime.
Really?
I can work overtime, but you should have a good attitude.
I don't think you want to go on working here.
I'll satisfy your desire and give you a day off tomorrow.
Why?
You need to meet your driver.
Copy the documents and codes for me.
Do you have time?
He's not my driver.
He is the son of my mother's classmate.
Anything else?
I've known him since childhood.
When we were young, we competed to have chicken wings.
And then?
Then, then we vomited as we ate so much.
Then he went abroad. You know what happened then.
Is he that sunshine man who can paint?
Why do you remember him so clearly?
Are you satisfied?
Can you copy the documents and codes for me?
Zhu Yun,
if you dare to lie again,
you'll have to bear the consequences yourself.
Come and copy documents and codes.
What about the sunshine man?
If he has nothing to do, you can ask him to go back sooner.
Copy now.
What's up? Order dishes.
It's my treat today, so don't miss this chance.
You finally thought of me.
What do you mean?
Let me tell you.
Look! I can make money now,
so surely I should treat you to dinner.
How do you feel when spending the money you earned?
Do you have a strong sense of achievement?
My heart aches.
Tell me. What can I do for you?
I'm not treating you to dinner for something.
You are treating me to dinner in such a good restaurant,
but you don't want me to do anything for you?
Do you believe it?
I'm sincerely inviting you to dinner.
Just the two of us for dinner today. Order the dishes you like.
Okay.
I want this, Heart-Broken Watermelon.
- What's that?
- Watermelon juice.
It has a strange name. Seeing its high price, I know why it's called so.
Xiuzhu, go back and have a good rest after dinner.
I made a strategy for you. You can visit Lishan Mountain tomorrow.
I won't go with you.
Well, this is your purpose.
No, our university has an urgent task, or I wouldn't have come back so early.
Is the urgent task related to your ordinary classmate?
Surely not.
I saw your ordinary classmate in the art museum last time.
Then, why didn't you say hello to us?
You usually look gentle and quiet, but you're actually a rather rebellious girl.
No.
Do you girls only like handsome men?
Unexpectedly, you're also a conformist.
So you also think he is handsome.
You're good at making deliberate misinterpretations.
Don't keep giggling like this, or you may have stiff plump cheeks.
I don't think he's reliable.
What do you mean by that?
I'll talk to you directly and openly.
He, a domineering man, lacks self-discipline.
You just met him a few times.
I don't want to warn you in the tone of your mom.
But I don't think he's suitable for you.
You can't change him.
Why should I change him?
Because you'll get hurt?
Are you sure about it? You don't know him.
I don't know him, but I know you.
Xiuzhu, you really speak in the same way as my mom.
You think you know me well.
You don't like those people different from you.
You can't accept others' pasts
no matter whether their past is under their own control or not.
You just blame others from a commanding position only according to the rules in your own mind.
To tell you the truth, your behaviors are so unreasonable.
I hope I'm wrong.
I'm sorry.
It's I who should say sorry.
Thank you, Xiuzhu. Have a good time tomorrow.
I'm sorry for what I just said.
Never mind. Go back quickly.
You should not rush to pay the bill. I said it was my treat.
It's mainly because this dinner is not big enough.
When you really make a lot of money, you must treat me to a big dinner.
That's a deal. I'll leave.
If my mom calls you, hide something for me.
I see.
Then I'll go back. Have fun tomorrow.
Bye-bye.
I'll leave.
Fang Shumiao.
I was looking for you.
Let me tell you. I met Mr. Lin.
He asked you to go to his office.
Why does he want to meet me?
There should be some good news.
He looked happy.
Why are you back at this time?
The Steering Committee of the Education Commission will come to listen to the class tomorrow.
I haven't hung the banner yet. I'll leave first.
By the way, I'm running for the Minister of Propaganda Department of the Student Union.
Remember to vote for me.
- Will you be promoted?
- Yes.
I've told you many times.
You're so thoughtless.
Does he look happy?
- What's up?
- Come here. Let her take part in it.
In what?
Let her go.
Wait.
What's the matter, Mr. Lin?
Next month, the preliminary of the Nanhu University Students' Information Security Competition
will be held at the Information Technology University.
Did you know?
It has attracted a lot of attention.
Surely.
Though this is the first competition,
it's a competitive event held among universities in the whole information security industry.
Normally, you freshmen are not qualified to participate.
The apps you designed have been well-recognized by them.
And they agreed and gave you a participation chance for the sake of me.
Many people sought but failed to get the chance.
I asked him to participate, but he declines with all sorts of excuses.
As the class rep, say something.
He should participate. He must participate.
If I participate in it, who can design the integration system of the godown entries and outbound delivery orders?
Don't place the unimportant before the important.
It won't take you much time to participate in it.
Gao Jianhong entered his name. He has the ability to handle it.
He can't go alone. All of you should participate.
- Including me?
- Sure.
Participating in the competition can not only broaden your horizons
but also enable you to communicate more
with the top industrial and academic experts and discover your weaknesses.
I don't need it.
What did you say?
- You don't need it?
- Mr. Lin.
Well, you actually said so.
Do you think you don't have any weaknesses?
Yes.
Mr. Lin, if you want us to win prizes for the university
and make a show, I really don't think it's necessary.
Li Xun, how arrogant you are.
You're so opinionated.
He left. How can I handle this?
Listen. You...
Mr. Lin, calm down. Take a seat.
Take a seat. Take a seat.
I've seen many naughty students, and he's the unruliest one.
Yes. He's to blame.
It's such a good chance.
The contestants are all top students in the country.
Even the sponsors are the most powerful enterprises in the industry.
After the award-winning works are announced,
they'll directly cooperate with those winners and have their work put to use.
After a long time of research on the base projects,
you've improved your professional ability.
It's time for you to show your real strength.
I know you are close to each other.
Is our relationship exposed?
You must persuade him to participate.
I'll try my best.
No, you must make it, or I'll take the blame on you.
I must make it.
He'll suffer a great deal because of his arrogance.
Zhu Yun, you are the class rep and the person he trusts.
You must control him for me.
Okay.
Li Xun.
Don't waste your time.
I know you, Talent Li, think it's meaningless to participate in the competition.
Others participate in the competition for learning,
but you, Top Scorer, just go there to broaden their horizons.
Just take our team to receive this test.
I know you're an excellent programmer,
but you should also pay attention to the overall improvement of the team.
Don't speak to me in the way of Fang Shumiao.
Political Commissar Zhu, don't try to persuade me.
Take it away.
You may not participate in the competition, but this is a very interesting forum.
Xinchuan Company specializes in the systems of dock godown entries and outbound delivery orders.
So?
So we can go and discover their bugs.
Do you agree?
No, I won't go.
I won't take it away.
Touch-typing,
touch-test, and touch-setting of breaking points.
Are you a god?
Mr. Lin managed to win a participation chance for us,
so you may at least participate in the forum. If so, he'll be very delighted.
You're so double-faced.
What are you doing?
Come with me.
Li Xun, accompany me to the forum. Okay?
What's the weather like next month?
He agreed.
Don't be so nervous.
This is the preliminary.
Are you afraid that your work won't enter the final?
I want to learn more from you, so that I can feel at ease.
Extreme nervousness will disturb your psychological state before the competition.
Relax yourself.
I often blame Li Xun for his arrogance.
But you really should learn from him sometimes.
He's very confident.
No matter what you young people do, you must have confidence in yourselves.
Mr. Lin, since I've decided to participate in the competition,
I won't take it lightly.
I want to prove my ability.
I can feel your confidence from that.
What is your topic?
Switch-based LAN ARP Attack Defense System.
It's of a certain difficulty.
- How long have you been preparing it?
- Two days.
No way!
Actually, it's been a while.
I usually sort out some data and collect some questions about this topic.
I intended to use it as material for my graduation thesis.
Good topic.
It should be a byway with practicability.
Remember. Opportunity favors the prepared.
Hello?
Yes, we're here.
We'll come to you in half an hour.
Okay, see you later.
Old Gao, go in first.
Help Zhu Yun and me register our names.
Where-Where will you go?
I'll go and meet the leader of Xinda Biotechnology.
They've always wanted to talk to me about the development of the biological database.
Did you agree to come here because of Xinda Biotechnology's interview?
Or else?
You're abusing the public trust.
What is Princess talking about?
Which side are you on?
Don't forget you're my team member.
See you later.
- Please help me carry my suitcase. Thank you.
- I'm leaving.
- Your book.
-  Hi, which university are you from?
- Nanhu University.
Nanhu University. In Zone 2.
It's through that door.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hi, which university are you from?
- Well, okay. How many of you are there?
- One.
Okay. Okay.
Give him one room card.
Okay.
Hello. I'm Gao Jianhong from Nan...
Are you from Nanhu University?
Hello, I'm Xu Lina from the Computer Science Department of this university.
I'm also a freshman.
Gao Jianhong.
You should have another two members, Li Xun and Zhu Yun.
Haven't they come?
They aren't participating in the competition but are just attending the forum.
Okay. Yeah.
How do you know about us?
I'm also a contestant.
Blue Crown app is a typical teaching case in our circles.
- Did you design it?
- Yes.
You guys are so awesome.
As freshmen, you have your representative works
and can participate in such a high-level competition.
Today, I've just received a small number of undergraduates, let alone freshmen.
It's mainly because we have good teachers.
What's up?
You're both talented and modest,
much better than the boys in our university.
Go and have your formalities handled first.
Let's talk later.
- Okay.
- Give him two room cards.
Okay.
Hi, which university are you from?
Hengjiang University. Two members. Give him two room cards, too.
Okay.
Are you free tonight?
Let's go out for dinner.
Emphasize which room everyone lives in.
- Yeah.
- Okay. Thank you.
Well, we've almost finished all the work.
Thank you so much.
See you tomorrow. Bye-bye.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Never mind. I just got here.
I booked a restaurant. Let's go for dinner.
Then I'll call a taxi.
No need. Follow me.
Please come again. Bye.
Miss Xu, we've reserved your seats for you. Still your favorite dinning place.
- Okay, thank you.
- This way.
This way, please.
- Please have a seat.
- Thank you.
- Please.
- Okay.
Sit down, please.
It's such a formal occasion.
I should have worn my only suit.
- Although my classmates all think...
- Please drink some water.
Thanks.
Although they all think I'm quite like a real estate agent in that suit.
Really? I also want to see you wear it.
Actually, it's not that formal here.
People are dressed differently.
If you dressed formally,
I'd have thought you were here to take photos and share them on your Moments.
Look at the two girls over there.
Do you want me to take some photos for you?
All right.
Good.
Let me see.
They look terrible. I'm deformed in the photo.
It seems I'm only 1.2 meters high in this one. Look at this one.
I feel as if the Oriental Pearl Tower grew on my head.
I see. I look sort of sentimental in this one.
No matter how beautiful the scenery is, it's just the background.
I'll take some more for you.
Make me look taller.
One more.
Let me see.
These look much better.
Let's take a selfie.
Stand closer to me.
Three, two, one.
The last two look good. Quite good.
Hello. Here are our menus.
Thank you.
This one also looks good.
Don't look.
The one you took is the lady's menu, with no price on it.
How does it taste?
Delicious.
Cheers!
If we can write codes in such a beautiful place later, we'll work efficiently.
Good idea. You should try the next time.
Then we would become the center of attention in the Bund.
Your great god Li Xun, why haven't I seen him?
Are you looking for him?
It's said he is the leader in the design of the Blue Crown app.
He established our practice base. Blue Crown is our project.
I downloaded and browsed your app.
Besides good practicability, I also like your idea "Click to Check the Illness Reasons and Treatment."
It's a particularly interesting design.
"Click to Check the Illness Reasons and Treatment." Good name.
To tell you the truth, I'm actually bad at programming.
Stop kidding me.
The Computer Science Department of your university ranks at the top among peers.
But I was enrolled as a special student with folk dance talent.
I applied for this program on sudden impulse.
I'm not good at math.
I can hardly understand my courses.
Can you understand me?
You're so modest. You're also a contestant.
My classmates all look down on me.
They all think I'm an art student, so they don't want to complete the group homework with me.
I just want to take a place in this competition and show my real strength to them.
How did you think of the idea of that app?
Can you tell me about it?
Are you curious about it?
Shopping websites have just emerged in recent years.
There're diversified shopping websites,
but in fact, it won't take so long
before most of the resources are slowly gathered into several large platforms.
Second, smartphones have become popular.
The reason why we gave up designing large websites
and chose to design apps was because large websites are wide in usage,
while apps stress fine functions.
We aim to design deep and fine app functions to meet the needs and usage habits of users.
In the future, apps must have a lower usage threshold than websites.
Why?
Because all of us who carry mobile phones can use those apps at any time,
but we can't use computers so conveniently.
Therefore, we added the illness search system based on different user portraits.
Users don't need to know their illness names.
They can obtain the corresponding information and treatment as soon as they enter their symptoms.
Second, we added the Mocap system.
Mocap?
Yes, it's the Mocap system.
It's widely used in many Hollywood blockbusters.
Our model is also based on this technology,
which is more intuitive than the entered symptoms. Right?
What do you think of it?
Very good, Old Gao. It sounds really great.
It still has many shortcomings.
It's already quite perfect. You're so modest.
I've talked so much today.
No, tell me more about it.
You want to hear more?
Although smartphones haven't been fully popularized yet
and the mobile internet speed can't meet the current requirements...
Here we are.
Old Gao, you're sure to win this information security competition.
Thank you.
Well, I'll go first.
Go back and get some rest early. Good night.
Bye-bye.
Good night.
You're back.
Did you have a smooth talk with Xinda Biotechnology?
Yes.
Here are our photos.
Don't play with your phone while driving. Tell me when you get home.
Who?
Old Gao, it's me.
I'm coming.
Old Gao, what are you doing?
Coming, coming.
- Morning.
May I come in?
Yes.
Only you?
Did you have breakfast?
I don't have the habit of eating breakfast.
Old Gao, can you check my project?
Sure. As long as you don't mind.
I'll treat you to these sweet-scented osmanthus cakes.
It tastes good.
It's good, right?
It's the specialty of Lübolang Restaurant.
Surely it's delicious.
Look.
This is our software piracy self-discovery system,
and this is the feature extractor.
Look.
What do you think?
Very good. The topic anti-piracy is good.
I didn't expect it.
Really?
Yours is much better than ours.
What's your topic?
Our topic is...
Let me introduce you.
This is Li Xun.
Hello, Li Xun. I'm Xu Lina.
I've long heard your name.
Sorry to disturb you.
Li Xun, could you check the project of our group
and see if there's something that needs to be improved?
Look!  This is our software piracy self-discovery system and its principle...
This isn't your work.
Li Xun.
How do you know?
There're only two principles for software companies to detect piracy.
First, to use the embedded digital watermarking.
Second, to capture information when software is updated and connected to the internet.
You adopted the second principle,
but both of them are of no use.
The information can be captured on the premise that your software can directly access the internal data of files
related to the C disk operating system across Windows operating system permissions.
But the personal security and firewall functions of Windows operating system are strong.
At present, many Chinese companies use PPPoE Internet.
The IP address of the external network changes on a regular basis.
However, MAC can only be displayed only after the SNMP service is enabled and it's uploaded.
The rest interact by port number.
Don't make a fool of yourself.
Li Xun, it's enough.
Li Xun, can our project be improved?
Others may see it easily.
Find good programmers to redo it.
Let them change the idea and do it according to the first principle,
which is easier than the improvement of your current project.
Wait!
Can you repeat the first idea you just told me?
Sorry, I'm very busy.
Can I come to consult you next time?
After I redo it, can you give me some advice?
No. This isn't my duty.
My name is Xu Lina.
I'm from Class 132 of the Software Engineering Major at Information Technology University.
He just speaks in this way. Don't take it to heart.
He's really a top programmer.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to our Information Technology University.
Thank you for your participation and support.
The organizing committee of the competition received the works
submitted by more than 300 contestants from universities across the country.
After three days of selection, 14 works were selected to enter the final.
Well, see.
They are the team and individual contestants who entered the final in this competition.
Congratulations.
In half a month, you'll come back here to fight it out.
Now I announce the official launch
of the Jianguang Electronics Cup First Nanhu University Students' Information Security Competition.
Let's welcome the leaders of Huake Technology Co., Ltd.
and Fang Zhijing, who won the Special Attention Award in this competition,
to come to the stage and press the crystal ball with us.
Thanks. Thanks.
Come on. One, two, three!
Cheese!
- Well, one more.
- Okay.
One, two, three. Cheese!
Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Is it good?
- May I have your WeChat account?
We'll establish a final communication group.
I'll invite you to join it.
- See you in the final.
See you in the final.
- Establish a group.
- Okay. Bye-bye.
Senior, may I have your WeChat account?
Okay.
Scan my QR code.
The project of your group is impressive.
Only you won the Special Attention Award.
Thank you.
Which university are you from? I can make a note.
I'm from Nanhu University.
Nanhu University?
Is Li Xun from your university?
Yes. We designed the Blue Crown app together.
Is this also your common project?
He didn't participate in this project.
It's my own design.
- Fang, let's go.
- Okay.
Let's talk later.
Come on.
One, two, three.
Is it good?  Is this okay?
Yes. Thank you.
Not at all.
- Old Gao.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Where's Li Xun?
He must be busy with something.
He's so busy.
No wonder when I requested him on WeChat he still hasn't accepted.
How did you get his WeChat account?
Don't forget. I'm a volunteer.
Old Gao, can you tell him and have him accept my request.
Okay.
I'll invite you to have dinner tonight.
- I'll invite some of the finalists to celebrate together.
- Okay.
Be sure to let Li Xun join us.
He helped me a lot this time.
I should thank him sincerely.
- I'll try my best.
- Okay.
Fang Zhijing.
It's you who plagued Xiaoyan.
You caused her to be slandered by others for a recommendation certificate.
She killed herself because of you.
- It's you who killed her—
- Zhu Yun.
It's because she had psychological problems.
- Join me in the competition to beat this project.
- Not enough.
♫  It's the intuition of the dream  ♫
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I am leaning on your shoulder  ♫
♫  We will not separate  ♫
♫  Avoid the hustle and bustle by staying with me  ♫
♫  It's the center crease of your palm  ♫
♫  That holds me up by giving me the courage to move forward  ♫
♫  Just like a burning flame in the night  ♫
♫  'Cause I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  It's the intuition of the dream  ♫
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I also want to stand by your side  ♫
♫  As long as I am brave enough  ♫
♫  Every dream that I have  ♫
♫  Will not, will not, will not lose to time anymore  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫