♫  Everything is different from the sea to the sky  ♫
♫  The person I used to be has disappeared without a trace  ♫
♫  I no longer believe one person can redeem another  ♫
♫  Until when you broke into my world  ♫
♫  Even if the world exploded into darkness  ♫
♫  We bloom in the dark  ♫
♫  The knight and the king  ♫
♫  Sail at night with white sails to navigate
and protect the vast ocean  ♫
♫  I can see a clear direction  ♫
♫  In which a touch of golden color flickers
at the end of the wheat field  ♫
♫  Even if I am the king  ♫
♫  With supreme glory everything would be meaningless without you  ♫
♫  Going through fire and water is to make you remember  ♫
♫  The way everything was at the beginning  ♫
♫  If I am the king  ♫
♫  Who is as arrogant as the fierce wind and wild grass  ♫
♫  I only want you to be at my side, whatever it takes  ♫
♫  And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning  ♫
Why didn't you answer my call?
Even if I didn't answer my phone, couldn't you still find me?
Tell me. What are you up to tonight?
There's nothing to tell.
Don't you think you should explain yourself?
While I can still accept your apology.
Explain what?
There's no way.
I just can't stand people like you.
What kind of people are we?
Your mom is right.
People like us are scheming for profits and anxious to achieve quick success and get instant benefits.
And people like you are cold and heartless, looking superior.
You take studying abroad as a handout and always look superior to teach others a lesson.
So you deliberately stimulated them?
Yes.
In fact, I'm very happy to see them getting furious.
Because they were willing to let you go abroad with me and you wouldn't have to pay the tuition?
You made up those words to irritate them?
You don't care that they're my parents? This was your first official meeting.
You don't care how I face them in the future and whether they still accept us?
Do you think they will?
Even if I listen to them.
Then you can at least try.
You also proposed meeting them today.
Like today, I really doubt you.
What do you doubt?
Tell me what you doubt?
I doubt your intentions.
I just said what I would say later.
You will face this problem sooner or later.
Go home.
What do you mean?
It's what you understand.
You made my parents so angry. Can I go home?
Otherwise?
You want to stay tonight?
Li Xun, I think it's not too much for me to ask you to apologize to me for what happened today. Right?
You can let me go. Then think it over.
After I leave today, will I come back?
That's your choice.
Okay. You said it.
So Li Xun quarreled with your mom
and then you quarreled with him?
Marvelous.
He was quite strange today. You know.
But I can imagine how your mom reacted.
People like Li Xun were born to ruffle feathers.
Ms. Liu's high-toed manner must have forced him to show his true colors.
Besides, Li Lan just died.
The hurdle in his heart must not have been passed yet.
You're helping him find a reason.
You know what? If he doesn't explain it to me today, I won't go back.
Then what happened to him?
There must be a reason for the abnormality.
Has he been hiding something from you recently?
Zhu Yun, isn't Li Xun going to meet your parents at your home today?
He seems to be with Xu Lina.
Where are you going?
You broke your words too fast.
No, I still have to find a reason to ask him.
I forgot something.
Take it.
Li Xun, we can talk if something happened to you. Right?
I was in a bad mood tonight. So I had a bad attitude.
But you were worse. I won't let this go so easily.
But I can forget about this now.
I just want to know. What did you do before you went to my home today?
Didn't you come back for the key?
Is this important?
Do you know the golden 24-hour principle?
If some misunderstandings are not resolved in time, they will lead to greater ones.
I think it's pretty irresponsible for me to speculate like this.
So can you tell me what you did and whom you met today?
Don't think I don't know. Fang Shumiao told me.
The bathroom in your company is quite far.
Why is she here?
Why can't I be here?
This is not a misunderstanding.
♪ Do you feel regret? ♪
♪ Forget him ♪
♪ Wipe away tears ♪
♪ Wipe away tears. And send him away ♪
♪ Like two parallel lines,
we will not be concerned about each other again ♪
♪ Turn into a one-person lonely island ♪
You are awake.
What song is this?
A new song I'm writing.
I haven't decided on a name yet.
Cheer up. You'll make up in a few days.
After I finish this song, I'll give it to you as a graduation gift
and sing it to you on graduation day.
Hello. Hello.
Hello, this is Xu Lina. I'm looking for Zhu Yun.
Zhu Yun. For you.
I won't answer his call.
It's Xu Lina.
Hello.
Zhu Yun, are you free? Let's meet.
Zhu Yun, I've never liked you very much.
It doesn't matter. I don't like you either.
We are about to graduate. What's your plan?
It's none of your business.
My father set up a fund for me.
Recently, I've been running back and forth to several cities to investigate projects.
I prefer those at the conceptual stage,
so I can participate in them during incubation.
It will give me a sense of achievement and the rate of return will be high.
I heard one interesting business plan yesterday.
The slogan is to increase the cure rate of cancer by 1%.
I'm quite interested in this company.
L&amp;P, are you familiar with it?
So I asked you out today because of this.
I think highly of this company.
Since your parents don't have this vision, I'll invest in it.
But the condition is that,
you're out.
Then you can try.
If I don't agree, can you take it away?
It doesn't matter. Li Xun has promised me.
What did he agree with you?
Didn't he tell you?
It seems that you are really not important to him.
It's ridiculous if you are trying to test me with bluffing.
If you want to control Li Xun, that's even more impossible.
He won't accept you.
He's not under anyone's control.
Then you still don't know him well enough.
Have you considered how much time and cost must be paid to achieve that goal?
Internet technology development is much faster than you think.
As long as we can master the first-hand clinical data,
under the integration of big data, we'll see its value soon.
Where is the data?
We have mastered the diagnostic data of core departments of major hospitals.
China is too big.
You only made a few statistics and become arrogant?
There's still a long way to go.
I'm willing to do it.
You're willing?
Is he willing?
You are pathetic. You don't even know if someone sold you.
Li Xun told me personally he doesn't want to waste time
but to develop L&amp;P as soon as possible.
By the way, here is a tip.
We're on our way.
What are you up to?
Meet my dad.
- Let's go.
- Okay. Let's go.
Li Xun.
Wait for me in the car for a while.
Where are you going?
When are you going to tell me?
After coming back.
With Xu Lina?
She said you promised her. What did you promise her?
Shares.
It doesn't matter if it's Xu Lina or others.
Now, as long as someone is willing to invest in it,
I can promise to give up 50% of the shares.
That 50% you said belongs to me?
It used to be.
So before you met my parents, you'd decided it. Right?
No.
Since you asked for the shares back,
you'd decided to exclude me. Right?
Kind of.
What if I don't agree?
Legally speaking, you don't have this right now.
I don't have this right?
So you won't say one more word to me?
Have we reached this point?
Being emotional is a burden for everyone.
The two of us fighting alone might look heroic.
But if one day when we break up because of the problem of funds, you'll regret it.
What do you think of me?
I just don't want you to regret.
That is my business if I were to regret it later.
You have to go today, don't you?
Think about it twice. What exactly do you want?
Go home.
Don't let your parents worry.
Li Xun, if you take one more step forward today, we will break up.
What happened exactly?
Are you hiding something from me? What are you planning?
Nothing.
This is what I want.
♫  Memories lie  ♫
♫  Hope ends up being disappointed  ♫
♫  Hiding the dream privately  ♫
♫  And returning it to time with your bare hands  ♫
♫  There is nowhere to hide  ♫
♫  How do I forgive the torn past?  ♫
♫  I'm somewhere  ♫
♫  Looking back  ♫
♫  I want to give a little light  ♫
♫  To the extreme darkness  ♫
♫  Just like the shoulder you lent me back then  ♫
♫  Some things from the past can't be said aloud  ♫
♫  I have to learn to let go  ♫
♫  I admit the way I look in your eyes  ♫
What princess?
What hell?
All of it was fake.
♫  I have never gone against time  ♫
♫  and have always been by your side  ♫
♫  I want to give a little light  ♫
♫  To the extreme darkness  ♫
♫  Just like the shoulder you lent me back then  ♫
♫  Some things from the past can't be said aloud  ♫
♫  I have to learn to let go  ♫
♫  I admit the way I look in your eyes  ♫
♫  is vague, clear, painful, and stubborn  ♫
♫  I have never gone against time  ♫
♫  and have always been by your side  ♫
♫  I want to give a little light  ♫
♫  To the extreme darkness  ♫
♫  Just like the shoulder you lent me back then  ♫
♫  Some things from the past can't be said aloud  ♫
♫  I have to learn to let go  ♫
My dad works up there.
Are you sure you don't want me to go up and meet him?
Thanks this time.
I cooperated with you to tell such a big lie.
You owe me a favor.
I will repay you.
What are you going to repay me?
How about giving me a chance?
I know you won't accept my dad's help.
But I can work hard with you.
I can accompany you to start a business.
I'd made up my mind before I came here this time.
I can give up clothes and shoes, bags and cars.
- I can leave everything they give me behind.
- Xu Lina.
I haven't finished yet.
I can also accompany you to have box lunches and live in a small house.
I can do whatever she can do.
Am I worth a chance now?
I've made a lot of mistakes and I love to flaunt my superiority.
I have a sharp tongue.
You don't need me to give you a chance.
I'm not qualified to be arrogant.
You deserve a better man.
That's how I refuse others.
I'm leaving.
Li Xun.
Can I ask? You drove Zhu Yun away so hard this time,
what are you trying to do?
I always feel uneasy when you look like this.
Don't think too much.
I'm just annoying her.
That's it.
Does Zhu Yun know this?
I advise you better not tell her.
What you are holding now also has her shares.
It's this time and you're still in the mood to joke.
In the future, she'll learn about it.
She will come and ask me.
How should I answer her?
What will she think of me?
I'm not afraid.
What are you afraid of?
Of course, you don't have to be afraid.
You don't have to think about this. But I do.
You don't have to worry about her.
She will go abroad...
and leave here.
She doesn't need to pester everything.
But this company can only rely on you in the future.
I'll try my best.
Li Xun.
Thank you for trusting me.
Old Gao.
I have no family.
I don't have any friends.
You may hate me.
But you are the person I trust most.
I made you cancel the competition.
I have been very sorry.
This company can give you a place to stay.
I'm sure you will run it well as we said.
What are you going to do with Fang Zhijing?
I don't know.
I agree with you to teach him a lesson.
Scum like him should have been dealt with long ago.
But I don't think it's necessary if we want to use the method of killing each other.
I don't think it is necessary to kill a thousand enemies and lose eight hundred.
Is it worth it.
Not at all.
But something must be done.
Old Gao.
Tomorrow is the last day of the information security competition.
Yes. Tomorrow is the final award presentation.
How is it?
It's okay.
You don't know how hard it was for me to win the first prize this time.
You're mad at your mom?
Yun Yun, you're an adult.
Sometimes you have to learn to think in terms of others.
You have to figure out why your parents do this to you.
And for an outsider, you go against your parents like this.
Your mother and I have spared some time.
Let's go to Sanya to celebrate the Spring Festival this year.
That bastard Fang Zhijing said that Li Lan asked him where there was a cheap hotel,
so he kindly introduced one to her.
I think he was just afraid you'd get in his way in the finals,
so he tricked Li Lan out of there to scare you.
Won't he come back for the finals?
- Since high school…
- Dad, today is the 18th?
Today is the 18th?
Yeah. What's up?
Stop.
Yun Yun, where are you going?
Now I will read out the list of winners.
The team from Anhua University.
Team leader, Shao Bing.
The team from the University of Electronic Science and Technology.
The team from Information Engineering University.
The team from Hengjiang University of Posts and Telecommunications.
Team leader, Zhao Zijie.
Congratulations.
Finally, I announce the team that won first place is
the team from Information Technology University.
Team leader, Fang Zhijing.
Let's welcome the leaders of the organizing committee to present awards to them.
Let's welcome their team leader Fang Zhijing to deliver an acceptance speech.
Respected leaders and teachers, dear students, hello.
Great.
First of all, I would like to especially thank the teachers who led the team, the judges,
and teachers of organizing committee.
Thanks for your hard work.
Secondly, I also want to thank all the students who participated in the competition.
Without your enthusiastic efforts, we would not have had such a spark of passion.
Thank you all.
- Great.
I believe that in the future, the general trend of information security development
is a kind of big security from traditional security towards integration and openness.
With the continuous development of the internet, the traditional network boundary no longer exists.
Traditional security technology can no longer meet the needs of the new generation.
With the development of network security technology,
whether enterprises or individuals,
all will have changing demands for information security.
And these changes
will bring huge impact to the future internet applications and services
and it will also bring new challenges to information security.
But at the same time, it will also bring us new opportunities,
new data, new applications.
New, new applications, new computing, and new networks will become a new generation.
Li Xun!
Stop. Stop now.
Guards! Where are the guards? Stop him.
What are you doing, Li Xun?
Pull him away! Pull him away.
Pull him away.
Leave now.
Yun.
You've been sleeping all day.
Would you like to eat something?
What are you looking for?
Dad, where's my cell phone?
I've taken it away.
Get some good rest at home these days.
Give me back my cell phone.
Yun Yun, you shout at me again.
Did I tell you earlier Li Xun would cause great trouble sooner or later?
Now you see it?
See what he did.
Wasn't it just a fight?
Just a punishment record. He can drop out of school.
He doesn't care anyway. What's the big deal?
What's the big deal?
Yes.
Fang Zhijing was rescued.
But his left eyeball was removed.
Hundreds of people on site watched him blinding another man.
That's horrible.
In my opinion, his sister died because of him.
For such people, that's an eye for an eye.
I beg your pardon?
I said it's an eye for an eye.
What's wrong?
Now this matter has widely spread.
Do you think the Fang family will spare him?
Their own child was blinded by him.
You see how people deal with him in the future.
Then I'll find him.
No need. He has been detained.
- You can't go anywhere.
- I'm going to meet him.
- You go abroad now.
- I won't go.
Mom, look at him.
Are you going to make it more troublesome, huh?
Zhu Yun! You're an adult now.
Why can't you tell right from wrong?
Is this a small matter?
Their child was blinded.
The rest of his life is over.
You're still backing that bastard?
What about Li Xun? Why don't you think about Li Xun's future?
What future does he have after he did such a thing?
Whether Fang Zhijing is blind or dead has nothing to do with me.
Don't hit her.
How can you say that?
Yun Yun...
You have now become someone we don't know.
No matter what Li Xun did today, I will definitely go and meet him.
Let me out.
Defendant Li Xun, at about 1:30 p.m.
in the afternoon of January 18, 2016, in the No.1 Lecture Hall of Nanhu University,
beat the victim,
causing serious injury to the victim's face and eye.
According to forensic identification,
the victim suffered bilateral nasal bone and septum fractures and left eyeball enucleation. A serious injury.
The public prosecution agency believes that the defendant
deliberately injured others and caused serious injuries to others.
Thus behavior has violated the regulation of Article 234
of "Criminal Law of the People's Republic of China."
Yun Yun, eat something.
The defendant should take criminal responsibility
and we recommend a sentence of more than three years and up to 10 years in prison.
Defendant, do you have anything to say to the victim?
No.
Doctor, how is she?
She is suffering from qi deficiency and congestive blockage.
She has signs of depression.
Nine out of ten people suffering from depression have a tendency of committing suicide.
You need to watch her this time.
Thank you.
Have you prepared everything for going abroad?
Yes.
She must leave this year.
She must leave.
Yun Yun,
you've been calm for so long.
Listen to me.
I've arranged everything for you to study abroad.
As long as you nod your head, we can leave anytime.
Listen to me.
Go out and relax.
Change your environment.
Maybe it'll be fine.
Yun Yun.
You don't eat or drink all day.
You torture yourself like this.
If you're determined to destroy yourself for that boy
and make your parents suffer for a lifetime,
we'll let you go.
It's up to you.
Dad.
Mom.
Can you promise me one thing?
Gao, we will talk about work only later.
Do you need me to report work in such a place?
Now L&amp;P has nothing to do with you.
You have such an end because you asked for it.  You deserve it.
You occupied L&amp;P by making use of Li Xun's trust in you.
I came for Gao Jianhong.
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I am leaning on your shoulder  ♫
♫  We will not separate  ♫
♫  Avoid the hustle and bustle by staying with me  ♫
♫  It's the center crease of your palm  ♫
♫  That holds me up by giving me the courage to move forward  ♫
♫  Just like a burning flame in the night  ♫
♫  'Cause I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  It's the intuition of the dream  ♫
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I also want to stand by your side  ♫
♫  As long as I am brave enough  ♫
♫  Every dream that I have  ♫
♫  Will not, will not, will not lose to time anymore  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫