♫  Everything is different from the sea to the sky  ♫
♫  The person I used to be has disappeared without a trace  ♫
♫  I no longer believe one person can redeem another  ♫
♫  Until when you broke into my world  ♫
♫  Even if the world exploded into darkness  ♫
♫  We bloom in the dark  ♫
♫  The knight and the king  ♫
♫  Sail at night with white sails to navigate
and protect the vast ocean  ♫
♫  I can see a clear direction  ♫
♫  In which a touch of golden color flickers
at the end of the wheat field  ♫
♫  Even if I am the king  ♫
♫  With supreme glory everything would be
meaningless without you  ♫
♫  Going through fire and water is to make you remember  ♫
♫  The way everything was at the beginning  ♫
♫  If I am the king  ♫
♫  Who is as arrogant as the fierce wind and wild grass  ♫
♫  I only want you to be at my side, whatever it takes  ♫
♫  And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning  ♫
Hello.
Zhu Yun, Li Xun has come for morning self-study.
What?
Where are you?
Whose coat are you wearing?
Mine.
What a fool.
- Where did you go with Li Xun last night?
- We didn't go anywhere.
But you stayed out all night.
But he is attending the morning self-study.
Don't be nervous. We're not here for invigilation.
Don't worry.
Mr. Lin and I are here for something
but not giving you a class.
Li Xun, tell them.
I've applied to our department for establishing a digital practice base for us students.
Led by Miss Zhang and instructed by Mr. Lin,
this base can work as the second classroom practice
and offer credits as an elective course.
During practice in the base, you can be exempt from morning and evening self-study.
It's excellent.
- We can be exempt from morning and evening self-study.
- That's great.
How did you persuade him?
We even won't have morning and evening self-study.
You pleased him but hurt us.
Be quiet. Be quiet. Any problem?
Miss Zhang, can students of other majors join it?
Of course.
Let me add something.
Students of other majors can join it, but we have requirements.
Only after passing the final exam can you gain credits.
As freshmen, you should focus on studying.
If you want to fulfill the learning task by taking part in social practice,
your learning can't be affected.
That's all.
Go on with your self-study and discuss it after class.
Don't you think Li Xun is fighting against our interest group by doing this?
Li Xun!
Zhu Yun, do you dislike me so much?
Why didn't you knock at the door?
I don't need to ask for your approval for returning to my dorm.
I didn't mean to throw it at you.
Who did you want to throw it at?
You dislike him so much that you want to hurt his body.
Read this.
Sorry, Yun is sleeping.
Is this the Li Xun who gave your phone back?
Bad. So bad.
Let me join you.
Infect my computer with virus!
Absent from morning self-study!
Die in the river!
Replies with random messages!
Absent from morning self-study!
It seems that Li Xun and I have only this one enmity.
Zhu Yun, you two have many conflicts.
Be cautious.
Why?
Hate begets love.
Impossible!
What do you think of the three-pointer this afternoon?
Cool.
- Let's continue another day.
- Okay.
Invite more players.
Yes. Invite players of the university basketball team.
-  Even if it rains, we'll also play?
- Men should play basketball in rainy days.
Li Xun, you've never taken part in any activity.
Join us. Play basketball with us.
- I'm not interested in it.
- You can't?
I can't.
I'm only good at one sport.
I see. Men shouldn't waste physical power in something meaningless.
Join us.
Let's go.
Li Xun, the establishment of the base today was discussed between you and Mr. Lin. Right?
Does it have anything to do with you?
Mr. Lin knows that my interest group
is organized for mutual learning and improvement.
It's fine if you don't participate,
but establish a base that can offer credits instead.
Where did this policy advantage come from?
It turns out that you care about this.
I want to compete with you fairly,
but you put pressure on us publicly in this way.
As university students, we should do something meaningful but not waste time.
I don't waste time.
If the interest group wastes time, the base won't waste time?
You're being paranoid.
I mean, don't waste time competing with me.
Li Xun, you run your base, and I'll organize my interest group.
We mind our own business.
I won't occupy your space, and you can't poach my members.
Whatever.
Zhu Yun, have a look.
How is it? I made it by using Java.
It looks simple but it's easy.
Let me show you its system architecture diagram.
First, create a new Maven.
Based on POM, Maven can facilitate our management of project dependencies,
build projects, and generate code documents.
After setting up some parameters...
After setting up some parameters,
we can get a new project with a perfect organizational structure.
Good, Gao. You designed a well-organized structure in a short time.
Well, Zhu Yun, I also searched the CCPC.
An online contest of the China Collegiate Programming Contest (CCPC) will be held every August.
We can't take part in the CCPC this year, but we can be prepared for the next one.
Its prize is good for studying abroad and a postgraduate recommendation,
and we can exercise ourselves in it.
You think about much as a freshman.
You're foresighted.
I used to it.
Zhu Guang, do you have any talent?
No, I don't have any talent.
- Li Wei, can you play any musical instrument?
- No.
- Play the piano?
- I can't.
Violin? Or Erhu?
- No. No.
- Monitor Fang, can you be quiet for a while?
No.
This classroom is for the interest group.
You can go somewhere else to invite others to the performance.
Shut up if you don't know anything.
I can program. Can I perform it?
Stop and take a break.
This group only has a few members, but you've driven away all of them.
Students are no longer active in activities.
We just need to choose a performer for the welcome party, but nobody has signed up for it.
Why don't they have a sense of collective honor in the university?
In high school, we always actively took part in all the activities.
During the sports meeting, even many students ran the 800-meter or 1,000-meter race.
At the art performance, I even performed crosstalk on stage.
Crosstalk is good.
Can't you perform it?
You assist me?
Impossible.
Unreliable. Unreliable.
Did you ask Ren Di about it?
Of course.
We filled the student information sheet when the university started.
You may find one after browsing it.
You're going on a date?
I'm going to accompany a patient at the hospital.
Who?
Wu Mengxing.
I learned from the information sheet that some classmates
are Level 10 pianists or Level 9 violinists,
but they told me that they haven't played for many years.
They're all unreliable.
Wu Mengxing is incommunicative,
but he's good at playing a traditional musical instrument and often gave performances.
He is awesome.
Would he like to perform on stage after having an operation for appendicitis?
Only by exploiting himself can he know how much potential he has.
I'm leaving.
Wu Mengxing. Wu Mengxing.
Monitor, why are you here?
Don't get up. Don't get up.
You, you sit.
How are you? Are you all right?
I'm all right.
Wu Mengxing, you've been sick for some days, but I didn't come to see you until now.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
Monitor, you're busy with class affairs.
I understand you. I can take good care of myself.
Well, are you doing better?
- Can you leave hospital?
- Almost.
I had an operation yesterday.
The doctor said that I can leave after discharging gas.
Discharge gas?
That is... fart.
How can you fart?
Do activities.
I see. Stand up.
Let me help you walk.
Now?
It doesn't matter. Go on walking.
You should have said something earlier.
That you were having an operation and your family isn't here.
Don't stand on ceremony.
I can look after you.
You farted. You farted.
Now that you've farted, so you can leave the hospital?
Don't worry, monitor.
I won't reduce our class attendance rate.
I'm going to apply for discharge tomorrow.
It doesn't matter.
Take your time, as long as you have a certificate for sick leave.
That classmate, Wu Mengxing, I think you are quite well-rounded.
You can also play traditional instruments and have participated in many performances.
What can you play?
Suona.
You, you're awesome.
Suona is the quintessence of Chinese culture.
Mengxing, our department will have a welcome party next Monday.
Would you like to promote traditional culture and play it in public?
I can't play it, but my father can.
I can only sound it.
Why did you write that you often gave performances?
My father was invited to play it at weddings or funerals in our village,
so I just sounded the suona and served as a stopgap.
It doesn't matter. Let's talk about it another day.
It's late. I'm leaving.
Have a good rest.
Monitor, take care.
Why didn't my father teach me?
Old Gao, this is the Maven dependency of Java web.
It's really much easier for you to do this.
And it also looks clean and tidy.
Old Lin told us to simplify codes as much as possible.
After finishing this, let's learn how to turn web pages into desktop programs.
Fang Shumiao, have you finished programming?
Fang Shumiao.
Fang Shumiao, you're absent-minded.
You talked to Wu Mengxing at the hospital?
Don't mention him to me.
You just came back from the hospital, but he has become your enemy now?
Wu Mengxing looks honest but is actually bad.
He told a lie.
He didn't give performances often,
but just sounded the suona at weddings or funerals instead.
What traditional instrumental music?
He can't play the suona at all.
When you needed him, you thought highly of him,
but now you scold him.
Fang Shumiao, you're bad.
Yun Yun, I only have you.
- Old Gao.
- I think it really needs to be revised here, right?
Yes. It's not simple enough.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Fang Shumiao from the Computer Science Department.
I'm Zhu Yun.
Today, we're going to perform crosstalk...
...to amuse you.
Zhu Yun, today, I'll ask you a question in front of so many people in the audience.
Okay.
Did you go to college?
Are you talking nonsense?
Aren't we in college now?
Thank you.
You've finished?
Isn't it funny?
Turn on your computers and learn now. Don't waste time.
What do you mean?
Monitor Fang, you've given a performance,
and we've also acted as the audience.
It's time to get down to business.
Well, now that you watched our performance, you should make an evaluation.
Do you want to know the truth?
If you don't want to defame our class, don't perform it.
Just this? You might as well ask Zhu Yun to touch her navel round her back.
Is our performance really so bad?
You performed very well.
What's the name of this performance?
You two created it?
I think it should be named "living sculpture."
Li Xun, don't insult us.
Why aren't you typing your code on the rooftop but yet have come to make fun of us instead?
Don't you have self-knowledge?
I don't think your place should be called an interest group, but play house instead.
If you still do such meaningless things in university,
it would be better for your interests group to break up.
Stop wasting time and resources.
Li Xun, we are all classmates. There is no need for you to speak so harshly. Right?
Yeah. You are too contemptuous of people.
Now that you look down upon us, why are you here?
Mr. Lin has approved this place for our practice base.
From now on it will be ours.
Why?
Stop!
We're indeed inferior to you. We played house.
But is it interesting to compete with us for this territory?
It's interesting.
Welcome party?
I really think you guys should do a show.
Other performers will play musical instruments, sing or dance.
They're boring.
You will be laughed at as soon as you stop there.
It'll be very good.
I have the ability to go on stage.
Do you have the ability to see?
You're inviting me?
You want me to go?
Immature.
Pupil.
Class cadres can get 20 points.
Excellent classes will get an extra 20 points.
Students who participate in the municipal first-level project of social practice can get 50 points,
and the prize winners will get an extra 50 points.
You haven't finished yet?
I just edited a paragraph and sent it to you.
Zhu Yun, stop writing.
I didn't sign up for our performance at all.
Our class already quit this activity.
You can give up, but I won't. I can turn it into a talk show.
Yun Yun, give up.
No.
I'll absolutely perform this talk show.
What's the function of this paper plane?
This is the theme of this freshmen's joint performance.
Take care. Take care.
Take good photos.
This girl plays the violin well.
She also looks good.
Yeah, she is pretty,
but maybe I can't conquer her heart.
Her heart doesn't want to be conquered by you, either.
I'm Zhu Yun from Class 1 of the Computer Science Department.
Since I was young, I've never liked my family name.
As we know...
Okay?
You can do it.
Thanks. Thanks, everyone.
Actually, I played it for a boy.
He just got here.
Li Xun from the Computer Science Department!
Maybe you don't know me, but today I must tell you something.
I...
always like you!
Li Xun!
Express love?
Li Xun is here?
Yes, he is under the stage.
Li Xun is too much!
He shouldn't leave that girl alone.
You say I'm fake, you're also fake.
Zhu Yun, Li Xun is here.
Can you give up?
He's so dead.
Girls who learn music are really extraordinary and enthusiastic.
She was so brave and outspoken in expressing her love.
Now, let's welcome Zhu Yun from Class 1 of the Computer Science Department
to bring us a talk show.
Let's welcome her with applause!
Zhu Yun! Zhu Yun! Zhu Yun!
Hello, everyone. I'm Zhu Yun from Class 1 of the Computer Science Department.
Since I was young, I've never liked my family name.
As we know, regardless of whether a girl is pretty or not,
as long as her family name is related to animals,
such as pig (zhu), sheep (yang), and cow (niu), her name is vulgar.
My father dotes on me.
He has encouraged me since my childhood.
He even gave me a cute nickname, Piggy.
"Piggy," he said, "whatever you want, I'll do my best to get it for you."
"Really, dad? I want a dog," I replied.
"No way!" He said.
I'm very happy at university,
because single students (single dogs) are everywhere.
One day, I saw an in-your-face ownerless dog near the first canteen.
It was a golden retriever.
It is said that it's very clever and promising,
so I decided to keep it.
Now that I want to keep it, I want to cultivate it into a top dog.
I told the chef of the first canteen that I wanted the dog at the gate.
Then the chef came out with a kitchen knife
and asked me whether I wanted a braised or steamed one.
I refused him and told him that I wanted to send it to school and cultivate it into a top dog.
The chef took a dislike to me.
He asked me whether I was insane or not.
Regardless of whether I was insane or not, I insisted on keeping this dog.
I wanted the golden retriever to attend morning self-study.
I stroked it and asked, "Golden Retriever, do you want to go to school?"
Do you think it's useful to study in the morning?
Three chances.
- If you make it, I'll attend the morning self-study.
- Game over.
But it bit me.
You are so fake.
While I had myself vaccinated against rabies,
I thought about whether I stroked it in the wrong way or not.
I still went to see it the next day,
because I could have myself vaccinated against rabies,
but it couldn't have itself vaccinated against me.
Are you afraid to hand it in?
Afraid?
This seems to be a virus.
The third time, I specially brought it lamb skewers.
Do I have to give my heart to you after eating ten of your lamb skewers?
I… I didn't take my phone. Open the door.
Hello, Zhu Yun is busy now.
Okay, okay.
As you expect, it ate my skewers but bit me again.
This dog is a real dog.
To achieve my goal, I was going to brainwash it.
Since then, I'd been calling it genius, master, or champion.
It seemed to understand my meaning.
Once I call it champion, it kept wagging its tail and was very happy.
Everyone knows that the Department of Computer Science has a golden retriever called Champion.
K.O.
After all, I'd paid so much sunk cost,
so I decided to educate it for the last time.
But it didn't appreciate what I did for it, so I got angry.
I thought it might be better to raise a pig than keep it. I should kill it.
I asked the chef to take it away angrily,
but after all, it was a dog, so I should rescue it.
I hurried to the first canteen,
but I saw this golden retriever fade in the pot after opening the door.
It turns out that the golden retriever was just a rural dog.
It fell into the paint bucket and was dyed golden,
but it finally restored its original appearance.
The chef muttered, "It's just a rural dog."
After hearing this,
this dying rural dog immediately barked,
"Who are you scolding? I'm the top dog but not a rural dog."
Thank you, I'm Zhu Yun.
Great! Great!
Hi, dear students, it's surprising that the girl from the Computer Science Department...
- What are they doing?
- What's up?
Piggy,
it turns out that you have been keeping an eye on me.
You don't have to keep an eye on me.
We can be together in the open.
♫  If love remains warm  ♫
♫  This dream will automatically abort  ♫
♫  When you wake up, please stay  ♫
♫  Don't go, fate is not a journey  ♫
♫  Hold onto me, don't get lost  ♫
♫  It's the depth of one's soul  ♫
♫  You're my everything  ♫
♫  Take one step back and try to understand  ♫
♫  I care so much about you  ♫
(Several Friend Requests)
You're awake. Your phone has been vibrating all this time.
My Renren account has been flooded with messages.
It's not a big deal.
The post has been pinned to the top of the forum.
You went viral, Zhu Yun.
Little Piggy,
it turns out that you have been keeping an eye on me.
Tell me the truth. When were you with Li Xun?
You should be blamed for it.
- I bravely gave myself up for you.
- You really gave yourself up?
Fang Shumiao, you want to be beaten?
As the saying goes, only those who care about you keep an eye on you.
If you didn't like Li Xun a little bit, why pay attention to him so much?
Okay, I'm wrong.
Go wash your face and brush your teeth. We need to attend class at 10:00.
I'm about to take a bath. I was so tired that I forgot to take a bath yesterday.
Fang Shumiao, will I be recognized if I go out?
Did you really think you were the heroine of celebrity gossip?  Heroine?
Others are just interested in it momentarily and will forget you soon.
You're awesome. I heard that you've been with Li Xun.
Oh, no. Even people like you who don't go to school for a week know about it.
Fang Shumiao, come with me.
No one will recognize you without your clothes on.
Did you watch yesterday's video?
At the welcome party, that girl from the Computer Science Department seemed to express her love.
I even secretly searched her account to browse on Renren.com,
but I couldn't search that boy's account.
That video is really sweet.
And that boy is very handsome.
He seems famous. His name is Li Xun, right?
- Yes.
- He even called her Little Piggy in a low voice.
So warm.
The love story of Little Piggy and the ownerless dog is sweet.
I ship them. I ship them.
I seem to have forgotten to bring my campus card.
Search for it again.
Girl, I want to borrow your campus card.
I also forget to bring it.
Whose is this?
Zhu Yun, is this that girl from the Computer Science Department who expressed her love?
- She seems to be that girl.
- She's really that girl.
- Is it hot?
- No, it's not hot.
Why were you so shy?
You were recognized. Why escape?
My lie was exposed on the spot.
Of course I escaped.
What are you doing?
I'm about to issue a statement.
Why don't you invite a few reporters and hold a press conference?
What's the use of this explanation?
I just learned web programming yesterday and I am using it today.
How is it?
Solemnly declare that everything that happened at the orientation party yesterday was just a stage effect.
I'm still single.
Old Gao was right.
We students of applied technology need practice.
We may learn everything at a crucial time.
Zhu Yun!
That was just a part of my performance.
What I did was just for the stage effect.
I don't like Li Xun. I won't be with him.
Are you satisfied?
Really?
Look. I just issued a statement on Renren.com.
Can you believe me now?
Sorry, I shouldn't anger you.
Zhu Yun, you liar!
Is this really Li Xun?
Does he also use this software?
He'd do anything to play tricks on me.
Dear teachers and students, this is the broadcast station of Nanhu University.
I'm Yuan Xiaoyun.
Good afternoon, everyone.
This afternoon, I'll host the column "Free Speaking" for you.
If you have something or worries to say,
please feel free to contribute to our broadcasting station’s Weibo public account.
Now, please listen to a piece of music.
- Zhu Yun.
- Little Piggy.
Xiaoyun, I want to contribute.
Hello, everyone. We received a special contribution, and the contributor is sitting next to me.
She is Zhu Yun from Class 1 of the Computer Science Department.
Something has been troubling her these days,
so she wants to issue a statement through our broadcast station.
Hello, everyone. I'm Zhu Yun from Class 1 of the Computer Science Department.
At yesterday's welcome party,
I performed a talk show on behalf of our class,
but something happened at the end of my talk show
that made you misunderstand my relationship with Li Xun.
Here, I want to tell you that Li Xun was just my guest performer,
and we don't have any personal relationship.
I hope you don't misunderstand.
I'm sorry for taking up your time.
Thank you.
Zhu Yun's statement is really effective.
When I went to a student union meeting, people chased me and asked if Li Xun in your class was single again.
Congratulations, Little Piggy.
It's finally clear.
Almost? Yet?
I don't care. Anyway, I'm relieved.
Fang Shumiao, if I hear "Little Piggy" again,
I'll beat the speakers, especially you.
It's strange.
Besides good grades, what are Li Xun's other advantages?
Why do good girls all like him?
Just because of his unique hair style and personality?
Zhu Yun, I agree with you about making fun of him on stage.
Look.
What-What happened?
You made it clear?
The golden retriever's hair faded?
♫  Don't know how you've been there  ♫
♫  Don't know how I've been there  ♫
Zhu Yun, he didn't really dye his hair black for you, did he?
♫  Nothing wrong, so alone  ♫
That's all for today.
Class is over!
Let's have a talk.
It's bad to talk here.
They bickered.
I want to talk about something important.
Let's talk outside.
No need. Just talk here.
I'll finish soon.
In front of so many classmates?
- You...
- Go ahead.
Why did you make that comment on my page?
What comment?
Forget it. Can't you assist me in clearly explaining that
I'm not your girlfriend?
- Why?
- What "why"?
Now that you're not my girlfriend, why should I help you?
You're glad about being watched by so many classmates, right?
Yes.
Who is your guest performer?
Did you ask me?
Li Xun, why did you dye your hair black?
You did so due to my words?
If my words hurt you, I'm sorry.
We can take this opportunity to make this matter clear together.
You're touchy-feely but cute.
What else do you want to do?
Issue another statement?
Do you know the more you explain, the more darker and darker it gets?
Aren't you getting darker and darker now?  Completely dark.
- Hello, Mr. Lin.
- Hi, Mr. Lin.
- Hi.
Li Xun.
You dyed your hair black?
It looks better.
You asked me not be so eccentric.
Yes.
Does he look better?
Good.
I'm telling you for the last time.
I'm not your guest performer.
It's not my duty to help you.
♫  Who controls the marionette? ♫
♫  The flickering candle flame is asking me  ♫
♫  What hides behind the deep fear?  ♫
♫  Love and hate are reversed  ♫
♫  Forgotten stories. Days covered with dust  ♫
♫  Time is waiting for me like amber  ♫
♫  The reflected world makes a knot in the heart  ♫
♫  How could love be inexplicable?  ♫
♫  Cruel truth is revealed in the blink of an eye ♫
♫  Who is acting vigorously with the masked face?  ♫
♫  Sad truth is uncovered in a trice  ♫
♫  Presumptuously shout and laugh at me  ♫
♫  Cruel truth is good or bad?  ♫
♫  Who mourns for the silent solemnity with soul?  ♫
♫  The definitions of love and hate have been blurred  ♫
Thank you.
Thanks, everyone. We're Light Red Band!
How was our song?
- I can't understand.
- Would you like to invest in our band?
What will I get?
If you invest in our band, you'll be our boss and have shares in our band.
The shares in your band?
When our band makes profits, the profits will be allocated to you at the agreed rate.
- Okay.
- Keep your word?
Of course. Do I need to pay a deposit today?
It's a deal.
Boss Li, feel free to request any song that you want to listen to!
We'll only work for you today.
Why are you here?
Hard to listen to.
Do our songs sound so bad?
Don't get me wrong.
I'll definitely invest in your band.
I just didn't want to waste time inside.
Listening to our songs is a waste of time.
Isn't your current behavior a waste of time?
Please respect the fund source of your Light Red Band.
You earn so much money by doing this?
You shouldn't go to university.
If I were you, I would have dropped out.
Anyway, you neither attend self-study nor do homework.
I neither do homework nor attend self-study because they're very easy for me.
I don't want to do anything meaningless.
I've established a practice base.
You can join it.
I made a special application with the department.
Credits can be added and early self-study can be exempted.
It's good for you.
That's why you dyed your hair black?
I need to slightly respect Mr. Lin.
Gosh, it's amazing.
Li Xun is going to be a good boy.
I thought you did so due to Zhu Yun.
Your base has seriously affected our interest group.
This classroom is for our base. You'd better dismiss your interest group.
You are nobody. Don't look down upon us.
Do you dare make a bet?
If Old Gao and I get better C Language scores than you,
your practice base must be incorporated into our interest group,
and you listen to us.
What if you lose?
♫  It's the intuition of the dream  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I am leaning on your shoulder  ♫
♫  We will not separate  ♫
♫  Avoid the hustle and bustle by staying with me  ♫
♫  It's the center crease of your palm  ♫
♫  That holds me up by giving me the courage to move forward  ♫
♫  Just like a burning flame in the night  ♫
♫  'Cause I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  It's the intuition of the dream  ♫
♫  It breaks through the boundary  ♫
♫  The first glance during the first meeting  ♫
♫  Spreads and later it wins the world for me  ♫
♫  The clock keeps ticking without stopping for rest  ♫
♫  I also want to stand by your side  ♫
♫  As long as I am brave enough  ♫
♫  Every dream that I have  ♫
♫  Will not, will not, will not lose to time anymore  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫
♫  Because I believe I love you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course ♫
♫  The one by your side is me  ♫
♫  Spending such a long time with you  ♫
♫  Because I believe I want you  ♫
♫  True love will take its course  ♫
♫  That hot firework  ♫
♫  It's always you who keeps it lit up for me  ♫