This account seems to be wrong
Something wrong
Three years ago
Officials under Zhou Junlan
To help Song Hongjian transport disaster relief grain
Purchase eighty ships from the shipyard
Boat nails on this cost order
All provided by Gu Family Quotation Gu Family
More than three times more expensive than usual
Could it be that Gu Gu and the shipyard
The price of iron nails is high
Then the difference in each
All gave the official as rebates
This matter needs to be investigated in detail
Now the ship is parked in the capital
Just nailed inside the boat board
Look at the surface alone
Not yet known
in this way
Is the Marquis still checking?
Of course, I have to check
But how to check this
Zhou Shilang
Do you have money
have
About how much
Ensure you have no worries about food and clothing in this life
Enjoy all the glory
It's enough
Let's go
Where to go
shipyard
Don't go for now
The Marquis won't go
But someone is going to take the lead
Still don't believe me
How could it be
Recently, Mrs. Qiu helped me a lot
You said you can see the future
I naturally believe
Insight into the future
Yes, it's not
How to say this
This is rice cake
If fate puts this piece of rice cake before the ant hole
If the ants follow the original trajectory
You'll find this pastry
This is the future I see
But if an ant found the pastry
But I didn't report it to the exclusive
Then will these ants still find this pastry
Maybe it will
Or maybe not
Destiny
These ants would have owned a pastry
But a traitor appeared among them
The future of the pastry should have happened
Offset
You can see the direction of fate
That's true
But it cannot control the variables of the hit
This is not
It's easy to understand at one point
This is a teaching for children
So say
Mrs. Qiu has been predicting things like a god recently
It's because of the fate you see
And no variables
certainly
Mrs. Qiu is gifted
I admire you
The talented one is Ji Yunchao
Not me
I'm just in front of her ant hole
Just put down the rice cake's hand
Compare yourself as fate
Why did it become
Ants in the cave
On a whim
That's it
Ji Yunchao's talent
It's just a gift from fate on a whim
Will be taken back one day
And I'm different from her
She is the struggle to survive ant
I
It's the hand of life and death
What she's going through now
All you do
yes
Not really
I was destiny in the past
Looking down on all living beings
You're in it too
いました
You are accusing your father of refusing the country and the people.
Work hard and work hard
All are just for the good
Ji Yunchao's stepping stone climbing the cloud ladder
I've seen your destiny
In the future, Ji Yun Dynasty will be repaid for great revenge.
You will be abandoned
Rather than being used by her
Not as good as
Convert to me
Great revenge is repaid
She hasn't told you yet
Then just pretend I didn't say it
Why do you tell me this
One is a child who can teach
Two is a whim
Three for
I already know Zhou Junlan well
Now I'm interested in you again
You've thought about it
Again
Give me some time to think about it
I don't have much patience
Can make an example for you
You believe me
I'll remind you one more sentence
Zhou Junlan and Ji Yunchao rushed to the shipyard overnight
We're going
Still not to go
Don't go for now
reason
Let others pay
Wouldn't it be better
Zhou Shilang
Please
You see
It's this ship
This ship
It was three years ago
One of the ships ordered by the imperial court
Of course this
The young man dare not deceive Mr. Zhou
Thank you Mr. Zhou
If there is anything else you need help
The young man goes through fire and water without hesitation
Burn it
What
Can't
sure
Since Mr. Zhou has bought this boat
You have the final say on how to deal with it
What is Mr. Zhou thinking
The beacon plays with the princes
Just for this
The difference between Zhou Shilang
King You of Zhou played with the princes
A smile to make a beauty
Mr. Zhou spent money to burn grain ships
A thousand money to spend money
What's wrong
how
It's really inappropriate to compare this
I think it's good
If you like it
I'll give it to you
Qiu Baosi'er
Tip-toothed and sharp mouth
Thank you for the praise
What are you doing here
Ship nail prices are more than three times higher
However, it is too cumbersome to remove the ship and pick up the nails
Why not buy a ship
Burn it
Take the nails and count them
This is the boat I bought
What does it have to do with you
Of course not
Just take a look
Report to the Minister of State Zhou
All the nails you want have been here
Follow your instructions
Count count
Please check it out
Pay attention to the family bill carefully
The number of nails required for a ship
It can indeed match this one
Just why
This nail is three times more expensive than an ordinary ship nail
This nail is a cast iron nail
More durable than ordinary nails
Get out
The Gu family's account can be settled
Flat
The remaining eleven officials involved in the case
Yiping
That's the examiner
With the remaining fifty-one tributes
No
Over the past few days
I have checked nearly 300 books in total
Sixty-three people involved in the case
No problems with the accounts
No corruption and fraud
Why are there all southern scholars on the list
The barbarians invaded the world all year round
Life activities
How hard is Northern scholars live
And because of the turmoil in the north
Most of the test sites are located in the south
Northern scholars traveled long distances and worked hard
Poor natural condition
In addition, the climate in the south is humid and hot
Very easy to be unacceptable to the local environment
All of the above
All for reasons
How could Your Majesty not know
His Majesty
The eleven people found by Mr. Zhou
I have reviewed it in private
No problem
I know
Why is Your Majesty
I and Zhanwu led their troops to death
Open up territory and expand land
It's been twenty-years since you came
I'm old
His Majesty
The building will collapse
How to suppress the group of monkeys at the foot of the mountain
The northern Hu people are constantly harassed
Already turbulent
This time the North and South list is released
Add fuel to the fire
I ordered Zhou Junlan to investigate the case
He must clarify the truth
Just want him to kill the chicken to warn the monkey
More than a dozen northern scholars were recruited
Stable Northern People
Stronger the country
He doesn't meet my wish
His heart can be punished
Punishment and fraud
Deadly
Fifty-one tributes
Fifty-one lives
Mr. Zhou is too kind
Fifty-one life
With my country
Which one is more important
It's a life-threatening
The country is heavy
I heard that the Marquis Xuanying and Zhou Junlan have always been disagreeable
Zhou Junlan can't find any problem
I ordered Xuanying to investigate again
Until the problem is found
Put those fifty-one
Removed with Zhou Junlan's party members
Now there are 63 people involved in the case
Sixty-three lives
With the glorious future
I'm curious
How did he choose?
His Majesty
Xuan Yinghou asked for a meeting
Promotion
Report to Your Majesty
I have thoroughly investigated the case of the North and South
Fifty-one tribute men involved in the case
An examiner
Eleven inspectors
All are suspected of fraud and bribery
Without exception
According to our dynasty law
How should it be handled
Corruption and bribery
The crime should be killed
It's just that this time there are a lot of people
I'm afraid I'll kill too many animals
Aggression of the dragon veins in the city
It's better to choose a good day
Ship to Liangzhou execution ground for disposal
So very good
but
The officers and soldiers escorting the car
It must be my person
If there is any mistake
Take you as a question
Subject:
Eat quickly
You haven't eaten for a few days
No appetite
This hike is high and the road is long
How to be hungry
Just go to death
You and I have no regrets
Not yet reached the end
I can't accept my fate
The sky has no eyes
The world is unfair
I've accepted it
Long sunny and heavy fog
It's going to rain heavily
This rain has been on the verge of a long time
I'm afraid something will go wrong
On the way to escort
Suddenly there was a heavy fog and rain
The rain overnight caused a mountain collapse
Sixty-three death row prisoners
All buried by huge rocks
There is such a clever thing in the world
Everything I say is true
I dare not deceive the king and the emperor
What are the great opinions of Mr. Zhou?
This is a natural disaster
No human can do
Jiang Shangshu
It is both a natural disaster and a punishment
God has eyes
Don't want blood to stain the emperor's soil
So this is how it is done
I'd like to help Your Majesty
Relieve the troubles in your heart
Become a virtuous and beautiful name
Although it is a natural disaster
Should we punish according to the law
I punished Xuan Ying Hou forty to whip forty
Tomorrow, I will go to Dali Temple to receive the punishment
Mr. Zhou, come and sentence me
yes
His Majesty
Master Ye is already waiting outside
But Master Ye, who is proficient in the art of immortality
It's exactly
Please come in quickly
Yes Yes
quick
Account Book
Zhou Shilang
Do you want to protect eleven lives of your command
So what if you want
Then you and I might as well make a deal
If I can do it
You handed over Zhao Peng's account book to me
Qiu Xianer told you that mountain collapse
So what
You can stand her
Have made a choice
It's time to give up your position
You should let go now
What if I insist on fighting with you
Then I only have
Stay with you to the end
Forty whips
No Ji Yunchao
I'll depend on how you can bear it