This is so cute.
Look at this.
So cute.
And his little hat.
Do you remember this?
Of course.
He was so tiny back then.
So cute.
You sure we want to try again?
Of course.
I'm fully prepared this time.
Kai must experience the parade.
Ya, his first parade.
First parade.
(Papa & Daddy EP3. Taipei Pride)
Status report.
The first year.
Jerry's mom suddenly appeared
the day before the parade.
To stop her from finding out,
I took Kai out.
But then his mom
had a stomachache and slept over.
Jerry had to accompany her.
Kai and I had to wait till she left
to go back home.
We missed the parade completely.
Solution 1: Mike's home.
Yes, what should we do?
We'll take Kai to your place
the day before.
Will you be ready?
Sir, yes, Sir.
My sister will stay home to keep Mom
occupied the day before.
You guys
take care of Kai for a few hours.
Till my mom's asleep,
and made sure won't show up.
We are ready.
Good.
The second year.
Kai brought his favorite toy out.
Halfway through
his toy
flew out the window.
He cried so hard.
We went back to find it.
It took us forever.
Missed the parade again.
Solution 2:
Sasa's place.
Yes, Sir.
I'll drive right behind you,
in case anything falls out of the car.
This is Kai's new favorite.
Pipi.
One, two.
We'll prepare extras in the car,
in case it drops and cannot be found,
or taken by aliens.
Then we can recover immediately.
There won't be any aliens that day.
You never know.
Okay.
Remember to take off the labels.
I'll pay you later.
Gay parade.
We will make it!
Here comes Kai-Kai.
Cheers.
Kai's asleep?
Yes.
You're sure your mom's asleep,
and won't raid Taipei?
I'm sure.
Positive.
100%.
My sister kept an eye on her,
and she is sure.
Okay.
I'll take him into the room.
Turn off the TV.
(Alarm)
Parade…
Must succeed.
Let's go see your pretty uncles and aunts later.
- They're really nice.
- The Rainbow Gathering.
How did you know?
Kai, the uncles and aunts are great,
because they're also brave like you.
Yes.
They will love you,
and care for you a lot.
It's so early, who could it be?
Can it be your mom?
What if she took an early morning ride?
My sister left in the middle of the night.
No one watched over her this morning.
What should we do?
Let me take a peek.
If it's really her,
we'll just pretend we're not home, okay?
Okay.
There's someone outside.
Open the door.
Parade.
Kai, go!
Finally succeeded.
You need to thank me
for keeping mom busy last night.
We took the early train this morning,
we're exhausted.
Ya, bro, I didn't sleep at all.
Alright, here…
- Go buy some food to eat.
- Thank you, Damian.
You're the best.
Your legs are sore, daddy hug.
Daddy, my legs are sore, too.
These two are exhausted.
I'm exhausted, too.
Let's find somewhere to rest?
Sure.
I know a nice shop nearby.
You lead the way.
Come with me.
Lead the way.
Let's go, let's go rest.
Go…
Isn't it pretty?
So beautiful.
This Barefoot Bubbly
is a rainbow sparkling wine to celebrate
equal rights and same-sex marriage.
I asked my friend to mail it
from the States,
the only one in Taiwan.
Thanks, hubby.
Can I really drink it?
Of course, open it up.
Yes.
Of course you can drink it.
Barefoot
is your favorite wine.
You haven't drunk much lately.
Alex's taking care of the kids today.
We can celebrate.
Drink.
No problem.
I agree to drinking.
Then I'll drink a little.
But don’t push me.
We won’t.
No pushing.
Look at today's occasion.
Heartwarming.
I like that.
You're good.
Cheers.
Let's play a game, okay?
Great.
Play what?
"Never have I ever".
Sure, cool.
I'll go first.
Okay.
I've never had a one-night stand.
Be honest.
Who?
Hurry up and admit it.
I've never raised a son.
I've never been with someone older.
Fine, I'll drink.
I've never left someone for another person.
Fine.
Getting exciting.
I've never had sex in public.
You two.
I want to know.
I've never had a boyfriend.
This is too targeted.
1 2 3 4, go go.
You're too good at this.
Play 10 15.
- 10.
- 15.
How drunk are you?
50-50.
Everyone must toast to her.
We all have to.
Come on.
All together.
Rock, Paper, Scissors.
We should go back to the parade.
Time to go back.
Okay.
Finish the wine.
Finish the wine first.
Hubby, you go pick up Kai.
Hurry up.
Matt.
Okay, I'm going over now.
Okay, we're going back to the parade.
Parade.
Come on.
Thanks everyone.
I'm very happy that everyone
gathered here today because of love.
Later,
I'll pass the mic around.
When you get the mic,
you can make a wish for next year.
Does anyone want to make a wish?
Here's a pair of cute transnational couple.
Come on, make a wish.
I wish that our love is something
not just for pride,
but every day for the year to come.
Oh my gosh, so touching.
What about you?
Don't lose.
I hope our happiness can last very long.
Your "happiness" means sex, right?
You're good.
I hope gay adoption can be legalized.
Just like us.
Great, I want a kiss, too.
Here's another couple,
very cute and handsome.
I hope the person I love the most
can express their love loudly.
Love…
Wish you happy forever.
Baby, did you have fun today?
I haven't had this much fun in a long time.
Kai is so cute.
I love him so much.
Do you remember?
Every time Kai sees
street artists,
he runs over and take their mic.
Yes…
Those still performance artists,
he runs over and tickle them.
Like this?
Kai learned that from you.
Fine, I'll leave you alone.
Remember that time you got sick?
Of course I do.
He came to touch my forehead
every 3 minutes.
And took a bucket of ice
to reduce my fever.
My pillow was completely wet.
That's his way of showing love.
We are so happy.
So I must work harder,
to give Kai a better future.
And lots and lots of love.
And ice cream.
Kai.
When was the last time you saw Kai?
He was walking with Sasa's kids
right behind us.
That was ten minutes ago.
Kai-Kai.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Kai-Kai.
Come on, hurry.
Sasa.
Sasa, have you seen Kai-Kai?
Was he with you?
No.
What's wrong?
Was Kai playing with you?
Yes.
Where's he now?
Where's he?
Did you see him?
Okay, hold on.
Matt, tell Mom.
Was Kai playing with you?
- Yes.
- Okay, then what?
Why weren't you playing after?
I want to take his Pipi.
He said he wants his Papa to protect him.
I should have protected him.
I didn't protect him.
We keep looking.
Keep looking.
Don't worry.
Kai-Kai.
Excuse me.
We just lost a little boy.
Four years old and about this height.
He was wearing denim shirt and jeans,
white shirt,
rainbow bowtie,
red shoes,
the Spider-Man kind.
Can you help us find him?
Please.
Thank you.
I'll ask the staff to make an announcement.
Hold on.
We lost a little boy.
This was his outfit.
Please broadcast it for me.
Okay.
May we have your attention, please.
We have a missing kid.
Hey, let's not panic.
Or you can think about
which route you've taken today,
and trace your way back.
We went to
watch the show, right?
Then that…
Cafe.
We'll go to the cafe.
Okay?
Let's go.
Thanks, Mike.
Let us know if you find him.
Be careful.
What happened, bro?
Kai's missing.
How?
Ok, calm down.
You calm down.
Let's call the cops.
No.
If you call the cops, they'll kill him.
Don't you watch the news?
No one's killing him.
We're not rich.
No one's kidnapped him.
Did you set up any enemies at Verso?
Took others' money?
What are you talking about?
That's mpossible.
Stop fighting.
Do you guys have Kai's video or photos
from today?
Send it in the group, ask everyone to help.
Yes.
A lot of people came to the parade today.
Everyone can help.
Great.
Hurry.
Sasa,
could you trace back
the parade's route,
and see if you find Ka?
Of course.
Alex, you go over there.
We'll go this way.
I'll send it to you, thank you.
Kai.
Hi.
Hello.
I want to ask about your monthly fee.
Our usual monthly fee is 7 USD.
Today….
Free of charge.
How come there's a kid here?
- Little kid.
- Kai.
Where are your parents?
Over there.
Papa and Daddy are looking for you.
Kai, can you tell your uncles and aunts
that you're looking for us?
Are you saying this is your Daddy's voice?
Yes.
You sure?
- Yes.
- Then hurry.
Ya, he's probably lost.
I need to take him to Information.
His jacket.
May I have your attention please.
We have a missing kid.
About four years old.
Wearing white shirt, denim jacket.
Kai.
Papa's so sorry.
Look at my Pipi.
You're probably the Dad.
Thank you.
Great.
You're welcome.
Kai, where were you?
I saved Pipi.
You saved Daddy.
Kai.
We were scared to death.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
My staff was too careless.
They were too focused on playing with him.
Forgot to think that a kid his age
being alone might mean he's lost.
I should be the one apologizing.
Kai, were you scared?
No.
Why?
Because everyone here
is very kind.
They played with me.
Wow.
- Thankfully he ran into you.
- Kai.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Look who it is.
We were so scared.
Where's Kai?
How did you find him?
Fortunately he ran into them.
Thank you.
Kai, what do you want for dinner?
No ice cream,
only savory food.
I want ice cream with scrambled eggs.
Kai, that's so disgusting.
Baby, what do you want?
Hello, hello.
I'm Pipi.
- Hi, everyone.
- Kai, no.
Pipi will fall.
My Pipi fell.
Husband.
Stop.
Stop the car.
My Pipi.
I want my Pipi.
- Hello?
- Sir.
Don't worry.
We got it.
You've been behind us this whole time?
Yes, sir.
Here, Kai.
Kai, your Pipi.
Come one.
Thank you.
- Kai, what's this?
- Your Pipi.
Thank you all.
Thank you.
It dropped.
Are you happy?
Fortunately they picked him up.
I know.
- Thank you.
- Group hug.