[Reunion]
[The Sound of the Providence]
[Episode 17]
I said it many times
When I came in
I saw her lying on the bed
with the boss face-to-face
But when we came in
she was standing here
Right
But
Fatty
where did you go
I went to have a meeting with Uncle Erbai
Why don't you believe me
I'm telling the truth
Were you sleepwalking
Of course not
OK
Then you brought her into your room
I don't have that kind of hobby
I doubt it
All right
Right
I know you very well
You always took her when you were on the mudflat
You must have brought her in
Kanjian
turn off the lights please
What's that
What's that It's you
Uncle Erbai come here
What's this
What's this Give it to me
Uncle Erbai
This is the shellfish monster I told you
Have a look
Naive
it gets out with us
There are so many in the South Sea King's Tomb
As soon as I see it I want to kill it
Erjing
Take these two things back
and protect them
Hand them over
to the Cultural Heritage Administration later
OK Mr. Second
Xie
go back to Wuzhou and check your mental health
Slow down Slow down
Xie
Be careful
Did you conceal anything from me
No I didn't
What can I conceal
Really
Yeah
Uncle Erbai I'm a little tired
I'd like to go to bed
OK it's done
You'll die of smoking
This logistics company looks pretty cool
This is the car of the 11th warehouse
What warehouse
Warehouse 11
Haven't you heard of it
Of course I have
It means
there are 11 brothers
moving things together
It's nonsense
It's said that
this 11th warehouse
has a history of more than 100 years
No one knows where it is exactly
And no one knows who these warehouse keepers are
You can hide anything
in the 11th warehouse
As long as you keep the receipt
no matter how many years have passed
you can take your thing out
Why is it called the 11th Warehouse
What should it be then
It should be
Super Century-old Warehouse 11
It's so mysterious
But how do you know that
I read it in my grandfather's notebook
Give it to me
I left it in my room
You know what I mean
Give me your cigarette
I don't have more
You're an adult Don't lie to me
I didn't
I saw you taking a new pack from Uncle Erbai
We can do nothing about the truck
Get that girl's camera back for me
Yes sir
Come here get on
Take a seat
Thank you
Where are you going We're going to leave
I'm sorry Give me a minute
I'll say something to my sister
OK be quick
Don't wait
He won't come
Let's go
Mr. Second
what about our next plan
Where is Liu Sang
He's here
I worked for two days in the underground river
This is the structure I got
based on the reflection of sound
I tried my best
If you take me
and we walk slowly
I will finish it gradually
When we near the Thunder City
I can know where it is
If we want to go deep into it
we have to prepare supplies enough for six weeks
apply for government permission
and prepare ourselves for the exploration
Is that clear
Are we really going to look for the Thunder City
Do you remember the words Sanxing left
We were threatened to hide the cultural relics
of the South Sea King's Tomb
under Yang Daguang's house
Yang Daguang died
for being forced to listen to thunder
Mu Xuehai refused them and got crazy
They believe
there are treasures in the Thunder City
that can make them get what they want
I'm forced to go there
If you can see it
please come to help us
If there are cultural relics
I will try my best to protect them
Wu Sanxing
The one that forced him took so much effort
to go to the Thunder City
I want to go there too
The map of this place
is hidden in the thunder
Don't you think it's amazing
Why can we get all the answers we want
when we reach the Thunder City
Mr. Second
do you still have any regret in your heart
After Qi Jin came back
from the South Sea King's Tomb
she left Wuzhou
I've checked all the places in the country
but I can't find her
I don't know where she is
I heard
she was sad about what happened
in the South Sea King's Tomb
I also want to know the truth
I want to find her
I also want to understand that movie
Come here
After you pass the border
someone will take you to the train station
I hope
Come here
you can figure out something on the bus
Where is Kylin
I want to have a talk with him
He'll catch you up later
Uncle Erbai that's not a good idea
We came here together
We should go back together
Let me ask him
I have to ask him No no
No more nonsense
What's wrong with him
You should come out and see us off right
Goodbye Uncle Erbai
Please take a seat
He is too thoughtless
We'll return if we miss the train
Kylin is so thoughtless
Should we break off the contact
between Mr. Third Junior and the outside world
I've arranged everything
We've been to so many places
and taken so much effort
Everything is taken away
by your Uncle Erbai
Kylin is left there
You're sick
What the heck do we get
It's easy to get carsick to read in the car
Have a drink
You shouldn't
give up the milk tea
You should drink up
Uncle Erbai has a very interesting theory
The reason why people look for the Thunder City
is because it can make them get what they want
Get whatever they want
It sounds great
But it's hard
to get whatever we want
What do I want
Can I be as thin as the sculpture
of the Thunder God in the Thunder City
But I know
it's tempting to you
You want to go there right
Fatty
let me ask you a question
If you were going to die soon
I said if
what would you want to do most
What would be your plan
Have a hot pot
Do what you want
It's great
I'm telling you
You don't have to go to the Thunder City
I can help you to get what you want
Tell me what you want to do
Really
Yes
Then I think
I want to sleep for a while
What a dry sense of humor
Fatty
Here we are Get off
No
What are you doing
I know
what I want to do
Help me
to steal the figurine
Why
Why why
What do you mean
Why did you ask me why
Well
I got you wrong
or you didn't make it clear
Well
think about it
Every time the figurine appears
it will bring me some unexpected clues
I think she was in my room
as if she wanted to tell me something
So Fatty
I have to steal her back
Uncle Sanxing
Say it
I've heard it
OK OK
I see Don't worry
He said
the shellfish monster made her
find you
You shouldn't be so romantic
Do you think she had a crush on you
She wanted to eat you
He also told you to take care of yourself
Don't fall in love with some female figurine
I'm serious
Don't talk nonsense
Are you serious
Of course
I saw an iron pendant in her skull
If I guess right
that's what she wanted to tell me
You're daydreaming
The Warehouse 11 is not a place
where we can enter and get out so easily
Do you know what it is
It is the territory of Zhang Qishan
It's a century-old store
It's well guarded
It's famous in the world
but hard to see
The people inside are mysterious
There are many kinds of mechanisms
There are mountains of treasures
I know what you think
What
Are you
Are you going to take some treasures
How can you say that
Am I right
I guess
I'm right
Be honest
Tell me how to get there
How to get there
You must have a plan
I I
Tell me tell me
Tell me
Wait I should think about it
Think about it
Tell me now
Tell me
OK OK
This is my plan
First we try to contact the Warehouse 11
and tell them to take the goods
When they're coming to take the goods
I have a way to follow them
and enter the Warehouse 11
How
You'll find it out in Wuzhou
Give me your ticket
Here you are
I don't want to drink
I want to see this
I've studied the tour routes on Ctrip
Let me tell you
There are many kinds
of food and games in Wuzhou
We can go anywhere with Ctrip
What did you say
Doctor
Where is it
This one
Hello
I'm Mr. Black's friend
He said that you can find him or treat a disease
Yes
I'm on my way to Wuzhou
Are you looking for him or treating a disease
Is he in Wuzhou
Treating a disease
Hello
you're so busy
You're busy too
Excuse me
Let's go
Your disease is a little complicated
I can't explain that clearly by text message
Please call me
I can call him with my phone
Hello Doctor Xie
I'm Chuchu's brother
Hello
Let me tell you something about her
Her disease
is congenital
Yes
She can hear
but she can't speak
We've been to a lot of big hospitals
I've learned a little about the operation
Yes
Yes yes
OK
Thank you so much
Thank you Thank you
OK OK
OK thank you
How about it
Let's go back first
Sister I think
this doctor
sounds very young
I don't trust him
Hey bro
can you turn it down They are sleeping
You are handsome
but your behavior is not that good
I'm sorry
Um
I mean
he sounds really young
He said he would come to pick us up
I'm afraid he'll blackmail us
He won't
Listen to me We should be careful
There are many frauds
Think about it
Come on The train is coming
It's here
Let's go It's in front
Wait for me
This way This way
He said he would come to pick us up
He didn't give us his license plate number
Why don't you give him a call
and ask him
Hello
Get in the car please
Are you the doctor
I'm not the doctor
I'm here to pick you up
You're Chuchu
You're her brother
That's right
Get in the car please
I've seen this kind of car
I've
I've never been in this kind of car
But I've seen it a couple of times
It's very expensive
It's really very expensive
Well please load our luggage
Come on Get in the car
It's expensive right
Is it over 600,000 yuan
800,000 yuan
The fee this doctor might charge seems expensive
How about we get out of the car
No
Even if I have to sell my kidney
I'll find a doctor to cure you
Don't talk about it anymore
We can go now
I'm waiting for another person
Why do we
have to carpool to see the doctor
Are we going to share the bed
with others in the hospital
The doctor has just arrived in Wuzhou
We'll go together
He is quite efficient
I wonder if she'll have an operation
as soon as we reach the hospital
It's so fast
I haven't got the money
Please wait for me
I have to draw out some money
Never mind
Mr. Black has paid all
What did I say
I told you he was a good man
You are too stubborn
Tell me
why did you break up with him
I can help convey your apology to him
He didn't accept me at all
Old men like to say that
But actually
he knows
he's not worthy of you
It's true He must think so
Hello
You are Doctor Xie
Let's go
We're on the beltway
Check if there's a car following us
before and after three kilometers
Doctor Xie I'm sorry
I shouldn't have said that on the train
That's what I am
I'll feel bad
if my sister is in a bad mood
So my words were a little blunt
Please forgive me
Don't worry
Patients should have a good rest
Look
Doctor Xie is so magnanimous
Doctor Xie
I want to know
which hospital you're working for
Are we going to Fuyang now
I have a private clinic
The equipment is better
You can have a test there
OK
Sorry I wonder
if Mr. Black has booked
a hotel for us
Or should we
book a hotel
No
It’s all taken care of
Mr. Black is our VIP
His guest is my guest
By the way
how did you know Mr. Black
We're more than
friends
As you can see
Mr. Black has done many things for my sister
But he hasn't admitted it
so we can't tell others
right
Look at my sister
I see
It's rare
OK I'll sleep
My brother is such a man
Don't take it to heart
We are just friends
[My brother is such a man Don't take it to heart
We are just friends]
We're really friends
You're right
Someone is following us
By the way
you'll pay for that right
If I cure Wu Xie and her for free
I'll get poor
It’s been an established convention
If you accept one then there'll be more
They are my friends
Please protect them
Do you think she will be cured
When do you start to care about others
Mr. Black
come and look at this
I gotta go
He's afraid to tell me
Really weird
From the South Sea King's Tomb
to the Mute Village
we almost lost
our lives again
The relevant agencies will explore
and restore the South Sea King's Tomb
The local government has also taken over
the underground river site of the Mute Village
Uncle Erbai has been invited
to participate in investigating the site
He took account of my physical condition
and let me come back first
Now my illness is getting worse and worse
But there are too many mysteries
about the disappearance of Uncle Sanxing
I'm eager to know about it
I'll find the truth in my own way
Tell me
You know you may die
for getting the figurine in the Warehouse 11
And you ask me to be with you
What do you mean
The jar
is full of wine
You want to put me into the wine
and make it tribute
What's your intention Naive
What are you talking about
What am I talking about
What are you thinking about
Am I that stupid
Am I that ungrateful
How can I put my brother into the wine
and make it tribute
What do you mean
It's
Come here
No
Come here and help me
Help you with what
Hurry up
There is a mechanism
Of course
Let me take a look
Fatty
do you know what it was
used for in ancient times
What
Big jar
In ancient times
what were you used for
Were you a monk's urn
Fatty
this is used for hiding in ancient times
When rich families in Shanxi met bandits
they would use this to hide
Naive you're a bandit
Fatty
let me tell you the plan
You will stay inside
and close it
Then I will fill it with wine
Then we'll get into the Warehouse 11
and they won't know that
I know
You want me to drink the wine
instead of steeping me in the wine
OK
That's our plan
How can you think of it
Hello Uncle Erjing
Wu Xie
I'm calling
because I've got an ancestral treasure
It's a large jar
It's in Wushanju
I don't know how to deal with it
Can you
help me
to contact the Warehouse 11
I want to deposit it there
Got it
Before seven o'clock tomorrow morning
put the jar in Mr. Second's house
I'll deal with it
OK thank you
Fatty
I'm here
You're in
Help me
Fatty
Come on Smash it to save me
But I'm not Sima Guang
who samshed a jar to save his friend
Come on
OK I'll smash it
Smash
Fatty hold on there a littler longer
I'll do it right away
Help help
I'm smashing the jar
I smash you
You want to cheat me
You're not stupid
I'm stupid
I can't be more stupid
than you
Tou
Let me introduce to you
This is Tou
She'll give you a test
to check if you can be treated
I have something else to do
It's up to you
Doctor Xie
let me see you off
Why don't we go to a regular hospital
Come in
Don't worry
She is a postdoctoral student in medicine
It has a valid business license here
It is registered
It's done
Vocal cords are fairly intact
Shall we have a try
OK
[OK]
I have original medical records
Would you like to take a look
I have read it
In ancient times
there was a technique
to change the thickness and angle of vocal cords
by using a gold needle
It was often used for disguise
Your vocal cords never fully developed
It's impossible to cure them
I'll insert a thin gold needle
into your throat
to place a two-prong alloy reed
to replace your vocal cords