♪The original dream stays buried♪
♪Through the wind and the rain♪
♪It waits for the sunshine♪
♪To slowly revive♪
♪I want to travel through the skyscrapers♪
♪Even if the trip may be bumpy♪
♪Sooner or later the mist will clear♪
♪I'll realize my dream without hesitation♪
♪Through the crowd, it's hard to see♪
♪As cramped as the stars♪
♪Yearning for each other's sky♪
♪Forget we used to sparkle too♪
♪I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not hesitating at all♪
♪I'll seize the future, suspecting nothing♪
♪Because I'm dauntless♪
♪So, I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not giving up♪
♪I will always believe in miracles♪
♪Even if I have to look for them endlessly♪
=As Beautiful As You=
=Episode 23=
(Su Zhizhou)
Xing, where are you?
Why haven't you come to work yet?
Hello.
(Ji Xing)
I...
I'll be right there.
(Tu Xiaomeng)
Xing, where are you?
Xing, take some good rest at your friend's.
Go to bed early.
OK. Say it, please.
What?
I know.
Go on.
OK. I get it.
Miss Ji?
I'm in a hurry.
I know.
OK. I get it.
Boss.
Miss Ji opened the door for me.
She has left
in such a hurry.
Looks like she has some emergency.
Here's this month's sales report
of Dongyang Medical's products you asked for.
The price of old products
can go down by 5%.
Clear out our inventory quickly.
For the next batch of new products,
bring the price up by 10%.
If the price goes up,
will...?
With excellent quality,
some people will buy it.
I get it.
(Xing)
(Xingchen Technology)
Remember
to have this file delivered.
OK.
Miss Ji.
- Morning.
- Xing.
Morning.
Be honest.
Where were you last night?
Coming to work with an unchanged outfit?
I...
I was at a friend's.
Friend? Which friend?
Do I know this friend?
Is it a man or a woman?
In Xinggang, you even have
a closer friend than Xiaomeng and me?
I'll be jealous.
Last night, I was with Han Ting.
This is good.
Why are you shy?
When will you have Mr. Han
invite us to dinner?
What relationship do you think
he and I are in?
Love relationship.
But he hasn't said he loves me.
You think you're still in college?
Does he have to play the guitar downstairs,
put a ring of heart-shaped candles,
and yell "I love you"?
I could tell he had feelings
for you a long time ago.
I didn't know he could hold it until now.
What's wrong?
What are you worried about?
I still think it happened too fast.
Don't rush, then.
Take your time.
Business isn't busy lately.
Go on a vacation and think about it.
Before that,
you have to sign this contract.
I should go.
Mr. Han.
Are you here for Xing? She has just left.
Left?
Where has she gone?
For some business,
she went back to her hometown
on annual leave.
If you want something, tell me.
I'll get the message to her.
No need.
I'll talk to her when she's back.
Goodbye, Mr. Han.
Let me guess.
Mr. Han, you want me at this moment
for emotional issues, huh?
Don't you think
it's really hard to guess
what some girl thinks?
Some girl? You just mean Ji Xing.
After I left last night,
what happened between you?
She's avoiding me.
Worse still,
she went back to her hometown on annual leave.
Mr. Han, she isn't avoiding you.
She's just being shy.
When a pure girl like Ji Xing
had intimacy with you,
she'd be shy.
You should give her some space.
Try to get her slowly but surely.
So, when I watch romantic dramas,
I can really learn something.
Kitties,
eat slowly.
Be patient.
(Han Ting)
Bon voyage.
You freaked me out.
Aren't you supposed to arrive tonight?
I want to give you a surprise.
What? You're on annual leave?
Such a good job.
(Han Ting: Bon voyage.)
Xing, stop checking your phone.
Come have lunch.
Hurry. Come have lunch.
Xing, work is always endless.
Be right there.
Don't let your father down.
He was cooking for a few hours
without leaving the kitchen.
My favorite beef balls.
The steamed fish head with chopped chili.
Such a big dish. Great.
Shall I drink with you, Dad?
- Come on.
- You will, of course.
♪Time passes so quickly♪
♪Go slowly and do not hurry♪
♪In the distance, the sky is warm♪
♪As bright as the day we first met♪
♪Sweet moments soak in fragrance♪
♪And grow freely over the noise♪
♪Looked back, only the unchanged happiness♪
♪Deserves to be valued and remembered♪
♪Time passes so quickly♪
♪Go slowly and do not hurry♪
♪Looked back, only the unchanged happiness♪
♪Deserves to be valued and remembered♪
Thank you so much.
Why are you sitting here?
Go get my prize here.
Come on. Be seated, Miss Xiaomeng.
Since you taught me to sing,
I think I've been improving quite a lot.
- Really?
- I get the right key
almost every time.
I only fail once.
Really?
You should keep practicing, Ms. Han.
It's your prize from the singing competition?
Yeah. Come on, Miss Xiaomeng.
Have some water.
Oh, look. I have this, too.
An honor certificate. Look, son.
(Honor)
Award of Touching Everyone.
See?
Besides the certificate
and the sparkling water,
nothing else?
What do you mean?
If you don't like it, don't drink it.
Miss Xiaomeng, seriously.
I have to thank you so much.
You've taught me so well.
Or how could I possibly
win this award?
You flatter me.
If someone can marry you...
He'll be really lucky.
Ms. Han,
you're making me shy.
Don't be shy.
This is the truth.
It's getting late.
I should go home, Ms. Han.
It's late, indeed.
It's not safe for you to go alone.
- Linjia...
- I'll drive you.
OK.
No need. It's OK.
Don't bother. It's done.
(I still think it happened too fast.)
(Don't rush, then. Take your time.)
(When a pure girl like Ji Xing)
had intimacy with you,
she'd be shy.
You should give her some space.
(Try to get her slowly but surely.)
What are you doing?
You're laughing so much.
Not as much as you.
I'm not.
Look in the mirror.
Look what a big smile
you're wearing.
I'm not.
I really didn't expect this.
My fearless son
would be flushed someday.
What are you talking about?
Son, I'm serious.
I support you.
I want you to enjoy a relationship
and get married early.
Family before job.
Yes. I get it.
(Bartender: Your mother went viral.)
Let me show you.
(Many customers came for her.)
Look at the photos.
(She sings beautifully. Confident lady.
She's so charming.)
Son, look at my photos.
Whose message are you reading?
You're lost in it.
Xiaomeng's?
Mom.
What happened to Xiaomeng?
You went viral.
I went viral? Come on.
What do you mean?
How did I go viral?
Come check out this video.
You went rival.
What video?
What?
Look.
All the comments
are praising your mother for her singing.
Mom, you've really gone viral.
My bar gets popular, too.
Really?
Today, my bartender told me.
Really a lot of people came today
because they watched the video
and they came for you.
Really?
Son,
I really didn't know
I could help you like this.
Now, I'm an Internet celebrity.
So...
I've made a decision.
What decision?
I'll buy into your bar.
I'll invest in it.
You will?
Yes, of course.
Thank you, Mom.
In this case,
you will be
my second largest shareholder.
I'll work hard to make money
for your dividends.
No. I want more than that.
Since I buy into your bar
as the second largest shareholder,
I'll regularly
visit your bar and sing
to attract more people
and increase popularity.
Are you happy about it?
Yes.
Stop it. Stop.
I need to learn more songs.
I... I'll go practicing singing.
I need new songs.
I can't always sing Jasmine.
What shall I sing?
No, this isn't inappropriate.
How about...?
(Honor, Award of Touching Everyone)
(Bon voyage.)
(Dongyang Group)
Boss, Miss Ji is back.
She's gone to the Innovation Center
to check on Zhang Fengmei.
Xingchen's strategy plan...
Is it not finished yet?
I'll rush it
and have Miss Ji report it soon.
(Xinggang Hospital)
Why are you out of bed?
- Miss Ji, Dr. Shao.
- Sit down. Hurry.
I told you many times.
You must rest and not move too much.
You have to listen to the doctor
so that you can recover soon.
I'm just out of bed
to have a stretch.
I'm tired of lying. Thanks.
This is my husband.
Xu, this is Miss Ji I often told you about.
This is Dr. Shao.
Hi, Miss Ji and Dr. Shao.
Don't worry. The surgery was successful.
Her recovery is good, too.
She'll be observed for a while.
When everything is OK,
she can check out in a few days.
Well, Mr. Xu,
take good care of your wife.
Don't worry. She'll do what you say.
I have something to ask you.
I have a leg problem.
In her case,
how soon can she start to do farm work?
(Xingchen Technology)
(Sales Cycle, Pricing Strategy)
Production and Sales.
This strategy plan is great.
Xing, I think you can show it to Mr. Han
and brief him directly.
No.
You'll do that.
Xing, don't be kidding.
I said,
unless you're gravely ill,
I won't brief Mr. Han again!
(Invitation)
Look what this is.
Forum of Leading Entrepreneurs
in Manufacturing and Medical Industry.
Good for you, Xing.
This conference has big barriers.
When you're invited,
it means Xingchen has made its presence
in this industry.
So, if we can show out
at this forum,
we'll advertise Xingchen, right?
It's such an important opportunity.
Shouldn't I prepare for it?
You should.
Zhizhou, how about this?
If you don't want to brief Mr. Han,
you can go give a speech.
Don't...
Xing,
we can never have both.
You go give a speech
and I'll go brief Mr. Han.
Not scared anymore?
No. I'll go.
It's a deal. I'm on it.
Boss, someone from Xingchen is here.
It's Su Zhizhou.
Come in.
Mr. Han,
this is Xingchen's latest
strategy plan.
(Strategy Plan)
Please review it.
Take your seat.
(VI Market Opportunity)
What is Miss Ji up to lately?
She's preparing for the speech.
Speech?
Yes.
Lately, our product
has developed very well.
Word gets out in the industry.
For this year's Forum of Leading Entrepreneurs
in Manufacturing and Medical Industry,
Xingchen is invited.
Xing will give a speech on behalf of us.
She wrote this?
Yes.
It mainly includes
her ideas and concepts.
Well, Mr. Han,
is there anything
we need to modify?
No. This plan is clear.
From product research to market positioning,
everything is well planned.
Thanks for your recognition.
Xingchen has real strength.
Miss Ji deserves to be invited.
Off you go.
OK.
Goodbye, Mr. Han.
Get Tang Song in.
OK.
Boss.
I was invited to the Forum
of Leading Entrepreneurs
in Manufacturing and Medical Industry, huh?
Yes. I rejected it for you.
But the organizer
is still trying to persuade you.
I'll tell them you can go.
(Yushan Bypass No.3)
Every other day,
there are all kinds of conferences
and forums.
It's the same in every circle.
A few people do things
while a lot of people speak.
I'm not talking about myself.
I've done a lot of things.
(Speech Elements)
Of course...
(I A Humorous Start)
I've talked a lot, too.
(Prospect of the Medical Industry)
The prospect of the industry
has been the biggest concern
of the practitioners.
I can't predict the future.
But I want to briefly talk with you
(II Industry Knowledge)
about the future trend
of the medical industry.
(III Personal Experience)
Small and medium-sized enterprises
shouldn't wish
to conquer the world in the first place.
They should learn to open up new routes
by wind directions and currents.
Start from small businesses.
(II Xingchen's Feature)
Wait a minute.
Let me introduce her.
♪Everything you wanted me to be♪
♪I tried to let you be my destiny♪
♪The stars are shining thru the day and night♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪Hold my hand across the land and sea♪
♪Call my name from distance guiding me♪
♪We are the ones that God keeps blessing♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪You are everything♪
♪Everything you wanted me to be♪
The kind of soil decides
what flowers will grow.
The macro environment is
the foundation of industrial development
and the soil for the growth of companies.
It includes a series
of external factors that influence
industrial development.
We can start from politics, society...
♪Call my name from distance guiding me♪
♪We are the ones that God keeps blessing♪
♪Restlessly♪
♪You are everything♪
(Forum of Leading Entrepreneurs
in Manufacturing and Medical Industry)
- Hi, Mr. Wang.
- Hi, there.
- Ms. Liu.
- Long time no see.
Look. This industry
has been developing well.
That's right.
(Han Ting)
Why are you here?
Why can I not be here?
You're avoiding me?
No.
Then why did you send Su Zhizhou?
I would give a speech.
I was preparing the script.
Let me see.
(Someone like me
has brought Xingchen all here.)
Good speech.
Really?
The style looks familiar, though.
It's like something
I may say.
It's about to begin. I should go.
Remember.
When you give a speech,
you should speak not only properly,
but also sincerely.
Speak with your heart.
I should go.
Are you available after the speech?
What for?
There's a dinner.
For men in this circle.
Go with me.
(Yellow Box Art Museum)
Next, Ji Xing,
general manager of Xingchen Technology.
Actually, I am
a terrible entrepreneur.
When I first started my company, I had nothing.
I tried to get financing with one mere idea.
I guess I misunderstood
the definition of "angel investor".
I thought all investors were angles.
I'm not embarrassed to say this.
I wanted to get 1.5 million
when offering 20% of the stock.
Once I met a fraud.
After he talked with me,
he said to me,
"Miss, I thought I was good at fooling.
Unexpectedly, you can even do better.
You do much better than me."
Before, I was ignorant of many things.
But I've been studying.
In this world, many people
won't take action
before everything is ready.
(Forum of Leading Entrepreneurs)
But some people like me start first.
(Manufacturing and Medical Industry)
During the process,
we mend and learn.
I think someone like me
isn't that bad.
Someone like me
has brought Xingchen all here.
Our staple
has been in the clinical experiment.
Some other skeleton products
are being developed, too.
Some days ago,
the clinical test
of our intervertebral cage
received an unplanned volunteer.
She had a serious lumbar spine problem.
After having the surgery,
she's recovering very well.
This volunteer
has poor family conditions.
A clinical test
is her only way
to get an advanced medical treatment.
We have limited clinical tests.
But there are
many more patients like her.
So, Xingchen
is dedicated to producing
more personalized and customized
implantable medical devices
with a lower cost
and a lower price
to help more people
so that they can be treated
and then live a better life.
This is what Xingchen expects
and what we will do.
I'm Ji Xing.
Ji Xing from Xingchen Technology.
How will Xingchen Technology develop?
Please wait and see.
Thanks for listening.
She's good.
Smart.
Indeed. She's intelligent.
She advertises her company with herself.
Young guys are awesome.
What do you think of your speech?
I feel good.
What do you think it is?
Excellent.
Oh.
After checking our strategy plan,
do you have any advice?
Didn't Su Zhizhou tell you?
He did.
I just want to confirm.
Then report to me personally next time.
The positioning is set.
Next, you should focus on the human problem.
It's the end of the year.
Bonus, promotion,
and other money-related problems
should be aboveboard.
Focus more on that.
I'll take care of that.
There you are, Mr. Han.
- Mr. Han.
- Hi, Mr. Han.
- Sit, please.
- Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Be seated.
Mr. Han,
the dishes are getting cold.
Mr. Han, tonight,
let's have a good drink.
I have something else to do.
Drinking tea instead,
I'd like to propose a toast.
Come on. Cheers.
Since Mr. Han is here,
let's start to eat and talk.
Mr. Han, I heard Dongyang Medical
had a new contract with Xinggang Hospital
for two years' procurement
and the price went down by 5%.
Tell us more about it.
Is it exclusive to this contract?
Or is it the same price
for every other partner?
It's the same.
The price of all old products goes down.
Even Dongyang Medical has to stay competitive
by reducing the price.
Looks like small companies like us
will have no choice.
In the last five years,
we've never reduced the price.
Now, the process is better
and the cost is lower.
The reduced price of old products
will be a reward for our partners.
Besides,
the market share is equal,
even if it's very little.
Previously, my company didn't want it.
But I want more shares.
So, I'd like to learn from you
about how to reduce the price.
Being fussy about it will hurt our harmony.
Instead of having a lose-lose game,
why don't we have a win-win cooperation?
You have big-picture thinking,
Mr. Han and Mr. Chang.
Come on. A toast to the two of you.
Cheers, Mr. Han.
Cheers.
Hello, everyone. I'm Xia Lu.
I'm honored to attend this forum
and get some guidance from you.
I'll drink it up first.
Xia Lu is from Gangxing Technology.
A company I invested in.
Please help her as much as you can.
Xia Lu.
These are big shots of our industry.
Proposal a toast to them one after another.
Have a good drink with them.
Then they can help you, huh?
OK. A toast to you, Mr. Han.
I'd appreciate your help.
Thanks.
You must be Miss Ji
from Xingchen Technology.
I'm Ji Xing.
Do you not drink, either?
Come on.
Come on, Miss Ji.
I don't usually drink spirit.
There's red wine. Here.
Here, Miss Ji.
I'll drink it up.
In this case,
I'd like to propose a toast.
- Cheers.
Miss Ji, you can't drink with all of us
with only one glass of wine.
We're OK with it.
But Mr. Chang is a big shot.
Show some respect and drink with him alone.
♪Once again, you stand opposite me♪
♪Telling the worlds I'm not familiar with♪
♪They seem remote, but get in between us♪
♪We test each other
to see who'll first cross the line♪
♪If I can get closer to you♪
♪Can we have our memories overlapped?♪
♪Time puts walls up to keep my loneliness safe♪
♪Hope understanding will not endanger us♪
♪We each take a side♪
♪The chess board is set,
leaving us with a dilemma♪
♪We always expect each other to relent first♪
♪Before we're relieved♪
♪Pretend love isn't about winning♪
♪We each keep a half♪
♪Completing ourselves before revealing♪
♪Instead of expectations♪
♪We need each other's answer to judge♪
♪When love is a game of exchange♪
♪It is truly terrible♪