♪The original dream stays buried♪
♪Through the wind and the rain♪
♪It waits for the sunshine♪
♪To slowly revive♪
♪I want to travel through the skyscrapers♪
♪Even if the trip may be bumpy♪
♪Sooner or later the mist will clear♪
♪I'll realize my dream without hesitation♪
♪Through the crowd, it's hard to see♪
♪As cramped as the stars♪
♪Yearning for each other's sky♪
♪Forget we used to sparkle too♪
♪I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not hesitating at all♪
♪I'll seize the future, suspecting nothing♪
♪Because I'm dauntless♪
♪So, I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not giving up♪
♪I will always believe in miracles♪
♪Even if I have to look for them endlessly♪
=As Beautiful As You=
=Episode 15=
- Cheers.
To Xingchen's new office.
Thanks.
Indeed, fried chicken
and beer pair well together.
After having too many light meals,
I still think fried food
makes me happiest.
My pretty bosses,
hope you don't mind this humble gift.
We don't.
Since I started a company,
we haven't had dinner together
for a long time.
Yeah.
Luckily,
your efforts aren't wasted.
The two of you
have your own offices now.
I'd like to thank the lady
who always has my back
and the lady who works hard with me.
Because you've convinced me
Xingchen will be a great stage.
When the product is done,
I won't make you regret
hiring me.
She's a top salesgirl.
I've been feeling lucky, you know?
Now, with a new start,
our future will be more smooth.
Come on. To our new start.
Cheers.
So cold.
(Dongyang Group)
(Xingchen Technology)
Hi, interviewers.
My name is Xu Youyou.
I'm Zhang Jie.
Hi, I'm Feng Yu.
I'm Chen Zuo.
Hello, I'm Jiang Jingxuan.
Jiangyang Technology and Business University.
I majored in business administration
with a bachelor's degree.
Xinggang University of Engineering Science.
I have a master's degree.
Jingxi University Of Technology.
Xinggang University of Engineering Science.
I majored in product engineering.
I graduated from Computer Science
of Xinggang University
with a bachelor's degree.
We're from the same school.
What are your salary requirements?
As a new graduate,
I have no requirements.
I hope
my salary is about 50,000.
I want that, too. Next.
Why did you leave your last company?
I resigned.
My last company is too small.
The environment is so poor.
It's old in winter and hot in summer.
A rather terrible workplace.
You've got a good office.
- Next.
What is your dream?
Dream?
I don't have a dream.
I want to be admitted
to a top Fortune 500 company.
I want the products I design
to be patentable.
I just want to do something I like.
Write programs or codes, for example.
I can do it all day.
Li,
from today's interviews,
I realize you are really awesome.
You're as good
as professional HR roles.
You had a long day. Have some water.
Let's just see the next interviewee.
Next.
Hello, I'm Huang Weiwei.
You used to be Miss Ji's colleague, huh?
Miss Ji told us
that you would come.
You're an acquaintance,
but we have to keep it professional.
I want to ask you some questions.
You don't mind, do you?
No, I don't.
I don't want to take advantage of Xing.
Feel free to ask.
(Work Experience)
You're experienced.
You've also worked
in this field for many years.
You're exactly what we want.
However...
Xingchen can't be as good
as a big company like Guanghua.
We can't tolerate too many mistakes.
When I worked in Guanghua,
I did make some mistakes.
But since Ji Xing left,
they've set me up for more mistakes.
I've grown a lot, too.
In the future,
I'll do my best
and take my work
more seriously.
If you join Xingchen,
can you guarantee
you won't make the same mistakes?
Yes.
I can have a probation period
like anybody else.
You can see how I work
before you decide if you'll keep me.
Well, you'll have a three-month probation.
Hope you'll do a good job.
Thank you.
I really want to join you.
If we can work together,
we will not let you down.
Every one of us
does the business together.
The welfare and bonuses
will be offered.
OK. Next.
Check it very carefully.
What's going on, Huang Weiwei?
It's not time to knock off yet.
You're here just in time.
(Letter of Resignation)
Come on, you...
Are you having any trouble at work?
Or is there a misunderstanding
between the colleagues?
Don't rush to pack your things.
Come on. Let's talk in my office.
No need, Director Chen.
I've made up my mind.
Guanghua can't give me what I want.
Tell me the real reason.
In my letter of resignation,
I've explained everything.
Since Ji Xing left,
I've been the scapegoat of our team.
You and Lin Zhen took turns
to do mean things to me.
What are you talking about?
What's the point of working here?
I would rather join Ji Xing
for a business.
Huang Weiwei,
you'd better think carefully.
Xingchen is a startup company.
Nobody knows how it'll end up.
So what?
Xingchen and Guanghua
are both invested by Mr. Han.
When I join them,
I'll be a founding member.
Sadly,
you offended Ji Xing too much.
You won't have a chance.
What are you looking at?
Focus on your work!
A snobbish employee like her
won't stay long in any company!
Everybody,
after nearly six months,
our company has completed
its preliminary HR reform.
This is Dr. Jiang Huai,
director of the AI Department.
You know him.
These days,
he led the team of Doctorcloud
to have quickly completed
the upgrades
(Dongyang Medical)
and cooperated
with many hospitals.
This is Luo Ping,
new director of the Product Department.
The former director
was assigned
to Dongyang Base in Germany.
From this day on,
our product lines
will be in the charge of Director Luo.
Nice to meet you, everybody.
The combination of software and hardware
is the strategy we've been sticking to.
I hope Dr. Jiang
will work with Director Luo
to fully achieve business upgrades.
Besides,
I have another thing to announce.
Zhang Xinhua, the former director
of the Sales Department
resigned for some personal reasons.
Wang Chong,
the former deputy director,
will be the new director.
You're experienced professionals.
I want you to do your own part.
If you need any help in business,
I'll give you as much as I can.
I, Han Ting,
only focus on the result.
What are you doing here?
What's up?
Isn't Ji Xing going too far?
When she just moved in here,
she poached my employee.
Some days ago,
I even gave her a bouquet.
Dongyang Medical encourages
free movement of employees.
Isn't it normal
that an employee gets another job?
It's the crucial period
for Bay Phase II.
When she has my employee,
things are hard for me.
When a mere engineer is gone,
things are hard already?
She poached
a core member.
With a slower progress,
it's Dongyang Medical
that will finally be affected.
But if Dr. Jiang Huai
can serve as our consultant soon,
the effect won't be too terrible, I think.
Don't worry.
I remember what I promised you.
Dr. Jiang Huai's team
will be in Guanghua in a day or two.
Really? That'd be great.
- I just...
- Ms. Yuan.
There you are, Ms. Yuan.
You guys talk.
I should go.
What's up, Yuan? Come and sit.
Don't play dumb.
You know what I'm here for.
Dongyang Medical is a big company.
Personnel changes are normal.
If you defend those old employees
who made some mistakes,
isn't it unnecessary?
Han Ting,
either as the vice president
or as your family,
I need to remind you something.
If you want to reform,
don't be too radical.
Take action slowly.
Haste makes waste.
You rushed
to replace those core directors
with your own men.
Anyone with a discerning eye can see
what you really want.
What I want
is to race against time.
After all, in front of the directors,
I made a pledge.
Time is pressing.
I can't do anything slowly.
Am I right?
You have a good reason.
But don't forget.
Those old employees who you fired
worked for Dongyang Medical
for a lot of years.
When they're gone,
a lot of things have to start from scratch.
Thank you for reminding me.
Now, I know
Dongyang Medical
hasn't developed all these years
depending on the healthy operation
of the company itself,
but on those old employees.
In this case,
we can't keep them.
You're terribly set on it.
Will Grandpa approve?
Grandpa only values the result.
I'll prove it with my accomplishments.
I have things to do.
Do yourself a favor and leave.
OK. I'll wait and see.
No problem. I won't let you down.
(Ji Xing)
Mr. Han, at four this afternoon,
Xingchen will hold
its first official meeting of the year.
Do you have time to attend it?
It depends.
(Han Ting)
Li, be seated.
Thanks.
Hi, Mr. Su.
- Miss Ji.
Miss Ji, everybody is here.
OK. Let's get started.
This has...
This is...
So handsome.
This has been the first meeting
we've had since we moved
to Dongyang Building.
We're going to discuss
Xingchen's future strategy
and detailed work arrangements.
Any ideas?
Miss Ji, the parameters
of our analog intervertebral cage
have been perfect.
So, I wonder if we should
expand into new directions.
I have some ideas.
(Surgical)
♪I'm going to the land of dream♪
(Surgical guide, Rehabilitation equipment)
♪I'll seize the future, suspecting nothing♪
♪Because I'm dauntless♪
(Osteoarthritis, Musculoskeletal diseases)
(Unknown market)
♪I will always believe in miracles♪
♪Even if I have to look for them endlessly♪
(Preoperative planning, Implant, 3D)
(Surgical guide, Rehabilitation equipment)
(Surgical guide)
(Cage: Lumbar, Cervical vertebra, Tooth)
(Material, Rejection of Titanium)
♪It's always you♪
Some chemical materials
inhibit the interaction between bone tissues
and the implants.
I think we should try to find
some new materials.
If we can find a more suitable material,
I believe
it will be
a significant advantage of ours.
You have very good ideas.
Hope you will always
remain sensitive like this
and communicate more with each other.
Yingying,
email me minutes of the meeting soon.
OK, Miss Ji. No problem.
Mr. Su,
the printer will arrive in a day or two.
Make the proposal of product experiment soon.
- OK.
- Li.
List the raw material suppliers
and get their offers.
We'll purchase some.
OK.
Hope we can be
comrades-in-arms at work
who completely trust each other.
In daily life,
hope we can communicate
like friends.
Let's work hard together
for our future.
OK. So much for the meeting. Dismissed.
Weiwei,
who is that man?
Our investor,
Mr. Han Ting,
CEO of Dongyang Medical.
Seriously?
The big boss came personally
for our meeting.
He thinks so highly of us.
Miss Ji,
don't you invite me to your office?
This way, please.
Come in, Mr. Han.
Mr. Han, you've never attended
a meeting of a startup company, huh?
Just the opposite. I've witnessed a lot.
Then do you have any advice
for our meeting?
Sell dreams, build dreams,
and paint a rosy picture
with sympathy and dream
to drive its employees to work hard.
Most startup companies
are doing this.
I didn't paint a rosy picture.
We're different from those companies
that sell dreams and emotions.
What's the difference?
We have real dreams.
And for my employees,
I really hope
they can get along like friends.
My company will
offer them
a free and open
work environment and platform.
They can develop
and grow together.
Even if one day,
someone leaves my company,
I still want Xingchen
to be where they have improved.
Don't stare at me like this.
We're indeed different.
In the future,
we will achieve something great.
You really have
way too much confidence.
In Qingtian Fishing Village, who reminded me
to always remember my dream
and original purpose?
Yes. It's a good thing to have a dream.
But realizing the dream
is another thing.
To start and manage a company,
you need to be practical
instead of convincing your employees
with mere sympathy.
Whoever joins a startup company
has no shortage of dreams.
As the boss,
you should get them down to earth.
Make them work steadily
works better than chanting.
When the experiment proposal is done,
report it to me.
Thank you, Mr. Han, for your support.
Otherwise,
Hanhai wouldn't have gone this far.
I owe you this
and I'll always keep it in mind.
I just did what an investor
should do.
Hanhai has gone this far
because you're capable, Mr. Chen.
But Mr. Han,
is Luo Ping reliable?
After all, he just joined Dongyang Medical.
If he knows
you're the investor of Hanhai,
will he...?
Don't worry about this.
Before we employed Luo Ping,
I had fully investigated him.
I'll be relieved, then.
Mr. Han.
Let me introduce you.
This is Mr. Chen Ningyang,
CEO of Hanhai Technology.
This is Luo Ping,
product director of Dongyang Medical.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Chen.
I've heard a lot about you, Mr. Luo.
Take your seat.
After you.
I'll get straight to the point.
Next, Dongyang Medical
will strengthen its main product line.
We need technical support from Hanhai.
You two can communicate more.
However,
keep it very secret.
- Got it.
To be honest, Mr. Han,
you kept saying
we would combine software and hardware
and start 3D medical printing.
I used to think
we would cooperate with Xingchen Technology.
I worried that we had to wait for too long.
Unexpectedly, we can work with Hanhai,
such a big company.
Now, my confidence is rising.
You flatter us, Mr. Luo.
Hanhai just started a few years
earlier than Xingchen.
Mr. Han invested in Xingchen
and this company must have
something remarkable.
Based on Dongyang Medical's resources,
Xingchen will soon develop.
By then, they'll work with us
to support Dongyang Medical.
That's right.
I trust Mr. Han's taste.
I believe in Miss Ji's capability, too.
Cheers.
What?
In a bad mood?
No.
Why would I be in a bad mood for your date?
What would you like to drink?
Whiskey, please.
OK.
What do you want me for?
Must I ask you out for something?
Why do you suddenly give me a gift?
I heard
your parents have gone abroad on a vacation
with your grandfather.
If I knew you would
spend the festival alone in Xinggang,
I wouldn't have gone to another city.
I'd have stayed here to keep you company.
It's a belated New Year's gift.
It looks good on you.
Be straightforward.
What do you want from me?
I heard Han Ting invested in a new company.
Before they achieve anything,
they've moved to Dongyang Building.
What's that girl's name?
Ji Xing?
You've really been focusing
on whatever Han Ting does.
I don't focus on Han Ting.
I focus on you.
Now, Xingchen is above your company.
They're obviously competing.
Guanghua and Xingchen
do different businesses.
What do you mean, "competing"?
Competing isn't only about business,
but also about love.
Anyway, she used to be your employee.
Now, Han Ting has invested in her.
Your companies are so close.
When she keeps wandering around,
you'll certainly get upset.
She's just a former employee.
I won't bother.
And you stop worrying about me.
Recently, Han Ting
has been reforming Dongyang Medical
with plenty of changes.
It puts such strains on your company, huh?
That's why I need you and Guanghua.
Mr. Chang, I can't accept it for doing nothing.
I...
Di,
timing is important
for business and love.
I'm patient enough to wait.
Happy Chinese New Year.
(Dongyang Group)
There it is, at last.
♪The original dream stays buried♪
(Project: Intervertebral Cage)
(Gap between the scraper and the platform)
♪To slowly revive♪
♪I want to travel through the skyscrapers♪
♪Even if the trip may be bumpy♪
(Heating temperature
of the PEEK material: 350-440)
♪I'll realize my dream without hesitation♪
♪Through the crowd, it's hard to see♪
(Wall thickness is the thickness
of the model's outer layer)
(Scanning speed)
♪Forget we used to sparkle too♪
(Printing time)
♪I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not hesitating at all♪
♪I'll seize the future, suspecting nothing♪
♪Because I'm dauntless♪
♪So, I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not giving up♪
♪I will always believe in miracles♪
♪Even if I have to look for them endlessly♪
♪I once followed the guidance of time♪
♪It's always you♪
♪I can't help approaching you♪
♪Move forward together♪
♪As if another journey starts♪
♪The world is brand new♪
♪I spread my arms and breathe♪
♪Until the wind raises my wings♪
♪Through the crowd, it's hard to see♪
♪As cramped as the stars♪
♪Yearning for each other's sky♪
♪Forget we used to sparkle too♪
♪I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪By flying♪
♪The clearer path proves♪
(Proposal of Product Experiment)
(Dongyang Group)
(Cancellous vertebra, Bionic perforated needle)
Beidi's printer has arrived.
The commissioning is successful.
The back pages are about program designs.
It's relatively professional.
Do you need me to elaborate?
You think I can't understand?
No, no, no.
How's that possible?
I do have some confusion.
Miss Ji, please elaborate.
What confuses you?
What does this read?
Similar elastic modulus
to that of cortical bone.
Miss Ji, you like to encrypt your handwriting.
What about this?
Polylactide.
Luckily, you didn't
write your investment proposal by hand.
Or you could hardly get an investor.
How's everything going with Xingchen?
So far, so good.
The supply of raw materials,
the approval of regulatory authorities,
the permit,
and application for clinical approval...
They're being solved one after another.
Don't worry, Mr. Han.
When we burn the investor's cash,
we don't waste even a single day.
The application for intervertebral cage
has been submitted
and is waiting to be approved.
As for raw materials,
we plan to cooperate with Kebo.
They have a good cost-effectiveness,
a stable quality, and a nice reputation.
But a lot of companies buy materials from them.
Xingchen is waiting
for their delivery.
Raw materials haven't arrived.
When you have the printer alone,
isn't it like making a web out of nothing?
How can you advance the experiment?
I'll think of another way.
Do you need my help?
Will you help? I do need it.
5% of the stock.
I don't actually need your help now.
Well, I'll let you work.
I'm going to get the raw materials.
Is my handwriting really so terrible?
Ji Xing.
Oh, hi.
You're here for my nephew?
For a business talk.
So am I.
I'm here to get his investment.
Doing business with a capitalist...
Hope you'll get what you want.
- I should go.
- OK.
I will get what I want.
I have great blessings,
don't I?
Ting.
Su, you need to sign this.
OK.
Oh.
Su.
What is this?
You bought the bag?
Has Li arrived?
I didn't see her.
Close the door.
Li Li,
this is such a pretty bag.
Miss Li, a friend of mine told me
this bag had been sold out.
It's not available in Xinggang for the moment.
It's so popular?
Of course.
This brand doesn't have an online store.
Online products are all fake.
All fake? Are you sure?
Girls, how can you
distinguish the bags?
You don't know about girls.
Li Li,
did your boyfriend buy you this bag?
I'm sure he loves you pretty much.
He spent so much money on you.
You're such a happy girl.
OK. No more talking.
You get back to work.
- Morning.
You know what?
My proposal is nearly perfect.
The guest flows
will certainly rocket.
Wear glasses properly,
or take them off.
You know nothing.
You're young but so old-fashioned.
This is fashion.
By the way,
I've got the supply channels.
For wine lists and menus alone,
(Cocktail)
I designed three editions.
Every festival, big or small,
there will be special activities.
I often visit bars.
I'm very familiar.
(Proposal of Tell Mother)
Tell Mother.
What are you going to tell her?
It's the name of the bar,
you old-fashioned...
You cool guy.
You know what?
This bar will be a hit.
It has a good location
and a perfect size.
I took you there, remember?
Where Ji Xing got drunk.
The positioning isn't clear.
The mode is too average.
It's not different from other bars.
Within 200 meters of that street,
there are at least five or six bars.
Why will people visit yours?
Your proposal has no highlight.
Even if I want to advertise,
I don't know where to start.
Are we reading the same proposal?
I'll modify it. Right away.
Ji Xing is right.
You're a capitalist
who exploits working people like us.
Here, Mr. Ma.
- Taste it.
- OK.
I had this tea
brought back from Hangzhou.
OK.
Thank you for your help.
Not at all.
But I wonder
if I will offend Mr. Han.
After, he's the investor
of Xingchen.
It's not that you won't
give them the raw materials.
You'll just do it late.
Besides,
a lot of companies have placed orders.
First come, first served, right?
Oh, Mr. Ma,
my grandpa said
he would invite you to dine at our house.
If Dean Zeng needs me,
call me at any time.
OK. No problem.
I'll make an appointment with you.
OK.
Sorry,
the subscriber you dialed
cannot be connected.
Please redial later.
Mr. Ma still doesn't answer.
Han Ting is right.
Dining with them a million times
won't help.
Come on. Don't think too much.
I'll think of another way.
I'll keep contacting Mr. Ma.
In the worst case,
I'll visit him in his company.
I'm going now.
The roast meat is ready. Enjoy it.
Thanks.
Now, our progress is stuck in raw materials.
Qiuzi, I hear your institute
is very close to Kebo Material.
Mr. Ma came from your institute, too.
Tell me about him
and I'll see what I can do.
Mr. Ma?
He used to do academic work.
He's a simple man
and he's straightforward.
Oh.
He's crazy about wine, I think.
When he's available,
he often visits Dean Zeng
and drinks with him.
But you know.
New employees like us
can barely talk
to a big shot like him.
If I have a second choice,
I don't like to see him.
The point is, we don't need
a lot of raw materials
for the first batch,
but we need many types.
Only Kebo Material can offer them.
We can't even find a Plan B.
It's OK.
I'll see what I can do.
Xing...
Will she not help?
Now, there are a multitude of things to handle.
She doesn't have time.
I'll take care of this.
How's she doing lately?
She broke up with Yichen
a long time ago.
Is she still single?
She has no time for a relationship.
Someone's pursuing her, though.
Who's pursuing her?
Come on. Let's not gossip now.
That doesn't matter.
Career matters most for a woman.
You just said Mr. Ma was crazy about wine.
What's his favorite wine?
Hi, Mr. Ma.
Miss Li.
Mr. Ma is really stubborn.
I wasted several bottles of good wine.
Where's he now?
Vomiting on the toilet.
I'll think of another way.
Bye.
What happened?
You're so anxious.
We have to wait a very long time
for the raw materials.
We don't have that much time.
Just now, I visited Mr. Ma of Kebo Material.
But he would not help.
Come on. Work never ends.
Don't let my problem
upset you.
Where do you work now?
Xingchen. Xingchen Technology.
No wonder you often get off
at Dongyang Building.
So, you've joined Xingchen.
You've heard about my company?
A little bit.
- Well...
- Didn't enjoy the lunch, huh?
What would you like to eat?
You pick the food and I'll pick the canteen.
Spicy food.
The spicier, the better.
Let's go.
My bar will be profitable.
Why do I have to make a proposal?
I'm not a writer.
Why do I have to type this much?
Done.
Hello, sweethearts.
This is Smart Lemon.
Today, let me show you around a cafe.
This is the fancy cafe
my best friends and I often visit.
Let's immerse ourselves here.
Shh.
The moment I step in, I smell
strong coffee.
Look, so many plants here.
How refreshing!
Here.
The spots of my best friends and me
with an ocean view.
OK. Let me reverse the camera.
I can't wait
to order a cup of coffee.
This chair
is very big, soft, and comfortable.
If any of you want to work here
for a long time,
this seat will be
your best choice.
I've put a link of the address
below the video.
Thanks.
Thanks for the gift from Mr. Lu.
Thank you, sweethearts, for your follow.
(Mr. Lu is a fan now.)
Let me see.
(Smart Lemon won't lose!)
Mr. Lu commented,
"Now, young people
love to go to bars.
Few of them visit a cafe."
Anyway,
we're visiting a cafe.
Yeah. So, we'd better
talk about the coffee thing.
Please.
(Bar Proposal)
Well, I thought about it.
I think Mr. Lu has brought up
a good proposition.
If any of you have an idea
about the bar thing,
comment on the screen.
We can prepare
for a bar visit, huh?
(Many cool guys are in the bar.)
"I love a place with many young guys."
"Cool guys and pretty girls." That's right.
Looks like you have good ideas
about the bar thing.
OK. Later, I will plan
a visit to the bar.
Mr. Lu asked again,
"Smart Lemon, what kind of bar do you prefer?"
I personally think
a livehouse is good.
Singers sing on the stage
while the guests
can drink and chat off the stage.
It won't be too noisy.
And because I'm a live streamer,
I think it will be
a good idea
to have a big screen in the bar
where the guests
can express their emotions
and feelings
through bullet comments.
This idea
may be fun.
Thanks.
Thanks for Mr. Lu's big gift.
Thank you.
All right, sweethearts.
Follow me and give me a like.
Then you'll find me next time.
(You're welcome! The name of the bar?)
Today, I'm visiting a cafe, huh?
I can't wait to order a cup of coffee.
I'll go.
I feel so relaxed.
Let's come and see
how coffee is made.
(Bar proposal. You're welcome! Name of the bar?
Sour-Sweet Livehouse)
(Mr. Ma)
Miss Li, I have
moved up the material delivery for Xingchen.
Within one month, it'll be sent to you.
Thank you, Mr. Ma.
I'll invite you to dinner someday.
(Xiao Yixiao)
You're just in time.
The problem is solved.
That's good.
You helped me, right?
A friend of mine knew Mr. Ma
and I asked him to set us up.
Didn't I tell you?
I don't need you
to solve my problems at work.
♪Once again, you stand opposite me♪
♪Telling the worlds I'm not familiar with♪
♪They seem remote, but get in between us♪
♪We test each other
to see who'll first cross the line♪
♪If I can get closer to you♪
♪Can we have our memories overlapped?♪
♪Time puts walls up to keep my loneliness safe♪
♪Hope understanding will not endanger us♪
♪We each take a side♪
♪The chess board is set,
leaving us with a dilemma♪
♪We always expect each other to relent first♪
♪Before we're relieved♪
♪Pretend love isn't about winning♪
♪We each keep a half♪
♪Completing ourselves before revealing♪
♪Instead of expectations♪
♪We need each other's answer to judge♪
♪When love is a game of exchange♪
♪It is truly terrible♪