♪The original dream stays buried♪
♪Through the wind and the rain♪
♪It waits for the sunshine♪
♪To slowly revive♪
♪I want to travel through the skyscrapers♪
♪Even if the trip may be bumpy♪
♪Sooner or later the mist will clear♪
♪I'll realize my dream without hesitation♪
♪Through the crowd, it's hard to see♪
♪As cramped as the stars♪
♪Yearning for each other's sky♪
♪Forget we used to sparkle too♪
♪I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not hesitating at all♪
♪I'll seize the future, suspecting nothing♪
♪Because I'm dauntless♪
♪So, I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not giving up♪
♪I will always believe in miracles♪
♪Even if I have to look for them endlessly♪
=As Beautiful As You=
=Episode 29=
(Xingchen always talks with its products.)
(Our original dream and goal)
(Personnel)
(are to offer medical resources)
(to every common guy)
(and enable ordinary people)
(to have customized medical products.)
(The starlight is faint,)
(but it can light up somewhere.)
(The starlight is faint,
but it can light up somewhere.)
(Junk company, close down.)
(An entrepreneur like me resonates.)
(Don't talk big unless you can do it, OK?)
What are you doing here?
Good.
You turned it around.
There are still many cursing comments.
Stop reading, then.
How are you feeling? You must be tried.
Shall I take you out for a walk?
Where are we going?
To see the best night view in Xinggang.
Let's go.
When I worked in Guanghua,
after a late night working,
I saw this night view,
I would find this city very strange.
I had no place here.
I worked so hard
and I was excellent.
Why could I not get what I wanted?
Because I wasn't powerful enough then.
Later, I established Xingchen.
In the middle of the night, I also sighed.
"Wow, I could finally
have a place
in this city."
But today...
This city looks strange again
just as how it looked
in the very beginning.
Not because I'm not powerful enough,
but because I've grown.
I realize
I've got something
and I've lost something.
Today, I had a fight
where both parties were hurt.
To be honest,
I don't care how Huang Weiwei feels.
She betrayed me.
In her eyes,
maybe I also hurt her.
It's hard to tell.
The only thing I feel bad about is...
I think I lost something
that I would never get back again.
Look at the road in front of you.
When you walk on it,
you'll meet someone and experience something
that you can't avoid.
Nobody's comfort will help.
Before you feel everything personally,
you can't pass along it.
You must have experienced this
hundreds of times.
How does it feel?
After experiencing too much,
you have no feelings at all?
Not really.
It's just an attitude.
This is life.
We give and take.
At best, it's an equal exchange.
Actually, it's just a deal.
Whatever you want to get,
you have to pay something for it.
When you see it through,
you'll be used to that.
What?
Nothing. I just want to touch you.
Are you feeling better now?
I'm very happy now.
(Because of you.)
Done.
Oh, wonton is ready?
It's a treat for you.
(Laosi Wonton Shop)
I hear
no tech companies
dare to employ Huang Weiwei.
Han Yuan paid her
and then discarded her.
She has totally
ruined herself.
It's her own choice.
She deserves it.
I didn't expect Ji Xing to be so resolute.
She's grown really fast.
Where's the stuff I want?
You guessed right.
Han Yuan and Chang He
colluded a long time ago.
They saw each other three times a month.
In order not to attract attention,
they met somewhere very secret.
It's also Han Yuan
who told Chang He
about our acquisition offer
for Zhu's Medical Instrument.
Since the last board meeting,
she's been investigating
outside partnership of Dongyang Medical.
Has she figured out
your relationship with Hanhai?
Then your investment in Hanhai
will be revealed.
If Ji Xing knows
Hanhai has developed
with your full support...
I'll find the right opportunity to tell her.
It's better
than she's informed by someone else.
This...
What is this? So sour.
Son,
are you being upset
because I'm in your bar?
No.
It's not about you.
Then...
You...
Ms. Han,
I have a friend.
When he confessed his love,
the girl said they could be brother and sister.
What do you think he should do now?
Don't be discouraged.
In love,
you must not shrink.
You...
No, I mean...
You just tell your friend
not to back down.
You know what?
When I pursued my father,
if I gave up,
you wouldn't have existed.
But I fear
if I keep pursuing her, she'll stay farther.
You have to endure hardships.
You know what?
I always think
Ting and Ji Xing
must have communicated
when they were in college.
Look how far Ting has gone
over all these hardships.
Son, you're still staying put.
You aren't even in the position to run.
No way. You have to be fast.
For your father,
I even went to Taiwan, China.
Right.
Come on, Ms. Han.
A friend of mine, not me.
I understand.
It's not you, Mr. Lu.
Ms. Han, you know that?
I'm your mother, OK?
During the Spring Festival,
when I used your phone
to give some presents
to Miss Xiaomeng,
I got to know
you were her bitter enemy, Mr. Lu.
Every day,
in another girl's live-streaming,
you kept giving presents
and helping her beat Miss Xiaomeng.
Now, you want Miss Xiaomeng
to accept you soon.
Do you think it's possible?
I get it.
Come on,
Mr. Lu.
Ms. Han, stop calling me that.
Fine, fine.
Mr. Lu...
Linjia.
Give me another drink.
Here. It tastes awful.
OK. Just a second.
Put less lemon.
(Shao Yichen&amp; Wei Qiuzi)
Next, the bride and groom
will make wedding vows.
Qiuzi,
thank you.
In my toughest
and most important times,
you were there by my side.
In the future,
I'll be there for you, too.
Together with you,
I'll keep our family well.
Qiuzi,
for the rest of my life,
I'll love you every day.
Yichen,
since the day
we were in a relationship,
you've always been the one
I want to spend my life with.
A simple life
is what you want.
And what I want
is to see you every day.
This is the future I want most.
We just heard
what the couple said
from the bottom
of their hearts.
I know.
The life they want
is very simple.
I'm happy for them.
All they want is to laugh in the living room,
cook in the kitchen,
and hug in the bedroom.
Then, let's
sincerely wish
the couple
can always love each other
and always be happy.
Bride and groom,
exchange your wedding rings.
Let's give them
our applause and best wishes.
We witnessed the happiest and sweetest moment
of the couple.
Next,
we'll spread the happiness.
Unmarried guests,
please come up here
to fight for the bouquet of happiness
from the bride.
Come up, please.
Let's go.
Bride, please turn your back
to the guests.
Out for a walk?
OK.
Come on.
Next, let's
countdown from three.
Get ready. Three, two, one!
- Here.
- Give it to me.
Great.
Congratulations, madam.
Congrats on getting it.
Congrats, Li Li. You got the bouquet.
I believe in the near future,
you will also get
your happy life.
Friends, next comes
the photo session.
Dear guests,
follow an order to take a photo
- with the couple.
- Let's go.
There you go.
I just realized today
that a wedding could be so romantic.
The light, the vibe,
the flowers,
and the music.
With all these things,
everybody easily gets moved.
I got the bouquet.
Why do I think
the bride threw it to you deliberately?
I fought for it anyway.
A bouquet won't prove valuable
until its meaning is fulfilled.
What kind of wedding do you want?
A church wedding?
Or a seaside wedding?
Actually, I think
a wedding trip is good.
Li Li.
I'm not getting married again.
You know all about my situation.
I'll take care of you all my life.
But I really don't want
another marriage.
But I give you my word.
I'll try my best to give you
all the other things you want.
What can you give me?
Keep me company all the time?
Or stay with me
for the rest of your life?
You can't even give my marriage.
What do I need
your promises for?
Forget it.
I won't give you a hard time. Let it be.
Why did you not fight for the bouquet?
A bridal bouquet represents love and beauty.
I have both. Why would I fight for it?
This is
a good model answer.
That is my truth.
You don't think
I'm still sad, do you?
No.
I just fear it may stir up your feelings.
A saying goes like this.
"Before leaving the wrong guy,
we can't meet a Mr. Right."
So, I'm your Mr. Right.
What do you think?
Many people spend a lifetime
looking for something that pleases them.
When I'm with you,
my heart beats faster.
I want to spend my life with you like this.
You can't be proposing to me, can you?
What are you thinking?
I don't want our proposing anniversary
to be their wedding anniversary.
When will you propose to me, then?
If you want it,
I can do it now.
Ji Xing,
will you...?
Will you take my car home?
Annoying. I'll take a taxi.
Just kidding.
Are you going or not?
Will you take a bike?
I'll take a tricycle.
Now, you're watching
- the wedding of my friends,
- Wait.
Miss Wei Qiuzi
and Mr. Shao Yichen.
These little accessories
are of the palace style.
And this is my friend.
Pretty, huh?
Hello.
Xiaomeng, come to my bar.
I'm busy. I won't go.
You said you liked Dashu, right?
I have him sing at my bar.
Be right there.
Dashu!
♪It was the first snow♪
It's really him.
It's Mr. Dashu.
See? I'm awesome, huh?
I know you like him.
I have him here for you.
Don't say anything.
Just listen.
♪We haven't seen for a year. You're thinner♪
♪You look a little bit silent♪
It's the first time I've seen him personally.
He's more handsome than he is on TV.
I don't agree.
Shh. Don't talk.
♪The distance summoned me♪
Shh.
♪A few years passed by after we broke up♪
♪Now♪
♪How have you been doing?♪
Do you think I can take a photo
with Mr. Dashu?
That's not necessary.
Mr. Dashu.
May I take a photo with you?
Sure.
Lu Linjia.
Take a photo of us.
Mr. Dashu,
the audition is almost done.
Thank you.
I'll contact you later.
OK.
Thanks for today.
Lu Linjia,
you only took one photo?
I wanted a photo with my idol,
but you did a selfie.
The three of us are in the photo now.
Isn't he also in it?
Zoom up and he's gone!
There'll be more chances.
Tell me.
Is Dashu your cup of tea?
What are you talking about?
I just admire his talent.
Then tell me. What kind of man do you like?
Why did you say
we would be brother and sister?
Why on earth do you keep
asking questions?
You used to like Snow White.
What if you like Snow Black later?
You're so changeable.
Why did you always bring up Snow White?
Tell me. Do I have a chance?
No, for the moment.
Xiaomeng.
Where are you going?
To see Dashu.
I'll prove my love over time.
Why are you back so late?
And you're so drunk.
Li Li.
I'm sorry.
That day,
I shouldn't have said that.
I didn't care about your feelings.
My apologies.
Did you not care
or did you not want to care?
Don't be mad, Li Li.
You really matter a lot to me.
You know what?
Every time you feel sad for me,
I'll feel even worse.
I haven't had this feeling for a long time.
I can't give you a family.
But this ring
shows my love for you.
Don't leave me, will you?
Xiao Yixiao,
let's break up.
Why must a relationship
be defined and maintained
through marriage?
Ms. Yuan,
Xingchen Technology
will start its Series A financing soon.
You're not going
to let Han Ting continue, are you?
What is destined to happen will happen.
We can't always stop it.
Why are you so anxious?
Getting along with such a tough man
like Han Ting
is like a tightrope act.
I can't help feeling anxious.
Mr. Zhou, this is crazy.
Even if Xingchen gets financing,
Han Ting can't fulfill his pledge
to double the stock price.
But I always think
Han Ting's pledge
can't be that simple.
When he was back from Germany,
he was so confident.
And he invested in Xingchen
after he made his pledge.
Think about it.
Could he have some other plans
before he came back?
Ms. Yuan, Mr. Zhou.
I hear Yang Qiong, the former product director
of Dongyang Medical,
has been resentful since he was
deployed to Dongyang Base.
He thought he was replaced by Luo Ping
because Mr. Han excluded his dissidents.
I'm thinking if we can have him
get more information.
Maybe he can get a lot
that we aren't aware of.
Let's make use of Yang Qiong, then.
Got it.
- Mr. Han.
- Sit.
What do you want me for?
Mr. Han,
a subordinate of mine
applied for the Pioneer Project.
I really didn't know
we would replace Xingchen.
I'm so sorry.
So, this is why you want to see me.
I'm always professional.
Yes, of course.
I certainly believe you, Mr. Han.
Hanhai and Xingchen are competitors.
Even if you, Mr. Chen,
applied for it personally,
that would be a very normal
market behavior.
I just fear Miss Ji will misunderstand us.
What scares you?
You and Miss Ji are in a relationship.
I don't want
to offend your future wife.
Mr. Han,
what did I say wrong?
Nothing.
I just sighed.
Even a man like you
who pursues technical dreams
can also be overcautious
for this worldly wisdom thing.
- Have some tea.
- OK.
Mr. Han,
I heard
Xingchen would start
Series A financing, huh?
Yes.
Mr. Han, don't blame me for nagging.
Xingchen and Hanhai
fought for the Pioneer Project
and it was just the start.
I'm worried
more things like this
will happen in the future.
It's not convenient to reveal
your relationship with Hanhai.
And Miss Ji is your girlfriend.
In terms of our competition
with Xingchen,
I really don't know how far to go.
You once mentioned
to merge Hanhai and Xingchen.
If I want this plan to continue,
what do you say?
That's great.
But it's not a pure merger,
but an organic integration.
Keep Hanhai's comprehensiveness
as well as Xingchen's innovativeness.
Think about it before you reply.
I don't need to.
I'm OK with it.
When I'm back, I'll work out
the merger proposal.
I'll let you know.
OK.
I'm on it now.
Xing.
Did you see?
Hanhai replaced us in the Pioneer Project.
Yichen told me.
But we were verified
for that project, weren't we?
Be seated.
We were verified.
But at the very last moment,
Hanhai applied, too.
And they got the spot.
Do we still stand a chance
to fight for it?
What is the reason
for our disqualification?
Hanhai is more famous.
This is normal.
Then why didn't they
just give Hanhai the spot?
Why did they offer an open application?
Besides, doesn't this project
help small and medium-sized businesses?
Look at it this way.
It also proves
our company has grown better.
Even Hanhai takes us
as its competitor.
Come in.
Miss Ji, Mr. Chang of Tongke is here.
I have him wait for you in the meeting room.
OK.
Xing,
what is Chang He doing here?
When I see him, I'll know.
I should go.
OK.
Miss Ji,
I'm here uninvited.
Am I disturbing your work?
Not at all. Mr. Chang,
your presence is an honor.
Before getting down to business,
I want to apologize to you.
When we had dinner last time,
I saw you and Mr. Han.
In a good mood, I drank too much.
Later, I got to know
Mr. Han was allergic to alcohol.
I nearly forgot it.
No discord, no concord.
Miss Ji,
you know what I'm here for,
don't you?
Does my company stand a chance
for your Series A financing?
Either you think I want to use Xingchen
to make some money
or you think
I seek cooperation
to develop a new manufacturing model,
what I expect is some progress.
It'll be a win-win, right?
You have a point, Mr. Chang.
But
Xingchen's every big decision
is regulated by Mr. Han.
It's OK. I don't invest in Xingchen
to kick Dongyang Medical out.
I don't mind cooperating with him.
And I think you and Mr. Han
can separate your career
from your relationship.
My competition and my investment
are very different things.
For a merchant,
the top priority is always
the maximum profits of his company.
No offense,
but love is changeable.
I know many businesswomen
who sacrificed their interests for love
but were hurt in the end.
Some other businesswomen
can also coordinate work and love very well.
I'm sure you understand.
I do.
I want maximum profits, of course.
Either Mr. Han
or any other investor...
Maybe they can offer more profits
than you do.
And of course,
we may cooperate with you
in the end.
Business negotiations take time.
If you say other investors
are more competitive, I'll believe it.
But Han Ting...
My investment
only leads to fractional shares.
Xingchen will still be yours.
But Han Ting will centralize the shares.
Xingchen will be his.
To be honest,
I think a neutral third party is the best
for our Series A financing.
Fine.
Let's talk in detail when possible.
But anyway,
I still want you
to think carefully about it.
See who gives you a better offer,
someone else or me.
OK.
Li.
What's up?
Are you available tonight?
I want to invite you to a movie.
Why do you suddenly want that?
I hear
a comedy film has been on
and it's very popular.
I think
after you watch it,
you may feel happier.
It'll be my treat.
OK.
I'll get to work. See you after work.
Hello.
I'd like to see Miss Zeng.
OK. Come with me.
Miss Zeng, you've got a visitor.
Get him in.
Such a beautiful view here.
Mr. Chang?
What brings you here?
This is Dongyang Building.
It's my first time here.
Don't you give me a seat?
My place
is your territory, too.
You flatter me.
I texted you, but you didn't reply.
I had to come personally.
I was dealing with a contract
and didn't check my phone.
What's this?
I had my man pick you
some offices to choose from.
Pick one and tell me.
If you're not satisfied,
I'll look for more.
You want me to move away?
Why?
I haven't taken revenge yet.
Leave the revenge thing to me.
I just came out of Xingchen Technology.
Xingchen?
What were you doing there?
To see Ji Xing.
I talked with her about Series A financing.
This is the way you avenge me?
You don't like it?
Unless Ji Xing falls out with Han Ting,
she won't accept your offer.
Nothing is absolute.
To achieve something,
we can always find a way.
OK. I'll be right there.
Li, here's the coffee.
I have an emergency.
I'm sorry.
We'll watch it another day.
For Xiao Yixiao?
This gentleman is drunk.
Because he's our boss's friend,
we don't dare to move him.
You're the emergency contact on his phone.
We had to call you.
Thanks. I got it.
Xiao Yixiao.
Xiao Yixiao, wake up!
There you are.
I'll drive you back.
Where will you drive me?
To your place or mine?
Xiao Yixiao,
since you can't give me what I want,
let's not contact anymore.
We're over.
Then why are you here?
Li Li,
let's get back together.
OK.
Really?
Marry me tomorrow.
I got you a designated driver.
You go back home alone.
(Dongyang Group)
Zhong.
You called me in a hurry.
What happened?
Mr. Su, I had meant to work overtime
to sort out the quotation.
But suddenly, my monitor went black.
When I restarted it,
the file was gone.
Don't panic. Let me check.
I think I can solve it.
I'm sorry, Mr. Su.
I had meant
to ask our webmasters for help.
But they were off work.
I had to call you, then.
It's OK. I'm available.
(Windows can't find "mscofig".
Confirm and try again.)
(Quotation)
Done.
Thank you so much, Mr. Su.
You did me a big favor.
If you don't mind,
I should go.
Mr. Su.
Anything else?
I like you.
You...
I know you adore Miss Li.
So, I just want you to know
how I feel for you.
Since I came here,
you've helped me a lot.
Since then,
I've been in love with you.
You're the vice general manager,
but you don't put on airs.
When you work,
you're so serious.
I hope
you'll consider me.
♪Once again, you stand opposite me♪
♪Telling the worlds I'm not familiar with♪
♪They seem remote, but get in between us♪
♪We test each other
to see who'll first cross the line♪
♪If I can get closer to you♪
♪Can we have our memories overlapped?♪
♪Time puts walls up to keep my loneliness safe♪
♪Hope understanding will not endanger us♪
♪We each take a side♪
♪The chess board is set,
leaving us with a dilemma♪
♪We always expect each other to relent first♪
♪Before we're relieved♪
♪Pretend love isn't about winning♪
♪We each keep a half♪
♪Completing ourselves before revealing♪
♪Instead of expectations♪
♪We need each other's answer to judge♪
♪When love is a game of exchange♪
♪It is truly terrible♪