♪The original dream stays buried♪
♪Through the wind and the rain♪
♪It waits for the sunshine♪
♪To slowly revive♪
♪I want to travel through the skyscrapers♪
♪Even if the trip may be bumpy♪
♪Sooner or later the mist will clear♪
♪I'll realize my dream without hesitation♪
♪Through the crowd, it's hard to see♪
♪As cramped as the stars♪
♪Yearning for each other's sky♪
♪Forget we used to sparkle too♪
♪I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not hesitating at all♪
♪I'll seize the future, suspecting nothing♪
♪Because I'm dauntless♪
♪So, I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not giving up♪
♪I will always believe in miracles♪
♪Even if I have to look for them endlessly♪
=As Beautiful As You=
=Episode 9=
(Yushan Bypass No.3)
Yichen,
when I'm done working,
let's go visit your parents.
I'll buy your father
his favorite tea
and buy your mother some skincare products.
Let's watch the movie first.
Yichen, when we're old,
let's move to such a beautiful place,
OK?
Do you remember we said
we would run a guesthouse in Yunnan?
Yeah.
You said I cooked very well.
So, I could be a chef
and you could be a receptionist.
But you also said
you didn't want me to work too hard.
We would rather
hire some local employees.
Then we could go fishing,
climb the mountains,
and go anywhere we want to be.
When we were fed up with somewhere,
we could move to another place.
And when we grew old,
we would sit in the rocking chair
in front of our house,
waddling and waddling.
We would live a simple and stable life
for the rest of our lives.
Xing.
If only we could really
live such a life!
(PPT of Proposal Plan to Get Yichen)
(Proposal Plan to Get Yichen)
(3. I'll meet Yichen
when he arrives at the cinema.)
(4. Thirty minutes later,
I'll pretend to go to the toilet.)
(1. All my best friends involved
should arrive before seven.)
Xing, I made breakfast.
Have some.
How happy I am!
It's so nice to have you.
You have some, too.
Hello.
Hello. Why haven't you come down yet?
You're arrived, sir?
Wait a minute, please. I'll be right down.
Hey, it's difficult to park here.
OK. I get it.
It's difficult to park here.
I'm coming down. Bye-bye.
Yichen, I have to go.
Today's summit is very important.
Wish me success.
I think I can come back early today.
I'll buy you a big dinner.
Xing,
let's break up.
What did you say?
I said,
let's break up.
If you joke about this,
I'll be angry.
Shao Yichen!
I've been waiting. Why haven't you come yet?
Don't you know I can't park here?
I told you I would come.
Can't you just wait?
Why can't you just wait?
Go ahead, Xing.
The choice is yours.
Think it over.
(Wisdom Medicine
Innovation and Development Summit)
(Lu Yiming, Zhou Zhiwei)
(Zeng Di)
(Han Ting)
(Jiangyang International, Wisdom Medicine
Innovation and Development Summit)
(Wisdom Medicine
Hey, here we are.
Excuse me, sir.
May I put on makeup in your car?
OK. Go ahead.
Thank you.
Young girl,
here's what I think.
When you look back later,
however big the trouble is,
it'll be nothing.
Look on the bright side. It'll pass.
Thank you, sir. I'll pay later.
Where would I have met her?
Mr. Han, we're about to start.
Please prepare for a speech backstage.
- OK.
- Go ahead, Mr. Han.
I'll head over there.
Let's go.
(Total Hip Arthroplasty)
(Surgical Exposures in Orthopaedics
Approach and Anatomy)
Thanks again for the entrepreneurs
to have given such wonderful speeches.
The morning session is over.
We have prepared
a delicious lunch for you.
Please go get your food.
(Yichen)
Ji Xing.
Mr. Han.
Mr. Shen,
this is Ji Xing from Xingchen Technology.
Her company is new,
but it is promising.
This is Mr. Shen from Ke Technology.
Hi, Mr. Shen.
So,
it's Xingchen Mr. Han has just invested in.
A company Mr. Han thinks highly of
certainly has a bright future.
All thanks to your lucky words.
We'll learn from you.
Mr. Han and I are going to have lunch.
Join us. Let's eat and talk.
Mr. Shen.
Long time no see.
Ji Xing, you're here, too.
Miss Zeng.
Miss Zeng, you also know Miss Ji?
I do, of course.
Mr. Shen, you have no idea, huh?
Ji Xing was a produce engineer
of my company
for a few years.
Ji Xing, Mr. Shen is very authoritative.
Consult him if you have any confusion.
Don't keep checking your phone.
Ji Xing,
if you want Mr. Shen's contact,
just ask him for it.
He's very nice.
Come on, Ji Xing.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
Thanks, Mr. Shen. I'll scan your code.
Done.
Let's get over there. Eat and talk.
- OK. Let's go.
- OK.
There will be an after-party.
Let's go together.
Mr. Shen, are you interested?
I'm here
just to communicate with peers.
What about you, Miss Ji?
My company has just started
and I have a lot of things to do.
I'm not going.
Ji Xing, I suggest you should go.
You're not what you used to be.
When you were an employee,
you could avoid social intercourses.
Now, you're a boss.
You have to contact more people
in case you lose some opportunities.
When work is done perfectly,
there will be opportunities.
Without strength,
even the best opportunities won't help.
Here's the thing.
I have a speech to make.
I'll go get ready.
You come with me.
(Sign-in Reception)
You've been absent-minded all day.
What's bothering you?
Nothing.
You asked me for the invitation.
But now, you're negative.
This isn't the right attitude.
Maybe I have low sugar blood
when I eat nothing in the morning.
I'll be OK this afternoon.
What on earth happened?
Nothing.
I'll adjust myself.
Adjust your mood
and cheer up,
Ji Xing.
Done comforting her?
You didn't have to be so competitive, huh?
Oh, I was?
I just tried to remind her.
I don't want others to think
a former employee of Guanghua
has no social etiquette.
Anything wrong?
No.
Don't worry. I'll instruct her.
Then, she should work hard.
You have high standards, after all.
(Lu Linjia)
Ting, how about you check up
on my bar tonight?
Get in the car.
No need, Mr. Han. I called a taxi.
Don't waste time.
Thanks.
Mr. Han,
sorry for today.
I behaved poorly.
I won't do it next time.
Since you know you feel bad
when you don't eat anything,
you must have meals regularly.
The choice is yours.
Think it over.
♪In old time♪
♪We count the diamonds in the sky♪
♪Then you smile♪
♪Bringing my dark world some light♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪You go away a hundred miles♪
♪Overnight♪
♪No more diamonds in the sky♪
Shall I invite you to my company
and see the stars?
Your future is about to prosper.
Our future, actually.
♪Goodnight♪
♪The love is blind♪
♪But at least we’ve fought and tried♪
(Xing)
Hello.
Open the door.
Look, Yichen.
This is our agreement with Dongyang.
It has the stamps and the signatures.
Look.
Look at it.
And here.
(Han Ting, Ji Xing)
Their first payment
has arrived, too.
Look.
(Details)
Soon.
Soon, Xingchen will develop
along the right lines.
Xing.
Congratulations.
Xing,
no other girl.
Only you.
I only had you all the time.
Xing, stop crying.
I'm no longer your girlfriend.
It's none of your business.
Can't you wait for me?
I told you I would soon succeed.
Wait for me, will you?
Could you please wait for me?
- Could you?
- No.
I can't only
keep you company
when you need me.
And when you don't,
I'm only the background.
Sorry. It's my fault.
Sorry.
I won't do this again.
I just won't.
Sorry, Yichen.
Sorry.
Xing,
we can no longer
stay in each other's life.
I'm to blame.
You failed to get financing,
failed to buy a printer,
and you had research problems.
Every day, you have terrible troubles,
big or small.
But all I can give you
is pale and useless comfort.
I can't give you anything.
I don't need anything from you.
That's all about work.
I don't need that from you, Yichen.
But I do, Xing.
I can't only be an onlooker
to watch your life
while I can't get involved at all.
So, stop saying sorry.
You've done nothing wrong.
Xing, we'll just go different ways.
Actually, last night,
I saw your proposal plan.
But Xing,
I can't accept it.
Sorry.
Because what I want
is a simple life
where the couple stays together.
But what you want
is to realize your value in life.
So, our relationship
really can't sustain.
Xing,
I want you to do very well.
I want you to be happy,
healthy,
and successful.
I want you to get everything
you want to have.
(Don't Be Afraid of the Wind)
I bought two opera tickets.
Let's watch it
to celebrate our fourth anniversary.
OK. I'll come and pick you up.
You keep the tickets.
I don't need to go anywhere.
Because every day, I can see
the most beautiful star.
Xing,
will you marry me?
I'll keep the ring.
When I get financing,
I'll propose to you.
OK?
Pinky promise.
There it goes.
(Lu Linjia)
Ting, where are you?
Hurry. I've been waiting for you.
What smells so good?
What have you cooked?
Oh, seafood porridge.
Every time you're in trouble, you cook.
Today, you cooked something so complicated.
Are you in some big trouble?
What happened?
Did Ji Xing send you
a wedding invitation?
She broke up.
It's a good thing.
Go get her now.
She's in urgent need of comfort.
What are you doing here?
Stop being arrogant.
Just do what I tell you.
Now, go give her
proper care and comfort.
Then you'll get her.
I never allow myself
to swoop in.
Come on.
To get what you want,
never mind how you get it.
OK. I have something else to do.
I'm going out.
After all this trouble,
you won't taste any?
You enjoy it.
Clean the kitchen for me.
What I just told you,
think carefully about it.
That's a shame he isn't a chef.
(Tell Mother)
Lemonade, please.
Thanks.
Ting, there you are, at last.
She's been sitting there
and drinking for more than one hour.
Don't worry.
She must be drinking alone
for something she's sad about.
Look. She can even dance.
More hyper than me.
Rest assured.
Let me show you around the cabins.
- I have ideas for design.
- I'd like...
Go check it for me.
I'm OK.
I'm OK. Don't be scared.
I'd like
a Bloody Mary.
OK.
Awesome.
Thank you.
Who are you?
Who do you think I am?
Han Ting?
Come on. Drink with me.
I'll drive you home.
- I'm not going home.
- Bill, please.
- Take her coat.
- What are you doing?
Put me down!
I'm not done drinking!
- The bill is on him.
- I can drink more!
I'm not drunk.
I... I can even swim.
I can swim in backstroke and freestyle.
All kinds.
I can swim.
Ting, where are we going?
Driver her home first.
Boss, I only know which community
Miss Ji lives in.
But I don't know
which room it is.
Call Wei Qiuzi.
That's right. It's smart of you.
Tang Song, open the window.
Don't.
Cold air may make her feel worse.
OK.
Wei Qiuzi is asleep, I think.
She doesn't answer.
Keep calling.
Boss, shall I contact the HR of Guanghua
and ask about Miss Ji's address?
No need.
She still doesn't answer.
Ji Xing has another best friend.
That's right.
Tu Xiaomeng. She must be doing live streaming.
Let me ask her.
(You're silenced.)
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday to this sweetheart!
- (Oh, I forgot. I'm silenced.)
- Thank you for your support.
Please give me a like.
Thank you, everybody.
The Coolest Mr. Lu
has entered the live room.
(Why is he using his alt account here?)
I have your roommate now.
Text me back.
Room 201, Building No.17,
(Smart Lemon)
Meigang Community.
Tu Xiaomeng texted me back.
Turn around.
I'm just saying
Tu Xiaomeng sent me the address.
Tang Song, let's go.
Closer, please.
Come in here.
Be careful.
Well, you take care of her.
- We should go.
- Thanks.
Don't go.
I feel bad.
Get a basin.
Wait a minute.
Why is she so drunk?
Is there any honey?
Honey?
I... I'll go buy some.
It's dangerous to go out alone so late.
Fine.
- Then...
- I'll go with you.
Thirsty.
I'm thirsty.
Here. Be careful.
Drink slowly.
Don't go.
You must not leave.
You must not.
Don't move.
Fine. I won't move.
Cold.
I'm cold.
Don't go. Don't.
Don't go.
Seriously?
♪Once again, you stand opposite me♪
♪Telling the worlds I'm not familiar with♪
♪They seem remote, but get in between us♪
♪We test each other
to see who'll first cross the line♪
♪If I can get closer to you♪
♪Can we have our memories overlapped?♪
♪Time puts walls up to keep my loneliness safe♪
♪Hope understanding will not endanger us♪
♪We each take a side♪
♪The chess board is set,
leaving us with a dilemma♪
♪We always expect each other to relent first♪
♪Before we're relieved♪
♪Pretend love isn't about winning♪
♪We each keep a half♪
♪Completing ourselves before revealing♪
♪Instead of expectations♪
♪We need each other's answer to judge♪
♪When love is a game of exchange♪
♪It is truly terrible♪