♪The original dream stays buried♪
♪Through the wind and the rain♪
♪It waits for the sunshine♪
♪To slowly revive♪
♪I want to travel through the skyscrapers♪
♪Even if the trip may be bumpy♪
♪Sooner or later the mist will clear♪
♪I'll realize my dream without hesitation♪
♪Through the crowd, it's hard to see♪
♪As cramped as the stars♪
♪Yearning for each other's sky♪
♪Forget we used to sparkle too♪
♪I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not hesitating at all♪
♪I'll seize the future, suspecting nothing♪
♪Because I'm dauntless♪
♪So, I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not giving up♪
♪I will always believe in miracles♪
♪Even if I have to look for them endlessly♪
=As Beautiful As You=
=Episode 11=
Here.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
I'll clean the cardigan
and give it back to you soon.
It's OK. Take your time.
When I'm back home,
I'll read your comments carefully.
You go get some rest early.
OK.
I should go.
Bye-bye.
(Smart Lemon: Super vigorous!)
It's photoshopped too much.
I don't think this is what you look like.
(Has enabled Friend Confirmation.
Send a friend request.)
How dare she delete me?
It's the first time someone dares
to delete me on WeChat.
Just you wait, Smart Lemon.
I'll let you know how it feels
to be deleted by me mercilessly.
Here. Have some fruit.
Why did you turn it off?
Why have you been so thin?
Have you worked too much?
I'm not thin. Look at my chubby face.
Don't laugh.
You're much thinner than last time I saw you.
You know what?
A mother's biggest wish
is to keep her child
happy and healthy.
It's OK to be ordinary,
but don't be worn out.
I'm doing great.
I'm very happy.
How come I can't see that?
You can just fool your father.
Come on.
You've been emotional since little.
But in life,
we can't always get what we want.
Actually, I think it's good
when you make a fresh start.
The only thing that never changes
is the change itself.
Nothing is permanent.
I get it, Mom.
Think I'm nagging, huh?
Here's my point.
Look, at work
or in love,
what's gone is gone.
When you're at my age, you'll understand.
Throughout your life,
many people will pass by.
Some of them
can only have meals with you.
can accompany you for several years.
The one who'll accompany you for a lifetime...
Maybe you'll meet him soon.
Yes, yes.
It's OK if I can't meet him.
Don't be silly, girl.
People get married.
You eat it.
The strawberries are so sweet. Eat more.
You just think I'm nagging.
You loved to watch the film
of the three siblings, right?
Let me find it for you.
I'm on it.
A boss like you must be busy.
Do you have time
to dine with your parents?
(Emergency Room)
The place of the accident was remote
with limited healthcare resources.
First-aid treatment wasn't available.
The patients lost too much blood.
There's not much else we can do.
Sorry for your loss.
(Affixes of German Words)
Miss Smart Lemon,
we're an electric bike brand.
(Electric Bike Experience Store)
Are you interested
in advertising our brand?
Yes. What do you need me to do?
Come to our store anytime you want.
I'll send you the location.
You just need to advertise
in your live streaming.
(Electric Bike Experience Store,
Xingyuntai Road)
OK. I'll be there tomorrow.
How time flies!
Yeah.
Throughout the year,
how many times have I seen you?
When you had a job,
you didn't have much free time.
Now, you have a company and you're even busier.
Then think like this.
If your daughter's dream comes true,
you can tell your neighbors
that your daughter is awesome.
Just like how you bragged
when I was the first place at school.
I don't care if you can succeed.
I hope you'll finish work soon
and go home for the Spring Festival.
I will.
There's nothing new
with the Spring Festival.
But only when
the whole family stays together
and celebrate it excitedly
would it be the real festival, right?
I'll go home and stick to you.
Don't get bored of me
every few days.
Your father and I
have totally spoiled you.
You know what?
You're not what you used to be.
You're a boss.
Learn from Han.
- OK.
- Be steadier.
I will.
Look how independent Han is.
He's more mature than his age.
He must have
suffered a lot.
Speaking of this,
the moment I saw him,
I felt familiar with him.
Say goodbye to him for me.
Ask him to take care of himself.
When he has time,
invite him to our home.
I'll always welcome him.
OK. I'll bring your regard.
You care quite a lot about him.
I care more about you.
(Niu Electric Bikes)
Hello.
I...
Lu Linjia?
What are you doing here?
Advertisement day, huh?
Come on.
You're the advertiser?
I own a wide range of businesses.
Come on.
Add me on WeChat.
Now, text me your phone number.
I'll contact you when there's a job.
Hurry.
(Friend Confirmation)
You added me and then deleted me.
What do you mean?
To let you know how it feels to be deleted.
Are you just too bored?
Yeah. I'm too bored.
Are you insane?
I am insane.
What a weirdo!
Listen up, Lu Linjia.
Never dream of adding me
on WeChat again.
Discard the advertisement?
Lu Linjia, what on earth do you want?
There you are, Mr. Lu.
Hi, Mr. Liu.
Let me introduce her.
This is a very famous
Internet celebrity.
Smart Lemon.
You'll take care of the rest.
Count on me.
I should go.
Smart Lemon, let's get in and prepare.
When you buy one now, you may possibly
get lavish presents.
OK, sweethearts.
That's all
for my live streaming
in the electric bike store.
Thanks for your support.
Bye-bye.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Lu kept recommending you
for your high real-time interaction rate.
I watched it and he was right.
Thanks for your hard work.
This electric bike is for you.
For me?
Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- You deserve it.
If there's another chance,
let's cooperate again.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
It's not that I don't want to thank you.
But anyway,
you deleted me.
OK, Boss.
I'm downstairs.
- OK.
- Assistant Tang.
Miss Ji?
Hi, Assistant Tang.
Well, I have something
to consult you.
- But I'm going to...
- Let her finish.
Go ahead, please.
Can we
buy a 3D printer
through Dongyang's channel?
The number of high-density printers
is way too small.
A small company like us has to
line up for a long time to get one.
Let her continue.
Here's the thing.
I'm done reading
Mr. Han's comments.
I made a new work plan.
Now, Xingchen has
three priorities.
To expand our team,
get a lab,
and buy a 3D printer.
The Spring Festival is coming.
I plan to recruit employees
and get a lab after that.
But the printer thing
must be solved before that.
Then...
Ask her what she wants.
So, what do you want from me?
Is it convenient for you
to make a group chat of the suppliers and me
for communication?
What about Boss?
We don't need
to tell Mr. Han now.
Put me on speaker.
- OK.
- OK?
Thank you. It's so nice of you.
Thank you so much.
(Mr. Han)
Then...
Come to my office.
Let's go.
Why did you not come to me for a request?
I didn't want to bother you
for something so small.
Instead of taking a shortcut,
you chose to do it the hard way.
Can I?
Are you saying
I can buy a 3D printer
through Dongyang's channel?
It depends on whether you approve.
Another 5% of the stock.
I'll find a way out myself,
Mr. Han.
I'll let you work. I should go.
Li Li, help.
Is there any way
we can buy a 3D printer soon?
I'll see what I can do.
Queen Li Li,
you're awesome!
(Sales Director Li Li
breaks her client's family as a mistress.)
(To maintain connections,
she has a long affair with her client.)
Emergency?
Dining with you is always the priority.
If something bothers you,
I can take care of it.
If someone curses me,
Mr. Xiao, will you curse him in turn?
Who's so daring?
How dare he curse you?
Someone unimportant.
Never mind.
For such a little problem,
I don't need your help, Mr. Xiao.
Our current relationship is comfortable.
It's pure, too.
I don't want to sabotage it.
Once something else is involved
and we rely on each other,
it will be hard
to get out of it.
Whatever you say.
I'm back.
Xing, you're back from work so early.
What happened to you?
You're so energetic.
You know what?
I've got a bike.
An electric bike.
I've got a plan.
I'll buy you a helmet
and take you for a ride.
OK.
Why did you buy an electric bike?
I didn't buy it.
It's because of Lu Linjia.
He got me a job.
He isn't very smart
or very reliable.
However,
I got an electric bike for his sake.
I'll stop complaining about him for now.
Do you think I've been lucky in money?
Tomorrow, I'm going to expand
the new territory of my career.
New territory?
What are you going to do?
I'll do a part-time job
to make some extra money
in the music store my friend just opened.
Meanwhile, I can sell my vocal lessons
to those instrument purchasers.
This is target advertising.
Kill two birds with one stone.
Awesome. Come on. I support you.
Xing,
have you heard
about this?
"Instead of supporting,
you'd better buy me a yacht."
Oh, you poor spirit. Don't expect a yacht.
I'll buy you a feast of pancakes.
I'll order it right away.
Pancakes, huh?
Don't make them spicy.
Oh, no. Excessive calories.
I'll do more strength training.
(Pearl River Piano)
♪Time passes so quickly♪
♪Go slowly and do not hurry♪
♪In the distance, the sky is warm♪
♪As bright as the day we first met♪
♪Sweet moments soak in fragrance♪
♪Looked back, only the unchanged happiness♪
♪Deserves to be valued and remembered♪
You not only play very well
but also sing beautifully.
Thank you, madam.
This piano has a superior tone.
Would you like to try it?
I'm not here to buy a piano.
I can't play the piano.
Attracted by your singing and music,
I walked in here.
You flatter me, madam.
Everybody starts
from scratch.
In my opinion,
the beauty of music
actually lies in...
Even if there are cultural differences,
as long as the music begins,
the whole world can communicate.
That's sweet of you to say so.
Are you a student
from nearby Xinggang Conservatory of Music?
Yes. I was from that school.
But I've graduated.
I do a part-time job here.
Part-time job?
Yes, madam.
If you have a kid
who wants to learn music,
come to me at any time.
I can give door-to-door lessons.
You'll have a discount.
Really?
That's great. Music brings us together.
I'm looking for a music teacher.
You are?
Then how old
is the child?
What level is he at?
Or when is convenient for you?
I can go meet him.
The kid is actually
50 years old.
That's me.
But I'm zero-based.
I can't play anything.
Do you teach adults?
Yes.
Sorry to have bothered you, Mr. Liu.
Bye.
(Sales Director Li Li
breaks her client's family as a mistress.)
This is outrageous!
What?
Mr. Wu, who harassed Li
is divorcing his wife.
His wife threw mud at Li online,
posted her photos,
and said she was a mistress.
Check it.
It happened a long time ago.
Why is she still tangling?
(A mistress! Shame on her!)
Who could bear such comments?
Xing, shall I write a little app
to curse in return?
Not now.
Let me call her first.
Queen Li Li, what are you doing?
I was about to call you.
I've found a supplier.
Tomorrow morning, we'll visit their factory.
This is great. You're awesome, indeed.
Umm...
Are you aware of the posts?
I am.
It's no big deal.
Some ignorant netizens
just curse me.
It doesn't disturb me in dining,
dressing, or dating.
I don't care what they say.
All right. I'll hang up, sweetheart.
So cool, Li.
OK. I'll be relieved, then.
Tomorrow, shall we go together?
OK.
Deal. Bye-bye.
Li Li is fine.
You focus on your work.
Xing.
Think about it.
Li
lost her job
because of us.
Shall we invite her
to join us?
Just be clear,
I really think
she's very capable at work.
I thought about it.
But I fear our company
would be too small for her.
How could it be?
Xing,
we get support
from Dongyang Medical.
We're a big company.
I'll think it over.
You get to work.
OK.
Come on. Look.
Over here, we have SLM800.
Totally 25 sets.
The rest sets are SLM600.
These are our products
to be delivered worldwide
within a month.
Oh, Miss Ji. How many sets do you want?
We need only one set.
One?
Then I'll submit it for you.
Taking manufacture and shipping into account,
it can be delivered in six months.
- So long?
- Such a long time?
We're in urgent need of it.
Is there a better way
to get one sooner?
Look, you have so many sets in stock.
Can you give us one of them?
I'm sorry.
These are booked by other clients
in advance.
They're urging us, too.
The delivery time is too long.
Can we negotiate on the price?
Miss Li,
you want only one set.
We're already offering
a purchase price.
If I give you a discount,
money will be deducted
from my pay.
Our company is
in the pilot stage.
But it develops
very fast.
When our products
are massively produced,
we'll buy more printers.
I'm just sticking
to our company rules.
In terms of price,
I can't help more.
Please understand.
- We'll leave to it, then.
- Thanks.
- Thanks for today.
- Come this way.
You've arrived, Mr. Chang.
You seldom ask to see me.
I should come early.
Recently, I've been busy
with the Robot Bay thing.
At such a crucial time,
I've been really busy.
The promotion in primary hospitals, huh?
This circle is small, you know.
Have you been exhausted?
You look really haggard.
Just get to the point.
In previous projects, we used
to cooperate with big hospitals.
Robot Bay, however,
needs some resources of primary hospitals.
I don't have enough reserves.
How about you introduce some to me?
Not a problem.
Dongyang Medical is combining
software with hardware, right?
My company needs a transition, too.
Our medical devices
take a large proportion
in second and third-tier cities.
Our companies complement each other.
How about
we sign an official strategic agreement
for cooperation?
OK.
But after all, my company
is invested by Dongyang Medical.
Yours is the strongest rival
of Dongyang Medical.
How do you think
we can have a close cooperation?
Umm...
Will we fear nothing?
Before Han Ting came back,
we had been getting along nicely.
I shared with you
all my resources.
When Han Ting is back,
why are you being so aloof?
What are you talking about?
If I meant to be aloof,
I wouldn't have invited you here.
Miss Ji, you're young
but you start a company with all your money.
Great courage.
When your company
needs printers for massive production,
we'll prioritize that.
But this time, we can't help.
I get it.
Li Li,
let's go back to Dongyang and tell Boss.
One would be too little.
Beidi can't sell it to us.
Let's go back, then.
OK.
Thanks for today.
We should go.
You just mentioned Dongyang.
Which company do you mean?
There's only one Dongyang in China.
Our investor is from Dongyang.
May I ask who he is?
Han Ting.
Oh, of course.
Xingchen Technology
has a bright prospect.
Please sit here for a while.
My boss Mr. Lin
is out for some business.
I'll call him and tell him about it.
- OK.
- Please be seated.
- Thank you.
(Beidi Technology)
Smart move.
He's so snobbish.
Salespersons judge people, don't they?
You didn't lie, anyway.
Han Ting's name is really useful.
So it is.
(Mr. Wu)
Sorry, Miss Li.
I've deleted all the posts.
Mr. Wu texted me
and apologized.
He awakened?
That's impossible.
Someone must have helped behind my back.
When are you coming to my place?
(Li Li)
Do you know what I like you most about?
Your strong sense of purpose.
But sometimes,
when you're anxious,
you appear to be utilitarian.
Burning bridges really upsets me.
And when one is angry,
he'll easily lose his mind.
Oh, Mr. Chang.
Get angry with me
or instruct me as you wish.
But it's hard for a woman like me
to do business.
Don't be fussy about me.
Don't always scare me.
Your tea tastes better, indeed.
I could tell a long time ago.
You're pretty obsessed
with Han Ting.
Have you thought
about whether he cares about you?
Whether he cares about me,
he's the biggest investor
of my company.
Who else
should I be obsessed with?
(Mr. Lin of Beidi)
Hello, Mr. Lin.
Miss Zeng,
do you know
Ji Xing from Xingchen Technology?
Ji Xing?
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Have some water.
- Thanks.
According to Mr. Lin,
we can give you one printer
out of someone else's order.
Thank you so much.
What about the delivery time?
Here's the thing.
The Spring Festival is coming.
After the festival,
we'll prioritize your delivery.
- Thanks.
Shall we talk about
the details of the contract?
OK.
Excuse me.
You talk to Miss Li.
I have to take this.
OK.
In terms of price,
can we have
a 5% off?
Here's the thing, Miss Li.
Getting one set
out of someone else's order
is already the best we can do.
And you want only one set.
In terms of price,
we can't do anything else.
There is no precedent, either.
Don't worry.
Xingchen isn't a team of amateurs.
We'll have plenty of cooperation
with your company.
The profit margin
will be more than 5%.
Miss Ji
was Mr. Han's schoolmate in college.
And Mr. Han thinks
highly of her.
Hearing about her business,
Mr. Han was the first to invest.
Don't tell anyone else.
Miss Ji and Mr. Han
both keep a low profile,
expecting no one to pay much attention.
I get it.
Miss Ji's idea
is in sync with that of Mr. Han
in this industry.
That's why he invested in Xingchen.
Mr. Han has such a good eye.
Mr. Lin and I
also admire your courage
and execution, Miss Ji.
How about this?
I'll venture to make a decision.
In this cooperation,
I'll make the price 5% off.
We can make friends.
What do you say?
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Oh, Mr. Lin just called,
inviting you to lunch tomorrow.
I wonder if you...
- OK.
- We'd love to.
But it should be our treat.
I'll text you when the canteen is reserved.
OK.
Mr. Lin just said
he was stuck in traffic
and would be late.
(Han Ting)
How's it going with the printer?
If you still can't buy one,
the offer for 5% of the stock
is still valid.
(Ji Xing)
Mr. Han,
the printer is successfully ordered.
I'm sorry,
but we'll keep
5% of the stock to ourselves.
How did you order one?
(Han Ting: How did you order one?)
(Ji Xing)
It's a trade secret.
(Zeng Di)
Hello.
Are you available later
and shall we have lunch?
I have something
to tell you face to face.
OK.
I really had no idea.
(Stay Always Safe)
A freelancer like you
also has to work so hard.
It consumes your throat and mental effort.
Especially Poison Apple...
She's terrible.
Look.
This...
It doesn't look good here, right?
Give me... Give me a white one.
- This?
- Right.
Oh, I can't do anything about it.
Mr. Lu backs her up.
Poison Apple and Mr. Lu
are really birds of a feather.
They stand my way
and they're jinxes.
If Mr. Lu
annoys me again in my live room,
I'll block him and kick him out.
That's right. You should have done this.
You should have
blocked that...
That Mr. Lu.
Well, what you're saying
reminds me...
Of my son.
His father died at a young age.
He's my only son
and I brought him up alone.
In case he lives a bad life,
I've been spoiling him.
Sadly, he's spoiled.
It's been a long time
since he graduated.
Every day, he just fools around.
He's nothing like me.
Look, even though I'm aged,
I still learn to do flower arrangement
and sing songs.
Ordinary guys can't compare with you, Ms. Han.
And anyway, you're not aged.
It's so sweet of you.
When the soup is ready, have some more.
Thank you, Ms. Han.
How does it look?
Pretty good.
Ms. Han, I'll take a photo.
Come on.
Quite an expensive canteen.
500 for each diner, huh?
That's a lot of money, Miss Ji.
We owe them a big favor, you know.
Order more dishes you like.
Here.
With the investment,
we'll have normal business meals.
Give me a chance
to buy you a big lunch.
You can buy me a spicy hotpot.
Men will buy me expensive meals.
What are you up to these days?
Would you like to work in Xingchen?
Xingchen has just started,
but Dongyang Medical
backs it up.
If you join us, you can do
purchasing and sales.
You can help me as well.
Xing,
I don't want to bother you.
And being best friends
is different from being partners.
If something is mishandled,
I don't want it to affect our relationship.
I don't think that will happen.
You and I can separate life and work.
But now,
I can't give you a very good offer.
Capable as you are,
if you weren't in this trouble,
I wouldn't get a chance to recruit you.
Xingchen needs you.
I need you, too.
I'll think about it.
Come on. Order more expensive food.
Miss Ji, Miss Li.
Mr. Lin.
What do you want me for?
I've reserved a private room.
Let's get in before we talk.
Miss Ji, you have good taste.
It's hard to reserve a private room
in this canteen.
Yeah. What do think of the food here?
Fancy.
Glad you like it.
Thank you.
Miss Ji,
I hear you're close to Mr. Han.
Not too bad. We were schoolmates in college.
A company Mr. Han favors
must be very good.
Miss Ji, you and your company
have an amazing future.
Thanks.
Come on. A toast to you, Miss Ji.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
Thank you for helping us.
My pleasure.
Just a little favor.
Miss Ji,
are you satisfied
with our product?
I am, of course.
Its performance
is as good as that of a foreign brand.
Good supporting service is provided, too.
That's right.
In terms of performance,
I'm very confident.
Well, Miss Ji,
since you think highly of our company...
Actually,
I do have a favor to ask.
Go ahead.
Look.
Now, business has got
rather difficult.
I'm going to make a request of you.
Could you please
introduce us to Mr. Han
for future cooperation?
The boss of Beidi is interesting.
You've invested in so many companies.
If every grantee
could introduce people to you,
you would be way too busy.
Yeah, Miss Ji.
To you, this is
a very small favor.
As you're close to Mr. Han,
when you introduce us,
he'll meet us for your sake.
Rest assured, Miss Ji.
We are
very tight-lipped.
We won't gossip to anyone
about your relationship
with Mr. Han.
After you help us,
we will offer
what you deserve.
Ji Xing used to be
a technical guy.
But she turns out to be smart.
She takes advantage of you, too.
Don't get angry, though.
Ambitious guys like her
usually do this.
You got me here on purpose, right?
What do you think?
- I...
- Mr. Lin.
Let's handle things one after another.
A toast to you.
(Make do with the lunch talk.)
Today, we become acquainted.
Hope we'll help each other in the future.
OK.
Mr. Han and Miss Ji
are both technical guys.
Your company has such good products
and talent spotters will appear.
When lunch is over,
I'll invite you to karaoke.
OK. We can keep talking there.
I have to get back
to write some materials.
Next, I'll have
Miss Li talk to you.
It's the critical phase of our product.
Miss Ji
has to keep Mr. Han informed.
Please understand, Mr. Lin.
Do not misunderstand
that we think less of you.
I won't.
Come on.
A toast to you, Miss Ji.
- To pleasant cooperation.
- To cooperation.
- Yes.
What else would you like to order?
Miss Li, take care of them.
I'm going to the toilet.
Let's eat.
Enjoy your food.
Mr. Han.
Let's talk.
Who were you eating with?
Mr. Lin from Beidi.
You bought the printer
from them?
Yes.
Has my name
helped a lot?
How does it feel
to cheat others with my name?
I used to think
you worked hard and steadily.
You were so stubborn that you offended people.
Turns out I underestimated you.
You're really wise.
You don't need a teacher.
I just told them
you were my schoolmate in college.
We were indeed schoolmates.
I didn't lie.
That's why I say you used a good trick.
They just got the wrong idea.
You think you are not wrong?
Would you dare to say
you didn't give them the idea?
What relationship
do they think we have?
An affair.
Right?
In this case,
since I'm slandered,
I'll make it true.
I...
Look at you.
You're so scared when I joke.
When someone else
says something dirtier,
can you bear that?
I don't care about pink news.
But it will hurt you.
If you can't bear the consequences,
don't take a shortcut.
To take a shortcut,
you have to pay a price.
♪Once again, you stand opposite me♪
♪Telling the worlds I'm not familiar with♪
♪They seem remote, but get in between us♪
♪We test each other
to see who'll first cross the line♪
♪If I can get closer to you♪
♪Can we have our memories overlapped?♪
♪Time puts walls up to keep my loneliness safe♪
♪Hope understanding will not endanger us♪
♪We each take a side♪
♪The chess board is set,
leaving us with a dilemma♪
♪We always expect each other to relent first♪
♪Before we're relieved♪
♪Pretend love isn't about winning♪
♪We each keep a half♪
♪Completing ourselves before revealing♪
♪Instead of expectations♪
♪We need each other's answer to judge♪
♪When love is a game of exchange♪
♪It is truly terrible♪