♪The original dream stays buried♪
♪Through the wind and the rain♪
♪It waits for the sunshine♪
♪To slowly revive♪
♪I want to travel through the skyscrapers♪
♪Even if the trip may be bumpy♪
♪Sooner or later the mist will clear♪
♪I'll realize my dream without hesitation♪
♪Through the crowd, it's hard to see♪
♪As cramped as the stars♪
♪Yearning for each other's sky♪
♪Forget we used to sparkle too♪
♪I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not hesitating at all♪
♪I'll seize the future, suspecting nothing♪
♪Because I'm dauntless♪
♪So, I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not giving up♪
♪I will always believe in miracles♪
♪Even if I have to look for them endlessly♪
=As Beautiful As You=
=Episode 20=
I'm in love with a lady.
She has a beautiful name.
Li Li.
- Lili?
- Yes.
Sounds uncool.
It's L-I, Li.
It means "more beautiful than phoenix".
Just like her name,
she's gorgeous.
I've never met a girl
as beautiful as her before.
So, it's like I fell in love with her
at first sight
and then loved her deeper.
Then pursue her.
I did.
But she has a boyfriend.
Even if she doesn't,
I'm not her cup of tea.
She's dazzling
while I'm ordinary.
Look at me all over.
Nothing makes me good enough for her.
Bro,
let me be honest.
What makes a man attractive
is that he's loyal to himself.
You should find out what makes you special.
Stand up and let me see.
Yeah.
You're handsome and fit.
But...
Why are you dressed like this?
Do you think
I still stand a chance?
Yes.
Yes, of course.
To be honest,
I'm the owner of this bar.
I've seen a lot of men
just like you.
Then tell me.
How should I be dressed
to make myself
look charming?
OK. For the sake we get acquainted,
let me give you a new look.
OK.
Wait a minute.
I'll write it down.
(Su Zhizhou, Xingchen Technology)
You're from Xingchen Technology?
You know our company?
Yes. I'm quite familiar.
Your investor
is my nephew.
Your boss Ji Xing
and her best friends.
Tu Xiaomeng and Li Li...
We're very familiar.
That's right.
Wait.
Is Li Li you just mentioned...?
Shh.
Keep it to yourself.
Don't tell anyone else.
- Fine.
- I beg you.
I know. I get this a lot.
I'll keep it secret for you.
Fine. Don't bother to write it down.
Come with me.
Where are we going?
How on earth
did you get
this ordinary programmer style
from all these fancy clothes?
Programmer style?
It feels comfortable, I think.
The root of all evil
is being ordinary.
How can you be
the most handsome guy?
Forget it. I'll pick an outfit for you.
Weird.
Really weird.
Put on your suit.
Spin around.
Twitch your mouth.
Why do you look
like a funny comedian?
Oh, I know.
Your appearance decides
how fashionable you look.
Don't be discouraged.
You aren't as handsome as me.
But you're above the average.
How about we stop?
I don't think I'm a fashion type.
My fashionable outfits
would never fail.
There must be a perfect outfit for you.
Attractive, young, and fashionable...
Oh, yes.
Morning.
Bonjour.
Who did that?
Me.
Mr. Su.
You look quite...
Bright.
Thanks.
Our department will have a meeting.
The Purchasing Department should attend it.
Inform them.
OK.
Miss Li.
Anything urgent?
No.
If you're busy, get to your work.
I'm going out for a moment.
Your outfit is...
Extraordinary.
Xia.
Ask Miss Ji to sign this.
OK.
Extraordinary?
Is it a compliment
or is it sarcasm?
Li made a very clear point.
You look good.
But never dress like this again.
I told him I wasn't the wild type.
You're on vacation?
I have a day off. So, I'm here to see you.
See me?
But you didn't visit me
when you had days off before.
Oh, I see.
You took all the trouble
to recommend Shao Yichen to me.
He's a handsome talent, indeed.
No wonder my niece did so much for him.
Don't make fun of me, uncle.
I only recommended him.
He wouldn't be hired
until he was screened
by your hospital.
And remember.
Don't tell Yichen about this.
Or he'll feel sick about it.
Is he very busy today?
Why do I not see him?
He's been busy
with the clinical test
on 3D medical printing
I started with Xingchen Technology.
He's in the Innovation Center, I think.
Why don't you just call him?
OK.
Mr. Han.
This is the volunteer's recovery report.
The volunteer has started
basic rehabilitation exercises.
The intervertebral cage and his bones
fuse very well, too.
What have you been up to lately?
Yes. A tricky question.
Think carefully before you reply.
Can you give me something
for reference?
No.
Recently,
I've left some small things
to my subordinates.
I signed up
for an inspection trip to Germany.
I want to study further
and quickly figure out
Xingchen's product positioning.
A barely good answer.
Boss, the meeting is coming up.
Don't limit yourself.
Think outside the box.
What do you mean?
Think for yourself.
Oh, Miss Ji, I guess you forgot
something very important.
What is it?
Regularly tell me
how Dahuang is doing.
Dahuang.
Pretty cat.
(Han Ting)
It looks thinner.
Feed it more tinned food.
OK, boss.
(Ji Xing)
You've been back for only a few days
and you're going out again?
Here. Have some juice.
Yeah.
I'm going to Germany.
Germany?
It's a far and strange country.
Why are you going there?
I'm going there
to learn something
from excellent old manufacturers
of medical devices
and broaden my horizons.
OK. I support you in your career.
We should work hard.
Unless we die...
We should always learn.
- Come on.
So cliche.
Dahuang,
cheer up for Mom, OK?
Oh, my cat.
It lies here so comfortably.
I was taking photos of it just now.
Good cat.
It's asleep.
Qiuzi, come on in.
Yichen,
congrats on working at Xinggang Hospital.
Thank you.
I'm making soup. Have a seat.
OK.
Yichen,
you're done cooking?
I had meant to cook for you
for celebration.
You're my guest.
And you did me such a big favor.
How can I let you cook?
Qiuzi,
you were taking care of me
so that I had time
to prepare for the interview.
And the reference materials you gave me
really helped a lot.
Thank you.
You're always excellent.
Even without my help,
you would be admitted, too.
I brought you some wine. Taste it.
Oh, plum wine.
Yes. I tasted some and found it good.
So, I brought you one bottle.
What? How does it taste?
I haven't tasted it.
We'll drink together.
Taste it now.
OK.
Tastes good.
I knew you would like it.
Looks like you have
a similar taste to mine.
You made me my favorite dish,
Kung Pao chicken.
Taste it.
How does it taste?
Delicious.
Thanks.
Drink it.
Li, recently,
you've been glowing with romance.
You must be in sweet love.
I have?
This boyfriend seems different.
But considering how fast
Li has a new boyfriend,
I wonder when they'll break up.
This one is kind of different.
He's my cup of tea.
I really don't want to break up with him.
So, you're serious.
When will you have us meet him?
Not until Xing is back from Germany.
You guys can also
check him for me,
Ji Xing.
No problem.
Have you packed the euro cash
exchanged from the bank?
Yes.
It's here.
These days, I'll leave Xingchen
to you and Su Zhizhou.
If anything happens,
you can call me,
regardless of the jet lag.
And Tu Xiaomeng.
Dahuang is naughty.
If it disobeys you, deduct its cat food.
Don't worry.
Leave Dahuang to me.
I'll take good care of it.
Well, Xing,
if you have time, can you
buy me some skincare products
from the duty-free shop?
I'll send you the list later.
No problem.
Send me the photos.
Thanks.
Xing,
when you're there alone,
you have to stay safe.
If anything happens,
tell us in the group chat.
I will.
Come and press the suitcase for me.
Like this.
I'll go help her.
- Have you packed your passport?
- Yes.
ID card.
You should carry it with you.
Why do you keep it here?
Why?
The shoes...
Don't press it now. Wait.
Put the shoes here,
or they would be broken.
- Don't put them here.
- High-heeled shoes.
I insist on putting them here.
- I have some. Don't go.
- Where?
I'll put it here.
Hello, sweethearts.
I was so busy with my best friends
that I started late today.
You can't wait, can you?
Thank you.
Thank you for your gifts.
Today,
what do you want me to do,
to sing or talk with you?
Today, Smart Lemon looks
really smart.
(Lu Linjia)
You know I'm doing live streaming.
How dare you disturb me?
(Smart Lemon)
Long time no see.
I'm here to give you some money.
Your live streaming in my bar
worked very well.
Many visitors claimed to be your fans.
It's your KPI.
The email has been sent
for fee confirmation.
Read it when it's over.
After you confirm it, I'll pay.
(Smart Lemon)
In this case,
I'm no longer sleepy.
I'll confirm it now.
Today, I'm in such a good mood.
What about you, guys?
How about
I sing a happy song?
Miss Ji.
Mr. Han?
Excuse me.
I should go.
Hello, madam.
- This way, please.
- Thanks.
Excuse me.
A blanket, please.
- OK. Just a minute.
- Thank you.
- Madam, your blanket.
- Thanks.
♪The face in my memory gives me mood swings♪
♪It tells something♪
(Han Ting)
Why are you alone?
What about your MBA classmates?
♪This is the man I'm waiting for♪
They went there one day earlier.
(Ji Xing)
(Han Ting)
It's hard to get a taxi when the plane lands.
I'll give you a ride.
♪Every rainy day, you're the first to appear♪
OK. Thanks.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our flight is about to take off.
Please fasten your seatbelt,
place your tray table back,
and set your seat back upright.
(Munich, Germany)
♪We don't need to accept each other too fast♪
♪Nor do we need to love too rashly♪
Hey, madam. Please wake up.
The plane has landed.
♪I'm not absent♪
♪At the crossroad, I'll hold your hand tightly♪
♪We don't need to accept each other too fast♪
♪Nor do we need to love too rashly♪
♪We stay where we are♪
Miss Ji.
Mr. Han.
Thank you for your neck pillow.
Are you here on a business trip?
To inspect Dongyang Base.
Which hotel do you live in?
Weeknd Hotel.
Me, too.
(Weeknd Hotel)
Weeknd Hotel.
What specifically will you scout?
It's all in this manual.
(Content, Introduction)
So, this is the trip
you signed up for.
How much does it cost?
45,000.
Not a very high cost for a useless trip.
Is it really so useless?
I looked these companies up.
They're good.
You can only read
what they want you to read.
Pen.
(Corporation Directory)
(Kerber Technology)
Kerber
(Hans Technology)
and Hans.
They used to be glorious.
But now, they're in decline.
Few people in China know it.
I really didn't know
they were in decline.
According to the materials, they're powerful.
It's OK. You can visit them.
Take them as a reminder.
If you can't keep up with the times,
they'll be your lesson to learn.
Tabea and Seme.
These two companies
have never had highlights.
In the name of "Made in Germany",
they fool foreign companies.
But on the professional domestic forum,
there are many compliments on them.
Long posts.
Take them as negative examples.
Correct the mistakes if there are some.
Deman, Bivar, and AJ Tech.
These three companies
can be your focus.
These are the top three
I'm interested in.
Deman has the top technology
and advanced equipment.
Bivar
focuses on management.
Their management mode is worth learning.
AJ Tech is excellent
in innovative research.
(Innovative)
It has been setting the trend.
Deman has...
Top technology
and advanced equipment.
(WEEKND HOTEL)
- Hello.
- Welcome to Weeknd Hotel.
Miss Ji, give it to me.
Thanks.
Your passport photo is handsome.
What are you doing here?
Where are you going?
The tour starts this afternoon.
I'm going out for a walk.
It's the first time I've been in Munich.
I'm going out, too.
Shall we go together?
OK. Let's go.
Go.
Looks like the pigeons don't like you.
I want to take photos of them.
Here.
Where did you get this?
Stores here
offer free pigeon food to visitors.
You're indeed a local guide.
Hi, pigeons.
One.
Two.
Pretty.
Nice.
One more.
You can't photograph them
without their permission.
Oh, I see.
Let's ask them
to take a photo of us.
Could you please take a photo of us?
What did she say?
She asked if you could take a photo of them.
OK, OK.
One, two, three.
Is she your girlfriend?
Not yet.
This one looks good.
She's as cute as an angel.
Yes, yes.
That's right.
Try harder, then.
OK.
Good.
Thank you.
- Thank you. You're gorgeous.
- Gorgeous.
Really gorgeous.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Bye-bye.
Did you understand?
I guess they said thank you.
I can get it.
What did they say later?
What does that mean?
"You're gorgeous."
Slow down.
♪Everything you wanted me to be♪
♪I tried to let you be my destiny♪
♪The stars are shining thru the day and night♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪Hold my hand across the land and sea♪
♪Call my name from distance guiding me♪
♪We are the ones that God keeps blessing♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪You are everything♪
♪Everything you wanted me to be♪
♪I tried to let you be my destiny♪
♪The stars are shining thru the day and night♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪Hold my hand across the land and sea♪
♪Call my name from distance guiding me♪
♪We are the ones that God keeps blessing♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪You are everything♪
(Xing, Lemon, Li, and Qiuzi)
(Li Li)
Mr. Han is also there?
What are you laughing at?
Look. Ji Xing is having so much fun.
When you're not busy,
how about we visit Germany, too?
There are many fun places
in Germany.
I didn't tell you
Ji Xing went to Germany.
How do you know?
I've been there before.
I recognized it.
I wondered why you were so busy.
So, Ji Xing is away.
I can hardly see you lately.
I'll make it up to you tonight.
Is your fridge that big?
I'll get them for my friends.
This one is for you.
But I don't drink.
That's why I give it to you.
When I drink next time,
you can clink it with me.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
How will you go this afternoon?
A car will be sent.
On this scout trip, pay more attention.
Learn from good experience
and take warnings from bad examples.
This is so adorable.
OK.
Excuse me.
This one.
How long have I been here?
For six days.
Shall I cancel
tomorrow's schedules for you?
(Ji Xing)
Are you available today?
I'll see you in the hotel canteen
in ten minutes.
(Han Ting)
Mr. Han.
What have you got?
I think every enterprise
makes me think
and introspect.
For example?
Hello. What would you like?
Water.
You said Deman,
Bivar, and AJ Tech are good companies.
I focused on these three companies.
I think their handlers
are very humble.
They give me a feeling
that they're really steady.
Here's your water.
Then I realize
some companies succeed for a reason.
And what you said at Shenzhen Summit...
"Start with small businesses
and seize the chance.
Conform to the market and seek for demands."
So, you came to Germany
to verify what I said.
No, I just...
After I experienced it personally,
I could truly feel it.
What about other companies?
I also visited Tabea and Seme.
They're a little bit boastful.
The bosses and the employees
kept talking about dreams.
But when asked about detailed businesses,
they couldn't say anything.
So, it's a very important thing
to follow an excellent leader
and learn from good companies.
Tell me. What do you want?
I'm going back to China the day after tomorrow.
Before that,
may I visit
Dongyang Base?
At two tomorrow afternoon,
see you in front of the hotel.
That's great. You approved.
Have you had lunch?
No.
The treat is on me.
Nice language.
Here's the menu.
(Dongyang Group)
Dongyang Base
was established in October, 2017.
There was only one building.
Phase I covered nine acres.
So far, Phase II has been completed.
Twenty acres in total.
That is Phase III.
It's under construction.
What is that building for?
That's the R&amp;D center.
And the lab is over there.
Beside it is the production site.
Such a great place.
Welcome
to Dongyang Overseas R&amp;D Center.
Robot Huang is here for you.
Its name is Huang?
H-U-A-N-G.
Huang is a robot guide.
It will show us
around every exhibition hall.
Hello, Mr. Han.
- Hello.
- Follow me.
Please move forward with me.
Is its system
in Chinese?
By distinguishing
our appearances
and conversations,
it can tell we are Chinese.
In this exhibition hall
(Schematic of AI Medical)
are AI products
of Dongyang R&amp;D Base.
There are different sections
according to functions.
Please come along with me.
OK.
This wall of photos
records Dongyang's development in Munich.
(Unsuccessful Products)
Why are unsuccessful products
exhibited up there?
The glow of success fades away quickly.
But lessons from failure
urge us to move forward.
Then why were they
unsuccessful?
Technology bottlenecks.
Mainly the inaccurate analyses
about the market.
Actually, developing a new product
is like gambling.
Some people are just proficient
in principles and algorithms.
But no one can win all the time.
Dongyang is a big company
with great power.
It can tolerate errors.
Once a small company like us
makes a mistake, it may be destroyed.
I've been thinking
about Xingchen's product positioning.
I don't want to pick the wrong product.
I even studied all the products of Hanhai.
I thought about competing with them
but didn't want to be crushed.
It's good to be competitive.
But don't let your rival disturb you.
You should pick a product
based on your own conditions.
A company
can't be competitive
without a feature or a style.
There's even a basketball gym?
Yeah. I came here
every time I was stressed out.
When you were in Germany,
you were stressed out?
But later, I figured it out.
Stress would bring motivation.
I just need to get my mind right
and move past it.
Can you shoot?
Of course.
Let me teach you.
Here.
♪I tried to let you be my destiny♪
♪The stars are shining thru the day and night♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪Hold my hand across the land and sea♪
♪Call my name from distance guiding me♪
♪We are the ones that God keeps blessing♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪Hold my hand across the land and sea♪
♪Call my name from distance guiding me♪
♪We are the ones that God keeps blessing♪
♪Restlessly♪
♪You are everything♪
♪Time moves forward♪
♪Two hearts connect♪
♪Even if all the lights go out♪
♪The world with you around♪
♪Is everything to me♪
♪Gradually, I forget how it hurts♪
♪I count and count the days we were together♪
♪How I miss those highlight moments♪
♪The day will finally come♪
♪I'm scared of the pain♪
♪But I can accept it♪
♪When I break out of it, I shine♪
♪I run crazily♪
♪I search desperately♪
♪For your bright face♪
♪Then my eyes are red♪
♪Because you're still by my side♪
♪Everything you wanted me to be♪
♪I tried to let you be my destiny♪
♪The stars are shining thru the day and night♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪Hold my hand across the land and sea♪
♪Call my name from distance guiding me♪
♪We are the ones that God keeps blessing♪
♪Restlessly♪
♪You are everything♪
Sausage platter, tuna salad.
Beer bread.
Chicken nuggets.
That white beer
looks so good.
How about some more stout beer?
A glass of white beer
and a glass of stout beer.
OK. A moment, please.
You're a stranger here.
If you get drunk, no one will recognize you.
Why does it sound like I'm a drunkard?
I witnessed that.
You must be tired. Have more water.
Tastes great.
Come on, cheers.
Thanks for your care
these days.
You're welcome.
Doing sports really helps with stress.
Now, I have a lot of ideas.
I have a lot of concerns, too.
Regret starting a company?
No.
Don't stress yourself out.
Take your time.
I won't withdraw from Xingchen
just because you're slow.
Taste this salad.
It's super delicious.
Wait.
An investor cares most about the return,
doesn't he?
Do you actually
think less of Xingchen and me?
I don't mind if you're slow
because starting a company
is like living a life.
Everyone has his pace.
Don't bother to catch up with anyone
or any other company.
Make your own way.
One day, you will proposer.
You don't drink wine.
But you're so good at inspiring.
Slow down. Don't get drunk.
I won't.
When someone is happy,
he won't get drunk.
So, you're happy today?
The music here is so beautiful.
German sounds sexy.
Beautiful, indeed.
That's too bad you can't drink.
Be careful.
I'm OK.
Two glasses of beer won't get me drunk.
Good evening.
Oh, Han Ting.
When you were in Germany over the years,
did you have
a relationship with a girl?
Did you?
- No.
- Really?
Your appearance...
What?
In Germany, I had to learn German,
take classes,
and start up a business.
I was in no mood for love.
I didn't have a colorful life as you did.
You enjoyed work and love.
Why do I think you're satirizing me?
In your eyes,
do I only satirize you all the time?
Not really.
Then what do you think of me?
♪Everything you wanted me to be♪
♪I tried to let you be my destiny♪
♪The stars are shining thru the day and night♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪You are everything♪
♪Once again, you stand opposite me♪
♪Telling the worlds I'm not familiar with♪
♪They seem remote, but get in between us♪
♪We test each other
to see who'll first cross the line♪
♪If I can get closer to you♪
♪Can we have our memories overlapped?♪
♪Time puts walls up to keep my loneliness safe♪
♪Hope understanding will not endanger us♪
♪We each take a side♪
♪The chess board is set,
leaving us with a dilemma♪
♪We always expect each other to relent first♪
♪Before we're relieved♪
♪Pretend love isn't about winning♪
♪We each keep a half♪
♪Completing ourselves before revealing♪
♪Instead of expectations♪
♪We need each other's answer to judge♪
♪When love is a game of exchange♪
♪It is truly terrible♪