♪The original dream stays buried♪
♪Through the wind and the rain♪
♪It waits for the sunshine♪
♪To slowly revive♪
♪I want to travel through the skyscrapers♪
♪Even if the trip may be bumpy♪
♪Sooner or later the mist will clear♪
♪I'll realize my dream without hesitation♪
♪Through the crowd, it's hard to see♪
♪As cramped as the stars♪
♪Yearning for each other's sky♪
♪Forget we used to sparkle too♪
♪I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not hesitating at all♪
♪I'll seize the future, suspecting nothing♪
♪Because I'm dauntless♪
♪So, I'm going to the land of dream♪
♪Not giving up♪
♪I will always believe in miracles♪
♪Even if I have to look for them endlessly♪
=As Beautiful As You=
=Episode 31=
One day, when Hanhai
is powerful enough,
will it...?
Will it annex Xingchen?
Xingchen plans to go its own way.
But someday, will it
have nowhere to go?
Even when Han Ting was in Germany,
he invested in Hanhai.
When he was just back in China,
he had a shaky foundation.
Han Yuan could have a lot of ways
to stop him from merging Hanhai.
Then he made a pledge,
buying himself some time
to reform Dongyang Medical
and make preparations for Hanhai's merger.
As for Xingchen...
It's just a smokescreen.
Xing.
Xing?
(Merger Proposal of Hanhai and Xingchen)
(When was Dongyang Base built in Germany?)
(Hanhai Technology)
(Investment Agreement of Hanhai Technology)
(Merger Proposal of Hanhai and Xingchen)
(The name is supposed to be
"Hanhai Xingchen Technology".)
Come in.
What? What brings you to see me?
Series-A funding.
Take your seats.
Now, many investors want
to invest in Xingchen.
We have enough options.
But you should choose one soon.
What do you guys think?
Should we
prioritize Dongyang Medical?
No.
With another financing,
their shares and our shares
will be diluted.
If we take the investment from an outsider,
with a majority of the stock,
we'll still have the decision-making power.
But if we still take it from Dongyang Medical,
we may possibly be...
A total figurehead.
Considering Xing and Mr. Han's relationship,
I don't think it'll happen.
Love is love.
Business is business.
Xing,
we just give you some advice.
You make your own choice soon.
I'll think about it.
OK. I'll go back to work.
What happened?
You don't look very well.
I'm fine. I guess I've been too tired.
I just need some rest.
When the financing is over,
have some days off
for some good rest.
Boss, will Miss Ji not go with you?
She has left.
One day, when Hanhai is powerful enough,
will it...?
Will it annex Xingchen?
Xingchen plans to go its own way.
But someday, will it
have nowhere to go?
The market needs Hanhai.
It needs Xingchen, too.
You don't need to compare.
Han Ting.
Do you love me?
How do you define love?
You'll die for me.
Without me, your world will collapse.
That's not the love I understand.
What is your definition, then?
First, match.
Xing,
"match" isn't a pathetic word.
“Love” isn't noble, either.
It's hard to find
the right person.
Why do you get me here so early?
What's up?
The water is boiling away. Don't you make tea?
She knew it.
Who?
Ji Xing.
You finally told her.
I no longer need to worry.
She knew it from someone else.
Not me.
What did she say? Where's she?
Discussing Series-A funding with Chang He.
Chang He?
Why don't you stop her immediately?
She's angry now.
There's no point in talking.
You've made up your mind?
For this investment in Xingchen,
I'll use a third-party investment company.
No word will get out.
In this way,
the directors of Dongyang Medical
will approve the investment.
Miss Ji, don't worry.
Can you make it quick?
Of course.
OK.
(Series-A Funding Agreement)
Boss,
Miss Ji has agreed to the cooperation
with a Series-A funding company.
Shall we talk to her?
No need.
Hold the board meeting.
OK.
Congratulations, Mr. Chang,
for investing in Xingchen.
Thanks, Ms. Yuan.
Without your help
at the board meeting,
the financing proposal
wouldn't have been smoothly approved.
Mr. Chang,
it has nothing to do with me.
Ms. Yuan, don't worry.
I'll keep it very secret.
When the directors realize
Tongke has invested
in Xingchen's third-party company,
become a shareholder of Xingchen,
and touched Dongyang Medical's assets,
I'll see what Han Ting can explain.
Impressive, Ms. Yuan.
This time, even if Han Ting
fulfills his pledge,
the directors will still blame him.
Then your next logical step
is to take back Dongyang Medical.
But Han Ting always
has many precautions.
At this financing meeting,
he cast a yes vote
without hesitation.
I fear he has some other plans.
I used a third-party company.
It's normal that he doesn't know it's me.
Even if he does,
he can't
overturn the directors' resolution.
Ms. Yuan, don't worry.
Why are you back?
I'll live with you for a few days.
You don't want me here?
I want you. I totally do.
When you were away,
I missed you so much.
I made some soup. Would you like some?
No. I want some sleep.
Fine. Go get some sleep.
When you wake up,
we'll go have a big meal.
(Dongyang Group)
I will redraft
the sales goals
for the next month.
OK.
The meeting is over.
Dismissed.
Xing.
Our Series-A funding
has been approved by Dongyang Medical.
We can move to the next step.
(Series-A Funding Agreement)
OK. I'll have it arranged.
Fine. I'll go back to work.
Anything wrong with the financing?
How come?
It's very smooth. Don't worry.
These days, you've been absent-minded.
Is everything all right?
Yes. Don't worry about me.
I'm really fine.
Tonight, I'll dine at Xingyue Club
with Mr. Ma of Kebo Material.
Will you go?
I have something else to handle.
You guys go. I won't.
Fine. I'll go with Zhizhou, then.
Don't put all the pressure on yourself.
You have us.
I'm fine.
I won't.
Congratulations.
You've got shares of Xingchen.
Mr. Chang, you keep your word.
It's the first gift you give me.
Thanks.
Next, how will you
deal with Xingchen?
Check this.
(Share Purchase Agreement)
(Party A: Dongyang Medical)
Party B: Tongke Medical)
(Party A agrees to sell
all shares of Guanghua to Party B.)
(Party A: Dongyang Medical)
Party B: Tongke Medical)
What do you mean?
Mr. Han.
You wanted to see me in such a hurry.
What for?
Mr. Chang, I guess you know that.
I know a lot of things.
But I'm not clear
about every single one.
(Share Purchase Agreement)
Mr. Han, why are you so sure
that you're offering
what I want?
Everybody knows what you want,
don't they?
You offer to exchange
all your shares of Guanghua
for my few shares
of Xingchen.
So, Mr. Han,
you really care about Xingchen.
Will you or will you accept?
I appreciate your sincerity, Mr. Han.
I just wonder
if Miss Ji Xing
will be upset.
That is not your concern.
Han Ting offered me
all his shares of Guanghua.
I couldn't say no.
So, in his eyes,
Guanghua is just like rubbish.
He dumped it so causally.
But I take Guanghua
as my treasure.
Bay is important.
But what I want more
is that you're no longer involved
with Han Ting.
He thinks the same way, right?
Mr. Chang, don't worry.
From this day on,
Guanghua and Tongke
will be real allies.
Mr. Ma, thank you
for supporting Xingchen all the time.
We couldn't have come this far
without the superior materials
from your company.
It's very kind of you.
Above all,
Xingchen has made
very good products.
My materials
are just like the cherry on top.
Well, I also want to thank you
for buying materials from my company.
Come on. A toast to you, Mr. Su and Miss Li.
Mr. Ma.
I'm a technical guy.
So, I know it very well.
Without your superior materials,
our product research
couldn't have gone so smoothly.
So, now,
I should propose a toast to you.
Hope our future cooperation
will go more smoothly.
- Cheers.
- OK. Hope everything goes well.
Cheers.
Mr. Ma, sorry to disturb you.
There you are, Mr. Xiao.
Oh, I know everybody here.
Come on. A toast to you.
OK.
Miss Li, you have a stomach problem.
Don't drink wine.
Have a beverage instead.
Miss Li can't drink, indeed.
But to show
our sincerity,
I'll propose a toast to you
on behalf of Miss Li.
I have things to do.
I'll leave you alone.
Have a good time.
The treat is on me.
OK. See you.
Come on, Mr. Ma.
Let's continue.
OK.
Mr. Su, you can hold your liquor.
Come on. Let's drink.
You flatter me.
Mr. Ma, we're glad to have you here.
- Enjoy the food.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Come on, Mr. Ma. Don't just drink.
Taste the dishes.
Here.
Madam,
your meal is on the house.
You don't need to pay.
No need. I'll pay.
How much? I'll scan and pay.
Sorry,
but Mr. Xiao told us
not to charge you.
Let me see the bill, then.
Thanks.
Li Li.
I was about to see you.
Just now, I asked the chef
to make you some sweet yam soup
with honey and milk.
It will be delivered soon.
You have a weak stomach.
Keep it well.
No need.
I transferred the money to you.
I didn't mean to come here tonight.
Mr. Ma picked this place.
I want no connection to you anymore.
You don't need to do anything for me.
Li Li.
Li Li, give me a minute.
I really want to talk with you.
There's nothing we can talk about.
Li Li, listen to me.
Listen.
We can have a try.
Forget it.
If you had said this earlier,
I would be happy.
But now, I've figured it out.
Let's just split.
It was all my fault.
Don't be angry. Give me...
Mr. Xiao,
don't push it.
It's between Li Li and me.
Mr. Su,
do not interfere.
Li Li, give me a second...
When can you stop hurting her?
If you break your promise again,
what can she do?
Say no more.
Li Li,
what is wrong with you?
He fooled you again and again.
When do you say enough is enough?
The old you
recklessly slapped your client
who discredited you.
But look at you now.
Will you really trample on your principles
again and again like this?
This isn't the lady
I'm in love with.
Li Li.
- I...
- Xiao Yixiao.
He's right.
When I was waiting for you to change,
I conceded too much.
Now that you have principles,
stick to your bottom line.
I don't like you this way.
Nor can I allow myself
to keep conceding like this.
We're done here.
Tired, huh? I'm washing some strawberries.
You can eat some later.
I've cooperated with Chang He.
The third-party company
of Xingchen's Series-A funding
is Tongke.
I know.
You're not angry?
You want me to be angry?
You have nothing to say to me?
I should ask you this.
Aren't you supposed to tell me
why you did that?
Tongke is my competitor.
What were you thinking?
Do you even care?
You have Hanhai.
Do you really care who Xingchen belongs to?
Or do you think everything
is under your control?
You'd rather destroy Xingchen
than give it to someone else.
I invest in other companies
and hold shares of Hanhai.
What is the problem?
I'm OK with other companies.
But Hanhai...
Why did you keep it from me?
It was a trade secret
and I couldn't tell you before.
Why on earth did you invest in Xingchen?
To have a smokescreen for Hanhai?
It was you
who needed financing.
Without me,
could Xingchen come this far?
Indeed, you helped Xingchen.
But it's my hard work, too.
I designed the products,
pushed the clinical tests,
and found partner agencies
all by myself!
Xingchen is mine,
not yours.
You have no right to play with it.
How do I play with it?
Did I interfere with its strategy
or did I do anything harmful?
Xingchen's development
does good to me.
Why would I destroy it?
Right.
You don't want to destroy Xingchen
because it develops well enough.
But if it can develop better
just like Hanhai,
you won't leave it uncontrolled, huh?
That's why you want
the merger of Hanhai and Xingchen.
Xing.
A startup without a background
always has a hard time.
Instead of being crushed by a rival,
it's better to be acquired by a big company.
When a small company wants to grow,
its best chance
is to develop fast
on the shoulders of giants.
Hanhai and Xingchen
are affiliated with Dongyang Medical.
Instead of a useless internal competition,
a favorable integration will be better.
Opportunity and choice
are always more important than hard work.
Far more important.
This is reality.
So, I yielded to reality.
I chose to rely
on Tongke.
I ripped you off for interest.
Shouldn't you praise me for what I've learned?
You have reasons.
I have my preferences and interests.
I chose Tongke which I preferred.
You can certainly make your choice.
But you need capital first.
Do you have it?
You don't.
I can disapprove of your choice
because I have 33.4%
of Xingchen's stock.
You set me up
just because you knew
I wouldn't give you a hard time.
Have you thought about it?
What if I give you a hard time?
I was living here for a long time
and keeping you company.
I deserve some reward, don't I?
A generous man like you
will not give me a hard time.
You'll have to stay for a little longer.
(Share Purchase Agreement)
Chang He sold me
his 30% shares of Xingchen.
Now, I hold 53.38%
of Xingchen's stock.
(Party A: Dongyang Medical)
Party B: Tongke Medical)
He...
You...
But you're competitors.
Because I exchanged
something he wanted more
for his shares.
I told you.
In business, there are no permanent enemies
or permanent friends.
Only the exchange of benefits lasts forever.
Why did you do that?
If you were only worried
that I would usurp Xingchen,
you could have told me.
For our relationship,
would I not give it to you?
What is our relationship?
What on earth do you take me for?
A pet?
A puppet?
Your concern for me
and your promises... Are they real?
Or is that just a trick
you're good at
and you can do it to any other girl?
Do you think I have so much time
to pamper and cheat you?
You always have poor judgment.
Why did Tongke invest in Xingchen?
Have you thought about it?
Because they want to collude with Han Yuan!
Then they'll crush me!
Han Yuan is using Xingchen
to take back Dongyang Medical.
For interests,
they'll soon sell you.
Can you understand?
You knew
Tongke would do that.
You even wanted them to succeed!
So you could get the evidence
of Han Yuan's leaking information to Chang He.
You got something on her.
To you, Xingchen
is just a pawn!
Pawn?
If it was only a pawn,
why would I try so hard
to get it back from Tongke?
Xing,
as long as you want it,
Xingchen is still yours.
(Party A: Dongyang Medical)
Party B: Tongke Medical)
This is horrible.
Stop telling me
what we have to do
in the business circle.
Stop using such excuses!
In my eyes, you're just hypocritical!
You're indifferent and mercenary!
You're heartless!
Cut it out, Ji Xing!
When we were together,
we could be so happy.
You celebrated my birthday.
You shared your location.
You even used my birthdate
as the password to your door.
You took me to see your family.
I...
You...
I thought you adored me
and then I fell in love with you.
Or I wouldn't have loved you!
I indeed adore you.
You're just a liar.
You're nice to me
just because I'm right for you, huh?
Liar!
- Listen.
- Stay away! Don't touch me!
- Listen, Ji Xing.
- I don't want to listen!
I just don't! Don't touch me!
You're terrible.
Really terrible.
(Dongyang Group)
Dongyang Medical announced
that they held shares of Hanhai Technology.
To such great news of Dongyang Medical,
the market reacted immediately.
The stock price of Dongyang Medical rocketed
(Honeycomb News)
and hit an all-time high.
Dongyang Medical vigorously develops
3D medical printing.
After investing in Xingchen Technology,
a cutting-edge startup,
Dongyang Medical holds shares
of the leading company, Hanhai Technology.
It's spreading tracks in business.
It's reported that Dongyang Medical
will integrate Hanhai and Xingchen.
(Dongyang Group)
Mr. Chen, long time no see.
Yeah.
But in the future,
we will often meet.
I look forward
to more communication with you.
Actually, Xingchen used to take Hanhai
as its strongest rival.
Unexpectedly,
we have the same investor.
Mr. Chen, did you know it a long time ago?
Miss Ji,
I'm not having
social pleasantries
just because we have
the same investor.
From the bottom of my heart,
I appreciate Xingchen's products
and corporate culture.
I admire you, too.
In your previous speech, you said
you would do your best
to make a difference
for ordinary people.
I've kept that in mind.
Thanks.
Actually, I invited you here
to talk with you
about the merger of our companies.
But Miss Ji, why don't you
just talk to Mr. Han?
Because you're in charge.
I want to tell you
about my requirements
so that I can appease my employees.
I understand.
Actually,
I proposed to Mr. Han
about the merge of Xingchen.
But he rejected me.
Later, when he brought it up again,
he emphasized
Hanhai would not merge Xingchen,
but have an organic integration.
If you have any requirements,
feel free to let me know.
I'll be sure to tell Mr. Han.
I have only two requirements.
First,
after the merger,
you must not fire my employees
unless they make a mistake.
Second,
retain Xingchen's right of independent R&amp;D.
OK.
Miss Ji, please give me some time.
I'll talk to Mr. Han.
OK. I'll wait for your reply.
No problem.
I'll go up, then.
OK. I'll let you work.
Mr. Han,
Miss Ji had two requirements.
If you approve,
I'll put them in the merger proposal.
(Merger Proposal of Hanhai and Xingchen)
She had only two requirements?
Yes.
Miss Ji looked calm.
This is a business strategy.
You also considered what was best for Xingchen.
I believe Miss Ji will understand.
Don't worry about the merger.
I'll take care of it.
I talked to Mr. Chen of Hanhai.
He will reply.
Are you OK?
Mr. Han...
Mr. Han has his considerations.
The three of us will
just take care of Xingchen.
OK.
Xing,
we all listen to you.
(Chen Ningyang)
Miss Ji,
Mr. Han approved your requirements.
The merger proposal
will be emailed to you later.
Get everybody to a meeting.
Miss Ji,
is the news true?
This is what I'm going to tell you now.
Hanhai and Xingchen
will be merged.
Really?
Miss Ji,
what do we do?
After the merger with Hanhai,
will we be fired or replaced?
I know what you're worried about.
I talked to Mr. Chen of Hanhai.
He revised
the merger proposal.
Mr. Han approved it, too.
First, Hanhai Xingchen
will not fire our employees
unless you make a mistake.
Second,
Xingchen's right
of independent R&amp;D will be retained.
You'll still work in this place.
After the merger,
you'll share the welfare and right
as you have now.
Actually, the merger isn't a bad thing.
Hanhai started five years
earlier than us.
Their materials and research results
are more exhaustive than ours.
They're strong and powerful.
I believe talents like you guys
will have a bigger stage
after the merger.
It's an opportunity and a challenge.
Xing,
what are we going to do next?
Next, you will
go over your work at hand
and get ready for the merger.
Their guys will be sent for the takeover.
As long as you guys stay,
Xingchen will not fall apart.
Miss Ji,
after the merger,
we will not disgrace Xingchen.
♪Once again, you stand opposite me♪
♪Telling the worlds I'm not familiar with♪
♪They seem remote, but get in between us♪
♪We test each other
to see who'll first cross the line♪
♪If I can get closer to you♪
♪Can we have our memories overlapped?♪
♪Time puts walls up to keep my loneliness safe♪
♪Hope understanding will not endanger us♪
♪We each take a side♪
♪The chess board is set,
leaving us with a dilemma♪
♪We always expect each other to relent first♪
♪Before we're relieved♪
♪Pretend love isn't about winning♪
♪We each keep a half♪
♪Completing ourselves before revealing♪
♪Instead of expectations♪
♪We need each other's answer to judge♪
♪When love is a game of exchange♪
♪It is truly terrible♪