What war have you won?
First come is first served.
Finally, all work is done.
Yinesima died in July.
YOU CAN'T Türktersk
Why have you been forced to fight in such a Crow
I wanted to lead you toyt
Why won't life continue.
I can't find the answer
I'm not sure if I can find the answer
music
facts
Cover the room
Leave it alone
After the war, a good man brought me here
You didn't come again
Sit
Good boy
You want to try this too?
Thanks
How's that?
If you still want to eat something,
I'll send you off immediately.
Thanks.
Why would he listen to you?
Because I raised Xiao Bai.
Don't think that Xiao Bai is so naive.
He's actually very young.
When the young man was killed,
he hasn't been able to break the shell yet.
He's been holding the big one for a long time.
I can't break the formation.
Otherwise, I'll be in the whole Cicada.
This pattern is so familiar.
Have you seen it?
It's the jade pendant that the Master gave me.
It's time to take the
I'll cut it.
No.
You and the Master of the Ling Yu Pavilion have a secret plan.
I'm afraid that they'll find out before they get close.
What should we do?
A man and a woman can never let you steal.
The cakes are gone.
I'll bring them to you tomorrow.
Okay?
I'll go get them.
It's open now?
Xiao Bai, you're so great.
The Master actually put the jade pendant here.
Boss.
How did the jade pendant get so dark?
I've been injured.
How could you repeat the same thing?
If I can't stop the jade pendant,
the God Clan will definitely destroy the jade pendant.
Let's start.
Master.
I feel so uncomfortable.
I can't control it.
It means that the jade pendant is dead.
Don't be hit by the jade pendant.
Thank you.
Sorry.
I didn't take it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You've recovered the jade pendant of the Dian Feng period.
But you're still in a big trouble.
I'll feel better after eating it.
How could you have the jade pendant?
This is the jade pendant of the Dian Feng period.
I'll take it if I can.
When the war is over,
I'll explain to Ge Zhou.
I'll implore you.
I was worried about you.
I was afraid that the jade pendant wouldn't be effective.
Then why did you run to Master Yin?
Maybe because I was in a relationship with Master Yin.
We got married and got married.
But I was the master of the body
after I was in the prison.
What did you say?
That he wasn't dead.
He would appear in my body
and call me a ghost.
He even used his magic.
Do you think this is his magic?
He made me feel the power
and then I became a big bad guy
like him.
He was with me.
What's more amazing is
that He Wan is exactly the same as me.
Do you think
he will be the same kind of knight as me?
We absorbed the same kind of jade pendant.
That's why the human form is the same.
Where is your birthplace?
A place called Mount Puxi.
Mount Puxi?
Master Zhang, what's wrong?
He Wan's life is not a knight.
He used to live in Mount Puxi.
You should have seen him often.
Maybe this is the reason
that he will be the same as me.
I see.
I really have no idea
what other people think.
Master Zhang,
why do you know He Wan so well?
He used the Soul-Giving Master.
Only He Wan's memory
can have a second soul-giver.
The problem is that
he can't be combined with the soul-giver.
Could it be?
Master Zhang, are you all right?
Is that Yin Sun's soul-giver?
He is too stupid.
We should report him to the Heaven Hall
and get rid of this evil.
This body is indeed He Wan.
But now,
you are already
in the Soul-Giving Master.
You can't feel any He Wan's breath.
He won't come out again, will he?
Then I'll have to leave this body
and be able to be the last fairy again.
It's not too late.
You still have a fairy.
If you forcefully break your soul,
I'm afraid you will die because of this soul-giver.
Don't worry.
I thought you had no soul
and no soul-giver.
When I get He Wan's missing soul,
I'll find a way to get rid of your soul
and re-release the body.
Really?
You have helped me a lot.
I should protect you from the evil.
You...you...
Be careful.
It's all right.
Master Zhang!