PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY...
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS, AND TOURISM
ALL FIGURES, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
INCIDENTS, GROUPS, OCCUPATIONS, AND OTHERS...
IN THIS DRAMA ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS.
EVILIVE
EPISODE 6
I guarantee their skills.
And they can start right away from next week.
Okay, I'll report this.
Anyway, are you dropping out for real?
I'm sorry, sir.
For troubling you that time.
And thank you.
Thanks to you, I might pay off my debt in no time.
Have a safe trip home.
Let's grab a meal together before we wrap up.
MOKYUN BANK
CARD, RECEIPT
WITHDRAWAL
PLEASE PRESS YOUR PIN NUMBER.
ATM
Once the money is deposited in the account,
withdraw it immediately.
Deduct a 10 percent fee,
and deposit the rest.
MOKYOUNG DISTRIBUTION
Wait!
Hello.
Boss isn't here.
I see.
YUSEONG MIRAE CONSULTING
Gosh.
Beom-jae.
Han Beom-jae.
I'm sleepy.
I stayed up all night,
and I'm about to die.
I wonder how much they're making.
Who knows?
The Yuseong Gang members...
do all the charging and exchanging work.
What about the number of users?
Even Si-deok can't access the database these days.
They've installed a firewall and security program.
Why? What is it?
Think about it.
We both received double the amount promised.
- That means...
- The sales must be twice higher.
We worked hard for nothing.
But what can we do?
Take it away from them? Fight them?
There's nothing we can do.
We'll just take the money they give
and leave quietly.
I'm going back to sleep.
THE CENTRAL CRUISE HOTEL
When is the gambling house scheduled to open?
We'll have to postpone it a little.
We're not getting as many
customers these days.
Is it because of the inspection?
Gosh, darn it.
- Assemblyman Park, congratulations. - Gosh.
Thank you.
- Have you been well? - Yes.
- Gosh. - Congratulations.
Goodness.
Congratulations on winning, Assemblyman Park.
I've been elected a long time ago.
You're quite slow...
when it comes to these things.
MARINE RESORT COMPLEX BUSINESS
Anyway, will it be realized this time?
The resort.
Don't worry.
The marine development industry...
...will be pushed ahead within this year.
Then, the tourist industry...
...will definitely benefit along with it.
It will be smooth sailing.
That's nice.
Oh, Mr. Seo.
Say hello.
This is President Seo Do-young.
He runs a consulting company.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Seo Do-young.
What a young business owner.
It's nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Assemblyman Park.
- Yes, madam.
Long time no see, sir.
Are you acquainted with each other?
We have a long history.
I used to learn how to work under him.
We used to be business partners for a bit too.
Business partners? What business?
House.
House?
House... You mean housing development?
Did you do work in that field too?
Let's talk for a bit, Mr. Seo.
Go on ahead.
What's gotten into you, coming here?
Your share for the nightclub business.
It's heavy.
Did I put in too much?
Let's part ways now.
Are you behind what happened to Hae-jun?
It's you, right?
And you joined hands with Park Choong-ho.
It has me wondering too.
Was it me or not?
I hope it's not too heavy for you to carry.
MARINE RESORT COMPLEX BUSINESS BRIEFING
HAN DONG-SOO
Are you home?
Could I visit you right now?
Sure, come.
First...
Let's get out of here.
What?
No. Don't.
Doesn't it feel like a dream?
You know, there are times when you wish...
...what you caused were a dream.
Here's information on the new programmers.
Si-deok recommended them.
They're quite skilled too.
I always wanted to know how much
Kim Jae-yeol made.
It seemed like I was doing all the work.
Everyone is the same.
Well, I'll get going.
The takeover process will be over next week.
Then my brother and I will drop out.
Tell me if you need anything.
You're moving to another country.
We're friends.
I want to help.
Right.
Bye, then.
Keep a close eye on Han Dong-soo.
Welcome.
SMOKING CANDY
Just a moment.
Give me a pack of Wild Plus...
...and a lighter, please.
Gosh.
I didn't know you smoked.
Well, I was torn on whether to smoke or not.
It's been two years.
That won't do.
Let me help you.
We're in the same situation.
I quit smoking six months ago too.
Gosh, I'm swayed many times a day.
Whether to smoke or not.
Is something bothering you?
An acquaintance I know...
...won the lottery.
I didn't care when I didn't know who won.
But to know it was my acquaintance,
it felt strange.
I pushed him...
...to buy that lottery ticket.
I gave him the numbers too.
Oh, dear.
I felt...
...a little jealous.
And later on,
it felt...
...inexplicably empty.
I thought I had lived my life to the fullest,
but it felt like nothing.
As if my life...
...was worth less than a lottery ticket.
I feel the same way sometimes.
When I confiscate the proceeds of crime.
It's several times bigger than my salary,
which is a huge downer.
There are tons of people...
...who earn and spend money so easily.
It has me wondering what I'm doing.
But most people struggle in life like us.
They are the ones who support this world.
Well, why don't we get going?
If we stay longer,
we might really want to smoke.
Sure.
Oh, right.
Here.
If it's a winning ticket, treat me.
This is the fun of living, isn't it?
And if you have any concerns,
tell me anytime.
Pardon?
You know, like the noisy neighbor...
...you mentioned the other day.
Sure.
Not to mention my payment,
I'm worried about her.
Yes, I know.
But only immediate family
can report someone missing.
Wait patiently for now.
We'll look into it and give you a call.
All right.
- Have a good day.
- You too.
Goodness, this is not good.
- Hi.
What was that about?
Her boss isn't opening
the store without any notice.
She won't answer her phone either.
Which store is it?
It's a bar.
Misty Purple?
How did it go?
You were right.
It's certain...
Seo Do-young made a connection with Park Choong-ho.
Did you look into why Han Dong-soo...
...and Seo Do-young joined hands?
That...
I'm not sure.
First,
stop Seo Do-young's money source.
So he can't move.
And keep looking into how they joined hands.
What is it? Darn...
Seo Do-young runs an Internet cafe?
Yes.
It opened a month ago.
Rumors say it's doing really well.
An Internet cafe is his way
of raking in all the money?
Hey, you moron.
This is why you can't beat Seo Do-young.
How much could you make
by running an Internet cafe?
Look properly into it.
What his money source is,
and why he opened an Internet cafe.
Do you understand?
If I get caught,
he won't even let me collect money.
I need some kind of insurance.
Hey, are you trying to bargain with me?
It's not that, sir.
Why do you think Seo Do-young kept you alive?
Because he adores you? No.
If you weren't Kim Yu-seong's nephew,
he'd have killed you already.
You remember, right?
You came to me first.
What do you think will happen...
if Do-young finds that out?
I don't think he'll keep you alive twice.
- Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday - Happy birthday
- Dear Granny - Dear Granny
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
Mom.
Mom, you have to blow out the candles.
Right.
Wait, Mother. You have to make a wish.
If you make a wish...
...before blowing them out, it'll come true.
A wish?
A wish...
I know what your wish is.
A hundred bags of yakgwa.
I hear a rat squeaking again.
I'm not a rat. I'm Min-hee.
Stay quiet.
My wish...
...is for Dong-soo...
...to live comfortably.
Not doing anything hard...
...and making a lot of money...
...so he can live in comfort.
That's all I need.
And this brat coming to his senses.
What? What kind of wish is that?
Is this some kind of discrimination?
- Gosh, you.
- Come on.
Hurry up and blow them out.
Otherwise, all your wishes won't come true.
It's good, right?
It's better than yakgwa, right?
You can have a cake like this every day...
...until you get sick of it
once we move to Australia.
Gosh, I can't wait to go.
I'll get to see kangaroos and koalas.
It'll be so much fun.
Come on, Grandma!
Mister.
Try this.
It's really good.
Here.
Thank you.
Darn it!
Seriously...
What will you do about this? Gosh.
It's good, right?
Darn it.
You told Seo Do-young that we're quitting, right?
Yes.
You've really made up your mind, right?
It seemed like you were hesitating.
When?
You did.
I'm glad Min Hee seems to like the idea.
But will Mom be okay there?
What if she sets things on fire in Australia too?
It's warm there.
She only does it when it's cold.
Dong-soo.
I got you red bean buns.
The house we used to live in.
It was heated with briquettes.
Back then, I was young too.
I didn't know what briquettes could do,
so every time she went to work,
it must've weighed on her mind.
Once it went out,
I had to stay in the cold room the whole day.
That's why...
she always carried around a matchbox in her pocket.
Honey!
Her discharge next week.
They need your signature.
Okay.
SEO DO-YOUNG
It's the same card again.
Give a card each.
Will you keep going? One, two!
This is great!
GAME OF CARDS
Here we go.
It's a bomb.
Nice. Godori.
Let's go.
What was that?
Yes, double!
Yes, I'm on my way.
U STAR INTERNET CAFE
Aren't you the attorney?
Oh, hello.
What brings you here?
KIM YE-RI
These are the portfolios of the new staff members.
I'll meet them first...
I'll meet them myself.
I need to choose one who's as good as you.
I'll set the date.
Are you sure?
That we can avoid
the inspection within five minutes?
Without leaving any evidence?
Yes. You don't have to worry about it.
You never know...
...until it happens.
I need to check on that...
to be able to keep my word.
That's what I'm saying.
U STAR INTERNET CAFE
It's the same card again.
- Oh, darn it.
- Nice move.
From 10 p.m. to 2 a.m. It's peak time.
We have only a few hours to go. Focus.
- Yes, boss.
What is this? Darn it.
Sir!
I think the police are here.
The servers are okay, right?
There are no problems.
- Yes?
- It's Kwon Oh-jae.
Inspection coming to the Internet cafe.
What?
YUSEONG MIRAE CONSULTING
What is he doing?
Move the car! How many times must I say it?
- Move!
- What are you doing?
If you moved it earlier,
this wouldn't have happened.
- Darn it. We're busy as is.
- Move it.
- Will you move each one?
- Let's get in!
How can you park your car here and leave?
Hey!
Even if it's online gambling,
there could be inspections.
But you don't have to worry.
They won't be able to find the evidence...
...that we planned this
and transfused them.
Then, do we just do nothing?
We'll have to erase the records...
...of accessing the exchange site.
ACCESS HISTORY
Will it take longer?
Stop talking to me.
DELETED SERVER DATA
In the meantime, the server managing team...
...will change the domain address...
...and hide the hard disks as a whole.
Then, all the evidence will be gone.
How much time will it take?
Five minutes.
PAGE NOT FOUND
Is there a problem?
Give us more time.
POLICE
PROCESSING
It's done.
The carrier just left.
GAME OF CARDS
WILL YOU LOG OUT?
What is this?
Hey.
What is it?
Oh, we got a report.
What is this about?
I'd like to check the inside.
Let me through.
You can't do this!
You can't do this.
Are you going to search the office...
...without a warrant?
We got a report.
What kind of report and how?
Let them in.
YUSEONG MIRAE CONSULTING
I don't think this is a gambling house.
No matter how much we search,
we can't find a single card.
Maybe it's like a gambling Internet cafe.
They're all legal sites.
I don't see any gift cards either.
We didn't find anything.
Yes.
Okay.
It's over.
Attorney Han, this actually worked.
Gosh, what a great day.
When I first moved into this place,
the weather was just like this.
When was that?
Ten years ago?
As soon as I saw this place, I was amazed.
That's why I picked it.
In the end, you owned it.
Everything you wanted.
That's not true.
I'm still far from done.
What more do you want to own?
I'm not sure.
A baseball team?
Is that even possible?
Unless you're super rich.
It's not impossible...
...if I continue running
the business like this.
I'll buy one one day.
I never miss out on anything I pick.
Whatever that is.
Take it.
What is this?
A severance pay.
Goodbye.
You stupid fool.
You should just...
...get out of here...
...and drown yourself
in the waters of Shinnam.
I'll be sure to find out.
Please give me another chance.
MOON SANG-GUK
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
What must I tell him?
Gosh, you scared me.
What's with this jerk?
Isn't he a zombie?
It's tomorrow, right?
- Han Dong-soo's nursing home.
- Yes, sir.
SHINNAM FERRY
What brings you here?
The gambling house must not be busy.
Are you working on something with Kim Jae-yeol?
Why? You want in?
Is collecting interests from karaoke rooms...
...quite tiring?
You jerk!
Darn it!
Learn when to butt in, jerk.
Let's go.
Gosh, there are so many things to throw out.
Leave it. I'll do it.
- I'll come with you.
- Okay.
Hey, Seon-kyo.
Is the preparation going well?
We're just packing and throwing things out.
Let me see you before you go.
Okay. Let's grab a meal.
- Call me.
- Okay.
Boss.
Going somewhere far?
Darn it.
Today's my lucky day.
I'm sorry, boss.
Please cut me some slack.
I had no choice.
Kim Jae-yeol told me...
...that he'd kill me
if I didn't listen to him.
Please spare me, boss.
Get rid of him.
Han Dong-soo!
It's about Han Dong-soo!
I heard that the Family Gang members...
...are making a move on.
Attorney Han Dong-soo.
I definitely heard it.
Boss, please spare my life.
I'm Chang-yong, Boss.
I want to go back to...
...being your little brother Chang-yong.
Boss.
Tonight, the Family Gang members are making a move.
I'll gather more information and take action.
What about Attorney Han?
Let's see.
Darn it.
Hey. Did you send the men?
Yes, they're on their way.
AUSTRALIAN IMMIGRATION E2 PROGRAM
Here's your e-ticket.
You are a total of five people.
The departure time is at 7:50 p.m.,
and the estimated duration is 10 hours and 10 minutes.
Please double-check and contact me...
...if you have any questions.
Thank you.
- Goodbye.
- Take care.
- Bye.
SUNGSIL TRAVEL AGENCY
HYE-YOUNG
What are you doing?
Did Seo Do-young order you to do this?
He wants to kill me...
...and my family now?
No, it's not that.
We heard that Moon Sang-guk...
...and Kim Jae-yeol are targeting you.
We observed the movements of the Family Gang members.
But it seems like they weren't after you.
- Fire!
- I see her!
Go in!
Lee Hye-ja.
Have you seen Lee Hye-ja of Unit 202?
I am not sure.
Hello. Where's my mom?
Oh, dear.
Mom.
Mom!
- Are you the guardian?
- I'm her son.
Get in quickly.
AMBULANCE
Mom.
Dong-soo.
It's me, Dong-soo.
Can you recognize me?
Yes.
My baby.
It's not too cold today, is it?
It's not cold.
Goodness, my son.
You got old.
You've got wrinkles.
Where has the time gone?
You know I've always had a lot of wrinkles.
My son.
Next time,
be born into a good family...
...and live a comfortable life.
Don't suffer.
Why...
Why next time?
We can live comfortably now.
I am rich now.
So,
let's eat good food...
...and go on trips together.
We will do that.
Okay.
Let's do that.
Dong-soo.
I am sorry.
Why? About what?
Just everything.
Dong-soo.
My son.
In the next life,
you must...
Mom.
Mom!
- She's in cardiac arrest!
- Start CPR.
Mom!
No!
Mom.
Oh, no.
Mom...
No, Mom.
AND A BEAUTIFUL ENDING
WE'RE HERE TODAY BECAUSE OF YOU
Thank you.
It must be tough, but I hope you get through this well.
Honey.
Can I talk to you?
Go.
EVERY DOCTOR COMPUTER
BLOOMING BASE
Excuse me.
What are all these?
These all came for Mr. Han Dong-soo, the chief mourner.
YUSEONG MAN POWER AGENCY
WITH HEARTFELT CONDOLENCES
How did you know I was here?
It's your routine.
Going for a jog on this path every morning.
Right. We've run together a few times.
How many people...
have you killed so far?
...did you kill like this?
How am I supposed to know that?
Am I supposed to count them one by one?
I heard you are emigrating.
It might be a good idea
to change your flight schedule.
I don't know what connection you have with that thug,
but we'll uncover everything.
You'll have to pay for your sins.
Sit.
I'm not done.
You little punk.
What are you doing?
I...
I am not leaving.
It's you...
...who should be leaving.
You murderer.
You rat!
Let go!
Feel it.
Feel what it's like to be the victim,
to be stepped on.
Feel it for once.
I didn't know you smoked.
Thanks to you,
I was able to send my mother off well.
Thank you.
You look a lot like Mother,
especially your eyes.
What's wrong?
Well...
...I can't call my friend's mom
Ms. Lee. It's too formal.
I am curious about something.
Can I ask you a question?
I've seen you...
...on TV before.
In the 1989 high school baseball finals.
Why...
...did you do that then?
BONGJU HIGH
If it weren't for that incident,
you could have
become a national baseball player.
You might have been
the first Korean major leaguer.
Perhaps it could've been you,
not Park Chan-ho.
He was a bought-out umpire.
The baseball field was such a mess.
That's all?
Then what else could there be?
I don't know.
Well, I don't think that's all there is to it.
I admit there might have been bias.
The umpire might have possibly been bought out.
But ultimately,
wasn't it you who made that decision?
I'm not curious about why you got angry...
...but rather why you made that choice.
That's what I want to know.
That game.
It was the last game I could play.
I was injured.
But I don't regret it.
The timing was just right.
The timing?
"I quit baseball because of my injuries."
That sounds bad, you know.
It was the right time,
so I had to go for it.
Is what we talked about last time...
still...
valid?
You will go after Kim Jae-yeol,
and I'll go after Moon Sang-guk.
I thought it was a ridiculous idea,
but I want to try now.
You look much better without glasses.
EVILIVE
Attorney Han became much more involved.
You will end it with Seo Do-young...
once you take down Moon Sang-guk, right?
We are headed towards victory,
so don't you worry.
It won't be easy to separate...
Moon Sang-guk from Kim Jae-yeol.
He will come to his senses if he goes broke.
You've done enough.
Something might happen to you too.
Did you think having a thug by your side...
would change things?
Once cornered, he will be busy to spare himself.
We got a report.
I thought it might help the investigation.