So you find a fake baby...
It’s just a fake baby to replace the real Ying Zheng
Fortunately
Otherwise, the prince would have grown up in the Proton Mansion
Zhao Mu used alcohol and sex to numb his will for a long time
In the end, it will be like today’s fake Ying Zheng
Become a waste who is greedy for life and afraid of death
Now that we know the whereabouts of the prince
We need to bring him back as soon as possible
I wonder where Niujia Village is?
Thirty miles east of the city
The foot of a mountain called Niutou Mountain
More than ten years later, how do we know
Which one is the real prince?
There is also one beside the prince
Identical white jade ring
As long as you show it to the old farmer and his wife
They will know that I sent you.
That's great, it's getting late now
We'll do this immediately tomorrow morning
We have no choice but to stay here temporarily
Madam, please don't be offended.
Lord Wubao, you're welcome
This place is already a hundred times better than Zhao Mu's mansion.
Madam please
By the way, it’s been so long since I came back
Why don't you see my apprentice and princess? Where are they?
Master, let me go
I want to kill Zhao Mu to avenge my mother
Revenge for... what kind of revenge? You have this kind of three-legged cat kung fu
If you go out to take revenge
They will definitely be chopped into pieces.
No matter how many copies of Lu Gong's Secret Records I have,
I can't bring you back either
I would rather die by the enemy's sword
Don't live an ignoble existence either
Young Master Pan, listen to your elder brother
A gentleman's revenge is not too late in ten years
Yes, if you show off your courage
Isn’t it just like dying in vain?
Cousin Pan, calm down
Aunt Quanxia is well aware and doesn’t want anything to happen to you.
Master understands how you feel now
But now is really not the time to avenge your mother.
So when is the time?
Now the first thing we have to do
Just send Zhu Ji mother and son back to Qin.
After finishing this matter
I will find another way to avenge your mother
Is your name A Zheng?
no…
Big brother
Why are there funerals in every household in this village?
yes
Sir, is your name A Zheng?
no
Do you know where Daddy Cow lives?
Daddy Niu?
Everyone in our village has the surname Niu
Which cow daddy are you looking for?
There is a man named A Zheng in his family
Ah Zheng? Ah Zheng lives in this room
Working
How many of them are…
Are you a cow daddy?
That's right
Is A Zheng here?
A Zheng?
It’s a woman named Mrs. Zhu
Ask me to come to you with this white jade ring
Everyone, please come in
What's up?
Tell me what those five words actually say?
It says "Niu Zheng's Spiritual Position"
Niu Daddy
Didn’t you tell me that Mrs. Zhu’s Azheng...
We are useless as a couple. I'm sorry, Mrs. Zhu.
In recent years, there have been frequent battles
All the men in our village have been drafted into the army
The army sent back several corpses a few days ago
It's a pity that Zheng'er is so young and about to die in battle.
You two, let’s go indoors and rest first.
Impossible, it won't happen
Qin Shihuang would not die like this
I don’t believe it…
Brother, calm down and go away
Big brother
It can't be such a prank, right? People will die.
Big brother is crazy
Why so upset?
More than upset? I'm about to die
If eldest brother can trust Teng,
Just say it and let my second brother take care of your worries
You wouldn’t believe it if I told you
What's the use of telling you?
If you don't tell me, how will your second brother understand?
Even if you tell me, you won’t understand.
What if I told you that I suddenly disappeared in front of you
Do you believe it?
Suddenly disappeared? Brother, you are still here
How should I tell you?
I want to tell you
I am not the person I am now
I'm from the future world
I'm not from ancient times, you understand?
Future world?
The world of the future...that is, the world of the future
The future world is not the present
Now we call it ancient times
You understand ancient times, right?
Ancient times are the dynasties before your current dynasty
Do you understand that the previous dynasties are called ancient times?
I understand this, the ancients are...
Just understand it
The opposite of ancient times is the future world
I am from the future world
Do you know what I'm saying? Epcot
Let me give you an example, like...
You and your wife had a son
Your son gave birth to another son, who is also your grandson
Many, many generations of grandchildren later, then...
Which generation of grandson is that?
It doesn’t matter which generation of grandson you are.
Possibly the grandson of the generation after the 98th generation
Come back to visit your ancestor, when...
By that time, I'm already dead
I don't care if you live or die
In short, your 98th generation grandson
Come back to visit your grandpa
The era of the 98th generation grandson
It's called the future world
In that world, anything can be done, then...
Is it really possible?
OK
Look at me sitting in front of you alive
I knew it would work, so how could it not work?
Anyway, the world at that time had everything.
Do you believe what I said?
Believe it, even though I don’t quite understand it
But I definitely believe what you said, brother
Actually this is also very interesting
Big brother can visit people anytime and anywhere
Are you kidding me?
The worst thing is
Now history has been messed up by me
The dead Niu Zheng you just saw
Originally, he would become the King of Qin in two or three years.
Then the Qin Dynasty will appear in twenty or thirty years
Then the six countries were unified, did you know?
Is he really that powerful?
Of course he was awesome, he even called himself Qin Shihuang
Then they burned books and harassed Confucians
Later, many people were hired to build the Great Wall
The dynasty after the Qin Dynasty was the Han Dynasty
I don’t know what dynasty came after the Han Dynasty
Anyway, many years later
It was in the second thousand years, that is, my time
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Brother, are you saying that you are a person born more than two thousand years later?
Yes, originally it was
But the corpse you just saw
He is the future Qin Shihuang
Now that Qin Shihuang is dead, there is no Qin Dynasty.
The Qin Dynasty is gone
Then there will be no more Tang, Song, Yuan, Ming and Qing dynasties.
In other words, even the SAR government is almost gone.
Then...then I'm almost gone
Big brother is alive here now and has not disappeared.
Yes, how can we have grandchildren without a grandfather?
Just like how can there be eggs without chickens?
Now that the egg has been laid
In other words, there must be chickens
There must be chicken?
I also thought about the whole thing the other way around.
Brother just said
As long as Qin Shihuang unified the six countries,
there will be your presence
Since you already exist, that means
There must be a Qin Shihuang who came out to unify the six countries
You look a lot like Jesus
Master…
What should I do with this white jade ring?
Niu Lao Ma and Niu Lao Ma asked us to return it to Zhu Ji
Save it for me
keep?
Brother, Ying Zheng is dead
How do we explain to Mrs.
If Zhu Ji knew about her son's death
Must be heartbroken
What to do?
Xiang Shaolong, have you found it?
actually…
Zheng'er, you must be my Zheng'er
Over the past ten years, my mother has missed you so much.
Congratulations, madam...Congratulations, madam, on your mother and son reunion
Shaolong, he is obviously... I know
He is Wang Zizheng
division…
What is the teacher? I have said it many times
My surname is not Shi, my surname is Xiang, Wang Zizheng
Zheng'er, are you feeling uncomfortable?
It's okay
I think he may have been there for more than ten years
I have never seen my own mother-in-law
So I was overly excited for the moment
I don’t know how to express my inner feelings in words
So he might be a little sluggish
It'll be fine later
Zheng'er, mother said she would never leave you again.
You go in with your mother
Mom wants to have a good talk with you, come here
lady
Shaolong, what are you doing?
Big brother…
Kill a chicken to thank God for his kindness
Let's go over there and tell the castle owner slowly. Come on
Replace Ying Zheng with Zhao Pan?
Who said Ying Zheng is really dead?
This is the only way
What can I do? What if my wife exposes me?
Don’t worry, Zhu Ji has been
I have never seen my biological son at all.
Otherwise she wouldn’t have seen Apan just now
Treat him as his biological son
I think if we don't talk about this
It won't be revealed
You must not do this. Impersonating a prince is a capital offense.
Besides, Prime Minister Lu is going back to Ying Zheng this time.
It is the successor to the Qin Kingdom
How can you find someone to pretend to be someone when the matter is so important?
Lord Wubao, I know you are loyal to Qin
But I think you were deceived by Mr. Lu this time too.
Shaolong, why did you say this?
In fact, Ying Zheng was not the biological son of King Qin at all.
He is the illegitimate son born to Mr. Lu and Zhu Ji
Is this true?
Of course it's true, before I came to Zhao country
Mr. Lu told me this personally.
He also warned many times
After asking me to save his son
Take him back to Qin so that he can be the emperor
Then he can dominate
No wonder Lu Cheng attached so much importance to saving the prince
It turns out that he was pretending to be a public servant for personal gain
If Mr. Lu knew that his son died tragically,
Wouldn't he be furious?
I can't imagine it anymore
He originally planned to take his son back so that he could become the king.
Now there is nothing
If he knew about this
I don't think any of us will survive
Then let’s go to Qin on this trip
Isn’t it a dead end?
Since it's a dead end
I think it’s better to follow what brother said
If you make a mistake, you will make a mistake. Use Zhao Pan to replace it.
Anyway, Madam already regards him as her biological son.
Master Wu Bao, you also saw it just now
Zhu Ji meets Pan'er
The excitement of reunion between flesh and blood
It's like a person who hasn't eaten for more than ten days
It feels the same as giving him a chicken leg
How can you bear to tell Zhu Ji?
Madam has been looking forward to it for more than ten years
Just waiting for the day when flesh and blood meet again
If the lady knew that her son was no longer alive,
It's so pitiful
Master Wu Bao, I know I want you to deceive Mr. Lu
It's a very difficult thing
But if you think about it carefully
We have no choice anymore
Ying Zheng is really dead
Besides, Pan'er's nature is not bad either.
As long as we teach him well
He will definitely become successful in the future
Now we can only make mistakes
One, it can save our lives
Second, it can also help Zhu Ji find her biological son
Why not?
Shaolong's words make sense
If this matter is publicized,
Not only are our lives at risk
I'm afraid the Qin State will also undergo great changes.
The only solution now is to do what you want
However, what saddens Wu the most is...
Looking at the country of Qin
Will fall into the hands of people with foreign surnames
Even though Wu Mou is patriotic, he is also powerless.
It’s been more than ten years in the blink of an eye
Zheng'er has grown so big
I left you for so many years for my mother
She has not even shouldered a little responsibility as a mother.
really ashamed
Mom, you have suffered a lot in the past ten years
Call me mother for my mother and other political children
I have been waiting for more than ten years
Now I can see Zheng'er
Mom, the hardships she has endured for more than ten years are finally not in vain.
Mom, stop doing this
By the way, Zheng'er, tell your mother
How has your life been in Niujia Village these past ten years?
Pretty good
Are you well fed and warmly clothed?
Mom, look at the kid, he’s tall and strong
Just know that I have never been hungry
Zheng'er, why are your hands so tender and smooth?
Nothing like coming from a rural home
That's it, mother, you don't know something
Cow Father and Cow Mother are very good to their children
So the children don’t have to do any heavy work.
That being said, my mother had nothing to blame back then.
Think about those days
Mom only gave a sum of money to Niu Lao Ma and Niu Lao Ma
As a child’s childcare expenses
I really didn’t know I would be separated from you for so long
The longer I am my mother, the more I will miss you.
I'm afraid that you will have a bad life and will starve and freeze
Mom, stop thinking so much about the past.
madam, prince
I've got hot water ready
Is it convenient to bathe and change the prince's clothes?
Wei Niang only cares about chatting with Zheng Er
Forgot you haven’t…
You go take a shower and change clothes first, and wait until you finish washing up
I’ll talk to you again at night by holding a candle for my mother’s sake
Good guy, he really knows how to act.
And know how to adapt to changes
If I have the chance, I really want to introduce you to Hollywood.
You will definitely get rich
Master, Pan'er really doesn't understand
Why do you have to pretend to be Ying Zheng?
Didn't you see Zhu Ji's appearance?
She has been waiting for her son for more than ten years
If you tell her that her son is dead
I think she will commit suicide
But in this case, how long will Pan'er continue to pretend?
I have discussed this with Master Wu Bao.
We feel that the best thing at this stage is to make mistakes
Will it be a mistake to make a mistake?
Anyway, Zhu Ji has already regarded you as Ying Zheng.
Just use your identity as Ying Zheng
Isn’t it okay to follow her back to Qin?
Want me to follow her back to Qin...
Want me to follow her back to Qin? How can I do that?
I am from Zhao country
Doesn't this mean that the thief is the father?
You said yourself that you are from Zhao country
It’s a pity that King Zhao and Zhao Mu didn’t think you were from Zhao.
Have you forgotten?
but…
I want to stay in the Kingdom of Zhao and take revenge by killing Zhao Mu.
Please use your brain to think about it
When you become King of Qin in the future,
Not to mention revenge, you send a team of soldiers every day
You can just teach him a lesson when you have time.
Now that you have no power, how can you take revenge?
I'm worried that if you stay in Zhao State, your life will not be guaranteed.
Just trust me
Your master, when will I not lie to you?
No...when did I, your master, lie to you?
All in all, this matter is doing a lot of harm and no good at all.
No, it's completely beneficial and harmless
Brother, there is an inn in front of you
Then let's take a break in front first.
Dear guests, please...this way...
This way…
Zheng'er, the sun is scorching hot outside, are you working hard?
Mom, don’t worry, the baby will be able to survive
By the way, mother, are you tired after traveling for days?
Not tired, I just want to return to Qin as soon as possible
Reunion with your father's family
Two of them, one lost his mother and the other lost his son
Now that's a good thing
Therefore, there is a master in everything in the world.
Lord Wubao, how long does it take for us to reach Qin?
We can meet up with Tao Fang tomorrow
We can reach Qin in another two or three days.
Then won’t we be able to meet Tingfang soon?
Since the last time we said goodbye in the palace
I haven’t seen Tingfang for a long time.
Lord Wubao, how is Tingfang?
Thank you princess for your concern
But my daughter is unruly and willful
I have always liked traveling alone
I'm afraid I've reached the border of Qin now.
Ten days ago, we received a transaction
Someone offered a lot of money
Want us to track down a Mohist named Zhou Ping
On the surface, this person seems to be an alchemist who makes alchemy and medicine.
But secretly, we find
He is secretly developing a powerful weapon
Powerful weapon?
Could it be that this person died from such a powerful weapon?
You should be able to tell from the corpse.
In addition to his missing limbs
And there are signs of being burned by fire
But if it's just fire
The limbs should not be so mutilated
Yes, if this powerful weapon existed
Anyone who can grasp
I will definitely be invincible in the world
Shanrou, you want to find out the secret, you know?
Kind and gentle, obey orders
Beat you to death...
Is it comfortable? Isn’t it more comfortable this way? Smelly bitch
Spit out the happy elixir that I worked so hard to refine?
Want to pretend to be dead? I won’t let you die so early.
Smelly bitch, I'm going to ask you to test the medicine.
Eat it...eat it
Hero, spare your life
If you don't want to die, just do it immediately
Hand over the secret recipe for the secret weapon you developed
What’s the secret weapon recipe?
You don't have to act crazy in front of me
I pay…
Hero, spare your life...
If you don’t want to die, hand over the secret recipe immediately
The secret recipe? I don’t know what the secret recipe is
Stop pretending to be crazy
A few days ago, I had a brother
He died because of your powerful weapon
A few days ago? You mean that?
You misunderstood, a few nights ago
Someone really sneaked into my alchemy room secretly
The villain's alchemy furnace is refining a five-stone powder
I don’t know how he knocked over the alchemy furnace.
Suddenly there was a loud noise like thunder and lightning
The entire alchemy furnace turned into pieces and scattered
Your brother is...
Good man, believe me, it really has nothing to do with me
Why does a good alchemy furnace turn into pieces?
This kind of alchemy thing happens all the time.
I don't know either
Then can you still remember that day?
What medicinal stones did you put in the alchemy furnace?
After so many days
I don't remember, I really don't remember
Really don’t remember?
I have many prescriptions here
Hero, spare the villain's life, take it.
You are a man with evil intentions and do all kinds of things
Do you like alchemy so much?
I will make it happen for you
Girl, let me get you out
The eldest lady of the Wu family?
danger, go
What does it mean?
What do you think?
Has the medicine not worn off yet?
I think you're hungry too. Let's have some porridge.
What happened to you? Tell me, okay?
Do you still recognize me? My name is Shanrou
Think about it carefully
I'm your eldest brother Xiang Shaolong's friend
Do you still remember Xiang Shaolong?
You just said you just walked out of the alchemy room
The alchemy furnace suddenly turned into pieces and scattered
Fortunately, my subordinate walked quickly
Otherwise, I will never have the chance to serve you, my lord.
Could it be as Zhou Ping said?
The so-called powerful murder weapon
It was just an accident that happened while refining the elixir
It's a pity that at that time
I poured the medicinal stones into the alchemy furnace randomly
I didn’t write down the contents of the medicine stone one by one.
otherwise…
Things happen suddenly, you don’t have to blame yourself
Shanrou, can you remember
I ordered you to be with Xiang Shaolong that day
Stealing the Juzi Order
Of course Shanrou remembers
The buyer who asked us to steal the huge order that day
After getting the Juzi Order, I discovered a hidden pattern in the order
But the secret grid turned out to be empty.
Could it be that the Lord doubts Shan Rou?
Keep the secrets in the Juzi Order as your own
I'm sorry you don't dare either
But to prove your innocence
You'd better try something on Xiang Shaolong
Find out the secret hidden by Ju Zi Ling
but…
No need to say more
I don't care what means you use
You have to do it within three months
On Xiang Shaolong
Find out the secret hidden by Ju Zi Ling
Otherwise, you know what the consequences will be, right?
But for a while
The Lord asked me how to find the whereabouts of Xiang Shaolong?
You can rest assured about this
According to the spies' report
Xiang Shaolong is currently on his way back to Western Qin via a detour
As long as you rush to Xianyang immediately
Of course there is a chance to meet this person
I hope to see you next time, what you brought back
It's Juziling's secret, not your head
Why are you doing this?
Why did you save me? Just let me die
Although I don't know what happened to you
But you die like this
Are you willing to let go of Xiang Shaolong in your heart?
I have already forgotten this person
You can deceive others, but you cannot deceive yourself
You keep this hosta by your side all the time
You just remember him
Don't say any more
This hosta was given to you by him
If you really forget about him
Why keep it around?
So what?
He never put me in his heart
He said that you are his true love
then you are wrong
He just used me to piss you off that day
When he knew you didn't go back to Wujiapu
Do you know how nervous he is looking for you everywhere?
real?
But why would he bother to do this?
I only know that he regretted his marriage that day
There must be something unspeakable about him
Unspeakable and hidden?
if you want to know
You should save your life even more
Go and ask him in person for a clear explanation
Bystanders know clearly, authorities are confused
If you are seeking suicide now
Xiang Shaolong will regret it for the rest of his life
And will you give up under Jiuquan?
Death is not the best solution
Have you made a fire?
I caught a fish, no need to eat dry food tonight
Where have you been during these days?
Why did it fall into the hands of the alchemist again?
Border towns are also quite lively, right?
Mrs. Zhu Ji and Wang Zizheng are back
Hurry up and see. Hurry up...
Come on, come over and watch the fun
Uncle, what happened earlier?
Don't you know?
Mrs. Zhu Ji, who has been under house arrest in Zhao for more than ten years
He and Zizheng returned to Qin
He seems to be a great hero named Xiang
Rescued them from the Zhao State Hostage House
wait for me
Xiang Shaolong
Why are you standing still and not chasing him?
I really can't understand your thoughts
You obviously miss Xiang Shaolong very much
Why didn't you go up and acknowledge him just now?
Didn't you just see...
Does he already have a princess by his side?
Deceiving oneself and others
Even if Xiang Shaolong has an extra princess by his side
as long as you want
You can also go up and ask for clarification.
Unless you have something to hide in your heart
After this battle
I know that I should plan everything for myself
Why did you betray me?
Eat it...you will be very happy after eating it
I practiced very hard
It turned out to be you?
Shanrou, are you sick?
Take me to a place like this in the middle of the night
He also said he would bring me to meet someone.
How is it? Who are you meeting?
Can't you see me?
Of course I can see you
But you don’t have to bring me all the way here to see you, right?
Just because I'm about to die and see my old friends.
Who is dying?
I mean this time we meet
may be the last time
What last time?
Forget it, I'd better not say it, so as not to embarrass you
Then just say it
If you don't tell me, how will you know that I can't help you?
Still don’t want it
Anyway, eighteen years later he is a good man again
I have nothing to offer, so I won’t say anything anymore.
Auntie, don't be so long-winded and talk in circles.
You tell me, only then can I help you.
So you agreed? Yes...
But you can’t tell me to commit suicide by cutting my pulse now.
I promise you too, right?
Don't worry, I won't force you
Last time I borrowed a huge token from you
Do you still remember?
Did you borrow it? You stole it?
If I had known that the huge order would kill me, I would not have stolen it
You stole something and said I killed you
You are so unreasonable
Tell the truth
My lord asked me to steal that huge order.
I don’t know how the lord actually knows
There is a secret hidden in the Juzi Order
He gave me a month to hand over the secret book.
Otherwise, there is only a dead end
Are you still a human being?
You stole my huge order last time
This time you asked me to give you the secret
You are so whimsical
I also said you won't help me
Forget it, if you don't care for yourself, you will be punished by heaven and earth.
I won't blame you
Anyway, if you drop by for the Spring and Autumn Festival, come and pay homage to me.
no problem
Just kidding, don't be so thin-skinned
Come on, come and sit down
how?
I'm not afraid to tell you the truth
That secret book was given to me by my master before he died.
He repeatedly told me to keep it well.
What if it falls into the wrong hands?
When the time comes, life will be ruined and death...
If I didn't have that secret book
I can only die
Have you ever watched The Legend of the Condor Heroes?
I know you must not have seen it
The trick we used Huang Rong to deceive Ouyang Feng
Why don't you just come and lie to your lord?
Just give him a fake secret book
But my lord is no ordinary person
Not so easily fooled
Of course not the whole book is fake.
But one sentence is true and one sentence is false
Half a sentence is true, half a sentence is false.
Let’s use Huang Rong’s trick
Write fast as slow and slow as fast
Left is written as right, right is written as left
Line before is written as after, after is written as...
You can imagine such a brilliant strategy, it’s awesome
Actually, it’s not what I thought of
It was Ajinyong who thought of it
A Jinyong?
Yes, it’s Ajinyong
Pan'er always thought
The scale of Handan City is already very grand
Now come to Xianyang City
Only then did I realize that there is another mountain that is higher than the other.
You know that Master made the right introduction, right?
Anyway, starting from today
Qin is the place where you can show your talents
Show off your skills?
Of course, the most powerful country today is Qin
If you don’t develop here, where can you develop?
Believe me, as long as you pay attention
You will definitely have the opportunity to stand out in the future
But Pan'er is always a little worried
After entering Xianyang City
Is it possible to deceive everyone
I heard people say
Lu Buwei of Qin State is a very powerful person
Don't worry, I'm here with your master
Anyway, you have to remember that after entering Xianyang City
You are no longer Zhao Pan
You are Ying Zheng, the prince of Qin
Pan'er...Zheng'er knows
The humble minister Lu Buwei, under the order of the king
Came here specially to welcome the lady and the prince
After more than ten years apart, Madam, how are you doing?
Prime Minister Lu has good intentions, everything is fine with Zhu Ji
Zheng'er, you haven't met Mr. Lu yet?
yes
Zheng'er met Lu Xiangye
Is he Ying Zheng?
I really didn’t expect that the government…
Wang Zizheng has grown so tall
Thanks to Prime Minister Lu Hongfu
Xiang Shaolong and Lord Wu Bao
Has successfully brought the wife and prince back to Qin
good, well done
Madam and Wang Zizheng travel long distance
Must be exhausted
Invite Madam and Wang Zizheng
Let’s go to Lu Mansion to settle down for a while.
See you again, Your Majesty
Then there is Prime Minister Lao Lu
Prince, please