No matter how powerful this person is
You have to point him out in public
I want to become the prince of the Qin Kingdom
The position of prince was originally within easy reach
If it weren't for your appearance, Ying Zheng
How could I be reduced to such a situation?
Cheng Xi, you haven’t answered me yet
I'm really unwilling
I just want to take back the throne that belongs to me
Listen, Ying Zheng
This incident was entirely planned by me alone
Be indifferent to others
Cheng Yu, what kind of hero are you trying to be?
Why cover up the mastermind?
Since Cheng Xi failed,
Behead or kill, please do as you please
you…
Come, take him out
Tomorrow morning, he will be executed together with all the people involved in the case.
Retreat from the court
How unreasonable
Lu Buwei is clearly the mastermind behind the assassination.
I really don’t understand
Why is Chenglong so stubborn?
He's actually willing to take the blame on his own
King
Could it be that Lu Buwei has something to do with Cheng Xi?
Chenglong has already subdued the law
What's there to fear when it's already a death sentence?
But Wei Chen still feels strange
Since Lu Buwei was able to capture all the Chenggan family members in one fell swoop,
Why did Cheng Yu let his wife, who was pregnant with Liujia, escape?
Lu Buwei did it on purpose
Collect Chengyu's pregnant wife
To threaten
In order to protect the safety of his wife and children, Cheng Xi
He will also bear all the charges
Unexpectedly, this old fox Lu Buwei
So cunning
It's rare to lure a snake out of its hole this time
But we have to let the tiger go back to the mountain again
The more I think about it, the more unwilling I am.
Your Majesty, why don't you let me take action?
Get rid of this old fox Lu Buwei
Your Majesty, Lu Buwei not only monopolizes military and political power,
Moreover, there are party members all over the government and the public, and this person will not be eliminated in one day.
It is really difficult for the king to control the political power, so he shows his ambitions
Lao Ai is willing to make another contribution to the king
I also want to put Lu Buwei to death
But Taifu Xiang...
It's better to wait for Taifu Xiang to recover from his injuries before making long-term plans.
See Mr. Lu and General Meng...
Lu Buwei
Open the door Yes
It's none of your business here. You go out and take good care of it.
No idlers are allowed in
yes
Lu Buwei
Isn't this my wife's?
What have you done to my wife?
Your Majesty asked me to bring this hairpin to you.
She wants to tell you the truth
Now I have the truth to take care of me, everything is fine
Tell you not to worry about her
You can rest assured
As long as you don't talk nonsense in front of the king
Your wife and belly fat
It will be safe and sound, otherwise...
You must not hurt my wife and children
It is not a pity to die as an adult, but the young son is innocent
Mr. Lu, just treat it like a dragon, please.
Do you think of it for the sake of the late king?
Leave this bit of blood for me
Cheng Xi only hopes that someone can inherit the incense lamp for me
It will not lead to the end of having no children or grandchildren.
Then Chenglong will die without regrets
Cheng Xi... I never imagined that you have deep feelings for your wife and children.
Lu Buwei, you have to remember
The promise between you and me
If not, Cheng Xi will go to hell after his death.
I won't let you go even if I'm a ghost
Have you finished cursing your true nature?
Once the curse is over, you can die peacefully
Lu Buwei
Lu Buwei, you must remember what you and I said
Otherwise, I want you to die badly
I really can't believe it
He dared to curse even when he was about to die.
Meng Ao, after he has completed the Dharma rectification
Get rid of his wife immediately
In his wife’s womb…
To cut weeds, we need to get rid of the roots to avoid future troubles.
But... Prime Minister, you just promised him
Even the king is not afraid of this
Are you afraid of a curse from this person?
Brother Xiang... wake up quickly
Don't make the one who loves you sad
Brother Xiang…
Xiang Shaolong, are you dead? Wake up
Brother Xiang, what should I do if he’s still awake?
His pulse has strengthened
Maybe because of too much blood loss before
This made him weak and he still hasn't woken up yet
Do you think he knew it was us who sent him here?
What exactly do you want him to know?
Do you decide to stay here with him or come with me?
Do you really want to leave?
certainly
The assassination attempt on Ying Zheng and Xiang Shaolong failed.
Of all the assassins, I'm the only one who's okay
Sooner or later, my lord will find out that it was me who betrayed the organization.
I must leave Xianyang
You can wait until Brother Xiang wakes up before leaving
It doesn't even matter whether he wakes up or not
The person he wants to see is not me at all
But as for you…
Maybe he has already forgotten me
I believe Xiang Shaolong is not someone who is greedy for the new and forgets the old.
It's a pity that I am no longer the Wu Tingfang of the past
Someone, go
Brother Xiang…
Brother Xiang, you must recover
I won't let you break your promise
Since I remember Xiang Shaolong’s words,
You should go back
I...I'm afraid
What else are you afraid of?
It used to be because Xiang Shaolong had a princess beside him
Now the princess is dead
Are you still worried so much?
But I am no longer...
Anyway, I don’t know how to face him again.
Although I don't know about you
What happened
But no matter what
That day you also ran away from home because of Xiang Shaolong
So much suffering
If Xiang Shaolong is a kind and righteous person
no matter what happened to you
He will love you more
I really don't know what to do
Shanrou, how dare you betray the organization?
The Lord has ordered us to take you back
Handle according to door rules
This operation failed
I will go back on my own and explain it to the lord
As for you saying I betrayed the organization?
I'm afraid there's some misunderstanding
You don't have to act pretentious here
The person who will act with you this time
The entire army was wiped out
Are you the only one okay?
Okay, I'll go back with you now
Tell the boss the whole story
Never hurt innocent people
Walk
Look at the arrow
The organization has started sending people to hunt me down.
In order not to inconvenience you, we will go separately
No, if I hadn't ruined your big deal
You won't be hunted by the Assassins
After all, I am the one who has caused you trouble.
How could I abandon you at this time?
What about Xiang Shaolong?
Since his life is no longer in danger now
Things between me and him
It’s not too late to talk about it slowly in the future
The most important thing right now is to leave this city as soon as possible
Shaolong, please don’t let anything happen to you
By God, as long as Shaolong can recover
Qin Qing is willing to sacrifice everything
I have made up my mind
I will never escape again
As long as Shaolong is by my side
I want to make him happy
clear
Shaolong, are you awake?
Do you still remember that I promised you before?
For you, I will never die
I know you won't leave me alone
don't leave me again
I promise you
Even if these days are only ten or eight days
Let’s also spend time happily, okay?
Shaolong, what are you doing?
I'm practicing the Eighteen Dragon Subduing Palms
Eighteen Dragon Subduing Palms?
After lying down for so many days
If I don’t practice again, I will really die.
I don't allow you to say the word "death"
Barker
Barker?
It means you are stupid
If I could hit the target, I would have been rich a long time ago
Anyway, I don’t want to hear the word death in the future.
come with me
For your speedy recovery
My godfather and I brewed it specially for you
This kind of barilla wine
It is brewed with many kinds of medicinal materials.
Drink quickly
Drinking in broad daylight is too boring, right?
Let's do this, I'll teach you how to play Bee Buzz
Little bee?
very simple
Two little bees flew into the flowers, flying...
Stop playing and drink quickly
Right
I planned to give this chain to the person I love the most
I wonder if you would mind being the master of this chain
Aren't you going to give it to your beloved Qin Qing?
In fact, when I first met you
I really thought you were Qin Qing
But you are you, Qin Qing is Qin Qing
It's impossible to mistake it for anything
when i first came here
I really can't let go of Qin Qing
But there is a saying that is right
Time can really dilute everything
I know clearly now
There is only you in my heart
I know better
No one is more suitable to wear this necklace than you
Miss Lu, if you are doing it for your third brother’s benefit
You shouldn't associate with him anymore
Brother Teng, what did I do wrong?
You want to stop me from interacting with Jing Jun
you are right
The mistake is that you are Lu Buwei’s daughter
I don't know what my dad did
I only know that I am me and my father is my father
What did my father do to interact with me and Jing Jun?
It doesn't matter at all
Yes, second brother, don’t be so unreasonable
Am I being unreasonable?
Lu Buwei almost killed our eldest brother
all in all
Our Taifu Mansion does not welcome anyone named Lu.
Please leave immediately
you…
Niangrong third brother
let her go
Second brother, you are going too far
How could you treat Miss Lu like this?
Third brother, I am also doing it for your own good.
you should know very well
Lu Buwei was the mastermind behind Cheng Yu's rebellion.
He even hired someone to kill our eldest brother.
If Lu Buwei and his eldest brother meet each other in battle one day,
I ask you, are you going to betray your elder brother?
Or do you want Miss Lu to kill her relatives out of justice?
I will never betray brother
But I won’t force Miss Lu either
Second brother, I can distinguish between public and private matters.
easy to say
I'm afraid that it will be difficult for you to distinguish between public and private affairs.
Now, Cheng Yu's rebellion has failed and the nine clans have been punished.
If Lu Buwei makes the same mistake again in the future,
So what do we do?
Do you want to be beheaded with him?
I…
Second brother, what did you just say?
Because Cheng Yu refused to confess
Lu Buwei is the mastermind behind the scenes
He took the blame alone and was executed at noon today.
Li Si, read out to everyone the charges against Cheng Xi.
Yes, Your Majesty
The traitor becomes a dragon and commits rebellion
The crime of assassinating the king should be punished
Cha Chengqiu has already harbored evil intentions
In the past, they fought for the position of prince
Buying murder and killing brother fails
Spread rumors and slander again
Cheng Xiu failed to accomplish his plan many times, but actually committed the crime himself
To correct the party and rebel, to assassinate the king
Only the emperor has eyes, and he will be captured if he fails.
He said: The crime of becoming a dragon is so heinous that he and his nine tribes
and be sentenced to death by beheading
They were all pulled out of the palace and circled around the city, paraded through the streets.
Then he beheaded him in front of the east city gate.
Your Majesty, can you please listen to what I have to say?
Mr. Xiang, please speak
If he rebels, he should be executed.
But his family and relatives are all innocent
Why did you kill them all?
Xiang Taifu
Do you think the reason why I want to execute them is
Is it because I am murderous?
You might as well look at the eyes of Cheng Yu and others
The look in each of their eyes
Full of hatred and spite
If I don’t kill the weeds as soon as possible today,
There will be revenge one day
So...there is no other way
They must be sentenced to death to eliminate future troubles
If your Majesty can conquer the people with virtue,
Why should we be afraid that they will retaliate?
Damn it, I'm the king of a country
The majesty of the monarch must not be shaken
I just want to take advantage of today's events
Warning to all those who intend to rebel
Anyone who betrays me
There is only a dead end in the end
Regal power does not necessarily require killing people.
Forgiving people also has royal power
There is no need to say more, Mr. Xiang, I have already made up my mind.
What's more, it has just been announced to the world
Is there any reason to take back the destiny?
This is unreasonable, Ying Zheng is simply arrogant
Those words just now were clearly referring to Sang and Huai.
Judging from the situation, it seems that the king has already understood the assassination.
Related to the prime minister
So what?
Now Chenglong has been executed, and there is no evidence of his death.
He can't do anything to me at all
It’s just that with the king’s character
Even if he is in the Ming Dynasty, he will not be able to deal with the Prime Minister
But there is no guarantee that he will not secretly murder the Prime Minister.
Ying Zheng's throne is not yet stable and he is still in his infancy.
Forgive him for not daring to act rashly
I miss you, Lu Buwei, who knows the world and has three thousand diners.
As long as I, Lu Buwei, give the order
Naturally, there are people inside and outside the government who are making comments for me.
As long as the trend of the king being humble and the minister being respectful is established,
Even if Ying Zheng doesn't want to abdicate in favor of someone more worthy, he can't
Ying Zheng, I want you to see clearly
Who is the real one in the world today?
What? You told me to let Lu Buwei go for now?
Mr. Xiang, you should know very well
Lu Buwei is so ambitious
If I don’t get rid of him today,
I'm just afraid that sooner or later he will bite me back
Also, don’t forget, Taifu Xiang
You almost died this time
It’s also thanks to him
To be honest, Lu Buwei and I actually
There's no deep hatred
He wants to kill me this time
I just want to use this matter to attack you, the king.
In short, since Lu Buwei wants to go against me,
I will never let him go
Taifu Xiang, you said
Are you willing to help others get rid of Lu Buwei?
Your Majesty, it’s not that I don’t want to help you deal with Lu Buwei
But what I care about now is more
Your Majesty, what path should you take in the future?
Lu Buwei has always been eyeing the throne of others.
As long as this person is not eliminated for one day
I walk on thin ice every day
What future is there?
Lu Buwei has been the prime minister for so long
Whether internally or externally
All have certain influence
Besides, Your Majesty, you have just ascended the throne.
Even the throne is not yet secure
In fact, you really need it
Use Lu Buwei to calm people's hearts
This will be good for you in the future
So how long do we have to wait?
History has actually been doomed for a long time
The king will definitely annihilate the six countries in the future
Unify the world
And Lu Buwei will also have a dismal ending.
Your Majesty, why are you still in a hurry?
I almost forgot
Taifu Xiang is a person from the future world
You must know about the future world
When can I get rid of Lu Buwei?
When will we be able to rule the world?
Become the Qin Shi Huangdi in the mouth of Taifu Xiang?
In fact, things in the future
It is not convenient for me to reveal too much to the king.
Because I'm afraid it will affect history
affect the results
But looking at it the other way around, if I tell you
This will only make you, my king, do nothing
What Taifu Xiang said also makes sense
But no matter what
As long as Taifu Xiang can know the past and the future,
beside the widow
I believe that I will be able to dominate the world in the future
This is the most important thing
Taifu Xiang has made great contributions to others many times
I will definitely order someone to record it in the history books.
What do you think would happen if history changed?
Come, pass on Li Si
Li Si meets the king
Li Si, I order you to bring Taifu Xiang immediately
The merits of helping others many times
Recorded in detail in history books
So that Taifu Xiang’s name will remain in history
The king really ordered Li Sijiang’s eldest brother’s deeds
Is it recorded in history books?
It’s rare for the king to put his elder brother in such high regard
Why does eldest brother still seem so unhappy?
The problem is the history books I read in my time
There are mentions of Ying Zheng, Lu Buwei, and Li Si
Even Mr. Zou’s "Theory of the Five Virtues from the Beginning to the End" mentioned it
But the three words Xiang Shaolong
Never mentioned it
Shaolong
Will it be the history book you read in the 21st century?
Because the records are too complicated and numerous
So what if you haven’t read yourself yet?
yes
Maybe when big brother returns to the future world
I will see my name in the history books again
It would be nice if it was
At least you don’t have to worry so much
But I'm just afraid before I go back
Something has happened
Big brother means...
Will Lu Buwei still harm you?
I'm not worried about Lu Buwei
Now I'm most worried about one person
It's all my fault, I said not to mention the word "death"
Don't be unhappy
I traveled a long way that day and came back with some courage.
All to fulfill your wish to return to the future world
But I don't know why, when I think of you leaving
I can't help it anymore
Stop it, it's not my decision whether to go or not.
Just let it take its course.
But as you said
You stay in ancient times for one more day
You will become more and more dangerous
I don't want anything to happen to you
Go back
Give it to you
What is it?
lucky star
Lucky star?
I'll watch the stars with you that night
Didn't you say that you really want to pick the stars from the sky?
I can't pick off the stars in the sky and give them to you
Now I will give you a lucky star instead
in our countryside
Think lucky stars can bring people luck
What's wrong?
I don’t know why every time I feel happy
I'm afraid I'll lose everything suddenly
In fact, happiness is momentary
As long as you're happy at this moment, that's fine
Who knows what will happen in the future?
Shaolong
These days are the happiest in my life
I hope I can keep it forever
The sunset is infinitely beautiful, but it’s almost dusk
If the sun never sets today
You said how good that would be
Did you know that the sunset is infinitely beautiful?
What does it mean that it's almost dusk?
Of course I know
Then why are you saying such things at this time?
What does it matter whether the sun goes down or not?
If you go down today, you will rise again tomorrow.
Although the sun rises and sets, it remains unchanged
But the change of personnel is always unpredictable
I'm afraid I'll be separated from you after today
It’s so rare to wait for thunder and lightning
Big brother is not here at all, which is really annoying
Brother, it would be nice if you came back, follow me
missed this opportunity
I don’t know how long I have to wait
What happened?
You will know if you come with me, come on
Come on, look, Brother Teng
Big brother
Thanks
Brother, have you seen it?
I added a dozen more copper coils
When thunder and lightning comes from the sky
Those fish shreds were intact
Stop talking so much and get the communicator
Shaolong, you can finally go back to the 21st century
Brother, what are you waiting for?
Such big thunder and lightning doesn't happen very often.
Come here quickly
Brother, it worked
Shaolong, please go back
missed this opportunity
You may never go back
But after I go back
I'll never come back again
That's where you belong
But you are not there
Shaolong, when you love someone, you want them to be happy
You have gone through all kinds of hardships just for this day
Since I love you
I can't even force you to stay here.
You go
Brother, the communicator is responding
Does it mean that the future world has received your signal?
Shaolong, let’s go
You go
Brother, let’s go, it’s too late if it’s too late
Shaolong, let’s go. We’re almost out of time.
Shaolong, let's go. We can't make it in time. Let's go.
Shaolong, take care of yourself
Shaolong
Big brother
Unexpectedly, there was a big thunder and lightning
They actually created a match made in heaven
It’s hard for me, I spent so much effort
In the end, being a villain is useless
What's wrong with being a villain?
If it weren’t for my second brother, you are smart
How can you force your eldest brother to decide to stay?
Our future sister-in-law
How can I be as happy as I am now?
Are you laughing from the bottom of your heart?
I said, second brother, you have been their matchmaker this time.
By the way, brother, what should I do with this communicator?
I have decided not to go back
If you like it, take it
Otherwise, just throw it away
No, throw it away if one day he
Shaolong, if you regret it, what should you do?
I will keep this communicator for the time being.
Qing'er, according to godfather, you are not interested in keeping
but to prevent future
What if the young dragon cannot leave when he wants to?
Even my godfather, you make fun of me
I think Mr. Zou must have been stunned by the electric shock.
You are stupid, you can leave even if you don't want to
I would rather stay here and be an ancient person
Qing'er, let's talk about it
You should toast Mr. Teng with a glass of matchmaking wine
As long as everyone is happy, I'm happy to be the host
Are you good at drinking?
Of course this kind of thing is done by men
Third brother, go get some wine
Stop fighting, brother
In short, one meal per person will never fail
Future sister-in-law, are you right?
Yes...one meal per person
good
Third brother, you really have a way
Even Jixiang Winery
You can also buy Daqu Zunjiu that has been treasured for many years
Of course, it’s rare that today my eldest brother thanks the media
Are we going to drink bad wine?
Second brother
A lot of gold, go and take a look...
Second brother, he said there is a lot of gold ahead
Go over and have a look
A word of gold? What is it?
Brother, do you know what it is? Brother
I don't know, brother
A word worth a thousand dollars?
Second brother, what word is this so valuable?
"Valuable" is not a word
They are all the talented people under the leadership of Prime Minister Lu
The astonishing masterpiece "Lu's Spring and Autumn Annals" compiled by
Lu's Spring and Autumn Period?
This set of Lu's Spring and Autumn Annals is truly incisive and unique.
Every word is a pearl
So Prime Minister Lu specially rewarded
As long as anyone can change any word in the book
You can get a thousand gold reward
Come and see, one word is worth a thousand taels of gold
Let's go and see
Li Taishi
Brother Teng, Brother Jing
Li Taishi, I really didn’t expect that
Even you want to get Lu Buwei's thousand gold reward
You two don't know anything
Li Si used to be under the Prime Minister's door
Lu's Chunqiu also contributed to the writing
According to Taishi's opinion
Is it true that not a single word of Lu's Spring and Autumn Annals can be deleted or modified?
It's not as simple as it seems
More than one word of Lu's Spring and Autumn Period is worth a thousand pieces of gold
This Lu's Spring and Autumn Annals dares to boast that every word is worth a fortune
There must be some extraordinary opinions contained in the book
I still can't believe that not a single word in it can be changed.
You don’t know something anymore
Lu's Spring and Autumn Period is Prime Minister Lu
It was compiled by combining the strengths of hundreds of his disciples.
It’s really every word.
Not to mention anything else, it was just what Lu Shi Chunqiu proposed.
Talented people should be elected to govern the country
Just what he said in the minds of the people all over the world
Now we have been fighting for many years, and we have just completed our military service
We have to rush to build the Great Wall again
The monarch who works so hard for the people
May I ask who is capable?
It's a pity that the current king is not only ignorant of the people's sentiments
They even forced a wedding during the period of observing filial piety, regardless of filial piety.
Eliminate dissidents and kill your own brothers
It’s true that both humans and gods are angry
Therefore, Lu's Spring and Autumn Period also proposed
If the king is foolish and unprincipled
We should choose more talented people and return the government to the people
Really insightful
You're right...choose a worthy person...
Words are tools to express emotions
How could it not be possible to change it?
It’s just about the relationship between the Lu family and
So no one dares to change
I really bow down to Lu Buwei
To be able to act like this
Thinking about the time when I was under the sect of Lu Mansion
He also participated in the writing of Lu's Spring and Autumn Annals
The reason why Lu Buwei wanted to write Lu's Spring and Autumn Annals
The purpose is only to spread bad words against the king.
Make a move for him
I have just read this volume of Lu's Spring and Autumn Annals
Although it combines hundreds of political theories into one
But in the final analysis
The focus is always on advocating the idea that the king is humble and the people are valued
and the abdication system that promoted Yao and Shun
Lu Buwei used this to create public opinion
Praise yourself, belittle the king
Obviously he wants to take his place as king
Mr. Xiang, if we don't stop this immediately,
I'm afraid Lu Buwei will become more and more popular.
The time of great achievement
At that time, only the monarch and his ministers will change their positions.
The status of the king is not guaranteed
Don't worry
No matter how powerful Lu Buwei's power is,
History is always doomed
He always ended up miserable.
Why is this so?
Godfather, what happened?
Just now I watched the stars
Found that the new star of the emperor was dim
And there is a faint tendency of decline
This is a sign of great evil
How could it be?
Brother, Eunuch Zhao is here
Eunuch Zhao is here
Taifu Xiang, I don’t know what happened to the king.
I have been locking myself in the palace bedroom today.
Don't let the slaves in
I just ordered my servant to invite Taifu Xiang into the palace as soon as possible.
Report to the king, Taifu Xiang has arrived
King
Xiang Taifu
This time it's amazing
Look, I can't see myself in the mirror
Actually even you, Taifu Xiang...
Tell me quickly
Is the widowed person going to die soon?