Our little princess does sew every day
I miss Xiang Shaolong day and night
You Jing Jun
The third brother didn’t even call out.
Why do I call you third brother?
I am Brother Xiang’s sworn brother
Don't you want to call me third brother?
Third brother, be good
It turned out to be a scented towel
Hang on the man's body and remember the sister's heart
Brother will be very happy to see you
Xiaoqian is not in the mood to joke with you
I know you are worried about your brother's safety
Don't worry, big brother always turns danger into good fortune.
But the one we have to deal with is Zhao Mu
What about Zhao Mu?
With the intelligence of the eldest brother and the help of the second brother
Zhao Mu will definitely be captured without hesitation.
It's easy to say, but I just got pricked by a needle
I'm afraid it's an ominous sign
Being pricked by a needle is said to be a bad omen
Prince Zheng doesn’t need to make a special trip to invite a wizard back.
Start a hexagram to ask about good or bad luck.
I'm not the only one who said Brother is fine
Even the wizard's oracles
He also said that the eldest brother would live up to his orders and come back.
prosperous
real?
If you don’t believe it, you can ask Wang Zizheng for confirmation.
How could the wizard's inscriptions be piled up randomly by me?
Brother will be back soon
You should finish sewing this scarf soon.
Otherwise, there will be no time to make the wedding dress.
Your mouth should be sewn shut with needle and thread
My mouth can only speak happy and pleasant words
If someone is really cruel and wants to sew my mouth shut
If someone is unhappy then, there is nothing I can do about it.
Our country of Qin is located in the west
The other six countries all regard Qin as a barbarian.
Qin Xiaogong's political reform and Bude's political reform
In order to make Qin rich and powerful
Duke Xiao appointed Shang Yang to carry out reforms
Wang Zizheng…
This prince can hear it
Let’s continue talking about Shang Yang’s reforms. Yes
Shang Yang believed that as long as a saint can strengthen the country
There is no need to follow ancient methods
As long as it benefits the people, there is no need to follow the old etiquette
Shang Yang's views are somewhat similar to Xiang Dafu's.
Taifu Xiang is also a person who does not adhere to ancient methods.
People who don’t cling to the old ways
Often he is unexpected and bold in his words and deeds
Just like the relationship with Princess Zhao Qian
Not only did he break the ethics, but he also disobeyed the king's order.
Yes, it’s indeed heartwarming
Prince Zheng, let’s get back to business.
In the sixth year of Qin Xiaogong, Shang Yang carried out reforms
First, establish the system of fifteen consecutive sittings
Take five families as one and five, and two and five as ten.
The law stipulates that picketing each other on the 15th
Fifteen...unknowingly
It has been more than thirty days since Taifu Xiang left Qin and entered Zhao.
We should be on our way home, is there any obstacle?
Do you think whether Taifu Xiang can successfully capture Zhao Mu and return?
Prince Zheng doesn’t have to worry
Taifu Xiang will definitely live up to his trust
Wang Zizheng…
Xiao Gao, is there any news about Taifu Xiang?
Report to the prince, the king has arrived
The child meets his father and mother
See the king
Wang Er
The lonely king also knows that you have been working hard here recently.
The child was trapped in Zhao country
I wasted a lot of study time, so I have to make up for it
Fortunately, I have Li Si reading with me.
Studying hard is a good thing
But Zheng'er, you should also pay attention to your health
That’s right, you also need to exercise besides studying.
Only when you have a strong body can you manage everything on a daily basis
Therefore, the skills of riding, archery and swordsmanship cannot be neglected.
That's right, as a prince of Qin
Must be proficient in riding, archery and swordsmanship
So that he can lead troops to fight at any time in the future
It's a pity that Taifu Xiang has not returned for a long time
No one accompanies Zheng'er to practice sword practice
If the prince wants to practice martial arts
The villain is always there for you
The child is only worried about Taifu Xiang and has no interest in practicing
King Hui
The guards at the Qin-Zhao border post reported quickly.
Taifu Xiang has successfully captured Zhao Mu alive
Now on the way back to Xianyang
Taifu Xiang has indeed lived up to expectations. Okay, step down.
Taifu Xiang is wise and resourceful
Even Zhao Mu, a dog thief, can be captured alive
It's really not simple, yes
Capture Zhao Mu and return to Qin
The lady and the prince can take revenge.
Congratulations
Taifu Xiang made a great contribution this time
Father must reward you well
Prince, what should the lonely king reward Taifu Xiang?
Or should I give him some official position?
This matter is decided by the father.
this…
Your Majesty, based on the friendship between the prince and Taifu Xiang,
In fact, we can make him Prime Minister
There are already left and right prime ministers
Do we still need to make him a Prime Minister?
Third brother, are you tired?
Not tired, go shopping with the princess
It's what my eldest brother told me to do. I'm not tired.
The shop in front seems to sell clothing and fabrics.
let's go and see
But we have bought a lot of things
I don't have much talent. Now the dowry is distributed publicly.
How can it be so shabby? Let’s go
walk faster
Brat, trying to take advantage
Girl, if you're blind
Just don't go out casually
How unreasonable
It was you who bumped into me first, yet you were so rude
you…
Third brother, we bumped into this girl
I'm not right, girl, I'm sorry
Don't worry, this girl
This girl is a great person and does not remember the faults of small people.
you…
Third brother, stop arguing, let's go in
Boss, I can just look at it myself. Okay...
You two, would you like to choose clothing or fabric?
Boss, we want to choose the best fabrics
It's used to make wedding clothes
Of course, the wedding dress requires red material.
We have some fine red fabric
It must suit your liking, come and take a look
Come on...these horses are of the finest red material.
See if you like it?
I want this cloth...
These two girls are really discerning
This fine silk
Fine workmanship, novel patterns, rare
It's a pity that I can only make one dress
What? You can only make one dress
Let's buy it, let's rush to make the wedding dress
The cloth that this girl likes must be bought.
You are really unreasonable
Girl, do you know what adult beauty is?
If so, be more polite
This girl should also be able to be beautiful as an adult
To an unreasonable person like you
Why should I be polite?
Third brother, since this girl doesn’t want to give up love
There is no need for us to force ourselves
Boss, together with these red cloths beside
Wrap them all up for me
You are so unruly, you can't get married even if you want to
You buy all the red cloth to make shrouds
You are so vicious
Aren't you afraid of losing your children and grandchildren?
What did you say? Say it again
Third brother, no
A gentle and beautiful girl
She actually wants to marry an uncultured brat
It's like a flower stuck in cow dung
You really have little knowledge
Standing in front of you is Princess Zhao Qian of Zhao State
The one she wants to marry is Xiang Shaolong, Taifu Xiang
What? Envy, jealousy, or shame?
Look at your deer head and rat eyes
It should not be Xiang Taifu Xiang Shaolong himself
May I ask what your surname is?
I am Xiang…
It seems that you are no longer famous
Frivolous and impetuous, I simply don’t know what it means
May I ask what your surname is?
Princess Zhao Qian
Thank you for parting with me. See you again when we are destined.
You haven't said your bad name yet
Sir, keep your voice down
She is Lu Niangrong, the daughter of today’s Prime Minister Lu
What about Lu Buwei’s daughter?
Third brother, Brother Xiang said not to cause trouble
Third brother, how do you understand these three grown men?
Fighting till the face turns red
Are they fighting over who has the stronger arm?
It's a gambling game
Look at the two of them
Let's see who can take the Kunlun slave in the middle first
If you pull out of the circle, you can win the dealer's money
Okay, who else wants to try their arm strength?
This girl wants to try
Okay, this girl bets a copper coin
Who dares to come up?
I
Women show their faces
Just let me accompany you once
A majestic man won over a woman
Not necessarily glorious either
Okay, I will let you
You use both hands, uncle uses one hand
That's okay
OK, if you lose
I must return that piece of cloth with both hands
good
you lose
Miss, you are too happy too early
The loser is you
Can't you see that Kunlun slave fell on my side?
Please be willing to admit defeat and return the cloth with both hands
OK, Xiao Tao, give me the yellow cloth
You don't keep your word, what I want is red cloth
I'm willing to admit defeat, the cloth has been given to you
You didn't say you wanted red cloth just now
you…
Brother Xiang told him not to cause trouble
Bizarre, this is your careful design
It’s the perfect fit for dad.
What kind of appearance do you have? The style is weird and the clothes don’t fit you.
What do you want me to wear?
Your father is the prime minister
How can you wear such strange clothes?
You said you want to be well-informed and travel around the world
Dad lets you go
If you don’t come back from learning piano, chess, calligraphy and painting, you will only become addicted...
What fancy clothes to design?
What fancy clothes?
My daughter is also well-informed
I just designed this pajamas.
Night clothes?
You can wear this pajamas to bed without a quilt
You don’t have to worry about catching a cold when you take a walk in the courtyard at night.
What's wrong with my pajamas?
It’s hard to spend all your time on your daughter
Design this dress for you
Not only do you not appreciate it at all, but you also make a lot of negative comments.
It's not that I don't like it
It's just that dad didn't know this was called pajamas.
As long as you don't have to wear it outside to show others
It's a big deal that Dad won't take it off today.
You said it yourself
How dare I offend my good daughter
Ronger, since you returned to Xianyang
Just go shopping, big and small bags
It seems like I want to buy the whole market back home
My daughter loves sewing clothes the most
Of course I bought the most beautiful clothing fabrics.
Dad doesn’t know how to appreciate clothes and fabrics.
Dad, but some people will appreciate it
Even Princess Zhao Qian of Zhao State
She also has the same good taste as her daughter
Princess Zhao Qian?
And her future husband Xiang Taifu Xiang Shaolong
Who is he? I’ve never heard of him before.
You just returned to Xianyang, and you received new news so quickly
Dad, I want to know about Xiang Shaolong
Does it match Princess Zhao Qian?
I have seen with my own eyes the beauty of Princess Zhao Qian
Who is that Xiang Shaolong? Dad, tell me
Dad takes care of everything
How can I have so much time to gossip with you?
Dad, I want to know, you said
Okay, let dad tell you slowly
Xiang Shaolong is in Zhao Kingdom...
It's so deceiving
Third brother, you don’t have to be angry
Don't be angry, this girl named Lu
He obviously relies on his father being the prime minister
That's quite unreasonable
Actually, this girl is also very cute
So cute, she knew that the piece of cloth was used to make the wedding dress
She won't let it go to you either, and you still say she's cute
She is just playful
This piece of cloth can't be used as a wedding dress, but it can also be used as casual clothes.
Princess, why are you so good?
People obviously treat you badly
You also think people are treating you well
Third brother, you are usually tolerant of everything to others.
Why are you targeting this Miss Lu in particular?
Because people named Lu are particularly annoying
Princess, there is a girl named Lu outside who wants to see you.
If you have bad intentions, please leave quickly
The person I want to see is Princess Zhao Qian
Please get out of the way quickly
Miss Lu
Princess Zhao Qian
Why did Miss Lu come to visit?
A gentleman does not take away people's love
Niangrong made a special trip to send this red cloth material
To Princess Zhao Qian
In fact, Niang Rong did not intend to compete with the princess for cloth.
It’s just that I’ve always loved tailoring clothes since I was a child.
I can't put it down as soon as I see good fabrics
If the princess doesn't dislike it
Niang Rong also wanted to personally design the wedding dress for the princess.
Then I would be disrespectful
Arrogant at the front but respectful at the back, with ulterior motives
Princess, Brother Xiang often says
It is essential to be on guard against others
This girl is your prime minister’s daughter
To you, an unknown brat
What would be the intention?
This girl just wants to make friends with the princess
What does it have to do with you?
I have never designed a wedding dress for anyone
I just drew a few random patterns
Do you like it?
Miss Lu, you are too polite
Princess, have some tea.
drink tea
If you are curious about everything
You might as well do a flower bun
Wear a dress and pretend to be your daughter
In this way
Our three daughters can talk about our concerns together at home.
If something happens to the princess, she can shout loudly at any time
If we want to use tea again, we will naturally call you
Miss Lu
The styles you designed are all unique.
Xiaoqian is really hard to choose
If the princess wants to marry
They are ordinary princes, generals, noble ministers
Designing a wedding dress
It's not Niangrong's turn to worry about it at all
The princess doesn’t have to go to the market herself
Choose the right clothing material
But now the princess wants to marry
Is the love that overcomes all difficulties and shares life and death together
So the wedding dress should be a little more unique.
Do you know what happened between me and Brother Xiang?
I only know a little about it from my father's mouth
The twists and turns in it must be quite touching.
Give up everything to pursue what you love and want
Finally, lovers can finally get married
Niang Rong is the most envious
I heard that Taifu Xiang and Princess Zhao Qian were both talented and beautiful.
He's still very nice to you
Xiaoqian used to be like a caged bird
I never imagined that I could be with the one I love
if i don't run away
I just met Miss Lu.
Thank you for your courage
Otherwise I would have lost one good friend
I think we are very compatible
Niangrong is really interested
I want to know more about you and Taifu Xiang
Okay, why don't you stay for dinner?
I'm sorry, we can have a heart-to-heart talk tonight
Come over and take a look at the style, okay
This one is also very beautiful, you see
Lao Ai meets Madam
Mr. Lai came to pick up Prime Minister Lu again. Yes
My wife seems to have reduced her income recently.
Life in the palace is rich and luxurious
The lady is favored by the king again
Why are you still frowning?
If there is no gossip in the palace
No malicious slander from sinister villains
Of course, you can stretch your brows, and your heart will be wide and your body will be fat.
It turns out that Madam is for
Unnecessary gossip is unpleasant
Wouldn’t the person who caused trouble get what he wanted?
There is a saying that one mountain cannot hide two tigers
Tigers blocking the road should be eradicated
Rather than sit back and wait for death, it is better to strike preemptively
Mr. Lao, if you are not in your position, you will not do anything.
I just care about my wife and have no other intentions
Absolutely no other intention?
The lady is in the palace
There are only two relatives, the king and Wang Zizheng
Everyone else is my lady's enemy
If there is no old friend in the palace
Who else can take care of Madam’s worries?
My wife and I finally have some connection
Of course I will be happy to share your worries for Madam
Report to Your Majesty: Madam Huagui and Prince Zheng are requesting an audience.
Passed Yes
The king has an order to pass on the noble lady and the prince's government.
My concubine meets the king
The child meets his father
Okay, free of charge
Madam, Zheng'er, what do you want to see the lonely king for?
Your Majesty is busy with things
The king has invited his concubine and Zheng'er to have a meal
I am troubled by this and I don’t know the time. Please forgive me, madam.
Your Majesty pays most attention to political affairs, he is indeed a wise king
It is unknown whether the child can share the troubles for his father?
Tingwei in charge of the palace guards
He actually bent the law for personal gain and has been dismissed from his post and investigated.
Now the king is arranging candidates
The inner court guards in the palace have great responsibilities
Zheng'er has been attacked and frightened more than once
King, you need to arrange the candidates as soon as possible
fill this gap
Of course
Wei Chen suggested that it would be better to come from outside the customs
Choose a general with extraordinary skills
Return to the palace and serve as a court lieutenant
As the saying goes, water far away cannot put out fire nearby.
Redeploying manpower from border areas
Back and forth, it takes too long
It’s better to find another talent
Your Majesty, I have a suitable candidate in my mind.
It’s Lao Ai, the bodyguard in Prime Minister Lu’s palace.
Lao Ai?
That's right, Lao Ai saved Zheng'er from danger twice
His skills are indeed extraordinary
That's right, but Lao Ai is Prime Minister Lu's beloved general
In this case, doesn't it mean that Prime Minister Lu must cut off his love?
Prime Minister Lu always puts the king and state affairs first
Always very generous
As long as the king needs or likes it
Even if Prime Minister Lu is the most beloved
I will also offer it with both hands, Prime Minister Lu, do you think so?
Madam knows that the old minister is loyal to the king.
Prime Minister Lu is so loyal that heaven and earth can monitor him
What we want now is not Prime Minister Lu’s wife and children
Just a guard
Prime Minister Lu will definitely be willing to part ways with her
That being the case
He promoted Lao Ai to the position of palace lieutenant.
Father, although Lao Ai is a suitable candidate
But the child feels that there is someone more qualified than him
He is Xiang Taifu Xiang Shaolong
In terms of martial arts, he is better than Lao Ai
In terms of intelligence, no one can match it
Moreover, he and his children are both teachers and friends.
Wouldn't it be better if he stayed in the palace to accompany the children?
That's right, Your Majesty
Taifu Xiang is indeed better than Lao Ai
Please, Your Majesty, listen to Wang Zizheng’s opinion.
But Taifu Xiang still has a mission and is out of town.
The station has sent back the message
Taifu Xiang will return to Xianyang soon
Mom, my child doesn’t want to go against your will.
But if there is Taifu Xiang to protect the child,
The child will feel more at ease
Xiang Shaolong was successful in capturing Zhao Mu alive and should be promoted
In this case, just follow Zheng'er's wishes
The subordinates see the Prime Minister
Do you know why I have called you?
Does the Prime Minister have something important to send to his subordinates?
Today you are the guard in my house
Take orders from me, Lu Buwei
But with your intelligence and skill
One day it will soar into the sky
The gorgeous lady is in front of the king
I highly recommend you to take up the post of palace lieutenant.
The king is also very satisfied with you
Heroic performance in rescuing Wang Zizheng twice
You are indeed very capable
You can actually get Mrs. Huagui to recommend you personally
If my subordinates have this opportunity, it is because they are promoted by the Prime Minister.
If you are talented and loyal,
Of course the truth can be greatly improved
If you have a crooked mind, you will follow the wrong path
In its true form, it can also be trampled into underground mud
My subordinates have always been loyal to the Prime Minister.
The sun and the moon can monitor
Loyal and loyal, the sun and moon can monitor you
I advise you not to flatter the noble lady anymore
No matter how you are promoted,
How does Madam Huagui recommend you?
How does the king appreciate you?
Not as good as a prince
For the position of lieutenant in the palace, the prince has already chosen Xiang Shaolong.
Xiang Shaolong happened to capture Zhao Mu and made great achievements.
You are always one step behind
You should stay in the house and submit
Just stay safe and become a bodyguard.
You look so tired
It must be caused by rushing to make the wedding dress day and night.
Have you finished sewing the wedding dress?
Just a little decoration left, it's almost complete
just a few days
The princess has completed a wedding dress, and she is indeed very skillful
Mrs. Xiang hasn't arrived yet, but the wedding dress has already been prepared.
You really want to marry
But Niangrong also envies you
Can have a day and night hanging
The worried husband
You said I want to get married, but you're not the same
My daughter’s family all want to find the right person
With Niang Rong’s beauty and character
She must be the ideal person in the minds of many men
It's because you have high standards
The young master who came to Lu Mansion to propose marriage
Nine times out of ten, they all want to curry favor with my father.
Stop talking about me, let’s talk about your wedding dress.
I think my wedding dress is a bit boring
If you want to add some decorations, please give me some advice.
Decoration? Which is better, embroidery or ribbons?
concentric knot
Concentric knot?
Adding a concentric knot on the wedding dress means we will always be of the same heart
Good luck, come here
many different styles
Of course
They are all collected by Niang Rong from various countries.
This one, this one is the most suitable for your wedding dress.
so beautiful
In fact, except for this
Niangrong also wants to give you something
It's a little white rabbit
You meet your Brother Xiang
All because of a little white rabbit
It means that the little white rabbit is your matchmaker
It's impossible to find the one before
So I'll give you a new one
it's so cute
I really want to see how much your brother Xiang takes care of you
Is it like you take care of a little white rabbit?
Take care of you so much
Thank you, I really don’t know how to repay you
We are sisters, you're welcome
Miss, the master wants to see you
Dad wants to see me? I'm greeting guests
It's getting late, it's time for me to go
The carriage is waiting for me outside
Oh well
Make the wedding dress and bring it to me to see
When Xiang Shaolong returns to Qin, he must pass by Longfeng Inn
So I started to kill the princess.
Why panic?
The little white rabbit is missing, I'm looking for it
I'm going to find the little white rabbit
The letter in your hand is mine
What do you want?
I want to kill people and silence them
Please, don’t kill Brother Xiang
Brother Xiang is a good person
He didn't harm you, why did you kill him?
Because if you have me, you can’t have Xiang Shaolong
I don't want to kill you
It's a pity that God wants you to see things you shouldn't see.
You can only die with him
if you kill me
Brother Xiang will definitely avenge me
How can the dead take revenge?
No, Brother Xiang will not die
God will definitely bless him
You have evil intentions and are despicable and vicious
There will definitely be retribution
If it weren’t for Xiang Shaolong’s appearance,
I won’t lose my beloved Fang’er
My destiny will not be reversed
Don't blame me
It’s only my fault that you are Xiang Shaolong’s woman
Brother, are you okay?
I don’t know why, but suddenly my eyes twitched a little bit
i.e. restless
After passing the small town in front is Xianyang
Are you worried that Zhao Mu will be kidnapped?
It's going to rain
See if there is a place to rest ahead
Welcome, thank you for your hard work...
Come on, pack your things
Welcome, guest...Thank you for your hard work
Come... feel free... have a glass of water and wine
Alan, come and greet the guests, hurry up
This way…
Thank you for your hard work. Dear guests, please take a seat...
Four guest officers, right?
Please take a seat...have some drinks first
We have very good side dishes
What do you want?
Just write me some side dishes
OK, be there soon
How unreasonable
Sorry, don't break it. Take it over quickly.
Sorry, my hands are shaking
Big brother
Really come up
Sir, here comes the wine
She has a voice like an old cow and pretends to be pregnant
Sir, please use it with caution
Say, who ordered you?
Brother, they are not as simple as ordinary robbers
Qing'er, have you made a decision?
There are three roads here, heading north is beyond the Great Wall.
To the south is the Kingdom of Wei, to the west is the Kingdom of Qin
Where should we go?
Let's go north
Heading north? Beyond the Great Wall is a bitter and cold place.
Qing'er, do you want to torture yourself?
Or do you want to torture your godfather?
godfather
Good daughter, now you are tortured in your heart
Although I know medical skills, I don’t know how to treat heart disease
Youdao is that a heart disease requires a heart medicine doctor
I'm afraid I won't have the medicine you need until you go to Qin.
The godfather talks more and more mysteriously, and my daughter doesn’t understand at all.
More mysterious
It is the star that represents the new saint. It is sometimes dark and sometimes bright.
What I saw last night has moved westward
Appeared in Wei State on that day
Xiang Shaolong also appeared in Wei State
Moved to Zhao Kingdom, Xiang Shaolong appeared in Zhao Kingdom again
Now the new star is moving westward
Xiang Shaolong returns to Qin by coincidence
Could it be that the new saint who will unify the six countries is Xiang Shaolong?
Godfather, is your guess far-fetched?
Guesses should be verified
But no matter what
I must seek clarification and ask for clarification.
To avoid worrying about you day and night and torturing yourself in your heart
The godfather decided to go west to Qin State
Qing'er, are you following?
It's up to you to decide
I am now the prince of the Qin Kingdom
Mother, I will avenge you today
Go back
Yes, Taifu
Big brother…
Something happened to the princess
How could anything happen to the princess who was so good?
I asked you to take care of her
Damn Jing Jun, the princess went to Lu Mansion that day
I didn't follow, so the princess disappeared.
Now it turns out...