Cloud-Piercing Arrow
You extras
well played
I thought you were a master swordsman
Unexpectedly, it is nothing more than this, vulnerable
Before, you bullied the weak and humiliated me in public.
Not only that, I also want to seduce my young master’s mother
Now new and old grudges
I will settle matters with you once and for all.
Lift it out...
Take him down and eat the whole bucket of shit
How much did he give you?
twelve taels
Extras are so cheap here
There are more than ten liang here, right?
yes…
How could this happen? You guys
Being a human being does not necessarily require the use of force to solve problems
Problems can also be solved using your brain
What? Do you like forcing people to eat feces?
Come, eat it yourself
If you want to kill, kill
Why should I kill you? I'm not you
I just want you to eat shit
I'll give you a chance
If you are willing to kneel down and kowtow to me three times
I'll let you go
I will never kneel down and beg for mercy.
So brave? Then I can't help you.
Eat
Why bother doing it like this?
Only now do I know what it means to harm others and ultimately harm yourself.
Don't do this next time
Next time, don't fall into my hands
Shaolong, I have been waiting for you for a long time.
Madam, I'm so sorry
Because I was delayed by a group of villains on the road just now.
So I'm late
A villain is blocking the way? Are the servants being held back?
No, just some unimportant people
Ignore them
Madam, shall we start admiring the flowers?
OK
Madam's flowers are blooming so beautifully
As pretty as a lady
It can be described in four words
It’s the beauty and fragrance of the country
The country is beautiful and fragrant? You are so flattering
It's not a compliment. Madam, you are young and beautiful.
And it's so well maintained
There is such a big mansion
It's really enviable
If Shaolong you like
You can be the owner of this mansion
Isn't it?
There is a person who is thirsty for talents
I admire Shaolong’s wit, strategy, talents and skills very much.
He hopes to recruit you as his disciple
As long as Shaolong agrees
This mansion will immediately become your residence
And beauties, fragrant cars, and gold
sounds really attractive
But I wonder if that includes you, madam?
Brother Xiang really has a vision
A man of courage and intelligence
Why worry about not having a woman?
I believe that your wife also admires you very much
Brother Xiang, please
Do you like this mansion?
I like...it's so big and luxurious, of course I like it
But I have never lived in such a big mansion.
I'm afraid I might not get used to it
Everyone has their own preferences
If Brother Xiang can serve me,
You can definitely do whatever you want
But I'm used to being free
suddenly need to serve others
I'm afraid I really won't get used to it
People always want something, and there is always a price
Brother Xiang, just say it
But there is such a thing as freedom
It can't be bought with money
I hope you will understand, Mr. Hou.
In this way, it is not speculative to be honest.
Madam, could you please greet him for me?
yes
Madam, the owner of your big house has such a character.
Shaolong
Why do you have to reject Mr. Hou in person and contradict him?
I'm afraid there will be trouble in the future
I'm afraid it will be more troublesome if I do things for him
You were in the garden just now
Have you asked the Marquis if he would send me away?
Madam, I was just joking in the garden just now
I didn't mean it
I hope you understand, madam, and don't make me angry
In fact, a man must achieve great achievements
What's the point of sacrificing a woman?
Madam, why do you say this?
In fact, I respect Madam very much
The most important thing for a person is to live a wonderful life
It doesn't matter whether you have money or beauty.
The most important thing is that you can do what you like to do
If you are always at the mercy of others
So what’s the point of being a human being?
It's a pity that everyone's fate is beyond their control
especially women women
Look at it from my perspective
I think men and women should be equal
If you can have the courage, madam
I believe you will be like me
Can do the same
May I?
sure
Just think about it, if you start from now on
You can change your lifestyle
You can spend more time caring for your son
Then your son will also care about you
He will naturally come back to you
Then he won't go out and cause trouble.
Do you think so?
Is it too late to wake up and make corrections now?
Of course not, doing it is better than not doing it
It's better than never doing it anyway
It seems that Shaolong also has worries in his heart
Don't know why?
Madam, you really seem like a psychologist
But even if I tell you my worries
You can't help me either
I'm afraid Shaolong still has a grudge against me.
So it’s inconvenient to say it clearly
Of course I have no grudge against you
I treat you like my friend
But you really can't help me with my problem.
If you need my help, just ask
I am willing to go through fire and water
Then thank you in advance, madam.
But if you have anything, you must tell me
Not only am I going through fire and water
Even if it means going up a mountain of swords or going down a frying pan
I can do it even if I hang myself from a beam.
really?
Of course it's true
Shaolong, I really have something to ask of you.
You don’t want me to hang myself from the rafter now, do you?
Can you accept me as your apprentice?
Brother Xiang
Mrs. Ya seriously gives this pot of special orchid to you.
Do you also think this potted flower is beautiful?
More than that, you know?
This orchid is abundant in the Xiongnu
General Li Mu defeated the Huns
The King of the Huns sought peace
I specially ordered someone to send three pots of this orchid to Handan.
As a result, a pot was placed in the palace of King Zhao
Give one pot to Zhao Mu as a reward
The last pot was given to Mrs. Ya.
Now Mrs. Ya actually gives this pot of flowers to you
It seems that Mrs. Ya values ​​you very much.
It's just a pot of flowers. Look how elegant you say it.
If you like it so much, I’ll give it to you.
Is it true?
Of course it's true
No, as the saying goes: a gentleman does not take away people’s love
What's more, Mrs. Ya specially gave this pot of flowers to you.
How can you let her down? No way...
That's good
You talk like you are a master of flower cultivation
Please help me plant it
Help me water the water every day, is that okay?
That's no problem
Planting this kind of flower can only drip water
Watering is absolutely not allowed
Really? Otherwise this flower…
Manager Tao, when did he become the gardener of Wujiabao?
Miss
Mr. Tao must be very leisurely.
There are so many things to do in Wujiapu
He actually came here to teach people how to grow evil flowers.
What evil flower? You are so ignorant
Tell her what Mr. Tao said just now
What is this potted flower? Iron King Kong defeated the Huns
Just snatched it back
If a person is not upright
Of course they are evil flowers.
I advise you to plant carefully
Otherwise, one may accidentally plant it to death.
make people unhappy
I'm afraid it will be difficult for you to be a guest again.
But I miss this evil flower
Definitely not as good as those domestic flowers
After more than 20 years of planting, the domestic flowers have already gone bad.
Xiang Shaolong
(Shit, I am like a governor, life is cheaper than an ant)
Xiang Shaoxia, this confidential letter has just arrived from Xianyang
i have seen
It’s more sloppy than English. What should you write?
It was written by Prime Minister Lu himself
He said that Yang Quanjun, the left prime minister of Qin, wanted to lobby the King of Qin
Make the second prince Cheng Xi the crown prince
What? What should Ying Zheng do?
good
So Prime Minister Lu said about saving Ying Zheng’s mother and son
Must be fast
besides
besides?
Prime Minister Lu sent someone to deliver a token
He said that Zhu Ji and her son saw this white jade ring
Just know that we are the ones who save them
Too bad, I still can't find out
Where are their mother and son hidden, and what should they do?
Brother Xiang
Have you ever thought about starting with Mrs. Ya?
Mrs. Ya has a close relationship with Zhao Mu
This time I invite you suddenly
It's obviously Zhao Mu's intention
I want to use Mrs. Ya to test you.
If this thing is true
We should not stay in Handan for a long time
It is even more urgent to save Ying Zheng’s mother and son
Since Mrs. Ya has contact with Zhao Mu
She may know the whereabouts of Zhu Ji's mother and son
So starting from her is also a way
younger sister
Big brother
Look how much big brother loves you. When you say you want a rabbit,
I'll go up the mountain to catch it immediately
It took me two hours to catch it.
I know you worked hard
At worst, I'll be in front of the princess
Let me say a few more nice words for you
Even if you still care about me, your big brother
Why catch a rabbit for no reason?
The rabbit the princess used to raise died of illness a few days ago
Usually in the palace, the princess seldom sees people
Just rely on that rabbit to relieve boredom
So I want to give her a rabbit
I really can’t tell that you care about the princess too.
Here you go, but be careful, it's very cunning
Got it, don't worry
ran in
What are you afraid of? Go in and look for it
This room belongs to the thief, I won't go in
Don't be afraid, the guy named Xiang isn't here anyway.
Don't move
Still can't catch you?
You don't break anything, but you want to break this potted flower.
I knocked over a pot of flowers, what's the big deal?
you don't understand
Don't do it again. It's all broken anyway. Let's go.
what to do?
Did you break my potted flower?
Which of your eyes saw that I broke your potted flower?
I saw with both eyes that you damaged my potted flower.
You are really a petty person.
It can be done this way, are you right?
Mr. Xiang, you are really... Yeah
I'm a kid, I came in on purpose and broke your flowers
So what?
Now it's you who broke my flower
You are actually more fierce than me, you are really powerful
Do you want to see an official?
I'll call an ambulance and take you to the hospital.
See if you are mentally ill?
Neurosis, it’s really miserable
Princess, don't you like this rabbit?
no
I see
The princess must still remember the rabbit that died of illness
Tingfang
We may not be able to see each other again soon
Why?
Both Wei and South Korea sent people to propose marriage to their father.
Now I'm just waiting for my father to make a decision
What about the princess? Have you decided?
I?
Have you ever thought about yourself
Would you rather marry in South Korea or Wei?
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Wedding is a major event, it is related to your lifelong happiness, princess
Of course it's up to you to decide
I don’t even know the person I’m about to marry
I don’t know whether I’m tall or short, fat or thin.
The princess can marry neither of them
Neither of them will marry?
Tingfang, I am different from you
There are many things that I can't decide on my own
Princess, you haven’t tried it yet
How do you know it's not possible?
Just like this rabbit
You didn't ask about it
How do you know she likes to eat vegetables?
Maybe it doesn't like it at all and only likes to eat radishes
Be it vegetables or radishes
As long as you are hungry, you still need to eat.
It’s better to stop talking about me and talk about you.
Where's that pervert of yours?
Do I still like to annoy you that much?
Don't mention that guy again
By the way, princess, don’t you like planting flowers very much?
I wonder if there are orchids growing in the palace?
Yes
That's great. Princess, can you give me a basin?
sure
Tingfang, when did you start learning to grow flowers?
I just plant flowers to pass the time
Princess Qi, Mrs. Ya is asking to see you outside the building
Auntie is here?
aunt princess
Is the eldest lady of the Wu family here too?
I'm leaving
Princess, will you send me a pot of orchids?
You and Xiaoxiang go to the back garden
Take whichever pot you like
Then I'm leaving
Does Auntie have something to do with Qian'er?
Listen to the king, your body is not in harmony
So aunt came to visit you
Auntie no longer has to say good things for my father.
Father always pays little attention to Qianer
The princess is in very good spirits today
Auntie is also very relieved
I want my aunt to worry about Qianer
Qian'er is really sorry
Silly girl
If your aunt doesn't care about you, who else will care about you?
By the way, the king agreed
You can come to my house to stay for a few days
Did your father really agree?
Yes, it depends on when you recover
Don't worry, aunt, Qian'er's illness has long since recovered.
Silly girl
drank this cup
Uncle, it’s really huge, eat a grape
Uncle Wu is so partial, he only cares about drinking with Ziwei
Ignore people at all
How could I ignore you?
Can I feed you grapes?
I want to drink with you
Who is it?
Damn, you're harassing my elegance.
It’s a villain, Uncle Wu
There are two uncles in the wing opposite
I want to invite Ziwei and Jinhua to come over.
How unreasonable, knowing that two girls are accompanying me
Who dares to ask them to have sex?
Yes, even villains know something is wrong
But I don’t know how to explain it to the two uncles
You don’t know how to explain it, do you?
How about I accompany you to explain?
good
Wait for me, I'll be back soon
Come back quickly, don't make me wait too long
Wait for me, lead the way
Stop fighting, uncle
Why do you want to beat me?
Dare you be cruel in front of me?
Are you looking for death?
Brother, help me seek justice.
You two, please give me some face for what happened today.
Just forget it
Damn it, why do you want me to give you face?
Walk
If you don't want to die, continue
Brother, thank you so much for today
Where
Thank you very much, brother, for coming to the rescue.
Tingwei, a toast to my brother
Seriously, please
It's none of your business here, go out
You two gentlemen, please use it slowly.
You guys can go out too
Brother Wu
Why is there such an elegant person coming here to drink?
Don’t you need to help the Lord of Uborg?
Now everything in the fort is big or small
My dad always listens to Xiang’s words
It seems that I won’t even have a foothold later.
That surname
Is this really how to win the favor of Lord Wubao?
I don't understand what dad thinks either?
The person with this name has not been in Wujiapu for less than a month.
Is there any reason to use him so highly?
Could it be that the person named Xiang is the same as the Lord of Wubao?
have a special friendship
Then I really don't know
What special relationship does Dad have with him?
I only know the future of the surname Xiang before Wujiapu
I have never heard my father mention Xiang Shaolong
Is it really that weird?
Really, if you don’t believe it, you can ask Tingfang
By the way, how is Tingfang doing lately?
Okay, I'm going to be pissed off by that guy named Xiang.
Are they often vindictive?
More than just fighting spirit? It’s simply incompatible with fire and water
All in all, this boy with this surname
Never leave our ranch for a day
Just one more day of trouble
In fact, those who want to leave Wujiapu with the surname Xiang
It's not impossible
Brother, you really have a way
Let that boy named Xiang leave the ranch?
Yes, but a few horses from Wujiapu will have to be sacrificed.
Miss
Mr. Tao, where is the prostitute?
Are you talking about Xiang Shaoxia?
Now within Wujiapu
Is there a second adulterer besides him?
Mrs. Ya just sent a carriage to take him across the house.
Miss, do you have something important to do with him?
Did I say I was looking for him?
No, I saw you holding a pot of orchids
I thought the lady was because of what happened last time
So I gave him a pot of orchids to apologize to him.
Damn it, why should I apologize to that adulterer?
This pot of orchids was given to me by the princess
Take it if you like it
You two are so...
You really can't find the young master?
The villain has already been to the places where the young master often goes in and out.
But I still can’t find the young master
Where do you think Pan'er will go?
I thought he might have been out chatting or drinking with friends
I drank too late, maybe I'll be back later
But Shaolong, you have to wait for him here for most of the day
I'm so sorry
Madam, please don't say that
I have this opportunity to be alone with you, madam
I'm really happy to chat at such a close distance
Shaolong, you really know how to joke.
Master...
I said I don't need you to help me anymore
Pan'er
What happened to you? Are you fighting outside again?
Don't worry about my affairs
You can continue to have a romantic relationship with your sweetheart.
Pan'er, stop
So what?
Mom wants to introduce you to your master
Him? When did he become my master?
How could you be so rude to Master?
Damn it, how can he be so good?
Why do you have the ability to be my master?
I have a lot of skills
But if you don’t have any ability,
I don't care if you are Jackie Chan or Bruce Lee
It's useless if I teach you anything
Name, you don’t need to make any mockery here
If that Zhao De hadn't bullied others by relying on the large number of people and the small number of people,
How could I not beat him?
Which Zhao De?
Zhao De is Shao Yuanjun
That is, Mrs. Pingyuan’s son
Please, you are so old
Don't rely on the latrine if you can't poop.
No matter if there are ten people or a hundred people
If you have the ability, you can beat him.
Why are you talking so much?
It's easy to say, it would be you instead
Probably worse than me
Will it? So be it
Do you dare to take a gamble with me?
What to bet on?
Just bet on my bare hands
You can choose a weapon at will
I'll fight with you alone
If you defeat me, I will disappear immediately
If I beat you
You have to kneel on the ground and kowtow three times
Do you dare to call me Master?
It’s a deal
OK
Madam, the fragrant tea is ready
Are you really willing to let me go empty-handed?
Such a big man has to keep his word, come on
Wait a minute
Are you scared?
Will I be afraid of you?
I just want to know
That Bruce Lee you just mentioned
Who is it?
Even if you tell me, you won’t know
In short, he is an international superstar, come on
Okay, you brought it upon yourself
Don't blame me for being heavy handed.
Still coming?
I have no choice but to use the Eighteen Dragon Subduing Palms
Master, please pay homage to me, my disciple.
This is the first time that the maid has seen the young master willing to bow his head to others.
I hope Pan'er won't do anything wrong again in the future.
Uncle, the hosta has been repaired
Awesome, it can really be joined together
Uncle, you have given me a reward
How much?
sixty cents
Sixty dollars? Why not buy another one?
Thin gold flakes are also very valuable
But there is always a thin piece of gold on top
I suffered a loss
Neither will
All right…
sixty cents
Thank you sir...
I will definitely come back to see you next time
Thank you, uncle. Walk slowly, uncle.
Uncle, I have already done what you asked me to do
well done
Thank you sir
Uncle, why are you...
This is the only way to ensure you don't reveal secrets
Brother Xiang
Why is there an extra pot of flowers here?
This pot of orchid is the eldest lady
Zhuan Cheng brought it back from the palace
Yeah?
To be honest, I know the eldest lady’s temperament best.
Although she is a little willful
But she has a good heart
No grudge at all
You and I can be said to be a match made in heaven. Enough...
Since the eldest lady gives you this pot of flowers,
Obviously I just want to apologize to you.
Why are you still angry about this?
How could I be angry with her?
Honestly, don't blame me for being nosy
Could it be that Brother Xiang treats our eldest lady?
No good feelings at all?
Are you saying this is not troublesome?
Do you understand that I don't...
I mean I didn't think I'd be here.
I can't even talk to people here
Any emotional problems occur, do you understand?
but…
Don't be too impatient. It's night and I'm going to bed.
But our eldest lady...
You sleep here, I'll go out
No need... you rest here
Thank you for your help
Although our eldest lady is not the most beautiful woman
But...it's really...
That's good. Think about it.
I originally planned to restore the old one
Okay, now not only is it impossible to rebuild
And caused so much trouble
Don't mess around, Mr. Xiang Shaolong
Lord of the castle
What happened?
My subordinate inspected the horse pen early in the morning.
It was discovered that a batch of our horses were all poisoned and died.
Dad, how's it going?
if i read correctly
These horses are not simply poisoned by feed
What dad means is that so many horses died on the ranch this time.
Did someone poison him intentionally?
Castle Lord, originally this batch of horses
It's a war horse planned to be sent to the military camp in two days.
Being poisoned now
I think there must be something wrong with it
Lord of the castle…
Marquis Julu led a large group of troops to Wujiapu
The Marquis is here, but I don’t know what’s important?
Wu Yingyuan, you are so bold
Why did the Marquis say this?
I want to ask you, inside Wushi Ranch
Have any war horses been poisoned?
If this is indeed the case, how did the Marquis know about it?
I have received a secret letter
A foreign spy sneaked into Wuzhi Ranch with evil intentions
Now it seems that this is indeed true
I'm afraid the Marquis has misunderstood.
Wuzhi Ranch is not a military base.
Why are there foreign spies?
Wushi Ranch is responsible for training war horses for the king.
Used to kill enemies on the battlefield
If there are foreign spies mixed in to maliciously destroy
I am afraid that Lord Wubao will have difficulty explaining to the king.
Which foreign spy?
Japan, Italy or South Korea?
Xiang Shaolong, you don’t have to pretend
You are the spy
Mr. Hou, please check it out.
Xiang Shaolong will definitely not be a spy
Whether this person is a spy or not will be revealed later.
Look at the arrogant way he talks
Must have been prepared
Let's wait and see the good show
Mr. Hou, evidence of the crime has been found
Is a hosta a secret letter of collaboration with the enemy?
Of course that's not the evidence
Xiang Shaolong, no one has stolen the stolen goods yet?
Lord Hou is really awesome
The first time I saw this box, I knew there were hidden compartments inside.
I also know there is a letter in there
Don't be proud of yourself. Just rely on this secret letter of collaborating with the enemy.
Enough to make your head fall to the ground
You haven't read the letter yet
I knew it was a secret letter of collaboration with the enemy. It was really powerful.
Even when death is imminent, he still speaks uncontrollably
Okay, I will let you die convinced.
It's really a secret letter of collaboration with the enemy, but you did it the other way around
Don't leave, my real name is Bruce Lee
In my hometown, someone brought a group of Japanese people to play in the gym
They say that we Chinese are the sick men of East Asia
Then force him to eat the piece of paper
Kick the gym? Believe it or not, I want you to eat this letter
This time so many horses in our ranch died of poisoning
It must be the conspiracy of that bastard Zhao Mu
Want to take advantage of the opportunity to frame the fault
Fortunately, Brother Xiang used an erotic picture in time
Replaced the so-called secret letter of collaboration with the enemy
Otherwise, the consequences will be unimaginable
It's none of my business whether he is the owner of a jade shop
Give us gifts because we buy things
let's have fun
Stop messing around. Who else would I be if I weren't you?
How do I know who it is?
anyway
It seems that there is really a traitor in Wuzhi Ranch
You don't have to hide anymore, come out
How? Are you satisfied with the erotic picture?
Not bad, but a bit too erotic
I also guessed it was you, thank you
Just a little effort
What did you say in the letter you exchanged?
Take it and see
See for yourself
I almost forgot that our uncle Xiang is illiterate.
This letter is written to you personally by Chun Shenjun
The content is that as long as you manage
Poison all the horses in Wushi Ranch
There will be great rewards
There is also Chun Shenjun's personal seal supervisor on it.
What’s the explanation?
You mean to ask why Zhao Mu and Lian Jin want to harm you?
no
I mean, why did he insist on saying that I was a Qin spy?
Or a spy from Wei State
Instead of saying that I am a spy of Chu State?
Unless there is only one possibility
It’s Zhao Mu and the others who have always been in contact with Chu State.
Zhao Pan
Zhao De, I didn’t expect that we would meet again so soon.
You think I didn’t hit you enough last time?
Come out today and let me teach you a lesson again?
Things are different now
I'm afraid I'll be beaten like a pig's head today
Not me, but you
Okay, let me see how different you are today
I'm afraid you will regret it after seeing it
There is no reason to speak arrogantly
If I don’t teach you a lesson today, my surname will not be Zhao.
Mozi's swordsmanship?
What do you want?
How is it? Are you afraid that I will kill you?
Don't worry, I'm in a good mood today
Decided to let you go
Wait a minute
Have I ever promised to let you go?
What do you want?
Damn it, didn’t I have a name for you to call me?
Yes, I don’t know Gongzipan
How can I be willing to let my husband go...
Let me go?
It's easy. You want to go, right?
Then could you please get out of here?
you…
How is it? Are you ashamed? Or are you afraid of being made fun of?
Zhao Pan, don’t be so cruel
I just like to do things very well
I will ask you again
Are you going to drill or not?
Able to bend and stretch, he truly deserves to be Mr. Shao Yuan
I have to feel sorry for the princess and stay in the east wing temporarily.
Auntie, this place is very elegantly decorated.
It’s good if the princess doesn’t dislike it
If the princess needs anything
Just give your servants whatever orders you want.
Why didn’t I see Cousin Pan along the way?
Pan'er was practicing sword practice with his master in the backyard of the west wing.
When did Cousin Pan get a master?
Pan'er has only been apprenticed for a few days.
He even made Cousin Pan willing to worship him as his teacher
This master must have very good skills
Indeed, his master is not only highly skilled in martial arts
He's also a good person and very interesting.
Can Cousin Pan be so impressed?
My aunt was full of praise again
It seems that this master is indeed not simple.
Master, you didn’t see that bastard Zhao De
When he got under his disciple's crotch
I don’t know how ugly my face is
I just learned two moves and three-legged cat kung fu and I'm looking for someone to take revenge.
Of course, if not
Why should a disciple learn martial arts from his master?
Look how arrogant and arrogant you look
have you ever thought about
What should you do if you can't beat someone?
If my disciple wants to learn martial arts
We must learn from the best in the world
Then naturally I will be the only one to hit others, and no one will hit me.
Then let’s skip the level and teach you the Eighteen Palms of Subduing the Dragon.
really?
Do you know what it means: a mountain is as high as a mountain
Does the strong have its own strong hand?
You can't be invincible forever if you learn kung fu
I don't know about others
It’s natural for a disciple to have a master to teach him...
Save it, you sycophant.
Starting today, you must first learn the basic skills
You take an hour every day
Learn physical training well
No, what is it...an hour?
Physical training?
yes
Master, how long will Pan'er continue to practice?
Palm presses are just one type of physical training
You didn't even do palm pressure well
How can I, your master, teach you other skills?
Just put more effort into practicing.
Master, you also have many great principles
It's because no one usually talks to you.
That's why you ended up like this today
So your master and I will start from today
In addition to teaching you kung fu
I will also teach you some principles of life, you know?
What are you doing? Why are you staring at me blankly?
master
What do you want?
Pan'er grew up
No one has ever said this to me
Only Master is willing to care about me
Silly boy, how come no one cares about you?
In fact, apart from your master and me,
Your mother also cares about you very much
My mother?
Believe me, your mother really cares about you
It's just that you didn't give her a chance.
No matter what, Master, from today on
Pan'er will definitely learn martial arts from her master.
Then be good, okay, let’s continue doing palm pressure.
Princess, I can’t imagine Mrs. Ya’s mansion
There will be so many exotic flowers and plants
There are many things about my aunt that you can’t imagine
This flower pot is planted crookedly
give me a shovel
Princess, the slave forgot to bring the shovel.
You go back and get it, I'll wait for you here
yes princess
What's wrong with you? Are you bored after being locked up for so long?
Do you want to go out to play?
Is there a toilet nearby? Is it so big?
Is it you?
How could it be such a coincidence?
Do you still recognize me?
How could I not recognize it? I'm sorry
Why are you, a palace maid, here?
Me? Palace maid?
The maid should stay in the palace and serve...
Empress Dowager Cixi may be the unruly princess
I have also acted on TV
television?
Even if I tell you, you won’t understand.
But it's really a coincidence
The two times I saw you, you almost fell into the water.
Yes, I haven't thanked you yet
Why are you here?
Tell the truth
I am Xiang Shaolong, Zhao Pan’s master
It turned out to be you
Majestic, right?
What you say is interesting
If I guess correctly, you must not be from Handan
That's awesome. What's your name?
I?
What am I? Is your name ugly?
Could it be called Cat and Dog?
Otherwise, it’s Ah Zhu or Amao.
You are the cat and the dog
My flower seedlings
I'm sorry...I didn't mean to
They have been planting all morning, and you see they were trampled like this
I'm back, is it you? Sir...
Madam, there are still many things for us to do
Let's go, let's go he...
Let's go
Am I not looking for the toilet?
Let's go back and ask our disciples.
master
Do you really not need to ask your servant to prepare a car for you?
No, I want to go for a walk by myself
That's it, go back, goodbye
Okay then, master, walk slowly
Master?
Isn't it? You sent someone to follow me again?
I'm going to give you a good beating this time
Do you want to fight in these clothes?
Just wait a minute