You are worse than a scumbag
Stealing people's property, raping women and children
They will be struck by thunder from heaven, and they will have no children or grandchildren.
Because Brother Beard helped me catch that horse before
I saw you fighting with him, so I gave him a helping hand
Anyway, I did bad things with good intentions before.
Now make up for it
it hurts
This person is Zhao Mu’s number one swordsman Lian Jin
Little slippery, stealing dragons and turning them into phoenixes
Do you think you will have laxatives?
The medicine is indeed effective
Lian Jin is indeed Lian Jin
I also take the jade pen with me when I go to the toilet.
I'm afraid we won't be able to start this time
wait a minute
Brother Xiang, why don't we just stun him?
Then steal the jade
Lian Jin is so clever
If he wakes up and finds that the jade is missing
It's troublesome, of course it's not good
Take...
Brother Xiang, what’s the countermeasure?
Anyway, you believe me, I have a way
Anyway, just wait and see the good show
Go up…
Young Master, Young Lady
Kill this thief for me
Everyone will stop
Miss, it was a misunderstanding, please discuss it slowly
Manager Tao Fang'er
Let Brother Wei help you teach this pervert a lesson
good
Young Master, no
Big brother
Watch out on the left
left, right
above, below
Get out of here
you lied to me
Master, are you okay?
Sorry...didn't mean to...
Come again
you have blackheads
You deserve a spanking if you bite your finger
If you come again, if you come again, I will use the Eighteen Dragon Subduing Palms
Dad... Master
Sir, I have something to report to you.
He is the thief who bullied his daughter
Dad, Tao Fang is so bold
He actually stole He's Bi with this lewd thief
Sir, that's not the case
No need to argue, just take it back and talk about it later
Lord Ubold, that's what the whole thing is like
nonsense
Lian Jin is a humble and benevolent gentleman
The indomitable swordsman
I will never collude with horse thieves
Not to mention exchanging the fake for the real and embezzling He's Bi
You defend him so much, are you dating him?
Don’t understand what dating is?
It's two people who love each other
Ridiculous, many quibbles
It was obviously a horse thief who robbed the Wu family's property.
Trying to humiliate this lady
If things fail, I will pretend to save Mr. Tao
Now he is slandering Lian Jin everywhere, with ulterior motives
Forget it if you don’t believe it
I have Mr. Tao to vouch for me
Master, although my subordinates have not personally witnessed Lian Jin
Kill people in the village and seize He's Bi
This is basically what this pervert is talking about.
One-sided words are really unconvincing
Fang'er
Let Manager Tao continue.
The subordinates indeed witnessed Lian Jin in Changting Town
Call a jade craftsman
A piece of fake He's Bi
Lian Jin indeed carries the Heshi Bi
As for his intentions? His subordinates could not figure it out.
Why not take the opportunity to recapture He's Bi in Changting Town?
Because I want to play the long game and catch big fish
Figure this out slowly
What is the meaning of this statement?
Because I heard Manager Tao say
The route of escorting He Shibi this time is very confidential.
Only four people know
The Lord of Uborg, Manager Tao, and the Eldest Lady
And Zhao Mu
Apparently there is a traitor in Wujiapu
Ridiculous, Fang'er didn't tell anyone
That's it
It was basically Zhao Mu who asked the horse thieves to rob
Then send Lian Jin to kill the horse thieves
Take back He's Bi
It makes sense, Lian Jin settled in Zhao Mu's hotel
Apparently he was ordered by Zhao Mu
Of course, Lian Jin was basically helping Zhao Mu
Although Lian Jin took He's Bi to explain to Zhao Mu,
Unexpectedly, Lian Jin suddenly had a wrong idea
Find a craftsman to make a fake Heshi Bi
Then he embezzled He's Bi
As you say
You know the whole thing well and have the upper hand
Why didn't you expose them immediately?
denounce it directly
Because I want to take advantage of the situation
Use Lian Jin to safely transport He's Bi back to Handan
But He's Bi has fallen into the hands of others
Even if it arrives safely in Handan, it will not help.
The Wu family also committed a dereliction of duty, which is a capital crime.
Lord Wu Bao, don’t worry
I've already thought of a way for you
What can you do?
But I can’t say it yet, Lord
Rhetoric, there is no solution at all
I could have said
But because of your close relationship with Lian Jin
I'm sure it's not simple between you two
if i say it now
It would be bad if you go tell Lian Jin
Castle Lord, let’s find a private time to talk slowly later.
You don't need to make excuses here, I'll call Lian Jin right away
Face to face and make it clear
No, if you say it, you will be betrayed.
What is cheating? Nonsense
Are you afraid that your lies will be exposed?
Castle Lord, I dare to guarantee it with my head
If the jade cannot be returned to Zhao intact tomorrow,
My head fell to the ground
Sir, I guarantee this with my life.
you…
Dad, brother, please say something
Dad, I think this Xiang Shaolong
Mysterious identity, strange words and deeds
There must be many secrets inside
Why don't we torture him to extract a confession?
No need to be polite
Yes, torture
I'm at the mercy of the slaughter now
Just one day
If there is no miscalculation, I will have a solution tomorrow
Ask Zhao Mu and Lian Jin to hand over He's Bi
Dad, you must not be deceived by him
Now I have lost Heshibi
More than 40 people from Wujiabao will be implicated
You also know about forty lives
Now only the troops are in danger
Lord Wubao, do you believe me?
Okay, Wu Mou will give you one day.
Dad, you are relying solely on his one-sided words
Just hand over forty lives to him
No, I have to go find Lian Jin
Fang'er, stop, you are not allowed to leave the ranch for the time being.
And you can’t contact Lian Jin, you know?
Dad, you don’t even believe your daughter, you believe this pervert
Fang'er, you can't mess around anymore.
You disguise yourself and go out with Mr. Tao
Dad hasn’t punished you yet
Will is
You can't leave the ranch either, you know?
Me? Yes, Dad
Xiang Shaoxia, please go to the study with me
good
Whether he is a villain or a gentleman, you will know tomorrow
Brother Xiang, please
good…
What I want to raise is not a bunch of dogs that I am flattering.
Be a disciple of this prince
We must try our best to show our true skills
Cuju is not a game
Think of it as a battle formation on the battlefield
So we must win and come again
Mr. Hou, Zhongli’s leg bone seems to be broken.
It's really vulnerable, since it has no use anymore
Drag him out and chop off his feet
Lord Marquis, I still have a noble family to support.
Okay, just in case you are unfilial
Even your high hall has been buried, go away
Mr. Hou…
What a disappointment today, that's it for now
Mr. Hou, is everything done?
Everything has been done
crystal clear
It’s really the best of jade, a unique treasure
Obtaining this rare treasure is a great joy in life
But the most important thing
It can prevent Qin and Zhao from making peace
Zhao Guo couldn't get He's Bi
We will definitely not let Ying Zheng go
Qin returned He's Bi, but could not get Yingzheng
They will definitely send troops to attack Zhao Guo
When the time comes, Qin and Zhao will fight
What is most beneficial to our Chu country
Lord Marquis, you have made great contributions to Lord Chun Shen again.
You won’t lose a share of the credit this time
I will give you a good word for you.
Mr. Xie
Lord Marquis, please forgive me for speaking frankly.
Your Majesty sent Lord Marquis to the State of Zhao to lurk for many years.
Now King Zhao also obeys the advice of Lord Hou
Why don't the Marquis rebel as soon as possible and achieve great success?
Bold, I have always been loyal to you.
How dare you say something treasonous?
I only hope that Mr. Hou will achieve great success as soon as possible.
When the time comes, your Majesty will have your own instructions
You don't have to worry, just do your part
Yes, Mr. Hou
This treasure hunt is of great importance
Are you sure you didn't leave any survivors?
All the horse thieves in the village have long been gone.
but…
Tao Fang, the general manager of the Wu family
Before the subordinates arrive at the village
Already escaped, not knowing where to end up
Did anyone escape alive?
Mr. Hou can rest assured
Tao Fang only knew that it was a horse thief.
Absolutely no idea that the oriole is behind
Things will always go wrong
Lord Marquis, come to the palace tomorrow morning
If the Lord of Wubao fails to hand over He's Bi, it is already a capital offense.
Tao Fang, the general manager of the Wu family, failed to escort
Even if you return to Wujiapu
It will also end badly
This time Wushi lost the priceless Heshi Bi
I am afraid that only by killing the nine tribes can King Zhao be appeased.
About Wei and South Korea
Asking for an alliance with one's own country
Your Majesty, don't worry, I'll take care of it on my own
Your Majesty, this matter should not be delayed and a decision should be made early.
Qin is a country of wolves and tigers, and a foreigner has just ascended the throne...
Doctor Feng
Your Majesty has handed over this matter to me.
You don't have to be nagging anymore
Lord Uburg arrives
Juluhou, what you say makes sense.
Has the Lord of Uborg arrived? Quick message
Yes, Your Majesty
Juluhou
This time the Qin State returned He's Bi to its own country.
What a surprise
Things are unpredictable, Your Majesty, don’t expect too much
Are you afraid that Qin will go back on its word?
Under Wu Yingyuan
Take Tao Fang, a general from the same family, to see the king
Lord Wubao, you don’t have to be polite
Where is He's Bi now?
I did not bring anyone with me to the palace
When you meet the king, you must bring He's Bi
The Lord of Uborg came empty-handed
Do you want to deceive the king?
Your Majesty, please listen to Tao Fang’s explanation.
Say it quickly
The villain was ordered to escort He's Bi from Qin back to Zhao
But when they were about to reach Handan, they encountered horse thieves.
He Shibi was robbed by horse thieves
Heshibi was robbed by horse thieves?
It’s really a shameful thing to entrust to someone. He’s Bi is priceless.
You failed to escort me well and were taken away by mistake
Should be sentenced to death
How unreasonable
Your Majesty, there is more to this matter
Your Majesty, please introduce me to someone.
Who?
He is a young knight named Xiang Shaolong
With this person's help, He's Bi was saved.
Quick pass to Xiang Shaolong
Lord Wubao, are you trying to be mysterious?
Since He's Bi was lucky enough to be preserved,
Why not submit it immediately?
See the king
Tell me quickly, where is He's Bi now?
at his home
Nonsense
It is indeed in the Marquis's mansion
What is the meaning of this statement?
In fact, He's Bi was successfully recovered this time.
It's entirely his fault
He first sent Lian Jin to Mazhai to kill all the bandits.
Then put the He's Bi in your own home
He knows things like a god
I couldn't help him even though I wanted to.
He could just go and set up a stall to read photos.
Julu Hou, are you serious about this?
Why don't you make it clear early on
I think he wants to give you a surprise
Scare you
Bold Juluhou
He actually made a fool of himself and made fun of others
He's simply audacious
Please forgive me, Your Majesty
What are you guilty of?
Julu Hou, you have made great achievements
Prepare your horse immediately
I will go to your house immediately to welcome He Shibi
I dare not bother the king, so I will go back to the mansion immediately to get it.
No need, I can't wait anymore
Quickly spread the news that the descendants of the He family are traveling together
The two Qing family members also traveled with the widow's chariot and horse.
Thank you, Your Majesty...
Brother Xiang, you are so witty
It is indeed much more transparent than the fake one in the palace.
He is the king
You are the only one who has seen this jade
Please identify it for me. I obey.
Kiya...
Congratulations, one look at you
Both handsome and wise
You must be his assistant
You have indeed made a great contribution by finding the Heshi Bi.
Remember to treat me to a meal, you know?
your hands are so wet
Are you nervous? Relax
He family, which one is true and which one is false?
Originally on the edge of jade
There is a tiny fetal stain
has disappeared now
Fake?
No, this is the authentic Heshi jade
I heard that King Qin Zhao was alive
Likes to hug He Shibi while sleeping
Biyu absorbed the popularity of King Zhao
So even a little bit of fetal stain has disappeared.
Congratulations, king
He's Bi finally fell into the hands of a few people
The Lord of Wubao, the Marquis of Julu has made great contributions to the people.
Tomorrow we will hold a banquet in the palace
Thank you to the two noble families
Thank you, Your Majesty...
You are familiar with Miss Wu family
Did he collude with Wu Yingyuan to frame me?
The subordinates will only be loyal to the Marquis
No different intentions
But how do you explain this?
I just blame my subordinate for being careless
Didn't realize that Wushi sent people to follow his subordinates
You've always been smart
Why don't you notice that you are being followed?
Do you have any other feelings?
If my subordinates intend to murder the Marquis,
You should offer jade to the king in private
If one of my subordinates has an affair with Wushi
There is no need to hand over He's Bi
Subordinates kneel down to plead guilty to show their loyalty and courage.
You'd better remember your identity and status
Never try to eradicate me
can be replaced
The subordinates will only serve the Lord and the Marquis with all their heart.
I hope your words and deeds will be consistent, get up
Mr. Xie
Now that Wu Yingyuan has learned that this Marquis has privately collected He's Bi,
Not only did he report the slander, but he also gave the credit to me.
Really ulterior motives
And Xiang Shaolong is not a simple person either.
Wu Yingyuan relied on herding war horses for Zhao Guo.
Don't take this prince seriously
He also targets me at every turn
I must punish him
Sooner or later, Wujiapu must be eliminated
You are familiar with Miss Wu family
Just make good use of this chess piece
Yes, Mr. Hou
Xiang Shaoxia, thanks to your ingenious plan this time
Otherwise, Wu Mou would have been dead.
Lord Wubao, you are too polite.
In fact, everyone worked well together this time
Only then will there be such a good effect
Brother Xiang is not only witty
Be a humble and trustworthy person
He is truly a rare gentleman
Is he a gentleman? I said he is simply a thief
Fang'er, don't be rude.
Xiang Shaoxia, please sit down. Okay
That's right, compared to your crush Lian Jin
I am indeed not as gentlemanly as he is.
The peep show was torn down and he still kept his appearance.
Brother Xiang, what is a diorama?
The peep show was a treacherous trick that was discovered
I see
He must be furious this time
Steal the chicken but lose the rice
I feel so happy when I think of the expressions on Lian Jin’s master and servant’s faces
I sat
Brother Xiang, this seat is mine
Your seat is over there
Xiang Shaoxia, please take a seat. Okay.
Xiang Shaoxia’s wise words just now
It's really apt description
In addition to being furious this time, he
We should also smash the fake He's Bi.
Dad, Lian Jin will never exchange fake for real.
Embezzling He's Bi
Don't listen to this pervert's nonsense
But the fact is before us
Dad, the origin of this thief is unknown at all.
He might be a spy. Don't let him deceive you.
Dad, there is something unclear about my child
Now that we know that Zhao Mu secretly exchanged He's Bi,
We can tell the truth
It is a capital crime to deceive the king
Can't we use this to eradicate Zhao Mu?
Dad has also considered this matter
But our greatest purpose
It is to rescue the proton and return to Qin safely.
Moreover, Zhao Mu’s power overturned the state of Zhao
Even the king wants to avoid him
If he is forced too hard on this matter,
Might be bad for protons
So Xiang Shaoxia’s plan can be said to be the best of both worlds
Lord Wubao is so complimentary.
Dad, my daughter is unwell. Please forgive me for being with her.
I have been waiting for you at the East City Gate for two hours.
I just saw the banner too
What's the urgent matter for brother Lian to ask Fang'er?
I heard you were robbed by horse thieves
So I'm a little worried
Fang'er wants to know
Did Brother Lian go to the village to kill horse thieves?
Seize the He clan's jade
have
I was ordered by the Marquis, so I couldn't help myself
Mr. Hou knows things like a god
He's afraid that your Wu family doesn't have enough troops and will make mistakes.
So I was sent to pick him up
As a result, I encountered a horse thief in Changting Valley.
Even if I want to get back He's Bi
There is no need to kill all the horse thieves
Unless you have selfish motives and want to keep silent
Because I know they disrespect you
Even rude, so I killed them all
Why exchange falsehood for truth on the way?
Substituting the fake for the real is just a safety measure
In case someone robs you on the way
What is lost is just fake
Why did Zhao Mu get He's Bi?
Not presented to the king
Do you want to trap the Wu family into injustice?
I was just following the order of the Marquis to take back He's Bi
As for what the Marquis’ intention is?
I don't know
But if the Marquis does not present He's Bi
And framed by the Wu family
I will definitely stand up and tell the truth
really?
Absolutely no lies
Fang'er has long believed that Brother Lian
I will never embezzle He's Bi.
That pervert wants to slander Brother Lian
Which thief?
Xiang Shaolong
It was he who teamed up with the group of thieves to seize Heshi Bi.
Being rude to Fang'er in the cottage
He has been following Brother Lian and slandering him to his father.
He also secretly gave laxatives to Brother Lian
I see, no wonder I had a stomachache that night
This Xiang Shaolong is really cunning
Fang'er wants to peel off his skin and pick out his bones
Miss Wu, there is no need to be angry
If I have the chance, I will definitely help you out.
good
Brother Lian no longer needs to keep calling Miss Wu
Just call me Fang'er
OK, Finger
Brother Xiang, how is it?
The clothes are already made and there are buckles
this
Thank you, guest
I don’t know if the guest officer needs to be behind the scenes.
Make a famous name
Okay, please spell it out
Just a moment
The two guests can go to the teahouse in front to have a bowl of tea first.
How much?
Very cheap, twenty dollars
You come and pick up the goods and then pay.
Quite honest, okay, see you later, let's go
Brother Xiang, what do you mean by what you just said?
There will be a period soon
The two guest officers take a look casually
The engraving on this buckle is very special and exquisite.
Brother Lian, look
Very suitable for you, buy it
Okay, boss, I want to buy this buckle
Sir, I'm sorry
This buckle has been bought by someone
Someone bought it
I pay double the price
Be true to your word
ten times
Sir, you'd better choose another one.
Is there anything exactly the same as this one?
Our store's buckles are unique
Really disappointing
Twenty times the price
Sir, money is not everything
But if you don’t have money, you can’t do it.
Miss
Since this uncle likes this buckle so much
Just sell it to him for twenty times the price.
Besides, this old man smiled for Bo's beauty
How could I let him down with this beauty?
Thank you, four hundred dollars, uncle
Thank you, guest officer…
It's better to meet by chance than to invite, and it's better to have a meal together.
Thanks
Is this your first time to Handan City, Brother Xiang?
so to speak
I'll be the host for this meal, so you're welcome
No need, I have to spend money on my brother
Everyone just pays what he deserves.
To each his own?
Everyone pays his own way is my country dialect
It means you pay your own money
I see
Brother Xiang’s accent is so unique
Where is the unknown hometown?
Hongkong
Hongkong?
Stop talking about this. Is there anything delicious here?
It's already written on it
Stop playing tricks on me
You know I can't understand your words
If you don't mind, why don't I take the order?
What are your orders? Two pounds of wine.
Brother Xiang is brave and resourceful. In these troubled times,
If you can find a wise king to show your talents,
Will definitely become famous all over the world
I still prefer to be free
How can you be as broad-minded as my brother-in-law?
Find an owner to follow up with
Brother Xiang defected to Wujiapu
Isn’t it a follow-up?
No, I can leave at any time
Brother Xiang's way of eating is really unique
I heard that uncivilized southern barbarians eat like this.
We in southern China use chopsticks
This method of eating with a knife and fork
Only used in Western countries
Ridiculous, I once went to Xianyang, the state of Qin in the west
Never seen the weird utensils in your hands
Little girl knows little
The West I am talking about is a West further west than Qin
nonsense
Even eldest brother and Manager Tao have traveled around the world
They are all well-informed people
Have you ever seen it?
I really haven't seen it
Sorry for my ignorance
I've never seen such a strange fork
No, sir
You spilled rice wine on me
I didn’t even blame you
I just want to kiss Fangze, no
Toast, don’t drink, drink as punishment
This is really unreasonable
Brother Lian, go over and teach him a lesson
I don't know what happened before
Don't mind your own business
It's obvious that he is a big pervert who is teasing women from good families.
Don't mess with him, he's a young master
His mother is Mrs. Huang Meiya
And Zhao Mu is backing him, so he can’t be offended
Spare your life, young master... drink...
Are you okay? It's okay
bull riding…
You just spilled your wine on the girl
I don’t blame you, I just want to ride the bull
Scream, sir, no
Master, please spare my life. Master, please let me go.
Please let me go quickly, call it like this
What does this young master’s business have to do with you?
It’s not called, is it? This cheng is good
Scream or not... spare your life
Louder, please forgive me
By the way...a bit sadder
Spare your life, sir
Okay, you look so good
Apologize to the girl now
This strong man, let it be done...
No apology...I'm sorry...
Be louder, be happy
Sorry, louder
Sorry, be louder
sorry
Brother Xiang, forget it
I see that you are very well behaved today.
I've had enough riding
Don't do this next time, you big pervert
Don’t let me see you again in the future
I should have said what he said
I'm afraid there will be more trouble in the future
Have you ever heard that the emperor committed the same crime as the common people?
Can he act unscrupulously just because he is the emperor's sister's son?
That's right
Did I hear correctly?
For the first time, the eldest lady agreed with my words
This young master Pan’s evil words and deeds
The whole of Handan knows
This time he learned a lesson, which was really satisfying
Brother Xiang is brave enough to do what is right, I really admire him
Maybe you are new to Handan
I don’t know the sentiments of the people here
There are some people here who should be avoided
If you push ahead, you will only be self-defeating
I beg you...this is your salary this month
You go back to the countryside and farm the fields.
Boss, you pity me
The fields in the countryside are not cultivated enough to make a living.
You have offended Mr. Pan
If you don't leave, we won't be able to do business here anymore.
You should pity me and please leave quickly...
That girl just needs to be bullied by Young Master Pan
Or just apologize and beg for mercy, and everything will be fine.
Now she has lost her job
Might starve to death on the streets
Or be forced to sell to a place of drinking and prostitution
Her fate is even more tragic
Please untie the sword and wait here for a moment.
He also said that there was music to listen to, dancing to, and food to eat.
There's nothing, and we're trapped here
This is the place where you wait to be summoned
I'm going to the toilet
Be careful to get lost
Thanks
Where is the toilet?
Go straight, turn left, then turn right
Across the corridor, next to the kitchen is the toilet.
Thanks
Dad, I want to find...
Do you want to find your soulmate?
soon
come back soon
Go straight, turn left, then turn right
Across the corridor, next to the kitchen is the toilet
Don't lie to me, eunuch
Xiaobai, don't run
Xiaobai, come here
Madam, where is the bathroom?
Xiaobai...don't run
Xiaobai, come here, danger
noob…
Working
Found it, great
Otherwise, I will be blamed by the queen again
He is...
let's go
Don't I need to go to the toilet?
Princess
Tingfang, you finally came back from Qin
I waited so hard for you
What did you experience in Xianyang?
Did you encounter any thrills along the way?
Have you ever encountered bandits?
What gifts did you receive from Qin?
Is there Qian'er's share?
It's a long story, please let me have it easy
I envy you so much
I envy you that you can travel around and experience things
There are also many people who envy you for your golden branches and jade leaves.
The glorious princess
The princess is like a caged bird, unable to leave the palace
What is there to envy?
Everyone has their own merits
The king has the airs of a king
A high official has the authority of a high official
The princess has the nobility of a princess
Look at you, you're always wearing palace maid's clothes
I must be feeding the rabbits again
I didn’t know the truth, so I thought you were a palace maid.
Look at how I'm dressed today, I look more like a princess than you do
Even if you dress up beautifully, no one will appreciate it.
Stop talking about this, what does Qin know?
Tell me, you will be very happy
There are not many happy things
But there are more things to be angry about
I met a thief
A thief?
This pervert is despicable and shameless
This time I got He's Bi back.
Thanks to the dedicated efforts of Lord Wubao and Marquis Julu
Their disciples Xiang Shaolong and Lian Jin
He is a rare talent, which is really gratifying.
Congratulations to the king for getting back the treasure
This time I finally lived up to my expectations.
Your Majesty, Prime Minister Lu hopes that the two countries will be reconciled.
Since the State of Qin kept its word, it sent back He's Bi
I also hope that the king will keep his promise
Sending Ying Zheng’s mother and son back to Qin
What Lord Wu Bao said is true
Your Majesty, what Lord Wu Bao said is wrong.
He's Biben is a treasure of the State of Zhao
At that time, King Zhao of Qin threatened and deceived
Promise to exchange fifteen cities for this treasure
At that time, Shangqing Lin Xiangru
Although he is both wise and brave, he does not disgrace the national constitution.
But he was still regarded as an old fox by King Zhao of Qin
Secretly pretending to be real and deceiving the country
The State of Qin is so unkind and unjust, and has broken its promise before
Now the king does not need to keep his word to Qin
Besides, there was no covenant in this matter
Even if we don't send the proton back
Qin can’t do anything to us
how can you say that
That means you can go out and fool around behind Mrs. Ling's back
Madam Ling no longer has to keep her chastity
You can go out and have an affair
How dare you insult me?
sorry
Your Majesty, the people of Qin have strong horses and strong soldiers, and they have many generals.
If the king breaks his promise and angers Qin,
Therefore, sending troops to attack Zhao is not a blessing to Zhao.
Your Majesty, Lian Jin has a foolish opinion. Tell me quickly.
Qin is a country of wolves and tigers
And they continue to use troops to attack foreign countries and conquer cities and territories.
Ruoran, the king will return the hostage
Qin will definitely use troops against Zhao
And no worries
Now the King of Qin and Lu Buwei attach so much importance to proton politics
Don't hesitate to exchange He's Bi
If Zhao Guo has a proton in hand,
Qin must be wary of using troops against Zhao
Never dare to act rashly
Lian Jin said it well
No, Your Majesty, if you really don’t let me go
When Qin really attacks, wouldn't it be very miserable?
Your Majesty, what Xiang Shaoxia said makes sense.
Lord Wubao is always worried about Qin
Could it be that Lord Wubao has colluded with Qin?
Why did the Marquis say this?
Your Majesty, I am loyal to you.
Please, Your Majesty, take a closer look
There is no need for you two good ministers to argue anymore.
Now He's Bi is in hand
As for the protons, we will decide later.
Come and have some singing and dancing
Wait a minute
Your Majesty, I have a suggestion
please say
Lian Jin, a disciple of Weichen
and Xiang Shaolong, the main gatekeeper of Wubao
A swordsman with superb swordsmanship
Why not invite the pair to perform impromptu to spice things up
Good suggestion. Come on, get your sword.
Your Majesty, Lian Jin has a request
It's too monotonous to play swordsmanship alone
I want to invite Xiang Shaolong to compete with me
Okay, guard, get another sword.
King, you are so handsome
It's better to invite the girl to dance.
What’s so cool about dancing with knives and guns?
Be bold, you dare to go against the king's will
This is really unreasonable
Do you want to behead? Kneel down
Your Majesty, Xiang Shaolong is a grassroots man in the mountains.
I don’t understand etiquette, please forgive me.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty
The king's golden mouth has been opened. He will resist the decree without using a sword.
If you resist the decree, your head will fall to the ground. Come here.
Your Majesty, please forgive me.
Your Majesty, I mean
Dancing with knives and guns is too dangerous
It would be bad if it bleeds
It’s both disappointing and unlucky, and it also hurts the harmony.
What I'm most worried about is
With such a handsome appearance, the king
It would be bad if such a ridiculous thing got spread.
It sounds unreasonable, but it seems to make sense
It is indeed unlucky to splatter the palace with blood, so retreat
Your Majesty, I think dancing with swords and guns is too childish.
Let's play a more exciting game, shall we?
But I wonder if Brother Lian has the guts to play?
What is it?
This game is very simple
Let’s get a fruit first
Then put the fruit on the other person's head
Draw your sword and chop it down
If you don’t lose your hair or bleed, you win.
On the contrary, you lose
quite interesting
Interesting, right? Why don't I go first?
Brother, please lend me a sword
Why don't I go first?
King, I have already put it away
Brother Xiang
Don't worry, Brother Lian is so smart
He won't make me bleed
And made his own head fall to the ground
Brother, it’s time to start
Do you want to chop or not?