Yan Ping, since you are here
Why don't you come out to see me?
Senior Brother Yuan
I didn't expect that we would meet again so soon
Little brother, you and I are just afraid that this will end
It has nothing to do with you here, you go first
Senior, I won’t leave
Since the old timer told you to leave, let's go
If you are afraid, you go first
You don't have to push and pull.
No one can leave here today, kill
Little brother, go quickly
This huge order is related to the fate of the Mohists' Guild
You need to help me find a suitable successor
Everyone is dead and should go
Wasn't it you who brought Yan Ping here?
Ask the seniors to teach me martial arts
You just want to delay time
Wait until Yan Ping comes
Just use the old-timer to kill him, right?
Yes, everything is my arrangement
To survive in the arena, the law of the jungle means the strong eat the strong.
Either you die or I die
If you want to avenge Master, kill me
Xiang Shaolong, listen
Without me to lead the way
You can't go to Xianyang
Senior, although you may not regard me as your disciple
But you taught me swordsmanship
In my heart, you will always be my master
Please accept my worship
If I hadn't returned to ancient times
It probably won't kill you.
Don't be so mean
Do we have to go to Xianyang before we move?
Don't turn off your phone, wait a minute, I'm coming
Ah Qing, give me some iced lemon tea
Wait a minute...
take me back...
Xiang Shaolong, we finally succeeded in sending you back.
Our time travel experiment
This time it finally works
Xiang Shaolong, have you really returned to ancient times?
Have you ever met Qin Shihuang?
Is he as smart as me?
Xiang Shaolong
I know you must really want to meet someone
Aqing Shaolong
Shaolong, I am not married to Peter Wong
I've been waiting for you to come back
I miss you so much, you know?
You're not really married to Peter Wong
No, I'm waiting for you to come back
I miss you too
I really want to drink the ice lemon tea you made
I’ll make it for you every day from now on
OK, let's get married
Open the door, why not open the door?
Ah Qing
open the door...
Ah Qing…
The sun shines and it rains
Play with me, I can definitely go to Xianyang
I will definitely see Ah Qing
Is there any soap? It’s so comfortable to take a bath
What would you like, sir?
What can I eat with this money?
You can eat three steamed buns and still have one money left.
It's over, penniless, and I'll starve to death sooner or later.
three steamed buns
Boss, how long does it take to get to Handan from here?
It’s not that far away from Handan.
If you ride on horseback, it will take about two or three days.
Boss, if I help you work here
How long does it take to buy a horse?
Can you make steamed buns?
Slaughter sheep and pigs
I'm sorry I can't help you. Thank you.
You should be able to sell your labor, right?
How come?
Isn't it true?
is true
don't want
good…
Coming
Stop touching me, I'm going to beat you up if you touch me again
You three guys only have three dollars
I was asked to take off my clothes in public, and then you were asked to touch me
I'm sending you off before I leave. Go and die.
Uncle, you are here, please sit down...
Three steamed buns, arriving soon
Sir, please use it slowly
I didn't call these, I called them three steamed buns
Enjoy it, uncle
Boss, I don’t have any money to give you.
An uncle has already paid
Ask me to entertain you well
who?
Sir, please use it slowly...
Who?
Dozens of layers of clothes and uncut hair
It's so frustrating
I beg you not to make a noise
Your voice is so annoying, it keeps making noise
If you were two thousand years from now
It would be great if Happy Valley was born
At least twice a week
There are tens of thousands of people shouting for you
Now you call me, I'll rub myself here
Don't even know why?
There's no soap, it's over, I've been rubbing it like this for three years
What? Have you finished eating? You want me to wipe your mouth?
Be quiet...
Don't wake up Uncle Xiang, you know...
Uncle Xiang, please bear with me.
This little worker didn't understand the rules and woke up Uncle Xiang
It doesn't matter, my feet are numb, don't say anything more
Uncle Xiang, did you sleep well last night?
Okay, look at me like this
I knew it was great
Is this horse for sale?
You said this horse
This horse already belongs to Uncle Xiang
The old man yesterday
Everything has been prepared for Uncle Xiang
Prepare the saddle for Uncle Xiang immediately
Mr. Ma, you and I are really destined and we get along well.
You heard me say so much last night
Let's go on the road together so that you don't tell anyone.
Come on, Brother Ma, it’s third gear, it’s fourth gear
Stifled to death
Show up, sneaky
Brother Xiang once said, I don’t want to see you
What I hate most is seeing people who are blind to money.
Your Excellency is not much better.
If you have backbone
You shouldn't accept favors from your enemies
What you say is so annoying
Don't think you have arranged everything for me
You can atone for your sins
Pay your bills, rent a house, and buy a horse for you
It's just to return half of the reward you deserve.
It's so amazing, I don't want it anymore, I'll give it back to you
If you are so noble,
You should spit out the food you ate last night
Give up this horse and walk back to the blacksmith shop to make blacksmiths.
earn your wages
Don't fool me, I don't believe I will starve to death
Of course I won't starve to death
But I believe you go to Xianyang City
It was a few years later
By then the woman you like will be married to someone else
This is the map to Xianyang
As for whether you want it or not, it’s up to you to decide
Survive in this troubled world
There's no use sticking around
Survival of the fittest is the way to survive
Walk
Very good
I'm gray beard
I passed by this place with a group of brothers and it was a pleasure to meet them.
Hello…
Don't go, help me
Thanks
Brother is awesome...
bearded brother
Your riding skills are really amazing
What this brother said is really true
Didn't ask for Gao's name?
Xiang Shaolong
Brother Xiang, it's a pity that I have to drive the horses back to the pasture.
Otherwise, you can have a few drinks with Brother Xiang
That's a pity
See you later
Will see you later…
So majestic
This way is north, this way is west
You have to go through Dongping to reach Handan.
There are no longitude and latitude lines, is that okay?
fight
Isn't he the bearded brother just now?
Miss, go quickly
You bunch of sterile thieves
Must not die well
Okay, leave no one alive, kill them for me
Kill you all...
How unreasonable
If you don't stop, I will bite my tongue and kill myself
don't want
Brother Beard, why don’t you take her back and play slowly?
good
The thief…
You all deserve to die, especially you
If you want to kill, just kill, no need to say more
What fun would it be to kill him?
He hurt so many of us.
Why don't you take him back and torture him slowly? Okay
take him back
let me go...
Brother Xiang, let’s go back to the village to celebrate
Come drink with me...
Drink
Drink more, smile, so happy
Cheers everyone, cheers…
Big brothers, hugging each other
There are beauties and delicious food, cheers
How can this be?
The girl gets a bottle of wine, you get a cup
Give you a piece
OK, give me one
Of course it’s a cheng, I’m happy
Come... drink, drink up... do...
Brother Xiang, if there's nothing important
Stay here for a few more days
If you don't tell me, I plan to stay here for a few days.
Brother, I’m so happy today
Let's have a drink too
Cheers, come
Brother, you look so heroic
Why only drink a small cup?
There is a bottle of wine here, let’s drink from the jar
Drink from a jar? Come on
Interesting. Drink it.
Brothers, let’s have a drink with Brother Xiang too
Okay, do it…
Brothers, I am so happy today
How about we have a good drink with Brother Xiang?
Come, everyone is happy, you're welcome
Bro, are you drunk?
Drunk but not drunk
If you don't get drunk today, you won't get home. I'll drink up the whole place.
OK?
drink…
I have this cup
No, just be happy
I drank the whole meal, so...
Happy, drink drink…
bearded brother
What is the treasure you just snatched back?
Why not take it out and let the brothers open their eyes?
Okay, brother, we also want to broaden our horizons...
Okay, I'll take it out for everyone to enjoy.
OK, come and take a look...
Brother, what is the significance of such a treasure?
It seems to be called He Shibi
Heshibi?
Isn’t it time for the Heshi Bi to be returned to Zhao intact?
How could he be snatched away by his elder brother on the road?
Then I don't know
Brother, why is this jade called He's Bi?
You don’t even know about He Shibi, you’re so out of date.
Listening to your tone, I heard everything in detail
Brother Xiang, I would like to hear the details
Actually, I know a little bit about it
This story happened a long time ago
There is a man named Bian He
Bian He discovered a piece of jade at that time
This piece of jade was not polished at that time.
He gave it to the King of Chu twice
King Chu actually didn’t believe it twice
The last time he ordered his feet to be cut off
How outrageous do you say?
So tragic?
Not tragic anymore
This Bian He did not believe in evil, so in the end...
Please hold it for me, please
But you have to drink it all
When Bian He presented this to King Chu for the last time,
King Chu actually believed it
I also asked someone to cut open this jade
I found that there was really a piece of beautiful jade inside.
This piece of jade is the He's jade that everyone sees.
I see…
It turns out that this piece of jade really has a great background.
Brother, you risk your life to win this jade for others
Just receive fifty taels of remuneration
Really too cheap
What? I only got fifty taels after working so hard to get it.
Otherwise I would be very angry
You must drink to vent your anger, come on, drink
drink…
Five hundred taels is enough.
Okay, I will collect it from him then
Brother Beard, don’t be angry
We must collect enough five hundred taels from him by then
Let's drink this wine and make everyone happy
OK, drink drink…
There’s not only good food and wine tonight
There seems to be a beauty
Yes, that beauty we just snatched back
take her out
OK, take her out... OK
Brother Xiang, who can throw the arrow into the wine pot?
The beauty belongs to him
So simple?
But I think
The mouth of the pot is so big and placed so close
Even a blind man can put it in, why not change it?
Change to another one…
This is almost enough, the mouth of the pot is just right
Put it further away, where should I put it? Put it...
Might as well put it here
Put it here, that's it
Brother Xiang, I will definitely miss it from such a distance.
Are you sure you won't win?
If you don't win, you automatically give up, so you don't have to throw.
start
Come…
Go, next person
OK, not successful…
You just bought me a drink, I'll give you one more
good
So awesome
I won, Brother Xiang, I won
Brother, hit
Didn't you just say that it's difficult and far to throw, and the mouth of the pot is narrow?
How do you hit it with one throw?
I don't know why either
Beauty, you belong to me tonight
What tonight?
Can't you see? I haven't thrown it yet
you throw
I don’t know if it’s possible? It’s so far…
Put the wine bottle away
No need...you put it away and I'll throw it harder
How to throw? Such a small spout
This time I brought it upon myself
Brother Xiang, you've crossed the line.
Have you crossed the line? I'm so sorry.
hurry up
Brother Xiang, do you want to throw or not?
If you don't throw, you abstain.
I'm exchanging feelings with the jug
Is there a limited time to throw now?
I'll get it tomorrow morning and you'll have to wait too
Why don't you go have breakfast first?
It's great to use the tail end
Amazing skills
Brother Xiang is awesome. I won.
I won, thank you…
Brother Xiang is indeed very skilled
Beauty is yours
I'm so sorry, girl.
I have no choice but to hurry up, okay...
I'm leaving first, brother Xiang is awesome
Great, so happy
Don't make any noise
You are so heavy, close the door
frowning
Don't move, I'll help you untie the rope and let go...
What are you yelling for? Stop making noise...
You are a thief who is worse than a scumbag
Stealing people's property, raping women and children
Destined to be struck by thunder from heaven
The wilderness of violent corpses, dead bodies without intact bodies, no descendants or descendants
Are you done?
You stinky bitch is so articulate.
No need to spit, right?
You pervert, how dare you be rude
This girl will bite her tongue and commit suicide immediately
You're such a tongue-tied woman, your tongue is ten feet long
Even if I bite ten times, I still can’t finish it.
Don't move
Let go...don't move, let me help you...
If you are rude again, I will exterminate your children and grandchildren.
Absolute sons and great grandchildren
I really want to see how you can make me have no children or grandchildren.
It hurts and bites
If I don't kill you, you slut
It’s hard to express the anger in this girl’s heart
It's safer to hold a sword
count you lucky
No need to be so vigorous
Manager Tao
Miss
It’s no use, leave the dangerous area quickly and return to Wujiapu
Let's go together
you listen to me
Leave the dangerous area and report back to Wujiapu
Those bandits will definitely kill you
Fang'er can't leave without paying attention
My life is a small matter, but He's Bi is of great importance.
It is related to the future destiny of Qin State
Mr. Tao won’t leave, and neither will Fang’er.
Miss, it's a big deal
What are you doing? Don't mess around
beauty
So you are really here
you are so cunning
Knock me out while I'm taking off my pants
You really don't know how to appreciate it
Brother Xiang, execute him on the spot
It’s better to rectify the Fa on the spot
Anyway, there are cages and chains here
Come on then
let go
I really don’t know what to say, and it spoils our fun.
Miss
The more the woman is beaten, the more obedient she becomes.
Brother Xiang, why not rectify the law on the spot?
OK
I wonder if you two are interested? You go first.
OK No
Can you walk? If you can walk, come with me. Come on
someone
May I ask your surname?
Xiang Shaolong
Brother Xiang, why do you understand that you were the accomplice of a tiger before?
Now I have to save Tao again
Because Brother Beard helped me catch that horse before
I saw him fighting with you, so I planned to help him.
Helping out? What is helping out?
In short, he did bad things with good intentions before.
Now make up for it
That's it. Stop talking and let's go.
Brother Xiang, Tao has a merciless request.
What's up?
I hope Brother Xiang
You can escort the eldest lady back to Wujiapu to report the news.
What about you?
I must go to the cottage once
You have been injured. If you go back, you will die.
No, I must take back He's Bi
Heshibi is important, but your life is also important
Tell the truth
The Wu family was entrusted by Prime Minister Lu of Qin State
Bring He's Bi back to the State of Zhao
In order to exchange for returning to the prince government and returning to the country
Huang Zizheng? Isn’t Huang Zizheng the same as Ying Zheng?
Is he still a hostage in Zhao State?
The matter is of great importance. Tao really cannot miss this important matter.
The eldest lady is going to leave it to you.
Ying Zheng is still in Xianyang, and I can't return to Hong Kong.
Brother Xiang said that Tao really didn’t know why
Okay... Anyway, you take care of her
I'll help you go back to the village to get He's Bi
Brother Xiang is so brave, Tao is really grateful
but…
Nothing better
I'm waiting for your good news in Changting Town ahead.
He's Bi depends entirely on you.
careful
It is indeed a unique treasure
Thank you for your appreciation, uncle
The remuneration was changed from fifty taels to five hundred taels.
This treasure is priceless
Five hundred taels is definitely not expensive
Five hundred taels is not expensive at all
Will all Wushi’s generals be killed?
I originally arrested a man named Tao
It's a pity that he was rescued
Did Wujiapu send someone to rescue him?
No
Hui was rescued by a random friend.
Not friends at all, even the beauty was saved
It should be the eldest lady of the Wu family
Why is the eldest daughter of the Wu family here?
She disguised herself as a man and joined the team
When catching her
It seems like someone called her some kind of eldest lady
She is indeed a stunning beauty
The uncle will also be moved when he sees it
The three of them won't go far without riding horses
Should be able to catch up
No need, get your reward first
Anyone who offends Miss Wu family
There is only one way to die
Manager Tao
Don't keep claiming to call him Brother Xiang
He's basically a thief
Brother Xiang was misbehaving with the eldest lady in the village
It's an expedient measure
You still defend him, if he hadn't helped those horse thieves
There's no way we'd end up like this
He just hit it by mistake
Hit by accident
He looks like a thief and has a thief heart. He cannot be trusted.
Mr. Tao, you don't need to wait here.
Let’s go back to Wujiapu together
Bring all the men and horses to wipe out the stronghold of these horse thieves.
I must keep my promise and wait here for Brother Xiang
Miss, please go back to Wujiapu first to report the news
If he takes back He's Bi
I'll go back to Wujiapu right away
No, let's go back to Wujiabao together to ask for reinforcements
There is no need to pay attention to this thief
He will definitely not keep his word
If he takes back He's Bi
They will definitely be taken away by others.
Miss
It was indeed Brother Xiang who rescued us from the village
Let's just believe him once and go our separate ways, okay?
Okay, Fang'er will trust Mr. Tao once
Brother Xiang, how are things going?
I just returned to the cottage
meet a handsome man
He took away He's Bi
People who know our market route
Apart from our Wujiabao, there is only Zhao Mu
Could it really be him?
Who is Zhao Mu?
Zhao Mu was a powerful minister of the State of Zhao
It can be said that one person is inferior to ten thousand people.
He must have great power
He's handsome yet a bit cold and arrogant, and he's good at martial arts.
Isn’t it invincible?
you misunderstood
This person is Zhao Mu’s number one swordsman Lian Jin
Lian Jin?
I have a question that I've wanted to ask you for a long time.
please say
When I was a kid, I heard people telling idiom stories
Obviously Lin Xiangru has returned to Zhao intact.
Why are you transporting it back to Zhao now?
The Heshi Bi that Lord Lin Xiangru brought back
is fake
Can you please stop talking behind my back?
You sit down and look at me and say, I'm asking you
I really don’t understand you costume people
I like carrying people on my back so much
Or just go to the window and look at the moon and talk.
What if the jade is returned to Zhao?
I've finished
Finished? How about that?
At that time, Lord Lin Xiangru
The Heshi Bi brought back is fake
Fake? Did Lin Xiangru lie to the emperor?
No, the one who bullies others is King Zhao of Qin
On that day he pretended to have fifteen cities
Exchange He's Bi with Zhao State
Although Mr. Lin is witty
Seeing through King Qin Zhao’s lack of sincerity
Threaten King Qin Zhao by breaking the jade into pieces
King Qin Zhao superficially submitted
Show your sincerity by fasting and bathing
I see
Lin Xiangru must have taken advantage of this opportunity
Stole He's Bi
That's right, but King Zhao of Qin is more treacherous
When I was already admiring the jade in the main hall,
Taking advantage of the opportunity of various concubines and concubines vying to watch
Replaced the real jade
Clever move
A clever move?
It means good strategy, cleverness and cleverness
Yes, it's really a clever move
Now a stranger has ascended the throne and become the Emperor of Qin
So I was very anxious to get the real jade
Offered back to Zhao as a gift in exchange for political hostages
Then you are still sitting here
Let's go and keep an eye on that Lian Jin
What does it mean to keep an eye on it quickly?
I'm really pissed off by you, talking while walking
Go through the back door
This piece is the Heshi Bi that the old man imitated.
It really compares to the piece on the young master’s hand.
Are they exactly the same?
Really good handiwork
Thank you uncle for your appreciation
In those days, my late father also worked for a Qin man.
Forged a piece of He's Bi
The old man witnessed it personally
That’s why the imitation is so similar