Team Leader! There's a fridge full of ice cream.
Plus a coffee machine and a massage chair!
Team Leader! Big news!
Check the company message board right now.
- What's going on?
-  Hurry! Look at this!
What do I do?
He came back before I could even process the breakup.
From being a junior employee to the director.
From a boyfriend to an ex-boyfriend.
Where did you find something so cute?
I'm glad you think it's cute.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Because you're so pretty.
­- What?
- What?
Did I just say that out loud?
­I...
I mean, that wasn't all of a sudden...
For a while?
No...
You look especially...
pretty today.
What? Ju Won, you're so funny.
I wasn't trying to be funny.
I meant it.
♫  I sleep without sleeping  ♫
♫  I dream without dreaming  ♫
But that's too bad.
I'm not into younger guys.
I don't like older women, either.
- What?
- It's not that I like older women.
I like pretty women.
♫  Sweet drama, will it be there for me?  ♫
♫  Will I embrace love like it's love?  ♫
I'm sorry if I made you uncomfortable.
♫  I promise you  ♫
I'll be careful moving forward.
♫  Sweet drama only we can make  ♫
Why would he say such a thing?
Thank you.
Okay, then.
They wanted to transfer me abroad,
but I convinced them to have me stay. That's why I'm late.
Why did you do that?
- That just makes us uncomfortable.
- I'm not.
If you want to break up with me, that's your right.
But...
it's up to me to chase after you.
From now on,
I will cling to you.
I'm going to be as pathetic as I can be.
Take pity on me, Yun Seo.
Director.
Vice Chairman is waiting for you.
Yes. Let's go.
See you later.
I must've surprised all of you.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you before.
No worries! There must be a reason you couldn't tell us.
I agree. We're sorry for not noticing.
You must've been flustered when I left my post for a week.
Thank you for understanding.
Understanding? Ju Won.
I mean, Mr. Ju Won.
I mean, Sir. You can go on vacation anytime you need to.
When I heard you went on vacation, Sir,
I thought, "Maybe he needs healing time." I totally got it.
Sir? Mister? Please don't be so formal.
Keep teaching me the ropes like before.
I brought you coffee too.
This is for you, Deputy Bae.
- For you, Deputy Lee.
- Thank you.
You don't have to do this anymore.
I know you don't like it hot
so I took special care to get two sleeves.
Two?
Right, Deputy Bae would get so angry when you got only one sleeve.
Ye Yeong, wh-when did I get angry?
I wasn't angry. It's just my face.
Just an angry-looking face. It's a misunderstanding.
And this is for you, Team Leader.
Thank you.
But, Director, what brings you here?
You're not working around here anymore.
How can you say something so cold?
Here, here. Go ahead.
May I escort you to your office?
My office...
is right there.
How can this be the Director's office?
I got it remodeled over the weekend.
Oh, my, why...
Why didn't you go somewhere nicer?
I like it here the best.
I've learned so much from you all and want to keep learning.
I felt it was best to stay close, so I set up my office here.
They say out of sight, out of mind.
I don't want to be out of sight.
Then, should we get to work?
Yes...
What? What?
The youngest on our team is Chairwoman's youngest son
and Vice Chairman's brother?
On top of that, his office is right here? Is this real?
There are so many empty offices. Why over there?
I know!
Wait.
Maybe there's someone he wants to see here.
Someone he wants to keep seeing
and make them uncomfortable.
Hey!
Why would Ju Won, I mean the Director, want to make me uncomfortable?
What did I do?
I mean, I guess you didn't do much.
You just made him do coffee runs, criticized him for being slow,
badmouthed the company for having crappy benefits,
told him his hair was weird, picked on his appearance... Aigoo.
I should write my letter of resignation.
You should have known better.
Whoa.
It looks like our team leader might quit, not me.
What? Why would the Team Leader quit?
Hear me out!
She worked so hard, got promoted quickly before her peers,
but he got promoted even faster because of his parents!
She must be furious.
- You think?
- Of course.
What is this? What do you mean you'll chase me?
What do you mean you convinced the chairwoman?
I already explained. Why are you acting like you don't get it?
The chairwoman said if we break up, you'll get transferred abroad–
That was her plan,
but I convinced her to transfer me here.
You were able to convince her?
I pretended that you blindsided me and broke up with me.
If I said I heard from Hyeong, he'd get in trouble.
I thought you might be at a loss, too.
I said the breakup was so unexpected that I needed time to process it.
I told her if I went abroad now, I'd drink constantly and mess up at work.
What?
And I pitched a vision I prepared under a good team leader.
That I'll take the AL Card from No. 2 to No. 1 in the industry within two years.
If I don't succeed, then I will go abroad.
Is that possible in two years?
I'll have to make it possible.
If my mother wants to expand our business through a strategic marriage,
I'll prove that I can do it on my own.
That's how I can stay by your side.
Where is your pride?
I took money under the condition that I break up with you.
Ha Yun Seo likes money. That's nothing new.
Since when do I like money?
You stay at work late to get overtime pay and work on the weekends for the bonus.
That was just fulfilling my duty as a disciplined employee–
Anyway, I promised the Chairwoman that I would break up with you.
So you did.
Then you've fulfilled your promise. Can we date again now?
You didn't promise her that you wouldn't get back together.
What...
Wait.
But why are you suddenly speaking informally to me?
Actually...
I couldn't figure it out, so I looked up how to get your ex to come back to you.
It said the best way was to show them a new side of you.
It said one way for younger men to melt someone is to speak informally, Yun Seo.
I also read that this might make her melt.
Yun Seo, you're so cute.
What are you doing?
Why not? You're so cute.
- What?
- So cute.
What are those two doing?
Those two... It can't be.
How do I explain this?
They caught us doing that. It's game over.
What you saw earlier...
It's okay.
- No need to explain. We get it.
- What?
But honestly, we feel betrayed.
How can he get ahead of us like that?
What?
Get ahead of us?
Yes! What he just did!
This thing! Pretending like you're cute because he got promoted!
This thing! Treating you like some kind of lowly puppy!
Petting you like that! That's what he was doing.
I know. I didn't think he was like that. I'm scared!
- That's not it...
- What do you mean?
Don't protect your pride.
You must be so upset. Your subordinate became a director overnight.
You went in there to scold him, then got overpowered.
If we don't get it, who will?
That's not it–
Wait, is it better if they misunderstand?
But when you think about it, this isn't the worst.
If he's willing to remodel an office just to be near us,
it means his memories with us aren't so bad.
It's not bad to get along with the owner's son.
This might be a pretty sweet deal for us.
You're right, but...
How come he never came across as a chaebol at all?
What? What do you mean? Maybe not a chaebol, but I knew he was rich.
He always smelled like money.
His clothes were all luxury brands.
Really? They never had logos. I thought they weren't branded.
No, no.
Real rich people never wear logos.
People who buy luxuries once in a blue moon wear ones with huge logos.
Aigoo...
Now that I think of it, he was different at the convenience store.
Here they are...
Ju Won! It's buy one, get one free.
I just need one.
What? He doesn't want a freebie?
Is he a chaebol or what?
I trash-talked him, not knowing he was an actual chaebol!
On top of that...
Daebak!
Wait, you said you couldn't make it to Deputy Oh's wedding, right?
I'll deliver the gift money for you.
Thank you.
I've never done this before. How much do people usually give?
For a work colleague, like five?
Five?
Here's 500,000 won.
I mean, not 500,000.
I meant 50,000 won.
Laying down a cool 500,000 for a colleague's wedding?
Carrying that much cash in his wallet? It made no sense!
­Gosh.
See? 3,000 won.
This is the reality of office workers!
But 3,000 is so little.
I just carry this to get a pastry.
Anyway, when Ju Won first got here, I thought he was nuts.
I thought, "What kind of person is this?"
Now that I think of it,
it was all because he was a chaebol!
I should have paid more attention. How did I not catch that?
You didn't know, either, Team Leader. Right?
Well...
It must be confusing for all of you, but nothing has changed.
Please continue to do your jobs from where you are.
You might feel pressured by the director's office being so close,
but we won't have to see him as much as before.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- Dinner?
- Yes.
I feel like I caused you concern unintentionally.
You're working late, and I saw you head out to dinner. So, I want to treat you.
How does beef BBQ sound?
No, thank you. We decided on seolleongtang*.
(*Korean bone broth soup)
That works, right?
Gosh. We didn't know the Director was going to treat us to BBQ.
That's right.
If we're talking about BBQ, seolleongtang is like a cow washing its toes in the water.
If we're eating out, beef BBQ sounds a hundred times better. Aigoo.
The place across the street is supposed to be amazing.
How does that sound, Director?
I'm into anything. Should we go?
Let's go.
I'm okay. I'll stay back and look over some paperwork.
Stop making us feel uncomfortable! It's not like we're eating noodles.
If you don't eat, how can we go eat? Let's just go.
He's right! Let's just eat quickly and come to work after. Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Well...
- Excuse me, I'm okay.
- Let's go get some beef!
Let's just go eat and enjoy.
What a great day we're having!
Soju and beer would make all this even better.
Soju and beer? We need to have a meeting after this.
I'm joking.
We've been working late nonstop to prepare for the presentation.
I'm just saying. Do you think I would actually drink?
Then should we have a drink tonight and delay the presentation?
Delaying the presentation for alcohol? That's nonsense.
It's not that.
I looked over the materials. It's lacking a lot.
Lacking? How? Which part do you mean?
Lacking time.
The timeline was tight to start.
When I left the team, you were short on hands.
I meant that it could be perfect with an extra week.
Right. You said that a few more days would help, Team Leader.
Right, right.
That's true, but...
Let's have a drink tonight to bond as a team.
Tomorrow, we'll work even harder.
Can we get some beer and soju over here?
And four more orders of sirloin, please!
I love this!
Ju Won!
Director.
I'm so sorry for everything.
Please don't fire me.
Why would I fire you? Don't say that.
Get home safely.
Seriously? Let me go with him. I'm going in the same direction.
Sure, sure.
Promise me you won't fire me.
Promise me! Pinky swear!
Pinky swear.
Pinky swear? Go home!
- Get home safely!
- Okay!
Excuse me.
Why are you following me, Director?
I wasn't following you. I'm going to the office too.
Stop lying! You're following me.
No, I'm not.
I thought you didn't drink so you could get back to work.
I'm doing the same. I have a lot to do, so I just had one beer.
All right then.
I have a lot of work. Bye.
♫  Every scar, every tear, one less spark, clouds in your eyes  ♫
♫  Fading you  ♫
♫  Fading you, like a fog  ♫
♫  If I try to reach you, to catch you  ♫
I thought he would leave if I pretended like I hated him.
I thought he would accept it once he knew I took money.
♫  The more I get to know ya, can't tell the feelings I feel  ♫
♫  Sometimes it doesn't feel so right  ♫
♫  Boyfriend, boyfriend  ♫
♫  Why you looking at me like I'm your boyfriend, boyfriend?  ♫
♫  Why you looking at me like I'm your boyfriend?  ♫
♫  Call me back when you're sober, I'm afraid I might just love ya  ♫
And after that day, like his declaration of war,
he started to throw himself at me.
What should we get for lunch?
How about crispy fried tonkatsu?
I love the sound of tonkatsu.
Director!
Are you going to eat with us?
Let's get some crispy tonkatsu.
Director, are you going to keep eating with us?
Yes.
I've been used to eating with you all ever since I started.
More than anything,
I like eating with you.
Me, too.
I'm heading out.
♫  When I call out your name  ♫
The bill, please.
One moment.
Okay.
♫  Sweet drama  ♫
What? What are you doing?
Sorry, I thought it was candy.
Candy? What?
Don't be like this at work.
We're not at work. We're in a restaurant.
You must be crazy!
♫  Before the morning comes, I'll hold your hand  ♫
Are you headed home?
Can you drive me?
Please stop it. You can't come onto me like this at work.
Then can I come on to you outside of work?
♫  When my heart full of feelings for you opens up  ♫
Are you okay?
I'm not okay. Please go out with me.
What does that have to do with your foot?
Go out with me.
I'm hungry. Can you buy me dinner?
Buy dinner for a chaebol?
- Then can a chaebol pay?
- No thanks.
Why would we have dinner? What are we?
Exes?
If you know that, please go your own way, Director Seo Ju Won.
You're obligated to buy me dinner.
I did the math roughly.
While we were dating, I paid for dinner more often.
About 27 times more.
What? What a specific number.
Do you have proof?
Of course.
My phone.
I photographed everything we ate and did.
Plus, I can do the math from my credit card transactions.
Bye.
You're the one who said splitting is the new way.
Let it go. You're rich.
So are you. Pay with the money you got from my mother.
I'm going to spend that money slowly later.
I'm not spending a penny on you, Director.
Wow. See? You love money.
That's why I'm perfect for you.
If you date me, you get money and me.
Buy one, get one free.
Buy one, get one free only goes so far!
Stop following me.
She's really gone.
Are you really okay?
Maybe I shouldn't have told you.
Ignorance is bliss sometimes.
No.
Thanks for telling me everything.
I thought you might chase after Yun Seo
but didn't expect you to reject working abroad.
You've never gone against Mother.
She's never offered me a deal I wanted to refuse.
Alberto! Come out.
That little...
Hyeong, why are you dressed like that?
Who cares? I'm alone.
Ju Won, do you know when I'm glad that I'm in an arranged marriage?
- Do I need to know?
- Right now.
Right now.
Freedom like I've never experienced before.
As soon as we got married, my wife went to France, and I started living alone.
But wow...
All my life, I felt locked up, even at home, with all eyes on me.
I was so uncomfortable watching my behavior.
All that...
is gone. I am so comfortable.
I don't know how I got through it all this time.
Okay. Congrats.
- I'm leaving.
- Already?
Hey, come on!
You must feel down. Have another drink!
Hey, you don't feel like drinking?
Do you want to watch a movie?
You know, I set up a little home theater recently.
I want to watch romance movies and cry as much as I want.
Right.
You don't like movies.
I do.
- Watching movies is my hobby these days.
- What?
You said cinemas are dark and cramped.
You feel suffocated staring at the screen.
I did.
Going with Yun Seo makes it feel okay.
Yun Seo loves horror movies.
- Horror movies?
- Yes.
You especially hate horror movies, don't you?
Ju Won is trying hard.
It's easier said than done to chase an ex like that.
Hey. It's hard for me, too.
Worry about me. I'm your friend.
I'm saying this because you're my friend.
Honestly, so what if the mother is against it?
Right. Not everyone in the world can approve of you.
It's not that.
Yun Seo, if you look up our restaurant-
Not "our" restaurant.
My restaurant.
Anyway, if you look up CEO Yi Rae's restaurant, you see a score.
But some people give it one star, and some people give it five.
Even though they had the same food and makgeolli.
That's what life is.
So what if your future mother-in-law gives you one star?
The young master Ju Won is giving you five stars so generously.
You can't satisfy everybody in life.
That's what I'm saying.
Parents disapprove of their children's partners all the time.
That's right! To be blunt, your parents can oppose a chaebol son-in-law.
Get it together. She doesn't have parents.
Right.
Yes! Did you call for me?
Yes! Coming.
How dare you talk back to me?
I told you to go buy some alcohol!
Look at you... Do I need to throw something at you?
Go!
Yu Na! Give it to me. Mommy will carry it.
I can carry it. It's not heavy.
People will badmouth me if they see a kid carrying alcohol.
Does your dad need soju this badly?
Let's go.
- Do you have a cold?
- Yes.
I think I was out in the cold for too long yesterday.
If I had known, I'd have made some soup.
So you can have something hot.
Mess up my soup like you messed up your midterms?
Hey!
Cough or nag, pick one!
Eat.
The more I think of it, the more pissed I am.
That weakling made my sister stay out in the cold.
The weakling?
My sister's boyfriend. I don't like him.
It's so annoying.
Want to feel less annoyed and go play some games? Skip school?
No, I'm not skipping school.
Why not? You never study. Why do you even go to class?
My sister says not to skip class at the very least.
It's not like I'm paying attention.
You bastard!
Carry some cash.
Are you poor?
Next time, bring more.
What are friends for?
You should lend me some money when I need it.
It started as a joke, but it's getting worse.
I know. Are they still doing that?
Do something.
- They listen to you, though.
- I need money.
I need money.
Hey. Answer me!
- Why bother?
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Let's go.
- Why don't you answer?
Wait, please.
The door is closing.
He said he heard from his brother. He knows I took the money.
He knows I dumped Ju Won.
This is so awkward.
It's cold out today.
Yes, the temperature really dropped.
- Ju Won is bothering you a lot these days, right?
- Sorry?
He can be quite unpredictable sometimes.
He surprises those around him.
But it's cute, so it drives you crazy. Right?
Yes.
No.
Yesno?
I mean, I'm not feeling well.
I misspoke.
Your brother and I have already broken up.
So...
please don't talk to me about this at work.
Sure. Got it.
I was just giving you some information.
Information?
Ju Won is strong-willed and stubborn. No one can stop him.
I'm telling you, it won't be easy to beat him.
Sometimes, I think he has bigger guts than I do.
If he's met someone he really likes, he won't give up easily.
Actually, I was surprised when he told me about movies yesterday.
You made a kid who hated movies into a cinephile.
That was kind of unbelievable.
Pardon?
Going down. The door is closing.
Seo Ju Won doesn't like movies?
- Here you go.
- We would always eat and watch movies.
If we liked a movie, we would often see it over again.
Honey.
The Exorcist is back in cinemas. Want to go today?
He knew about releases way more than me.
He doesn't like seeing movies?
Good morning.
♫  I like the warmth  ♫
♫  Don't know at the start (The shine on my place)  ♫
♫  You laugh at my boring jokes  ♫
What does he like besides movies?
The opera.
Did we ever go to the opera?
Honey, want to go to the opera next week?
No.
Right.
Did that happen?
He never mentioned the opera again after that.
♫  Anyway  ♫
Seo Ju Won, are you going to keep making me a bad person?
Team Leader, could you take a look at this?
Yes.
♫  You listen to the stories that happen around me  ♫
♫  I just like thinking about you  ♫
What? When did you get here?
Just now.
I got you some porridge. You look tired today.
Director, aren't you busy?
I am.
But this is more important than anything else.
Eat this...
and take these.
It's okay. I'm fine.
You don't look fine at all.
I'll take care of myself. Don't butt in. Go.
This isn't from your ex-boyfriend. It's from your colleague.
You're sick but still here because of the presentation.
Have some. Let me get you some water.
You don't look well.
Why don't you take a sick day off tomorrow?
Maybe you forgot since you became a Director.
It's not easy for an office worker to take a day off.
Look.
This is the difference between you and me.
You can take a day off anytime.
I'm an office worker who struggles to take a day off.
Then give me your car keys. I'll drive you.
Take my help today.
I'm fine! I don't need your help, Seo Ju Won–
Yun Seo! Ha Yun Seo!
Yun Seo.
Yun Seo!
Are you awake?
Where am I?
This is the VIP room, right?
I'm heading out.
Where do you think you're going? Finish your IV.
I don't have time for this.
Workers compensation?
Workers compensation only goes so far.
What kind of company gets a VIP room for an employee?
This one.
Team Leader Ha Yun Seo sets the standard for benefits.
Well, you can be proud.
I'm really fine. I'm leaving.
Are you actually fine?
It looks like you're pretending to be fine.
Am I wrong?
Yun Seo...
I'm having a hard time.
I told myself I would do this,
but it's hard to keep getting rejected.
It's hard to watch you pretend like everything's fine when it's not.
If it's hard,
why did you do it?
I heard it's hard for you to watch movies.
I heard you don't like sitting somewhere cramped.
Why did you endure it?
Who said that?
The Vice Chairman.
We...
went out for a year and six months.
But I just found out today from someone else.
It wasn't on purpose. I...
Was it for me?
No.
For me.
I wasn't white-knuckling through something I hated.
I wanted to like the things Ha Yun Seo likes.
You're right.
Honestly, I was white-knuckling it at first.
Those times were hard at first.
But it was cool to see you enjoy yourself so much.
When you watched something you liked, you were so pretty and shined.
So I watched another one, then another one.
I started enjoying myself, too.
After that, I started to genuinely enjoy movies.
I even collect DVDs now.
It's more than just movies.
I couldn't eat spicy food before.
I didn't like mixing beer and soju because it's too strong.
I didn't like winter. Too cold. But I do now.
I wasn't white-knuckling myself through things I hated.
Thanks to you, there are more things I enjoy.
You should have told me earlier.
I never expected you to accommodate me so one-sidedly.
The opera might have felt strange and boring,
but if I knew how much you liked it,
I would have tried to enjoy it for you.
You never gave me a chance.
I'm sorry.
Let's...
eat together. Twenty-seven times.
What?
I don't like how you did it, but you tried for me all this time.
You tried hard at dating,
so let's try hard to break up.
I don't want to try hard at that.
But still.
I had a thought.
Maybe it's like a cold. You have to get over a big one.
Maybe that's how you get over emotions.
What?
Do you want to get over me like a cold?
Treating me like a virus?
Is that how it is?
Then I'll cling to you like an antibody.
Fine.
No matter how we eat, 27 times.
I just want to eat with you.
I'll show you how much I like you and why we should stay together for real.
♫  You're like a chore on a chaotic day  ♫
Here you are.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
♫  You were the one who helped me deal with others  ♫
Eat.
♫  Those confusing days of the past  ♫
♫  After facing the truth  ♫
♫  We are here now  ♫
♫  Just wake up, any time  ♫
That's how we started eating together.
♫  Can you be awake all night, wait for me?  ♫
♫  The moment I had with you  ♫
♫  Just follow me, all right  ♫
♫  No need to say anything, I can tell from your face  ♫
♫  I know you feel the same, I can always feel it  ♫
You have to pour the sauce on the sweet and sour pork.
♫  Just make a smile, anytime  ♫
♫  Seeing you makes me smile  ♫
It felt like the start of a non-date date.
♫  Wait for me, those moments with you  ♫
♫  Just follow me, all right  ♫
- So good.
- It's good here.
Try this.
This?
While we were eating, it felt like we were back as lovers.
♫  No need to say anything, I can tell from your face  ♫
♫  Do you feel the same?  ♫
♫  I can always feel it  ♫
♫  You're coming to me  ♫
Ju Won is upsetting you, isn't he?
I didn't want to take it this far.
I thought they broke up. Why are they still seeing each other?
From what I know, Ha Yun Seo is trying her best.
Ju Won is chasing her intensely.
Even if you gave your blessing, Ha Yun Seo would refuse.
That feels uncomfortable in its own way.
Just keep your eye on them. You know you can't cut someone off at once.
Anyway, she seemed responsible. I'm sure she'll keep her word.
Can you take care of these?
Don't let Ju Won see them.
Why not? You don't want him to see these?
Nothing good will come out of it.
Also, you're sure Ju Won doesn't know I met with Ha Yun Seo, right?
He doesn't know I'm taking these pictures, right?
Of course not.
So stop taking pictures like these and give them some time.
Ju Won will handle it.
But do you want Ju Won to have an arranged marriage?
You did the same,
but Father hasn't been back from New York for the past two years.
Mother, let me take care of these right away.
By the way.
Why are all the pictures of them eating?
Are you ready?
Okay.
But why do we seem like we're going for a foodie challenge?
So what? Let's go.
Ma'am, we're here.
Welcome!
We'll have the really spicy one.
- A bottle of soju as well.
- Okay.
Actually, no alcohol, please.
Okay.
What?
You always have soju. Why not today?
We said we would eat. Not drink.
Are you worried getting drunk will weaken your resolve?
- Weaken my resolve?
- You're holding it in.
If you drink, you might want to take back the breakup.
Ma'am, a bottle of soju over here!
Make that two.
Okay!
The car is waiting for you. You're headed home, right?
Could we stop by the wine store? I feel like a drink.
Sure.
Don't you have the 2000 vintage Chateau Doen?
I'm sorry. It's so expensive that not many ask for it.
But when Director Lee Mi Jin posted about it a few days ago,
there was a surge in orders.
My wife?
Yes.
She's quite an influencer.
What...
Did we have this at home?
When did we get it?
I don't remember getting it.
What a daebak event.
- So, you know their Chairman?
- Yes.
What is he like in real life?
He's exactly like how he is on the news.
So how do you call him?
Ahjussi.
- So weird.
- What?
I feel like I'm with a celebrity.
Plus, you seem so nonchalant about it.
Wow, Seo Ju Won.
Okay.
- Want some fan service from a celebrity?
- What?
Go away!
Aigoo...
You two are always so cute.
When is the wedding?
Ma'am, we broke up.
What? What are you talking about? For real?
Yes, we broke up for real.
So I'm being clingy, but she's stonewalling me.
Aigoo! Whatever! Broken up or not,
here's a bottle of beer on the house. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- No!
Ma'am, no free bottle.
I need to empty out her wallet.
What? Is she paying today?
Yes. Twenty-two more times.
You don't know this, but this guy here is super rich.
But he keeps wanting to eat for free on me.
The rich are the stingiest.
Fine. If you pay 22 times,
I'll pay 220 times. That works, right?
Aigoo, come on now! Stop the lovers' quarrel.
Enjoy your meal and go.
It's not a lovers' quarrel. We really broke up.
I'm so sad.
So...
should we mix soju and beer?
- You just wait. I'll mix it in golden ratio.
- Okay.
- So good.
- Right?
Give me one.
Broke up? My ass.
They're hopelessly in love.
Why do you keep doing that?
Ju Won.
Seo Ju Won.
We should get home. Call a... I mean,
call your secretary.
Call him. I'm leaving.
Wh-What? What are you doing?
Yun Seo.
Let me ask you one thing.
Will you really break up with me?
Don't you like me anymore?
♫  Fading you  ♫
Why did I do that?
The night was dark.
The wind was blowing.
We were drunk. Is that why?
♫  So I just let the color wash over me  ♫
I ended up telling him the truth.
No.
I still...
like you a lot.
♫  Looking at you makes it true  ♫
♫  Every moment we'll go through  ♫
♫  Shining you  ♫
♫  Shining you, like a starlight  ♫
♫  When I look at it, follow it, it's always shining  ♫
♫  You stay deep in my heart  ♫
I was the worst yesterday.
Husband!
What luck? He definitely remembers everything.
I think I was pathetic just now.
You can keep your promise to break up with Ju Won, right?
This is how she looks at my son?
Want to hang out with me tomorrow?
What?
Let's laugh a lot and hang out.
I want to spend one last day with you.
Can't we?
♫  Fading you, like a fog  ♫
♫  If I try to reach you, catch you, you might just disappear  ♫
♫  I just let the color wash over me like this  ♫
♫  Every breath, every word  ♫
♫  Hold on tight, the lonely struggle  ♫
♫  Always by your side  ♫
♫  Time is treasuring us  ♫
♫  You know, right?  ♫
♫  Shining you  ♫
♫  Shining you, like a starlight  ♫
♫  When I look at it, follow it, it's shining on you  ♫
♫  You stay deep in my heart  ♫
♫  Looking at you makes it true  ♫
♫  Every moment we'll go through  ♫
♫  Shining you  ♫
♫  Shining you, like a starlight  ♫
♫  When I look at it, follow it, it's shining on you  ♫
♫  You stay deep in my heart  ♫