My Girlfriend is an Alien
Jiang Jinghuai, welcome to the Demon World.
You are destined to be chosen by my Demon King.
Come on.
The secret path of the Demon King is at the bottom of the cold ice of the Cloud.
Jiang Jinghuai, where are you?
Jiang Jinghuai, I know you don't want to forget Jiang Zhiyu.
Then take me down.
I will help you mend your broken love.
But you will be taken into the Demon Realm by the Demon King.
Are you willing?
I am willing.
Are you really willing?
The Demon King is here.
I will help you mend your broken love.
Jiang Jinghuai!
Daughter.
hes is mulher of Head Funeral.
ufén率,
Android convenz en en
探是國字
What are you afraid of
for him to guess your fate?
Ah Yun.
Wait for me.
I'll definitely come back to save you.
First bow to the Heaven of Heaven.
Second bow to the Cloud Lord.
Second bow to the Heaven of Heaven.
Husband and wife hold hands.
Why?
Not happy?
Second bow to the Heaven of Heaven.
She is my woman.
This bow
must be due to my Jiang Jinghuai.
Jiang Jinghuai,
you are not dead yet.
But she is only one bow away
to become my husband's wife.
I am so happy.
Let's go.
But for the rest of my life
Every transmission There is another sky
I will dream every dream
For the rest of my life
I can't help but dream
for how long
she loves me
My love wrapped around my arms
This ancient item
She chopped my heart into small pieces
Something artificial
was left only for you
For everyone
Drop into the snow
Don't Let me down
Do it
His Excellency
You...
You're from the demon clan?
Don't you recognize me?
Don't I recognize you?
LAUGHTER
Sister
Who on earth is he?
Brother
His memory has been erased
by Nangong seperti
I got some Exp wagon,
save odd palaces,
and
Sword Holding Messiah
Brother.
Although you obtained Satan's spirit Stone,
it's hard for you to sub bible 약간,
it's not the best way
for you to holy sword by practicing.
I have my own plan.
Don't worry about me.
Brother.
I'm sorry.
Now Jiang Zhiyu has lost his memory.
Why didn't you take this opportunity
to cut it off?
I still remember
when I was practicing in the Demon Realm,
I had to endure the pain of being hurt by the blood of Wan Qian.
Every time I felt painful,
Ayu would appear by my side
and accompany me.
I'm sorry.
Ah Hui, are you all right?
Do you know
it's worth it to be in the Demon Realm for me?
For you,
it doesn't matter if I die or not.
I only live for three words in my life.
Jiang Zhiyu.
Ah Hui, I'm worried about you.
Don't worry about me.
Look.
I'm fine now.
I promised you
to spend every day with you.
I'll help myself first.
All right.
That's enough.
Otherwise, I'll feel painful again.
And I know
this blood of my real master
canoks in his own hand.
But I don't want to live a life
like my real master against a demon.
I don't want to see any slander
against this murderous studio.
I'll take you back
to save my line of work.
Understood.
I won't let A Yan
steal away my coat
and hid in Five Dragon Hall.
to protect her for a while.
It's not easy for me to walk with her all the way.
So I really hope
you can bless us.
But
Jiang Zhiyu has lost his memory now.
What are you going to do?
He has the heart to survive in the Forbidden Land.
I'll take him to find it.
The Forbidden Land
I didn't expect Jiang Jinghuai
to get all the divine power of the Demons.
Now he has added more power
to make us so weak.
Master,
what should we do next?
Maybe someone can help me.
I'll use their
deep-seated weakness
to let them know that
love can melt the honey and sugar
and be faster than the knife.
Sooner or later,
I'll guide this
The clouds and birds know how to get up
It has nothing to do with avoiding it
The vast sky continues to look for you
Where will you be
The flower is a path that the wind has to walk
I continue to follow the path and don't talk about the maze
If you go back to the sky
I can only put it in your heart
You and I look at the Milky Way
Want to be so close
If I have a gorgeous shadow in my life
The power of love that is empty
But the yin and yang can't reach
Waiting for your memory to recall