YoYo English Channel YouTube
Madam,
I said you were my life.
Now you look like this.
I feel so sorry for you.
You don't have to be so cruel.
You kept me.
You just want my spiritual stone.
Why are you so humiliating?
It's good that you know.
The Li people have fallen into the cold ice lake.
They have long been dead.
You are so vicious.
You are not worthy of being threatened.
I said,
You are my life.
You will leave me even if you die.
Don't think about the Li people.
His name is Jiang Jinghuan.
You can't even beat him with a finger.
If the Li people had not fallen into the cold ice lake,
You and I would have been husband and wife.
Even if you get my life,
You can't get my heart.
I will see what you can do.
You can marry,
Become the master of the sky,
Accept the status of the Li people and the sky,
It's your highest honor.
Honor?
But,
It's your duty to the Lingxiao clan.
It's my duty.
Then I will let you see
What is the pain of love without a break.
What are you going to do?
From now on,
I will not let you go.
I will be the only one in your heart.
No.
I, Jiang Jinghuan, swear,
I will marry you.
I will love Jiang Zhiyu forever.
I want to marry you.
Do you agree?
I agree.
No.
Today is our wedding.
This is the rule of our Li people.
Jiang Zhi Yu,
I like you.
I don't want my sister.
I like her.
I want to marry her.
The first night is the city of the moon.
The night wind blows the west of the mountain.
The moon is in the east.
I will spend the rest of my life with you.
I will be with you forever.
No.
Have you forgotten?
I will marry you.
I will love you.
Jiang Zhi Yu,
Jiang Jinghuan,
I have a gift for you.
I am very happy.
Jiang Jinghuan.
Father.
Madam.
Let us
have our wedding on that day.
Sister.
I am sorry.
I have hurt you.
I shouldn't have brought you out.
Your soul has been taken away.
I am also worried.
You should care more about your own safety.
Sister.
You must hate me now.
I am sorry.
Goddess won't hate you.
You worked hard for the Goddess.
But you were used by Nangong Xiao.
This is not your fault.
You shouldn't have suffered.
Sister has not yet trained to destroy the spirit world.
The spirit world has not been awakened.
She has been enduring the evil spirit of Nangong Xiao.
Just for
protecting the three realms.
You should live for yourself.
Thank you,
Yanluo.
Jiang Zhiyu's love has been removed.
He only thinks of me as his husband.
Li Nu fell into the bottom of the lake.
Goddess broke the love.
They will never be together.
You are so clever.
The Heavenly Emperor has agreed to my wedding with the Goddess.
Who said that the spirit world and the three realms
will be separated?
I am not a human.
I am a human.
You said that the spirit world and the three realms
will not be separated.
I, Nangong Xiao,
want everything.
Ying.
Sister.
Are you okay?
I...
I am fine.
But, Ying,
I always feel
that I have forgotten something important.
What is it?
You haven't forgotten anything.
Everything is fine now.
Isn't it?
You are going to get married.
Since I was a child,
I always thought
that you were the best person in the three realms.
I will always laugh at you.
You will be beautiful that day.
Right?
Sister.
No matter what,
I hope you will always be happy.
You are happy.
I am happy.
You are sad.
I am sad.
Ying.
What's wrong with you?
I am fine.
I am happy.
I won't cry.
Shouldn't you feel happy for me?
I am fine.