YoYo English Channel YouTube
Let's go.
Ayu, don't worry.
We'll go find the Demon Clan Spirit Stone now.
Madam.
Sister.
You let me find it.
Honorable God.
Luo Ying is an official this time.
You have to reward her well.
Sister, I didn't.
Nangong Xiao.
You threatened Luo Ying to lure out the Golden Butterfly
and seduced me to show up.
You are despicable.
Don't worry.
I will never treat those who follow me well.
But those who betray me,
I will never let go.
Give me the Spirit Stone.
Sister.
Huai.
How dare you?
You deceived the Goddess,
stole the Spirit Stone,
betrayed the Demon Clan,
and betrayed the Cloud.
She didn't.
I've already verified
the rules of the Cloud.
Even if I have to
miss the meeting today,
I will be punished.
Don't come for this woman.
Come for me.
Honorable God.
Li Ren is so arrogant.
She should be executed immediately.
But...
No.
It has nothing to do with Huai.
It's me.
I'm willing to do it.
Nonsense.
You were clearly
seduced by Li Ren.
You are the Goddess of the Cloud Clan.
You are Nangong Xiao's wife.
She is my woman.
Goddess.
Did you hear that?
Who are you?
I only love Zhang Jinghuai.
Honorable God.
Li Ren
wants to steal the Goddess from you.
You are all heartless.
I'd rather die than be separated from you.
Honorable God.
They are really in love.
Really?
What do you think we should do?
Why don't we
torture this Li Ren
who has been lost for thousands of years
and let him enjoy
the grace of the Honorable God?
As for the Goddess,
let the ice knife cut off the love thread.
Let the knife cut the love thread.
Then she will be
the Goddess of the Cloud Clan forever.
Okay.
What is the ice knife?
You can't bear it.
Anhui, go.
I'll do anything
for you.
A love-sucking case.
A painful yearning.
No.
I want you to be in the ice of this valley
and watch the one you love
fall in love with you.
Anhui.
Love thread for hundreds of years
will be cut off with a knife.
Anhui.
She will love you.
But you will
forget her name forever.
Her appearance
will be forgotten.
Her appearance.
No.
Brother.
Anhui.
You are not worthy.
Anhui, wake up.
Anhui.
I'll save you.
Anhui, wake up.
Anhui.
Kill me.
Brother.
Anhui.
It's not easy to
love someone.
The wind blows away the gray mark.
Suddenly the rain falls on itself.
The clouds and birds know how to get up.
No light deliberately escapes.
The vast sky continues to look for you.
Where will you be?
The wind blows away the gray mark.
I continue to look for the path.
If I can return to the sky
with your breath,
I can only put it in your dream.
You and I look at the Milky Way.
We are like the mirror.
If only I could have the beautiful meaning of life.
The sky is full of the power of human love.
The Milky Way is endless.
I wait for your memory in silence.