The Love by Hypnotic
Episode 16
Your Excellency, you are in charge of the three realms,
and you are doing your best to escape from the heaven.
I have been waiting for a long time.
The Love by Hypnotic
Your Excellency, you don't have to be polite.
We have something to say.
I heard that you are looking for someone.
That person is also with you.
Why do you have to bother?
You will become a mortal when you enter the reincarnation.
You will die and go to heaven.
I have to remind you that
you are not a mortal.
Then what do you need to exchange?
I am willing to give you my heart.
Good.
That mortal has been in the human world for 20 years.
I didn't expect that the new demon lord
is actually a love-hate relationship.
You will regret it.
The Love by Hypnotic
Your Excellency,
the spy reported that
Jiang Zhiyu was erased from his memory and entered the reincarnation.
Jiang Jinghuai found his news.
I'm afraid I will go to the human world to find him.
Good.
As long as you can exchange the memories of Jiang Zhiyu and hatred,
they will kill each other.
Ayu,
are you willing to marry me?
I will love you until I die.
You are just a substitute in the human world.
Even if you have the same face as me,
you don't deserve to marry her.
I don't want to marry her.
Even if you have the same face as me,
you don't deserve to marry her.
Ayu,
don't forget.
No matter where you are,
you and I will live forever.
The auspicious time has come.
Who am I?
My husband,
A'Jiu.
A'Jiu,
you are my husband.
Ayu,
let's forget hatred
and forget worries.
It's good to be a normal couple.
Husband,
can you love me?
Don't be afraid.
He is not your husband.
He is fake.
Two people you and me knew each other at first sight!
Why are you in my dream?
Telling my husband that he is fake!
Who are you?
The evil spirit kills your husband
Cashns him to Advisor
Your husband is in the Sakata cliche feels
I求我, 你去救他
I did not expect
that all that money
has gone to waste
The watched values
in such a human body
that veya
my husband
排 completely
Seel
Well
You're so stupid.
A Jiu is pure and kind.
Now,
how about the evil thing that wants to marry you?
A Jiu.
Where did you get this?
I got it from the temple.
It's said that if you take this sword home,
you can remove the evil and avoid evil.
I'll take it.
Why?
I'll take it to the evil.
Don't let anything in the temple go to hell.
Don't forget that we'll get married tomorrow.
A Jiu, tomorrow is the 72nd day of the lunar month.
They said that the wedding day was not in time.
Can we...
I lost.
Tomorrow,
you'll be my wife.
He is future baritone favor,
not future baritone favor.
Go and tell him to come back tomorrow to talk to me.
Where is that asked?
If he wasn't my husband,
who would he be?
Are you a jilted woman?
The scar on her chest
must be the hole
where you sewed her skin.
Don't touch it.
If you don't believe me,
stick this hairpin
into her chest.
Your husband will be alive.
I don't dare.
I can't stick it out.
She's here.
The wind blows away the traces of gray.
Suddenly the rain falls on her.
The clouds and birds know how to get up.
It doesn't matter if you're avoiding it.
The vast sky continues to look for you.
Where will you be?
The wind blows away the traces of gray.
I continue to protect the trace.
Don't talk about the distance.
If you're lonely,
go back to the sky.
I'm willing to put it in your heart.
You and I look at the Milky Way.
We look at the Milky Way.
We're so close.
If I can only hear the sound of rain.
I'm afraid to fall for the power of love.
The Milky Way is endless.
I'm waiting for your memory.