All right, Your Highness.
Get out.
The scroll of the treasure map is in Song Chen's hand.
This is his route back to the house after the blessing.
This is where we set up camp.
If we catch him
then we can get what we want.
Even if the whole world
we can get it too.
The Emperor is very ill.
The temple fair of Xi this year
calls His Highness to bless the country.
According to the tip.
The White Bird Society will try to
ambush the road back to the city.
and take His Highness.
just to find the treasure map.
At the temple fair,
you can take Song Chen after the prayer.
I'm going back the same way he came.
Let's just tell Your Highness to cancel the blessing.
No, this is Song Chen's chance to win people's hearts.
Don't worry about me.
She raised me up anyway.
And we still have some connections.
Yes.
Please don't let Yue know.
Wan Xingzhu's death has made her pained.
I can't relieve her
and can't make her more worried.
How could it be you, Song Chen.
Your Highness has been summoned.
He drove me back in his car.
I doubt it.
Perhaps he did it intentionally
and instructed you to take the blame.
Nevertheless,
And I am prepared to.
And I have no grievances.
Individuals like him.
Regardless of your importance to him
depend on their leverage.
I would like to witness both the world and you.
which path he would choose.
If I am arrested, please inform Ye Guangmao
and let Ye fight with the chairman.
Just let them fight.
You, Madam Flower.
You went behind my back and arrested Li Yunzhi
and you want to hide the treasure map.
No way.
Where are they?
They're in the fox's cave outside of town.
Let's go.
OK.
You must be disappointed.
You really are Song Yan's child.
He doesn't take any chances.
Not to mention dying to save you.
If that's what makes you happy.
You can feel that way.
What's the point of being tough
I was merely stating the facts.
Madam Flower, get out of here!
It's Ye Guangmao.
Open the door.
In Song Chen's eyes.
You're just tools of his power.
Madam Flower.
Choose between love and revenge.
I think you know what you're doing.
If you figure it out
then I'll kill Ye Guangmao.
Madam Flower, where are you hiding?
Get out!
Is your future more important
than the birth of your child.
If it doesn't give you two
a good future.
She was born
just to suffer.
Besides, it's a royal order.
For the future of the Ye family and my daughter
I have to go.
Let him stay with you both for me.
Ye Guangmao.
I know it now.
Why the first time I saw you
that I had a special feeling.
Because you killed so many of us, Li's.
And because I'm going to kill you today.
to tell me the whole truth about the Lee family.
I can tell you the truth.
But I have a request.
If I could just take a look at the birthmark on your back.
No.
Now.
We're even.
Ye Guangmao.
Guess what?
You will die at the hands of your own daughter.
What.
We're not even.
And you can't start over.
You just killed your own father with your own hands.
There's nothing I love more than
watching relatives kill each other.
What.
You hate me.
You might as well hate where you came from.
Ye Guangmao caused the Li family's extermination.
Why should he have a whole family
a beautiful wife
and a lovely kid.
He doesn't deserve it.
What?
I was the one
who secretly forged the exact birthmark.
Who are you?
What are you going to do?
Just remember, it's because of Ye Wan.
The Ye family owes the Li family.
Don't touch my baby.
Ye Guangmao's child has birthmarks.
But the miss's child did not.
Candles.
Right.
I made a birthmark on the lady's baby.
Ye Guangmao.
Your baby is mine.