The next one in danger
is Ding Chaozhong, right?
I'd like to see
who's hiding in the dark.
Who's there!
Stop!
Yun Wei!
Oh no, he was lured out.
Censor Ding.
Be quiet. He's in danger.
It's The White Bird Society.
You finally woke up.
I'm fine.
Your Highness, please leave.
No.
I'll be here with you.
Your Highness.
I'm just a female official.
We have different statuses.
Your Highness, please go.
I could have reached out and touched him.
But I can't.
No!
Old man.
You can't do it as well.
Your Highness.
The death of these officials on the list
has caused panic.
Should we try to ease the public?
No matter how many times you throw it,
the result would remain the same.
Give it to me.
Give it to me!
I don't believe it.
Heaven has sent her to me for many times.
Heaven just like to tease people.
One more time.
I'll try one more time.
No!
Yun Wei.
You know what,
she tried to protect me so hard.
The moment when she fell into my arms,
the only thought occurred to me was that
I don't want anything,
anything!
As long as she's alright,
I really can give up everything.
Why are you always here with me?
I'm your husband.
Who else could I be with?
Instead of keeping an eye on me,
you'd better persuade your father.
As long as he can give up,
maybe I can beg mercy for him
and spare him.
OK.
Why are you still following me?
Just going the same way.
I'm going to get dressed.
I.
Does it look good on me?
Yes.
Not at all.
We'll take it. Keep the change.
That's pretty.
Can you stop
following me?
I just happened to go the same way with you.
I'll go back to my home.
OK, I'll go with you.
My father doesn't want to see you.
I'll wait outside the door.
Yue.
I'm here waiting for you.
I heard that
you've been hanging out with Wan Xingzhu for days.
The progress is slow.
Maybe it's like others said
that no matter how strong you are,
you also have weaknesses of women.
You're stuck with
love.
No, I won't.
Go on lying to me.
But you can't lie to your heart.
Just ask yourself
if you have to kill Wan Xingzhu now,
can you do that?
Father.
To take down Wan Zhuo,
we don't need to kill them all.
Naive! If we spare them,
they'll become hidden hazards.
Aren't you afraid that Wan Xingzhu will
come back to take revenge on our family!
Actually, that's not the biggest concern.
What matters is that
if he really wants to
rebel against Family Song,
he would bring disaster to all the people.
Since our family came down,
you've been the only adult who is brave and astute
and could be counted on.
You can't let me down, daughter.
Father,
I won't let you down.
In front of your mother and ancestors,
say that again.
Mother,
I won't let you and father down.
Daughter,
you probably don't know that
the list you took was false.
You fell into Wan Zhuo's trap.
Li Yunzhi was also badly hurt because of it.