Hey, Kim Jung Pal.
You should have bought a poster too.
It's fine. It's enough to have
listened with my own ears.
Hurry up! It's a long walk
to the bus station.
I'm coming!
Deok Sun!
Oh my... Ho Young! It's been so long!
I know. Hey, why did you get so pretty?
Hey... that's not true!
What are you saying?
I tried to get in touch with you a few
times after we graduated middle school.
I know.
Your home phone number
hasn't changed, right?
Is it ok if I call you?
Hey, Ho Young, what are you doing?
Yeah. Coming!
-Deok Sun, I'll be going then, ok?
-Ok. Bye!
-I'll call you!
-Ok!
Hey, you know him, right?
No.
If you attended Banghak Middle School
and didn't know him, you were a spy.
He totally had the hots for me!
And he wrote me tons of love letters!
I was incredibly pretty, after all...
Then who's the person I knew
back in middle school? A ghost?
Who do you think you're lying to?
Stop spouting nonsense and stay here.
I have to use the bathroom.
Who was that chick?
My first love. Isn't she pretty?
Well, she isn't what I'd call pretty...
She's not exactly pretty,
but she's so cute, right?
I was crazy about her
back in middle school.
She's as cute as ever.
You sure have strange taste in women!
-Darn it!
-I'm sorry.
Darn it! Geez!
That jerk must be out of his mind!
Darn it!
Geez.
How do you not have a gram
of caution in you?
Where is there even a spot where you
could sprain your ankle around here?
Where? Huh? Show me!
Geez, you couldn't
even sit still for a second.
Hey. You think I sprained my ankle
because I wanted to?
It happened on my way to the bathroom!
Ow,Jung Pal, I don't think I can
even take a single step, what do I do?
Seriously...
Hey, hey, hey.
-Be careful!
-Ok!
You have to put more pressure
on this side! What are you even.
Ok.
You're killing me here. Seriously.
What are you laughing about?
You did nothing right.
Fine.
You have to put pressure here.
Are you stupid?
-Like this?
-Yeah!
Ok.
-Are you enjoying this?
-No.
It's really late, right?
Shouldn't we call home?
Yeah. I'll go make a call.
Ok. Hurry back.
Juicy fresh!
Fresh mint!
You're not going to sleep, Noona?
I'm a senior now. I'm going to study.
Then turn the TV off.
No Eul. Who's prettier,
Me or Chae Si Ra?
Noona. Who's more handsome,
Me or Tom Cruise?
To me, it's you!
To me, it's Chae Si Ra!
Jin Joo, want to sleep
in my room tonight?
No, she can't, sir. Jin Joo
is reading a book right now.
What book? She can't even read.
Jin Joo. I'll read that for you.
Let's sleep in my room.
So you're going with your older brother?
Good night, Mom.
Hmmph!
Hmmphity-hmmph!
Episode 13: Superman Returns
February, 1989
Seoul, Dobong-gu, Ssangmundong
Teacher, I mean, Father.
It's 7:20 a.m...
...time for Scholarly Quiz.
I will be going back inside now.
All right. Scholarly Quiz
is a great TV program.
Every student should watch it.
-Proceed to enter the house!
-Yes, sir!
Deok Sun.
-Soo Yeon.
All right, already.
Soo Yeon. Soo Yeon.
I have a wish, you see...
What is it, Dad? Tell me.
I'll grant any wish you have.
You competing on that show,
Scholarly Quiz.
I don't even expect you to win
first place on the show.
I don't care if you get
everything wrong...
...but I just want to
see you on the show.
Sorry, Dad.
Why's that, my child?
I don't think I'll be able to
grant you that wish.
Yeah, I thought as much.
Your honesty is very good!
Bo Ra. Don't be like that
and help Soo Yeon study.
She's a senior now.
No! I'm going to study
inside the room from now on.
So, you go to the library to study.
There's construction going on
at the library today.
Why don't you go to
Taek's place to study?
Taek is busy! I can't disturb him.
That's right. Next week is the finals
of the Fujitsu Tournament, right?
-Yeah.
-Wow.
If our Taek wins this, he'll have
achieved the Grand Slam, right?
So don't bother him, or disturb him,
or even go anywhere near him.
I know it better than you do.
So don't worry.
Wait a minute.
There's something else, right?
Sun Woo! Bring this over to Taek's.
What is it?
Oh, I'ved seasoned some seaweed.
I heard it's good for
high blood pressure.
Bring it to Taek's dad.
Ok. I will.
Mister!
What are you doing here?
Studying.
This house is the quietest place
in this neighborhood.
What about you, being here
so early in the morning?
-Oh.
-You're here, Sun Woo?
Oh,yes.
My mom wanted you to have this.
Oh. Thanks.
Sun Woo, about your plumbing...
Our plumbing?
At our house?
Yeah. Tell your mom to just leave it.
I'll go over there later and fix it.
Ok. I understand.
Soo Yeon, you haven't had
breakfast yet, right?
I did, but I can eat again.
Oh, don't go to Taek's room.
Entry is forbidden until Saturday.
Oh, I know.
Fujitsu finals. Bye.
Goodbye, mister.
Ok.
Thank you for the meal!
Mister.
Did Taek eat dinner last night?
No. He won't eat
breakfast today either.
Can you go get him?
I don't think I can provoke him
during competition time either.
I feel like, if I did,
he'd keel over and die.
-Taek!
-Be quiet!
Not this week.
Go play somewhere else.
Why, does he have
a competition coming up?
Futsuji.
It's Fujitsu.
Ah. Hurry up and piss off already.
Soo Yeon.
I'll just quietly play Blue Marble.
I'll be really, really quiet.
And the dean's at home.
It's just all around complicated.
So,just don't tell me to go home.
-Then, I'll be going--
-You can't. No matter what.
I can trust you, but not your
blabbering mouth. Piss off.
Fine. I'll go home. I'm going home!
Home!
Fine, fine. What a cruel world
we live in, seriously.
I'll play Blue Marble with the dean!
With the dean!
Yeah. Come in.
How did you know it was me?
My dad usually calls me and you knock.
Oh.
Come out. Let's eat breakfast.
It's ok. I'll just have coffee.
What about lunch?
What about dinner?
Should our Taek at least eat
breakfast then, or not?
I should eat.
Right? What a good boy. Let's go.
If you eat breakfast, I won't
bother you about lunch or dinner.
Ok. Thanks.
Geez...
I've never even taken my kids
to Nature's Farm.
Geez.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm Sung Dong Il, of the Hanil Bank
Fraud Department!
Want to try on some "silver bracelets"
with these shenanigans you're pulling?
Just let me go this once, please?
Hey this person. There's no such thing
as cheating in Baduk.
Don't you even feel sorry to Taek?
Baduk is a game that is to be played
with the utmost fairness.
Speaking of which, it's so quiet on
Sunday. Did everyone go somewhere?
The kids' mom is chatting out front
about the pollock bought yesterday.
And Jung Hwan is
studying in his room...
Oh, speaking of which,
Jung Bong hasn't left his desk today.
Bo Ra's dad. I guess my eldest son
is finally coming to his senses!
Luck will befall anyone
who has received this letter.
It may be difficult,
but consider this a great opportunity.
I wish you seven years of good luck.
Sung Soo Yeon
-Wow, look at those!
-They look great!
-So fresh!
-They look amazing!
No, no! You should have more
for yourself!
You don't need to be
giving us all of these...
It's not like the pollock
even cost that much.
Make a soup of them to have tonight.
Ok!
It'd be so great to have this
with a bit of soju.
That would be great!
You don't need to
say that again, for sure!
Shall we all have a drink later?
The kids are home today.
How about tomorrow,
after the kids are at school?
Sure.
-I don't need any more!
-Wow, they look delicious!
The men are so quiet.
Do you think they're drinking,
by any chance?
Just one sip.
Bo Ra's dad! Let's just have one sip!
I told you, let's just have soju!
Let's try a bit of
your wild ginseng liquor!
It'll go to waste
if you don't drink it!
Spouting some kind of
"Deok Sun winning...
...first place at Scholarly Quiz"
type of nonsense.
That wild ginseng liquor
is as precious as my own life!
I made it so that I can have it
on Bo Ra's wedding day!
Just a sip. Please?
Oh my, look at that.
Just what kind of
world are we living in?
How is it that robbers are breaking
into houses in broad daylight?
Geez... really.
It's a thief!
-Thieves just break in, like that!
-It's a thief!
It's a thief!
-Omo!
-What do we do? Thief!
Thief? Where? Where?
-Over there!
-Where?
He's gone!
Honey, are you ok?
Oh, I'm fine.
I can't believe it, a thief!
-Where? Where? Where?
-Hey!
Thief! Thief! Thief! Thief!
-Oh my God!
-Thief!
Where? Where?
Did you catch him, Dad?
Huh?
Where?
I don't know.
I think they got away.
Wasn't that the voice of the man
who owns the ice store?
What's this,
a thief in broad daylight?
He ran away via the roof!
I saw his backside!
-Really? -Yes! He looked
like he was flying away!
This jerk,
just wait until I catch him.
But, um, nobody is hurt, right?
-Yes.
Who's missing? Huh?
Um, Section Chief Jo.
Your mother is at a seminar, boy!
Oh! Where's Bonghwangdang
father and son? Where are those two?
Taek is practicing Baduk.
I bet he doesn't even care
about this whole thing.
All right, that's that for him, then.
What about Taek's dad? His father?
Sun Woo's mom,
your plumbing is all fixed now.
Taek's dad! There's a thief
on the loose in our neighborhood!
Yeah. I know. I heard.
But, why are you all outside?
It's so cold today.
Wow. I bet he'd be that calm
even if a crazy hog were chasing him.
He's like a bear.
Should I pour some hot water on him,
to see if he reacts to it?
Don't bother!
It's just a waste of water.
Let me know if
anything else needs fixing.
I'll do it for you. Well, then.
-Mother, I'll be going inside now.
-Ok.
I'll be going inside too.
Wow. He's no human.
Next time, I'll try having a dog
on the loose behind Bonghwangdang.
He's human after all, so he should
be a bit scared of that, right?
Geez, they're all in such a rush.
Are they the wind within the mist?
Come on baby.
Jin Joo. Jin Joo.
Go to Jung Bong oppa. It's time
for him to be having ramen.
-Ramen?
-Yeah!
Sun Woo.
What is it?
So seriously, how is it?
Huh? What is?
You know, Taek's dad.
You really haven't thought about
getting hitched?
What?
Yeah. I wish you two
would get together already.
Geez, why are you two
acting like this, again?
Stop saying such nonsense!
How is it nonsense? Both of your kids
are pretty much all grown.
It'd be great if you could spend the
rest of your lives with each other.
Yeah, it's not like
you two are strangers, either.
And you two have both
been through a lot.
Wouldn't it be great if you two
depended on each other?
I think that he does have
some feelings toward you.
Geez, you two must
be out of your minds.
I already feel
uncomfortable as it is...
...because I'm afraid the
neighbors will see it that way.
What for?
Yeah! Why trouble yourself
over something like that?
Geez, you two have
no idea what it's like.
I was afraid of this, which is why
I purposely avoided him before.
Because I was afraid that people
would misunderstand, like this.
This time around, I took care of him
a bit because he was ill...
...but look at what's happened.
People are talking again.
We really don't have
that type of relationship.
Don't just dismiss it like that
and just give it some thought.
Taek's dad is a great guy.
Geez, just before, you were saying
that he's like a bear!
He is, but he's a rich bear.
And he's good to you.
Yeah, Sun Young. Jin Joo will
start attending school soon too.
Wouldn't it be better for you
to raise her with someone else?
Geez, never mind that!
Sheesh. I don't want to hurt Sun Woo.
I will never ever remarry,
even if for Sun Woo's sake.
Also, of course Taek's dad
is a great person.
Even back in Gimhae, he was well-known
for being a good and kind person.
That's why I want to do at least
one more good thing for him.
If you two keep talking like this...
...I won't ever set foot
in their house again!
All right, already! Geez.
But even so, I'm a bit disappointed.
But Sun Young.
What about your own life?
I mean, your kids are important, yes.
You can ignore me,
saying that I'm just blabbing on...
...because I don't
understand your situation...
...but you only live once, too.
Ok?
Isn't that right?
You should live happily just once too.
I'm just saying this because
it's such a waste of your young age.
You're too young.
You're too young to pour everything
you have into your kids alone.
And a waste of your youth.
Geez, that's enough.
My kids being happy...
Wow, these garlic are stinging
my eyes like crazy!
...is my happiness.
That's enough for me.
That's enough.
Sheesh.
Sun Young.
The bear's here.
Oh, you're here, oppa?
Oh, you're all here.
-Yes.
Would you like some garlic?
Sun Woo's mom, you're coming with me
to the hospital tomorrow, right?
Yes, of course!
Of course I should come!
Um, it's Taek's dad's first checkup
since he was discharged...
...and he needs to get a prescription,
and get a lot of exams!
And it said on the notice that
someone has to come with him.
And I decided to come as this
neighborhood's representative right?
I mean, of course
I should be the one to go!
I'm the youngest of us all, after all!
As the oldest, you want to go instead?
-I don't think he'd like that.
-Oh, well, I should go, then.
Do you hate mister?
No, I like him. I like him, but...
...I don't like him being
too close to my mom.
Hey. Everyone is about that close
in our neighborhood!
It's not like it's just
the two of them.
Even so, I don't like it.
Don't concern yourself too much about it.
It's not like he said that he wants
to marry your mom right away.
Also,I thought it was nice to see the
two of them depending on each other.
Well, figures. Yeah. I can see
where you're coming from.
I understand how you feel.
I think I'd feel the same way.
What?
At times like these,
you really seem like an adult.
You have a death wish?
I'm not even scared
of your threats anymore.
Want to see each other
for a bit tomorrow?
I'll go to the front of your school
around dinnertime.
You just used informal speech
with me, punk?
Everyone else does it!
You can't, no matter what!
I'll meet you in front of the train
station in front of my school.
Yes, noonim.
=Noonim is the formal version of noona=
Are you mad at me?
Yes.
You sure have a lot of things
to get mad about.
When other people's boyfriends
get mad...
...the girlfriend tries to make them
feel better and kisses them... ow!
Ow, noona!
You're going to the hospital tomorrow,
right, Bo Ra's mom? What time?
Early tomorrow morning.
Why? Are you sick?
No. Bo Ra's dad's bank is
giving them a free physical.
Wow, what a great workplace!
They do that for you?
Not really.
What's so great about a workplace
that pays so little?
We only got it because he's
been working for them for 25 years.
He worked so hard for 25 years
and they merely give him that.
But it's still nice that
he has a decent job.
It's your first time getting
a full physical, right?
Yes. It's my first time.
But,what if there's something
that turns out to be bad?
Geez, why are you worrying
about such useless things?
To tell you the truth...
...I think I have a lump
under my left breast.
Since when?
It's been a while.
What if it's cancer?
-Stop saying such useless things!
-Missus!
Your words will sprout into reality!
Stop saying such things!
There's tons of people
who have lumpiness in their breasts.
It's probably just cyst. Don't worry.
But, are you going
to the hospital alone tomorrow?
Even the bear living next door
is going with his girlfriend.
Geez, really!
Sorry. It was a joke.
Don't you dare say that
where Sun Woo will hear.
-He'll pass out in shock.
-I won't, I won't!
If it's scary to go to the
hospital alone, I'll go with you.
It's ok. Bo Ra's dad is taking
the day off to come with me tomorrow.
I'm such a scaredy-cat, you see.
That's good.
Despite everything, it feels nice
to have your husband...
...by your side at
times like these.
Even if you feel like wanting to kill
them sometimes.
Geez, you, go to sleep already.
It'll be hard on you to get
all those exams tomorrow.
If, by any chance, there's
something wrong.
What could possibly be wrong?
Stop worrying about such
useless things for no reason.
Hurry up and go to sleep.
If, by any chance,
there's something wrong.
Tell me everything.
Don't hide it from me.
Geez, all right, already.
Now stop it and go to sleep.
-Ok! We understand!
-Yes!
Huh?
The electricity went out, right?
Yes, it seems like it.
Call your dad and
ask him to come home.
-Wow!
This is why you need
a man around the house.
What, is there anything else
that needs fixing?
All you did was switch a fuse.
I could do that too.
Even though it seems easy...
...it's a lot more intricate
and complex than it seems!
It's because it's me
that it was able to be fixed.
Is there something
troubling you, honey?
Not me.
Bo Ra's mom is getting
a physical exam today.
She'll be fine, right honey?
Of course.
She can't not be fine.
She'll be fine, no matter what.
Ok?
Don't you worry one...
...bit!
That's enough, already!
I feel cruddy enough as it is.
I thought that was a good one.
So there's nothing
certain as of yet...
...but we have to do
a biopsy to make sure?
Yes. There's a point of
concern on the x-ray...
...so we have to do a biopsy
to be sure of anything.
Then, will you be doing
the biopsy right away?
Yes. We'll be doing local anesthesia
and then be carrying out the exam.
You'll be able to be
discharged in the evening.
Um, Doctor. Could it possibly
be cancer?
Geez, what do you mean, cancer?
Stop saying things like that!
It's only natural for you
to be going through a biopsy.
Don't you worry about a thing.
Just trust me.
We don't know anything yet.
We'll need the results of the biopsy
to know whether or not it's malignant.
Don't worry too much, and
please prepare for the biopsy.
Ms. Lee Il Hwa? Please come out.
We have to get you changed.
Ok.
Yeah. Hurry and get ready.
Um, Doctor.
What are the chances
that it could be something bad?
It's probably not cancer, right?
Um, to be honest, the shape doesn't
look good, so I'm a bit worried.
I'm a bit worried,
but nothing's certain as of now.
We'll only know for sure when
the results of the biopsy come out.
I can't give you any definite
answers right now.
Yes, I see. Thank you, Doctor.
Please take care of her.
Ssangmun Girls' High
Yes!
Why not mix everything together?
-Yeah!
Hey, what about the red pepper paste?
-Is this enough?
-Stop putting it in, darn it!
-There we go!
-Looks delicious!
It seems a bit lacking
since Man Ok isn't here.
Our poor Mi Ok.
I'll bet she's so bored.
She couldn't even move for two weeks.
Is it really ok for us
to not visit her?
She said not to come
no matter what.
She says her dad is really scary.
I saw him on the street a bit one time.
He really does look scary.
But, what kind of work does he do?
You don't know either, right?
Yeah. I don't think Man Ok likes
talking about it...
...so I didn't bring it up.
Soo Yeon. Do you think,
by any chance...
...that he could be a thug,
um, Mr. Thug?
Or maybe, a mobster?
Maybe that's why she told us
not to come to the hospital?
Maybe?
Geez, no way!
She goes traveling with him often
and eats out with him every day.
No way.
-Right?
-Yeah.
No way.
He looks really scary, though.
Really?
Don't move. You'll hurt
yourself again.
Just endure it for one more week.
Dad, hurry up and leave.
It's already nighttime.
You have to go open up your store.
Hey, Bo Ra. Let's go get dinner together.
I already have plans.
Have fun, you two.
Hey. You got a boyfriend, didn't you?
Hey, Sung Bo Ra!
Judging from the fact you're
smiling, you really did get one, huh?
You're quite skilled, Sung Bo Ra!
When did you have the time to date?
I know, right? I'm shocked at myself.
Who is it? An upperclassman?
Someone in our year?
You guys don't need to know.
Come on, who is it?
Noona!
Who's that kid?
Hello.
-Oh, hey.
-Hi.
But, who are you?
-He's my younger brother.
-Younger brother?
I know what he looks like,
and he doesn't look this young.
Student. What's your relationship
with Bo Ra?
Um, I mean, he's a younger kid
who lives next door.
He's my a friend of
my younger sister, Deok Sun.
-Oh.
-Wow. What a great neighborhood.
An older girl from your
neighborhood is buying you dinner.
I guess there's a reason why Dooly
landed in Ssangmundong.
Eat a lot of delicious things, ok?
Little punk. You're pretty handsome.
Bye!
Ask her to buy you a parfait, ok?
There's a place that's famous
for them on Nokdu Street.
-We'll be going, Bo Ra!
-Ok.
Finish all of that, at least.
Ok.
Oh yeah. Didn't you
go to the hospital today?
Yeah. I went.
They said I'm fine.
No problems whatsoever. Don't worry.
You should have come with me.
I'm all better, anyway.
I just got a prescription.
I just have to go back for a checkup
once every two months.
I'm fine, so just
do what you need to do.
I'm sorry, Dad. I'm your son, and yet.
What are you sorry about?
I'm fine, so, Taek.
Please, at least finish your rice.
Quickly.
Yes.
Hey, I'm sorry. So hurry up and eat.
Their fried tofu stew
is really delicious.
You're such a good person.
You even buy dinner for the next door
friend of your younger sister.
I'm sorry. I'm apologizing now,
aren't I?
I'm sorry, so hurry up and eat. Ok?
Geez.
Hey. Look at me.
I'm going to count to three.
One. Two. Three.
Hurry up and eat.
Ok.
Thanks for the meal, Bo Ra.
-What?!
-Huh?
Why, I ought to.
I'm home!
I'm home, too! Soo Yeon's home!
Mom, I'm home, too!
Oh, you're here?
What a coincidence, all three of you
coming home at the same time.
Mom, I'm hungry. Feed me.
You didn't eat yet, right?
We have dinner early.
It was such a long time ago.
Mom. I want to eat too.
Ok, ok.
I'll get it for you, just wait.
Here we go, eat up.
Mom. We only have cold rice?
Yeah. I was busy today, and...
Geez, I'm just going to
eat ramen, then.
How come? Eat this.
You can mix it with the stew.
Mom. Just make ramen for me too.
How can I eat cold rice
so late at night?
Mom, did you wash my button-up?
I was going to wear it tomorrow.
Oh, that. Something got on it,
so I put it in the wash.
If I iron it tomorrow,
you should be able to wear it.
Geez, you should have asked me
before washing it!
Darn it!
What's wrong with this food?
You rotten kids.
No Eul, you make yourself
your own darn rice!
Deok Sun, you make yourself
some darn ramen!
And Bo Ra, do your own darn laundry!
Why does your mom have to do laundry
for a grown-ass college student?
You rotten kids.
Geez, geez.
You terrible lot.
Do you think that your mom
will be with you forever?
Huh?
Don't you feel sorry for her?
Be nice to her while
she's still around.
Please, grow up a little!
You little rascals...
You're no children of mine,
you might as well be my enemies.
Jerks.
Hurry the hell up and eat!
Honey!
I bet those two fought again.
Then why are they taking out
their anger on me?
Um.
Bo Ra.
Let's have a chat.
It's nothing serious, right?
Of course not.
People sometimes get
a biopsy just in case...
...but I'm sure it'll all be fine.
You don't need to worry a single bit.
Despite everything...
...you're the eldest daughter,
so I thought you should know.
That's why I'm telling you.
Don't tell your younger siblings.
Just keep it to yourself, ok?
Ok.
Um, if, by any chance,
you're having a hard time lately...
I'm going to sleep.
Oh, ok. Go to sleep early.
Ahjumma, can I have some seasoned
cartilage and fish cake?
300 won's worth?
I want to give it to my wife.
Hey. Have a seat. Let's have a drink.
Apocalypse Now
Geez.
Oh, it's fine! I'm sure it's nothing!
Yes, don't you worry!
Right?
Of course. My younger sister
got a biopsy on her chest...
...and they said that the lump was
just a water pocket. Don't worry.
So when are your results coming out?
This Saturday.
I was so anxious that they
said they'd get me my results faster.
They're going to call me.
But, missus.
It's really probably nothing, right?
Of course! Geez,
you're such a worrywart.
I know. But I can't help how I feel.
-Oh.
-Oh!
Why are you coming out
from over there?
She was sitting in her room all day
so I brought her over for some coffee.
Oh, thank you so much,
Jung Bong's mom.
Geez, stop frowning!
It's really nothing!
Ok? I'm not worried in
the slightest! Sheesh.
Let's go inside and have some
goldfish bread together.
Oh, President Sung!
Oh, President Kim!
-It's so nice to see you!
Why are you coming out from there?
Oh, the lightbulb went out,
so I fixed it.
You hear that sound, right?
It turns out
that the filament is all worn out!
I fixed everything, so the light
should be nice and bright now!
All right, all right.
What's so amazing about
having changed a lightbulb?
In my house, my No Eul could do that
with both his eyes closed! Geez.
Honey. Do you know what happened
yesterday? Well, Bo Ra's father...
Wow, you're so talented!
All Edison did was invent it. I'll bet
he didn't know how to change one!
I'm just saying, the face of a
craftsman stands out from others.
Not just anyone can run a GoldStar store!
I'm cold, so I'll be going inside now.
-Ok.
-Yeah, get inside.
Ok.
She's really ok, right? I'm worried.
Yes, well, that is...
Geez, Jung Bong's mom!
There's nothing to worry about!
I secretly asked the doctor about my
wife while she was getting examined.
But he told me...
...that a lot of people get biopsies,
even for little problems!
I'm not worried at all!
Not even a tiny bit!
Yes.
It's the morning news for
Saturday, February 25th, 1989.
The final round of the Fujitsu
Baduk Tournament taking place in Japan...
...is just one day away.
The grand prize for
Fujitsu is 15,000,000 yen.
In Korean currency,
that's 70,000,000 won.
Choi Taek, of Korea who unfortunately
got second place last year...
...will proceed to the finals.
He will be heading toward Gimpo
Airport today for the tournament.
He seems to be quite calm,
just as usual.
Now, our next story.
All high schools in Seoul will be
starting their spring break today.
Most schools are planning to begin
the new school year on March second.
Taek hasn't left yet, right?
Oh, you're here?
Here. Give Taek this before he goes.
It's a lot easier to digest than rice.
Oh. That's good. Thanks.
Bye.
Ok.
-Mom, I'm going to the study room.
-Ok.
It's my spring break starting today.
You don't need to iron that.
Even so, I want to have it
ironed for you in advance.
Ok.
Oh yeah. Taek is going
to Japan tomorrow, right?
I guess it's a big match.
Oh, it's called Fujitsu...
...and it's a tournament where Taek
was the runner-up twice.
I'll be going now.
Ok. Bye.
Why isn't this working?
Honey! Honey!
Yes, Master?
What can I do for you?
-This iron isn't working.
-Huh?
Oh, I see.
The line is disconnected there.
Give it here.
I'll fix it for you right away.
Geez, how can you fix this?
Just call someone.
"Call someone?"
Because of this lousy thing?
Just give me an hour.
I'll fix it right away!
Geez, this makes me feel uneasy.
Manager Lee is already here.
He's waiting outside.
-Ok.
-Oh, Taek.
Where did you say your
hotel was this time, again?
Leave me the hotel's number.
Just a moment.
Tokyo Garden Hotel
Put this away.
We might need it again later.
Ok.
Hello.
I've parked the car down there.
We'll be late for the plane. Let's go.
Please take good care of him.
Yes.
Manager.
Just a moment.
Did you sleep well?
That's good.
So you're going now?
Yeah. Aren't you cold?
Nope. But, aren't you?
Me? A little.
Geez, close your zipper, you dunce.
Get me a souvenir.
What do you want?
-You're really going to bring me
back something? -Yeah
Geez, that's fine.
There's no way you'd remember.
I'm serious. I'll bring you
back something this time.
Never mind that. Just get me any
old thing you get from the tournament.
They gave you keychains and towels
last time for participating, right?
You'll be late. Hurry and go.
Ok.
-I'm off.
-You little.
Deok Sun.
It's ok if I lose, right?
Bye.
Honey, come on. Get up
and have some of this.
I don't think I'll be able
to get it down.
Geez, come on, get up. Come on.
Yes, just like that.
You haven't had breakfast or lunch.
You'll really die at this rate.
Don't be like that
and have this drumstick.
What about the kids?
I'm sure they'll take care of
shoving their own faces.
No need to worry.
Honey.
Why haven't they called?
They said they'd call this afternoon.
Geez, you, it's 2:00 p.m. now.
If they said they'd call
in the afternoon, they will.
I'm sure they have tons of people
to call.
Right? There are
tons of people to be called.
So just wait a bit longer
and don't worry.
Geez, also, just stay put.
There won't be anything wrong
with you.
Just trust in me.
Are you a doctor?
What good would it do to trust in you,
who's not even a doctor?
Geez, that's how it seemed like
when I was there!
I'm sure you're really scared.
But judging from how the doctor
and nurse seemed that day...
...it didn't seem serious at all.
So, don't worry.
Eat up.
-It's not finished yet?
-Yeah. Hold on.
You cut the cord?
How am I supposed to use this, then?
You're supposed to cut it a bit like
this to connect it back together!
Ms. Zebra, don't worry.
Go out and watch some TV.
Where did the kids go?
I don't see them anywhere.
First, take 4 million won each
as salary.
You have to watch the bank well.
Being the banker really
is no easy feat.
I feel uneasy.
Can I be the banker while I play?
Dong Ryong.
Do you know what marked
the beginning...
...of my long seven years as a
college exam retaker?
Blue Marble Game
It's this.
Oh.
But, um, I'm not really good
at Blue Marble.
What's the problem when I'll
tell you everything perfectly?
10!
Deserted Island
You're going to a deserted island.
You won't have any chances
for three days straight.
Next!
Taipei. I don't know about Taipei.
Even if you build there,
you'll only get 10,000 won.
I'm not sure it's worth investing in.
12.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine
-10, 11, 12.
-Ah, Seoul! You can't build there.
However, the towing fee
is 2 million won!
Golden Key!
You've gotten it again, Sung No Eul!
Please turn over a card.
Hey. I thought you said
you weren't good!
Why are you so good?
Practically everything is yours!
I heard that everyone has
at least one talent.
Hurry up and flip over a card!
An Invitation for Space Travel
-Darn it.
Noona, what does this
"Space Travel" card do?
They say, "A novice shaman kills."
How does someone who doesn't
even know the rules get...
...the Space Travel card and
Golden Key card all the time!
It pisses me off!
You don't even know that?
We told you in the beginning!
Soo Yeon. Bool Chi Ha Moon.
"Do not be ashamed to ask about
something to someone beneath you."
So you're implying that I'm beneath him?
999th place and 1000th place
are all about the same.
You're ranked last place on
the sciences track.
Darn you!
Can you all please be quiet?
Jung Bong hyungnim.
What kind of card is the
Space Travel card?
It's the best card in Blue Marble.
With this card, you can go
anywhere you want to go.
What the!
It's also my favorite card.
No Eul! Where do you want to go?
Just say the word!
Aw, yes!
Let's split up here.
I have to hurry home.
Did something happen at home?
No. I just have some
things to study, is all. Bye!
I'm home.
Oh, you're home, Bo Ra?
Geez, I must be out of it.
I need to be preparing dinner.
No, no, no.
Let's just order in today.
I want to eat jjajjangmyun.
Yeah, yeah, let's order in!
Call Deok Sun, Soo Yeon, and No Eul.
Ok, let's do that, then.
Did they call yet?
Go on in.
Stop.
Give it here.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mi Ran.
If you couldn't do it,
you should have just said so!
How am I supposed to use this?
We could have just left it to
a pro from the get-go!
It's really difficult to fix that.
Not just anyone can do it!
It's because it's me
that I even got this far with it!
How am I supposed to use this, huh?
Let's put that iron down
before we continue talking, ok?
See you all tomorrow. Mister,
don't remove the Blue Marble game.
Ok!
Um, Soo Yeon.
Yeah, what is it oppa?
You know, your friend.
Man Ok?
Oppa, it'll be a long time
before Man Ok is discharged.
I'm thinking about going to
visit her at the hospital.
What does Miss Man Ok like?
I want to bring her a gift.
What do you think would be good,
Soo Yeon?
She's rich. There's nothing
she doesn't have.
Still.
Well, I don't know.
-A bouquet of flowers?
-Her room is flooded with them.
-Cake?
-She doesn't like it.
What Man Ok wants the most
right now, is to go outside.
She's been cooped up in that
hospital room for two weeks now.
She feels like she's
suffocating to death.
We want to go hang out
with her at least...
...but her dad is super scary.
When she gets discharged later,
I'll help you out.
Just trust in me.
Bye!
Ok, Jin Joo.
Just wait a bit longer.
Ok.
Ta-da!
Sun Young.
It's all finished.
Already?
Wow, you're so talented!
Jin Joo!
Jin Joo can watch her cartoons now!
Jin Joo must be so happy!
I'll be going then.
Huh? Oh, Jin Joo!
Oh?
Oh boy. I have to go, though.
What do I do?
I have to go, though.
Are you having fun?
Oppa.
Have dinner before you go. If you
leave now, she'll cry all night.
Should I, then?
Ok. I'll eat dinner before I go.
Jin Joo, say "Ah."
Is that good?
Give that here.
Mom, I'm home.
Oh, you're back, Sun Woo?
Hurry over. Let's eat.
Hello.
Oh, hey.
The VCR broke...
...Jin Joo was watching a cartoon...
...but the VCR broke,
so I came to fix it.
But, she's stuck to me like glue.
Jin Joo, you like him that much?
-Mom, I want rice.
-Oh, yes!
I want that!
Here we go.
But, Ms. Il Hwa's results
still haven't come out yet?
The sun's almost setting.
I'm going to Jung Bong hyung room's.
I'm going to go meet Jo Hyun outside.
Mom, you're not eating any more?
I'm fine.
I don't really like jjajangmyun.
Hey. You should eat some more,
at least.
I don't like jjajangmyun
that much either.
Don't worry, ok? I'll bring you
the best one from my store tomorrow!
You think I'm worried about
some darn iron right now?
What, then?
Today's the day that the results of
Bo Ra's mom's biopsy comes out...
...but I haven't heard from her yet.
She told me she'd call right away
when the results came out.
Hello?
Yes, that's me. I'm Lee Il Hwa.
Yes, yes.
Go ahead.
The results are out?
Are they not good?
Oh. I see.
Yes. Yes.
Then it's nothing, right?
Ah, yes. Yes. I understand.
Yes, I will. Yes, yes.
Thank you! Yes!
Geez. I told you that it was nothing!
They said that it was
just a water pocket.
They said that I just have to do...
um...
...follow-up tests once
a year from now on
What did I tell you? I told you that
there's nothing to worry about!
Geez.
Not even once, seriously!
I wasn't worried for even a second
from the very beginning! Really!
Really? Even so, I thought that
you might have been a tiny bit uneasy.
But wow, my husband Sung Dong Il
is truly a man among men!
I wasn't worried for even a second
from the very beginning! Really!
I wasn't worried at all! Sheesh.
All right, all right.
Bo Ra's mom!
Judging from the look on your face,
I'll bet your results came out!
Sheesh, they said that
it was nothing, right?
They said that it was
just a water pocket!
Oh, thank goodness.
Even so, you were so worried about it
so I was getting a bit worried.
Wow, congratulations!
Yes, thank you!
I'll bet that Bo Ra's dad was going
through a lot too.
You can rest easy now!
What do you mean,
going through a rough time?
Seriously, I wasn't worried
for even a second from the beginning!
Oh, why not have a drink
tonight to celebrate?
Oh, good idea!
Thank you for the meal.
-Oh, ok.
-Head inside, then!
Good work!
We have some sake and a box
of dried pollock. Let's have that.
Yeah. Wait, no. Instead of that,
let's have some wild ginseng liquor.
Let's drink that today.
Wild ginseng liquor?
You have such a thing?
Wow, you have some balls, Jung Bong's dad.
He values that more than his own life.
He'll never drink that.
On a chilly day like this, warm sake
is just the thing to warm us up!
Bo Ra's mom. Did you know...
Let's have the wild ginseng liquor!
Should we drink it upstairs or
downstairs? Where?
He's talking about drinking
the wild ginseng liquor, right?
Yeah! Where should we drink it?
What does it matter,
when it's wild ginseng liquor?
Oh, come inside!
Taek's dad.
Have you heard?
-Heard what?
-You know that thief from before?
The owner of the ice store
said that the thief had a knife!
Really?
He didn't get hurt?
-He did!
-What?
Apparently, his arm
was scratched up a bit!
He could have gotten seriously hurt!
Oppa.
Aren't you scared?
Yeah, I am scared.
Excuse me, sir.
A person was stabbed!
I heard.
How scary.
I'm just wasting my breath.
Oh, it's a plane!
-A plane? Where?
-Breaking news...
...a plane headed to Tokyo carrying
182 passengers from Gimpo Airport...
...has run off the runway at
the Narita Airport.
We are currently checking how
many of the passengers were Korean.
We do not currently have any specific
numbers of casualties or injuries.
Based on our most
current information...
...it seems that Choi Taek, 6-dan,
and his entourage...
...who were headed toward the
Fujitsu Tournament, were on board.
However, we do not have any
specifics regarding the situation.
Based on our current
information, however...
...it is almost certain that
Choi Taek was on board.
Omo, what do we do?
What do we do?
Omo!
Um, mister!
Have you gotten any calls from Taek?
What time was his flight?
You know his hotel's number, right?
I wrote it down.
Wait, wait a minute. Wait.
Call the Baduk Club! The Baduk Club!
-Ok, I'll do that.
-Wait.
Taek put the contact info
in his journal this morning.
You call this wild ginseng liquor?
Are you messing with me?
Where's the wild ginseng?
There it is, floating in the middle!
It's been alive like that for 20 years
because it's a real wild ginseng!
It really is a real wild ginseng, though.
He secretly snatched a root off from
his branch manager's wild ginseng.
A plane en route to Narita Airport
from Gimpo...
...was involved in an accident where
it ran off the runway.
The names of the passengers on board
have not been released yet...
...but according
to the airport's reports...
...Choi Taek, 6-dan,
and his entourage were on board...
What kind of nonsense is this?
Now, now.
Please go back home, everyone.
The situation has already
been taken care of.
What do you mean?
Is Taek ok?
-Were they able to get in touch with him?
-Yes. He's fine.
He's at the hotel now.
Taek's dad is speaking with him now.
-Thank goodness.
-I felt my heart drop!
Wow. I still feel uneasy.
Is Taek's dad ok?
I'm sure he was very shocked.
Who, him? I've seriously never
seen such a collected guy in my life.
Geez, all right,
head back home, everyone!
I heard it's raining a lot there.
Yeah. Make sure
you take care of yourself.
And make sure to eat well.
Geez.
Are you all right?
No matter how much I think about it,
he isn't normal.
Yeah. I think so, too.
Geez, he's seriously not human.
He's like a bear.
Don't worry about your old man
and go to sleep early tonight, ok?
And don't take too many
pain relievers, ok?
Yeah.
Ok.
And make sure you pack
an umbrella in the morning.
Ok.
Ok. Good night.
Did you go somewhere?
Look over there.
A full list of the casualties
has not come in.
According to most recent news...
...Korean Taek had planned
to participate
Is that me?
People have been freaking out
because of that news.
Everyone's been calling to ask if
you're all right.
The corrected news will be out soon.
Oh yeah.
Did you speak with your father?
Yes, a little while ago.
My dad seemed to be completely fine.
He usually doesn't get worked up
that easily.
Are you kidding me right now?
I mean his child was potentially hurt
so how could he be completely fine?
I think Taek takes after his father.
He's like a stone Buddha!
But, even so...
...it's only natural for a parent's
heart to break over their child.
No matter how much I think about it,
I don't get it.
Geez, that bear jerk!
Are you kidding me right now?
Excuse me?
It's the first time I've seen
your father freak out like that.
I thought he was going
to blow a hole in my ear!
-Um, Manager Lee?
-Yes?
Just a moment, please.
Ok.
Rest up.
Hello?
-Choi Taek?
-Yeah.
Oh, I had to hear
your voice to make sure.
Oh yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, what the hell were you doing
that you didn't pick up the phone?
When?
You called me before?
We kept,
your dad kept crying because of you.
Hey, it was no joke.
Taek. I thought your dad
was Superman today.
What do you mean?
I don't know where he got such
superhuman strength.
I said, what do you mean?
What do we do?
Aigoo.
Here.
I'll do it.
It's the brown one,
yes, this one.
Sun Woo, my hands are shaking so much.
Can you call? I don't think
I can do anything.
Ok. I got it.
Aigoo, what do we do?
[Choi Taek]
He's not picking up.
Aigoo! My child!
-Oppa oppa! It'll be ok!
-Aigoo!
-Aigoo.
-What do we do?
Hello?
Hello? We're calling from Korea.
Who is it?
Is Taek there?
We're Choi Taek, 6-dan's family.
Is Taek in the room?
He's taking a shower right now.
Really? You're telling me the truth,
right?
But, what--
Where is Taek right now?
Where is he?
This is Taek's father, right?
Is Taek in the hotel room right now?
Huh?
Is he in the hotel room?
He really is there, right?
Yes, sir.
He's taking a shower right now.
I saw him go in with my own two eyes.
But, um, what is it...
He's there?
Huh?
Hello?
The news is saying that Taek
was in an accident, so.
What?
An accident?
Manager Lee, there's huge trouble
because of the media.
-Please come downstairs, quickly.
-Oh, ok.
Yes. I understand.
Hello?
Dad!
Is something the matter?
I heard it's raining a lot over there.
Ah, yes, it is.
The weather here isn't too good.
I see. Make sure you
take care of yourself.
-And make sure to eat properly.
-Ok.
And make sure you pack
an umbrella in the morning.
Ok.
I'm hanging up now.
Way to go.
You sure kept calm, didn't you, oppa?
Taek.
Be good to your dad.
It really seems like you're
everything to him.
Good night!
Hey!
It's ok if you lose!
I'm hanging up!
Mr. Choi! Let's go have a drink!
Let's have some soju!
Speaking of which, you must have
been really shocked. Are you ok?
Yes. I'm ok.
Geez, he's really not human.
No.
It's not like it was something that
would be resolved by getting worked up.
Wow, you're a true man!
If it were Bo Ra's dad over here,
he would've been crying up a storm!
What? It's just us men here.
What's so embarrassing
about crying?
Can't men cry a little too?
You cried?
Did something happen?
Geez, no, I...
Darn it.
On the day when Bo Ra's mother
got her physical examination.
She had to get a biopsy and he latched
onto me, as I was heading home...
...and cried up a storm!
What do I do about my poor Il Hwa?
My poor Il Hwa.
She had to meet a rotten husband
like me and suffer so much...
...and now it even seems like
she might have a disease.
What do we do?
My poor Il Hwa!
I can't live without my Il Hwa!
My Il Hwa!
Il Hwa!
But it's not like a biopsy is a big deal.
I'm sure everything will be just fine.
But what if, just what if, she has
a disease or something?
Say something, darn you!
It'll be fine Bo Ra's dad.
I'm sure it's nothing!
What are you just saying that
because it's not your situation?
No.
"It'll be ok?"
You're just saying that!
My poor Il Hwa!
I can't live without my Il Hwa!
If she dies, I'll die with her!
I'll just die, too!
But when the doctor said "Biopsy,"
he was definitely smiling.
But just if, if!
If Il Hwa is ill.
How can I raise three kids by myself?
Three kids!
I can raise them just fine
without her.
Right?
No, no! Who cares about the kids
when I won't have Il Hwa?
Everyone around us saw.
It was no joke!
Seriously, so embarrassing.
What about you? What a man you are!
You didn't even know how to fix
an iron so you cut the entire wire up!
Who said that?
There are no such things as
secrets in this neighborhood!
You didn't even know how
to fix something like that...
...and chopped it all up?
There's only one true man in our
neighborhood. Bonghwangdang over here.
All right, bottoms up!
But, was your personality
always like that?
Even when you were younger?
"Mool Ryung Mang Dong,
Jung Joong Yuh San."
What the hell does that mean?
It's what Admiral Yi Soon Shin
said to a soldier...
...quaking in fear during the
Imjin War.
"Don't act thoughtlessly."
"A real man should conduct
himself calmly.
And move his body with prudence as
if he were moving a mountain.
Ahh! A mouse!
Geez, why is she making such
a huge fuss about one small mouse?
-What are you doing?
-Over there!
What the heck!
-Over here!
-Oh my!
It's gone now.
She said it's gone!
Get back over here!
What's with you?
Oh, oh, it's not because
I was scared.
I'm fine with literally everything
else but mice are really.
Geez, aigoo.
-A mouse!
-Where?
Geez.
I'm telling you this in
case you misunderstand.
But, honestly,
I'm not scared.
It's just because I was bitten by
a mouse when I was 6 years old.
Um, so I got an illness sort of thing.
I guess that mouse
was freakishly huge.
Yes. It was about the
size of a Jindo dog.
And because I was bit so hard,
I developed a trauma.
Oh.
When I was in the army, I stopped a
wild dog the size of a bull...
...just by staring it down.
When I was young,
Superman lived at my house.
He was a MacGyver-type of guy
who could fix anything in the world...
Wow!
-"Esta Bom!"
So the blow dryer's broken, eh?
Give it here. I'll fix it.
He was the JJanga who'd appear
out of nowhere...
...to fix every sort of problem.
He was the hero of all heroes
who had no weakness.
-Bye, mister.
-Bye!
-Bye! Let's go.
However, I came to know the truth
after growing out of my childhood.
He was just not discovered.
But even Superman was human.
Mi Ran. Mi Ran!
I'm almost done fixing it!
Mi Ran! I can really fix it!
Ok? Give me just one chance!
I told you, I'm almost done fixing it!
We don't know how many dirty,
petty, unfair, sad, scary,or difficult
...worlds have passed Dad by.
And only now...
...I realize...
...no matter how dirty, petty, unfair,
sad...
...scary, or difficult,
the reason he endured...
...was because he had
people to protect.
It's because he had a family.
And he had me.
Because he had to live the world
by the name Dad, and not another.
[Victory at Fujitsu for
Choi Taek, 6-dan!]
Taek hyung is so amazing.
He won at Fujisu!
And the prize money was 70,000,000 won!
Wow, but wait.
What's that, noona?
I don't know.
Taek gave it to me.
What? Where did he get it?
Oh, I'm going to die of frustration.
He must be an idiot!
That's like the pot
calling the kettle black.
You have a death wish?
I mean, I asked him to bring me
anything he got from the competition
...and he brought me that thing.
I bet it was a hassle in itself,
just bringing that over.
So frustrating! That stupid idiot!
Soo Yeon. Lend me that pot.
I'll put this kimchi in there.
Sure.
You can't! Stop!
Are you out of your mind?
What?
[Choi Taek, 6-dan, holds the victor's
cup as he poses for the photo.]
[Choi Taek, 6-dan, holds the victor's cup
as he poses for the photo.]
But, where did Jung Bong go?
He dressed up and left this morning.
Where?
[Korea University Hospital]
[To: Ms. Jang Mi Ok
From: Kim Jung Bong]
[Jang Mi Ok]
[Korea University Hospital]
Excuse me!
Give it to me.
I'll give it to her for you.
To: Ms. Jang Mi Ok
From: Kim Jung Bong
He was standing in front of
your room all day today.
It was so frustrating to watch that
I told him I'd give it to you instead.
I won't tell your dad.
Thank you.
Soo Yeon knows nothing
about men, does she?
What the heck?
-Bro.
-Yeah?
Happy birthday.
I have something to tell
Mom and Dad.
I trust our Bo Ra.
Noona. There's really nothing
going on as of late, right?
-Why do I feel so uneasy?
-What?
My poor Jin Joo...
It's ok.
Don't worry. Don't cry.
I feel so bad...
Deok Sun!
Why do you like Deok Sun, though?
I just like her.
Why isn't there anyone
who likes me? Hmm?
I must be a woman
unworthy of being loved.
I guess this time was a fluke, too.
Do you like Jung Pal better,
or Taek better?
I have someone that I like.
And I'm going to confess. Soon.