This Lu Wei,
KTV colleague.
we interrogated him during
Qiao Sisi's car accident case.
KTV colleague.
So,
was he hiding something from us?
Go check it out.
Pan Shuping and Lu Wei.
Confirm if
they have any connections
to Huguang KTV
and the serial murder case.
Wait,
why are you back?
It's just tailing someone.
Lin Xiao and the others are there.
You're unbelievable.
You assigned your own task to others.
I came to see
if there's anything I can do here.
Why don't you be the captain and take charge?
Where are you going?
Have you eaten?
At the gate,
Old Han's place.
Put it on my tab.
Go.
Master.
I knew you
scold me on the outside,
but love me on the inside.
I told you to pack it for the guys.
As for you,
learn your lesson.
Don't eat today.
Leaving your post without permission.
Did you forget what I told you
on the first day we met?
The first lesson for a police officer is
to obey orders.
Follow commands.
I will
reflect deeply on this.
Hello, what do you need to buy?
Hello, Miss Li.
There's something
we need to ask you about.
From 2003 to 2005,
you worked
at Huguang KTV.
The boss at that time
was Zhang Biao.
He valued you
and put you in charge
of VIP clients.
You met
a friend there
named Guan Jing.
Yes,
we had a pretty good relationship.
On August 9, 2005,
you reported
that Guan Jing went missing.
On August 12,
you withdrew the case,
saying she was found.
Yes,
but
she was already dead.
Her tomb is at Xifeng Mountain.
Dead?
How did she die?
She had congenital heart disease.
Because of this,
she came out to work and make money
in order to survive.
When she passed away,
I also tried to contact her family.
They felt the funeral would cost money,
so no one came to claim her body.
I took care of everything for her.
But when you withdrew the case,
you said she
was sent to the hospital for a sudden illness.
Which hospital?
It was like this, officer.
At that time, Zhang Biao and Liu Jiang called me.
Guan Jing had an accident.
So when I saw her again,
she was already at the funeral home.
Liu Jiang,
right?
Yes.
Liu Jiang handled the hospitalization.
He has connections at the hospital.
Did Guan Jing have any friends while she was alive?
A boyfriend?
I'm not very sure.
The medical records say
her
heart disease
was stable.
How could she
die of a sudden heart attack?
It's heart disease.
You never know.
It's fate.
In January 2005,
you picked up something
at the mailroom of the City Photography Association.
Do you remember?
I remember.
I helped
Zhang Biao pick up a camera.
Zhang Biao?
Yes.
That camera
took a picture.
Could you please
take a look?
Is the girl on the coffee table
Guan Jing?
Can I take a closer look?
Yes.
It's her.
The Traditional Chinese Medicine Hospital is in the development zone, 25 kilometers away.
According to Li Ting,
Guan Jing fell ill suddenly.
They had to send her to the nearest hospital.
Hello.
Here is the copy of Guan Jing's medical records you requested.
In August 2005,
Guan Jing never came here.
All the medical records are here.
Guan Jing has multiple gynecological treatment records.
Zhang had an abortion once.
But during the timeframe Li Ting mentioned,
the hospital has no record of her visit.
Li Ting is lying.
She first reported Guan Jing missing.
Then something happened,
so she decided to lie and drop the case.
Guan Jing.
Could it be because
of her death itself?
If so.
The secret room.
Li Ting.
Guan Jing.
They are all connected.
And Li Ting
is the key to unlocking all the secrets.
They have already left.
You told me what to say,
and I said it exactly like that.
These flowers are nice.
They look
quite fresh.
Please wrap these flowers
up for me.
Wrap them to look like
how you used to be,
sweet,
beautiful,
and tender.
When will you give my things back to me?
Your things?
Hey.
What things of yours?
You promised me.
As long as I did what you said,
you would give my photos back to me.
Just because you're in them
doesn't mean they're yours.
Those are works of art.
My works of art.
Do you even understand art?
I just want back my...
The way you are now,
you'd pollute those works of art, you know?
I'm sorry.
I treated you like you were back in school again.
It was better back in school.
I remember back in school,
you liked sandalwood perfume.
The kind of person who likes this perfume is
strong-willed,
understanding,
and most importantly, obedient.
But now, you...
Hanging around so many flowers every day,
the scent is too overpowering.
You,
should just come back to school.
Come back to me.
Let me purify your mind
and your body.
I just want
to live a normal life.
Don't worry.
Everything you've done,
I won't tell anyone.
I...
I just want those photos.
Please.
Oh, Li Ting.
You really aren't as obedient as before.
Besides,
what you just said
is wrong.
What do you mean 'the things I did'?
Aren't they
the things we did together?
You need to remember this.
Anything,
can only be given by me.
You have no right to ask me for it.
Understand?
Sigh.
Even the most beautiful flowers
will wither
and fade.
Wrap the flowers beautifully for me
and send them to my office.
Captain Sun.
We found Pan Shuping's place.
I texted you the address.
Okay.
Yan and I are heading there now.
Yan.
Captain Sun.
The neighbors said
there's been no activity at Pan Shuping's place
for over ten days.
The water
and electricity meters
have stopped running.
The landlord is inside.
Let's go in and take a look.
About how long has she been renting it?
She's been renting for...
Three months ago,
she just rented it.
Did Pan Shuping come with Lu Wei,
or did she rent your place by herself?
She came alone when she rented the place.
How much was the monthly rent for this place then?
About 2,000.
Do you still have the contract?
I do.
I'll get it for you.
Okay.
This should be the primary crime scene.
The bathroom floor drain
still smells of disinfectant.
After the murder,
the killer must have
done some cleaning in the bathroom.
The kitchen knife was probably taken by the killer.
The bedding
and the curtains
are also missing.
It's highly likely
that during the murder,
they got stained with blood
or
were used to wrap the body.
The entire crime scene
and the body disposal method
are completely different from before.
It's probably not the serial killer.
I'll call forensics over.
Hello, Mr. Wang.
I've sent you Lu Wei's address.
Get here as soon as possible.
Okay.
This is the place.
Let's go inside.
The door isn't even locked.
Is anyone here?
Disinfectant,
cleaning agent,
shovel,
and saw blade.
Is anyone here?
Captain Sun.
He arrived at 2:00 a.m.,
which matches the estimated time of death
given by the forensic doctor.
I called the number on the business card several times on the way here,
but it was turned off.
Most likely,
it was a crime of passion.
He dumped the body and fled.
Lin Xiao,
go check this license plate.
Han,
contact the other departments.
Okay.