I really didn't know.
I was too sleepy then.
The fog was heavy,
and there were no streetlights.
I was just...
I just got distracted for a moment,
then I heard a bang.
It just...
I never expected
there...
to be a leg hanging.
Son of a bitch, someone is trying to frame me.
Captain Sun.
I have a right lower limb dressed in women's clothing here.
Based on the epiphyseal closure
and initial observation of the skin condition,
the victim is highly likely female.
The estimated age is between 20 and 35.
Crushed this badly.
What about the other parts?
Still looking.
The body is severely mutilated.
Some parts are scattered over there too.
Have a smoke.
Next time, remember to
stand upwind.
You won't smell the corpse,
but you'll smell
how cowardly you are.
Did you find the head?
Not yet.
Initially,
the victim's neck muscles are torn,
and the cervical spine has a scissor-like fracture,
which matches the characteristics of a high-speed impact
causing decapitation.
There's also an impact wound on the shoulder.
The scattered tissues
all show signs of abrasions and dragging.
Judging from the stiffness of the limbs,
the time of death
is within 12 hours.
Master,
why is there someone lying there?
Oh, my god.
Chief Zhao said you were coming back today.
I thought
you would go back to report for duty.
I didn't expect you to come straight to the scene.
Sir,
who is this?
This is my old partner,
Yan Mi.
Brother,
welcome back to the team.
Yan.
Let me introduce you.
This is my new apprentice.
His name is Jia Peng.
He's very hardworking.
Hello, Yan.
I'm Jia.
What are you doing, brother?
Captain Sun,
it seems our judgments
are the same.
This isn't a car accident.
It's a body dump.
A body dump?
Why?
Master, didn't you just get here?
How could you tell?
First,
we're nearly 40 kilometers from the city.
Apart from the factories around here,
there are no residential areas.
It's deserted.
Barely anyone comes here,
except for large trucks smuggling goods.
Judging from the condition of the body,
the victim took good care of herself
and her appearance.
She wasn't a manual laborer.
A woman like her,
why would she appear here?
And how did she end up here?
Second,
the bloodstains
start from here.
This is
the first point of impact.
It's a crushing point.
If it were an impact,
the body would fly out first.
At the same time, there would be
sprayed blood spatters around,
then fall back to the ground,
and roll over.
However,
the bloodstains left behind should have many patterns
instead of being so uniform.
But if someone familiar with this road
deliberately dumped the body in the heavy fog
to cover up the truth with a traffic accident,
they would only leave crushing marks.
Just like this.
Although it covers a large area,
there is almost no blood spatter.
Let me sort this out.
If they were dumping the body,
the killer should have
buried it in a remote place,
instead of leaving it on the main road
and drawing our attention.
Wait.
Why is that?
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
Is it a provocation
or revenge?
Have you determined the cause of death?
The direct cause of death was excessive blood loss
due to the complete decapitation.
On the surface,
the muscle, skin,
and cervical spine sections
are consistent with fatal high-speed impact.
But in fact,
it wasn't knocked off by an impact.
In decapitation caused by a car accident,
the skin wound edges show radial tearing.
The cervical spine cross-section shows multi-directional fractures
and comminuted bursting.
But the skin wound edges of this corpse
show wavy tearing.
There are unidirectional fractures
and local compression marks.
Furthermore,
we also detected
trace metals in the wound.
You mean
her head was forcibly severed by some instrument...
Cut with pliers.