What the heck?
Are you praying here?
Does it work?
No rush.
Keep holding your breath.
We have time to wait.
Forty-two seconds.
Liu Jiang,
your lung capacity is terrible.
Oh, my God.
Wait, you scared me to death.
Where am I?
Hey.
Who are you?
Hey,
you're quite handsome.
You look like an actor.
Thank you.
You too.
Why are you running?
Hey.
What's wrong with running?
Running is my right.
Running is my freedom.
I jog every day.
What's wrong with exercising?
Can't I just have some fun?
Having fun in a pile of dead bodies?
You two have a problem.
Looking down on the dead?
Let me educate you today.
Everyone dies someday,
either as heavy as Mount Tai
or as light as a feather.
You know?
Your values are problematic.
Don't look down on the dead.
Without life, there is no...
First Brigade,
Major Crimes.
Sun,
Gou...
Uh, Sun Ri...
Sun Ju...
You're a doctor with this level of education?
Cuff him.
This kid is pretty dedicated.
According to the information we have, yes.
Did you find Liu Jiang's wife?
We brought her back.
Xiaohan and I will go question her now.
Okay.
It's so hot, and you won't even pour me some water.
The... The air pressure is too low.
It's so hot. Can you pour me a glass of water?
What the hell is this?
You know why we brought you here, right?
I have no idea.
No rush.
Take your time.
Ah.
No,
Officers,
I just sold some medicine.
There's no need for such a big scene to bring me in,
is there?
You think it's as simple
as just prescribing some medicine?
No.
What's wrong with me selling some medicine?
I heal the wounded
and help others.
If that counts as healing the wounded,
then I'm the God of Medicine reincarnated.
That's not right.
Officers, let me tell you,
since I got out, don't I have to
survive?
Don't I have to support my family,
and feed my wife and daughter?
Are you two going to support me?
Then I have to find a job.
Let me make it clear to you first.
I...
My prescriptions
are all in the medical books.
And the medicine I sold,
well,
isn't fake.
It was prescribed by a legitimate Chinese pharmacy.
Legi-
Stop messing around, you hear me?
If there's no problem, why did you run?
I...
Liu Jiang.
Since May 17,
where have you been?
Officer, forget about May 7.
As for me.
On the 17th.
Right, the 17th.
The 17th, right.
As for me,
all 365 days are the same.
I work during the day,
from 7 a.m. to 8 p.m., rain or shine.
I go to work at the hospital on time every morning.
After work, I go straight home.
I don't go anywhere else.
Alright.
Hurry up,
officer.
It's time.
I need to go back and be with my daughter.
Hurry up.
He came back at 8 p.m.
On his way back,
he usually buys a toy for the kid.
Oh, he buys one every day.
There's barely any room for them at home.
But,
that's his only good trait.
He loves the kid.
Around
8:20
or 8:30,
he would be home.
After dinner,
he played with the kid for a while and went to bed.
He slept until
he woke up at 6:00 the next morning.
He had breakfast,
got ready,
and went to work.
His time at home at night
can only be proven by you.
Not necessarily.
We have a security camera at home.
Does that count as proof?
You have a security camera?
Yeah.
This thing is quite expensive.
My husband installed it.
He said it's
to scare those debt collectors.
If they dare to mess around,
we can take the video
to the police station to sue them
and let the police arrest them.
Qiao Sisi.
Do you know her?
Also known as Qiaoqiao.
I don't know her.
What about this one?
Kong Jiao.
I don't know her.
No.
You must know this one.
Zhang Biao.
You all know.
Isn't this
Abiao from Huguang?
I know him.
But we're not close.
Not close.
Then what about this person?
Hao Quezi.
Do you know Hao Weiguo?
Still don't know him?
Let me remind you.
Last year,
you gave him
a large sum of money.
I remember now.
I know him.
Doesn't he run a money-lending business?
I just gave him some money
to earn some interest.
Right?
His company is legit.
They have a license.
Officers,
there's nothing wrong with me doing that, right?
You're really something.
You're up to your neck in debt,
but you won't pay it back.
Instead, you go
to that Cripple Hao to help you
earn interest.
I can tell you two have no experience.
You've lived too comfortably.
Officers,
you can't pay back borrowed money.
Not even a single cent.
When it comes to paying back money,
if you pay it back once, there will be a second time.
And these guys chase me every day.
Let me tell you,
these bastards
will definitely kill me.
Just thinking about it
makes me furious.
What are you doing?
Look closely.
Look clearly.
Who is it?
Qiao Sisi.
Kong Jiao,
found murdered
on May 17.
Zhang Biao,
killed in an explosion
on May 19.
Wang Hongjia,
severely injured
on May 27.
This one,
Hao Weiguo, whom you gave money to,
was murdered the day before yesterday.
This person,
it's you, right?
Is it you?
Don't.
Don't scream.
Look.
Take a look.
No,
what do
you two mean?
Do you mean in the photo,
only
I'm the only one alive now?
I'm in danger, officers.
Ah,
you need to send someone to protect me.
No.
You,
what do you two mean?
Do you suspect me?
That I killed them?
Officers,
you overestimate me.
Overestimate me.
Do I have the guts?
Do I have the ability?
Let me tell you,
there must be a misunderstanding.
You,
take a good look.
You must know the girl
on the coffee table.
No.
I didn't look carefully
just now.
It's fine.
I don't.
Look at it now.
You are in this photo
together,
and now you are telling me
you don't know her?
Officer,
isn't this normal?
I was rich back then,
right?
I changed girls every day.
No,
not girls.
I hung out with different friends every day.
There were so many people.
Who could see who?
Would I notice her?
When was
that?
2004 or 2005.
Right before I went in.
Right,
it was all
A Biao
who arranged it.
Friends with similar interests
gathered together,
right? Just going out.
Observing and learning,
exchanging feelings,
looking to the future.
Who took
the photo?
I really don't remember.
Officer, it's been so many years.
Liu Jiang.
What?
What's the matter?
You really don't want the chance I gave you, do you?
Isn't this normal?
Officer.
Who takes photos in a place like this?
Let me ask you,
would you take photos if you went there for fun?
Wouldn't that leave evidence against yourself?
Secretly filmed.
It must have been secretly filmed.
Go investigate.
It has nothing to do with me.
Liu Jiang,
you just said something
that makes a lot of sense.
Of all the people in the photo,
besides this girl,
you are the only one still alive.
So,
do you think your current situation
is dangerous?
Listen to me, Liu Jiang.
You already understand
the current situation.
The reason we're telling you so much
is to protect you.
But you
must also give us a reason to protect you.
Take another careful look this time.
I'm thirsty.
Oh.
Caicai.
Huh?
Hey.
This is for you,
a little purple princess.
Daddy doesn't know her name either,
but I think she looks
exactly like you.
Right?
Come here, let Daddy give you a hug.
Look at you,
buying dolls all day.
There's no room at home.
What a waste of money.
So what?
Money is meant to make Caicai happy.
As long as you like it,
Daddy will buy you a different doll every day.
Red, orange, yellow, green, blue, indigo, purple.
I'll buy them all for you, okay?
Okay.
Daddy,
I made this at kindergarten today.
Oh.
Is this...
Did you make this?
By yourself?
Aww.
Daddy loves it so much.
Give Daddy a hug.
Oh,
thank you, Caicai.
Caicai, listen to Daddy.
If one day Daddy isn't around anymore,
you have to listen to Mommy, okay?
Promise Daddy.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's go home and eat.
Look.
It dropped.
Let's go.
Let's hold hands.
You wait here.
I'll go check it out.
Okay.
Who is it?
You shouldn't have
given my number to your wife.
What do you mean?
You asked me to meet you here.
It stinks in here.
With the crap you've done,
just stay inside.
I thought about having my wife call you.
But the cops are watching me.
I'm telling you.
If I call you, the cops will investigate you.
Don't rush me.
I'm only halfway done.
You ruined it.
I haven't even finished using the bathroom.
I'll talk to you when I get out.
Hey!
What do you mean?
Open it.
Open the door!
If you aren't afraid of the cops outside hearing,
keep knocking.
Let me ask you.
Who killed these people?
How should I know?
Could it be because
of what happened back then?
You were the one who handled it.
You said you handled it cleanly.
Absolutely clean.
I handled it absolutely cleanly.
What exactly is going on?
Bothering me every day.
Are you hiding something from me?
I think
right now,
it's quite dangerous.
I think we
should go lay low
to avoid the risk.
Back then,
you had the money to fund the cripple.
So could you
spare a little to fund me
now?
Let go of me.
The cripple dared to steal from me
and ask for money through you
because back then...
Someone testified for him.
What about now?
Who else?
Oh.
You killed them.
Now you want to kill me.
If I wanted to kill you,
it wouldn't be this much trouble.
Oh my god.
Liu Jiang.
You have to remember,
you have a wife and kids.
Now,
we must keep our mouths shut.
Except for us,
no one else can bring that up.
Go hide out for a while.
After things cool down,
you can come back.
Don't go.