Captain Sun,
between 12:00 and 2:00 when the case was reported,
17 large vehicles passed by this road.
Only one vehicle didn't get on the highway.
The license plate number is
Jiang E94845.
According to the surveillance camera,
this vehicle finally disappeared in this logistics park.
It never came out since then.
Search separately.
Okay.
Northwest corner.
Red truck.
Copy that.
Not unloaded yet.
The truck was just washed.
They shouldn't have gone far.
Excuse me, sir.
I'd like to ask if this truck can...
Who are you?
I'm...
Excuse me, sir.
Um,
how much to Dagang?
I...
I don't smoke.
Well, these days,
my car is getting maintenance.
I'm not taking passengers.
Find someone else.
Come on, sir.
Do us a favor.
We'll pay you extra.
Oh, right.
My client needs it urgently.
Around here,
yours is the only car available, right?
You'd better find someone else.
Hey, hey.
Sir, don't go.
Sir.
The people there said Lu Wei...
Forensic.
Take him over first.
Okay.
Let's go.
Are we interrogating him directly?
Let him stew for a while.
It's been less than half a day since the incident.
His memory is still fresh.
Let him think it over.
When the time comes,
he'll crack naturally.
Just a little push,
and he'll confess.
Understood.
Still the same.
Nothing has changed.
Let's go,
Lao Yan.
If you don't come back soon,
I really won't be able to keep that prime spot of yours.
You have no idea.
Every day, people fight over your desk
like cats and dogs.
I fought tooth and nail to save it for you.
I wipe it every day,
even more often than I wash my own face.
Comrade Yan Mi.
Rejoin the team.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Get a change of scenery for now.
Are you kicking me out?
We will always be partners.
I'll wait for you to come back.
We'll continue fighting together.
It was you.
You killed my parents.
Why wasn't it you who died?
Give me the photo.
Yan.
It's in the past.
Master's case is closed.
The facts are clear,
and the evidence is sufficient.
It was Ma Guangfu's deliberate revenge.
No one was behind him.
But what about the bomb?
He never confessed where the bomb came from.
He must be covering for the real culprit behind him.
Only by finding this person
can we find the truth
about our master's murder.
The best way to honor our master now
is for both of us to do our jobs well.
The living expenses you send to Guannan every month,
every time he receives them,
he returns them unopened
to the mailroom.
Five years,
a full sixty envelopes.
Lao Yan.
I believe Guannan doesn't truly hate you.
He just needs a little more time.
Time always moves forward.
We can't be trapped in the past forever.
We have to look forward.
But for some,
time hasn't moved forward.
Master.
The forensics team is checking Lu Wei's truck.
They called and said
human tissue and bloodstains were found on the tires and chassis.
The time is ripe.
Let's go get him.
Take them off him.
Yan.
Hurry up.
You thought you ran over a wild dog.
Lv Wei.
Ask yourself if that's believable.
If you ran over a wild dog,
why did you run when you saw the police?
Lv Wei.
Not taking the chance I give you, huh?
Fine.
Hey.
I didn't mean to run.
At first,
I really thought I ran over a wild dog.
When I got out to check,
that thing wasn't a dog at all.
How fast were you going?
I forgot.
Maybe 70 or 80.
Did you stop after hitting it?
Wait a minute.
Did you run over it or hit it?
I ran over it.
I didn't hit it.
When it crashes,
there's a bang.
There was no bang.
The car just jolted a bit.
It ran over something.
When you got out of the car,
what did the body look like?
Did it have a head?
How would I dare
to look closely?
It's so scary.
The killer was brutal
and professional.
And
they also left
a lot of false traces on the body
to confuse us.
It shows
the killer planned this carefully.
Yes.
The state of the body is shocking.
We have fully confirmed it.
The highway
is not the primary crime scene.
However,
the killer transported the body parts
very cautiously,
so
the specific details of the crime
are still being reconstructed.
To move the victim,
the killer must have used a vehicle.
I suggest
we return to the scene
to find a breakthrough.
If we find the car used to dump the body,
we can find the person who dumped it.
It is now certain
that this is a gruesome murder and dismemberment case.
I announce
the immediate establishment of the 5.17 task force.
I will take charge personally.
The specific investigation work
will be handled by the criminal investigation team.
All departments across the bureau
will provide full cooperation.
Without further ado,
everyone must stay alert
and bring the killer to justice as soon as possible.
Help!
Stay away!
Don't come any closer!