[Master Of My Own]
[Episode 25]
Sorry about that.
Sorry, it's a misunderstanding.
Just a misunderstanding.
Don't drink so much.
Qiqi, don't be angry.
We can talk it through at home.
Come.
What's your problem?
Let's go, Mengmeng.
- What's the matter?
- Mr. Jin, you're all right, yes?
Mr. Zhao, come. Let's drink.
- Let's go.
- Jin.
Let's drink some more.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
It's nothing. Come on.
What happened?
Last night, I took a look at his phone.
I saw a message about a karaoke room reservation for today.
So I asked him what he was doing today.
He said he was doing overtime in the office.
Clearly, he was lying to me.
I couldn't accept it...
and went looking for him.
What did he say then?
He said after his overtime work,
he went to accompany his client to the karaoke room.
What if what he said is true?
If it was true, you barging in like that would have embarrassed him
in front of the clients.
Mengmeng, but my intuition tells me differently.
I think He doesn't love me as much as he used to.
Look at you.
You're overthinking things, making yourself miserable.
The way Old He dotes on you is clear to all of us.
There, there. Stop crying.
Good girl.
Don't cry.
Let me ask you something.
If... he is indeed doing something behind your back,
will you forgive him or break up with him?
Is Old He really doing something behind my back?
Is he really cheating on me?
I'm saying if.
If.
If...
If it was you, what would you do?
I'd choose to break up.
Old He and I have been together for so many years.
It's not that easy to break up with him.
But he made such a huge mistake.
How do you expect to get along in the future?
No, Old He couldn't possibly have cheated.
If... If I were to break up with him,
I don't know if I could live on my own.
All right, don't cry.
I told you, it's just an "if,"
It was just a hypothesis.
Don't cry now.
[He Yueluan]
- Old He.
- Hello, Ning Meng.
Listen. Are you free tomorrow night?
I have to be.
I specifically made sure to keep tomorrow night free
so as to celebrate You Qi's birthday.
That's great.
Tomorrow, I plan to celebrate Qiqi's birthday with her.
With you there, I hope you can coax her for me.
She's been angry with me ever since the incident that day.
She wouldn't let me explain.
I'm hoping to use this chance to apologize to her.
You two do need a proper chat.
You Qi has been moody lately.
I know.
I'll send you the details for the reservation.
See you tomorrow night.
Okay, see you.
Hello, Senior.
Mengmeng, are you free tomorrow?
Tomorrow is You Qi's birthday.
Old He and I are planning a birthday celebration.
I mentioned to you that they weren't on good terms.
He wants to take this opportunity to apologize to her
and talk to her properly.
I won't intrude then.
Help me to wish You Qi a happy birthday.
Will do.
I thank you on her behalf.
Okay, bye-bye.
Ning Meng.
What a coincidence.
How have you been, my friend?
I've been good, my friend.
What's up with the weird speech?
So awkward.
Mengmeng!
Hello.
Mengmeng.
Ning Meng.
Mengmeng, is he your former boss, Mr. Lu?
This is my good friend, You Qi.
Hello.
This is her boyfriend, He Yueluan.
Nice to meet you.
I'm He Yueluan of Renning Insurance.
Hello.
We'll go to our room first.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Okay, let's go.
It's my friend's birthday today.
Mr. Lu, is everything fine with Qinhe?
So far so good.
Is Mr. Lu doing well?
He's well.
Don't keep your friends waiting. Go ahead.
Let's eat together some other time.
Okay, see you.
Bye-bye.
Why did you talk to Ning Meng so weirdly?
What's your relationship right now?
You heard us, right?
We're friends.
Sure. It's good to be friends.
Anyway, what about the thing I asked you to find out?
Right now, Lu Guoyu is out of options.
Looks like your dad is about to win this equity war.
I must say, the older, the wiser.
Fortunately, your dad approached Shuangxun to be his guarantor.
But it's not Lu Guoyu
that I'm actually worried about.
It's Shuangxun.
But your dad approached Shuangxun, didn't he?
Think about it.
If it was only to keep Lu Guoyu in check,
why did they have to buy so many stocks?
This matter isn't as simple.
But there's no point in worrying.
The only thing we can do now is to be alert.
Keep a close watch on the situation.
Okay, let's order food. I'm hungry.
[Happiness]
Take a look.
Didn't you say you wanted a new camera?
Thanks, Mengmeng.
It better not be a short-lived passion.
Mengmeng always treats me the best.
Of course.
Dear, I also got you a present.
Do you like it?
I'm sorry.
I was wrong. I shouldn't have reacted like that.
Don't be angry, okay?
You lashed out at me in front of everyone that day.
Yes, I acted too rashly.
Those were my clients.
It was an important occasion.
Please understand.
That Chen Xiaoyi. Who is she to you?
She is nobody to me.
She's just a colleague.
You dare swear on it?
Why wouldn't I?
Tell me. I'm okay with any detrimental curse.
Forget it. I'm not that childish.
So you're no longer angry, right?
Let me put it on for you.
It's lovely.
It would be even more lovely if the person smiled.
It's nice even if I'm not smiling.
There, it's beautiful.
Listen. This friend of mine has the mental age of a three-year-old.
Five at most.
You must take good care of her. Don't bully her.
If you dare bully her, I'll make you pay.
Don't worry.
I'm grateful if Qiqi isn't bullying me instead.
You should count yourself lucky to have me bully you.
Back then, many men dreamed of having me bully them.
But I picked you.
Yes, I sure am lucky.
Come, have tea in place of wine.
- Wishing Qiqi a happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
What's wrong with you? Your heart's not in it.
I'm tired. Let's take a break.
[Shuangxun continues to buy up Qinhe stocks and has become the biggest shareholder!]
What's the matter?
The thing I was worried about happened.
"Shuangxun buys more than 20% of Qinhe's stocks."
What's going on?
Shuangxun agreeing to work with my dad was a mere ruse.
Their real goal is to acquire the ownership of Qinhe.
Shuangxun is already the biggest shareholder.
Once their share reaches 30%, it will trigger a tender offer.
What are you going to do?
Help me gather the stocks.
I'll take care of the funding.
I have to take back more stocks.
How many are you talking about?
I calculated. From the secondary market,
I should be able to acquire 2% of the stocks.
Do you have the money for it?
2% isn't a small sum.
Don't tell me you're going to liquidate your assets.
I still have a private placement stock in hand.
Its performance is looking favorable.
If I sell it off, I should be able to make up the financial leverage.
The old man is feeling the heat.
I have to help him.
With his ailing health,
I worry he might not be able to take the toll.
Even if you get the 2%, what about the rest?
Don't worry. I have a plan.
[Shuangxun becomes Qinhe's biggest shareholder. Qinhe may lose control over the company!]
Hello, Mr. Lu.
Can you help me set up a time with Mr. He?
- You wish to meet with He Yueluan?
- Yes.
[Joint Capital]
You must have heard about Shuangxun.
This is how it all started.
My dad wanted to get a big shareholder to keep Lu Guoyu in check.
But he never thought Shuangxun would betray his trust.
They did not stop when they were supposed to.
Of course, this is what my dad thinks.
From my point of view,
Shuangxun's intention was never good, to begin with.
Their real motive was to acquire Qinhe.
I believe that at this time,
he would have more reasons not to stop.
They will continue to accumulate stocks.
Because they know. Once their share reaches 30%,
a tender offer will be triggered.
When that happens, they will decide what happens to Qinhe.
But it looks like Shuangxun's arrow is reaching the end of its flight.
Lately, their rate of stock acquisition is very slow.
It has almost stopped.
I'm guessing they're running out of capital.
And judging from their method of acquisition,
their capital is heavily reliant on leverage.
They're already deep in debt.
Doing this is risky.
One slight mistake and that could be the end of them.
Is it worth it for Shuangxun to take such a risk?
The investment market is never short on careerists.
As long as they're able to acquire Qinhe,
the profit would be ten times what they have now.
You asked me to set a meeting with He Yueluan.
Is it to discuss taking a concerted action?
So far, Shuangxun had made four acquisitions.
Their share is now at 22 percent.
My dad and the other Qinhe executives only have 21 percent.
Adding that to the 2% I purchased,
that makes 23% in total.
So you need another seven percent.
And it so happens that He Yueluan's Renning Insurance has that seven percent.
If Qinhe can come to an agreement with Renning Insurance
for a concerted action, the share ratio will then reach 30%.
So Qinhe must get Renning Insurance on their side.
My dad has been down on himself lately.
He feels like he let Qinhe down.
So, no matter what,
I have to help him get over this hurdle.
Is Mr. Lu all right?
He's fine for now.
He's hanging in there on a sliver of hope.
From what I know,
Mr. Lu should be acquainted with their management.
Why didn't he look for them?
Just recently, Renning had an internal restructuring. Right?
My dad's old acquaintances have all been replaced.
One more thing. I will be telling my senior about this.
But I won't go into the details.
Got it, my friend.
I'll be off then.
See you, my friend.
I disagree.
Did you think that was how I'd react?
Don't joke, please.
Although I know that this man named Lu Jiming covets my girlfriend,
I will remain professional.
You have my support on this matter.
He is your ex-boss after all.
You should help him out.
Your boyfriend isn't that petty.
Not only are you not petty, but you're also of exemplary conduct.
- That description is a little...
- Here.
Is this all the reward I'm getting?
You deserve it.
All right.
Coming.
Mengmeng, did you just finish work?
Yes.
You haven't eaten, have you?
I already have.
But I cooked the food today.
- You cooked?
- Yes.
Chopsticks. Try it.
You can give me some feedback.
Gosh. The sun must have risen from the west today.
You Qi actually cooked.
She's been cooking these past two days.
Take the tomato egg stir fry as an example. It tastes different every time.
It's because I want to practice more.
Try the one I made today. I think it's better than the one I made yesterday.
- Tastes pretty good.
- There's an improvement.
I told you. I can definitely master cooking.
Is it not good?
No, not at all. It's very good.
The reason I came today is to ask Old He for a favor.
No problem.
Wait! She hasn't said what it is yet.
No matter what it is, as long as Mengmeng asked, you ought to help.
Here's the thing. See, a friend of mine...
You guys met him. It was the guy we met at the restaurant on You Qi's birthday, Mr. Lu Jiming.
Mr. Lu, I remember.
He'd like to meet you.
I'm sure you've heard about what's happening with Shuangxun and Qinhe.
Yes, I have.
Our company has stocks in Qinhe.
I couldn't avoid it even if I tried.
Qinhe's boss is Mr. Lu's father.
You know the dire situation Qinhe is in.
Mr. Lu would like to talk to you to see if it's possible to work with Renning.
Old He, set up a time to meet him then.
Okay. I'll ask the secretary to make an appointment to meet up.
That's great. Thanks, Old He.
So you're saying, you hope Renning Insurance and Qinhe
could reach a concerted action. Right?
Yes. I came today hoping to come to an agreement.
Mr. He, if you have any doubts, do voice them.
Since you are Ning Meng's friend, I'll be straight with you.
Actually, before you came to look for me,
Shuangxun had contacted our company.
It was expected.
If we were able to think of this, I'm sure they could too.
Looks like Mr. Lu does know Shuangxun very well.
I won't beat around the bush then.
Before you came,
I had a meeting with the company's executives and the board of directors.
On the matter of a concerted action with Qinhe, everyone
is in favor of it.
After all, Qinhe is a well-qualified company.
Mr. Lu Senior had contributed a lot to the environmental business over the years.
It's well known in the industry.
Be it sentiment or reason, I am more than happy to help.
Thank you, on behalf of my father.
We're grateful to you for making the right decision.
Mr. Lu, you're being too polite.
You and Ning Meng are good friends.
And Ning Meng and my girlfriend have been best friends forever.
As such, our relationship is much closer than normal.
Besides, on a personal note,
it's my honor to be able to help Mr. Lu Senior.
Well then, Mr. He, when do you think we could sign the contract?
Here's the thing, Mr. Lu.
We are a large company.
Our internal structure is more complicated.
Our headquarters are not in Shanghai but in Shenzhen.
So, it's going to take a while to go through due process.
But rest assured.
Let Mr. Lu Senior know not to fret, too.
I will make sure the headquarters processes this matter quickly.
Okay.
I'll be waiting for your news then.
- I'll let you know.
- Okay.
Excuse me, Mr. He. Sorry to interrupt.
There are some urgent documents that require your signature.
Let's dismiss for today.
Okay, you go ahead. I'll be off.
- I won't see you out then.
- No need.
Thanks, Old He.
Hopefully, everything goes well.
Yeah.
Mr. Lu, you go ahead.
I need the restroom.
- Okay.
- See you.
I know you.
You are Mr. He's girlfriend's best friend, right?
Yes.
Is Mr. He's girlfriend doing okay?
She's good.
He apologized to her for what happened that time.
Mr. He sure has a good temper.
He was able to keep his cool
when dealing with such an immature girlfriend.
Outsiders shouldn't butt in a couple's affairs.
But I've been there throughout their relationship.
They've been together since university.
They witnessed each other's graduation and stepping into adulthood.
After they graduated, they put each other in their future plans.
They struggled together in Shenzhen and Shanghai.
Such a relationship really is hard to come by.
Don't you think so?
Is it?
A deep relationship can't be explained in a few words.
Is Mr. Lu not doing very well?
Yeah.
Being in that situation has to be tough.
Senior, where are we going?
You'll find out soon.
You're so mysterious.
Could it be a surprise?
Sorry. Let me get the call.
Hello?
- Hello, Mr. Su.
- Mr. Zhai.
About the bond issuance, I haven't had a chance to thank you.
I'll send you the thank you gift tomorrow.
You're too kind, Mr. Zhai.
I'm driving right now. It's inconvenient to talk.
I'll get back to you later.
Okay. That's good.
Bye.
I helped out a friend, so he wants to thank me.
This friend of mine loves giving local specialties to others.
What local specialty?
He is from Zhoushan. So it's mostly sea produce.
When I get it, I'll cook it for you.
Well? Do you like this surprise?
It's just been renovated.
Is this your new house?
Why didn't you tell me? I didn't bring a housewarming gift.
What gift?
You're no outsider.
Besides, this house has everything.
Aside from a lady boss.
Looks more like you're looking for free labor.
This house is so big.
It would be exhausting to clean it.
I still prefer my little abode.
It's easy and quick to clean.
And it's near my workplace.
Why worry about that? There's the house cleaning service.
I should serve you first.
Let me get you some water.
This house must be very expensive.
Is the loan repayment stressful?
I paid in full.
Don't look so surprised.
In a few years, you'd be able to afford one too.
Have some wine.
It will be late when we finish the movie.
How about you just stay the night?
I can't. I promised You Qi today to do yoga with her.
Maybe next time.
Then after we finish the movie, we can get a designated driver.
I'll see you home.
Ms. Shi, don't you have a strategic planning meeting this afternoon?
It's been canceled.
Mr. Lu couldn't make it.
Recently, Mr. Lu must be deeply troubled.
I reckon the profit this year won't be too good.
Why?
He has a private placement stock in new energy vehicles.
Its ban is about to be lifted.
Recently, it's been plagued by negative press.
The stock keeps falling.
There's no guarantee it would bounce back.
I'll go and check on him soon.
Hopefully, he'll get through it.
I'm going to get changed.
Hello.
Ning Meng, any update from Renning Insurance?
I asked Old He about it yesterday.
He said it was undergoing the process.
I see. Tell me once there's an update.
Old He, how are things with Lu Jiming?
When will the agreement be ready for signing?
Don't worry about it. It's going through the process.
But I've been keeping an eye on Shuangxun, too.
There hasn't been any movement.
They're probably at their wit's end.
This should buy us more time.
I know. But it's been a while.
And it's still undergoing the process.
Can't you speed things up a little?
Old He, just help bring it up again.
Easy for you to say. You think this is some simple matter?
The fact of the matter is, we're asking for a favor.
You can't expect me to push my superiors time and time again.
I understand.
Anyway, I'm counting on you, Old He.
Mengmeng, he couldn't do much because he was away.
But now, he'll put in more effort. Don't worry.
[He Yueluan said it was under process. But his superior has agreed.]
[It shouldn't be a problem. So he asks for your patience.]
Mingming, are the dishes today too bland and insipid?
I could ask the caretaker to cut some spiced beef.
It's okay, Madam Liu. The food is fine.
Is it because of my dad's high blood pressure?
That's right. It's a little high lately.
The doctor reminded us to keep the diet bland.
See the multigrain rice?
Dad.
- Let's eat.
Wait. What's up with you lately?
Why is it only vegetable dishes? I don't even see any oil droplets.
Also, look at the rice. And look at that.
Is this chicken feed?
It's not that bad. This is five-grain rice. It's good for you.
It's per the doctor's advice. You need a lighter diet. Eat more multigrains.
Is it too dry to swallow?
Oh, right.
I made Tremella soup. I'll get some for you two.
Dad, please have some.
Multigrain rice is good for your health.
Have you finished the supplements I got for you?
Not yet.
Did Shuangxun contact you again?
That Yan Shuangxun...
is a wolf.
An ungrateful traitor.
He should be ashamed to see me.
Honestly, we should have sensed something was up when they made
sweeping purchases of the stocks.
What is the point of saying this in hindsight?
I'm just making an objective analysis.
Dad.
The market now is way different from what you had back then.
The financial circle...
is much more complicated than before.
- When handling something, I think we ought to...
- That's enough.
You're in no position to teach me.
Dad, I think you need to be more patient.
It's normal for humans to make mistakes.
What's done is done.
If there's a problem, we'll just figure it out together.
Learn from it and don't make the same mistake again.
Lu Jiming, you helped me out with Qinhe.
So I'm supposed to sit here and listen to your lecture?
I haven't asked you yet.
Tell me honestly.
Where did you get the money to buy stocks?
It's from...
I had my ways.
Is the money clean?
How could you possibly get so much money?
Dad, regarding the money, there's no need to explain it to you.
No need?
Hold up. What's with your attitude?
You were just telling me to be patient. You were giving me an earful.
Now I ask you one thing and you lose your patience.
- No, Dad.
- I'm warning you.
Don't overestimate yourself.
Don't simply touch the money that shouldn't be touched.
Do you hear me?
Come on. You just won't listen to whatever I have to say. Is that it?
I was going to...
Forget it. Why did I fret about you?
Did I ask you to?
So long as you don't make trouble for me.
Eat your food with the soup.
And leave when you're finished.
You two...
What is the matter with you two?
Why can't you just get along?
Weren't you two talking?
Why did you butt heads again?
To be frank, your dad feels bad for troubling you.
He hasn't been eating and sleeping well these days.
So don't argue with him.
No, Madam Liu. I want to persuade him.
But what's the point? Would he listen?
His ego is too big and he can't let it go.
Your father just doesn't want to implicate you.
He doesn't want you to spend any more money.
Don't worry, Madam Liu.
I'll figure out what to do about the money.
Then, go and get your dad to come to eat.
He hasn't eaten yet.
Okay.
Hey. Once you get the bonus from the project,
you should listen to me and buy a car.
Taking the subway to get to and from work is too tiring.
It's fine. I'm used to it.
I almost forgot.
Your boyfriend can be your chauffeur.
No wonder you don't need a car. It's all good.
Sorry, excuse me.
How do I use WeChat Pay?
Click open and then pay.
Yes, click that.
Receive payment. There you go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I just returned from overseas.
I'm clueless about a lot of things.
Senior?
Ning Meng? You're Ning Meng, right?
Yes, I am. Long time no see.
[Frieda Restaurant]
You're so different from back when you were in university.
I almost couldn't recognize you.
And you've not changed much.
You're still as beautiful.
Thanks.
How long are you planning to stay this time?
I'm leaving tomorrow.
I was going to stay longer to keep my parents company.
But my child is abroad and is still young.
She fell ill after I left.
Her father isn't good at taking care of her.
What to do? My heart is with my girl.
Here, this is my daughter.
How adorable. She's like a doll.
You should have one of your own if you find her adorable.
With Weiran. You guys should have a baby, too.
You and Weiran are together, right?
That's good.
You had a crush on Weiran during your college days, right?
I remember he had a CD.
You gifted it to him, right?
- That... Well, I... Well...
- Don't misunderstand.
I am not implying anything else.
I just thought fate worked in mysterious ways.
At the time, Weiran mentioned you to me.
He said you were smart and could answer all sorts of questions.
It's not like I really could answer everything.
Ning Meng, Weiran went through a lot overseas.
It was tough on him.
As for me,
I feel bad about a lot of things.
Now that you two are together, I'm really glad.
I wish you two the best.
Thanks.
By the way, have you two ever quarreled?
No. Why?
It's nothing.
I just want to give you a gentle reminder.
If he gets angry in the future,
I hope you'll be understanding.
Give him some space.
Don't fight with him.
When he calms down, you can talk it through then.
This is because of me.
It's my fault.
Oh, I'm sorry.
My ride is here. I have to go.
If you need anything, you can contact me through WeChat.
Sure, I will.
Wishing you two happiness.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Bye, Senior.
This seafood was sent by my friend.
They're really fresh. Eat while they're still hot.
Let's have a clink first.
Try this one I made.
Okay.
It's good.
You're talented.
I bumped into someone today.
Who?
My senior sister.
TEAM CREDIT
♫ Is there a fable ♫
♫ That could predict when we meet? ♫
♫ Perhaps it's going to be a sight ♫
♫ If we could walk ahead of time ♫
♫ We refused to be defined, be discriminated ♫
♫ And be labeled ♫
♫ To be the best of me ♫
♫ To meet the best of you again ♫
♫ Every time I ever loved ♫
♫ No matter how reluctant you feel ♫
♫ You have to bid farewell when the time comes ♫
♫ Fallen leaves, fall in love ♫
♫ Watching the fallen leaves, listening to the wind ♫
♫ Saying that all colors have luster ♫
♫ Don't want to be bullied, to be brushed off ♫
♫ And to be treated like a fool ♫
♫ Breaking through the laws of the world ♫
♫ And reconnect with the sacred heart ♫
♫ Every time I ever loved ♫
♫ Every little thing we gain in life ♫
♫ Comes with huge obstacles ♫
♫ Fallen leaves, fall in love ♫
♫ There's no so-called happy ending ♫
♫ Just make your decision with bravery ♫