[Master Of My Own]
My surname is Ning. But you can call me Ning Meng.
I think money is something that you have to treat with respect.
[Three Years Ago]
It's not something superficial. Instead, it's quite noble.
The thing that matters is how we spend the money to maximize its value.
A career in investment can better help me spend my money on something worthy.
And that drives me to work harder.
Mr. Liu?
What's wrong?
Mr. Lu is on an international call. He needs a secretary to take notes for him.
The last one was fired, right?
Mr. Lu is furious now.
Go through the interviewees for today.
Find out who has passed TEM-8.
You too.
Hurry up.
She can do it.
Hurry up. Let's go.
With the massive market, its talents pool,
and highly efficient capital market, we believe that China
is absolutely the right choice.
Great.
I look forward to our collaboration.
Thank you for your time.
Sure. Goodbye.
Have you noted down everything?
Almost.
He has such a heavy Southeast Asian accent, but you managed to note down everything.
I noted them down by sections.
The core is made up of three sections.
Internet, AI, and global+ trends.
You are quite smart.
What is your name?
Ning Meng.
- As a secretary?
- Yes.
You were chosen by Mr. Lu.
Mr. Liu, today is April Fool's Day.
Are you joking with me?
Ning, don't underestimate this position.
Mr. Lu has high standards.
Not everyone can work as his secretary.
Before you, no one could handle the position.
You are the first one who was chosen by Mr. Lu.
But I applied for the Project Department.
Don't be so block-headed.
This is a once in a blue moon opportunity for you.
Have you seen any newbies who worked straight with the number one on the first day of work?
Those newbies will just start with the basics.
- But you'll be learning from the best.
- Yes.
I understand your concern.
After you enter the company, you can still change your position.
I've already come to an agreement with Mr. Lu.
When we find a more suitable candidate,
we'll transfer you to the Project Department right away.
What if you can't find a suitable candidate?
Three years maximum.
After three years, I can be transferred to another position no matter what?
Mr. Liu. Mr. Liu. Have you found a new secretary?
It's too soon. Don't be anxious.
You should gain more experience first.
Wu, I need to talk to you.
This is not the right attitude.
Mr. Liu, it has been more than a year.
You haven't found a suitable secretary to take over?
It's not that easy to find the perfect secretary.
Hang in there, Ning. I'm already working on it.
If...
I think I remember someone. Take this.
Let me think.
Bye, Mr. Liu.
Mr. Liu.
About my transfer.
I'm still looking for a suitable candidate, Ning Meng.
You've already survived for two years.
Wait a little longer. It'll be soon.
- Mr. Liu.
- The elevator is here.
- Hu.
- Mr. Liu.
Let's go.
We agreed to three years.
Now, you want me to work for three more years?
Mr. Liu.
I didn't get to choose in the past.
Now, I want to be an investor!
Sure.
Tell Mr. Lu about it.
Let's see if he'll give you that chance or not!
[Episode 2]
[Joint Capital]
- Good morning.
Mr. Liu.
- What are you looking at?
- Mr. Liu.
Come on, let's talk.
Ms. Ning, you are such a prestigious person.
Mr. Lu called me at three in the morning and asked me to prepare the contract for your renewal.
Three in the morning.
I didn't sleep at all after that.
Let me tell you. Look at this industry.
How many bosses think so highly of their secretaries?
You need to cherish this blessing of having a boss like Mr. Lu.
After you renew your contract, not only will your salary go up two grades,
but Mr. Lu has also taken the initiative to grant you an annual leave which is unprecedented.
Ten days.
Even I am envious of you.
Mr. Liu.
I already told you before this that my target is the Project Department.
On the first of April three years ago, you sat over there and I sat over here.
You personally promised me that this position as a secretary was just temporary.
Are three years not enough?
Do I have to continue for three more years?
Ning, about this...
You can blame me for it.
But you know about his temper, too.
How about this?
Let's think about it in the long run, right?
You just want to be transferred, right?
Let's use our time in exchange for an opening.
You've repeated the same thing too many times.
Ning.
Can't you be our savior?
Stop making a fuss about this.
Mr. Lu will lose his temper at any time.
Everyone in the company
is terrified of him.
You are different.
You can even withstand a missile.
Let me tell you. Like this.
Take this contract for your renewal with you first.
No need to reject my offer so quickly.
Think about it. Don't rush it.
Ning Meng.
Meng, come.
I heard that because of you, Mr. Lu called Mr. Liu in the middle of the night.
How did you make our two bosses lose sleep because of you?
Do you want me to give this fortune to you then?
I wouldn't dare to accept it.
Meng, I just happened to hear it when I passed by just now.
I didn't eavesdrop on purpose.
I heard that Mr. Liu is going to give you a 10-day annual leave. Is it true?
The 10-day leave is real.
But only if Mr. Lu can make do with me.
Even a 10-hour-leave is already a luxury. Let alone 10 days.
What are you going to do then? Aren't you going to renew your contract?
I still want to get a job transfer.
I need to talk to Mr. Lu about it again.
Ms. Xu.
The life of this princess is indeed different from ours.
I just saw that dress on a fashion public account yesterday.
And she's already wearing it today.
- Good day, Ms. Xu.
She's here to pester Mr. Lu again.
Meng, we'll have to step away for now.
Okay.
Deliver it to me after you sign it. That's it.
Mingming.
Why are you here?
Can't I be here?
Are you using perfume as body shampoo?
The smell is choking me.
Don't be like that.
This is a customized perfume from Creed.
It has woody and floral notes to it.
- First, you'll get the smell of Iris.
- Stop.
- Then...
- I'm not interested in any of that.
Another thing. If it's not something important, don't always come to my company.
Who says I'm not here for something important?
I'm here today to introduce an important guest to you.
Shi Ying.
Shi Ying from Eaglestone Capital?
- You met each other at the award ceremony yesterday, right?
- Yes.
She and I studied for the Executive Master of Business Administration together. We are close.
I'm sure you know how capable she is.
Yes. She's quite capable.
From a Sponsor Representative to an investor. And she managed to build her company in a few short years. She's not bad.
So, I brought her with me to see if there are any chances for you to collaborate in the future.
If you really become partners, you have to thank me.
It'll be good if we can collaborate.
Thank you in advance then, Ms. Xu.
You are welcome.
What time will Ms. Shi be here?
Around 20 to 30 minutes. There's a traffic jam.
You always do sneak attacks.
Mingming, I saw an internet-famous cafe that day.
Its interior design is so cute. Look.
- There's a panda...
- Ning Meng, come to my office.
- Mr. Lu.
- Please go down to escort Ms. Shi up.
Ms. Shi from Eaglestone Capital. Do you know her?
She's still stuck in the traffic jam, right? Why did you ask her to go down now?
Go and clean up the conference room then. We'll use it for briefing later.
Am I right, Mingming?
Why are you still standing there? Go now.
Hey. You don't even hesitate to order my employee around.
Well...
We are so close. What is yours is mine.
Don't simply touch me.
Don't cross the line.
Good day, Ms. Shi. I am Mr. Lu's secretary, Ning Meng.
So, you are Mr. Lu's secretary?
Thank you for yesterday.
You are welcome. This way, please.
I watched your interview before.
You taught us a lot of new concepts from the perspective of a female investor.
Especially the part about the industrial mindset.
It was so interesting.
Thank you. You are quite attentive.
What did you study?
Finance.
Not bad.
This way, please.
I'm more interested in new retailing as well as technology and lifestyle projects.
So, I'm here today to hear about your investment framework.
Let's see if we can collaborate.
Ms. Shi, you are too humble.
I have some projects with good potential, too.
I would like to hear about your suggestions about them.
I'm sure you don't need my suggestions, but I'm quite interested in those projects.
Ning Meng, bring Ren Pengfei and Qiu Junlin here.
Ask them to introduce the projects to Ms. Shi.
Mr. Lu, Mr. Ren and Mr. Qiu are having a meeting outside right now.
They'll only be back in the afternoon.
Ren Pengfei does need to attend a meeting.
What about Qiu Junlin? What is he doing?
How about I give him a call?
Shi Ying's time is precious.
Mr. Lu, how about letting me do the briefing?
Isn't there anyone else in the Project Department?
How can you let a secretary do the briefing?
Ms. Xu, I'll go through each and every one of the company's projects.
I know the progress, process, and non-disclosure agreement of every project.
It's okay. I'm here today just to find out about the overall investments.
You can do the briefing then, Ms. Ning.
Do it then.
Ms. Shi, let me first tell you about the strong points of our company's strategy.
The goal of our company is not only about investing in a profitable business.
We also hope that we can shape our future lifestyle through the creativity of the people.
That's not important information.
Tell her something specific about the projects.
Okay.
Let me talk about our latest project then. Kirin's Furniture.
Its main concept is to build an environmentally friendly home.
Environmentally friendly home?
Kirin's Furniture has a unique concept.
Wood is a living thing.
Through sustainable felling, the low-carbon production process,
and the advantage of being easy to recycle and reuse, we'll maximize the preservation of the original wood.
It also reflects the concept of even being eco-friendly.
We can showcase the value of traditional handicrafts through modern design.
As the angel investor, Joint Capital is now helping the corporation
to proceed into the venture capital stage.
So, now is the best time for you to put in your investment.
[Project Report on Kirin's Furniture]
This is the main project of Joint Capital now.
Mr. Lu, Ms. Ning has done a professional briefing.
From the features of the product to business logic,
she has explained them very clearly.
You have a hidden talent here.
You are too kind, Ms. Shi.
Ning Meng, hurry up and fill up our cups.
Ms. Ning, you are very observant.
How did you find out?
Although a right-hander will sometimes use their left hand,
I saw you using your left hand to take your phone and bag and make hand gestures.
So, I thought you were a left-hander.
You have a bright mind and you are meticulous.
You have the talent to take on a project.
Ms. Shi, she and money don't go together.
According to you, our company has many hidden talents.
We don't need her.
Yes.
Everyone in the Joint Capital graduated from top universities.
But I really think that she's a talent.
Mr. Lu, you should consider grooming her to become a great investor.
- Are you trying to steal my employee?
- Of course not.
Mr. Lu, how can she be that important?
If you lose her, I can take her place.
I wouldn't dare to trouble you to do these menial chores, Ms. Xu.
I can't see you pouring drinks for others.
Ms. Shi, the new samples of Kirin's Furniture will be out next week.
When the time comes, we can take a look at them together.
Make sure to contact me at once.
I really can't wait to collaborate with you.
Me too.
If you manage to collaborate, don't forget about me.
Make sure to treat me to a feast.
Of course.
Do you hear that, Mingming?
Okay, I promise you.
Okay. Farewell, Ms. Shi.
Come in.
Mr. Lu.
I didn't ask you to come in, right?
- It's about my transfer. I want to...
- The benefits that I'm giving you
are already the best compared to the others in the same position.
If there's anything that you are not satisfied with, you better make sure that you have the capabilities to match.
Or else, I don't have the time to listen to you crying for the moon.
I'm very thankful to you for the increment and benefits.
But I haven't even given it a try. How can you say that I'm crying for the moon?
You know who Zhao Kuo of the Warring States period is, right?
It's such an easy idiom.
You just have to say that it's just empty talk.
No need to use an allusion.
You did well for the briefing.
But handling a project and doing a briefing are two different things.
The capabilities that you had shown me could not convince me. Understand?
But if I just make coffee every day, then I can only show you my capabilities in making coffee.
Come in.
Mr. Lu, I heard that you were looking for me just now.
You know that, too? I was looking for you just now.
What's the point of being here right now?
I'm sorry.
When I didn't want to see you in the past, you were always around.
But when I need you, I can't find any of you.
In the end, a secretary had to do the briefing.
Others will think that our company is just a joke.
Do you know that?
- This morning, I went...
- Shut up.
You can't even give me a good reason. Stop stuttering.
I'm talking to you. Why are you looking at her?
Enough. No need to say anything more. Get out.
Now.
As for you, you should stop dreaming about becoming an investor.
Get back to your work.
Mr. Lu.
Hello? Mr. Tang, we've already gone through the contract.
When you come to the company tomorrow, we can officially sign the contract.
Yes.
Okay.
Ning Meng.
Mr. Qiu.
Ms. Ning.
Yesterday, when Mr. Ren made such a huge
mistake, you saved him at once.
Why didn't you save me today?
Where were you? It would be fine if you were here.
Is that any of your business?
By the way, thank you for doing the briefing for me.
Mr. Qiu.
Why is he mocking you again?
We just help them out of our kindness, but we don't have to.
Why does he always act like we owe him? So annoying.
This has nothing to do with him.
Is it because Mr. Lu refused to transfer you?
Meng, I support you in making the switch.
It's not easy for us to work for the investors.
If we don't take the risk while we are young,
it'll be even harder for us to make the switch after this. Right?
Exactly.
Hello. Here's the menu.
Limoncello. Thank you.
Okay. Please wait for a while.
Hello. Here's your drink.
Thank you.
[Lu XX]
- Mr. Lu.
- Ms. Ning, right?
I am Lu Jiming's friend.
Mr. Lu is drunk.
Please come to the whisky bar on Jing'an Road to pick him up.
- Now?
- Yes. Hurry up.
He keeps asking for his secretary to pick him up.
- Come on, let's continue to drink.
- Hurry up and come here. We can't take care of him anymore.
[HOUSE OF CARDS]
Ms. Ning? Mr. Lu is drunk.
Mr. Lu, let's go back now.
She is my secretary, Sour Orange.
Later, no need to call for a cab.
I'll ask my secretary to drive you home one by one.
It's okay. It's okay.
- He is drunk.
You just have to take care of him.
Okay.
Excuse me. We'll leave now.
Let's go. Let's go home.
Get up.
Please give me his phone.
- Here. Take it.
- Thank you.
Enjoy yourselves.
Be careful.
Don't vomit.
Swallow it back.
Let's go.
- Bye.
- Will you be okay?
- Yes.
- Take good care of him.
Mr. Lu, I need to discuss something with you.
No problem.
If you are drunk next time, can you ask Song to pick you up?
No. Song is dirty.
He dirtied the carpet of my house.
You know that, too.
All the bosses with bad habits are spoiled by obedient subordinates.
What did you say?
Why did I pay for your driving lessons?
You can enter my house because I give you my trust
that others don't have.
You should feel honored.
My foot.
You can still critique me. Looks like you are not drunk enough.
I'm not drunk.
I can still drink.
We don't have any projects that are so vital.
Why did you drink so much?
Because those people from Yunshang Capital kept asking me to drink.
As if I couldn't hold my liquor well.
So, of course, I couldn't lose.
Do you think you won?
You are drunk most of the time.
I wonder who the fool is.
Sour Orange.
Do you think that I won't remember what you said when tomorrow comes?
Let me tell you. I'll remember everything.
I'll teach you a lesson tomorrow.
You won't remember.
Why did you open the window? It's cold.
I don't want you to feel stuffy and puke inside the car.
I'll feel disgusted about it even if you don't.
♪ Where did the time go? ♪
How dare you ask me about that? I've wasted all of my time on you.
♪ I've gotten old before I get to enjoy my youth ♪
♪ Having children and raising them ♪
♪ My whole life ♪
Enough. Stop.
When you sang like this last time, someone reported you
that you were killing pigs in the middle of the night disturbing the people.
Who?
Where can we find a pig to kill in the middle of the night?
What a joke.
Sour Orange, listen to me.
You just have to keep working for me as my secretary.
Look. I've given you so many amazing benefits.
Where else can you find a boss like me?
You should be grateful
for my trust in you.
Do you feel honored?
Sour Orange, are you trying to kill me?
Your leg.
Ning Meng, isn't it great to be my secretary?
As if.
He has fallen asleep so quickly.
He's like an animal.
Are you a pig?
[Mom]
Mengmeng.
Why didn't you call us in the past few days?
Are you very busy?
Make sure you take care of your health.
If you are free tomorrow, message your mother.
She's worried about you because you've been quiet.
If you have any work issues,
you can tell me about them.
If you have any romance issues,
tell your mother about them.
Our family is offering a full package.
[Mr. Liu (Liu Yitian)]
Ning Meng. Everything is okay, right?
Don't forget to sign the contract and give it back to me tomorrow.
Check your e-mails, too.
Arrange Mr. Lu's next week's business trip schedule for him.
Remember to arrange the hotel and transport beforehand. Okay?
[Renewal of Employment Contract]
[Year 2000]
Dad, is there anything different about this battery?
Let me tell you.
This is a rechargeable battery.
For a normal battery, it can't be used anymore once it runs out of energy.
But for this rechargeable battery, after it runs out of energy,
you can reuse it after you charge it.
Not only can it reduce environmental pollution,
but it can also save more energy, too.
One is a disposable battery.
The other one is a battery that can be reused.
Is it like the difference between toilet paper and a handkerchief?
Yes. Mengmeng, you are so smart.
Dad, you have to make a lot of batteries like this
so that everyone can use them.
It's not easy to make a lot of batteries.
I need help.
I can help you.
The friend that I'm looking for is called an "investor."
What is an investor?
You'll know when you grow up.
Come on, let's continue to exercise.
[Three months later]
You said that you had a deal.
You had a deal, right?
I support you.
Or else, I wouldn't take out all of my money
so that you could collaborate with him. Right?
We had a deal.
I don't know why he suddenly pulled out.
If you don't know, go and ask him.
Come up with a solution.
But he won't pick up my call now.
I can't get in touch with him.
Mengmeng, you are back.
Dad, you made so many batteries? Amazing.
Mengmeng, go into your room to do your homework first.
I'll call you when the food is ready.
Why didn't you think about us?
We spent all of our money on them.
We need money to send her to school.
Can you stop?
This is my fault. I'll think of a way.
Worse comes to worst, I'll go out and sell the batteries.
I'll find a job to pay off the debt.
I won't make it difficult for you and our daughter.
[Property Ownership Certificate]
Use it to pay off the debt.
We'll shoulder the burden together.
♫ Is there a fable ♫
♫ That could predict when we meet? ♫
In the evening of the Autumn of 2000,
our family business failed.
But I think from then onward,
I started to have a fuzzy but determined mindset towards investment.
If I meet a determined entrepreneur like my father one day
as an investor, I'll invest in him.
I don't want the wings
of those invaluable entrepreneurs to be clipped again.
♫ To meet the best of you again ♫
♫ Every time I ever loved ♫
♫ No matter how reluctant you feel ♫
♫ You have to bid farewell when the time comes ♫
♫ Don't want to be bullied, to be brushed off ♫
♫ And to be treated like a fool ♫
[Letter of Resignation]
♫ Breaking through the laws of the world ♫
♫ And reconnect with the sacred heart ♫
♫ Every time I ever loved ♫
♫ Every little thing we gain in life ♫
♫ Comes with huge obstacles ♫
♫ Fallen leaves, fall in love ♫
♫ There's no so-called happy ending ♫
♫ Just make your decision with bravery ♫
- Good day, Mr. Lu.
- Good morning.
Mr. Lu.
Qingzhu Hotel has passed the second round of the Term Sheet.
We can officially proceed with the project next week.
- Next week? Okay, I'll take a look at it.
- Okay.
- Go.
- Good morning, Mr. Lu.
- Good morning.
Good morning, Mr. Lu.
- Good morning, Mr. Lu.
- Good morning, Liu.
Good morning.
Come in.
Coffee.
Mr. Lu, I've thought about it carefully.
I still want to get a job transfer.
We've already closed the topic, right?
You did, but I haven't.
In my career planning, I want to become the top investment director.
- Over the past...
- Ning Meng, when have you become so ambitious?
You are such a dreamer.
When you started your company,
what would you think if someone told you the same thing back then?
I think no one said that to me.
It has been three years. It's not a short time.
Back then, I was just a temporary secretary.
Why don't you find a more suitable secretary?
You are that secretary.
You have to know your worth.
You need to know where you stand. Understand?
Now, you have two choices.
You can be my secretary or you don't do anything at all.
You can go back now. Coffee.
I quit.
Thank you for the past three years.
I'll get going now.
[Letter of Resignation]
Meng, what's wrong? Why are you packing your things?
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
No. Why are you packing your things if it's nothing?
What happened?
Meng, talk to me. What happened?
- Feng.
- Mr. Zeng.
Ask Song to go to my car to bring up the rest of the crabs.
- Okay.
- One for each.
Ning Meng.
What's wrong?
The crabs are cold.
Steam them for Mr. Lu to cool him down.
Mr. Zeng, it's not good timing for you to go in now.
It's always good timing when I'm here.
Mr. Lu?
Lu Mingming, I brought you some crabs! Is this how you welcome me?
Get lost.
♫ Is there a fable ♫
♫ That could predict when we meet? ♫
♫ Perhaps it's going to be a sight ♫
♫ If we could walk ahead of time ♫
♫ We refused to be defined, be discriminated ♫
♫ And be labeled ♫
♫ To be the best of me ♫
♫ To meet the best of you again ♫
♫ Every time I ever loved ♫
♫ No matter how reluctant you feel ♫
♫ You have to bid farewell when the time comes ♫
♫ Fallen leaves, fall in love ♫
♫ Watching the fallen leaves, listening to the wind ♫
♫ Saying that all colors have luster ♫
♫ Don't want to be bullied, to be brushed off ♫
♫ And to be treated like a fool ♫
♫ Breaking through the laws of the world ♫
♫ And reconnect with the sacred heart ♫
♫ Every time I ever loved ♫
♫ Every little thing we gain in life ♫
♫ Comes with huge obstacles ♫
♫ Fallen leaves, fall in love ♫
♫ There's no so-called happy ending ♫
♫ Just make your decision with bravery ♫