What if I do not mind dying?
Then can I hold onto it
and keep loving you?
I told you that
I am willing to risk it all
and that we are in this together.
I will keep going no matter what.
So you should do the same
and stick to your confession.
Keep loving me to death.
Mu-deok, you should not glare like that.
Nobody would believe your words
if you glare at me like that.
Then tell me, Young Master.
How should I look to convince people
that I love you to death?
Well, first of all…
Glaring at me like that
will definitely not do.
They say one's eyes would be
brimming with sweetness.
I guess that is not possible.
So why did you say you love me to death?
You should have said
you were mildly attracted to me instead.
Say that I do my best
to look at you with sweetness
and keep loving you to death.
What happens after that?
After?
Should I keep loving you blindly
while Maidservant Kim
desperately tries to marry you off?
What would happen to me then?
Do not worry.
I have no intention of marrying for now.
"No intention," my foot.
Is that not why you refused
to drink chaste herb tea?
So what you are asking me is
a promise of some sort?
If I am to stay in love with you,
I need to be certain that you are mine.
Let us not rush into things.
So you refuse.
Why is everything so dramatic with you?
I am just saying that
we cannot rush things right now.
I have to discuss it
with Maidservant Kim too.
Good grief.
Never mind then.
"Eyes brimming with sweetness," my foot.
I will just glare at you like a dog.
A dog?
That is right.
I forgot to tell you something important.
It was that dog.
What are you talking about?
The dog that was with Master Lee
at Danhyanggok. Do you remember?
Sapsali?
Yes.
That dog was Gwigu.
Master Lee knew that you were
a soul shifter from the beginning.
Perhaps,
he even knows you are Naksu.
What brings the leader of Jinyowon
to Songrim at this hour?
She must be here for you.
I heard that
you took Gwigu, a relic of Jinyowon,
to the palace today.
It was to find traces
of sorcery at the palace.
I warned you not to get Jinyowon involved
in any more soul shifter cases.
Why is Songrim using Jinyowon at will?
Mage families under the Unanimous Assembly
must strive to stop sorcery.
If Songrim is striving to do just that,
Jinyowon should offer their assistance.
Do you not think so?
So you mean you will use us again.
Then I will take Gwigu.
Hand it over to me.
Or should I look for it myself?
Gwigu is right here.
Gwigu was a relic created
by Master Seo Gyeong.
Therefore, it also belongs to Songrim.
Why would Jinyowon's relic
also belong to Songrim?
Are you saying Jinyowon is
some kind of storehouse for Songrim?
That is not what he meant.
You boldly assume everything
in Jinyowon is yours to take.
You take things without asking
and never return them.
That must be
how the people of Songrim are.
You said something similar before.
That a mage of Songrim had taken
something from Jinyowon.
Who was that mage?
He is right before my eyes.
The one who snuck into Jinyowon
and stole Gwigu.
How dare you call Master Lee a thief!
What else do you call someone who steals?
Mother, please.
It was Master Lee who moved Gwigu
from the broken pottery
into the body of that dog.
It was Songrim that broke the pottery.
How dare you!
It is dead, Master.
I was protecting my daughter.
Master Lee, did you command
Gwigu to attack us?
Gwigu attacked because it sensed sorcery.
Then that means
that the young lady had traces of sorcery.
It must have sensed the sorcery
of the worm that sucked her blood.
Young Lady Jin.
Have you ever
used sorcery?
Sorcery? That is preposterous!
If not,
why would Gwigu have attacked her?
Songrim must be trying
to frame my daughter.
Please stop!
Master Lee is right.
A while ago,
I did use sorcery.
But it was not meant to hurt anyone.
It is quite popular these days.
It is a Lovers' Charm.
It helps grant one's love.
I think it was because of that.
It seems our daughter has
caused a misunderstanding.
Our apologies.
You stayed alive in the body of this dog
but now you are gone.
Gwigu has now completely vanished.
What do I do?
Is it my fault that Gwigu died?
Cho-yeon!
How dare you disgrace Jinyowon?
Gwigu is dead?
Yes.
Master Lee said he will bury it
in the daylight tomorrow.
So this dog was Gwigu.
It must have known that
I was a soul shifter from the beginning.
But it never barked at me.
Was it covering for me too?
Even though it is dead, it is still Gwigu.
There might still be traces of its powers.
Do not touch it.
Did the people from Jinyowon leave?
They are discussing
another issue right now.
Another issue?
It turns out Dang-gu and Cho-yeon
were lovers.
-What?
I was the one who destroyed
a relic of Jinyowon
so Songrim is not at fault.
We shall now leave.
-Let us go.
-Yes.
Lady Jin.
Have some tea before you leave.
We should clear misunderstandings
and make meaningful bonds.
Make bonds?
These two are in love.
The charm that you took out before
was for Dang-gu, right?
Yes. I am the cause of all of this.
Cho-yeon did not do anything wrong.
Be quiet.
I found out recently too.
He was talking nonsense
about how they will be together
when your late daughter returns
so I reprimanded him.
My late daughter?
Bu-yeon is alive and we will find her.
Do you really believe
Jin Mu will find her?
You are being fooled by him.
Did Jin Mu give you the idea
to search all over Songrim
looking for Gwigu at this hour?
I told you not to meddle in our affairs.
Now, let us not fight.
It would be wonderful news
to find Bu-yeon.
Lady Jin does not want to
make enemies with Songrim either.
Let us be cordial as we were before.
Who knows?
Cho-yeon and Dang-gu
may unite the two families.
I respectfully decline.
Cho-yeon will have a better suitor.
Who is better than
the Park family of Songrim?
A daughter of the Jin family
is good enough to be
the bride of the Crown Prince.
Mother.
What are you saying?
I do not want to.
The Crown Prince is unkind.
-I do not like him.
-Cho-yeon.
I wish to marry the one I love.
Yes.
I am the one she loves.
Dang-gu!
We will talk at home.
Let go of his hand and follow me.
Let her go for now.
Let go of her hand so she can leave.
Let go of his hand.
Let go!
Cho-yeon.
If you wish to be so disobedient,
do not bother coming home.
I think it is best that we leave.
Will you not come home with us?
I will not obey Mother this time.
Please understand, Father.
I will send word
when your mother's anger subsides.
Please take care of her for a while.
I will.
Uncle, I apologize for the trouble.
But I will protect my lady.
Get out!
Where should we go now?
I do not know.
Since he told us to leave,
we could go to an inn and get…
-Get a room?
-Sorry?
That is not what I meant!
Not one room,
but separate rooms of course.
I do not like inns.
There is nowhere else to go for now.
And it is getting cold…
It is cold…
Where can we go?
Young Master Park!
They said Young Master Jang was released,
but he is not in his room.
Have you seen him?
Is there something wrong?
-Maidservant Kim…
-What?
Maidservant Kim.
Please let go, Young Master Park.
Young Lady Jin? What is going on?
Maidservant Kim…
Gwigu, which caused mayhem at the palace,
was destroyed by Lady Jin
as she was trying to retrieve it.
Gwigu was destroyed?
Why would she destroy something
that detects sorcery?
Detecting sorcery was just an excuse.
It was a relic that Songrim used
to threaten the royal family.
Jin Mu is right.
Songrim wanted to show off
that they were more powerful than us.
Under the guise of rooting out sorcery,
Songrim can mobilize
the mages of the Unanimous Assembly
and dethrone the king.
Is that why they mentioned
the King's Star?
To warn me that they could dethrone me?
The reason Master Lee mentioned
the King's Star was to explain
that someone like Master Seo Gyeong
will come to save us from troubled times.
It was not to threaten us.
What if the one that saves us
wants to rule us as well?
Do you think you can stop him?
Gwanju Jang Gang of Cheonbugwan
predicted that
the King's Star will appear.
Master Lee said that as well.
Does Songrim know this too?
He tried to sire a son with the energy of
the King's Star from his many concubines.
Now he is trying to find one in Songrim.
It is natural
for the King to be so threatened.
To the royal household of Go,
the existence of the King's Star
could signal treason.
"Treason"?
People of Daeho do believe in
and worship the heavens,
but a centuries-old monarchy
would not crumble so easily.
It is preposterous to think
that one can become king
because of some constellation.
If he is from Songrim, it is possible.
Master Seo Gyeong of Songrim
saved the world 200 years ago.
He is still revered within Daeho.
If someone was born under the King's Star
like Master Seo Gyeong,
it could make a convincing reason
to become a King.
So you think
the King's worries may come true?
Do not be concerned.
As long as I am here,
that will never happen.
Very well.
I will not be foolish like my father
and live under constant fear.
When I brought Gwigu to the palace,
I could see that you were right.
The Queen is on Jin Mu's side.
But we cannot provoke
the royal family just yet.
If Songrim tries
to take on the royal family,
Jin Mu will surely use
the circumstances of Uk's birth
and turn him into
the enemy of the royal family.
Then Songrim will become
an enemy of the royal family as well
for taking him in.
We need Jang Gang.
Jang Gang knows the truth.
He must know Jin Mu's weakness as well.
How can you find someone
who has been wandering for decades?
We will have to wait
until he returns of his own accord.
The rumors about soul shifters
have spread throughout Daeho Fortress.
If he hears the rumors, he will return,
fearing for Songrim and for his son.
I came because I was summoned.
Where is Master Lee?
He left for Danhyanggok at dawn
to bury Sapsali.
What?
He is not here? Was it not Master Lee
who summoned me?
He did summon you.
He told me to give this to you.
This is the assassin Naksu's sword
that he retrieved from the Crown Prince.
He said you are the only one
who can keep this sword
so he told me to give it to you.
He just left me this sword?
Did he not say anything else
before leaving?
He did not take you in as his pupil,
so I do not understand
why he is treating you fondly.
You will not even practice chastity.
I heard from Park Jin that
you are head over heels for a woman.
If you were in love with Mu-deok,
why did you lead on my Yun-ok?
-I never led her on.
-Did you not?
You charmed Yun-ok.
How did you manage to charm Master Lee?
I did not do anything.
Just because someone is being good to me,
does not mean I charmed them.
Be mindful of Yun-ok from now on
and be respectful to Master Lee.
Yes.
Master Lee is not close-minded
like other masters at Songrim.
He seems to be open-minded and gracious.
I respect him.
You have no idea how strict he can be.
He is merciless towards those who stray.
So you must always be careful.
Take it and be off.
I forgot.
I almost got in trouble again.
I was told to give you this message
when I gave you Naksu's sword.
Why would he give you my sword?
Because I have you,
I should have your sword too.
Anyway, this means
he will continue to turn a blind eye.
That is good.
I was told to give you this message.
Jang Uk must keep that sword safe.
If anyone tries to use the sword,
they must be killed.
If he fails to do so,
he will die as well.
It was a warning that he will kill us
if Mu-deok ever uses the sword
as the assassin, Naksu.
The sword feels strange,
even though it is mine.
He must have let me live
because he knows I cannot use it.
It means you will be safe as Mu-deok.
If I become Naksu, I will be in danger.
Once I find the ice stone
and regain my energy,
I will also gain many enemies.
What happens to me then
will have nothing to do with you.
Why?
Because we will no longer be
master and pupil?
You will no longer
have a reason to protect me.
Nor will I have a reason
to go easy on you.
That was our promise from the start.
Then promise me one more thing.
Out of duty and loyalty,
and also out of the so-called love,
you can grant me one more wish.
Fine. What is it?
When you regain your energy
and if you must draw
and point that sword at someone,
point it at me before at anyone else.
If you stab me,
then I will die as the one
who released the assassin.
If you withdraw your sword,
I will make you another promise.
Something along the lines of the promise
you wanted to hear
from me about our future.
I will look for the ice stone
so you do not run wild
because I promised to do so.
The runaway couple
is staying at my house.
Dang-gu is there?
Why did you take them in?
If not,
should I have left them to go into town
to build a lover's nest
and become the talk of the town?
I ask you to be discrete
and take good care of them.
They are a sweet couple.
Why are you so against it?
They cannot marry.
So you kicked them out?
My lord, you must stop
this habit of yours.
You held Mu-deok and Young Master Jang
for no reason the other night.
You must become more tolerant as you age.
Such a shame…
I like Mu-deok a lot.
I like Young Master Jang very much.
Maidservant Kim.
What would you do
if Uk falls in love
with a woman he should not,
like Dang-gu?
Would you be tolerant?
Whoever Young Master Jang loves
is fine with me.
-Is that right?
-Of course.
I am sure you will.
I know that you care about
birth, appearance, age, and much more.
The heart is the most important.
If you are in love,
appearances do not matter.
So what if she is not that beautiful,
or if they have a great age difference?
Is that how you feel too?
Is it?
Pardon?
Anyone who is not as handsome as Jang Gang
and is much older
would still have a chance
if your heart is moved?
Well…
If my heart is moved,
he would seem more handsome
and younger in my eyes.
I see, Maidservant Kim.
I understand what you mean.
Goodness, he was quite straightforward
when he asked how I felt about him.
What does he mean by not being handsome?
And he is only two years older than me.
He worries for no reason.
How can she say she likes Master Lee
so easily in front of me?
Is he handsome?
He is more than
a hundred years older than her.
Dang-gu…
You little brat!
Right now,
I wish I could have
the wine hidden in Uncle's room
instead of tea.
What? You already have regrets?
No way.
I believed I could give it all up.
That is why I took her hand that day.
I did not know
he would grab my hand so suddenly.
I was just upset that
they were talking about the Crown Prince.
All I said was that
I do not like the Crown Prince.
But he suddenly grabbed my hand
and said he loved me.
Move over a bit.
I could not just let go of his hand.
I was simply swept up in the moment.
I had no intention to run away from home.
How long will you be here?
I was told to serve you two
while you are here.
I have no idea.
I do not wish to stay here for long.
If I say we should go back home,
I would seem irresponsible, right?
If I say I want to go home,
it would break his heart, right?
-What do I do?
This is for the best.
Serving Young Lady Jin here
is better than
running into Park Jin at Songrim.
If So-i is responsible
for the murder case you are embroiled in,
then it is dangerous.
You may not know her,
but she knows who Mu-deok is.
Why is So-i going around killing people?
If the blind girl
these men were picking on
is the same girl the broker knew as So-i,
then she probably
could not have killed them herself.
She must have someone helping her.
If the authorities take these bodies,
they will catch the murderer.
Mu-deok would know about So-i.
We should send her
to help with the investigation.
She will not recognize So-i.
She is not the same Mu-deok
who lived in Sari Village.
She will be falsely accused and suffer.
I will ask her myself if necessary.
I do not think you need to step up.
Yul seems to be on top of it.
We will be in trouble if
the Assistant Gwanju hears you are out.
Everyone who recognizes me
has been killed.
I would have to walk outside
even after I get into Jinyowon.
I should practice
walking like a blind person.
You should buy what you want.
I gave you quite a bit of money.
Let us go back after a while.
Wait a minute.
Why are you using an umbrella
instead of a cane?
Do not touch it.
I prefer using this.
You did help prove my innocence.
I hope you will be comfortable
while you are here.
Does the Jang family always eat like this?
This is too greasy.
Yes, Young Lady.
I will prepare a different meal.
This is too salty!
-It is not salty.
-It is salty.
I get bloated when I eat salty foods.
Yes, Young Lady.
This is too hard.
This is too sweet.
What is this?
I am so worried I lost my appetite.
Why is she acting exactly like Uk?
I have no appetite.
Do you have something to drink?
Like cinnamon punch or rice punch?
They are perfect for each other.
Why call off the wedding?
If they got married,
one of them would have died in a fight.
Mu-deok, the rice punch is…
Is it sweet? And too cold?
Rice punch is supposed to be like that.
Why are you raising your voice?
Are you tired of serving me?
Then would you say you were easy to serve?
I get irritable when I am anxious.
It is uncomfortable not being at home.
Then go home.
No. I am too scared.
Mother is very angry with me.
Even for a daughter, you are a handful.
I was never her favorite.
My sister was her pride and joy.
Even though she was blind,
she could see energy and handle relics.
Even at a young age, her abilities
were as powerful as my mother's.
Well, I heard that the Jin family members
are born with more divine powers
than spell-related powers.
You saw me handle Gwigu, right?
It is like that.
A really powerful priestess
can control people's souls
and trap them to be helpless.
-Trap the soul?
-Yes.
If the priestess traps their powers,
even the most powerful mage is helpless.
I heard there are shamans
who can erase or change
memories of a soul.
A Jinyowon priestess is
in a different league.
How did such an amazing girl like her die?
Because she is that great.
She is definitely alive.
We will see her again.
If she is alive
I am sure you will.
Uncle looked into Mu-deok.
He asked the broker about her.
Did you know about that?
Yes. I heard from her.
He has become suspicious
because of the soul shifter incident.
You are right.
If there are soul shifters in the palace,
Songrim may have them too.
Why is the cast-out successor of Songrim
worrying about such a thing?
-I am not totally cast out.
-He is already regretting it.
Hey.
You were so confident yesterday.
Uk is the one who always gets kicked out.
What am I doing here?
You will get used to it.
It is quite miserable the first time.
Only Yul would have no idea how we feel.
What do you mean?
Yul has been kicked out too.
No way.
Do you remember the time
that I broke the gold-plated inkstone
and we all lied together?
Uncle will get so mad at me.
Let us hide it.
We will bury it
and pretend to know nothing about it.
That is not right.
We must tell the truth
and ask for forgiveness.
Then Dang-gu will get in
a lot of trouble with the leader.
I cannot tell a lie.
It is all right, Dang-gu.
I am sure there is a way.
Eventually the three of us
agreed to cover it up.
But Yul became ill afterward.
I think Yul is very ill.
I think so.
My goodness,
why is Yul so sick? What is wrong?
I heard he cannot eat or sleep well.
What is wrong?
Yul had never done anything wrong.
He got sick worrying we would get caught.
We ended up confessing
because we thought Yul would die.
We were all kicked out together.
I got kicked out so many times
so I do not remember everything.
But I doubt that Yul was sick
because he was afraid of being caught.
He suffered because he knew
what he was doing was wrong,
and that fact was hard for him to endure.
He is someone who gets lost
if he is caught off guard.
He must have been worried
and scared to do something
he knew was wrong
just to protect his friends.
Yes. I remember it clearly.
I suffered quite a bit.
To punish oneself more harshly
than others would.
Is it some sort of
a heightened state of morality?
Gosh, you were already there
at that young age?
That is incredible.
Can you imagine what I felt,
burying a broken inkstone
with my immature friends?
We could not even bury it well.
We were soon caught.
-What?
We were caught? You said we confessed.
Dang-gu is remembering it wrong.
We did not confess to it.
Sang-ho found the half-buried inkstone.
That is how we were caught.
Is that right?
I must have romanticized the memory.
I thought we did the honorable thing.
How embarrassing…
What are you embarrassed about?
You are currently a runaway.
Who will be the next leader
instead of Dang-gu?
Will it be Sang-ho?
Is that right?
I should get on his good side.
You two cannot discard me like this.
You should take my side like before.
Come on, Uk.
I will not be much help to you.
-Hey, Yul.
-I am not good with words.
Especially about love…
Of course you two are on my side.
Yul, do you not sleep well these days?
Drink as much as you want today
and get a good night's sleep.
You have trouble sleeping?
No.
I saw you wandering around until late.
You usually go to bed like clockwork.
Are you concerned about
what is happening at Seoho Fortress?
I just slashed a soul shifter.
It is our duty to protect this world
from such monsters.
Even though it is dead, it is still Gwigu.
There might still be traces of its powers.
Do not touch it.
You are feigning ignorance, right?
Like the time we buried the inkstone.
It must be tough for you.
If I regain my energy and draw that sword,
will I be able to slash
anyone relentlessly like before?
Is that the assassin's sword?
Why did Young Master bring it again?
I am terrified of that sword.
It feels ominous. I do not want it nearby.
The guests are all asleep. Go to bed.
Maybe we need to have a charm written.
Terrifying…
and ominous.
Eunuch Kim,
who caused trouble at Cheonbugwan,
is not beside the Queen today as well.
Did you look into it?
They say he is ill and is resting,
but no one seems to know where he is.
Find out as much as you can about him.
Find out when he came to the palace,
when he started serving the Queen,
and if there is anything odd about him.
Be discrete.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
Do you remember what Eunuch Kim said
when we saw him at Cheonbugwan?
Did that wench Shaman Choi
tell you to kill me?
Shaman Choi…
She must be superior to Jin Mu
to have given him orders.
It must be the Queen.
Just as Mu-deok's true identity is Naksu.
Could the true identity of the Queen
be Shaman Choi?
That is probably right.
But only if the Queen is a soul shifter.
There was nothing to suspect
that the Queen is a soul shifter.
I checked her core of energy
as I was examining her,
but she was a normal person
without extraordinary energy.
She could have appeared so
if she had the ice stone.
The Queen is the younger sister
of General Seo.
She is Yul's aunt.
She is not related to the Heo family,
but she is a member of the Seo family.
If her soul has been shifted,
the soul in her body is someone else.
Is the Queen's soul dead?
That is not possible.
Each member of the Seo Family
has a Lantern of Life.
Because they guard the Seoho Fortress
near the border and go to battle often,
they each have a lantern that is lit
by the energy of their soul
so they know who is alive and dead.
If the Queen passed away,
they would know immediately because
her Lantern of Life would have gone off.
Yes, I remember the Lantern of Life.
Her soul would have been
kept alive in another body.
Like Master Kang of Daegangtongun
who is lying in Sejukwon right now.
Are you certain
that the Queen is a soul shifter?
If we can know for sure,
that would mean
we found Jin Mu's greatest weakness.
Songrim is suspecting me
and they will try
to prove the Queen is a soul shifter.
What is there to worry about?
We already have a body
for her soul to be transferred to.
Can you get her into Jinyowon
without a problem?
I will bring her to Jinyowon today.
If everything goes to plan,
Jinyowon will get their lost daughter back
and there will be a funeral at the palace.
Because the Queen will have passed away.
What should we do with my old body
that the Queen's soul is occupying?
We shall take care of it
since we no longer need it alive.
Your Highness,
I am here instead of Eunuch Kim today.
What a pity.
It would be better for you
to let go of your mind.
This must be Gaema Village.
You are looking for a shaman?
Yes.
Then try Gaema Village.
All kinds of shamans gather there.
I know the oldest shaman there.
If you are looking for someone, ask him.
-Fire Priestess is really--
-No thank you.
-Wait.
-Goodness.
Excuse me, do you know
where Shaman Bong's house is?
Shaman Bong?
He does not have powers anymore.
You should go to
the Fire Priestess instead.
-I will take you there.
-No, I am looking for Shaman Bong.
-I told you, he is not good.
-No, it has to be Shaman Bong.
Thank you.
Where am I?
All of the streets look the same.
I never said
I wanted to see the Fire Priestess.
You still have to pay
if you had your fortune read.
-Where are you going?
-Hey, do not touch me.
She did not get a single thing right.
Why should I pay?
Did you go and see Shaman Bong?
He is bad, is he not?
The Fire Priestess is the real deal.
Am I right?
"Fire Priestess," my foot.
Come on.
My goodness…
Did you come to get your fortune read?
How about you?
Did you come for an exorcism?
What did Fire Priestess say
to make you so angry?
She said I have no luck in government
and I should get into business.
I am the Crown Prince.
What did Shaman Bong say to you?
I am on my way to see him.
I have many questions for him.
Jang Uk.
Are you looking for Eunuch Kim too?
Why are you looking for him here?
He disappeared from the palace
since that day at Cheonbugwan.
His traces led me here.
So you came here alone without any guards?
I do not want anyone to know
that I am suspecting them.
So you agree that
Eunuch Kim is a soul shifter
and that the Queen is being
suspicious by trying to cover it up?
That is right.
Why are you here?
What are you looking for?
I think there are overlaps in
what we are looking for.
Shall we exchange information?
Share one piece of information each?
Fine. You go first.
If I tell you first,
you will not share yours,
saying, "I am the Crown Prince."
How did you know that?
Fine.
While I was searching for Eunuch Kim,
I found something strange.
It seems he left the palace every month
to go somewhere.
The place he visited every month
was Gaema Village.
I am looking for Shaman Choi.
Who is that?
That is for the next time.
Now if you excuse me…
Wait.
What am I supposed to glean
from that kind of information?
I do not have much information yet.
-Why are you following me?
-To meet Shaman Bong.
We do not have to go together.
I can go afterward
and get him to tell me what he told you.
I am the Crown Prince.
-I do not know where he is.
-You do know.
I really have no idea.
I have met your uncle and your mother.
What did she say?
Is she still very angry at me?
Will he really cast me out?
They said they will forgive you
if you submit a signed letter.
A signed letter swearing
never to see each other again.
Here you go.
The words are already written
so all you have to do is sign each copy
and you will be able to return home.
You can discuss it
before making your decision.
As for me, I am willing to provide
food and shelter for a while
if you insist on staying together.
Please excuse me.
Cho-yeon…
To tell you the truth,
I slightly regretted it.
I was scared that I may have acted
rather impulsively.
But…
the thought of never seeing you again…
I do not care about anything else.
I cannot sign this letter.
I cannot live without seeing you.
JIN CHO-YEON OF JINYOWON SWEARS NEVER
TO SEE PARK DANG-GU OF SONGRIM AGAIN
I was also annoyed at first.
But I want to keep seeing you.
The negotiation is off.
Set the table, Mu-deok.
Have some fish.
Have some meat as well.
Are you two really going to stay here?
Yes.
We are going to go home
and bring our belongings.
So you will build
your honeymoon nest here?
It is not like that,
but we at least need a change of clothes.
Could you go with her
and carry her luggage back?
Did you throw away the paper
that was here?
I was about to throw them out.
JIN CHO-YEON OF JINYOWON SWEARS NEVER
TO SEE PARK DANG-GU OF SONGRIM AGAIN
I need to think it over.
If I pack up and leave,
I really might get kicked out.
Did you get hurt?
Does it hurt?
Of course, it does.
You have a scar.
How did you get that?
I have no idea.
It was when I was young,
so I do not remember.
That is a scar from a laceration.
My sister had one in the same place
because of me.
She fell exactly like you did just now.
A scar formed on the cut.
This will do.
I will do my best, Father.
Do not call me that
unless it is necessary.
It makes my skin crawl.
Did he have to be so rude about it?
Why did he throw away
such a beautiful silk handkerchief?
Wait.
It has the same design as Mu-deok's.
-Did the lord from Jinyowon leave?
-Yes.
What is this design?
It is the crest of the Jin family.
You will go there today. Get ready.
Right.
Is that what this was?
Why would Mu-deok have something
with the crest of Jinyowon on it?
You have to get my things
without my mother finding out.
Follow me.
I wish she would just go in and stay.
Can this man really be believed?
He seems like a hack.
He must be something.
You are both piping hot.
You have shared something.
Are you perchance lovers?
-No way.
-No.
It is my business policy
never to breach confidentiality.
You can rest assured.
The two of you have already shared
something very meaningful, right?
He is good.
Come on.
I heard you have been
in Gaema Village the longest.
Do you happen to know Shaman Choi?
Shaman Choi?
Are you mages patrolling for sorcery?
It is nothing like that.
I just heard she was very good.
I just want to find her because of that.
Yes, she was.
It was already over 20 years ago.
Shaman Choi was famous
for her sorcery that put hexes on people.
One day, she almost got caught
by the mages from Cheonbugwan
who were cracking down on sorcery.
But she jumped into a fire.
Some say she died in that fire.
Others say she was burnt badly
but survived.
That was when
your father Jang Gang
was the Gwanju of Cheonbugwan.
If Shaman Choi was hunted
by the mages of Cheonbugwan,
are you seeking her because
she bears a grudge against your father?
I do not even remember my father.
How can I know
who bears a grudge against him?
PARK DANG-GU OF SONGRIM SWEARS NEVER
TO SEE JIN CHO-YEON OF JINYOWON AGAIN
You did not sign the paper.
I thought about signing the paper
and coming back home,
but that would be lying.
I cannot live without seeing her.
This did not happen overnight.
I was in love with her for a long time,
but could not express it for a long time.
I was only able to take her hand now.
Please do not call us childish
and give us a chance.
Take your bundle of belongings
and go to Uk's home.
-Uncle…
-I need you
to do something there.
If this person comes to his house,
let me know immediately.
Who is this?
Gwanju Jang Gang of Cheonbugwan.
He is Uk's father.
If he comes,
let me know
right away.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Shaman Choi had a brother.
Do you know where he is?
I have not seen him since the incident.
But there was a rumor that
he married a woman from a powerful family.
They said this girl
is very likely to be her.
Why is she wearing such ragged clothes?
As a child, she washed up
along Lake Gyeongcheondaeho.
She was barely alive
when the fishermen rescued her.
That experience must have
caused memory loss,
but she can sense things around her
even though she is blind.
You have the birthmark here…
You have a scar in the same place.
That is why they said
you are very likely to be my Bu-yeon.
However,
it could still be a coincidence.
Why not test her with the surest method?
Let us go and see
if you can open the doors of Jinyowon.
The Cheonbugwan people are here again.
They must have brought
another girl to see if she is Bu-yeon.
Since you have
Jin Cho-yeon's blood in your body,
you should be able to
move the doors of Jinyowon.
Try to move the doors even a little bit.
That should be enough.
So many girls were brought here,
but none of them could open the door.
Bu-yeon!
My goodness, Bu-yeon!
It is happening again.
It happens every time I come to Jinyowon.
If it was 20 years ago,
it was when Jin Mu
was your father's pupil.
Jin Mu may know something.
Should I ask him?
Absolutely not.
Please keep what you heard today a secret.
What we learned today does not seem
all that important, but I will.
Your Royal Highness,
did you say you came here alone?
I did.
But it seems like someone is following us.
Shall we split up
to see who he is following?
Mother!
Who are you and why are you following me?
I said…
who are you?
The Jin Bu-yeon that Jin Mu
has brought in is So-i, the swindler.
Why is this here?
Mu-deok is the real daughter.
What will become of me
if she finds that out?
Jin Mu must have something big
so that even if Jin Ho-gyeong finds out
her daughter is a fake, she will not
be able to do anything about it.
What do you want?
You must fight Songrim
in order to protect the ice stone.
Everyone, please settle down!
Do you mean you wish to become
a hero with the fate of the King's Star
by destroying every ice stone
and saving the world from chaos?
Is Seo Yul here?
He shall be the first person I kill.
Young Master Seo!
There is a soul shifter.
Jang Uk could die!
Jang Uk, my pupil…
Subtitle translation by: Eun Jung