Min Jae.
Someone's calling for you.
That's because you never wear your uniform properly.
I sometimes dress properly.
User Not Found
Why did you call me?
Notes for Korean. Can I borrow them?
Bye.
I recommend tracks No. 2, No. 7, No. 9, and No. 11.
What's this?
Who listens to a CD these days?
Attention!
You will practice passing in teams of two.
If you don't do it properly, you'll see my fireball shot.
To your positions.
Min Jae, will you be my partner?
Sure.
I'll throw first.
Da Ye.
Yeah?
You know the thing you said yesterday.
She has a crush on someone.
What? I didn't know.
Tell me, tell me.
He's just a friend.
But sometimes he says something that gives me butterflies.
Butterflies? That means he's more than a friend.
But he could be thinking of you as just a friend, right?
Catch.
- That's good.
- Right?
Thanks.
I...
I'm going through a similar thing.
I don't know if he feels the same way.
Maybe I'm being weird and reading into things.
No! No, you're not weird.
It's the same for me.
Well, well.
Are... you okay?
Yes, No-Min is fine.
I heard the other kids say that she's weird.
Really?
You have tied your hair quite well.
Wait a minute.
Min Jae, what are you wearing?
Huh?
Oh... This?
Destroy
Sicko World
What's this?
It's so...
It's cute!
It's similar to something
I wore in middle school.
Back when everyone...
Did you see her clothes?
- Terrible.
- Is she a cartoon character?
She's dressed like a loser.
Min Jae Chan!!!
Is that...
You're like Annie Chan from the anime Yiwanot.
I watched all of it except for the movie.
You have good taste.
You look cute.
You're such a goddess.
This is the hottest T-shirt these days!
It costs 384,000 won!
What is happening?
Wow, Hye Joon. You know quite a bit!
You're right.
It looks so good on you!
It's really cute.
No wonder it looks perfect on you.
Min Jae, can you tell me where you bought it?
Oh, the shop's hidden in an alley by Woojung Station.
I'll send you the address.
Can I have your number?
My number?
Here.
No, why me?
You said so yourself.
"I can change what everyone thinks and says."
I didn't put it like that.
I know nothing about girls' fashion.
You're smart.
Memorize it!
Think of it as a test.
Anyway,
no one will pay attention to me.
But they will listen to you.
Please do me a favor.
Then let me ask you a question.
What is it?
Why are you doing all of this to do favors for Yu Min Jae?
I told you.
Your idea of friendship doesn't exist.
You don't know everything.
To me...
- This.
- Huh?
Stop.
She could've been sincere.
Yeah.
It felt like I had a real friend thanks to you.
I want to protect her.
Her innocence.
It looks good on her.
She must be annoyed.
Min Jae is so nice.
Answering all of their questions.
Exactly.
She makes people feel comfortable.
Definitely.
Shin Yi Joon: Did you listen to it?
Hye Joon: Where are you?
This is strange.
Very strange.
Guy friend
My guy friend confessed to me.
It all leads to romance?
Is there anything else?
Gifts for a guy friend
Why did my guy friend give me a present out of the blue?
He could've given it to you as a friend.
I knew it.
Presents mean he has feelings for you.
Hi.
Oh, this is...
Let's call it even.
For the CD you gave me.
One ticket?
What?
Oh, you don't want to go alone. I'll buy another one.
What about you?
What? Me?
What are you doing this Saturday?
Saturday?
Come with me.
What?
Just the two of us?
Or I can ask everyone in the group chat—
You don't want to?
What?
You don't want to go with me?
I do.
Min Jae.
Can you take me to the clothing store you mentioned?
I want to go.
How about this Saturday?
Can we go another day?
I have plans this Saturday.
Really?
With who?
Oh... Shin Yi Joon.
What happened is that I—
Classic.
He likes to go to the cinema when he has nothing else to do.
Oh, you guys go to the cinema often?
But seeing that he hasn't asked everyone,
he must really like you.
Gosh, no.
No, no, no.
No. I know him well.
This means something.
You think?
Maybe he asked me to come with him as a friend.
Min Jae, did you get butterflies?
No, I...
Eun Ji and her guy friend—
Hey! Are you and Eun Ji the same?
I'll help you!
Do well!
Maybe he really likes me?
Min Jae, which one is the cutest?
Min Jae?
Min Jae.
Min Jae!
-  Min Jae—
- Stop
I'm looking at them.
Calm down.
What is the occasion?
Which one?
What's going on with you?
You're acting suspicious.
The seventh hair band.
Is this one of those "guy friend becomes boyfriend" situations
that I read about on social media?
We're sharing popcorn and then...
You're pretty.
Min Jae.
Can we talk?
User Not Found
Preview for the next episode coming up
Next episode
Shin Yi Joon asked me to be his girlfriend.
What would you choose between friendship and love?
The important thing is you,
not anyone else.
Sometimes it's better to stay as friends that aren't really friends.
Shin Hye Joon.
If you're not sure what's in her heart,
I'll help.
Don't fall for me.
Yu Min Jae.
What is in his heart?