What is this?
This is a Santa parfait.
What's that?
It's a perfect name for it, isn't it?
Grandmother, you can be very eccentric sometimes.
Why is it called a Santa parfait when it's not Christmas?
She's not eccentric; she is creative because she was an actress.
Wu Hyeon is correct.
Correct.
It's delicious.
The seventh rule:
even if you are alone, try to find friends to eat together.
I will have this one.
I will have a Santa parfait and coffee.
Okay.
Wait, did you say Santa parfait?
We have to make this parfait with the recipe that Papa made
because this is the signature menu of our cafe.
Is a Santa parfait a common menu?
Customers love it because it's only available here.
Why do you ask?
My grandmother made it for me sometimes.
Is that so? Is the recipe the same?
It looks similar.
Well, most of the menus can be similar.
The signature menu and stuff are all for the business.
The customer wants to cancel the parfait and order something else.
Is that okay?
I just finished making it.
What can I do? Why don't you try it?
We have to throw it out anyway.
Grandma...
What is this?
This is a Santa parfait.
What's that?
It's a perfect name for it, isn't it?
You can be very eccentric sometimes.
Why is it called a Santa parfait when it's not Christmas?
She's not eccentric; she is creative because she was an actress.
Wu Hyeon is correct.
Correct.
It's delicious.
It's so delicious that it makes me sad.
What?
Right? Because it disappears when you eat it.
Exactly.
Even when I'm not around anymore, you guys should gather like now,
eat together and live well.
Grandma, why are you saying stuff like that again?
Yu Ri will never eat alone.
It's tears.
Kaka, Toto! Yu Ri is about to cry.
We all live with such stories in our hearts
so we talk to each other and give each other comfort.
That's right.
Why don't you tell us about it?
It's a very personal story
so it's a bit awkward to suddenly tell you.
We have rules here.
We have to listen to the story of the person who's about to cry.
Because of those stupid rules, our work gets disturbed.
But it's all for the good of us.
It's all for the good, yes.
Okay, let's go ahead and start.
Toto! You have to be sincere.
Wait until she starts.
You are all doing this for the bonus, but why are you acting nice?
Shush! Don't worry about what he said.
Okay, why don't you tell us about your story?
Yes.
My grandmother passed away recently.
She had dementia.
She passed away in a car accident when I wasn't around.
I still have the food that she made in the fridge,
and the coffee beans that she used to drink are still left at home.
But I can't believe that she passed away.
As I expected, he's so fast.
I can't beat the speed of someone in their twenties.
Grandmother was like a mom to me.
My dad barely came home,
and my grandmother raised me since I was an infant.
What about your mom?
My mom...
I don't know who my mom is.
Aigo.
Oh, my...
An angel came to me.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Don't ask me who the mom of the baby is.
You know what kind of women are around me.
Look at her!
She's making eye contact with me.
Are you really not curious about anything?
What's important at this point?
It's good that you came to your grandmother.
Her eyes are like mine!
What? It's not.
She does have the resemblance, and her mouth looks exactly like you.
That's how I met my grandmother.
I came to her on December 24, so she called me her Christmas gift.
My grandmother only had me,
but I said hurtful things to her.
All right.
Let's eat and cheer up.
Here comes the curry!
The one who said mean things to you
must be eating well and living fine right now.
If you are like now, it's your loss.
That person never won in the first place! You don't know anything about it.
You don't have to listen to what everybody says.
You only need to say one thing to the people who gossip.
Look straight into their eyes,
and say, "So what?"
If you raise your chin like this,
you look proud and chic.
What is that?
It's not worth it to fret about useless things.
Just do what you have to do now.
That way, you can be happy.
And what you have to do right now
is enjoy this warm curry.
Grandma.
Please live a long life with me.
Yes, I should live long.
Please don't make that face.
And after what happened to my dad,
my grandmother was very shocked
so she wasn't like her old self.
Why is she not picking up her phone?
Yes, Yu Ri.
Grandma, where are you?
- What?
- Did you forget about my graduation ceremony?
Hello? Are you listening?
Today?
How could you forget about it?
You were picking the shoes to wear to my graduation this morning!
What's wrong with you?
Grandma?
Grandma? Are you there?
Wait...
Oh my, what should I do?
I'm out of my mind.
I must be crazy. What's wrong with me?
Oh, my...
Let's stop it right here. It's good to do everything in moderation.
We'll get many bonuses, right?
I know you are happy about it, too!
That day was a strange day.
An ordinary father figure of a regular family.
It was the view that my grandmother and I wished for so badly.
What's going on?
Am I a monkey in the cage?
What are you looking at?
Oh, don't be surprised.
What are you waiting for? Dig in!
This coffee is killing it!
Is it good?
It's good.
How is it?
It's delicious.
Right? It's killing it.
The weather is a killer too!
Hurry and finish the food. Let's go outside.
Let's go on a picnic!
What?
A picnic..?
Yes! The weather's this nice, so it's a shame to sit inside.
Let's take out the mat and pack some lunch.
And put on some makeup, Mom.
What are you waiting for? Hurry and move!
But I have plans with my friend today.
Plans?
Which friend?
Well... It's just my friend.
It must be Wu Hyeon. He's your only friend.
You don't know that much about my friends.
Wu Hyeon has been in and out of our place since he was a baby!
Let's go all together.
T-Together?
Yes. We can all hang out together.
Well...
The weather did everything for this year's picnic.
Right, Yu Ri?
Yes.
"This year's picnic?"
You're saying that as if we are always doing this.
You could've just let it slide.
All right, let's eat lunch!
Wow, there are three different kinds of rice balls!
Okay, cheers!
It's killer!
Hey, you should be grateful that you are not like your father.
You don't even resemble his looks.
And please don't take after your father's lousy personality, okay?
Okay.
- Wu Hyeon.
- Yes?
Isn't my daughter, Yu Ri, pretty?
Yes.
You know, I only see her once or twice a year.
So she's my daughter, but I don't know her that well.
It means I'm a bad father.
But you see her all the time, so you know well about her, right?
Yes.
It would be nice if someone who knows Yu Ri well is always by her side.
That's what I thought.
Unfamiliar happiness made me uneasy,
and my anxious hunch was always right.
Jae Hyeok...
Come here...
Yu Ri, you...
I like that you don't cry often.
Don't cry in the future as well.
And please take care of this woman.
This poor woman...
My mom...
Jae Hyeok...
Wow, that's intense. I don't know what to say.
Hey! It's not the place to say anything.
You went through a lot.
It would've been not easy for you to share that.
If you tell a story that's hard to tell, it's ten times the bonus.
I mean, you would have had a hard time.
Whether it's sad or angry,
there are things that you can't tell, even over time.
When my grandmother passed away,
I cried so much.
But in front of my dad's death,
I couldn't feel any feelings.
I guess I can say this feeling is sad in a way.
Still, he's my father.
I have to be sad.
♫  When the night is over,  ♫
♫  As if the morning comes again,  ♫
♫  Since my love, you are next to me  ♫
♫  I'm not afraid of anything in this world  ♫