=In the Wake of Shadow=
=Episode 3=
South wind.
Four sticks.
Well arranged.
Green dragon.
Oh, Young Master Su.
That's why I have to play with you.
Oh my, you...
You've hit it big.
Big three dragons.
Your luck is amazing.
I have something good for you.
Let's go, let's go.
Wait for me.
(Red Fox Strikes Again)
Xinyue.
This Red Fox is really ruthless.
He probably hates
these opium dealers too.
I heard Young Master Su
has annulled the marriage.
Keep your voice down.
But it's understandable.
Young Master Su is the one
everyone desires but can't have.
Young Master Su
is really a playboy.
I wonder what he's planning.
- Ma'am, I'm leaving.
- Take care.
Xinyue,
aren't you worried at all?
Shouldn't you think of a solution?
We can't rely on others.
Let's think of another way.
But...
- Tear down everything here later.
- Yes.
Set up a row of beds over there.
My opium den doesn't serve the poor.
The poor can buy from us,
but they have to go smoke outside.
What are you doing?
This is none of your business.
I'm telling you, I'm here
to take over the shop today.
On what grounds?
Master Tan, your nose is really sharp.
You came here
just by following the scent.
Little girl,
do you really think
you can rise to greatness?
I heard
you recently got a good cricket.
Hey,
I just so happen
to have a good cage.
I don't need it,
so why don't you
take it?
Young Master Su,
no gains without pains.
How can I accept this?
Don't be so polite.
A great gift is for a great man.
Right?
Young Master Su,
as long as you say the word,
I will definitely
try my best to get it done.
You said it yourself.
Just tell me.
Five years ago,
Master Du was killed.
Are you aware of that?
Well,
at that time,
I hadn't been transferred
to this district yet.
Are there any records
at the Police Station?
Yes, there are.
But
it's not very convenient.
Hey.
If you can't do it, it's fine.
It's not a big deal.
Young Master.
Ah?
I'll go take a look. Let's go.
Young Master Su, you go ahead.
- Hey.
- Hey, this cage...
You keep it.
Thank you, Young Master Su.
Well.
(Xingyue Tavern)
We are closed.
Please leave.
Master Tan is offering you a way out.
You even dare to slap people!
- So what?
- Get lost.
- Yao!
- How dare you act up in front of me.
Today, I'll show you
how powerful Master Tan is.
Master, today
it's a double occasion for joy.
Why not consummate the marriage first
and then take over the shop?
Good idea.
I want to see if she still dares
to slap people in bed.
Hold her down.
Let go of me!
Let go!
Don't touch me!
Well,
are you guys busy?
Su,
this has nothing to do with you.
Don't meddle in this.
Get lost!
Move aside, move aside.
Nothing to do with me?
- Don't hit my face.
- Nothing to do with me?
Yao.
Nothing to do with me?
Ling Hao! Knife!
Stop it.
Do you submit?
I submit, I submit.
Are you okay?
Listen up.
Du Xinyue is my wife.
If you dare to touch her again,
you're going against me.
Got it?
Got it, got it.
Get out.
(Xingyue Tavern)
Who hit you?
Master Tan's man.
Next time, I'll help you get revenge.
(Why isn't he saying anything?)
Just now,
thank you for helping me out.
But weren't you
quite fierce before?
(Since the tavern is now safe,)
(I can't hold him back.)
If you want to annul the marriage,
I understand.
Well,
I'm sleepy.
Going back to sleep.
Ah...
Du Xinyue.
Let's go.
Ah?
(Dock)
(Xinyue,)
(I'm back.)
♪The whole world stays awake with me♪
♪Have we all been hurt?♪
♪She always misunderstood♪
♪My tangled feelings♪
♪The moment I couldn't keep her♪
♪I'll remember it by heart♪
♪Maybe after many years♪
♪I will learn to distinguish lies♪
♪Her heart has changed♪
♪I'm no longer in it♪
♪Hugging myself under the streetlight♪
♪That timidity♪
♪Actually, I'm not that easy to deceive♪
♪I just love you a little more♪
♪Why take advantage of my pity♪
♪And give me more memories♪
♪You didn't hear♪
♪My last goodbye♪
♪I walked away♪
♪With tears in my eye♪
♪Actually, you have changed too♪
♪You just love him a little more♪
♪We couldn't withstand the test♪
♪It's better to cut ties with each other♪
♪Desperately showing my care for you♪
♪All I can get is a thank you in return♪
♪Maybe he understands you♪
(The right of communication
through information networks)
(exclusively belongs to
Shenzhen Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)