Translation and Timing Carefully Crafted
[Mr. Queen]
[The characters, organizations, and events in this drama are unrelated to any historical facts and all stories are fictional.]
Congratulations!
You've done well, My Queen.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
I'm going to be a father!
I'm... pregnant?
Freeze right there!
Get out! Get out!
Why is the queen so mad?
I don't think she's being angry, this might be her expression of happiness.
Y-Yes.
Is it... some sort of pregnancy syndrome?
This isn't just a crisis of my (sexual) identity.
This is the extinction of my identity, destruction of my soul!
Is my life over in this way now?
I told you! I've chosen to be single for my life to begin with.
Even if I happened to marry by accident, I was never going to have a baby.
It's hard enough for me to survive here in this battlefield-life, but a child!
It's as hopeless as taking off a bulletproof vest and dancing the samba in a rain of bullets!
That's not all. Pregnancy and giving birth is a terrible process to shorten your lifespan.
Well, it's basically me grinding my own life away to give birth to a child.
Why should I give my precious life to a baby I don't even know anything about?
Damnable Mother Nature. F*** the provision of Nature!
What do you mean I'm pregnant!
[Episode 17: Pregnancy is beautiful]
Please wait for a second.
[Episode 17]
I know you fabricated the corpse.
Did you think I wouldn't recognize Oh Wol until the end?
I did it just to enlighten you, Eui Bin.
To show your true self that you didn't even know yet, I mean.
The queen turned her back to the Ansong Kim Family.
Instead, the Ansong Kim Family joined hands with our clan.
This is the golden opportunity for you to ascend to the seat of queen.
Don't you ever try to control me.
The bird is already tamed by humans, so how many days will it survive if it leaves its cage?
There is news that His Majesty the King has ordered to officially announce to the world.
What's the news?
The queen is pregnant.
That's the sound of the drum which announces a big happy occasion.
As my storage rooms are completely empty,
there is no way to fill the emptiness in my mind.
My stomach, no, my mind which can't be filled with even various delicacies.
What can I fill it with?
I, who even turned his back to his own clan,
am now a loner.
My Lord!
My Lord... My Lord!
- What?
- There is urgent news from the palace!
Is it...
Did something happen to the queen?
The queen... is pregnant!
What is the reason?
Your Majesty, I think instead of looking for the reason,
lifting her spirits may be more effective.
Good idea, but what would that be? A way to make a woman feel better?
I just asked something you wouldn't know.
Who should I ask then?
So I came here and brought along a specialist for you, Cheoljong.
Since this man has been agonizing over that question all the time lately.
What are you doing!
Then the person would probably turn angry just like that.
That's when you say it.
"I just gave water to the flower."
It might be hard for me to come out alive if I did that.
She has an attitude, I see.
Then, there is a sure way.
What's that?
You make a funny face like this.
Now I'm disgusted with myself that I had the same idea as this man.
I'm sorry.
It certainly helped.
- Impossible!
- It made me realize how foolish I was, asking other people how to solve this problem.
When I'm the one who knows that woman the best.
Why are you crying? I should be the one crying.
Because I'm so happy.
Your Majesty, at least for today, please cry as much as you want.
Okay, cry, whatever.
You can cry a lot instead of me.
For the life...
I never chose.
Your Majesty,
you shouldn't be crying any more tears of joy.
Then, what should I be doing?
You should pay a visit to the elders of the Inner Court so that you can relay this good news and get their congratulations.
I don't want to! I tore (broke) ties with my in-laws.
Regardless if you tore it or sewed it, if you don't follow protocol, you will get in big trouble, Your Majesty.
I'm hating being pregnant more and more.
Her Royal Highness the Grand Queen Dowager is here.
Her Royal Highness the Queen Dowager is here, too.
We've lost the chance to initiate it.
What do we do?
You came?
I was supposed to go to your rooms and give you the news directly.
But as you can see, it's hard for me to walk.
What did you say the symptoms were?
It's extreme vertigo, caused by morning sickness and aches from pregnancy.
Yes, those.
So I came here myself.
Please sit...
right here.
That's all right.
Your body must feel heavy, so just stay comfortably, right there.
Yes, well then...
How happy I was when I heard the news!
I even got that talisman, which I haven't gotten for a while.
The present is because I wish your child to be born safely.
Well, this looks like a talisman curse, though.
Sorry, but since I'm an atheist, I don't believe in things like this.
When your child is born, you will know
the feeling that you'll want to believe things that you didn't before.
Like you'll want to wish on a rock on the street,
being of such a desperate mind, I mean.
Even you, the fearless queen,
will now fear everything in the world.
Losing a child is the mother's fault.
So I ordered the royal physician to prepare some healthy medicine to prevent miscarriage.
Please drink it every day without missing a day.
If there is anything wrong with the child, you will have to take full responsibility.
So you shouldn't act rashly, but be careful with every action for the royal baby you're carrying.
Coming here together as a pair just to threaten me. Ugh, I feel like I'm actually going to throw up.
Your grace is immeasurable, Your Highnesses.
This is Prince Yeongpyeong.
Please come in.
You came because you were worried about me, didn't you?
It's fine.
But I might not be able to congratulate the king and queen,
I have to follow my own path.
I came here to give strength to the king.
I considered the strength I could give to the king was just psychological support,
but looking at the queen, it doesn't seem to be necessary.
This is the golden opportunity for you to ascend to the seat of queen.
Your Highness the Queen Dowager what do I owe you for this honor?
Lady Eui Bin, what brings you here?
I see you joined hands with the Ansong Kim Family.
It's a decision made by our clan.
Don't you dare use the name of our clan for this unjustifiable fight.
Do you want to keep your position of Right State Minister?
You'd better make the right choice. Otherwise,
I'm going to gather all the power from the members of our family including my father,
who are sincerely concerned about the future of Joseon.
Did Father really give me all of this?
Yes, Your Majesty. All of them are presents for the royal baby you're carrying.
This isn't even all of it. There's tons more in the hallway.
Looking at this, I feel even worse.
I'll light the room now because it's getting dark.
That tiny candle won't really help, because now, my life
is just sheer darkness.
[...crime of bribing Left State Minister, Kim Seok-geun, every month. The crime of forging official documents for embezzlement...]
Again this time, they beheaded only the clerks, but not the magistrates?
Not beheading the magistrates must mean that they're trying to avoid committing treason toward the king.
How little the courage of mere farmers is, eh?
But this is a headache as they don't give us the excuse to mobilize troops on a large scale.
By the way, were the coded words of Donghak previously found within the palace? (Donghak - Neo-Confucianism Reformer)
[Kim So-yong]
It's big trouble that the Donghak influence has even seeped into the palace, so shouldn't you hurry?
If we just let it be and if a bunch of Donghak followers are found inside the palace, what are you going to do then?
Just do your own job properly.
[Daejojeon]
Your Majesty, starting today,
[Tae-gyo-shin-gi]
[Prenatal Care]
You will start prenatal care.
♫  Bonghwan-ah ♫
You must not lie down horizontally or lean on your arms
You should not lie down with your neck raised as well.
♫ I used to not be afraid of the world ♫
♫ Even I who is free and has no fears ♫
♫ How did I get stuck in this body? ♫
♫ What exactly am I supposed to do now? ♫
♫ How complicated this is!  ♫
You can't laugh, be surprised, be scared,
mourn, cry, or talk a lot as well.
♫ One night, two nights pass but the world is still the same ♫
Unconventional foods should absolutely not be eaten.
This is completely making it so that my body isn't my own!
Well, obviously it's not my body, but I was adjusting pretty well!
How is it that with pregnancy everything is reset!
Especially you! You said that you wouldn't nag me about certain things anymore!
This is for the child.
I have to live in order for the baby to live as well. Am I just some baby laying machine? A baby incubator?
Also, is prenatal care just for the mother? What is the baby daddy doing! Tell Cheoljong to do some prenatal care!
It just so happens that the prenatal booklet's first page, third line,
states that fathers are responsible for prenatal care, too.
So, tonight, when the king comes back from work, the two of you can do prenatal care together.
From the moment I wake up until I go to sleep, I have to do prenatal care?
My life has gone already.
No, you must not... No, no, no, no.
Take it away, Hong Yeon.
While I was working here, there has been no contact between the queen and Kim Byeong-In lately.
After being thrown out and even hearing the news about the pregnancy,
he must not have any place left to lean on.
How pitiful.
Have you eaten?
Please go inside.
Sleep at home.
Your face looks unwell.
Stress is the source of all illnesses so if I just let this be, it's very bad for prenatal care.
Stand guard.
Just one spoonful.
My Yihwaju!
Head Royal Chef!
My Yihwaju.
It was spoiled so I threw it all out.
You seem to be in a good mood.
I am the same as usual.
You said you lost laughter a long time ago.
I found it... laughter.
I lost Yihwaju and you found laughter.
What a coincidence.
Tell me the truth, Lady Choi. You are enjoying it right now, aren't you?
You are taking your revenge out on me now for giving you a hard time, aren't you?!
You probably shouldn't shake me, Your Majesty.
Vomit it out. Vomit out my Yihwaju!
Please, Your Majesty!
Use words, Your Majesty.
Words!
My Yihwaju.
Ah, you drank up all my Yihwaju.
Your Majesty!
I am so annoyed! My Yihwaju!
Your Majesty.
Why am I crying?
I was waiting for you.
Wow, you look good, like a prince on a white horse.
I can’t do anything, but you're happily riding a horse.
You're still angry today. That's a relief.
Let's ride together.
You cannot, Your Majesty!
The queen is expecting a baby.
She must not ride, Your Majesty!
Your Royal Highness!
It's dangerous!
♫ The heart-throbbing words to me, warmly like the sunshine ♫
♫ When they brush the tip of my nose, it flutters me somehow ♫
♫ Not to get caught with my mind ♫
Where are we?
I wanted to give you something you liked and wanted the most.
- Something that only exists outside the palace.
- Oh?
Freedom is what I'm talking about.
Don't you like it?
You could have told me we just came out for some fresh air instead of making such a big deal.
We came to get some fresh air at the royal family's hermitage. (Private retreat)
If you don't like it, we can go back.
Is it a villa or something like that?
It's nice! It kind of feels like a chaebol CEO is hitting on me.
(Chaebol - typically a large family-owned business group)
Since we are here, we might as well take a look around.
Oh, then let's take a look. This way.
Wow! It is good to be a king.
This grand villa and a garden...
I was thinking all night, why my queen would be so angry.
For most women in the palace, pregnancy is a blessing.
Why does pregnancy so bother My Queen?
And so, did you figure out the reason?
No. No matter how much I think about it, I don’t know.
I don’t understand, but I just decided to accept it.
What is a blessing to others, may not be a blessing to My Queen.
My Queen is this kind of person.
The Queen’s Dictionary was not in vain.
What's wrong with you? It's making me feel awkward.
My Queen.
Is this a roar?
As the writer of the Queen’s Dictionary, I have a question.
- What does "all-in" mean?
- Did I say that?
You were shouting it at the top of your lungs at the market gambling board.
Ah, "all-in" means
putting all your fragile eggs in one basket.
A very foolish act.
- Eggs?
- I did that, that foolish act.
Ah, while I am at my prime and should be running full force,
I tripped over a rock called "pregnancy."
Please don't worry, My Queen.
I will surely cut out the rotten part of Joseon.
Even if it's for our child who will inherit this country.
All right.
If this child becomes the king and inherits this country,
then I am... someone with omnipresent power?
[Sunwon's World] to [So-yong's World]
Why did I only think of that now?
- Think of what?
- My child, look!
Everything under the sky...
is yours!
- Let's go back. From now on, we are starting real prenatal care.
- Real prenatal care?
We will have to teach him how to win by fighting.
This child will have to live in this battlefield-like palace. Let's go. Start the engine!
But we just got here...
Even if I use 100 Queen's Dictionaries,
will I really be able to understand the queen?
- Wait for me. Wait for me.
- Hurry up!
[Daejojeon]
[Pregnancy Diary]
My child, in order to survive in the palace,
you must not be lazy about getting people on your side.
Wow!
As expected, the best warriors in Joseon.
My child, you must keep your enemies close.
1,000 soldiers?
By raising that kind of military power, are you planning on pushing your way into the Royal Secretariat or something?
Are you afraid?
It seems that you are the one preparing an army of 1,000 soldiers because you are afraid of me.
Why don't you cut that number in half and re-direct the rest to the Royal Guard?
My child, you must also make sure to have money on the side.
- This is the new coin we are pushing forward.
- How much?
One million nyang.
Oh... so this is the king's political fund.
With money, you can even buy power.
Lastly, my child, this is the most important thing.
Those who are not on your side, get rid of them all.
Life is the actual fight and the world is a jungle.
Eat or be eaten, that's the law of nature! Battle of blood! Slaughter party!
Of course, try to achieve peace. But if it looks hopeless,
you must use any and all means to win, my child.
Your Majesty, it is so fortunate that you pulled yourself together.
Is there that much to say even while the child is in the womb?
The child might listen to me while in the womb, but probably not after birth.
Now, it's time for sleep.
There is no time to sleep. I have so much to do.
Life is a running machine.
If you stop even for a moment, you'll get thrown off.
Even pregnancy can't conquer me.
Ah, I am being conquered.
My mind is a motorboat, but my body is a paddleboat.
It's been a while. You've been through a lot.
It's nothing.
I see that you completed the Byeongseo.
(Training book about the army and its soldiers)
It won't be easy to turn these men, who have never held a weapon
into soldiers, but it should help.
Be careful.
I see that the number of followers
have increased that much.
That means there are many who are suffering from oppression.
Recently, from noblemen in ruin to drunkards,
various people are gathering.
Perhaps, as the queen has said,
would abolishing the caste system of nobles and commoners be the answer?
We need to also be cautious of
an ideology that is too radical.
Of course, I am talking about far in the future.
I can't achieve it but perhaps
my child can.
Your Majesty, the king has arrived—
Don't wake her.
She is like a baby.
[My child, you must keep your enemies close.]
[My child, you must also make sure to have money on the side. With money, you can even buy power.]
[Lastly, my child, what's most important: The world is a jungle. Get rid of those not on your side. Eat or be eaten. Slaughter party! ]
Pahtee (Party)?
Pah...
Tee is the problem...
Pahtee.
The queen is all right so you did not get in trouble either.
As expected, the talisman I wrote worked.
Your grace is immeasurable.
So...
I take it that you delivered it well, the rumor that I told you?
How diligent you are so early in the morning.
Why don't you at least get rid of eye boogers before gossiping?
Why don't you listen, too?
It will wake you up instantly.
They say that Her Majesty the Queen...
I heard that's what happened.
What?! His Majesty the King and Her Majesty the Queen faked their night together!
His Majesty the King and Her Majesty the Queen
had a fake night together, I heard.
In reality, they did not spend the night together, right?
I heard that they just sleep in the same room, right?
Then, the pregnancy is by whom?
If it's not His Majesty, then whose child is it?
No way... Then, a fake...
I see that you heard it as well, the rumor that's spreading inside the palace.
Rumors always rush around belatedly.
They're so behind.
In the palace, rumors should not be taken lightly.
They could use that as an issue to dethrone you.
Seriously! Always trying to dethrone me over anything!
It's so petty and tacky,
I’ll never let them kick me out.
- Yes.
- Hong Yeon!
What are you doing with your hairpin?
What's wrong with you? Are you not ashamed of this pose?
We must hush up the rumor.
- Oh my goodness!
- Oh my gosh!
- I'm so ashamed.
Oh, in that case...
Would this be enough to hush up that rumor?
We need to do at least this much.
This is a bit excessive.
Though, it's nowhere near as excessive as me.
It's not enough.
Let’s put a little more soul into this.
If I put more soul into this...
We shall need a tent.
Is that what you want?
Who said I wanted to? No, it's just necessary for our public image.
Well, since it's necessary for our public image,
I'll come to Daejojeon Hall tonight.
Since there's the risk of dethronement, I guess you must.
Then...
See you a little later to do that.
Did they leave?
They are so slow. We need to stay this way longer.
Then it can't be helped.
Your Highness, Lady Eui Bin is here.
Queen Dowager, is it your doing?
What are you talking about?
The rumor.
It is, all thanks to you.
I remembered what you told me some time ago.
That the queen told you she lied about spending the night with the king.
With this, the queen’s pregnancy will be unwelcome.
The words you uttered...
ended up becoming an arrow and shot the queen.
Stop, please!
I can't do anything anymore now.
Once rumors start,
there's no turning back.
You, also,
cannot try to get out of it now.
As long as you’re in the palace,
you'll not be free.
Your existence itself will be used for the needs of our family.
Take the lead rather than being used.
I'm scared.
I'm sure.
But you are not alone.
Don't worry.
That I'm starting to become like you...
scares me.
Do you know the reason why our family obeys you?
Because you're a victim who was drowned in sorrow after losing her child.
But if you were a heartless mother who heartlessly caused her son's death in order to save herself;
and furthermore, if she's foolish enough to be bemused by all kinds of superstition,
relying on the words of Bodhisattva for her clan's fate,
will they still consider you the head of our family?
I will make sure to write down everything I have heard and seen in this palace,
so that every person in Joseon will know.
How much weight do you think those trivial matters hold?
You will find out... soon enough.
You told me once that you don't want to regret it again.
What you need to regret is not your failure to prevent the death of the late king,
but stepping on his dreams.
For breaking your son’s wings with your own hands,
regret that instead.
What the late king wanted so desperately to escape from was probably
coming out from under his mother's shadow.
You don't know anything!
How dare you say such nonsense?
It's the truth everyone knows.
Actually, you know it too.
I won’t let you trample on His Majesty's dreams.
That wench!
I'm going to Daejojeon Hall.
Yes.
You know they say that rumors and dreams are opposites.
Rumors, too?
I didn't tell people about the night spent with the king because it was personal.
Since, if you knew, you all would be really shocked.
During the night...
Goodness!
It's not like I can tell people about that fiery night.
The king is different from what I thought.
He's a great king who will go down in history.
No way... Was it recorded that way in history because of me?
Who would spread such a rumor?
The only person who would do something like that is Lady Eui Bin.
It's okay. It's okay.
What? What are you here to complain about now?
Are you confident?
Are you confident you and the king will win?
This is my fight as well. I also have a reason I need to win.
If that's the case then practice some archery, too.
With those skills, you'll be more of a burden than a help.
Then why don't you teach me, Eui Bin?
I don't have the time to do that.
Your Majesty, Lady Eui Bin is here.
Let her in.
- I have a request for you, My King.
- Tell me.
You must grant it no matter what.
What is it?
Let me leave the palace.
What do you mean by that?
I can't find myself in this palace.
Please throw me out so that I can live as myself.
I cannot. You know full well what living as a Bin who was thrown out means.
I don't care about what others think. No, I won't be swayed by them.
Since it is my last request, so please fulfill it for me.
I will not agree to it. I cannot!
Your Majesty, you and I cherish each other but are no longer in love.
I am now just someone who's living locked up in the palace under the name, Bin.
Your Majesty, all the ministers are present.
The reason I called you all here today,
is to relay an important decision I made.
As of now, I am removing Jo Hwa-jin
from the senior rank 1 of Eui Bin.
What's happened?
Shouldn't we stop him?
Eui Bin is no longer our person.
Your Majesty, please be healthy. I will be praying for your future.
My Lady!
Don't call me that from now on.
It can't be like this.
- The king shouldn't have done this.
- I asked him to.
- Why?
- This is best for everyone.
As long as I'm in the palace, I will be forced to block the king's path against my will.
I will make sure that doesn't happen. We can still fix this. I will tell the king immediately—
I don't trust myself anymore. If I continue to stay here, I might lose myself completely.
I... even ignored your feelings.... when I knew how you felt all along.
- My Lady.
- I used your feelings.
The emptiness I felt caused by His Majesty not looking at me the same way I looked at him,
I filled it with you.
I let you use me.
Since that's all... I could offer you.
Thank you for everything and I'm sorry.
Now, you should also let go of a love that is not right for you.
So that's what she meant.
She's a cool woman.
Is Cheoljong okay?
He probably isn't.
Why don't you spar with me once?
I am not in the mood.
When we were young... there was a game we used to play often in Ganghwa.
The one who steps on the other's shadow first is the winner. If you really don't feel like doing it...
you just have to lose.
Do you remember?
When we were young, I always won.
I do remember that I always won later on but...
I should have firmly set the pecking order earlier.
It's not that you didn't set the pecking order, but rather you couldn't.
Lady Eui Bin, till the very end, cared for you and worried about you.
For His Majesty who does not even know the value of her feelings—
I do know! That's why I am in pain!
You must be in more pain.
That's the least you should do to set things right with Eui Bin.
How much lonelier do I need to feel and how much more pain do I need to be in! How much more!
Our Jong, is he somewhere drinking?
I would drink with him if it weren't for the pregnancy.
Ah, does pregnancy mean becoming a newborn not giving birth to a newborn?
Why am I always sleepy?
I will go to Tongmyeonjeon.
You should be careful! Since it is a dangerous rumor...
If it is revealed that the rumor originated from you...
Before Grand Queen Dowager hears the rumor,
I have to relay it myself.
- But—
- Don't worry, Lady Ahn.
She won't even think that I would spread the rumor and tell it to her myself.
I didn't even summon you yet you came to visit me. You must have a favor to ask me.
I was worried that you would be so surprised to hear such a shocking rumor,
so I came here right away.
Rumor?
How is it that you chase after every pathetic little thing?
When you hear it, you won't be able to say that so easily.
I am curious though as to what kind of rumor made you come running to me so excitedly.
It would be a shame for me to miss
your facial expression upon hearing this rumor.
It would be difficult to see the facial expression you hope to see with just any rumor.
The child in the queen's womb is not a royal descendant.
It is the seed of Kim Byeong-in.
You cherished your family so much,
yet the Ansong Kim family will now be recorded in history
as the family that tainted the royal bloodline.
That is interesting. It has become very interesting.
Hey, did you hear that rumor?
I already heard the groundless rumor.
His Majesty and Her Majesty really—
I heard they really and surely bedded together. Fussing around belatedly...
That's not it. I heard that the child is not His Majesty's.
You'll get in trouble for saying such things!
The entire palace is laughing at our family.
Her Majesty and the Minister of Defense are close relatives and... adulterous?
I had such high expectations for the Minister of Defense...
I thought it was over after Eui Bin was removed from her position.
But hearing the news about the queen makes me feel like we've won.
Instead of being a royal descendant, it was a cuckoo chick.
(T/N: Cuckoos are known to lay eggs in the nests of other birds.)
For me, my family is more important than my life.
Therefore, I live for my family. What do you live for?
I, too, am the same as Your Highness.
Is that so?
Then, are you willing to do anything for the family?
Yes.
Then, bring the queen's head to me right now.
It is the family's order.
What in the world is the reason?
The queen completely destroyed our family's honor that we've built up for centuries.
Grand Queen Dowager, I do not know what made you so upset but I ask for leniency.
Everyone in the palace was talking about how the king and queen do not actually spend nights together.
Now, they are saying that the child she's carrying is yours!
That... That is not true!
If everyone believes it, then it is the truth.
When day breaks and the rumor spreads all over,
the queen will be a sinner who became pregnant through adultery, then she lied about the fact,
and is trying to taint the royal bloodline.
The rumor started because of me. I will take the punishment.
If a man gets hurt by a rumor, a woman dies by a rumor.
What is needed to restore the family's honor is the queen's head.
If you personally bring me the queen's head,
I will overlook your sin.
I cannot do that. Please punish me instead!
You said you live for the family but you live only for the queen, is that right?!
Then, I will just have to have someone else do it. Come in!
Immediately!
I will re-new the regency for you.
It seems that you got close to something dangerous.
On the book that has the queen's name written on it,
there is a Donghak code written in your handwriting.
A dangerous ideology has seeped into even the king and queen
causing them to try and overturn the country.
If this kind of danger is felt by those in power, what do you think will happen?
They will try to keep the current Joseon even if it meant killing half the people of this country, will they not?
A massacre of Donghak followers on a grand scale will start.
Then, why did you come to me instead of starting it right away?
Because Her Majesty will also get hurt.
But the Ansong Kim Family
made Her Majesty their target.
Using the rumor that she's pregnant from an adulterous relationship with me,
they are trying to kill Her Majesty's honor.
Since it is to attack me, I will stop it.
You cannot stop it!
Even if you can get her life spared for now,
if the family attacks Her Majesty by entangling her in an ugly rumor,
Her Majesty's life will no longer be that of a living person.
Not only Her Majesty, but it will be the same for the royal descendant who is to be born.
Don't you know how the ministers, who are bent on shaking your position,
will torment Her Majesty!
Only you can save Her Majesty.
What is it? How can I save the queen?
Go and put an end to the uprising.
You need to personally punish the Donghak followers.
Going after the king's woman while the king is out fighting to protect the country
is not righteous so the rumor will lose its power.
Also, by personally punishing the Donghak followers and proving that you are not connected,
then the code in the Dongmongseonseub will no longer be a threat.  (Children's practice (text) book in Joseon)
This is...
the only way to save
Her Majesty and your child that she is carrying.
You don't have time to hesitate. When day breaks, Her Majesty will be swallowed up by the rumor.
I will never...
let Her Majesty get hurt by herself.
♫ Like the faded moonlight ♫
I'm not sleeping.
I'm just thinking for a bit.
You should lie down so you’re comfortable. Why are you doing this?
I came to comfort you.
♫ Your soft heart  ♫
I've been lost in deep thought.
I'm so sleepy.
I'll comfort you tomorrow.
♫ The darkness comes in the sky I was watching  ♫
♫ And at the moment your beautiful face is also soaked in  ♫
You've already consoled me.
♫ The stars sparkling in your eyes  ♫
♫ Fell into my heart too  ♫
♫ It hurt so much  ♫
♫ Even the heart collapsing endlessly  ♫
♫ I want to embrace all of them  ♫
♫ Instead of the sorrow in your eyes  ♫
♫ I want to put me in them  ♫
♫ Wish you look back, please  ♫
The Samnam area has been swept by a rebellion so I am leaving in such a hurry.
While I am away, I request that you take care of state affairs.
Also,
I trust that you will take care of our child as well.
Although I was getting used to letting go of state affairs, I guess I must.
Don't worry about the queen and go.
Her husband is going to the battlefield and risking his life,
it is a definite duty to take care of a woman left alone.
I will trust in those words and leave.
Be careful.
It has already gotten light outside.
Your Majesty.
I'll do the rest.
Is it true that you are going to subdue the rebellion by yourself?
It is true.
What's going on?
The people you were supporting, you're going to harm?
Kim Byeong-In found out about the code in Dongmongseonseub. (Children's practice (text) book in Joseon)
If I don’t leave now, more people will get hurt.
Then, I will accompany you.
The condition is that I must go alone. Isn't it enough to have only me kidnapped?
This is a trap.
Have you ever thought if it was the queen that gave Kim Byeon-In the code?
You clearly promised me.
If you found out the queen became your enemy, you'd cut her head off yourself.
The one you must cut off is not the people, but the queen's neck!
Clearly, the queen is not our enemy!
The queen turned against everyone to take my side.
If I don’t leave right now, the queen will die!
Both of you must calm down. This is no time to fight amongst ourselves.
You told me I should be in more pain.
You're right.
I'll endure everything.
Your Majesty, your life will be in danger.
If I try to live, everyone will die.
I'm sure I saw him.
Was it a dream?
Court Lady Choi. Hong Yeon!
Let's go to Daejojeon. I think we missed the king.
- Yes, Your Majesty!
- Yes, Your Majesty.
His Majesty is leaving right now.
Leaving? To go where?
We will leave now.
Hold on!
Stop right there! Hold on!
W-Why?
Why?
Is this the right road? It doesn't seem like a road for people to go down.
We are taking a shortcut.
Stop.
You're late. If you were going to do this anyway, you should have hurried more.
Will you get off yourself or do you need help?
I don’t have a place to run to... so I'll have to do my best.
Don't worry.
It's enough for me to do alone.
I just have to get rid of you.
Translation and Timing Carefully Crafted
[Mr. Queen]
♫  Where are you? ♫
♫  Where is my dear? ♫
♫ Here I am, here I am, always standing in the same place ♫
This little one sure eats quite a lot!
Say, "Father, please hurry back."
I think I just felt something!
Your Majesty! The King...
Now, the owner of that seat will change.
What is the use of this?
You're not here...
They are not guilty.
Standing on the weak side is also a crime.
Hyungnim, how far are you going to take things?
Above all, please be born healthily and safely.
The life of the queen who, together with you, pushed the king to his death,
I will take with my own hands.
♫  Always standing at the same place  ♫
♫  Still I am, Still I am  ♫