Translation and Timing Carefully Crafted
[Mr.Queen]
[Joseon Queen Consort Runaway Soul Scandal]
[The characters, organizations, and events in this drama are unrelated to any historical facts and all stories are fictional.]
♫  Shivering in the frozen hours  ♫
There are so many things I am grateful for from you.
Even when I tried to leave here, you made me hesitate.
♫ Putting my longing in the wind  ♫
Because I would never be able to see you again.
♫ I'm wandering, looking for you  ♫
♫  Where are you?  ♫
♫ Where are you now, my love?  ♫
♫  Here I am  ♫
[1 hour earlier]
[McDonald's]
[Spring Potato]
[Are you asleep?]
[Episode 14]
Y-Yes, I drew these.
Are you really the one that drew these? Not the queen?
H-Her Majesty the Queen was at the banquet.
Then, what is the reason you used wild grapes, pine needles, and peaches for the appetizer?
T-T-That is because peaches are in season and well...
wild grapes are almost in season and pine needles are always in season—
Man-bok... look me in the eyes and tell me.
Her Majesty the Queen wanted to hide the fact that she helped with it.
Your Majesty, it's late. Please come back again tomorrow.
Brother, you should head in. I must hear it.
Why did she help me? What did she mean by betraying me?
[Dan...]
[Queen in Danger]
When daylight comes, report it to His Majesty.
Should we leave it overnight?
Do not hurry. It might be a trap.
So there are times when you sleep like a well-behaved baby.
I fell asleep.
Were you watching me this whole time?
How come you are like this?
Always worrying about me and trying to understand me.
Come to think of it, when I came here you were the first person I saw.
There are so many things I am grateful for to you.
Even when I tried to leave here,
you made me hesitate. Because I would never be able to see you again.
Hong Yeon.
Oh, has our Hong Yeon been working out lately? All bulked up...
It must be a dream. Even last time, Hong Yeon's face changed.
Are you awake?
What is this!
What happened? What kind of man did something bad to you?
You... It was you!
- Why did the face sparkle and then change into you?
- Pardon me?
Tell me properly. What happened between us last night?
How much of properly do you want me to say?
Tell me without leaving out a single detail.
This is one unusual hobby you have.
If that is the case then.
A white moon rose and shone brightly upon such a jet-black night
and the moment our fingers touched, fireworks burst—
No! Don't tell me. I will kill you if you tell me!
It is just starting... My Queen!
Oh no!
What is this... feeling of abandonment I feel?
Head Eunuch.
Hong Yeon! Where did you sleep yesterday?
In my living quarters, Your Majesty.
Th-Then I really did it with Cheoljong?
Your Majesty!
[Episode 14: The Woman Who Has to Die to Live ]
It was a dream!
His royal portrait was burning. How real it looked...
Since what happened to that fortune teller, I haven't been able to get my fortune read properly.
This seems ominous. Court Lady Han, I must get my fortune read.
Your Highness, that might cause big trouble again.
There is a monk I know.
He won't look suspicious to others, so it will be okay.
[Buddhist chant]
What do you see?
I see the palace full of red blood.
Red blood?
Someone is going to die in the palace today.
Who is going to die?
I can not tell that yet.
It will be a woman.
A woman...
It is not me, right? Write me a talisman... one that will protect me.
I am not... a shaman.
There must be another way!
If you must, you can make an offering to Buddha.
I will do it. I will do as many as needed.
I cannot be the one to die today.
Darn it!
I was not even able to ask the queen what I was supposed to ask her!
You...
I am going back to the queen's palace.
Your Majesty.
It is too suspicious.
Also, with his sudden disappearance.
Right... I can make the composite sketch myself.
I will choose you.
That's right. This is it.
I'll draw the exact one. That's right.
No! This is wrong!
That guy's face...
It's that guy's face.
Officer Hong!
Did you come all this way crying?
There... There...
Why didn't I think of the possibility that she wouldn't like me?
For what reason was I choosing between my lineage and love?
Why did I contemplate that for so many days?
Usually, the most difficult thing about love is
not the other obstacles, but
the process of gaining another's heart.
And what was her reason?
She said...
I do not like you.
Huh?
Then...
Miss!
The reason... Please at least tell me the reason.
What is the reason you don't like me?
I...
do not like an ambitious man.
There... There...
My goodness... How damp.
Usually, affection for love at first comes moistly
but finishes off damp.
But...
There's also good news, right? The king has gotten well so soon.
My prayers must have worked.
You should've heard some other news as well.
I heard that Elder Kim Jwa-geun will be removed from his office due to this.
I like the king and respect Elder Kim Jwa-geun, too.
My heart is split into two.
You haven't even personally met the king, what do you like about him?
That is because he is your best friend.
You are such a good person,
that it is only right, your friend is also a good person.
Oh, you!
Oh!
You were drawing an octopus?
An octopus? This is a person.
This is?
If you look at it one by one, I drew it quite well.
These are the eyes.
That is the mouth.
That is the mouth, right?
There are even lips.
As fortunes go, the morning fortunes are the best.
Your Highness, it is Lady Eui Bin.
Oh, my...
Ah, your face has gotten so haggard overnight.
If someone sees, they might think the king hasn't been able to wake up.
The issue regarding the queen, how did it go?
We gave up on the big picture and did what you wanted.
They probably went to the queen's quarters
and found that item by now.
Last night... the king stayed in the queen's quarters.
As soon as he recovered?
I have realized once more due to this incident...
If I lose the king, I will die.
The woman who is to die today... Can it be her?
I want to die. Should I just die?
If I die, I might feel better.
I'm sorry, Your Majesty. I'm sorry!
I clearly denied it, but the king was too certain.
Huh, what are you talking about?
What?
Where is this burning smell coming from? Who did this?
What kind of man did this?
Where are you going?
Geez, please!
Court Lady Choi—
I happened to reveal everything.
You did? So you're saying,
last night the king came to find me after hearing your words and that's why this whole mess happened?
I did not say it like that.
Ultimately, all of this confusion I am feeling right now is all
because of you.
W-What sort of confusion are you feeling?
It was good for sure. Better than before.
That is why I am going crazy! Why did I like it?
I shouldn't be like this.
Isn't the soul the owner of the body?
Or is both the soul and body not the owner? Are humans just slaves to hormones?
Your Majesty!
Why is she like this?
What are you talking about?
Her Majesty the Queen is acting just like herself.
Why doesn't it make me feel dirty? Why!
Feel dirty! Dirty! Feel dirty!
His Majesty the King is here!
Where is the queen?
Yes, she—
I'm sorry, Your Majesty. She was here just a moment ago.
Why in the world is she avoiding me like this!
Last night, she was like a tiger... Grr!
Will you help me with finding the queen?
Yes, Your Majesty.
As you can see, I have a lot of things to say to her.
Yes.
What sort of words?
No, if I meet Cheoljong right now, it will be really dangerous.
What if my body betrays me again?
That's right. Last night, this woman's soul controlled me for sure.
The thing I liked? Only because I thought it was Hong Yeon.
If I knew that was Cheoljong...
I'd still like it? Am I really crazy?
So, will Jang Bong-hwan disappear forever like this?
Is that what happened?
[I came for no reason...]
- Queen!
- Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty, My Queen!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, My Queen!
My Queen! My Queen!
Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty, My Queen!
- Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
For trying to openly assassinate the king,
it seems Lord Kim Jwa-geun is going to be impeached.
This I say...
No matter how much I think about it, this does not seem like a method Lord Kim Jwa-geun would use.
Perhaps he was put on the defensive.
With this explosion accident, Lord Kim Jwa-geun has lost everything
and the king has gained too much.
Even so, you don't think the king risked his own life and planned the explosion?
You're right...
- Y-Your Majesty!
- Are you on your way to the council meeting?
Yes. What is Your Majesty doing here alone?
The queen is...
Your Majesty, are you playing hide and seek?
I am so freaking good at it, Your Majesty!
- Finally!
- Damn it!
Stop following me! Are you a CCTV camera or some "sasaeng" fan? (T/N: An obsessive idol fan, like a stalker)
- What...
- Your Majesty!
- I will see you at the council meeting.
- Y-Yes.
Let's talk about what's right and wrong, My Queen!
(T/N: Right and wrong - sounds like CCTV in Korean.)
- They seem to have a good relationship.
- Queen!
Hide and seek, really? They're acting like children.
What in the...
Playing hide and seek as soon as he recovered from an almost fatal accident?
That's right, I have my Suk-uis.
The guardian of my (sexual) identity, the one I expressed my love to via Kakao Chat all night long!
(Kakao - A message chat forum)
- Your Majesty, hello.
Hello to all of you.
Now, goodbye.
Queen! Is there a running competition in the palace?
There's no gap between those two for us.
Sure seems like it.
But they look so good together!
Okay, I will recover my identity with Kakao texts.
- Queen!
- Your Majesty!
Queen?
She is not here as well.
I had something I really wanted to ask the queen, which is why I keep chasing after her.
Something he wanted to ask?
It seems the queen feels uncomfortable seeing me,
so I should stop.
When she feels like facing me,
then I guess the queen will let me know.
Let us go to the council meeting.
Yes.
You were here.
You were spinning all around the palace. I had a hard time finding you.
What is the matter?
You were here. Last night...
We will tell you on the way.
Let's go.
Where to, again? Again, where to?
How wide the palace is...
Did he leave?
What does he want to ask so badly that he's like this?
Usually, in situations like this, a man typically asks..."Was it good?"
To the usual place.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Something's missing.
Court Lady Choi!
Yes, Your Majesty?
Why haven't you been nagging me, lately?
"You shouldn't be going around like that, Your Majesty." You should be nagging me like that.
I have quit nagging, Your Majesty.
What a surprise.
- Okay, hurry and go.
- Yes.
What a surprise...
From today on,
I will withdraw my regency.
With this, I declare that I will rule for myself going forward.
- Long Live The King, Your Majesty!
I will die if I live like this.
I am so angry I cannot live this life span given to me.
Should I tell them you will not be eating?
You are actually wishing me to die and planning my funeral, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
But, does this mean you want me to bring in food or not?
If I do, you will definitely say it is food for your funeral.
Do I... have to tell you... every little thing one by one?
Your Highness!
Please calm down.
Do I look like I can calm down?
With this, my life in politics is as good as over!
I will find it for you once more.
You will definitely be able to regain your regency again.
You're so confident.
Your father was like that when he was young.
I gave a final chance to my brother.
What chance did you give him?
He said it's the way to break the king's heart.
If my brother succeeds, you should keep your position for now.
Yes. However, you will find out that an old tool has its limit.
The king is not as easy an opponent as you think.
Do you really think the explosion was the king's own plan?
The person who gained the most is the culprit.
To have such a tiger cub on that seat.
Your Majesty, congratulations on your sole rule.
Thank you.
While you were away, there was a letter from Daejojeon.
- From the Queen?
- Yes.
Should I say, I miss you? So, I miss you.
This will not do.
As expected my last resort. How hot it is!
Let us meet.
You came... to save me from this confus—
Cheoljong? How did you know I was here?
I told you to meet here, so, of course, I know.
- The person who called me here was Suk-ui!
- Which Suk-ui?
I like the thrill their anonymity gives me,
so I purposely didn't find out who she was among the three.
Anyway, it's not you!
"I sometimes think about something else."
"It doesn't matter even if I'm drowning in your thoughts to death,
so please row and come to me."
"Ah! I didn't let you go, my love."
- Stop.
- Do you know now?
No, I do not know that corny poem.
"I will die calling out your name."
"I cannot forg—"
Stop it! People are listening.
It's not like you wrote them, so what is the matter?
We have things to talk about privately, so all of you stay far away. Got it?
Yes, Your Majesty, Our Queen.
Are you surveilling me? Did you inspect my Kakao texts?
What are you talking about?
Through letters, you always express such enthusiastic affection, but when we actually meet, you completely ignore me.
How cruel!
- Accidental delivery?
D-Did you think I was someone else?
My new source of hormones is you?
How can my last line of defense for my identity be you?
The person my heart fluttered and pounded for every night...
was you.
That is why you had two faces.
Why did you come out? Why always?
Every time I opened my eyes it was you. Even in my dream—
Did you dream of me?
Don't get awkward! If you do, it's over.
There are many kinds of dreams. There are also spine-chilling nightmares.
Why did you help out with the banquet?
Did you chase me around to ask about that?
I thought you would thank me. I helped for nothing.
You told me that if I'm glad to see someone, I should curse at them;
and if I feel thankful, I should pick a fight with them for no reason.
Since when have you listened to my words so well?
You make a fuss even if I listen to you.
Which side am I supposed to adhere to?
You said you would do "no touch" toward me and then you help me.
And then you declare you are going to betray me.
For that, I...
Wait a minute.
You heard my words saying I would betray you?
- Oh...
- They said you lost your hearing, but was that a lie?
Don't tell me... Was the accident with the explosion perhaps your own scheme?
It is true that I lost my hearing.
When you were talking to me, it just happened to be the moment that the ringing in my ears disappeared.
Are you crazy? You almost died!
- Queen.
- Did you have to use such a dangerous method?
Y-You... I said this was forbidden.
Hugging like this, laughing, laying next to me.
All of this is forbidden!
I forbid you to forbid me.
I like you, Queen.
Are you someone who falls in love easily? How tacky to confess right after we slept together just once!
It is not like that.
Then, why do you like me?
You are arrogant and your actions are rough,
you only know about yourself and are inconsistent
and have many flaws.
That's right. So you shouldn't like me.
Still, I like you.
Even if you are the person with the most flaws in the world,
I still like you.
That night...
The day I ran into the lake,
do you remember the words I said to you?
You must love me.
I believed I was the only one who could protect you.
That's why I said that.
You needed to love me so I could support you.
That way you and I could both survive.
Is that what that meant?
But... that Kim So-yong does not exist in this world anymore.
The Kim So-yong from that night is dead.
I will no longer hurt you, Queen.
There is nothing more for us,
because I cannot forgive you.
I'm not the real Kim So-Yong.
So... it can't be.
Why? Does Her Majesty the Queen want anything from me?
I gave you trouble last time.
- Last time?
- At the pharmacy...
Oh, th-that was my fault for giving you poisoned water.
Well, even if you gave me the illness and then the medicine,
it still is not right to just pretend it didn't happen.
I picked this up on the way.
Where did she go to have picked up such a precious thing?
An assassination of the king... Why did he proceed with such a big event by himself that only led to his demise?
Lord Kim Jwa-geun lost his touch, I guess.
Even if you are crazy about money, how dare you siphon off weapons!
Do you want to ruin this country? You clearly said there was no problem!
Moving people around as you want, My Lord,
can not be done by your power only.
Are you saying you did this for me?
I only did my best for you to see the outcome, but not to know the process behind it.
For you, My Lord, and for our clan, I did this.
In the worst possible scenario, you must be prepared to face the consequences.
I will give you a chance to redeem yourself.
- Are you all here?
- My Lord!
The queen's father is not here yet.
I did not call him. We are here because of the mistakes he made.
The queen's father has
secretly kept a record of our clan's wealth and possessions.
Thankfully, that ledger is in my hands.
As long as I have power, this item has no use, so do not worry.
However, if I am impeached and lose my power,
I will not be able to protect this.
If you all protect me,
I will also protect you all.
If we protect you,
then what will you do with the king?
If we do not proceed with the impeachment,
then the king will get rid of us all.
There was something made for a country in crisis.
Border Defense Council?
If not for when an incompetent king assumes the royal authority, is there any other crisis?
From now on, everything related to politics
will be through the Border Defense Council.
The item is ready.
Like you said, we put arsenic in the center and froze it.
Once that ice melts, the arsenic will be released.
How long does it take before the arsenic is released?
It will differ depending on the weather,
but it will probably take a short time to finish one cup of tea.
All right.
But... who are you planning to use this on?
If just one woman disappears from the palace,
two men that threaten my position will be broken.
Thank you for not giving up.
I will not forget what kind of mindset you had in order to endure such torture.
Since all of your identities were revealed, it is dangerous to stay in the palace.
Now you must leave the palace
and all of you will each become a seed.
What all of you want...
I will be sure to make it happen.
It feels a bit lonely.
Which foolish man couldn't throw away his regret—
You came.
Put honeycomb-shaped ice blocks into the queen's beverage?
That's right.
All you have to do is put in the ice.
Your Highness the Queen Dowager, I have some important information.
So please, save me.
What is this information?
If you promise to save me first.
- What do you think you are doing?
- Court Lady Han.
For such a bold girl like you to be so scared,
I do not know what exactly it is
but I will do whatever I can as much as my power allows.
T-To me, Lord Kim Jwa-geun said...
If you were going to like me, you should've liked me sooner.
Then Kim So-yong wouldn't have tried to kill herself and I wouldn't be in this situation either.
But the most important part...
I was confident that I had undergone everything the world had to offer.
But there's more to life than I thought I knew.
Last night's feeling was how should I say...
If the life I knew was a fluffy piece of bread, this is...
It's new. I'm only tempted because it's different!
Come to your senses, Jang So-yong! Geez, now I'm even getting my name confused! Dammit!
Your Majesty.
Yes, come in.
Her Royal Highness the Grand Queen Dowager has asked to do brunch.
Brunch at this time?
I'm not in the right mindset to cook.
The Grand Royal Dowager has already prepared everything.
Do I just have to go to Tongmyeongjeon after running around all day, I'm hungry? (Grand Queen Dowager's quarters)?
They are trying to get rid of the queen.
Ultimately, the ledger has come into Lord Kim Jwa-geun's hands.
Who knew that it would come out of the queen's quarters? How come...
I must return to the palace at once.
- What are you doing? Hurry!
- Yes!
You're running off by yourself again!
I am very pissed off because of you, Sir Daeng-daeng!
I am so grateful, Your Royal Highness. How great, a brunch with this wonderful view.
With no more duties, I have a lot of time now.
Let's spend more time like this in the future.
Yes, Your Highness the Grand Queen Dowager.
It wouldn't be brunch without drinks.
The woman who is going to die in the palace is the queen!
Your mother is finally getting revenge!
Translation and Timing Carefully Crafted
Today, I specially prepared ice that is more precious than gold.
It's my first time seeing ice here.
As the sun is beaming down, it is the perfect weather to drink something cool.
Queen... please! Please, Queen.
How dare you!
For Her Majesty the Queen! I have something to tell the queen!
- This is not a place for you. Go away.
- It is important!
Dam-hyang?
Why are you being like this? My neck might also be taken off.
What exactly is this important information?
Do you know that child?
Yes, I see her often in the royal kitchen.
Dam-hyang, what is it?
That is...
I'm sorry.
I came to help serve Grand Queen Dowager.
I told you this was a place for women.
This is the first time I've met you in this setting, please forgive me.
It is my honor.
Like I told you, how is the monitoring of your husband going?
Ah...
It hasn't been long since the king woke up, so I will now do my best from now on.
Let us hurry and drink before the ice melts.
How is the taste?
How refreshing!
It was so refreshing that I couldn't help myself.
Queen!
Your Majesty!
How dare you! What do you think you're doing!
- Are you all right?
- Huh? Yes.
You dared to throw a rock at the queen?
I am all right, Your Highness.
Throw that child in prison right now. She will be punished for showing such disrespect.
Your Highness!
She is a child I cherish. I am fine, so please do not be angry.
This does not concern you.
This has shaken up the order of the inner court and broken Joseon's way of discipline.
She is but a young child. There must have been a reason. She wouldn't have done this for no reason.
If you keep acting like this,
then I will punish that child even more with the crime of showing no remorse.
Why were you running over here in such a hurry?
Did you know that the child would try and hurt the queen?
Are you trying to implicate even me in this?
The timing of your presence was so fitting.
The fact that the one who planned treason would be attending the queen's dining table
had me running here with uneasiness.
This good setting has been ruined. I will head back now.
I will be sure to punish the one who ruined my plans.
Brother, you should also be held responsible.
So that you are not a nuisance to our family clan.
What happened? They won't possibly hit that little girl, right?
Queen, are you really all right? Does your tongue tingle or your heart beat fast?
- What are you saying? The way you're talking sounds like—
- First, let us move elsewhere.
The queen and I will go to Daejojeon.
Yes, Your Majesty.
From now on, any food or drink
or whatever you have to ingest, you must be careful.
Is... someone coming for me?
Kim Jwa-geun and Grand Queen Dowager tried to poison your drink.
You're lying! But I didn't do anything!
Don't tell me... they're trying to kill me because I helped you with the banquet?
A ledger was found in Daejojeon.
Ledger?
Then that was what Kim Jwa-geun and my father kept asking about. What sort of ledger is it, exactly?
Did you not bring it from your parent's house?
I didn't even know it existed. I haven't seen it at my parent's house, let alone at Daejojeon.
I see.
Not even a dethronement, but poisoning...
Then Dam-hyang saved me?
- It seems so...
- So that's it.
But I drank for a long time.
I will ask that child, Dam-hyang myself.
I will ask her myself. Dam-hyang will be okay, right? She must be okay.
The people who wanted you dead will not stay put.
You need to save her.
I will do my best.
I... did nothing wrong.
It is not stolen money.
It is money I have saved up for years to save my younger sibling from slavery.
Please save me.
If I die, my younger sibling...
Everything about this accessory,
tell me in detail.
Dam-hyang.
Your Majesty!
Are you okay, Your Majesty?
It’s me who should ask you that.
I'm glad, Your Majesty.
That the ice didn't melt.
Ice?
Take the criminal!
Yes!
Take her? To where?
Your Majesty, you shouldn't be here.
You know that this child is innocent, right?
What are you talking about?
The only crime she committed was daring to save my life.
I don’t know where you heard that.
But for now, you should head back.
What if I don't want to?
That child will go through the appropriate measures and be dealt with.
If you stay here, even you will be harmed.
Escort Her Majesty, the Queen, to Daejojeon.
- Yes.
Let go of me!
I will escort her.
Please go back, Your Majesty.
Making a fuss like this will not help that child.
Your Majesty.
Dam-hyang, I'll get you out of here soon.
Don't be too scared.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, let's go.
I'll definitely save you.
How dare a child palace maid throw a rock at the queen?
This is blasphemy!
This is not blasphemy, but treason!
Even that child's father is a criminal charged for defaulting on the levy for military service and treason,
it seems like it runs in their blood.
Your reactions are excessive.
It hasn't been revealed yet as to why the child did that.
Even now, those thieves believing in Donghak have grown in their influence (Eastern Learning /Neo Confucian reform )
that they have been threatening the court.
We must justly show discipline and make an example out of them!
Are you trying to connect this to those that believe in Donghak?
Daring to throw a rock at the queen
was no doubt brought on by this rebellious ideology.
She is only a five-year-old child, but to say she was affected by a rebellious ideology...
I'm sorry, but during the time Your Majesty lived on Ganghwa Island,
some say that you too learned this Donghak ideology.
Is this your new weapon?
If you continue to protect that child and refuse to punish her,
it is no different than you as the king condoning this rebellious ideology.
That is how we will think of it.
If you punish this palace maid with certainty,
then this matter will be over.
(T/N: 'Donghak' = 'Eastern Learning' was a reform movement of Neo-Confucianism. It introduced the ideas of democracy and human rights, which threatened the class system.)
That should be enough.
Grand Queen Dowager told us to be strict with the king.
Is she throwing a tantrum because she lost her power?
How could that lowly child maid
have ruined a golden opportunity
to remove the queen?
Why isn't he coming?
He should be doing well, right?
The fact that the council meeting is going on for so long isn't a good sign though.
- Your Majesty!
- Yes?
Your Majesty, it's this way!
All of you, remember this for a very long time.
In the palace, you palace maids must not see nor hear
nor even think such blasphemous thoughts.
If you come across anything seditious like Donghak or its motto, "All humans are the same under the Heavens,"
know that you will receive the same punishment.
- She is but a child. How could she—
- Shush!
Quiet!
I thought we would catch a big fish,
but it is a mere child maid.
Am I too late?
Now you know how I feel.
She was only trying to save you.
That is why they killed her.
Because she stopped them from trying to kill me.
What crime has this child committed?
You told me
that this young child was taking the blame for the crimes of people like them.
Why didn't you save her?
I had to for the greater good. I had no other choice.
The greater good?
Your safety is for the greater good?
You are the one that said that nothing in life is fair!
With this small sacrifice,
I stopped a bigger sacrifice.
Small sacrifice?
Because she was just a weak, small little girl?
Being incompetent is a crime.
Not having the power to be able to protect even this one little child... is a crime.
Why don't we make a hand signal that we only know? Like this.
"What I'm saying right now is a lie."
That's what it means.
:  Translation and Timing Carefully Crafted
[Mr. Queen]
From now on, the crazy bitch in this palace is me.
I will let you all know who it is you tried to mess with.
Did you try to get rid of the queen?
Dam-hyang...
All-in!
What's scary about Kim Byeong-in is that he can even embrace the Jo Family.
Let's form an alliance.
From now on, you and I are no longer in a "no touch" situation.
Calm down, my heart.
Shall we say this is a sort of research or test?
Do you want to eat ramen before you go?
(Modern Korean code to have sex, like "Netflix and chill")