[English subtitles are available]
[Rising With the Wind]
[Episode 9]
[All animals in this show were filmed under safety guidance]
[Do not imitate]
Even now,
you're still safeguarding
his job in Free Unicorn.
Don't drink it.
That's my wine.
Put it down.
Don't drink if you won't join us.
What even is this?
Pretending to be someone he's not.
Even dressed in a suit,
a dog is still a dog.
Come on.
Jiang Hu.
You're the best.
You're the only one who's humane.
Come on.
Let's wrap the rest up and take it home.
It'll be a pity if it's wasted.
Let's drink.
Come on.
We've arrived?
It'll still take a while.
Have a good sleep.
I'll wake you up when we get there.
Jiang Hu.
I'm so unlucky.
How come I meet you here again?
Let me tell you.
If...
If I had a membership card for any other restaurant,
I would never
eat here.
If I knew you'd be here,
I wouldn't have stored so much money here.
Jiang Hu.
Keep your feet.
Xu Si.
You're so smug.
Seriously, you're so smug.
Don't be so smug.
Don't be so smug, seriously.
Okay?
Mr. Xu.
She's drunk.
I'll get this lady
some warm water.
Okay.
Jiang Hu.
Keep your feet.
How much did you drink?
And it's all liquor.
What are you doing?
You can lean on me,
but don't throw up on me.
Keep your feet.
Hang in there.
I'll take you to the ladies' room.
Let's go.
Mr. Xu.
Come on.
Let me.
Let me help you put it on.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Jiang Hu is drunk.
She's drunk.
Do you always drink like this?
No.
I've never seen her drink like this.
She's in a bad mood.
She took it hard,
so she drank too much.
Who were you
having dinner with?
The old employees
of Free Unicorn.
We wanted to get them
to come back and work with us in Teng Yue.
But
none of them agreed.
Human feelings of sympathy are as thin as paper.
They are all so ungrateful.
For real.
I'm sorry.
There's some more here.
It's okay.
It's all gone.
All right, Mr. Pei.
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm alright.
Okay.
You must feel sick.
Look at you.
Why do you have to let those people
rattle your cage?
The investors make things difficult for me,
the distributors put up a front,
and the old employees disdain me.
What I'm suffering now
is all to pay
for what I did in the past.
That Ren Bing.
Just ignore him.
But Xu Si
didn't relent
and let you use the factory.
You drank so much.
If you said something wrong
and offended him,
which affects Teng Yue's business,
it will only make things harder for you.
You really need to take care of yourself,
or your dad wouldn't rest in peace.
It's not safe
to drink this much outside,
especially for a girl.
Always bear it in mind.
When my dad nagged,
I used to think he was annoying.
Now I don't even have the chance to hear it again.
When you talked to me like that,
it felt pretty good.
I was immature before.
Sorry, Ms. Yue.
It's okay.
My dad said
you're a trustworthy friend.
Unfortunately, I'm retired.
I can't provide you with any more help.
Take care of yourself.
[Teng Yue Shoes]
Dad.
What should I do?
Teng Yue is too old.
No one believes it can change,
and no one believes that I can change it.
Is this really a fantasy?
But I want to turn
this fantasy into a barracks.
This is reality.
This is "Running against the wind".
Those are old employees
of Free Unicorn.
We wanted to get them
to come back and work with us in Teng Yue.
But
none of them agreed.
Human feelings of sympathy are as thin as paper.
They're are all so ungrateful.
I'll run against the wind.
♫I look forward to that day♫
♫When light comes♫
♫Look up at the sky♫
♫The dazzling fireworks♫
♫The past that should be remembered♫
♫Only by breaking through the mire♫
♫Can I embrace pride♫
♫Fly♫
♫With faith in my heart♫
♫The end of winter♫
♫Spring comes and flowers bloom♫
[Changle Restaurant]
[Wonton]
Today is a nice day.
Let's have a game first.
Okay.
Up to you, Sir.
Then...
Chess it is.
Are you planning
to establish an M&A fund
with Jingyang?
One plus one is greater than two.
We and Jingyang
can complement each other in many aspects.
I believe Aneda will understand that
we and Jingyang
are the best options for now.
Although it's not what I want,
sharing profits with others,
I believe in
your professionalism in this.
You're even so good at chess.
I have nothing to worry about.
Just have at it.
The advertisements in the atrium here
need to be adjusted.
The placement over there
also needs to be adjusted.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
The top host of TT Media,
Nan,
stalked the new host signed by TT Media, took candid photos of her,
and paid online haters to smear her.
I didn't expect
it turns out to be
your company's internal friction.
I can't believe
you got the surveillance footage of our office.
[Jiang Hu]
Hanging up on me?
How ridiculous!
I just want to remind you that
the internal management of your company
is going out of control.
This shouldn't happen
in a top influencer marketing agency.
I will fix
the relationship between Nan and Zhaoyang.
As for Nan,
what's your opinion on his punishment?
I'll leave it to your discretion.
After all,
there's currently no host in TT Media
who has a better performance than Nan.
I thought...
You thought what?
I thought the rumor Nan started was true.
We've known each other for so many years,
but you still don't know me well.
Now I do.
As long as it's about work,
no one is human to you.
They're all tools.
As expected from you, Xu Si.
I'm leaving.
You told me off
this early in the morning.
I need to cool off.
Hello?
What's up?
I dirtied your clothes
at C Club last time, right?
I bought a new one to make it up to you.
Today?
I'll text you where and when.
See you tonight.
Hello?
See you tonight?
What the heck?
[Wish you good fortune] [May wealth come generously to you]
[Bo's Ginger Chicken]
Have a seat.
What do you want to eat?
Take a look at the menu yourself.
You read it right.
The average cost here is 50 to 60 yuan per capita.
This doesn't match
your usual lavish lifestyle.
You're saving money for me?
This place is my choice,
so this meal is on me.
You're not trying
to make an issue of it
and mock me again, are you?
If I don't take the opportunity of this meal
to play some tricks,
I'll fail to live up
to your imagination, right, Ms. Jiang?
Xu, you're here.
Lu.
You brought...
A friend, right?
So, as usual, Ginger Chicken,
Steamed Sea Bass with Plums,
and Eggplant Stew?
Miss, would you like to order something else?
Chinese Kale with Black Bean Sauce,
and Dry-fried Green Beans.
Okay. Okay.
All vegetables.
You're too thin. You should eat more.
We're out of
sparkling water today.
How about
some Honey Lemon Tea?
Hong Kong-style Milk Tea, large, double sugar.
Something went wrong?
Don't worry.
After drinking the milk tea, your worries will be gone.
Hong Kong-style Milk Tea is our specialty.
Do you want to try it?
No.
I'll have lemonade.
I don't rely on sugar to relieve my stress.
Got it.
It's good for your health.
Take your time.
It seems
you're not in a good mood.
Is it because of that rumor online?
Don't ask about things that don't concern you.
I won't vent my anger on you,
and I won't make any issue of it.
Why are you smiling?
It seems that the rumor online
did cause big trouble
to your work.
Why are you so sure?
Couldn't it be for personal matters?
You're neither
Xiang Zhaoyang's type,
nor the type of person
who'd be troubled by
some private scandals.
You know me well, Ms. Jiang.
After all,
we've had so many weird interactions, right?
Didn't you say
you have clothes for me
when you asked me out today?
Is this it?
Yes.
Right.
Here you are.
Gifts should be able to blind the eyes,
but I'm an exception.
Even though you gave me a gift today,
the "military writ" of selling 20,000 pairs of shoes a month
is still valid.
I won't go easy on you.
What are you talking about?
This is just my compensation
for offending you last time, okay?
And to say thank you, Mr. Investor,
for taking some time off
your busy schedule to have dinner with me.
It must have cost you dearly.
How do you know my size?
I grew up in Free Unicorn.
Estimating the size of clothes
is my professionalism.
I thought...
What?
Don't make random assumptions.
Don't doubt
my professionalism in this business.
I will definitely make Teng Yue
rise again.
All you want to talk about is Teng Yue.
Thank you.
Try it.
I don't want to talk about work today.
[Bo's]
Thank you.
I'm off.
When did you get another moped?
I didn't charge mine.
This is Qin's moped.
54%.
Give me a ride to the parking lot.
Where's your car?
At that hour,
do you think four wheels could be faster than subway?
I came by subway.
I'll get a taxi for you.
It's hard to get a taxi at this hour.
I don't want to wait.
There're shared bikes over there.
A competitor invested in these.
I didn't install the App.
Why are you so troublesome?
It's just I've never given anyone a ride on my moped before.
Even if you dare to come,
I dare not take you.
There's always a first time for everything.
I'm not afraid.
Let's go.
Get down.
No.
I'll get you a helmet.
You ride it pretty well.
I'm on racer level, okay?
A financial elite like you
asked a girl to give you a ride home on a moped.
Aren't you afraid you'd be laughed at?
Shut up.
When you got drunk last time,
you tormented me, okay?
You're so vengeful.
Ride properly.
I just complimented you.
Aren't you on racer level?
I did it on purpose.
You're pretty good at riding.
It won't happen next time.
Are you leaving without saying goodbye to me?
Goodbye.
Be careful.
I tried it on.
It fits me well.
Not bad.
Especially the cufflinks.
By the way,
did you also treat
your former bosses with so much care?
I tried it on.
It fits me well. Not bad.
Especially the cufflinks.
By the way,
did you also treat
your former bosses with so much care?
I never had a boss before.
Then I'm honored to be the first boss
to teach you how to butter someone up.
Thank you
for giving me a chance to butter you up.
Good night.
[Teng Yue Shoes] [Company Profile]
Master Zhang.
You're still working at this hour?
I have something to ask you, Ms. Jiang.
That Mr. Du,
Du Wenhua.
Have you tried to contact him?
I called him.
He said
he wouldn't sell Teng Yue's shoes anymore.
The Du family
used to be a distributor in the wood and soil business 30 years ago.
They were the biggest distributor
of Teng Yue.
Companies,
schools, sports meetings,
big or small grocery stores,
wholesale markets,
and department stores.
Their family had all the
distribution channels.
They have very wide connections.
If they're this good,
logically speaking,
they should still be
one of the top distributors in the industry.
How did they end up like this?
Back then,
we were also one of the top brands
in this industry, weren't we?
Here's the thing.
You can try to have a talk
with him.
Okay?
You can bring some gifts.
He
likes coffee.
Master Zhang.
Rest early after your work's done.
Okay, go ahead.
[TT Media]
The company has found out
who's behind this, right?
Don't take it
too seriously.
It concerns my family.
How can I not take it seriously?
The news nowadays
can only be viral for 24 hours.
People will forget it very soon.
But I can't.
Our company has asked the website
to delete those malicious comments.
Your image
has not been greatly damaged either.
You even gained over 100,000 followers.
Although the process wasn't pleasant,
the result is good.
I'm not the one
our company is trying to defend, right?
I know who it is that can get you
to come forward and reconcile us.
Zhaoyang.
The planner has sent you
the new plan designed for you
on WeChat, right?
Take a look when you have time.
In the next stage,
the focus of the company
will completely be tilted towards you.
The budget made for you
is also the highest in the company.
We'll promote you to the top level
as soon as possible.
So our company plans
to turn a blind eye to it
and just move on?
If you still can't get over it,
I can make it up to you
in another way.
No need.
Since the company has expressed
its attitude,
I know
what I should do.
Xiang Zhaoyang.
Don't do anything rash.
Different makeup bases require
different makeup removal tools.
If you want to hold on to your position
as the No.1 host of TT Media,
you won't be able to achieve it
by such despicable means.
Remember.
If it ever happens again,
I'll do this
during your livestream.
Good.
Keep going.
Be careful.
Be neat.
Pay attention to your steps.
One, two, three, four.
Good.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Qin.
Watch your steps.
Okay.
Good.
Keep going.
Great!
They are all wearing Teng Yue's shoes.
That old man Du
is really something.
He's good at choreography,
and he's smart.
Look.
We're all in uniform clothing.
Good.
Excuse me.
Make way.
Watch out.
A truck's coming through.
Come on.
Make way.
Please.
Stand a bit aside.
A truck's coming through.
Make way please.
Thank you.
Come on.
All right, come here first, Madam.
Come here.
Move to the side.
Get ready to take
the things we need down.
It's okay.
Du Wenhua.
Why are you here again?
What?
This is not your backyard.
What? Are you kicking us out again?
Get off my back.
[Song Jiali, shoes and clothes distributor]
Go away.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Take care.
Let's go over there.
What's this about?
Let's go.
It's okay. Let's go.
Let's come again tomorrow.
They're bullying us.
Exactly.
Du.
After all, their team
is going to attend the competition.
You can't compete with them.
Besides, they even have a truck.
Their speakers
are also much better than yours,
which is about to be broken.
You're not professional.
It's okay. I know what to do.
Let's go.
That's all for today.
Let's come again tomorrow.
Music start.
That's all for today.
Let's go.
Start.
One, two, three, four.
Good.
Come on.
Left, right. Left, right.
Hands up.
Right.
Smile.
Show your energy.
Great.
Qin.
Something's not right with you today.
What's wrong?
Your couldn't get your tempo right.
Can you blame me for this?
It's all your fault.
Why is it my fault?
You asked us all
to wear the shoes you bought.
A pair only costs 30 yuan.
How good can the quality possibly be?
Look at my feet.
They've been swollen for a week.
How can I possibly get the tempo right?
Look.
It still hurts.
Exchange my shoes for another pair.
As long as the shoes are not damaged,
you can exchange them within 7 days.
But it's been 14 days. You can't exchange them now.
Let me see what the problem is.
Qin.
Your feet are different-sized.
You can't blame it on the shoes.
This is an old brand.
The quality is very good.
For real.
Your feet are different-sized.
-How about this?
-What?
You just squatted and took a look,
and suddenly it's my problem?
Of course.
I've been selling shoes for half of my life.
I can tell
whose feet are different-sized at a glance.
How about this?
Give me 18 yuan.
Your left foot is size 37,
and your right foot may be size 37.5,
or even 38.
I'll give you a pair of different-sized shoes.
I'll only charge you for 18 yuan,
and your problem will be gone.
It won't hurt, wearing these.
Du.
My feet hurt too.
Could it also be my feet are different-sized?
It's possible.
Don't be nervous.
It's normal to have different-sized feet.
Basically, everyone has it.
You won't feel it when you walk normally every day,
only during strenuous exercise.
If you need it,
I'll give every one of you a new pair.
It's definitely comfortable to wear.
Then give us a discount.
Yes.
Make it cheaper.
We can only wear those
for square dances,
not in any other occasion.
These shoes are only 39 yuan per pair.
How much does a cup of Starbucks
cost our grandchildren?
How about this?
You each hand in 13 yuan,
and I'll give each of you a pair of different-sized shoes.
And 3 yuan more
for loafer shoelaces.
One pair for each.
You won't need to tie your shoelaces anymore.
How's that?
Great.
You can exchange it within a month
if there's any problem.
Okay, okay.
I'll take one.
Do you want to buy shoes, Miss?
So you're an insurance agent.
Listen.
I have social security.
I don't need it.
Besides, I don't take health supplements.
I'm even healthier
than you young people.
I don't need
credit cards or anything like that.
Stop following me.
Mr. Du.
Hello, Mr. Du.
I'm from Teng Yue.
I brought you some coffee
as a gift to our old distributor.
Santa Ines?
Fifty dollars per pound.
Teng Yue never spends this much
on customer rewards.
Mr. Du, you're our regular guest.
You know how good the imported goods are.
Don't let such good stuff go to waste.
As for you...
Go back.
After selling this batch of goods,
I will never
stock your products again.
Mr. Du.
I hope you can help us
to expand other distribution channels.
I saw you selling different-sized shoes just now.
I think it's a great idea.
No wonder my dad always said
you know how to sell shoes.
Who is your dad?
Jiang Qisheng.
Jiang Qisheng would talk about me?
Are you Jiang Hu?
You're just like your dad.
You can make up stories even without drafts.
It's true.
Mr. Du, don't you doubt it.
Let me help you with the speaker...
Jiang Qisheng.
We stopped talking to each other
over 10 years ago.
There's no reason for us to get back in touch now.
It's okay.
We can start over.
If you need anything
in the future,
you can call me anytime.
I will do my best to help you.
Do your best?
[Changle Restaurant]
I've asked.
This is the established
coaxial speaker called Tannoy Stirling
sold in Hong Kong in the 90s.
No one we know knows how to fix it.
The limos
of San's wedding company
are all occupied for Wedding Expo.
The exhibition will only be over in 5 days.
Ke's car service and retail store
is under close watch by the brand.
There are 24-hour surveillance cameras in the store.
There's no way.
Does the car have to be so expensive?
It's just for square dances.
As long as it can play music, right?
Why does he have to make it
like a concert?
I didn't expect
Mr. Du would propose
such a ridiculous request either.
He asked me to repair his speaker
and rent a limo for him.
It's making my head hurt.
Is Mr. Du really that good?
He really is good at
selling shoes.
He has a lot of channels.
If I can get him,
I can get the investors.