Hold him.
Let's end it for all today, Father.
My goodness.
I hit him right at the spot,
but he's still conscious.
You really are sturdy.
Just lie down, you jerk.
If you left without causing any
trouble when I went easy on you,
you'd have saved your life,
and I wouldn't have wasted my time.
How great would it have been?
Why did you have to
complicate things?
Hey.
Are you laughing?
Are you laughing right now?
You wouldn't be able to laugh soon,
so go ahead and laugh.
You should go now.
Go and say hello...
to Father Lee for me.
Who are you?
We got a report that a wild boar
burst into the warehouse.
- What?
- Well...
We might have to
search around a little.
What's this?
I don't think we have to.
Gosh, it must hurt so much.
Let's go.
Where do you think you're going?
Stop right there.
Report to the cops,
and tell them we need
two ambulances.
- Hurry.
- Yes, sir.
Yes, Dong Ja.
He'll be quiet for a while.
Yes, okay.
Bye.
The Grim Reaper
in charge of the priest...
must've taken the day off today.
Let's go.
(Do not urinate.)
Father Kim. Father Kim!
Father Kim.
- Call... Call an ambulance.
- Okay.
Gosh.
Father Kim. Father Kim, wake up.
What... Father Kim.
I'm not going to die.
Goodness, Kyeong Seon.
You really are amazing.
People's opinions about the chief
of borough have changed completely.
Young people do have better insight
when it comes to dealing with...
the press and the web.
Older people like us
aren't so very good at it.
It's actually become a lot easier...
to manipulate the public opinion
compared to the past.
That's what's so interesting.
With the development
of the internet and media,
you'd expect that people
would become smarter.
But they get fooled more easily.
And even when the truth
comes out later on,
they don't admit
that they got fooled.
Why? Because they're embarrassed.
Not only do they not admit,
but they also attack the truth
because of their embarrassment.
Exactly.
And we just have to
put that to our use.
By the way, we'll no longer
have to worry about that priest.
Remember the guy...
I told you about last time
that took care of Father Lee?
It seems like he dealt
with the priest.
What do you mean?
He beat him up so much
that he's half dead.
Well, that's that.
I called you here to tell you
something important.
Kyeong Seon.
Oh, yes. Please tell me.
My gosh. Goodness, you startled me.
It's Yo Han and Song Sac.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I didn't get badly injured.
I hurt my head,
so I had to get stitches.
But I'm okay.
I'm more worried about you,
Father Kim.
Your hand got injured even worse.
You fractured your 3rd and 4th rib.
And your entire body is bruised.
Fortunately, that's it.
Father Kim.
I need to go back
to the convenience store...
because it's time for
the new products to arrive.
I also need to get up early
to move the ingredients...
and clean the restaurant.
I'm sorry, you guys.
No, don't say that.
Father Kim, we helped
because we wanted to.
Right?
- You jerk.
- I'm sorry.
Yes, you guys should go now.
And make sure you buy painkillers
on your way back.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
I know it hurts,
but doesn't it feel nice?
We did something huge.
You shouldn't let Jang Ryong
mess around with you anymore.
Just fight back, okay?
I won't...
get beaten up,
but I won't fight back either.
I need to work hard, earn money,
and send that to Thailand.
If I get hurt,
I won't be able to work.
But you still need to show
that you're angry.
You can't always let them
mess around with you.
A person who doesn't know
how to get angry is a fool.
But a person who chooses
not to get angry is wise.
Does that mean I acted like a fool
earlier at the restaurant?
Yes, so don't get angry from now on
for my sake.
You'll get hurt again.
Okay, fine. I'm the fool.
Live the rest of your life
letting them mess around with you.
- Hey, Yo Han.
- Let go of me.
Yo Han.
Kyeong Seon, would you like to
become a member of our group?
If you officially become a member,
you can go from Seocho-dong
to Yeouido and Hyoja-dong.
You can go wherever you want.
And of course,
you'll get paid more than enough.
What do you say?
It's a huge honor, sir.
But can you please
give me some time?
Are you trying to play hard to get?
No, sir.
It's just that I need to take care
of some stuff first.
Then I should give you time
to do that.
But don't take too long.
(Father Tsunami Kim)
It's weird for me to call him.
How much did he get injured?
Gosh.
What's wrong with you today?
What?
You sacrificed yourself
to rescue Detective Seo.
Then you made a report
and saved me.
And now, you're feeding me
abalone soup.
Did you choose to spend all day
doing nice things?
Yes, that's right.
I woke up this morning...
and set a goal to do just that.
Come on. Tell me why
you're being like this.
Well...
Well, the thing is...
If I didn't do anything,
someone would've gotten hurt.
That's why. There's no other reason.
- What are you going to do from now?
- What do you mean?
Are you...
going to continue doing nice things?
Or are you going to continue
being Cheol Bum's minion?
Let's not talk about him.
Gosh.
Goodness, Detective Koo.
You don't need to be in front
of the cross to atone for something.
Going back to where
you first started...
and choosing to walk
the right path...
is also an act of
atoning for your sins.
You should finish up.
No.
I want to go downstairs.
Can you get me a wheelchair?
What a relief.
Her fever's gone, and she's slowly
regaining her consciousness.
Why didn't they treat her with
good medicine from the beginning?
We should make Wangmat Foods...
pay for the rest
of her medical expenses.
Now that I see Eun Ji,
what you said to me
finally feels like reality.
What? The fact that
we at least got a half point?
(Ledger)
Check the names of the people
and firms that are in the ledger.
You might find
Cheol Bum's connections...
or additional information.
There's never a moment
when he's not cool.
(Ledger)
(Feb 5, 7pm: Business trip to
Hwang Cheol Bum's villa)
(Suicide Case of Father Lee
of Gudam Church)
(Personal Details Report)
(Feb 5, 7pm: Business trip to
Hwang Cheol Bum's villa)
(Date of incident: Feb 5, 2019)
(Sunwoo Hospital)
What did I tell you?
I constantly told you to be careful.
I told you again and again
that you'll get yourself in trouble,
but you never listened.
Now, look at what happened to you.
Okay, I get it. I'm very sorry.
But your nagging is hurting my ears.
Look at all those scars
on his handsome face.
It must hurt so much.
Weren't you with him, Detective Koo?
It... It would've been nice
if I was there to fight with him...
He came late because
he had to catch a robber.
If it weren't for him,
things would've been even worse.
I knew it. This time again.
Thank you, Detective Koo.
Thank you.
You didn't look nice at first sight,
but as I get to see you more...
What?
Goodness, Father.
You got more scratches
than I thought.
This is...
how my boss feels.
It's a special set.
It costs 100 dollars.
Why did you come to the hospital?
You should just go today, Mr. Jang.
I'm not here today
to pick up a fight.
As our boss is so busy,
I came here to give his word
on behalf of him.
It's the same as you give a word
in your church.
I don't want to listen. Get lost.
Listen to me carefully, Father.
If you play smart one more time,
my boss will make people prepare
for the funerals of you,
the part-timer at the convenience
store, and the Thai delivery guy.
You really...
Are you feeling bad?
I should go now then.
That punk.
I'm worried about you.
That evil gangs.
Father Han, please start
the discharge procedures.
No. You need to stay here longer.
No, I'm fine.
I'll get changed at the church
and go to the station, so go first.
Don't tell me you have pain
in your back later.
I won't.
Wait a minute.
Before I go to church,
I need to stop by at one place.
Why?
(You're a coward who hits
from the back.)
What a jerk.
Is that true?
Superintendent Nam
and Congressman Park?
Yes. I think they met
Congressman Seong Dong Cheol...
to make him a new candidate
for the chief of borough.
I'm speechless.
I guess it finally started.
Let's make the new player
play an exhibition game.
This is the message the Pope
sent himself at dawn.
I heard unfortunate news.
The behavior of Father Michael...
to save Father Gabriel
is becoming a problem.
I heard that public opinion
is not favorable.
We need to put
the national laws first.
If a legal problem occurs in Korea,
the Vatican cannot help you.
Please mind your words and behavior.
If a problem occurs again,
I will stop putting my trust
on Father Michael.
Any further measures...
on Father Gabriel would stop.
Father.
The news yesterday is not
Father Kim's fault.
I will keep in mind...
of what the Pope said.
Park Kyeong Seon.
(Gudam Police Station,
Superintendent Nam Seok Gu)
What's this?
These are materials on Nam Seok Gu,
Gudam Police Station Superintendent,
and Park Won Mu, the congressman
in Gudam Borough.
Aren't these two
among your party...
of Gudam Borough?
That's right.
I'm going to do
an interim evaluation...
to check if they're really qualified
to be a family.
Analyze those carefully.
Yes. I understand.
It's a little bit strange, isn't it?
You wonder if you're shooting
to an ally.
No, it's not.
You know,
I like treason, but I hate traitors.
You understand that, right?
Yes.
I'll check these out in detail.
People say everyone has a skeleton
in their closet,
but their closets are made of
skeletons in the first place.
If I follow my decision,
I'd like to take
all the responsibilities...
and leave the office
of chief of borough.
However,
as people of Gudam...
and netizens want,
I...
will reverse my resignation...
and stay at the office
of Chief of Gudam Borough...
once again.
Her comments are all so
a piece of dirt.
Gosh.
(Prosecution says, "It's not illegal
and we're investigating properly.")
What?
Are you going to have a new member?
Why are you being so sensitive?
She's not a member yet.
She's about an intern for now.
- Who is it?
- You know.
The one that helps us among
Chief Prosecutor Kang's juniors.
She took care of my business
so neatly this time.
She also stabbed
that priest in the back.
You can exchange greetings
with her later.
Dong Ja.
You didn't bring her
as you don't trust me, did you?
How can you say that?
She's working in a totally
different field from yours.
You're right.
Our fields are different.
It's fine then.
You should fill up the hole made
from Wangmat Foods.
You should save money
not to get the blame.
Right.
I need to fill up that hole.
That's my job.
(A good city to live in,
a city without a crime)
(Gudam District Council)
Hoon Seok.
You go around filling up holes
every day...
and take all the blame.
Aren't you sick of it honestly?
I'm just taking care of you.
Are you?
What are you going to do if I say,
"We'll risk our lives."
I'll be on the front line.
You're saying nonsense, you punk.
Are you going to be on the front
without me, you punk?
I get it.
Let's see.
Ukha.
It's coming.
Who's the woman
my husband is with?
Long hair and burgundy lipstick.
A leopard miniskirt
and cowboy boots.
Master.
She's filled with
female energy overall.
Two of them went inside a motel.
The name of the motel,
the name of the motel is...
Flower...
Oregon. Flower. Oregon.
Oregon.
The number of their room is...
The number is...
I can't see as my spiritual power
is decreasing.
With the power of enlightenment,
once again...
Ukha.
I see. I see.
The number... The number...
- You're going completely insane.
- You're going completely...
Gosh.
I'll tell the number later.
Ukha.
- Ukha.
I'm going to kill those
with my hands.
Hey.
Your nephew is ruining things...
and you're selling junks here?
She made a reservation.
And you will take care
of that part, I guess.
Shut up.
In two weeks, apply for a foundation
and make one quickly.
Do it as fast as you can.
I didn't get the orphanage yet.
Did the ones in the ranks allow it?
You punk. It's an order. An order.
You shouldn't do that.
If I listen to what you say
and get in trouble...
Just do as I say.
Master!
Who told you to think...
about if that makes sense or not?
Don't beat him!
You'd better beat me!
Are you really going to be beaten?
I will show Master my enlightenment.
Ukha!
Ukha.
Hey.
Wait a minute.
Help me!
He must be possessed
by an evil spirit!
Ukha!
Gosh, really.
What can you get from that?
Detective Seo, wake up. Wake up.
Take this off.
Go to the women's lounge
and sleep comfortably.
It's okay.
Isn't this the copy of
Wangmat Foods' ledger?
What are you doing with these?
Father Kim wanted me
to check on some things.
Why did he have to
spread himself so thin?
Why would you put it that way?
It'd be good to secure a list.
Father.
What happened to your face, Father?
I had a fight with Hwang Cheol Bum.
If you look this bad,
then he must be in the ICU.
- He's in a bad shape.
- I bet he is.
Bad shape, my foot.
He's totally fine.
He hit Father Kim first
from the back.
That cowardly jerk.
How dare he hit Father Kim's face?
I'll go and get them this second.
Don't get worked up.
You can do that next time.
- Did you find anything new?
- That's not what's important!
It is important
to find something new.
Yes, I found something new.
I found something suspicious.
Take a look at this.
(Feb 5, 7pm: Business trip to
Hwang Cheol Bum's villa)
"Feb 5, Business trip to..."
"Hwang Cheol Bum's villa."
Feb 5 is...
That's the day
Father Lee passed away.
- Where is the villa?
- According to its registration,
it's located on the outskirts
of Gudam, Gyowae-dong, 37.
How far is it from the place
where Father Lee's body was found?
It's 1.2km far.
1.2km? That's very close.
This must be it.
I'm getting the vibes. This is it.
Let's go. Let's go get them.
Let's go fight.
Let's go!
What is it? What are you up to?
You're making me nervous.
What happened?
There's a great duck restaurant,
so we were checking its location
on the map.
So you like a grilled duck.
My gosh.
What happened to your face, Father?
Why are you acting like
you don't know?
You got the call
from the paramedics.
It must've been obvious.
Tell me how the grilled duck is
after you taste it first.
(Violent Crimes Team 2)
He's just saying that
out of embarrassment.
- Detective Seo.
- Yes, sir.
Find the whereabouts of
Wangmat Foods' Ki Yong Chan first.
I'll go alone today.
Why?
You can work with me only when
you make your stance clear.
I can't work with someone
whose identity is uncertain.
One more thing. Reflect on yourself
and think about what you've done.
I'm off now.
- Father Kim.
- What?
Call me if anything unusual happens.
Since many are keeping an eye
on me, I'll be at the church.
Good.
Does that mean you're broke?
Darn it. Then what should we do?
You said we'd go to Guam together.
- Don't you remember?
- Don't worry.
I have so many
secret bank accounts.
Really?
What shall we do at Guam?
When we are at Guam...
Can't we just live there?
Shall we? Shall we live there?
I'd love that.
Then...
we'll go out of touch
once we reach Guam.
- Right.
- Then...
they'll never hear from us.
They'll never hear from us.
You're so funny.
Don't say such things.
That annoys me.
Sorry? I already paid a third
of the hospital fee.
I'll pay the rest even if I have to
borrow money from loan sharks.
Take a seat. I'm here
to talk about something else.
Okay.
I'd like a glass of ssanghwacha.
- Okay.
- Hurry.
Why did you deliver food...
to Hwang Cheol Bum's villa
on Feb 5?
Pardon?
Hwang Cheol Bum's villa
on Feb 5.
How can I remember that?
You must remember it since
it's related to Hwang Cheol Bum.
I'm not sure. I must've delivered it
because they made an order.
Of course you must've delivered it
That wasn't the point
of my question.
Who delivered the food?
I can't remember.
Here's your ssanghwacha.
It's still hot.
Thank you.
Gosh, it's hot.
Do you want me to make you
drink this in two seconds?
Only then you'd be able to remember.
Did just the two of you go there
on that day?
Yes, there wasn't much to deliver,
so just the two of us
could cover it.
Around how many servings
did you deliver?
It was a meal for 3 to 4 people,
and some snacks for wine.
What kind of snack suits wine?
- Pardon?
- Hey.
I'll just have soju then.
What was it like at the scene?
Hello.
- Many people were guarding,
- Will you hurry up?
and it looked like people of
high ranks were inside.
Who was inside the villa?
We were in the living room.
- All right.
- I only saw Mr. Hwang...
- Sounds good.
- and his employees.
Don't be late.
And I took a peek at the room
when Mr. Hwang entered it.
There were two more people
in the room.
Were they men or women?
They were men.
You didn't get to see
the people in the room?
No, they told us to stay outside
when they had their meal.
Did anyone new come to the villa?
Oh, right. Before we left,
one more person came.
I couldn't see him clearly.
I only saw the back of his head.
Can you remember anything else?
I think it was a man.
His back hair was long.
He had grey hair. Right?
Yes.
And also,
I could tell he was an old man
from the way he walked.
I think they're talking about
Father Lee.