(Episode 16)
That was 10 points out of 10 points.
Your life's been smooth, hasn't it?
You don't have to work as a cop
because you're helping the priest.
You slack off,
and drink whenever you want.
You smile even when you get hit
by a baseball bat.
When that priest attacked Maegakgyo
and Wangmat Foods,
you didn't even stop him.
- I didn't just stay still.
- How dare you?
I told you many times, didn't I?
I told you to keep an eye on him
and stop him at all costs.
And yet, you just fooled around
next to him?
Hey, do you not
take my words seriously?
Oh, my gosh.
Get up.
Dae Young.
I'm telling you for the last time.
Listen carefully.
Make that priest leave this country,
got it?
Yes, sir.
Don't let him
get anything on Wangmat Foods.
Mess things up.
Yes, sir.
You can go now.
If you don't listen to me
and fool around again,
I'll make sure to bury...
your dead friend's wife and son...
where nobody can find
their corpses.
Do you understand?
I've seen this look before.
It's from the old days,
the ones that ended up dying.
Do your job, okay?
Hurry up!
I think it's the Russian alley.
Just run!
Why are they so fast?
My goodness.
Come here.
Who are those punks?
Why are they blocking our way?
Hey, we aren't here to arrest you.
Make way. Move.
I told you to move.
Move before I kill you all.
He said he'll kill you.
Darn it.
Gosh, look at him.
You scumbags!
Detective Lee, follow him.
I'll take care of them.
You can't take care
of everyone here.
I'm doing what I can!
Come get me, you jerks!
I'll kill you all.
Detective Lee!
Young Cheon.
Stop it.
Young Cheon. Hey.
Young Cheon.
Young Cheon. Why... How...
You fools. I'll put you all
behind bars!
Are you a policeman?
How dare they attack
a police officer?
Who did this?
Young Cheon.
Young Cheon. Wake up.
Put them behind bars later.
Take him to a hospital first.
You just wait. I'll kill
every one of you jerks.
Young Cheon. Get up.
Young Cheon.
Hang in there.
What is it? What?
Don't die.
What?
You fool.
Okay, I won't die, so hang in there.
Stay strong, Young Cheon.
What's your problem?
- Sir.
- I told you not to go in there.
You were to call me first.
How can I call during a chase?
Be quiet.
You're the one
who got Young Cheon killed.
- How dare you?
- Dae Young.
How can you say that?
You idiot!
If you'd listened to me...
What's going on here?
That's him.
- Calm down.
- Hold back.
His minions killed Young Cheon.
Okay, stay still!
His minions killed Young Cheon!
I get it, okay?
Fine.
I won't die, like you said.
And I'll protect the others.
Wait.
It's just me again?
I'm the first one here again.
No one else is here.
What's this? Dae Young.
You slept here?
Why didn't you go home?
It still aches.
- Are you hurt?
- Yes, I am.
My body and heart both hurt.
What time is it?
8:40am.
I need to go.
You won't wait for Father Kim?
I'm boycotting him today.
What's the problem now?
If he wants to go somewhere,
you go with him instead, okay?
He might raid Wangmat Foods today.
- I don't care.
- Dae Young!
I don't care.
I just can't get to like him.
He'll value me only when I'm gone.
Let's see him ruin his case.
One dollar, please.
- Thanks.
- Enjoy your snack.
Hello.
I looked into the guy
you asked me to.
- Who is he?
- Why?
The first profile I got
was exactly what you told me.
I tried to get more details,
but I don't have access.
What does that mean?
That he's no ordinary guy.
He's a North Korean
we're protecting,
an ex-agent of ours,
or someone whose
real identity can't get out.
Hello, Head Nun.
Yes.
We just got a call
from Eun Ji's hospital.
If we don't settle her medical bill,
they'll send her home today.
What should we do?
I left to avoid him and we met.
Where's he going with that frown?
(Balance: 2,082 dollars 1 cent)
No, Father.
Please, sir.
I'll pay 2,000 dollars now.
Can't I pay the rest in three days?
It must be paid in one go,
so I can't do that.
If you can't pay today,
the girl goes home.
Show some lenience and
help me out just this once.
I've been doing this for years.
If I help someone out,
they keep asking for favors.
Handle this.
Don't say that.
I'm asking for your help
just this once.
We can't allow for
everyone's difficulties.
I'm begging you.
I'm not saying I won't pay
and she's a little kid.
Sir.
Come on now.
Hello, Detective Koo.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Have you ever seen a priest
who cons people?
I haven't.
Be merciful and give him
a week to pay the rest.
This isn't up to me.
If things go wrong,
I'll be penalized.
When you were caught
with a prostitute at a karaoke bar,
you got out the side door.
Who let you out?
Why are you bringing that up now?
Don't commit adultery.
Don't covet another man's woman.
But...
One week, okay?
They'll dock my pay.
I'll be penalized.
Wow, full marks.
You needn't thank me.
That will just be embarrassing.
Right.
Where will you get the money?
From those who are responsible.
Who would want to pay up?
Do me a favor.
You won't be able to stop
what will happen,
but don't get in the way of
Eun Ji's treatment.
How did I get in the way?
She's just a kid.
What'll become of her
if things go wrong?
She's an orphan
and the world is against her.
She needs to be healthy at least.
I don't care if you try to
block, ruin, or stop me,
but wait until Eun Ji's okay.
Then I'll take you on.
Did I do something to stop you?
You will soon.
I'm off to...
raid Wangmat Foods.
What if I help in earnest?
Father Kim Tsunami.
Who are you and what did you do?
Who are you?
Ms. Park, someone outside
wishes to see you.
Who is it?
Kyeong Seon.
This is crazy.
Did you come here
because you heard I was here?
Yes.
You came back home.
How could I not know?
I have nothing to say to you.
Kyeong Seon.
So...
Do me one last thing.
Do a favor for your useless father.
You're not a useless father.
You're a useless human being.
Kyeong Seon.
It's not something serious.
Our neighbors
are involved in a lawsuit.
Could you move things on for us?
Did someone send you here?
Did they promise you
money and alcohol in return?
What are you saying?
It's not like that.
Kyeong Seon.
They're all neighbors
who saw you grow up.
You made promises
you couldn't fulfill and...
ruined your life and
still haven't grown up?
Didn't going to prison
teach you anything?
Shall I send you back?
You were used your whole life.
Aren't you sick of that?
You abandoned your family
to live like trash.
I am...
just so sick of it.
It's such a relief that
I'm not like you.
Kyeong Seon.
Do you...
happen to have...
any money?
- Hello, Father.
- Hello.
Have you still not worked things out
with Dae Young?
There's nothing to work out.
I'd like you to come with me today.
I'd love that.
I mean, I'm in a great mood today.
Do you know Alive Young?
I got a 50-percent discount coupon.
Dae Young.
You left as if
you'd be gone for the day.
I did not.
I had a corndog.
Pack a high-powered camcorder
and anti-riot gear.
- Okay.
- What's the anti-riot gear for?
To fight a riot. Would we
crack walnuts with it?
That place isn't a thug hideout.
Why pack that
to visit a private company?
What if there's another Choco?
We have to bring them all in.
"Choco"?
I'll go and get a camcorder.
We can shoot the factory
with our phones.
My stomach hurts again.
Give me three minutes.
No.
I might poop right now.
What's he up to?
Don't let him
get anything on Wangmat Foods.
Mess things up.
Mr. Hwang. Father Kim's about to...
head over to Wangmat Foods.
He wants to take everyone down.
You'd best be prepared.
Things are really going pear-shaped.
- Jang Ryong.
- Yes, sir.
Take some good fighters and
if the priest acts up,
crush him good, okay?
Yes, sir.
Sir, why don't you
deal with this quietly?
If Ms. Jeong finds out...
What if she does?
How else are we to stop him?
Chat with him over tea?
Director Kim's being
awfully cautious these days.
You weren't like this before.
Did you see a ghost?
I'll flatten him for good, sir.
Sort him out properly.
- Yes, sir.
- Go.
Come in.
Why are you here?
Shouldn't you be at work?
Put me back where I belong.
I'll do anything...
you tell me to.
No.
I'll do anything without a mistake.
- Yo Han, bring the bean sprouts.
- Okay.
(Wangmat Foods)
Oh, right.
I'll bring some salt from storage.
Why isn't he back with the salt?
- What's going on?
- Honey, where are my socks?
I'm always out.
Leave it by the door.
Can we move on from kissing?
Okay.
What now?
Shall we hide it now?
Already? Why bother?
Where should we put it?
We'll be ruined if we're found out.
Why are you so scared?
What?
Sir. Just put it in the safe.
They'll search that first
with the search warrant, moron.
- Darn you.
- Then where...
(CEO's Office)
How about that place?
You should've brought one
that functions.
This is broken.
Will you keep still?
You're shaking the camcorder.
Be quiet. We're
staking out at the scene.
When scoping the setting or people,
pick an open spot
where you can look downwards.
If you're at eye-level,
you're likely to lose them.
Okay.
You sound like
a drill sergeant today.
(Gudam-gu Office)
Oh, hello, sir.
- 11 o'clock.
- Sir.
(Wangmat Foods)
Darn it.
You could've done that sooner.
Zoom right in.
Look at him take that.
He's so pleased.
Free money's always welcome.
Don't you like donations, Father?
That's a bribe, not a donation.
Think, will you?
Two o'clock.
The whole family's taking bribes.
Will you stop taking them?
You're all so slow.
That jerk with the bob's back.
- Take your spots.
- Hurry up.
They can't hear us.
They aren't bionic men.
Aren't you being overly tense?
My stomach hurts again.
Did I put on too much ketchup?
I need to poop.
This is going down now.
It's urgent.
It's at the rim of my anus.
Don't you watch movies?
If the detective disappears,
something bad happens.
Something even worse
could happen to me.
Stop complaining.
You'll feel better after a minute.
Hold it in and come back here.
Come here.
Song Sac.
Stop.
Darn it.
(Wangmat Foods)
What should I do?
Push me over that wall.
Are you trying to kill me?
Song Sac. There's no time. Do it.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Lift me up. 1, 2, 3.
Are you sure the priest
asked you to do this?
Yes.
Yo Han was given some sort of order.
Do you feel better?
Has the urge gone?
Yes, kind of.
Father. Did you expect them to
react like this?
Yes.
Then the reason
you came here yesterday...
To learn who's
watching this place...
and how they go about it.
Right. That's awesome.
You're good.
Wait. What are they doing?
That's it.
(Notice)
It's a formality.
That's right.
He's getting them a ticket.
Then do you think somebody
sued them?
I don't think so.
It's all planned.
- Pardon?
- They'll be suspended for a month,
and pay the fine.
When things settle down,
they'll start their business again.
Those jerks.
That must be how they've been
running their business so far.
That's right.
They ran it however they wanted
since no one could stop them.
Let's get going
since we saw everything.
Aren't we done yet?
We got all the evidence.
Darn it. We have to go catch them
since we have all the evidence.
Move.
Hold on.
Yo Han. Yo Han.
That pig.
Why did you leave me behind?
Be quiet!
(Wangmat Foods)
Why are your eyes so full of anger?
You look like someone
who's lost his country.
You're not going to
perform capoeira today, are you?
This one? That time,
it was a performance,
but you attacked me suddenly.
Isn't that cheating?
Can't you get rid of your bob cut?
It's annoying me like crazy.
You're also annoying like crazy,
hip-hop girl.
Why do you keep getting in my way?
You're so annoying.
- That scumbag.
- Hold on.
Hold on.
Let's do it
according to the procedure.
Those who have to be arrested,
leave with us.
Those who don't have to may stay.
Detective Koo, don't get involved
and move out of the way...
before I break your bone.
Okay.
I won't take care of the aftermath.
Gosh.
Let's see.
How many of you are going to get on
the bus to the fiery pit?
Let's see. 2, 4, 6, 8, 10.
A combination must be enough.
What did he say? A combination?
Okay, then. Let the fight begin.
Come here!
(Wangmat Foods)
Your skull's going to hurt
a lot today, hip-hop girl.
(The Fiery Priest)
Through the investigation,
the secrets of Gudam...
How could you handle it like this?
I told you many times
to do a better job.
(The evils are breaking up.)
The opponents need to be weakened,
so we can obtain the information
we want.
Are you okay?
You were beaten a lot earlier.
Thank you for helping me.
I can do that much for you
since I'm your senior.
Who took the ledger
of Wangmat Foods?
- Tell me.
- I don't know.
Don't kill me!
(A dangerous counterattack
will begin.)
- Get back to Seoul quickly.
- Yes, sir!
Shall we get rid of them?
What kind of nonsense it that?