(Episode 1)
How dare you!
How dare such
a loutish evil spirit...
throw a fit in this town?
You not only hurt the elders
of this town...
by harassing them...
but you also
went inside the body...
of the first son who has to
carry on a family line.
You're making so much trouble.
My goodness.
What's wrong with my son?
How can I save him?
What should I do?
He's a shameless evil spirit.
What did he say?
He said if you pay enough money
for him to travel, he'll leave now.
Are you sure you will?
- Please hold on.
- Okay.
My gosh.
Hurry up and give me your money.
Hurry up and give it to me.
- My goodness.
- Borrow someone's if you have none.
Hold that thought.
Father Kim?
They should pull out this huge rock.
I could've been hurt. How annoying!
Father Kim, I'll take care of this.
Why is my briefcase so heavy?
This evil spirit won't go away
with Catholic exorcism.
He's right, Father Kim.
Shaman Chundong here
will get rid of...
I think he's just dirty,
not possessed.
If you're confident,
then give it a go.
He was under control because of me.
The evil spirit in him
is a pretty strong one.
What are all these?
Dear leader of all angels,
St. Michael the Archangel.
Please protect us from the fight
against violence and power.
Protect us from the fight against
the evil spirits under the sun.
Gosh, it really hurts.
Evil spirit, hang in there.
What?
I think he's crying.
Are you hurt?
All right.
If you bear the pain...
after I hit your shin...
and the back of your hand 20 times,
then you'll pass the second test.
It's my earnest hope...
for Satan to stop
possessing humans...
and harming the church.
Sir.
I think the evil spirit is gone.
Seeing your complexion,
it's still in you.
It's really gone.
What?
You have no patience at all.
What on earth happened?
Cheol Yong told me that...
The evil spirit is still in there.
I was totally fooled.
Go and wash.
You smell like stinky tofu.
You scumbag.
Go home right now.
That evil spirit...
You're dead meat, jerk.
Come here.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
Who are you guys?
You shouldn't have
interrupted our exorcism.
What were you thinking?
Gosh, darn it.
Hey!
Gosh, why is he following me?
I'm going to kill you
once I catch you.
Didn't I tell you not to scam...
the elders?
Have you still not come
to your senses?
Come here. Get over here.
- I taste blood.
- Gosh, my neck!
- What?
- Your nails are hurting me.
You didn't plan this alone, did you?
Who told you to do this?
Mr. Oh!
Mr. Oh, the loan shark.
Is Mr. Oh inside?
You talk very rudely for a priest.
Brothers, please step to the side.
We don't go easy on priests,
pastors, or monks.
I never asked you to go easy on me.
Hey.
Gosh, my arm.
Brothers, you'll end up in hell
if you hit a priest.
I should book a bus that's headed
to hell for all of you.
(Customized loans for businessmen)
Paul.
You should come outside
while I'm being nice.
Do I need to shout
for you to listen to me?
Hurry up and come outside!
Gosh, it's so cramped in here.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
Hey, I'll be off now.
I'll come back for the cups later.
Goodness, Father.
What is wrong with you?
I know the Bible says it's a sin
to give out private loans.
But it's also a form of business.
Plus, I give a lot of offerings.
I'm not here for that.
I heard you were the one...
who told Cheol Yong to scam
the elders in the neighborhood.
Oh, that.
I was just trying to revitalize
shamanism in our neighborhood.
Cut the nonsense.
The people in the marketplace are
practically broke because of you.
On top of that, you even tried
to scam the naive elders?
Gosh, don't be so angry.
My guys always get beaten up by you
every time they try to collect.
And now, you're even
going to beat me up?
Forgiveness and love.
You should be doing
what God told you to do.
Wait a minute.
He's telling me something.
God...
just told me to beat you up.
(The Fiery Priest)
(Seoul Central
District Prosecutor's Office)
- She's here.
- It's her.
- Prosecutor Park.
- Hurry.
Gosh, you startled me.
- Are you filming me?
- Are you Park Kyeong Seon,
the prosecutor in charge of
the Nonhyeon-dong meth case?
Yes, that's me.
Can you give me a minute?
Let me put my bangs down.
The public doesn't seem to agree...
with the primary investigation.
I just asked you
to give me a minute.
Don't you think you wrapped up
the investigation too quickly?
We have testimonies
saying the same thing.
I don't want to do the interview.
Kim Keon Yong was the
distributor and main culprit,
but he was only accused of
abusing and possessing meth.
Meanwhile, Kim,
an idol singer who was...
only guilty of possessing the drug,
was accused of distributing it.
And some people think you went
easy on Kim Keon Yong...
because he's the son
of Hanjoo Group's chairman.
What are your thoughts on that?
Listen to me.
Let's say I have candies at home.
If people come over to my house
and eat those candies,
would that make me a distributor?
Or would it be the person
who took that candy...
and gave it away to other people
outside my house?
So are you saying Kim Keon Yong
was the one who had candies at home,
and the idol star was the one
who took that candies...
- and gave it away to other people?
- Bingo.
But didn't Kim Keon Yong possess
a huge amount of drugs?
Why are you acting like
you work for a tabloid?
We never announced whether it was
a large amount or small amount.
But the public are still
very much suspicious of this case,
so could you please say a word
to explain?
- Prosecutor Park, please.
- Tell us what you think.
- Please say something.
- Prosecutor Park.
- Wait.
I hope you all become rich.
- Ma'am!
- Prosecutor Park.
I'm so embarrassed.
How in the world
are you handling things?
We have proof that Kim Keon Yong
was the distributor,
and the testimonies of other
drug abusers are all coherent.
We should arrest
Kim Keon Yong first.
Please issue an arrest warrant.
Didn't I tell you to make...
the idol star become
the main culprit?
I was going to do that.
But I don't think it'll be possible
because the culprit...
is Chairman Kim Joong Chul's son.
The press already...
Let me get this straight.
You're going to get a warrant
and arrest the culprit...
which will make everyone
in the country trust you.
Meanwhile, they'll all be cursing
and badmouthing me.
Is that what you want?
- No, that's not it.
- My gosh.
Gosh, why do I have so many selfies?
The technology is crazy these days.
There's not a single outdoor lamp,
but I can see everyone so clearly.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Is this you?
Why would you even bother
counting the bills?
I'm pretty sure the owners
of the illegal massage parlors...
gave you more than enough money.
Prosecutor Park, you're mistaken.
I'm mistaken?
Cut the nonsense,
and listen to me carefully.
Do you want to get fired
for bribery...
and live the rest of your life
in shame?
Or will you do as I say...
and keep your job until you retire?
If you come here one more time
regarding this case,
I'll make sure I completely
destroy your career...
and your life.
Yes, ma'am.
You see,
our brains...
aren't just in our skulls
to fill in the space.
So what should we do with them?
What should we do?
We should use them.
Exactly.
Go use your brain!
Stress.
(Yeosu Police Station)
Why did you do that?
How could a priest be so impatient?
It's not about being patient.
You know what he did.
What did I do? Do you have proof?
Do you have proof of my scheming
with the shaman?
Proof? I've heard everything.
What are you looking at?
- Stop it!
- Did you see his face?
That's enough!
Words cannot be used as evidence.
Darn it, that little...
I almost cursed. I'm sorry.
Father Kim, please sit down.
I'll scold him,
so please spare us this once.
- I'd like to.
- Please...
But I can't let this one go.
My employees are all hospitalized.
- One of them broke his jaw.
- Hey.
- Be quiet.
- I'm telling you.
Where is he?
- Please be quiet.
- He's here.
Are you okay, Father Kim?
If you hit them with love,
that is reasonable.
- You did well.
- Sir.
They should switch places.
- That little...
- What do you mean?
Can't you see that I'm bleeding?
- Be quiet!
- Stop!
- I had my reasons.
- Stop it.
- Please calm down.
- I will...
- carry the cross.
- Stop it.
- Please be quiet!
- Sit down, please.
You guys are always like this.
(Receive your punishment.)
Hello.
I come to you to help.
I give it my all.
I'm Detective Koo Dae Young...
of Gudam Police Station's
Violent Crimes.
If you're a victim
of an illegal doing,
please report to me.
I will punish all the wrongdoers.
Goodness, you wish.
Goodness, Ms. Han.
Are you Miss Korea?
Why do you wear that?
It's a campaign.
I come to you to help,
and I promise to punish.
It sounds great.
Don't be ridiculous.
No matter how much we report,
the police ignore us.
I'm sure you help.
Do something about those Russians
from the neighborhood.
They get drunk
and cause trouble here.
We're always so anxious.
How dare they?
If they come again...
We will call you and only you.
Ms. Kim, you dyed your hair.
Enjoy the food and be happy.
Next time, give us
one more bowl of soup.
- All right.
- Eat first.
Yes, eat up.
Yes?
Sir.
Until when do I need to do this?
This is so humiliating.
If you don't do that, I can't assess
your performance at all.
If you want to gain points,
keep it up until this month.
Right.
I heard you're going to confront
those from Exit Three Gang.
What time?
You're coming?
Of course, I'm part of the team.
Right, I forgot.
They're at that
Hyundai Employment Agency, right?
Should I go there right now?
Hey, plans might change later,
so wait for my call.
I'll prove it to you this time...
how competent I am.
I'll prove my dignity.
When I...
I...
Hello?
He always hangs up on me.
(Director of Seoul Central District
Prosecutor's Office)
It's an honor.
- Enjoy.
- Thanks.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
- Thank you!
- Cheers!
It's been a while.
Look at her.
What has she been doing all along?
She was learning under me.
It's truly an honor
to meet you, sir.
If you help me out,
I'll give it my all.
She's truly amazing.
She is.
Which class are you in?
I'm in the 40th class, sir.
She's your senior then.
Well, yes.
But I started three years earlier.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry I didn't know, sir.
It's all right.
About Chairman Kim Joong Chul's son,
can you handle it?
I don't know about anything else,
but I am extremely resilient, sir.
You can trust me.
Resilience alone won't do.
You need to be strategic.
You're right. I'll plan out
a great strategy.
She's amazing, isn't she?
You will feel secure
with her by your side.
Let me pour you a drink, sir.
- Join me from today on.
- Goodness.
I might not be able
to protect you from typhoons,
but I sure can
protect you from the wind.
Thank you, sir!
I'll devote my life to you!
Great.
Let's clink in hopes that
he will become the chief.
- Cheers!
Let's go!
Stop right there, will you?
What?
Why were you acting
so conceited back there?
How dare you talk to me like that?
Since you won the director's favor,
are you looking down on me?
You're right. I've been looking
down on you for the past 10 minutes.
I can't look up at all.
- Hey.
- How dare you blabber back there?
Do you think a training institute
is a joke?
What do you say?
Shall I round up your class?
Just for you?
Aren't you also here
to gain their favor?
Then what should we do?
We should act modest
and do our jobs well.
Let's do our best.
Don't ruin the atmosphere.
Gosh.
If you're scared, just show it.
Don't laugh.
Let's do our best, okay?
Also,
stop eating the appetizers.
You're gobbling them all up.
I'm also hungry.
You know very well...
how much Father Kim contributed
to this neighborhood.
Who guided
all the juvenile delinquents?
You little...
Don't fight and get along.
Don't make me repeat myself.
All he did was beat them up.
We also use physical punishment
at the temple.
If they need to be awakened,
it's only natural
to use physical punishment.
That isn't all.
Who took care of the orphans
the most passionately?
The kids love him.
They sure do.
Still,
I can't let this one slide.
They need to settle it.
Is there no way?
I can't find
any other solutions, either.
All right, then.
Let's pray that he will be able
to find a solution.
Dear Lord.
Please cast away all the devils
that are in his head.
- Father, the Son,
- We pray desperately.
- and the Holy Spirit...
- Sit down.
Please stop.
Please lead him.
Please stop!
- Stop!
- Dear Lord.
- Through the Holy Spirit...
- I said, stop.
Darn it.
There is one way, but...
But I'm not so sure.
Why can't you sing past that?
I'm running out of breath.
Have you not stopped smoking?
I'm reducing.
You should quit. Your body will rot.
What a lovely surprise.
It's Father Matteo.
Have you been well?
Of course.
Is Father Kim Hae Il
doing well as well?
Well, yes.
I'm actually calling
because of him.
Is he still suffering?
Father Kim.
Please come on out.
I must've gained weight.
It used to fit me.
Hey, why's everyone onto this?
I think the chief wants to
get credit for this.
He needs to catch a gang or two...
and show a few photos
of their hideout.
- Of course.
- Attention, everyone.
Hurry up and hit these guys.
Catch them,
and take photos of their hideout.
It's a highly confidential case,
- so keep it under wraps.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
Hey, hurry up.
- Did you get the location?
- Yes, sir.
Did you call the guys
from Exit Three Gang ahead?
- I sent them texts already.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Wait a minute.
I have to tell Dae Young
what's going on.
I'm sure Mr. Lee already did.
Let's go now.
(Warm and trustworthy
police that serves our citizens)
(Gudam Police Station)
(Receive your punishment.)
(Hyundai Employment Agency)
What's taking them so long?
What's that?
Did they go up through that?
(Karaoke)
Darn it.
Welcome.
- Hello, sir.
It's good to see you.
You all know the procedure, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Yes, we do.
Put handcuffs on,
and say only what you were
told to say, okay?
- Yes, sir.
- This is the evidence?
- You can take photos.
- You're so well-prepared.
We're going to take pictures
of the evidence.
You're under arrest...
for operating illegal
gambling house. Got it?
- Yes, sir.
Where on earth is Dae Young?
(Hyundai Employment Agency)
Stand straight!
That jerk.
Receive your punishment.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
It's so hard to find
a bathroom in this building.
There's tissue
I've been looking for.
I need a lot of this.
Excuse me.
I'm about to wet my pants.
I'm dying here.
Turn your head.
I really have to go.
Swing! Strike out!
It's the bottom of the ninth inning.
The current score is 9 to 0.
It's 9 to 0? How terrible.
Oh, right.
Did I text Dae Young or not?
I'm sure he'll be fine.
(A city protected by Jeong Dong Ja)
(A city free from crime, Gudam)
It's so cold.
I thought it wouldn't be cold
if I'm embarrassed.
Excuse me.
Stop, stop.
What are you, a terminator?
Why are you naked?
It's me, Koo Dae Young.
Detective Koo,
what are you doing here?
Did you drink again?
I'm so glad you came fast.
Hold on.
No.
No picture taking. Hey!
The condition of releasing me
was for me to leave here?
You need to hurry.
We don't have much time.
Father Kang, please explain
in detail. What's going on?
If you don't leave before dawn,
they'll issue an arrest warrant.
Mr. Oh is determined to arrest you.
You should stay with
Father Lee Young Jun for a while.
Have you already contacted...
Why on earth did you do that?
Of course he should know.
He's like a father to you.
Why must I leave this place?
All those who have committed crimes
are still roaming around.
You need a treatment, Father Kim.
I don't need that.
What do you mean?
You can't control yourself at all.
How can you put up with trash
like Mr. Oh?
If you can't, then you should
stop being a priest then.
Then you can do whatever you want.
I've overlooked everything...
even though you broke several rules.
There was a reason I did that,
and I believed that you could
control yourself.
But I don't trust you anymore.
You're just full of anger.
I'll tell the other priests
and the kids in the orphanage...
that you've left.