It said "the following day".
It means I have to
be there tomorrow.
That sounds great.
I get to go to my hometown
in 20 years.
Chief. Where should I go first
in Yeongwol County?
Is there a place where I could
release this anger?
Cheongnyeongpo.
How about Danjong's place of exile?
That's unbelievable.
Are you telling me to go to
a place of exile since I'm exiled?
I apologize.
Just get me a box since I'm busy.
You could just stay at the church.
Did you really have to
get coffee outside?
The church only has instant coffee.
My money, my blood.
You seem like you pay with points.
I don't get points for free.
I've already spent a lot.
Here are the two americanos
you ordered.
Where are we going today?
The aroma of this coffee is nice.
Tell me honestly.
What?
Are you feeling lost?
You don't know what to do, right?
I know everything.
"I did everything I could".
"No one is going to say anything
if I give up now".
What are you talking about?
We're just starting.
What?
You have to do something for me.
Let's go in together.
Just tell me.
I'll do it.
Darn it.
Stop.
A beast or
a well-trained assassin...
are the only things...
that can attack you.
Perhaps...
It can't be.
Jang Ryong.
Yes, sir.
Contact the investigator
from Mullae-dong...
and ask him to do an investigation
on Father Kim.
That rude Father?
Yes, not like a background check...
but a detailed investigation.
If he tries to increase the price,
tell him I'll kill him.
I'll get a reasonable price
and complete it properly.
Is everything ready
for Savings Day?
Yes, they're ready.
There are people
who catch the cows...
and people who eat the steak.
What?
A briefing?
Chief Jeong Dong Ja,
Chief Nam Seok Gu...
Congressman Park Won Mu...
It's hot.
And Hwang Cheol Bum.
Everything about them.
Why do you need a briefing
about them when...
this investigation is
about Father Lee?
Because they're all related to it.
And you know that they need to be
beaten up to give us evidence.
Watch what you say.
What do you mean by "beaten up"?
Why are using vulgarism?
That word is in the dictionary.
And you said you'd do anything
for me just now.
But these are personal details
of the superiors.
That's not right.
(If you're appointed with a lawyer,
you can participate...)
(in the investigation
with the appointed lawyer.)
I'll give you meals.
What?
I'll let you have a meal per day
at the church for a month.
I'm dumbfounded.
Do I look like a beggar to you?
Chief Jeong Dong Ja.
She's a very outstanding person.
She entered the borough office
as a grade nine civil servant.
She reached a position
as a secretary...
of three chiefs in total.
Her political ability and charisma
is overflowing.
She must know everything
about Gudam.
Of course.
She knows literally
everything about Gudam.
She knows who owns what business...
and what goes on in every alleyway.
Come in and listen to this.
What? Who?
Were you eavesdropping?
Yes.
I was eavesdropping
and was also recording.
What's the relationship between
Jeong Dong Ja and Hwang Cheol Bum?
Just a relationship between
a chief and a local worthy.
They're close like siblings.
They address each other
as siblings in unofficial settings.
They publicly revealed that
they're step-siblings.
How do you know that?
I also looked into it.
Your meal at
the church is canceled.
I was about to tell you that.
It's rather like an alliance between
a chief and a gangster instead.
Yes, I know of that. An alliance.
How about Hwang Cheol Bum's details?
He's an orphan.
He's been a gangster in Yeosu
since he was 20.
He was ranked second in Yeosu...
and came to Gudam seven years ago.
I'll kill you.
He first earned a lot from...
adult entertainment establishment
and construction business.
He established Daebum Trading
company three years ago.
He must've smuggled things
if he runs a trading company.
He steals from enterprises in Gudam,
he manages the Russian district...
and uses them as his men.
Yes, you're correct.
How did you know all that?
Next.
(Seoul Gudam)
Our superintendent is
from a well-supported family.
Since the Japanese colonial era,
they've been a police...
Cut that nonsense.
That means
his family is pro-Japanese.
Like Japanese raiders.
That's enough. Next.
Congressman Park Won Mu.
He's a congressman
of the opposing party...
who has been elected
for the third term.
He served in the army.
He usually leads strikes.
His hobby is doing
intermittent fasting.
If he's a congressman,
he should use his head,
not his body.
Anything significant about him?
He has nine records
of receiving bribes,
4 records of sexual harassment,
3 records of fraud,
and five records
of physical violence.
However, all the charges
were dropped.
He's complete garbage.
They can hear you from outside.
Lower your voice.
What are you doing?
- Hello.
- What?
Nothing, sir.
Hello, sir.
(Prosecutor Park Kyeong Seon)
Darn it.
Goodness.
You should've been
more meticulous with your work.
Ms. Park.
Or can I talk casually to you
from now on?
I've wrapped up
the Nonhyeon-dong meth case,
so don't worry about it.
Be on your best behavior.
It doesn't take much to crumble.
Hey!
You dirtbag.
I think...
I should knock some sense into you.
- What's wrong with her?
- Come here, you punk!
(Written Decision Regarding
the Consignment of Gudam Orphanage)
How could they conclude this
so quickly?
What should we do?
We should turn the tables around.
It won't be easy
to persuade the public officials.
Shall we ask the pope for help
once again?
No way. He's not someone
we can complain to.
You're right. He's not Santa Claus.
We have one month
until the transitioning begins.
Until then, this is still ours.
We'll find a solution.
Father.
What is it?
It's Eun Ji. They said...
What about her?
They said there's no hope.
They want to discharge her
from the hospital.
Oh, no. Dear Lord.
It was about three months ago.
We changed our food service company,
and it was their first lunchtime.
That day,
the children ate like usual.
Suddenly, a few of them
started throwing up.
- My stomach hurts.
- Ye Bin.
The food was rotten.
But the worst happened to Eun Ji.
The other kids recovered
after a few days,
but Eun Ji had a weak immune system
to begin with...
and couldn't fight off the virus.
She suffered from complications
and is in a comatose state.
She needs good treatment,
but since we don't have any money,
the hospital said
they would discharge her.
We can't do that.
She needs to be hospitalized.
(Gudam's Corrupt Food Service Was
Once Awarded as a Great Company)
(Charges Dropped for the CEO
and Several Low Ranks Fired)
(Evidence)
(The grown-up's greed
may take a child's life.)
I'm sure
that food service company...
refused to take responsibility.
We sued them...
and told the media about it,
but it was to no avail.
What was the name
of that food service company?
Wangmat Foods.
Do you know that company?
Yes, it's around my neighborhood.
Be honest. How are they?
They make tasty foods...
and do meal services, right?
Fine, fine.
Their president...
is the nephew of Ki Yong Moon,
the leader of Maegakgyo.
Whose nephew?
Oh, my. I apologize.
Cult! It's a cult!
Is she unconscious?
Sometimes she wakes up
and looks at me.
But it's only for a brief moment.
In her current state,
a flu virus could cause...
blood poisoning and give her
a lethal shock.
Then how could we bring her home
in that critical condition of hers?
Please keep
administering antibiotics...
and make it painless.
In order to do so, she needs
a more effective antibiotic.
But the cost is...
I'll pay.
I'll pay,
so please don't let her
feel any pain.
No one is stepping up when
she's in a life-or-death situation!
I don't care about anything else,
but I won't allow something
like that to happen to a kid.
I'll destroy them.
This means he'd been doing
everything that he could...
just to save her.
Are you talking
about Father Lee Young Jun?
Then who else?
Where are you going?
Why didn't you accept
Father Lee's petition?
The company apologized,
and a correction order
was sent out to them.
The girl is in critical condition
because of their food.
They must take responsibility
for it.
We can't tell them to do that
just because of one girl.
Just because the rest of them
recovered doesn't mean it's okay.
The company needs
to be responsible for this.
What responsibility?
Did she die or something?
Hey! Come here.
- Repeat what you said.
- What?
Come here! Say it again.
- Come here.
- How dare you?
If anything happens to her,
I'll kill you first, understand?
Why bother talking to him? Let's go.
- Let me go.
- You...
Let me go.
(Wangmat Foods Chosen as
an Outstanding Food Service Company)
Let me go.
There. There.
(Wangmat Foods Chosen as
an Outstanding Food Service Company)
What are you doing?
Calm down.
We're just abiding by the rules.
Don't take your anger out on us.
Rules?
Rules, my foot.
You should abide
by the humane rules, okay?
Darn it.
(Gudam-gu Office)
I would've killed him
then and there.
That rude scumbag.
(Number One Rule of Hygiene)
Did you give him to me
because of what I said before?
Or are you telling me to catch them
one by one?
Why are you giving me
vague messages?
I think my faith in you was weak.
What are you raving on about?
It's still a revelation.
Let's go. We need to take down
Wangmat Foods.
What? Take down what?
Let's take down Wangmat Foods,
the company that made
those rotten foods.
That was so random.
Why would you do that?
What about Father Lee's case?
That's what I'm doing right now.
Listen up.
That company's CEO's uncle is
Ki Yong Moon.
Ki Yong Moon and Hwang Cheol Bum
are linked.
Hwang Cheol Bum and Jeong Dong Ja
are close,
and there's Congressman Park.
Isn't it amazing?
I just need to catch one,
and I'll be catching all of them.
On top of that, I'll be able
to clear Father Lee's name.
Lead me to Wangmat Foods.
Darn it.
I feel suffocated.
Hurry up!
My heart feels stuffy.
Hey!
You scumbag. Who told you
to throw this away?
Eat it. Eat it, you scumbag!
Don't waste anything.
Chop it more thinly.
Miss. Miss!
What are you doing with this?
Are you throwing this away?
Look. Pour this in and mix it.
How does it look?
Doesn't it look good as new?
Look at this mess!
Let's not waste anything.
Got it?
Put out that cigarette.
- Who are you?
- Do you use cigarettes for food?
Put it out.
You're a priest.
Are priests allowed to cause
a commotion in factories?
Put it out.
Leave.
Leave, you scumbag!
Just put it out!
He's a lunatic.
Why did you come here
and cause a scene?
Leave.
Put it out.
Come on. This is my factory.
What was that?
You scumbag!
You jerk!
Hey!
Wait.
Choco. Choco.
Choco.
Choco? Is that your dog?
(Wangmat Foods)
Choco.
Gosh.
I'm giving you another chance
since I'm a priest, not a cop.
Listen up.
Admit to your wrongdoings,
and compensate the orphanage.
The due date is two days
from now by noon.
Once you're done, call the church.
The number is online.
That's a tight schedule.
You should give him a week.
Two days are long enough.
If you don't listen to me,
you'll be rafting
at the Jordan River. Got it?
Answer me.
Yes, sir.
Now that you've answered me,
put this back in. Open up.
Open up.
You better not drop it.
Father.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I work part-time here.
You're like Forrest Gump.
You're at every crime scene.
I'm sorry.
By the way, why were you in a fight?
They make rotten foods.
No wonder.
How dare they mess with food.
Do they want someone to die?
How long have you been working here?
Since yesterday.
Then you must not know much.
How many hours do you work?
I work from 9am to 6pm.
That's not part-timing.
You should be a full-time employee.
Those jerks are trying...
to save money.
Go work then.
Tell me if they pay you less.
You're so amazing. I mean it.
Stop it.
(Daebum Trading)
Hello, sir.
- Hey.
- That way, sir.
Let's go.
That way, sir.
Hello.
Goodness.
Savings Day comes around
so quickly every month...
that I always forget.
For me, it's so slow.
A month seems to feel like
2 to 3 months.
The day before I come here,
it feels like the day before
going on a picnic.
"Savings Day".
You should give me credit
for naming it like so.
I named it like that
so you'll anticipate the day.
All right, let's go in.
All right.
One.
2, 3.
The fingerprints match.
Yes!
Every time I come here,
I feel totally rejuvenated!
I don't need any tonics.
For me to be completely rejuvenated,
I'll need to see this much
more money.
Even if gold was
showering down on you,
I doubt that you'd be content.
Goodness, you.
Well done this month as well.
Don't mention it, ma'am.
We are witnessing
the rise of our future.
(There is approximately
150 million dollars here.)
Pack them.
- You punk.
- How dare you?
I'm sorry, sir.
Be careful!
Yes?
What?
So you couldn't say anything
and just took it?
I'm sorry, sir.
They even defeated Choco.
How strong could he be?
Darn it.
I sense that the priest has...
an unspeakable past.
Like me.
Hey.
You're a cult leader.
What great past do you have?
You can bet that I have
an unspeakable past...
when I was back in...
Ignore him and listen up.
If something happens
to Wangmat Foods,
it won't end there.
You guys, me, the borough office,
and the Chief of Borough
will all be destroyed.
Is it my time to step up?
Leave that priest up to me.
I will send him to his God.
Drop that fork, and stop it.
Gosh, there he goes again.
Anyway, if you let that priest be,
it'll cause even more trouble.
The Vatican is supporting him.
Okay, okay, okay.
How about I take care...
of him?
What's your plan?
Issues caused by a believer...
should be solved by other believers.
We'll solve it together.
What is all this?
I saw you fighting...
with Detective Koo yesterday
over the eggs.
I prepared a lot because
it seemed like you liked them.
Do you want me to stuff myself
to death?
Not at all.
Father, you can't make such jokes.
Where is he?
We're eating lunch late
because of him.
He texted me, saying he had
some matters to take care of.
Anyway,
don't you hate Detective Koo?
Let's be honest.
He's not on our side.
He's interrupting us from getting
to the bottom of Father Lee's case.
We are aware of that.
And yet, you want to be nice
and prepare food...
for someone like him?
We must.
If Father Lee was still alive,
I know what he would've done.
Even though we hate him
for what he's done,
he would've offered him...
a nice, warm meal.
I know.
Isn't that why...
you allowed him into our church?
No, not really.
Goodness.
Who is this?
Goodness, again?
Yes, Sister.
What? Those Maegakgyo people
are there again?
Do excuse me.
Why do they keep coming?
Goodness.
- The big one, please.
- Okay.
(Yeongwol)
(Yeongwol County Bus Terminal)
(Welcome, the daughter of Yeongwol,
Prosecutor Park Kyeong Seon)
How simple.
(District public prosecutor's office
in Yeongwol County)
I came to eat.
Did Father Kim go somewhere?
To Gudam Orphanage.
Why so suddenly?
I have a bad feeling about this.
A really bad feeling.
- We hate going together
- Enlightenment is the best
- Smile, smile, smile
- We will follow him
Ukha.
We will follow him
Hey.
You're here, Mother...
I mean Father Kim.
For our children's joy.
- Ukha.
That lady flicked my head
because I didn't say "Ukha".
Me too.
When did I do that?
I was just patting your head
because you're so lovely.
- I guess my pat was too strong.
- How dare you...
Why are you doing this? Calm down.
I told you not to come here.
There was an official announcement
from the Borough's Office.
- Didn't you know?
- That's not my business.
I see. That's not your business.
We have to keep our laws.
A law is a law,
however undesirable it may be.
Socrates left that famous saying.
Do you know the spelling?
S, z, r, a, t...
My goodness.
I told you last time not to
talk about Ukha to the kids.
What's so wrong about teaching
them about enlightenment?
And is your God the only God?
What did you just say, cult?
Cult?
You're the cult to us.
Your God doesn't even exist.
Please come down for a while, God.
Are you there? He's not there.
It's proven that he isn't.
He's not there. He's gone.
How dare you talk about...
Come here.
No matter how you interrupt us,
I'll make sure that
these lovely kids...
become part of Maegakgyo.
Ukha.
- Ukha.
Say it louder.
Ukha.
- Ukha.
You...
- No, Father Kim.
- I won't leave you alone.
Not only that.
I'll make this place...
the chapel of Maegakgyo.
A Father hit someone.
It's Satan.
He hit someone.
Stay away, Satan.
Father Kim.
How could you cause a mess again?
- Are you okay?
- Of course I am.
But who's that man with the hat?
A man with the hat?
What are you talking about?
(The Fiery Priest)
It's old but at least it's quiet.
How disgusting.
(A prosecutor who lost her power.)
On the verge of death, wisdom
and agility will give you strength.
I think he should go
to the hospital once again.
(A supportive police?)
Let's work together.
You're like Lee Jung Jae
from "New World".
You start tomorrow.
(Finally, they become one.)
Are you sure Father Kim
asked us to do this?
Yes, I'm sure.
(Wangmat Foods)