(Episode 13)
I think I'm angry at
what just happened.
Why don't you let me
punch you in advance...
since you promised me last time?
This is driving me crazy.
It's the funniest thing I've heard
in the last 10 years.
Mr. Hwang. Father Kim!
You can't behave like this!
Stay out of this.
No, no. Be the referee.
My gosh.
It wouldn't be right
to beat a priest.
You'll never get to feel that.
You two shouldn't behave this way.
Removing that makes me
less guilty beating you.
Let's begin.
Fight.
You jerk.
You seem like
you've punched before.
Am I a gangster like you?
Why would I punch anyone?
That punch made me feel more awake.
I'm starting again.
- It's been so long.
- Goodness.
It's been fixed.
Game stop.
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
Father Kim.
Don't say something lame like...
how those people saved me out of it.
When is our rematch?
When you want to die.
Should we get it?
- Come here.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Really?
It really is.
Did you fight a lot
when you were in school?
The way you punch seems natural.
I can see that you're experienced.
I just did it randomly.
You can't just punch
Mr. Hwang randomly.
He used to be a boxer.
Apparently, he's never lost
a fight before.
Do the police believe whatever
the gangsters say?
Gosh.
It's this way...
Why are you going back in there?
Without enlightenment,
that ignorance has become
the cellulite on your abdomen.
- I see.
- The hands of the enlightened...
will make sure that the cellulite
will disappear one by one.
- It hurts.
- Enlightenment.
Ukha!
I'm sorry. Stop right there.
Father Kim, keep your manners...
I don't know anymore.
Why don't you step outside
for a moment?
The offering for the service
can be paid here.
- Ukha.
You don't seem like you're here
for some enlightenment.
- What brings you...
- Hey, cult.
- What?
- How come...
cults don't ever develop?
The power you provide is insincere.
Cult? How could you say that to...
My gosh.
- Father Kim.
- That little...
Why are being so rude in front
of a religious group's leader?
I don't keep my manners
in front of cult members.
You're the same level
of Satan to me.
Satan?
How does my physiognomy
relate to Satan?
I only believe in impressions
not physiognomy.
But your impression...
represents a cult.
I'd like to complain about
whatever you just said to me...
officially in the name
of your religion.
Do whatever you want.
I'm warning you.
Don't think about managing
the welfare facility.
And don't talk about ukha
to the kids in the orphanage.
I won't handle it
with words next time.
I warned you.
What?
Snow White, have this apple.
I see.
"I see"?
She looks like the witch who gave
an apple to Snow White.
That's right.
Are you going to let them be?
Even so,
I can't just leave people
like them alone.
I'll make sure they change
with enlightenment.
Ukha.
Why do you look unhappy?
Try digging around
the whole of Gudam.
Dig all you want.
Yes, I'll do that from now.
Wait.
Are you losing your temper
in front of me?
How could lose my temper
in front of a Father?
I won't interfere and just be
your guide from now on.
A guide?
- Are you sulking?
- No, I'm not.
Your eyes tell me that you are.
My eyes are naturally like this.
That's why my teachers always
punished me in school.
They thought I was staring
when I was just looking.
They always slapped me...
Darn it.
"Darn it"?
You may find whatever
I'm doing annoying but...
I was just making a fuss to
stop you from getting hurt.
What fuss?
And are you actually
doing it for me?
Yes.
But you never listen to me,
so what can I do?
Gosh.
Detective Koo.
That doesn't... Come here.
Hey.
Can you order
a mapo tofu rice for me?
I'm craving something oily.
- Okay.
- I want an oyster jjamppong.
What do you want?
Forget her.
She's testing my patience
for the whole day.
Tell me how you knew where
the witnesses were.
Or you can't leave this place.
From an informant I knew.
I knew the informant even before
I became a police officer.
Detective Seo.
People shouldn't just be faithful...
when they get their password
wrong for the fourth time.
They should always be faithful.
Especially times like now.
Or you'll be in big trouble.
My answer won't change.
And I can't reveal the identity
of my informant.
Hey.
This is driving me crazy.
I'm so stressed.
You can go.
(The policemen of Gudam
will never violate our duty.)
So what happened? Where did you
say you got the information?
I told her the truth and said
I got it from my informant.
And she bought that?
Of course. That's why I'm back here.
Are you sure you're not
hiding anything from me?
No.
It's not something informants
can easily find out.
My informant is very competent.
Detective Seo, you really
shouldn't hide anything from me.
Because if anything goes wrong,
I won't be able to help you.
Even if something does go wrong,
I won't ask you for help.
Hey, you're my partner.
I can't just stay still.
Yes, you can. You should stay still.
I'll take care of everything
on my own.
Hey, wait... That little punk.
So are you saying Father Kim...
was the one who sent her
the location?
Yes.
You should've checked
Detective Seo's cell phone.
She probably deleted everything
before she came here.
You can tell that she's not
an easy girl to deal with.
But how did he manage
to track them down?
It's not like he works
for a government institution.
Maybe someone who goes
to his church is a hacker.
I wonder how a priest managed
to find this kind of route.
Should I summon Father Kim?
We can charge him for violating
National Security Law...
and the Information Security Law.
Let's just...
keep it quiet for now.
What? You're not even
going to tell the chief prosecutor?
No.
Think about it.
Let's say we catch both Father Kim
and the hacker.
But what if it turns out
the hacker has a lot of information?
I'm talking about stuff
that should never get disclosed.
- Like what?
- What kind of stuff?
You know, stuff like...
Embarrassing videos
of high-ranking public officials.
- You know what I mean.
- My goodness.
I got goosebumps
even with these arm warmers on.
If that actually happens,
all of us will be done for.
Everyone here will be doomed.
You really are incredible.
To be honest, I also felt quite
uncomfortable about it.
- Follow my orders on that.
- Okay.
Can I have some of your
oyster jjamppong soup?
Sure.
Nice.
Why is that girl so stubborn?
I can't believe she just stood there
for four hours straight.
Father Kim.
I was right, wasn't I?
It's a cult, isn't it?
He's even working
with Hwang Cheol Bum.
Hwang Cheol Bum?
He came to church every Sunday,
but I guess he was actually
a member of Maegakgyo.
Goodness, how evil.
So he's doing this just so he could
increase the number of believers?
How could he do that?
I can't believe he's doing this
just to get more believers.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
You guys.
Do you think he's trying to
take over the welfare facility.
in order to increase the number
of his believers?
My gosh, I can't believe this.
Gosh, be gentle.
- Sir.
- Yes?
Did something happen?
No one's able to touch
Mr. Hwang's face.
So there's no way he could've
gotten beaten up by anyone.
Did you fall, sir?
What if I did get beaten up
by someone?
Why would you say
something like that?
A beast or
a well-trained assassin...
are the only things
that can attack you.
My gosh. A beast, my foot.
You dumb little punk.
Here.
- Let's drink.
- Yes, sir.
Let's clink glasses.
- Go!
- Let's drink!
Your food is here.
Yes, please put it over there.
Honey, jjajangmyeon is here.
Let's eat.
- 22 dollars, please.
- 22 dollars?
- Hurry, hurry.
- Here you go.
Wait. You need to take this.
(Seongwongak)
Gosh, I almost peed.
Thank you.
Hello. Did you think I didn't
recognize you?
You see, I also have eyes
on the back of my head.
Can you see my eyes or not?
I can see them.
- Really?
- Yes.
I can't see them.
- You can't?
- No.
- You can't see them?
- No, I can't.
Peter Piper picked a peck of
pickled peppers. Say it.
- Say it!
- Peter Piper picked...
a peck of pickled peppers.
A peck of pickled peppers
Peter Piper picked.
Bye.
What?
Peter Piper picked a peck of
pickled peppers.
A peck of pickled peppers
Peter Piper picked.
Gosh, let's be careful
and drive safely.
(Chief of Borough, Chief of Police,
Congressman)
Listen carefully.
I'm only going to say this once.
They're the bad jerks.
Father Kim.
You mean, "bad birds".
Okay, then.
I'll call them the bad birds.
This is our welfare facility.
And this is the foundation that
the bad birds are trying to build.
The bad birds have a lot of filthy
money. What's filthy money?
- Bribery.
- Hush money.
- Speculation.
- And so on.
Yes, good job.
You already know what it is,
so I won't write it down.
The bad birds need a way
to launder their filthy money,
and that's why they're trying
to build this foundation.
Then who's going to build
the foundation?
Good question.
(Hwang Cheol Bum, Maegakgyo)
On the outside,
Hwang Cheol Bum and Maekgakgyo
will be the ones building it.
In other words, they're the ones
taking physical action.
My goodness gracious.
They're a group of Satans.
So once the foundation launders
their money,
they'll be able to use that money
however they want.
That's right. Good job.
As you said, the foundation
will launder their money,
and that will enable them to use it
however they want.
They're not interested
in the welfare facility at all.
My goodness.
It's so obvious that they're
doing something really bad.
So why aren't they getting caught?
That's a very textbook question.
Listen carefully.
This foundation that these
bad birds are trying to build...
is being supported
by the chief of borough,
the chief of police,
and a congressman.
So there's no way
they'll get caught.
Gosh, those mean little scumbags.
Goodness, what did I just say?
Those bad birds.
Goodness.
Along with the foundation
and the expansion of our business,
we must make sure things stay
under control from now on.
But so many weird things
have happened recently.
Especially that guy.
What's his name?
That weird priest. He's the worst.
On top of that,
we need to deal with the kid...
that got hospitalized
after eating at the orphanage.
So I've been thinking.
You should find a new member...
that we can put in charge of...
dealing with all the problems
that occur in Gudam.
I'm not talking about
someone like Mr. Hwang.
I want someone who's smart
and can take care of things legally.
You're right.
Mr. Hwang's way of doing things...
can put things at risk.
Come in.
Hello.
You know who she is, right?
She's Jeong Dong Ja,
the chief of borough.
I'm honored to meet you, ma'am.
I'm Park Kyeong Seon.
I'm Jeong Dong Ja.
Have a seat.
- Have a drink.
- Thank you.
I've heard a lot about you.
You're very beautiful.
Thank you.
Did you find out
who the informant was?
She was right.
What?
Are you saying she really had
an informant?
It's a hacker she caught
when she became a cop.
I already checked who he is.
Gosh, this darn country
is filled with techies.
Why do they have to know
every single thing?
I'll arrest him...
and charge him for violating
the Information Security Law...
and National Security Law.
Okay, you can take care of it.
Yes, sir.
You can meet Ms. Jeong another time.
Enjoy your meals.
- See you next time.
- Yes, ma'am.
Goodbye.
He called me over during dinnertime,
and he's not even going to
offer me any food?
The sashimi looked really delicious.
Is she the one that
sometimes has our back?
I like her better now that
I've actually seen her in person.
She's smart,
and she's good with her work.
What do you say we bring her in
as a new member?
It's not a bad idea,
Let me tame her a bit beforehand.
I'll let you know once again.
"Tame her"?
Do you read such books?
I'm telling you this now,
but I majored in astrophysics.
You study celestial bodies?
Oh, really?
Then you should be staring at stars,
not checking out items here.
This is pure science,
so it's hard to get a job.
You should get a job
even though it may be different...
to your major.
I'm working a job that is
related to my major.
What?
If a celestial body is
the great universe,
then this world we live in
is a microcosm.
And we're just stars.
And every day, I study these stars.
While checking out.
It's a dollar and 80 cents.
What kind of a star am I?
Tell me.
Antares.
"Antares"?
It's in the constellation
of Scorpius.
It's 700 times bigger than the Sun.
Its mass is 15 times bigger.
It's 10,000 times brighter.
In China, they call it,
"a big fire".
"A big fire".
So you're saying that
I have a fiery temper.
That I'm ill-tempered.
No.
It means that you're passionate,
and there's something in your heart.
Like this.
Exactly.
Fine. So this is how
you've been perceiving me.
You checked this out, right?
The big star is now leaving.
I should've just simply said
the moon.
Hello.
I heard you shot an action movie
in Gapyeong with Ms. Seo.
Words spread so quickly.
Then you should know that
our witnesses were taken away.
Maybe they were just trying
to protect them.
What? Protect them?
You're ashamed about
what has happened, aren't you?
Me?
You are.
Come on. You should be.
Think about it.
You should be ashamed about it.
Forget it.
If you're going to investigate,
do it properly.
You made it sound like...
you were going to get rid
of all the bad men out there.
But people can always
see through you,
and you're done for.
You really seem worthless, Father.
I'm done for? I'm done for?
What was I done for?
It happened today as well.
What will you do if the pope decides
to check up on you later?
What if he asks what you've been
doing thus far?
How dare you talk sarcastically
about the pope?
I'm not being sarcastic.
I'm just frustrated, that's all.
What an SL.
What?
Hey.
What does SL stand for?
Suffocating Loser.
If someone's talking some sense
into you, you should listen.
He just won't listen.
He's completely lost right now,
isn't he?
Also,
why was he wearing sandals
in this cold?
Does he think he's that macho?
This is the last time I'm going
to be easy on him, Father.
It's really the last time.
No matter how much you smile,
I won't let him go next time.
That stinks.
Darn it.
I'm so stressed.
"Evidence at the crime scene".
"Primary investigation".
"Autopsy".
"The two witnesses".
Darn it, those dirtbags.
("Gudam Police Station's
New Superintendent Nam Seok Gu")
("Congressman
Park Won Mu of Gudam")
("Jeong Dong Ja,
Chief of Gudam Borough")
("Maegakgyo's Followers Grow in
Number and Cause Strife")
("Gudam-gu Office's Donation
Used for Illegal Purposes")
("Chairman Hwang Cheol Bum
Helps Gudam Shine")
("The Prosecution Claims That
Nothing Was Done Illegally")
Lord.
Please let me catch one of them.
I won't be greedy,
so please give me just one of them.
(Seongwongak)
Come on, now.
Why won't anyone listen to me?
Why?
Song Sac, I'm leaving.
Okay, goodbye, sir.
Make sure you turn the lights off.
Yes, sir.
(Woman's University)
What is it?
Thank you.
Dumplings, dumplings, dumplings
Oh, "ROTC".
Where did you get that?
One of the regulars gave it to me.
It was a girl.
(Woman's University)
"Woman's University".
Do you want this?
Never.
Get lost, you jerk.
I heard that you are...
an amazing detective.
Yo Han told me so.
That punk has told everyone.
I want to kill people too.
I want to kill them amazingly
like you.
I'm not amazing.
Are you teasing me?
I'm not.
I'm serious.
Fine, fine, I get it.
Cut that nonsense,
and give me some broth.
I'll give you the rest
that's in the kitchen.
Wait.
These punks are original
in their ways of making fun of me.
Indeed.
You don't know what kind of place
hell is, do you?
Do you think your limbs
will be torn apart?
Do you think there will be sulfur
to burn you?
No.
No, no, no.
You'll be reborn...
just the way you are.
And you'll live the same life
over again.
You fool.
You idiot.
You will live your pitiful life
over and over again!
Over and over again.
Can I go somewhere peaceful?
A place where...
I can be at peace, doing nothing?
Gosh.
Why are you here?
I prayed...
and thought to myself.
You're not a believer.
Why are you acting this way?
Doesn't everyone want to go...
to a church or a temple once a year?
Hey, is the church some kind
of a vacation spot...
that you visit once a year?
You get mad when I come...
and also get mad if I leave.
You're always chewing me out.
Let's eat.
Okay.
You...
You haven't eaten yet?
The food from a church is as tasty
as the ones at a temple.
How are you eating two bowls
of rice in the morning?
Make sure you pay for this meal.
I bought you so many meals.
We're treating you. Please enjoy.
How are you eating like that
when you've done nothing for us?
Just let him enjoy comfortably.
He's having his meal.
It's okay.
When I was younger, I used to eat
well even when my father slapped me.
I see. That's why your face is...
Don't touch my fried egg.
You should've told me.
I feel so bad.
Just have one.
Hey.
(Seoul Central District
Prosecutor's Office)
- Look at that.
- You should always do well.
(Personnel appointments
announcement)
(Special prosecution unit,
Park Kyeong Seon)
(District public prosecutor's
office in Chuncheon)
(As of the following day)
I couldn't do anything about it.
It was a direct order
from the director.
I do admit that
I made a mistake once.
- But how could you...
- I know right.
That's how his temper is like.
He's not naturally generous.
But didn't you say you could
do something with a small matter?
Prosecutor Park.
This meth case is not a small matter
but a big one.
Didn't you know?
Just head there first.
Think of it as a break
since it ended up like this.
(Today's schedule,
Savings Day, 10pm)