Fiona and Zeke...
kissed.
like someone had died.
You're in love.
Where's your ring?
Oh no.
I love her.
How many times have
you tried talking to Aemie?
I'm sorry, wife.
I never meant to.
she initiated the kiss.
You're staying here.
Why do you always
have to get your way?
I said I don't want to!
I'm pregnant.
Ouch!
We haven't even...
The only guy I remember
being with recently...
was Moo.
Fucking asshole!
I'm gonna kill that bastard!
Did you know Aemie's pregnant?
I'll give you 10
minutes to explain.
Aemie! Aemie!
That's impossible, I
second the motion!
Because...
Moo's gay!
I'm seriously the only
sane one left here.
Aemie...
Tomorrow.
Huh?
I'll tell you tomorrow.
For now,
get some rest.
Look at this.
Why tomorrow?
You can tell me
now. I'm already here.
You can do it now.
Nah, don't get too excited, wife.
I'm already nervous just
thinking about confessing.
Good night, wife.
Can you not, Louie Birkins?
Do you want the sun to
never rise for you again?
Calm down girl, this is Shan.
Oh, why?
I just wanna ask something,
I feel like you could help
I can't help you with
whatever it is that you're asking.
But this is about Aemie and
her husband, Mr. Roswell.
About Cuz and Mr. Roswell?
Kaizer reached out to me asking for help.
You know what? Maybe we
should just talk about it at school.
This will be quick
Later. You're going to
school anyway, right?
- Alright, bye, see you.
- Okay, bye.
Good morning, Momo.
Good morning, Auntie.
Ugh, it's still early!
What are you doing at our house?
Well, of course. I'm
here to pick up my Momo.
Come on, let's go together.
Huh?
Oh, dear.
Niece, you're so noisy
this early in the morning.
Go eat.
Oh, Louie, just help yourself.
Yes, Auntie.
I know your
cooking is always delicious.
Hmm, really?
Well then, keep eating, okay?
I'm just preparing the
food I'm selling later.
You know, Auntie,
if I didn't have class,
I'd even help you sell.
Ass-kisser.
There's no such thing as excuses
when someone truly wants to help.
Exactly.
Here.
Louie, sell my sticky rice
cake to your classmates.
Twenty-five pesos per slice.
But we have a promo, okay?
Fifty pesos, buy one, take one.
Huh?
Auntie, are you really making
me sell sticky rice cake?
Why are you complaining?
Auntie, I don't
think he wants to.
He's complaining.
No, no, no, Momo.
Auntie, I don't
think this is enough.
Maybe you have more back there.
Really?
Then,
sell my tapsilog,
my longsilog, and my hotsilog.
Don't worry, they're
packed in Styrofoam.
They won't be hard to carry.
Okay, Auntie.
That's fine.
Momo's coming with me
to sell them anyway, right?
Oh no.
Come on, we're gonna be late.
Auntie, we're heading out.
I'm gonna be late.
There goes my niece.
Take care, okay?
Louie, take good care
of my niece, okay?
Yes, Auntie.
I'll take good care of
your most beautiful niece.
- Most beautiful?
- Let's go.
I'm her only niece, obviously.
Move. You go first.
Bye!
- Bye, Auntie!
Yeah.
The boss already
knows about Yaji.
But I didn't tell
him about your dad.
If I tell him, then
surely even you...
What?
Aemie's husband
will kill me too?
Yeah, definitely.
But Aemie's my friend.
And...
I'm sure she wouldn't do
that to Aemie's friend, right?
Mr. Roswell...
killed Kaizer's parents,
Jerson's parents,
And Wallace's parents.
Those three are
her friends, right?
his friends.
And you're just his wife's friend.
But, Vash.
What if they find out Aemie
is Dad's real daughter?
How can we stop them
from killing each other?
No.
It's safer if no one finds out.
But, what about Auntie Yana?
I mean,
I wanna know more about
what happened to her.
Why does it feel like she doesn't
know anything about what's happening?
Cai, let's just stay out of it.
You might end up
getting hurt.
Alright. I have to
go. Call you later.
No, you can't do this!
Alyana, I have to do this!
No!
I am...
Alyana Heartily-Ferrer.
I finally remembered my name.
But I still don't understand.
Why is my last
name Ferrer when...
Miguel is my husband?
That's why I love you, babe.
I know, right?
Unless...
he's not really my husband.
Or maybe I'm a cheater?
Who is that man I keep seeing
whenever my head starts to hurt?
And...
why do I seem so rich?
And why are there
so many shootouts?
I feel like the villain
in an action movie!
Who?
Who is that girl I see?
Staring straight
back at me.
I need to find out
who I really am as
Alyana Heartily-Ferrer.
Before I tell Baby
Ae and my niece.
Hi!
You're Aemie, right?
Can I sit here?
Oh, sure.
Wow.
You know me?
Mmm.
You're...
Me?
I'm your...
guardian angel.
Oh my!
You're an angel?!
No wonder you're so beautiful.
Why did you come down to Earth?
Can I see your wings?
Where are your wings?
Can we be friends?
Of course! Seriously!
Why would I say no to being
friends with a real angel?
I'm not literally an angel,
but I'm your guardian angel—
Ma'am Aemie!
Jacob, come here, quick!
Hurry!
Oh no!
Huh?
Where did she go?
The angel?
Where'd she go?
Ma'am, who was that?
Oh, that was my guardian angel.
Why are you here?
Are you here to get
a free meal from me?
Oh, you just
missed Louie earlier!
There was so much
sticky rice cake!
Hey, Jacob!
Hey!
Oh, sorry, ma'am.
Oh, it's Mr. Roswell.
He wants to talk to you.
Hi, Dong.
What on earth have you been up to?
Oh no!
Oh, sorry!
I forgot to charge
my phone again.
Get ready later.
No. Just listen first.
That's not fair!
Why not just tell me now?
Yesterday you said tomorrow,
and today is already "tomorrow."
I'll be the one to fetch you later.
So meet me at the
gate. We'll go somewhere.
Really? Okay, okay.
Alright, alright, alright.
Aye, aye, Captain!
Bye-bye, bye-bye.
Oh, Jacob, your phone.
Hey, Jacob, your phone!
Oh, sorry, ma'am.
Thank you.
Ma'am, wasn't that girl pretty?
Here's the entire map
of the Grand Park Hotel.
Your target is the hotel owner.
Alexander Park.
There will be a big transaction
at around 9 in the evening.
So, we only have a
few hours left to prepare.
Do we need a negotiator
for that transaction?
No.
He's going to meet
someone, and we don't care.
Our aim is Young here.
Finish off his target.
Nothing else.
Do we really need
to go with Young?
Just so he can
take out his target?
I mean,
this guy is old enough.
He can handle it.
Don't underestimate
Alexander Park.
According to my sources,
there'll be a lot of guards
at the location later.
The more, the merrier.
Our directive is
to shoot on sight.
Anyone who tries to interfere with
our mission gets a bullet to the head.
And you, Young...
You will focus on your target.
Any questions?
Nah.
I'm good.
Okay.
Good.
Let's get ready.
We need to be there as early
as possible to survey the area.
And remember,
keep your guard up.
We don't know who's going
to be there until we get there.
Shit!
Are you ready?
How about you,
babe? Are you ready?
I'm so ready.
Let's do this.
You're ready?
Let's go.
Grand Park Hotel.
This place is huge, huh?
Are you sure the meeting with
Park is still happening tonight?
Of course.
He's meeting with the boss.
Once we're there, he won't have
any choice but to talk to the boss.
If...
all they're gonna do is talk.
I hope not.
That's the part I'm
looking forward to.
The...
action.
Well, look who's finally here.
Why are you always
off on your own?
Our starting five is never
complete because of you.
I've just been busy.
Busy?
We're all in the same group.
How come
we're not that busy?
Just make sure you're
not hiding anything.
So what's happening tonight?
Alexander Park, 43 years old.
A businessman,
and an arms dealer.
He's smuggling the
latest firearm models.
Arms dealing is
Roswell territory.
Exactly.
That's why Mr. Roswell
is meeting with him.
He's going to negotiate,
and if he refuses
to cooperate...
boom.
But did I hear that right?
Ma'am Aemie is coming too?
That's what the boss said.
Why?
Hello?
Dong?
Where are you?
You're taking so long.
Oh no!
Huh? But...
I still have five minutes
before dismissal.
I don't care!
Just go here in the entrance.
We need to go ASAP.
Oh!
My guardian angel!
Hi!
Who are you talking to?
My guardian angel.
How the hell can she be
a guardian angel if you can see her?
Of course she only appears to
me. She's my guardian angel.
Even Jacob couldn't
see her earlier.
You know, she's really beautiful.
Next time, I'll ask her.
If she's willing to
introduce herself to you.
Huh?
Why are you getting mad?
Do you want to become
a guardian angel too?
The next time we meet,
I'll ask her if they're hiring.
Hmm?
You talk too much.
Just go here already.
I'll show you the real me.
Huh?
The real me?
Why?
Was the Zeke I
married just a clone?
Oh no.
All this time?
All this time.
I've been talking to
a clone every day.
Here, have some juice first.
Thank you, Auntie.
Amesyl should be
on her way home.
I'm sure she's the
reason you came here.
Because if it's Baby Ae,
then, she's with her husband.
Actually, Auntie, I didn't
come here for Amesyl.
I came for you.
Me?
Yes.
I just missed
hanging out with you.
Really?
Then let's hang out.
What course did you
take in college, Auntie?
What was it again?
I can't remember anymore.
What was my...
my course again?
Wait, why are you asking?
I'm just curious, Auntie.
How about Uncle Miguel?
Did you meet in college too?
Ah.
Hey, Caileigh.
What are you really doing here?
Why are you asking
Auntie so many questions?
Girl, calm down.
I'm just curious.
Curious?
You know what, you
better head home.
It's already getting late.
You're just giving
Auntie a headache.
Oh, niece.
We're just hanging out.
It's okay, Auntie.
Amesyl's right.
I'll just head home.
Sorry for disturbing you.
- Alright, head home.
- I'm really sorry.
Damn.
They're all dressed to kill.
But seriously, guys.
No matter how much you dress up,
you'll never outshine
my good looks.
I'm so sorry.
Keep dreaming.
Yeah, yeah.
Lamperouge, that's a new one.
Wide awake, yet still dreaming.
Screw you guys.
Boss.
Hi, Kaizer.
Hi, Sebastian.
Hi, Jacob.
Oh...
You're...
Uhm, Vash, ma'am.
Vash Boulstridge.
Hello.
Mr. Roswell.
So you really are
bringing Aemie?
Did I look like I was
kidding, Lamperouge?
Things are getting worse.
She was receiving threats
from the fucking Yaji.
We have to keep her
close to keep her safe.
Got that?
Affirmative.
What are you whispering about?
None of your business.
Wow.
Wow, that's a lot of guns.
I knew it, you're a cop.
I'm not a cop.
A soldier?
Even less.
A bodyguard?
Close.
But no.
Then what are you?
A neighborhood watchman?
Good grief.
Ahh!
A traffic enforcer!
For someone this handsome?
No way.
Oh, and once again...
I'm the one getting picked on.
They're just jealous
because I'm handsome.
What?
Nothing, boss.
Oh!
Are we watching a movie?
Is it a horror movie?
It's been so long since
I last watched one.
Should we buy
some popcorn first?
Just shut up and watch.
The location of the night
mission is at Grand Park Hotel.
The building has a total of 25 floors,
Not counting the ground floor
and three basement parking lot.
At the penthouse you will
meet up with Alexander Park.
He will have a total of
17 bodyguards with him.
All armed with single
semi automatic pistols.
At the vip room you
will locate Roxanne Park,
Daughter of Alexander Park.
She will be an important
part of the mission.
Jacob Lee and Vash Boulstridge ,
You are asigned to the security area.
There will be atleast four guards.
This movie is so boring.
It's all narration and graphics.
And...
who are those
people in the pictures?
Are those Parks famous?
Look at Kaizer. He's
joking around, but...
he looks bored out of his mind.
Why do you always
drag me into this?
Do you want me to cut
you down, Lamperouge?
Huh?
There? Do we stay there?
It's always me, alright.
That's right.
Gear up and proceed
to the parking lot.
Aye, aye, Captain.
Why are you dragging me?
Except you.
I still have
something to tell you.
What?
Whatever you witness later,
just don't freak out
and avoid making a scene.
Okay?
A scene?
Is there gonna be a movie later?
Is it a Viva Films movie?
No.
There's going to be a meeting.
An underground meeting.
Underground.
Oh! Wait,
I thought we were
going to a hotel?
Oh, underneath it?
Who are you meeting?
Earthworms?
Underground
creatures or something?
Ouch.
That hurts.
That's because your
imagination keeps running wild.
What I mean by underground...
is that...
it's going to be illegal.
Oh no.
Illegal?
You mean we're about
to do something bad?
Oh no, Dong, what
if the police catch us?
We'll end up in pris--
What if I throw you
in jail for flicking me--
Ouch! Hey, that was hard!
That hurt!
I'm committed to doing
this even if it's illegal.
Because it's my job.
You don't get it, do you?
That's why I'm just
going to show you.
I know you.
It'll probably take ten years
if I try explaining it to you
before you understand.
So I'll just show
you who I really am.
Hmm.
Oh.
He thinks I'm slow, huh?
Ouch.
Let's go.
Oh, wait.
Didn't you say there
were two things?
You're just gonna
show me one of them.
So what's the other one?
You sure talk a lot.
Come on, you still
need to change.
Huh.
Why do I need to get dressed?
Does my husband think I'm naked?
What a pervert.
Pervert!
You're such a pervert.
Let's go.
Hello?
Do you recognize my voice?
Hmm?
Guardian angel?
Yes. I'm calling to warn you.
It's too dangerous.
There are three groups
at the Grand Park Hotel.
Dangerous?
Why?
Hello?
What's she on about?
The food here is so good.
Hey!
Oh no!
Oh, what's going on?
They all look so scary.
Just relax, Aemie.
We're here with you.
I know.
Just look at my handsome
face so you won't be scared.
You agree, don't you?
I'm handsome, right?
Mommy said lying is bad.
But if it's just a white lie...
Fine, fine. You're handsome.
Wait, why do you
sound so unsure?
Didn't you notice—
Stop blabbering, Lamperouge.
Let's go.
Me again?
I always get dragged into this.
Why is it always me?
Oh no!
They look like wrestlers.
Hey!
What's going on?
Why do they all have guns?
Why--
Why don't I have a
gun? That's so unfair.
One wrong move,
you're going to get your brain
splattered all over this entrance.
It's Mr. Roswell.
Mr. Roswell,
our apologies.
We didn't know it was you.
Please, come in.
Calm down.
I've been waiting
for Mr. Roswell.
Are you Alexander Park?
Fuck!
We've got company!
Shit's about to go down.
It already did.
How much longer do
you think they'll be?
Looks like we need
to make our exit.
Let's go.
Let's split up.
Alexander Park is going
to be on the top floor.
But we can't just charge in.
We need to be smart about this.
Copy?
Copy.
Let's go.
Put your gun down, miss.
I don't mind fighting women.
Shit!
That was just a warning shot.
Next time,
I'm aiming for your head,
Meisha Lamperouge.
Fuck!
What are you doing here?
Dumbass!
You're disrupting our meeting.
I knew Mr. Park was your target.
My dad?
What are you going to do to him?
None of your business!
You know,
I could kill you both right here.
But I'm not, because I'm nice.
So you owe me
your fucking lives.
So what now?
I'm going to give you the most
unforgettable night of your life.
With your clothes still on?
You handle this, okay?
Also,
I saved my number in your phone.
Just in case you want to beg
me not to tell Kaizer you're here.
Let's go.
Looks like you didn't
bring enough men, Roswell.
Even if I'd come here alone,
it wouldn't have
made any difference.
You should know that.
Now,
let's make this quick.
I'm only going to
give you two options.
First.
Sign this document.
If you do,
you have to stop interfering
with my arms dealing business.
Do so,
and I'll let you live
your life peacefully.
And the second choice?
I'll interfere with
your business.
Hey!
You're a funny kid.
Are those real gold teeth?
Those look like the
wrappers from chocolate coins.
I used to buy those
too when I was a kid.
At the corner store.
Care to introduce the beautiful
young lady with you, Roswell?
Perhaps, she's someone
important to you, huh?
Why don't we speak with
someone important to you instead?
Yo!
- Roxanne!
- Am I late?
Dad!
Don't you dare hurt my daughter!
Oh no!
This old man's so judgmental.
Who said anything
about hurting her?
Sebastian's
actually really nice.
And Zeke's even nicer.
He just looks intimidating.
Guardian angel,
where are we going?
There's too many of them.
I'll lure them away.
When I do, run.
Run the other way.
Here.
Oh no!
Pull the trigger if you have to.
Seriously?
Yes.
Now go.
Head to the lobby.
Once they leave.
I'm sure the
Roswells will be there.
I'll handle things here.
Okay.
Go.
Hey!
What's going on?
Why are so many people dying?
Is this...
Is this what Zeke
wanted to tell me?
Is this what he meant when
he said this was his world?
Is this also...
Is this also the
reason Dad died?
I hope Zeke's okay.
I hope, I hope he
hasn't been shot!
I hope I don't run into anyone.
I hope I don't-
Oh no.
Whose mom is this?
I'm looking for sour soup seasoning.
Huh?
Zeke!
Aemie?
Aemie!
Lamperouge!
Where's Aemie?
I thought she was with you?
Fuck!
Dad?
Dad!
Zeke!
Moo?
Why do you have a gun?
Dammit, Aemie!
Where the hell have you been?
Why do you keep wandering off?
Huh?
Because, because
of my guardian angel.
Your stupidity is
going to get you killed!
Hey, wife!
I'm talking to you!
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Please.
Don't make me worry again.
I love you so much
that I won't be able
to forgive myself
if something bad
happened to you.
I love you so much
that I don't want you to know
how fucked up my life really is.
I love you so much
and that's the goddamn reason
why I'm about to lose my sanity.
Hey.
Please say something.
Hey!
Hey! Come on, let's go!
Is this really the
time for a moment?!
Please.
Remind me to kill Lamperouge
when we get out of here.
Aemie!
Ma'am Aemie!
Wife!
Boss, we have to go!
Bro.
That raid really wore me out.
Keep quiet. You might
wake up Ma'am Aemie.
Was that all just a dream?
Did I fall asleep because
of that boring movie earlier?
How was your sleep, wife?
It was okay.
But...
Zeke.
What really happened
at the hotel earlier?
Why was there a war?
So it was real after all.
It wasn't planned.
I never meant to put
your life in danger, wife.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
You're sorry.
But...
But why did all that happen?
What is it that you
really want me to know?
That...
That I'm a mafia boss.
Zeke, what even is this mafia?
Are they...
Are they just burglars?
Those scam syndicates?
People like that?
Oops! Porn!
- What the fuck!
- Shit, sorry!
No, boss. Mr. Roswell, wait!
Just wait!
Don't worry. See you, then.
Where have you been, Auntie?
I love you.
Hey, where'd you get that, Dong?
Where's your ring?
How's everyone?
What happened?
Doing good?
You look pissed.
What happened?
What if I can't bring
myself to kill the last target?
Then you'll die.
And her.
And so will Aemie.