In the infinitely unknown universe there is an Earth-like planet.
On that planet, there is a country called Joseon.
If you think that it is strangely familiar, that is your delusion.
Coincidentally, two females sharing the same fate were born on the same day and time.
This story starts also by coincidence when their life and death fates diverted.
I say this again, but this story is fiction.
Edict Banning Marriage for any female age 13 to 18 What does this even say...
What does it say? Shouldn't someone explain?
It seems an edict forbidding marriage has been issued.
It hasn't been too long since the crown princess died.
Why are they already selecting a new bride for the royal family?
It says everyone's marriage is forbidden.
Forbidden marriage? What does that mean?
What that means is this!
The marriage ban
is a policy that is put into action while the royal family searches for a new queen or crown princess.
Simply said, the royals consider themselves a priority,
so they prohibit marriage for all females who are of age.
That is what it means.
What is this? Does that mean I cannot meet my future wife?
If I am not married, I cannot meet a husband?
But look at the time we live in!
A male and female cannot be in the same place if they're older than seven.
A man and a woman cannot meet and share affection freely.
Until marriage, they cannot even touch each other's hands.
And they dare forbid marriage for us?
They are too much!
Old man, what do you think about me learning how to determine marital compatibility?
Come on now, don't you know the meaning of the marriage ban?
People needing to be married come to me with a bundle of money to determine their external and internal compatibility.
Now all the compatibility readers will starve to death!
You're someone who knows one thing but you don't know something else.
Even if the country prohibits marriage officially,
do you really think men and women can be stopped from forming relationships?
What?
Just wait and see.
The longer they prohibit it, the more the fervor for love will boil over.
If you and I are in the middle of a relationship between people
there will definitely be a clever way for us to make a living.
Aigoo, I certainly do not have the guts for swindling.
Leave me out of this!
Wait, how is this swindling?
It is natural for man and woman to pair up and live together.
The country that prohibits that is crazy!
Come now.
If you must label me, call me a messenger of love for young lovers.
♫ The youths all over the country who have fallen in love ♫
- Get him!
Though this line of work looks a bit rough,
it has its rewards.
Forget about marriage in this lifetime anyway.
Let us go for one shot at life!
Let us go!
If you desire, I can find you a lady.
Did she say "a lady"?
And with this amount of money, I can even set up a secret marriage ceremony.
- Search the premises!
- Yes, sir!
Save your money for now.
Let us be sure to meet again. All right?
What in the world?
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, my!
I connected you two last time!
But why do you have that look...
Isn't this a little too rough?
♫ The youths all over the country ♫
♫ who have fallen in love, gather around ♫
♫ Here is So Rang, the best compatibility reader in Joseon ♫
♫ Here comes So Rang! ♫
♫ Yes, hooray! ♫
♫ Catch So Rang, catch So Rang! ♫
♫ Constantly on the move, left and right! ♫
♫ Aigoo, has anyone seen So Rang? ♫
♫ The best swindler of love connections in Joseon ♫
♫ Here comes So Rang! ♫
Edict Banning Marriage
Aigoo, darn it!
What kind of tyranny is this?
Don't you all agree?
They enforced a marriage ban for the people, yet the king's queen selection fails every time,
and the king fathers no children.
It has already been seven years since all the youths were forbidden to marry!
Aigoo! What to do...
My daughter will become a virgin ghost at this point!
Hey, hey! Take a look!
This is my daughter. Look how pretty she is!
What a waste of beauty!
The Forbidden Marriage
Ye So Rang, released!
When will you stop swindling?
I need some seed money to live like a human being.
Is this enough to make you stop?
Old man...
This money... Where did you get this?
I saved up while you were swind—
It's my savings from reading fortunes.
This money should be enough to open a store in Insagol!
Insagol?
Let us... go to Hanyang.*
(Capital city of Joseon, current day Seoul)
Hey, you said you would not go to Hanyang!
Your mind comes and goes due to age.
How much longer will you wander?
My goodness!
Episode 1
Do you really have to do this?
Yes, I must do this.
Drugging the king's tea is a crime whose gravity is immeasurable.
We have served his majesty for so many years.
Even if I get my tongue pulled out for treason and get castrated, I must do what must be done.
But Head Eunuch, you're already...
Never mind.
Do not be afraid.
This is a brave decision made for the sake of this nation, Joseon.
Where is the girl for today's feat?
Come here.
My name is Cho Ran.
No one can match her in Joseon when it comes to the art of yin and yang*.
(Intercourse technique)
With her skills, we will surely succeed in our mission to have his majesty sleep with her.
With this remedy, even an old man on the verge of becoming a corpse could father a late child. (Biageora: Ability to stand up, unlike oneself, to accomplish the job)
But his majesty is no ordinary man!
If we fail tonight once again, it means that his majesty
has either been castrated or is one of those who don't like women.
What?
Is this man the king?
Who is that woman?
Her name is Cho Ran. She is filling in for Sun Ah, who is ill.
She will serve you some tea to help with your insomnia.
Is that so?
It will be enough!
I heard even one cup turns a man's body to a pillar of fire.
If you are feeling hot, I will undress you.
So then... we shall take our leave.
Ja Yeon...
Please think of me as if I were Ja Yeon.
Who dares to have her name pass your lips so carelessly?
Is anyone out there!
Oh, my goodness...
Move!
Oh, dear!
Who is responsible for this?
Please kill me, Your Majesty.
Explain yourselves!
Why did you plot such a thing?
So, please... could you please get married, Your Majesty?
You must have had enough of this life.
It looks as though you want to end it here?
I am Chief Lee Sin Won of the Royal Investigation Bureau.
It has been a while since I have been in your presence, Your Majesty.
Everyone, leave.
What if this leads to a bloody sword fight?
They have been friends for a long time. I doubt it.
I have carried out your orders and returned, fulfilling my duties, Your Majesty.
You are reporting in a rather extreme fashion today.
Do you also see me as a madman and a tyrant?
You do seem that way a little bit at the moment.
Your Majesty, how can I be blind to your concerns?
However, you must effectively address the suffering of your subjects
due to the marriage ban that has been going on for the last seven years.
When the marriage ban is over, do you believe you, too, will be able to marry?
You are also still searching for her.
That woman who disappeared.
That is why the only one who can understand me is you.
Sin Won,
even if the people all point their fingers at me, I hope you remain by my side to the end.
I will abide by your orders, Sire.
Whoa, I have finally returned to this place.
Aigoo, you like coming back here looking like this?
What is there not to like?
We have all this seed money to start!
Let us go, go.*
(Guh-guh sounds like "Go, go")
Hanyang, this eonni* has returned.
(Elder sister)
Let's go!
Come and get some!
How do I look?
- Aigoo! Can't do that!
- Hello?
Aigoo, how can you do that?
Is anyone here?
Yes, yes.
(Realtor)
I am looking to set up a store in Insagol.
Yes!
What kind of store are you looking for?
Well, let me see...
I am thinking of setting up a tea house in a peaceful spot.
A tea house?
There are several places nearby for a tea house.
- Let us go.
- Yes, let us.
All right.
All right, come this way.
Urgent Sale: Tearfully Going Out of Business
This place is near the capital, so there's a lot of foot traffic.
Hey, hey... wait...
Wait!
Urgent Sale: Tearfully Going Out of Business
Look, how about here? It's good, right?
Tearful Closing Sale, Everything Is One Nyang
Farewell to Marriage
All right, over here...
Old man!
Would you like to see some more?
No, we will settle for this one.
Ae
Aedaldang
Aedaldang: Place Where Love is Mastered
Aedaldang, you say.
You plan to read compatibility here?
And what if people fall in love and get married?
You will be arrested right away!
So... do you plan to report us?
Well, no.
As long as I am paid, I am done here.
Oh, shoot.
So, there are already rumors about yesterday?
Unexpectedly, Biageora is all sold out.
My goodness. On top of that!
On top of that, what?
The ghost of the Crown Princess, who met an unjust death, appears in the palace,
and it has blocked the marriage fortune for all the youths in our country.
There is such a rumor going around.
You know, I heard the king has been hallucinating and all.
Come on, what ghost?
His Majesty...just can't forget.
Like you, sir?
Yes. Like me.
So... you just let go of that woman who visited you last night?
How would I know who sent her to me?
Is that what is important?
From what I hear, ambassadors from Arabia have secretly brought in
certain drugs into your palace, Queen Mother.
Shall I start investigating that first?
So, how far were you able to go?
Grandmother!
Dear, I am just worried!
I just wonder how your overall health is.
I am also worried that the street rumors may turn out to be true.
What rumors?
Aigoo...
Never mind.
The Gyotaejeon, the queen's quarters, should be occupied so I don't have to be plagued with doubts.
If we fill that place recklessly, you are well aware of what may happen.
Your Majesty, the long-standing marriage ban has resulted in a serious decline in the birth rate.
Instead of setting up a starter home for newlyweds, how can we forbid marriage?
In a nation where no babies are born, how can speak of our future?
Please hasten and begin the queen selection process.
According to the rumor going around,
you may be a tyrant who has gone mad
or someone who craves men
or a eunuch who cannot function as a man.
Is it not a relief, though?
None of them actually apply to Your Majesty.
And isn't it you who views me in such a manner, Minister of Defense?
I am simply relaying the gossip among the people who gather every night to chat.
So, if you abolish the marriage prohibition, it will put everyone at ease.
Was this ever something attached to me?
Why? You are attached* to it, are you not?
(Alluding to his testicles)
Minister!
Young people are busy preparing for exams and looking for employment these days
so much that they claim they can't afford marriage or children.
The way I see it, whether we lift the edict or not, the situation will not change very much.
Why do you take for granted that you have the right to take away people's rights?
Everyone, please listen.
As this Marriage Ban Edict should not stay in place too much longer,
I will make sure to select a queen by the end of the year and put an end to the ban.
It is already the third queen selection in the past seven years.
Did you not cancel all the previous selections, unfortunately?
But that will not happen again this time.
How can you guarantee anything in life?
You speak as if this upcoming selection process is bound to fail as well.
Of course not, Your Majesty.
It all stems from my dedication to your security.
My security, you say...
My security...
Your Majesty.
Where are you headed, Sire?
Regarding my security, should I not be the one to rise above the threat?
I will head to my late wife's dwelling place.
Your Majesty!
What is all this?
Please follow me.
Heon-i.
Oh, just...
Please call me that just once.
Yi Heon. Heon...
Heon-i. Heon-i. Heon-i. Heon-i. Heon-i!
How can I speak your name so casually, Your Highness?
Crown Princess, how is it that you do not fully open up to me?
How can I relax when showing my dedication toward you?
Dedication? No, I don't really like dedication. I want to be adored.
While you're at it, love and affection given to your husband. How about that?
Surprise!
I brought some sweet alcohol tonight.
That way, our relationship can also become sweeter.
I am both thankful and sorry
that you always cherish me so.
It's because you are lovable,
that you are receiving such love.
Even such beautiful feelings
can cause misunderstandings among the public.
For a husband to love his own wife?
Because, Your Highness...
you must not show any type of weakness.
There is no windstorm.
The ocean does not become stagnant because of the wind and waves.
Underneath the calm facade of these waters,
I am saying it may be stagnant.
If the power stays in one place too long, it too becomes corrupt.
That is why a windstorm is needed to turn the tide.
A windstorm that will change this nation may be necessary,
but those without a tether could end up being carried away by the waters.
So, there is no tether for you, Crown Princess?
How about I become that tether? I will be that tether for you.
Your Highness, you must separate love from affairs of state.
If I get caught in the storm that blows through the palace,
and even though I drift apart from you,
please do not worry and take care of yourself, Your Highness.
Why would we... drift apart?
Then promise me this.
That you will take care of yourself, Crown Princess.
Are you saying you cannot promise me this?
Please... take good care of yourself, Your Highness.
- No, Your Highness!
- Move...
- Your Highness, no.
- Move!
I am her husband.
- Move out of my way.
- To see the corpse of a criminal who committed suicide,
will bring bad fortune upon yourself, Your Royal Highness.
How dare you call her a criminal...
What do you mean by suicide?
For certain,
this is murder by strangulation. It's murder!
This is murder!
Your Highness...
Let go of me!
Who dares to kill the Crown Princess?
Who dares...
Crown Princess, why are you lying here like this...
Please, open your eyes... Oh, no...
Look! Call the royal physician right away!
Why are you lying here like this... Oh, no, Ja Yeon...
Ja Yeon, please open your eyes, I beg you... Oh, no...
Your Highness.
Your Majesty! Please, don't be like this.
- Please go back, Your Majesty!
- Your Majesty!
I need to rise above everything.
Those who don't know what happened could say so.
However, not us.
Please do not enter, Your Majesty!
Move out of the way.
- Your Majesty!
Crown Princess?
Please come here, Crown Princess.
It was suicide for sure, I'm telling you.
She took that fatal step because of her inability to adjust to palace life.
Such a disloyal crown princess who left you behind must never be forgiven.
Who says that? Who says this was a suicide?
Who dares to say that?
Crown... Crown Princess...
Crown Princess? Crown Princess?
Crown Princess, weren't you just here?
Crown Princess! I am over here!
I swear you were here just now!
Ja Yeon...
Your Majesty.
Yes, Sin Won, there you are.
The crown princess. She was just here. Didn't you see her?
She was really just here a moment ago.
Your Majesty. You promised to take a new queen this year
and end the marriage ban.
If you keep hallucinating about the deceased crown princess,
how will you be able to accept a new queen?
You must forget her.
Will that... be possible in this lifetime?
It's a lost cause in this lifetime.
Even if you gift all sorts of valuables and treasures,
will that be enough to capture a woman's heart?
Instead of that, why not come inside and chat over some tea?
I will give you the best advice on how to win over a woman's heart!
I do not love any woman.
How dare you try to swindle us by lying?
But that... Surely, you did not buy that for your mother?
- This is nonsense.
- Looks like a quack to me.
- More like a swindler.
- But—
Come now. No matter how hard you try, you cannot find a woman to love.
How can it be explained by words alone?
Even after we pass the current situation of the marriage ban.
No, you will not be allowed to marry even after a hundred or a thousand years.
You don't even know how painful that is...
Is he in your category, old man?
Stop deceiving yourselves,
and start accepting and loving yourself.
Loving yourself is the most important thing in the world.
Yes, of course.
Thank you, old man.
- Hey, take me with you!
- What's going on?
I guess that old man is for real.
As expected! As expected of Sir Gwaeng Yi.
He's called Sir Gok Gwaeng Yi* because he's able
(= "pickaxe")
to dig into people's hearts with his spiritual channeling.
Here, here. If you have anything you want to know about your love life,
please come to Aedaldang.
Please come!
Aedaldang
You!
Hey! I told you not to make up nonsense with your non-existent channeling ability!
My keen eye is more accurate than your on-and-off channeling ability.
So why are you suddenly making a fuss about this?
We're now in the capital city!
We're no longer wandering about!
And I told you that we should not do business in the daytime.
Are you trying to get me arrested by doing business and promoting like that?
You're making my heart beat so fast that I'm going to lose my mind!
Whom are you trying to blame for you becoming senile?
But hey, it's a bit of a shame to hear
that the handsome young master was on "that side".
I once was as handsome as he was.
- Right, let me try slapping you in the face. Come here.
- How dare you!
- Come here-
Well... So... Is this Aedaldang, by any chance?
I heard you were looking for an employee.
Your name is Hae Yeong.
You used to work in a rice soup restaurant,
and you stopped working for a while.
Oh, finding a job these days is really difficult these days.
My Scholar from the Star
Ten years ago, you fell in love with raunchy romance novels and became a master.
No!
Let me see.
Oh, "My Scholar from the Star,"
"The Heirs of Arabia,"
and "Concubines of the Sun"?
Oh, let me explain...
I give you this lanyard to show you've been hired.
Excuse me?
As a permanent employee, of course.
All right!
Thank you! I'll work really hard, I promise!
Hae Yeong is accepted into Aedaldang!
All right.
Aedaldang
A risky hub for relationships during a time when marriages are forbidden.
We really needed someone who's experienced in that field.
If you hold onto this well,
you will find a man who will bring you 30 years of great fortune.
Really?
Thank you! Thank you!
All right, next.
How's the taste of the tea?
So, are you going to do a compatibility assessment?
I heard that young ladies are disappearing every night these days
and only come back in the early morning.
Where do you think they're going to, at such a late hour?
- Is it perhaps-
- Is it true?
What the people say about me nightly when they gather...
That you are a mad tyrant?
No, not that one.
Oh, that you are either castrated or you prefer m—
I must go personally and check to see if what I have heard is true.
P-Personally check...
Welcome to Aedaldang.
Welcome!
I heard you are really good at fortune-telling here.
Yes, that's right! How did you know?
Aedaldang?
Welcome! Welcome.
It's a bit suspicious.
It is.
You did the right thing by coming here.
All right. Once I draw one more line
on this identification tablet...
24 years old
(Draws an extra line, turning the two into a three)
34 years old
Look. We turn someone in her twenties
into someone in her thirties.
What happens if you're ten years older?
Since you would be older than 25,
you will no longer be forbidden from marriage but be able to marry happily!
But if I say I'm 34,
will they believe me?
Of course!
Just say you look young for your age.
I feel like we're at the scene of a marriage fraud.
Why is this darn marriage ban edict lasting so long?
Well, well.
You still don't know the reason?
They say that the king of this nation is either castrated or prefers the love of men.
Which of the two is he, exactly?
From what I can see,
I think he's castrated.
If he had even some of the working parts,
do you think the marriage ban would have lasted seven years?
Let go of me.
So, how could I...
Do I need to show her? Should I pull down my pants
and show her? Do I show her?
If I write a love letter for you, it will be two nyang,
including express delivery.
I'll do that!
What if you get caught doing that?
I heard that they are cracking down on even love letters.
Do you know how many couples I have brought together, going from one corner of Joseon to the other?
I don't get caught!
You are under arrest!
So, you are the infamous marriage swindler?
Me?
That's not me.
- Arrest her!
-Yes, sir!
Are you all right...
This woman...
Did I just...
run into the arms of the Royal Investigation Bureau?
Damn it, I'm doomed!
So...
it's that woman.
Giddy up!
Young lady...
Where are you going in such a rush?
Damn it!
Did you prepare it?
You are under arrest.
W-Why would I be?
You dare to insult the king?
Hey, hey!
Let me go!
Ah, you're so loud!
Be quiet!
A marriage swindler, I see.
Why are you committing marriage fraud at a time such as this?
Sir.
Have you ever heard of the Matchmaking god?
The matchmaker connects the pinky fingers of a couple destined to be together
with a red string of fate.
So, how could a national edict sever such a connection?
A destined connection cannot be severed, you say?
All I did was just help others follow where that string led.
I have never done anything evil.
What is your name?
My name is So Rang.
To form a connection...
No matter how hard I tried,
some relationships never work out.
It appears that you have not been able to see
a person you have been loving deeply for a long time.
You wicked girl!
How dare you try to commit fraud here!
You're trying to commit fraud against the Royal Investigation Bureau chief?
This girl will end up in big trouble one day.
Although we live in a time where marrying is a crime,
having feelings for someone is not a crime.
If that's a crime, then you're also a criminal, sir.
Do you not already have feelings for her?
Everyone living in Joseon would be a criminal
for having feelings for another.
Until you repent for your crime,
you will not be released from this prison.
What? W-Wait!
Wow!
Your speech was amazing!
"Everyone who lives in Joseon would then be a criminal,
for having feelings for another."
- What is this...
- Then...
do you think people like us will be able to find a partner?
Who are you?
If love is a crime, then we are criminals.
- We've never been in a relationship before.
- I'm Wang Bae.
(Seol Ro: Someone who has a hard time talking to the opposite sex)
I'm Oh Deok Hun.
Seoll Ro*
(=Solo)
How dare they try to pull one like that?
Since it's fate that we've met like this, please help us.
Hey, don't even talk with these guys.
They got caught spying on women washing their hair in the creek.
- What do you mean we were spying!
- Spying?
I said we went there to wash as well.
Hurry up and pull out your head!
Geez.
I want everyone to leave me be.
Wow.
Man, how long has it been?
How do I get out of here?
To think that I came all the way here
for such a petty criminal...
Your Majesty, you need to hurry up and return.
Let us do that.
You wretches!
Do you know who I am that you're holding me in here?
I am...
the Matchmaker god!
The Matchmaker god?
H-Hey, hey! Look over there...
Is she being possessed?
Since she's a fortune teller, I guess the spirit comes in and out of her at times.
I, the Matchmaker god, say
that the Marriage Ban Edict will end this year!
She says the Marriage Ban Edict will end!
Does that mean a new queen will be selected this year?
However,
if the king does not get rid of the spirit of the dead crown princess that is in him,
the life of the new queen would also be in danger.
If that happens, you all
- will have to live as Seol Ro forever!
- No!
She's been arrested for committing fraud.
Do you all actually believe her?
Seol Ro!
I, the Matchmaker god, say
that if the Marriage Ban Edict does not end by this year,
there will be great woe upon this palace.
There will be
a plague of Seol Ro in this nation!
A plague of being Seol Ro!
Sin Won.
At the hour of the swine*,
(between 9 p.m. - 11 p.m.) bring her to me.
Criminal, listen to me.
Your crime has fallen upon the ears of the king.
What?
Wait, what?
The king will interrogate you himself,
so prepare yourself.
The king h-himself?
Hey, hey...
W-Why am I seeing the king?
Does a lowly commoner like me usually see the king for something like this?
Hey!
Since you cannot meet the king looking like this,
change your clothes first.
Prostrate yourself.
Lift your head.
So, you have a channeling ability.
Well, that's not entirely true...
It comes and goes.
I go back and forth, sir.
Supposedly, the Matchmaker god came into you earlier?
Well, that...
was not intended, but yes.
Lift your head and speak.
Do I really have a spirit attached to me?
He's the king?
Whoa, daebak.
He's a flower boy.
But his face looks like he hasn't slept for a few days, is gaunt, and his eyes are gloomy.
Even then, his face is hot, no, I mean...
One conclusion comes to mind.
It's just the face of someone hurting from losing a loved one.
Spirit, my foot.
He's being like that, been hallucinating.
You do...
have a spirit on you.
You probably have trouble sleeping at night
because it is the time when that spirit is most active.
And even though you're not really sick,
you have trouble eating food.
Don't you sometimes see and hear imaginary things?
And you probably felt great pain in your stomach
as if you've been hit with a metal hammer.
That's true.
It hurts. It hurts a lot.
The crown princess keeps saying something in my dream,
but I just can't seem to make out what she says. What...
is she trying to say?
If I knew that, I would be a true channeler.
What was the name of the king again?
Heon? Yi... Yi Heon?
Heon-i?
I saw the crown princess' face in my dream...
but her face was so faint.
If you truly have a channeling ability,
could you call forth the crown princess to appear before me?
Excuse me?
Well, her body's already gone, though...
Then,
how can I believe that you have a channeling ability?
I guess you don't have a channeling ability after all!
Oh, no, no.
No way!
Although I cannot show the crown princess to you,
it should be possible for me to channel her spirit.
Your Highness,
have you been well?
Is it really you, Crown Princess?
Let me first
offer you a bow.
My physical body,
even my bones have turned to dust,
and now,
even my eyes, nose, and mouth have disappeared,
and there is no more evidence that I even existed on this earth.
However, the reason why my spirit is still here
is because
I am hurting so badly.
Hur—
Hurting? How are you hurting?
It hurts me to see you in so much pain
because of me, Your Highness.
I have committed
a great act of disloyalty
by departing first and leaving you behind.
I don't know how I can be forgiven for my sin.
I am...
so sorry.
What do you mean by that...
It was my fault that I could not even protect my wife.
I have been lingering around in this world
because I was worried about you.
So now,
please let me go.
What do you mean, let you go?
Where are you going to go now?
You have to let go of me,
so that I can depart from this world.
I have wanted to see you...
even if it is like this.
You have to
let me go now.
You must erase any longing you have for me as well.
Will that be possible in this life?
The spirit of a dead person
cannot stay very long in a living person's body.
I...
must go.
Do not go.
Wait...
Please do not go. Be with me for just a bit longer.
Please do not go.
- Please do not go.
- Y-Your Majesty.
It appears that Crown Princess has left.
Your Majesty...
Everyone...
Everyone, leave.
So, what will happen to me, then?
Put her back into the cell.
Excuse me?
Excuse me? W-Wait, what?
Wait!
I-I'm going back? Y-Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Don't you have more to say to Crown Princess?
I'll deliver your message for you, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Let me go!
Hey!
How did it go?
Do not...
talk to me!
I told you.
She's just plain old fraud.
Did anything happen back there?
Chief.
Chief Lee Sin Won!
Lee Sin Won?
What's wrong?
Your name is Lee Sin Won, Chief?
The willow tree family's firstborn son?
H-How do you know that?
That's what I used to be called.
Well, I mean...
The willow tree family's firstborn son, Lee Sin Won.
You're going to be in big trouble if you underestimate
my channeling ability!
How did she know
that you're seeing apparitions?
I thought it was just my imagination...
Your Majesty, please end the Marriage Ban Edict quickly!
Who are you?
I asked who you are!
- Your Majesty, the crown prince's depression is severe.
- Go away!
- Please end the Marriage Ban Edict quickly
- and select the next queen.
- Please select your next queen.
Your Majesty, do you remember me?
- Your Majesty.
- Be quiet.
Supposedly, another body was left hanging in the crown princess' quarters.
How many days to go until the crown princess' memorial day?
If we can't find the murderer before then,
there will be another body of a woman hanging in the crown princess' palace.
This is already the sixth year.
Every year, on the same day and in the same place,
a body of a woman is left hanging.
We could not revive any of them.
During the last selection,
the most likely candidate selected within the inner circle died.
That's why we canceled the selection as if it were your decision.
The Marriage Ban Edict of this nation
is essentially the plot of a traitor.
The crown princess was not someone who would commit suicide, Royal Father!
Please...
Please let me at least hold a funeral for her.
Please, please, at least a funeral...
Crown Prince.
There's no way we could hold a funeral for someone who violates the law by committing suicide.
I will personally speak with my royal father and hear what he has to say.
I am the one who put His Majesty the king on the throne.
Therefore, there is no need for you to hear the king's will,
for my word is the will of the king.
What are you all doing?
Escort the crown prince back to his palace.
Royal Father! Royal Father!
However, if I manage to catch all the traitors,
will I stop hearing these sounds
and stop seeing these apparitions?
Sin Won, you're here.
I must be going crazy,
seeing how I am glad to see these apparitions...
If you are suffering that much,
how about keeping her by your side?
From what I can tell, she seemed to have some channelling ability.
Why not keep her by your side
and console the spirit of the deceased crown princess?
We can have her enter the palace under the guise of an inner court maid.
However, this will all be part of the process of letting the crown princess go.
Would you be able to do this?
Sin Won.
You told me before that I need to forget her.
Could you watch over that girl when she enters the palace?
As you already know, the palace is...
a bit dangerous.
Your will is my command.
Come out now.
The reason why I am still here is
because I am
hurting so badly.
It hurts me to see you in so much pain
because of me, Your Highness.
I have been lingering around the nether world because I was worried about you.
You have to let me go now.
You must erase your longing for me as well.
Follow me.
I will tell you where you will be staying from now on.
Crown Princess!
Are you here, Crown Princess?
I must be a bit crazy
if I am missing even the apparitions.
♫ On this night, where even the moon is asleep ♫
♫ Where are you headed in such a rush? ♫
♫ A night where you're headed on a long journey ♫
♫ Without even a word ♫
The Forbidden Marriage
Preview
It looks like I will have to act as a court lady from now.
Really?
I'll be entering as an inner court maid.
Whoa, that scared me!
Who made the rumbling noise?
Are you hungry?
Is the Crown Princess hungry?
How lost is he without her that he misses a dead person?
You need to help him forget her, even if it means deceiving him.
Will I not get taken away if they find out I deceived him?
I should get him on my side first.
If you drink that entire thing, we will be friends, all right?
Have you ever almost gotten married before?
Ye Hyeon Seon.
Do you recognize that name by chance?
♫ All of it is something I must carry ♫