We are far apart
A moment of flowers, a moment of love
I never know you are not here
How much love is in my heart
The most beautiful flower in my eyes
Hurry to mathematics, prepare to be a model
Spring is bitter, and when young the time feels strange
Promise to Mikuna is a love
Ending will be sure to share
I hope that the well-hesto love will plan for the 앞에
A Love So Romantic
Episode 05
I got it.
If you let go,
you can't find me.
Don't cry.
Master Wu Zhuang asked me to come and tell you
that Xuan Ye is fighting against the disciples of the Ling Sect
in Longyin City.
He's trying to break into the Ling Sect.
Please decide on this.
Rong Su is the first one to offend.
Xuan Ye is the second one to break into.
Then you tell me,
should I deal with Rong Su first
or solve Xuan Ye's problem first?
I dare to come here alone.
I'm prepared.
I told Xuan Ye
to go back in time
and blow up the entrance of the Ling Sect with the gun.
Even if I die,
I want you and the Ling Sect to die with me.
Good.
It seems that you haven't improved
in such a long time.
You're just a slave.
Lu Yi Zhou
has several disciples guarding the entrance.
He must keep Xuan Ye alive.
Right.
Tell Rong Jingfeng
that
Longyin City
is in danger.
Yes.
Go now.
Guards.
Take this girl down.
Yes.
Guards.
The leader should stay alive.
The rest
shall be killed without mercy.
Yes.
It seems that Lingxu Pavilion
also has a chance of being exposed.
Our Lingxu Pavilion
will not be taken down by anyone.
Today
the bloodbath of Longyin City.
I advise you
to tell him where the Hall Leader is.
Otherwise...
Otherwise what?
You plan to take this place as a flat land, right?
Your Hall Leader has this plan.
It's just a plan to return to the forbidden.
No.
He knew
he couldn't escape from Mohan's hand.
What do you want?
Don't worry.
Mohan won't kill him.
Don't struggle for nothing.
By the way,
I've sent all the fire medicine nearby.
Today, except you,
no one will leave alive.
I'll kill you today
to tell Rong Jingfeng
that he needs to pay
for the bloodbath of Lingxu Pavilion.
In the past,
whenever you heard about Mohan,
you must have been worried.
You fell into the Spirit Cult,
but you're so calm.
You're different from before.
Does the Grand Priest
always remain the same?
You came here
just to laugh at me?
I'm afraid I'll let you down.
I won't beg for mercy
and I won't let Longyin City down.
You people in Longyin City
are really kind.
You're the bad guys.
But you're so righteous
and so mischievous.
Won't you feel guilty
and guilty?
You just want to avenge Lingxu Pavilion.
I'm a prisoner now.
You can kill me directly.
Why bother?
Right.
YoYo English Channel YouTube
Mohan is right.
Even if you die for a while,
as long as you're alive,
there's still endless pain.
You're noble.
Like the darkness here.
There is no need
to be worried.
This is where I grew up.
Maybe my fear
is burried過 by this life of mine,
or I'm not used to it anyway.
These chains
were made specially for Mo Huan
to imprison me.
When I was young, I was not convinced.
I wanted to escape from here
by taking my uncle's life.
But I was cut off by two ribs.
Maybe the fear here
has long been gone.
You don't have to tell me this.
I used to
pity you for this.
But now,
I've seen through your heart.
No matter what you say,
it's no use.
By the way,
the disciple of Longyin City who came with you
has been killed with a rare skill.
Only Xuan Yi
is alive.
He's here to tell Rong Jingfeng.
I want you to know
that it's just the beginning.
It's not you.
No matter what you say,
it's not you.
You Yizhou,
you tried to deceive yourself.
But you can't deceive me.
If you're so cruel,
why did you
take the opportunity to come in
and stop Mohua?
You clearly have me in your heart.
But you dare not admit it.
Rong Su,
you overestimate yourself.
I wonder when
I'll destroy Longyin City
and kill your father.
I'll even order you to kill him.
I wonder if you'll have any pity.
I'll do it.
It's good.
In that case,
please do it yourself.
I don't want to fall into someone's hands
and take Mohua's heart.
Do you think I dare not?
I bet you dare not.
Okay.
Three days later,
I'll cut your meridians
and waste your martial arts.
I'll ask the disciples of the spiritual cult
to send you back to Longyin City.
I'd like to see
whether the love
is more important
in Rong Jingfeng's eyes
or his position as the City Leader.
Luo Yicheng, say it again.
Look at me and say it again.
Luo Yicheng.
부 receptor
Who's there?
The return hall, Xiaoxiao.
Why are you here?
Ms. Mei.
What on earth happened?
I'm sorry.
This time,
I took the disciples of the Holy Heir's Hall
to investigate Lingxu Pavilion,
but they were ambushed.
In my opinion,
Lingxu Pavilion is still alive.
It's in a state of emergency.
Where is Master Mei?
Where are the disciples of the Holy Heir's Hall?
I've already said it.
We were ambushed.
The disciples of the Holy Heir's Hall have no one to save.
Then why did you have to escape?
What do you mean?
A little sick disciple of the Holy Heir's Hall
You don't have to
put the Holy Heir's Hall in front of me.
How did you get the position of the Holy Heir's Hall?
We know it very well.
You just killed someone not long ago.
Now you've lost your man
and you report to the city.
Even if this matter
goes to the Holy Heir's Hall,
you can't blame him.
So you came here today
just to humiliate me in person, right?
Master Mei is serious.
I have a lot of things to do in the Holy Heir's Hall.
If it weren't for the Holy Heir's Order
to send me to pick up,
I wouldn't have bothered to care about your life and death.
I wouldn't have said anything about your discomfort.
Since we are both on different positions,
let's not waste time on each other.
Then I'll trouble Master Mei
to let Xiao Xiao check the injury
and give the medicine to Zheng.
No need.
It's just a minor injury.
I won't bother the Holy Heir's Hall to worry about it.
Since Master Mei said it's okay,
then Xiao Xiao will send someone back to report.
Please have a good rest.
As for the Holy Heir's Hall,
the City Leader has ordered
that Xiao Xiao will send someone to check it.
If there really is a fish in the water
and there is a hook in it,
it must be clear.
Goodbye.
Miss, please come in.
Although I'm not in any trouble this time,
I also trouble you to run away.
I thank you again.
Master Mei,
what do you want to say?
Ah.
When Miss Xiao Xiao goes to the Lingxu Pavilion
to investigate,
if there is any new news,
please tell Master Mei.
After all,
I took the disciples of the Holy Heir's Hall to investigate
and was ambushed.
I must take revenge.
survived?
Chen Hua living despite yourself was destroyed.
Who is actually winning darkly.
You want to fight?
and the whole army was destroyed.
So the City Leader sent us to help.
But he didn't hurt at all.
What's going on?
You two stay here.
You must pay close attention to Meiyin's actions.
If anything goes wrong,
report it to me.
Yes.
Yue.
That's the residence of Senior Bai.
Master is there too.
Thanks to Senior Bai and the others,
I can control the movement of the Snow Trap
and cut off their source of information.
The Snow Trap
doesn't look that simple.
So you have to be careful.
I know.
But only by using the Snow Trap
can I control some of the martial arts.
Don't worry.
I have my own sense of propriety.
By the way,
Senior Bai is a kind person.
When you see him later,
don't mention him as my master's disciple.
Otherwise, he will be offended.
I know.
I heard
something about Senior Bai.
I didn't expect that he really exists.
Senior Bai has been out of the martial arts world.
But his disciples have made great achievements
and made great achievements.
Did Senior Bai help you get the plum blossom?
No.
Only the senior masters of Black Mountain
know about the cultivation of plum blossoms.
Only the senior masters of Black Mountain know about it.
How did you know?
I worshiped my mother before.
Then I went to Meiyuan to inquire about it.
I happened to see someone cultivating the fan.
So I asked around.
I didn't expect it was really you.
Forget it.
Let's go back.
Master will be very happy
if he knows you are back safely.
Let's go.
Among my many disciples,
you are the most useless.
Master, calm down.
Bai is not your disciple.
Fortunately, I was wise enough
to kick him out of the sect.
Otherwise,
he would have embarrassed me.
Then what should I do?
With your attitude,
you are not a good teacher.
Hurry up.
I'll go now.
Come back.
You are a traitor of Longyin City.
You even want to show up.
I asked him to go.
Master, don't worry.
I have sent people to go.
There are my wild lines nearby.
Even if I go underground,
I can find it.
You can't blame me.
I wanted to go myself.
You bitch.
Where have you been?
You are making me worried.
You...
Sorry to make you worried.
I'm fine.
Good.
Well,
look who I brought back.
Yue.
Master?
Bastard.
Who is your master?
I was wrong.
I...
I only have you.
Master.
This is
the young master of Lingxu Pavilion,
Na Lanyue.
I'm not blind.
I can see it.
She is
laughing at me.
I'm Na Lanyue.
Thank you for your care.
I'm glad
you care about me.
I was young and ignorant.
I knew my master
was a playboy.
How could I take it seriously?
Now that
I'm married to Hua,
I should call you master
just like Hua.
I did something wrong.
Please forgive me.
Well...
Listen to me.
Our previous grudges
are over.
Over.
Good.
Master.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't be with you
before.
I swear
from now on,
I'll take good care of you.
I'll do whatever you want.
I just hope
you can forgive me.
Enough.
Stop acting pitiful.
My little turtle
died in your hands.
She is more pitiful than you.
Who will sympathize with her?
Young man.
Since you're fine,
why did you keep avoiding me?
I'm sorry
to let these people
care about you for nothing.
What happened before
was too chaotic.
I was injured
because I tried to protect others.
I was also
in the process of recuperation.
So I really didn't have a chance
to tell you this news.
Besides,
Linxu Pavilion was destroyed.
I really didn't have the face
to face the people of my clan.
Master.
It's not easy for Yu
to come back after escaping from death.
How about
I make some dishes
for you today?
I'll let you try.
Good idea.
We usually eat
light food in the mountains.
We can take this opportunity
to make up for it.
Make up for it.
It's a good idea to save the life.
Although I'm small,
I'm safe.
It's the best way
to heal here.
Little girl,
she lives in your room.
Take your husband back to his room.
Master.
Thank you, Qian Mei.
We'll leave now.
Let's go.
He's really lucky.
It's good that he can come back alive.
Master.
Do you think
there's anything wrong
between them?
He's a good talker.
Even if he's good at hiding things,
it's hard for him
to escape
from me.
Master.
You mean
he's hiding something from her?
Go ask him.
You're so close to him.
Why are you asking me?
Master.
I didn't explain it clearly before.
It's just a misunderstanding.
I've only
thought about you.
Go find out
where he went
recently.
Why did he get so badly hurt?
Who healed him?
Why do you
care so much about this girl?
I'll go check it out.
Go.
You're so happy.
I'm happy
that you're back safe and sound.
I'm happier
to cook for you.
You're so happy.
I'm happy too.
I'll help you cut the vegetables.
I didn't expect you
to be a cook.
Cooking
is not that hard for me.
Here.
Really?
I don't know why
you suddenly met Young Madam
and followed her to Black Stone Mountain.
I followed her secretly,
but you didn't need to follow me.
That's why I came back first.
How come?
It was clearly Brother Nalan
who was worried that
Rong Hua knew about this.
He told her not to leak it out
and hid it together.
Now he has made thousands of requests.
He can't let anyone
know about it.
Why did he...
Miss Mei, don't worry.
Young Master
has his own plans.
Brother Nalan
always knows what to do.
But when he met
Sister Rong Hua,
he was confused.
Now,
he hasn't recovered from his power
and he's taking a rash move.
If he meets
someone from Longyin City,
he'll be in a bad situation.
I'll go to Black Stone Mountain
and find Young Master.
I'll go with you.
If anything happens,
we can take care of it.
Where did A Yue
go in the middle of the night?
I don't know.
You're a married girl.
You're so lucky.
You didn't eat fruit
in the whole yard.
But you have this bad luck.
You're so...
Master,
A Yue hasn't recovered yet.
I have to take care of him.
You're so healthy
that you can eat and drink.
Of course you won't
argue with me.
That's true.
But you...
Thank you for your understanding.
By the way,
did you see A Yue?
She...
She wasn't in the room?
I thought you two
were together.
That's strange.
She said she'd help me
clean up.
Why did she disappear
so suddenly?
Don't worry.
Maybe
she's on the mountain
to have a look.
No.
I have to go find her.
Wait.
I have something to ask you.
What's wrong, Master?
Do you know
where this kid
is hiding these days?
I heard
Lingxu Pavilion was destroyed.
The fire was burning all night.
No one was alive in the room.
How did he escape?
I always feel
that I felt
a sense of loss
when I saw him this time.
Master,
I also want to ask
if you
have any idea
about the scene
that happened that night
and if he doesn't want to tell me,
forget it.
After all,
it's more important
that he comes back safe and sound.
I'll bear
the responsibility
with him in the future.
You silly girl,
you forgot
that the hatred between a family and a friend
is not fair.
If one day
Longyin City and the Nalan family
are really on the opposite sides,
how will you face your father
and Nalan Yue?
No matter how much
wrongful things Rong Jingfeng did,
he is your blood relative after all.
But he has a deep hatred
between him and Nalan Yue.
This...
Can you bear this?
The mountain road is uneven.
Miss Mei, be careful.
It's okay.
I'm worried about Nalan Yue.
We should take the necessary steps
to find him first.
I
have a question
for Miss Mei.
Brother Cang Qi,
it's okay to say it.
Why are you so persistent
and always stay by Young Master?
You know
he won't respond.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean anything else.
If you don't want to say it,
you can just say it.
Do you think I'm stupid?
I also think
I'm stupid.
But
I just want to
be with him.
It's enough
to see him well.
He doesn't need to respond.
Maybe
he can't understand
my thoughts.
I understand.
It's Brother Nalan.
This is the residence
of Senior Bai.
Senior's martial arts are unspecified.
You can't go any further
to avoid revealing your whereabouts.
I'm afraid that Young Master's secret
will be exposed.
It's not Brother Cang Qi's fault.
I'm afraid of Brother Nalan's safety.
So I asked him to bring me here.
Brother Nalan,
even for the safety of Sister Rong,
you can't show up here.
If...
I have my own plans.
You can do as planned.
I just want to see him.
After I make sure he's safe,
I'll go back soon.
Brother.
Yue.
Where are you?
Miss Mei, let's leave here first.
Young Master has his own plans.
We can't expose ourselves now.
I hope Young Master
won't forget the mission of the Nalan family.
Brother Nalan,
you must be careful.
Yue.
Who were you talking to?
I wasn't talking to anyone.
I've been here for a while.
I didn't see anyone.
You must have seen it wrong.
Did I really see it wrong?
It's cold and humid in the mountains tonight.
Why did you come out?
I came to see you.
I thought you left without saying goodbye.
I should have found you a rope
to tie you up.
Then you wouldn't have left me.
Tie me up?
That's too much.
How do you want to tie me up?
I can tie you up however I want.
I wanted to come back
and watch the stars with you again.
But I didn't expect the rain
to rain so suddenly.
Last time I saw the stars
was when I was still a child.
At that time, I thought
you were a thief who was addicted to the Chihua Beads.
I didn't expect
I married this thief.
Everything is as it was yesterday.
Your lies
have been gone for so long.
You may not believe it.
That night's stars
were the most beautiful stars I've ever seen.
What a pity.
I can't see the stars tonight.
How can you not see them?
I can see them.
Where?
Look at me.
There's only one in my eyes.
How annoying.
Why are you so romantic?
Hua.
Every word I say to you
is true.
Otherwise,
you can take my heart out
and take a good look at it.
I'll take a look.
I'm sorry.
Did I hurt you?
It's okay.
Why are you so nervous?
What's wrong?
I just hope
that I can be like this every day
and watch the stars with you for the rest of my life.
That's not easy.
When the dust settles down,
we'll have plenty of time
to watch the stars with me every day.
Okay.
When the dust settles down.
The End
Master,
did something happen?
What?
Su Er is in the hands of Ling Jiao?
A few days ago,
I went to the gate to investigate the lung of Ling Xuge.
I didn't expect that
he was ambushed.
Now Su Er
is in the hands of Mohuan.
It seems that
Ling Xuge is really a ghost.
Mohuan
is best at controlling people's hearts.
I think he has made up his mind
to destroy our Longyin City step by step.
Everything
must be in his plan.
Master, don't worry too much.
Yin Xiang and Xiao Xiao
have taken the disciples of Bingzi Hall
to pick up Mei Ying.
The priority now
is to save Su Er from Mohuan.
Su Er will be in danger
if she is in Ling Jiao for one more day.
Zi Yan,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
Look at your body.
Don't worry.
Come on, let's sit down.
Come on.
Slowly.
I don't want
Su Er to be out of danger earlier.
I've sent a letter to Xuanye.
The city will send more disciples
to support them.
But
to deal with Mohuan,
I'm afraid it's not enough
to rely on these disciples.
I wanted to
go to the north in person.
But the situation in the city
is that no one can be a witness for a day.
I've found that
Longyin City
has long been a place of humiliation.
People who leave
and die
are no longer
in the same situation as before.
Zi Yan.
If at this moment,
Hua Er and Bai are in the city,
I'm afraid
that...
Forget it.
The past is hard to accept.
It's okay if you don't mention it.
What?
What's wrong?
I'm afraid
I can hold on.
I can still hold on.
Or
I'll take you on a trip this time.
What nonsense are you talking about, Zi Yan?
Listen to me.
I'll meet up with Xiao Xiao and Mei Ying first.
Then we'll go to the north
to save Su Er.
In this city,
you have to be the witness.
At this moment,
Longyin City
can't be in any trouble anymore.
Zi Yan.
Stop talking nonsense, okay?
How can you
leave the city
with your body like this?
No.
I'm fine.
Don't worry, City Leader.
If you're not worried,
I'll prove it to you right now.
Zi Yan.
Zi Yan!
Someone, come here!
Come here!
Take it.
What's the smell?
Why is it so sour?
It's a vinegar-based fruit.
You're kidding me, right?
Try this.
This is sweet.
How do I know this is sweet?
You'll know when you taste it.
Then you try it first.
I worked hard to pick it up.
Of course you have to taste it first.
That's right.
You worked hard to pick it up.
That's why you have to eat it first.
You're right.
Then you have to eat it when I eat it.
I'll try it.
I knew it.
This is sweet.
It's very sweet.
It's so good.
Let's go.
Let's go back.
Here.
What's wrong with you?
It's okay.
It's just a relapse.
It'll be fine in a while.
Are you okay?
Senior Bai and Master are both here.
How about they help you look?
Do you want to go with them?
I'm relieved.
Hua.
Old man, are you reasonable?
Who is unreasonable?
You sneaked in.
You're lucky to meet me.
If you meet my master and my senior,
it's not as simple as you.
Find Miss Rong for me.
I need to talk to her.
I'm so confused with you.
I don't understand.
You're so noisy.
What did you say to me?
How can you know I don't understand?
Longying City's
patient, Zi Yan,
has been gone for a long time.
I know she's Miss Rong's aunt.
So I came to report to you.
Why do you treat her like a donkey?
Make it clear.
What's wrong with Zi Yan?
Miss Rong, you're finally here.
What's wrong with my aunt?
Tell me.
You're anxious?
Untie me first.
I...
I didn't tie your mouth.
I won't say it.
Untie me.
You should know better than me
about Zi Yan's condition.
Why did you hear the news
and take this?
I thought she was fine.
I...
I shouldn't let Zi Yan continue to practice poison.
Rong Jing Fang
didn't take care of her and protect her.
If I knew it,
I shouldn't have let her go
and handed Zi Yan to her.
Master, don't worry.
Although no one in Longying City can cure her,
it doesn't mean no one in the world can cure her.
You're right.
No one in Longying City can cure her.
But I, Bai,
will go back to Longying City right away.
If I still do nothing,
I'll show my face
and beg my master to go out.
I must cure Zi Yan.
I'll take her away from Longying City.
You're going back to Longying City now?
I'm afraid it's easy to go into the city and hard to go out.
Master.
My aunt is seriously ill.
I'm also anxious.
But we can't mess up the situation now.
We have to think of a solution.
You...
Master.
It's been a long time.
Mr. Nalan looks
much better than before.
I advise you
to be more cautious.
You should know
that you'll lose more words if you speak out.
Anyway,
I've sent you the message.
You can do the rest
as you like.
Miss Rong,
I have something to tell you alone.
Just tell me what you want to say.
Why are you so sneaky?
This is our own business.
You're an outsider.
It's none of your business.
Xue Meng.
When did Hua'er become your member?
I'm not the one.
Now I work with Xue Meng.
I'll share the news in the future.
I'll go.
It's quiet enough.
No one will bother us.
What else do you want to tell me?
Why is Nalan Yue here?
When did you two meet?
Xue Meng's people
knew that Yue was still alive.
I was afraid that I would offend Mohuan
and complained to my father.
I didn't say anything.
Don't panic, Miss Li.
I didn't mean to hurt you and Xue Meng.
What else do you want to tell me?
Mei Ying has the news.
She's staying in the town
and wandering around Mei's mansion.
I think she's made up her mind
to find the person who bought her house.
Then take this opportunity
to teach her a lesson.
Master.
I've made up my mind
to go back to Longyin City to save Zi Yan.
Please allow me.
Master, don't worry.
I've made up my mind
to protect you.
Your Natural gift
has been visited by Princess.
It's important
I love you with all my heart.
I can do anything for you.
I will be with you forever.
I love you with all my heart.