What?
We are far apart
A moment of flowers, a moment of spring
I never leave you
You don't understand
How much love I have
I look at the flowers with my eyes
One Sequence
Havoc
I am in error
Promise are my pen
I will devote myself
Hope, underthe Consumerял
Can be a gentle sun
A Thousand calor kilometers
Episode自由
Cast Ruanriosha,
Zhuo Xuanyuan.
Is your USA
I didn't even have a chance to say goodbye.
At that time,
when you made the choice,
I really didn't know what to do.
If Lingxu Valley and Longyin City are to be fought,
I'd rather be the one
who is destined to be sacrificed.
I'm sorry.
Today,
the immortal is finally safe.
When things are settled,
I'll go find a tombstone
and go back to the cave to make an offering to the immortal.
From now on,
it will be the anniversary of the immortal.
I will also come often
to worship the immortal.
Mother,
I made a mistake.
You're considerate.
I don't know where I'll go after a hundred years.
Your father's tomb is in the north.
If Lingxu Pavilion can be in your hands
and can spread the light in the world,
I can go to the Netherworld
and meet your father.
Mother, why are you saying this all of a sudden?
You will live a long life.
You have to be with me.
Watch your grandson grow up.
Watch your great-grandson grow up.
Watch your great-great-grandson grow up.
Watch your grandfather grow up.
Yes!
Yuer.
Mother, did something happen?
No.
I just want to tell you that if you are not here one day,
you just need to remember my kindness,
remember our love,
don't feel guilty or sad.
Because you are the most important light in my life.
Mother, what are you talking about?
I will never let anything happen to you.
I will protect you all the time.
Your father told me the same thing.
It's been a few days,
but there is still no news from the young lady.
The people of Longyin City have not stopped searching.
The same has not been obtained.
It's just that we can't communicate here.
I'm afraid we can't wait for the young lady to come back.
In the past,
Lingxu Pavilion has always been behind me.
No matter what I did,
my mother would forgive me.
But now,
Lingxu Pavilion is gone.
I can't go back to the past.
Maybe at this time,
there is no news of Hua'er.
It's good news.
But it's good news.
Although Rong Jingfeng took away the power of Longyin City,
with his surname,
it won't be so easy to lose.
He will send people back to investigate.
We can't stay here for long.
We'd better leave as soon as possible.
Don't worry.
The young lady will be fine.
Hua'er,
after all these,
you still have feelings for us
as usual.
If you remember,
will you come back here?
I must bring justice
to everything that happened this time.
I want the whole world
to see and accept the crime of revenge.
Yes.
Since then,
no matter how hard you try,
no one can come back.
If you ask for Buddha's help,
there won't be so many
unfair things in the world.
And no poison that can be used to kill.
Believe or not,
it depends on everyone's heart.
I'm so hard-working.
I just hope that my wish can come true.
I'm sorry.
There are some things
that can be settled
no matter how many wrongs there are.
What will happen in the future?
Who can predict it?
You left Longyin City
for the sake of Nalan Yuan.
Now Lingxu Pavilion is destroyed by Longyin City.
Has your mind changed?
I wanted to give up
the idea of being surrounded by my father
with my own money.
At that moment,
I gave up all the ideas
that I had.
I held the heart of being killed
but you saved me.
I know you will never
forgive Longyin City.
You want to do your best
to seek justice for your people.
Since you saved my life,
I can kill you or kill you.
Whatever you want.
Long Jingfeng, are you willing to do it?
Even if you use the whole Longyin City,
it's not a fault
for the death of Nalan family and Lingxu Pavilion.
Do it.
God arranged me to save you.
Do you know why?
Just because you are
Rong Jingfeng's daughter,
her sin
can't be punished
even if she dies ten times.
As a person of Longyin City,
you are not yet responsible.
You should take back
my debt.
Since I'm alive,
I can't be ruined.
Don't worry.
I will have an explanation
for Longyin City and Lingxu Pavilion.
Go.
Stop.
I can't even eat a bun.
Which family are you from?
Meiyang and I have broken up
our brotherhood.
Why do you have to come here
and force each other?
Meiyang?
You...
You are not from Longyin City?
I'm not.
It's okay.
I thought he sent someone
to chase me back.
Miss,
I heard you say
that you have broken up
your brotherhood
with your sister.
All along,
I thought my brother
was a little competitive.
But I didn't expect
he didn't care about
other people's lives
for his own interests.
I can't accept
or tolerate
such a brother.
It's okay if he doesn't want you.
But, Miss Mei,
it's not easy
to get rid of them
if you don't know martial arts.
How about
we go together?
You follow me.
We can take care of each other.
How do you know my last name?
I know your brother,
Mei Ying.
Who are you?
I am...
I am the apprentice of Na Lanyue,
the master of Rong Hua Girl,
and the owner
of the Lao Zi Hall in Longyin City.
But,
it's all in the past.
I told you just now.
I am not
a member of Longyin City.
You...
You are Senior Bai Weizhi.
That's me.
Why do you
light a lantern every day?
I just hope
he can come back safely.
It's so late.
Why do you light the lantern?
I don't believe it,
but I want to know
how you feel.
I don't believe it,
but I think
the one who wishes to do it
must be a promising person.
Such a one-time help
may be better
than not asking anything.
Yue,
how about
we write a wish again
and put the lantern back in the sky?
What do you think?
It's just a trick
of the person who sells the lantern.
It's just a joke.
What evidence can prove
that he can help people make their wishes come true?
I'll go see what they write.
Is it okay to write something?
Let's go.
When it's dawn,
we still need to find a place to hide.
In the dark,
we can go wherever we want.
If praying is useful,
I'd like to use all my luck
to change to living in peace.
You said you were going to the Snow League in person.
At this critical moment,
the world is in a panic.
It's not peaceful at all.
You're special.
How can you show up so easily?
Besides,
we can't go to the Snow League.
Yue told me
that the real master of the Snow League is Mohua.
Everything related to the Snow League
is controlled by her.
When the Lingxu Pavilion was raided,
the people of the Ling Sect were there.
It seems that
they are not involved.
I suspect
Mohua has saved Yue.
Now she's in the Snow League.
So I have to go there.
If the answer is not what you think,
you'll be more disappointed.
I'm already in the bottom of the valley.
I can't sit and wait.
Every time I hear news,
it's hope for me.
Anyway, I don't understand you anymore.
Since you want to go,
I'll go with you.
You're right.
Although I have many grudges against her,
she's the descendant of the Nalan family.
I can't just let her go.
Even if she's dead,
I have to see it with my own eyes.
You're in a cold state.
Plus, that sword is badly injured.
It takes some time
to recover.
You have to learn to stand up.
From now on,
no one will pity you
and help you
no matter how low you are.
Saving your life
is my greatest kindness.
From now on,
you can only rely on yourself.
I'll go with you.
Have you found
the person you want to see?
Who?
You knew
I had nothing this time.
You agreed to let me go back to Lingxu Pavilion
just to thank you
and agree to your offer.
You're smart.
So what?
You have no choice.
Really?
Then I'll be straight.
I won't accept your offer.
I'll take back everything
Lingxu Pavilion and the Nalan family
suffered from
with my own strength.
Whether it's dignity
or my life,
I'll make Rong Jingfeng kneel down
and apologize to everyone.
As for the Ling Sect,
I will never be part of it.
I will never be involved
with the Ling Sect.
You're not a coward.
You're not filial.
Do you know what you're saying now?
What price you'll pay in the future?
I don't care what price I pay.
As long as it's the thing
I decided to do with Nalan Yue,
no one can change it.
You...
You're so stubborn.
You really went with your mother.
If the people of Luyun City
knew you were still alive,
they wouldn't let you go.
You can't be angry
if you don't go to the Ling Sect.
I don't
have any worries now.
No matter what the purpose of Luyun City is,
I'll follow it to the end.
Ayu,
the situation is already dead.
No matter how you fight,
you can't change the fact.
It's just your persistence.
If you want revenge,
you have to bear with what you can't bear
and take the long-term measures.
Please think twice, Young Master.
The Ling Sect's invitation
is a very important decision.
Your Majesty,
someone is asking to see you.
Who is it?
It's...
Nalan Yue's wife, Rong Hua.
Since everyone is here,
let's invite them in.
Yes.
Ayu.
It seems that this girl is really lucky.
She's still alive after seeing her.
She can still avoid
the chase of Long Yun City for days.
She's really unlucky.
Ayu.
Master, the Zhihua Pearl in her body
has returned to life.
Now only you can save her.
Please help us.
That day,
Master Ming promised his wife
and saved Young Master.
You can't break your promise.
Rong Jingfeng only knows
that the Zhihua Pearl can bring people back to life.
But he doesn't know
that her real purpose is more important.
After three lives and three deaths,
the Zhihua Pearl is completely different from the ordinary one.
Only those who use it
can use the Xuanbing Talisman
to remove the poison of self-reflection.
Otherwise,
you will die in the night
without any mercy.
No way.
You think the Nalan family was chased and killed,
and Lingxu Pavilion was destroyed.
That's your end.
That's before you met the Zhihua Pearl.
It's still far away.
That's your end.
You forced my mother
to sacrifice for me
just to make me like this?
That's right.
Since I came back to the Jianghu,
I've been keeping her life
since I found her.
What I really want
is not only the Zhihua Pearl,
but you,
Nalan Yu.
Nalan Yu?
I wonder if the Snow League has the information I want.
Miss Rong should know the rules of the Snow League.
If you want to know the information,
you have to pay a corresponding price.
The Snow League never does business with losses.
I understand the rules of the Snow League.
As long as you can give me the answer I want,
I will pay you the corresponding price.
Come with me.
For so many years,
I've never stopped looking for information about Mohuan.
But I still didn't get anything.
I didn't expect
she would hide here.
Revenge is not a matter of one move.
Don't be impulsive.
Let's go.
You knew all this, didn't you?
I...I didn't know.
I didn't know it would turn out like this.
You were unconscious.
This is the only way to save your life.
It's okay.
Why?
Why did you save me?
I naturally have my own plans.
Your Majesty,
Ruohua wants to see you.
Open the door.
I want to ask you
about the Snow League.
Do you know where the people of Lingxu Pavilion are?
It seems that someone saved you that night.
God made me live.
He must have his own plan.
That day,
I saw the people of the Ling Sect were there.
I don't know.
That day,
we went to Lingxu Pavilion,
but it was still too late.
Too late?
The Meis were destroyed.
The people sent by the Snow League
were detained by Longyin City.
So the news of Longyin City
was not reported in time.
Lingxu Pavilion was also not informed.
All this
is due to your father,
Rong Jingfeng.
If you can have the same
evil thoughts as me,
I'm afraid you can help Lingxu Pavilion
to avoid the disaster.
You are worried about the people of the Jianghu,
knowing that the Chihua Bead was destroyed,
and it would be difficult for Longyin City.
So you hurried back to save it,
and you brought your beloved one.
But do you know
that your father, Rong Jingfeng,
wanted to kill his own sister
and his clanmen,
and set a trap
to scare the world?
I ask you,
if Rong Jingfeng were here,
would you help
Lingxu Pavilion
to get justice?
You don't dare?
Right?
Then what qualifications do you have
to ask about the lives of the people of Lingxu Pavilion?
I will definitely
confess to Longyin City
for Lingxu Pavilion's death.
I have my own way.
The most important thing now
is to get justice.
I will do it.
The most important thing now
is to find the whereabouts of others
in Lingxu Pavilion.
Everyone in Lingxu Pavilion
died in the way of the day.
Your father, Rong Jingfeng,
set up a heavy ambush
at every exit.
Do you think anyone can escape?
Then the last fire
destroyed everything in Lingxu Pavilion.
Even the body was burned to ashes.
Do you think
the people you are looking for
still have hope to live on?
No matter what,
I have to hold on until the end.
As long as you know
about any news about Lingxu Pavilion,
tell me.
I will pay
whatever you want.
Rong Jingfeng once said
whether you are alive or dead,
he will find you
and take you back to Longyin City
to be punished.
Now your whereabouts have been exposed.
Aren't you afraid that the Snow League
will sell your news to Longyin City?
After all, the price he gave
is much higher
than yours.
That's good.
If the people of Lingxu Pavilion
know that I am still alive,
they will come to Longyin City
and take me back.
I'm sorry to bother you today.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Your Highness,
the snow leaves of Longyin City
have been brought back by the peonies.
Now they are in the Snow League.
If you want to leave now,
I will take you back
to Longyin City.
I wonder
if we need
the people of the Snow League to protect us.
People of Longyin City are everywhere.
How long can I hide?
If I can't even get out of this door today,
how can I still stand in the underworld?
Yu.
Have you ever thought
what you can change when you go out?
Everything you want
can only be achieved
after you have been through it.
Isn't it what you want
when he is alive?
Yu.
You can't leave me.
I will take you back
to Longyin City.
Yu.
I'm sorry for what I did this time.
Please forgive me.
Stop talking nonsense.
But I...
Go away.
Welcome you.
I'm sorry.
Miss Liuli.
I think
we should apologize to the chief
for Longyin City.
Don't be so rude.
I said I don't welcome you.
Just go.
But I think...
Miss Liuli.
You have been missing these days.
It's different.
You just let them go.
Now you only apologize
after you send them back.
Is Longyin City
going to
let Xue go so easily?
So I have to apologize
and explain the reason.
Miss Long.
Thank you for covering for me.
It was really too late.
Then we should go.
Let's go, Jingyuan.
So you are not
always on guard.
I didn't expect
that you would be
in our team.
What's going on?
Where are they?
Don't worry, Chief.
They have left safely.
They didn't show any flaws.
I think
they are not in the same team.
They are not.
They have left safely.
They didn't show any flaws.
But Xuanye Island is here.
I'm afraid Longyin City
will be
on our side.
Bai Weizhi has been out for so long.
We can't even
find him.
What?
Did you
become a
white-shirt?
You don't even know
what to do.
Chief Bai always
knows about
Longyin City's
hidden secrets.
It's hard to find
his whereabouts.
But I heard
that Chief Bai has a master.
He was a master
who taught him
the martial arts.
If he insists
on finding him,
he may
use this master.
You are so
open-minded.
Don't you know
that this old master
of Bai Weizhi
is a martial arts expert
who was in the same team
with Mo Huan.
You can't even
defeat him
with your little help.
Since we have to
go back,
Longyin City
will have to
use some unusual methods.
You are still talking back.
Chief Bai,
don't worry too much.
Bai
is just out
to relax.
When he's out of anger,
he'll be back.
We can't
push him too hard.
Otherwise,
he will do
something more out of line.
You guys...
Chief.
If you guys
are so soft-hearted,
how can you
help Longyin City and Chief?
As the leader of the Hall of Life,
I can't just sit around and do nothing.
Chief,
why don't you
let the Hall of Life handle this?
The Hall of Life
won't let you down.
You haven't
found your sister yet.
Don't be in a hurry
to do something else.
Enough.
Stop arguing.
This matter
should be handled by the Hall of Life.
But you have to remember
that this is an internal matter
of Longyin City.
Don't let it go unnoticed.
Yes.
Don't worry, Chief Mei.
If there's a chance,
the Hall of Life will
bring your sister back.
Here.
All the way here,
I didn't see Mei Ying
send someone to find you.
She can even
give up the whole Mei family.
I'm not that important
to her.
Only power and status
are what she can't give up.
Here's the food.
Two guests.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you.
Two taels in total.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm a quick-witted person.
I don't have any money on me.
All the way here,
I spent all the money
of Senior Bai.
Don't think like that.
You're a weak girl.
How much money can you spend on me?
The point is,
I'm used to
spending money on you.
I didn't save
much money on the way.
Eat.
Do you know?
I heard that
there's a man
living on the Black Stone Mountain
five or six miles from here.
He's good at martial arts,
but he got
a incurable
small problem.
Now,
he's looking for
a master
to help him.
I know that.
I know that, too.
It's said that if he can
cure his illness,
it'll be a lot of trouble.
I heard that Senior Bai
is good at medical skills.
Why don't we
go to the Black Stone Mountain
and try it?
Not only can we cure people's disease,
we can also make some money.
I can see that.
Walking around the world
is not about
martial arts skills.
It's about money.
Money.
You're right.
I've found out
that the man
who lives in the Black Stone Mountain
is helping
the man who's on the side.
However,
I heard that many people
who came to the Black Stone Mountain
without any merit
were even more kind
because of that
weird-tempered man
who scolded him for a long time.
Miss Rong Hua,
after leaving the Snow League,
I asked you what you were going to do.
But you asked Xiao Feng
to come to the Black Stone Mountain
to ask a master called Bai Su.
You even asked him
if he was a playboy.
Why is that?
I heard from Master that
Senior Bai
is the only master
who can be compared with Mo Huan.
Although I don't know
why Master
was kicked out of the sect,
Senior Bai is my master.
He's also a bit distant from me.
You want to use this Bai Su
to help you
to stand firm in the martial arts world?
Senior Bai has a lot of master.
He's a famous senior
in the martial arts world.
How sure are you
that he will come to the mountain?
Before I met him,
I didn't know
how sure I was.
But this time,
we must go to the mountain
to do our best.
When the Linxu Pavilion was attacked,
the spiritual cult was there.
They must know
where the people of the Linxu Pavilion
who survived are.
But I joined the Snow League.
The people of the Snow League
didn't put me in the dark.
I must stand firm in the martial arts world
to be able to
talk to them.
I must stand firm in the martial arts world
to be able to talk to them.
This time,
we don't want to reveal
our identities.
When I've cured
Senior Bai's playboy,
I'll make a plan.
Yes.
According to the news
of the Snow League,
Hua'er
must have come to the mountain
to find the spiritual cult.
The spiritual cult
is the place
where the people of the Linxu Pavilion
who survived the attack
came to the mountain.
The spiritual cult
he must have come to this Black Stone Mountain.
You still can't rest assured about him?
As long as Hua'er is with me,
I can go to the North Desert without any worries.
I don't know
when I can see him again.
After I practiced the Black Ice Talisman,
I don't know if I'm a man or a ghost.
Young Master.
Senior Bai,
I've asked around.
This master
is arrogant and hard to get along with.
The doctors haven't taken care of him.
He might get angry
because he doesn't know what to say.
He'll be driven out of the house.
It must be hard to cure him.
In my opinion,
this master's little plaything
is probably caused by his bad temper
and his constant anger.
You know what?
When he gets angry,
he'll only get worse
and you'll live a long life.
You're right. Let's go.
Little girl, let me do it.
I'm Bai Weizhi.
I heard that you're a great man.
So I came here
to learn from you
and share your worries.
Master.
Little girl,
you're säul of a bright mind.
Why is it that you knows everything about you?
You don't know
only Bai Su.
Everyone hasta
aneny of his round-about skills.
He't dare regard his name
and how could he
make
I was just a little greedy when I was a kid.
I was kicked out of the school.
Who would have thought that after so many years,
I'd still be so rude to me after we met.
I...
Greedy?
Senior Bai,
you were kicked out of the school because of this?
Don't mention it.
Let's go back to the past.
Let's not mention it.
But now it seems that
we want to make some money.
I'm afraid we're going to be left out.
But Senior Bai,
you can take this opportunity
to repair the relationship between you and Bai Su.
How can I repair it?
I've never been convinced of Rong Jingfeng.
Back then,
Master and Mohuan were well-known.
So after Rong Jingfeng was defeated by Mohuan,
I naturally didn't accept it.
I was so embarrassed
and was defeated by Master Bai Su.
If Rong Jingfeng betrays the spiritual cult,
and I'm kicked out of the school,
I...
I'd just come to Longyin City with him.
But Master broke off the relationship.
Senior Bai,
how did you get into the school?
Why don't you try the same method this time?
I didn't know what's wrong with my back when I was a kid.
Now I...
Let's think of another way.
The mountains are
Pi's hometown I went to
My heart has lost
You're gone
Mhm
I'm afraid that I can't protect you.