a pure white mud
brings good luck to the world.
I
嘛
you
and I
Episode 16
I've made up my mind
to go back to Longyin City to save Zi Yan.
Please help me, Master.
Master,
don't worry.
I've done everything properly
to protect Master.
According to your description,
I'm afraid that person has returned to heaven.
In that case,
you can't go back to send him off.
It's not a good idea.
Zi Yan will be fine.
Even if it's you,
you can't say that.
Master.
Master,
even if it's like what you said,
I'll try my best with Master.
After all,
Zi Yan is my family.
He's also the one
I care about the most.
I'm fine
because you guys
are so shameless.
You've made me
suffer from the same problem.
What concern?
What hatred?
It's just unbearable.
Drive them out.
Master.
I've said it before.
Bai Su won't help us.
Even if Master Bai doesn't help us,
Master and I
will try our best to save Xiao Yi.
What's wrong?
Maybe you forgot
that the Lingxu Pavilion was destroyed
and Zi Yan did something.
Yue,
I've never forgotten
the revenge of the Lingxu Pavilion.
I'll never forget it.
The design of the Snow Dome
was also to cut off
the people in the Jianghu City.
When the time comes,
I'll take back the title of City Leader of Longyin City
and tell the world
to give the Lingxu Pavilion a clean break.
But I don't want to see
the people of the two tribes
keep fighting like this.
Anyway,
please let my father
and my sister go.
They are all my close friends.
Did Rong Jingfeng
give us
half of the life you asked for?
Mei Ying is still wandering in the town.
As her position in Longyin City,
you can take advantage of it.
This is also part of my plan.
It seems that we have thought of it together.
Let's go.
Master,
I'll go first.
I was too harsh
and hit you.
After I finish this,
I'll come back
and kowtow to you.
Please let me go.
I'm sorry Huzäh Luuplu opponent,
I shouldn't have Small
I think
Take it.
I taken it when I went out will be
left here on purpose.
Is...
Is it really truerade doll
from The Cry of theẹTmin Everyday?
I was still untrained
even in the history flow.
I said I could not bear the trauma😥
Are we being treated
Master, she's so kind.
She won't die.
Whether she can be saved or not
depends on her own fate.
But Master and my brothers
have made up their minds.
But there's one thing
I want to talk to you about.
What is it?
Just say it.
Zhiyuan has found out
that Nalan Yuezi was killed by Lingxu Pavilion
and has been hiding in the spiritual school.
Lingxu Pavilion
followed Mohan to the north.
He's been hiding for so long.
Why did he suddenly appear?
It's really suspicious.
But...
Nalan Yuezi and Mohan
have been in a relationship for a long time.
It's impossible.
We outsiders
don't know about the internal affairs of the spiritual school.
But you know that
Zhiyuan's news
will never be wrong.
We just want to
remind you and Rong Hua
to be careful
and pay attention to this news.
People's hearts are changing.
Sometimes people can't do anything
to get revenge.
Nalan Yuezi and Mohan
are not impossible.
Go here.
clothes.
I don't know what's happening to this Mei Ying.
I went to watch.
I'm afraid that we need to find out
who's behind Mei's house.
I didn't expect that our Hall Leader Mei
would be so weak.
Miss Xiao,
what should we do
in the next round?
No hurry.
Just wait and see.
After the mantis is hunting the cicada,
I don't just want to see
Mei Ying's fox tail.
I also want to know
who's behind Mei's house.
What should I...
Do I let so much trouble
affect Mei and the embrace?
I wonder
who you are
I dare not reveal my identity.
Mr. Mei, please.
Please.
I wonder
where the master is.
You're playing tricks on me.
You're pretending to be a ghost.
I never regret what I did.
If it was an old friend of yours who came to kill me,
then you'd better die now.
Zhi...
Zhi Hua Zhu.
It's just a spirit incense.
It's really good for him.
Let him live first.
He'll find a place to live in the future.
Young Master, Young Madam.
Long Yin City is sick and dead.
Xiao Xiao came alone.
She's outside the gate.
Should I drive her away?
No need.
I'm waiting for Xiao Xiao.
Young Master, this is a good opportunity.
If Zi Yan dies,
Long Yin City will definitely make a mistake.
I've said it.
I won't let anyone in Long Yin City go.
But I promise you,
I'll do it.
Master, please follow Young Master's order.
Take Rong Su and go to Long Yin City.
Okay.
I'll meet them tomorrow.
Young Master.
Are you different from the others?
You're not different.
Young Master, you did well.
I've improved so much,
I should be trolling the elaehearted people.
But...
who will also be this big?
That's right.
Everyone is good.
Don't worry about being a mess.
However,
Don't tell Big Sis hyus will go down to Chen آ works.
I've lost a lot of weight.
Second Young Mistress.
Why are you in the Mei's Mansion?
I know you'll follow Mei Ying
to the Mei's Mansion to find out the truth.
So I'm waiting for you here.
I'm here to tell you
about the rescue of the aunt.
I'll do everything for you.
But where is Mei Ying now?
She's fine.
I just took care of her.
Mei Ying.
Second Young Mistress is so honest.
We've been watching her
from head to toe.
We're not afraid of anything
since you're back.
fs
What are you thinking?
Dialogue
Yepşallah
You have something to tell me?
How do you feel?
What do you mean?
I'm充 Cohen.
I'm afraid I'm afraid
we can't go back to before when I tell you.
I told you before.
I'll tell you the truth.
Therefore,
you can ask us anything you want.
We met
The Immortal Lanterns were punished by the Meiyin Sect.
If I'm not wrong,
that person is you.
Last time I went to the Snowy Alliance
to find out about you.
You were there too.
You watched me come
and watch me go.
Yes.
You knew it all?
Yes, I didn't know that.
I didn't know that.
But as I think about it,
I realized it's not about that I knew it.
Then I heard you talking about it again.
I always wanted to ask you a question.
Where have you been these days?
Why did you avoid me?
I thought about thousands of possibilities.
But I didn't expect
it would be a dream.
I know you have your own difficulties.
I just want to face them
and share them with you.
OK.
I'll tell you the truth today.
How did I
survive?
I had a jade bead in my body.
It belonged to my mother.
My mother
gave me the jade bead
from her body.
My mother risked her life
to use her life
to pay for my life.
This jade bead has been through three lives.
It has a stronger ability to react.
If I can't think of a way to cure it,
I can only die.
So now
I can only rely on Mohuan
to live.
That's the only way
to see you.
How could Mohuan save you so kind?
There must be something wrong.
I know.
But I can only live
to avenge my mother
and Lingxu.
I can find a way to help you
to live without the jade bead.
Hua.
You grew up in Longyin City.
You know the power of jade bead.
Impossible.
Even if I can't,
I still have my master and grandmaster.
There are so many famous doctors in the world.
I can't trust you.
Even if I have to sacrifice my life,
I'm willing to.
If you sacrifice your life,
what's the point of me living?
When I was in Beihong kid,
I kept running
thinking of you
and missing you
every time
when I got healed.
I could only
survive until today
because I kept thinking
about you.
That's why I can
be like this.
This hairpin
is my mother's legacy.
When the spring
Is the thing that always Leave me
I used to want to
give him to me
As our love
Day ?
After that
I will go with you
with every ship
I'll walk with you.
Hua.
You've already known
that the Chihua Bead in my body
is not an ordinary Chihua Bead.
If I can't control it anymore,
I'll be the one
who hurts the innocent in the whole world.
I hope
you can kill me yourself.
Do you know what you're talking about?
Hua.
For the sake of the world,
for the sake of the whole world,
you have to do this.
And you
are the only one
who is willing to die in the Seven Swords.
Nan Lanyue.
You're so naive.
If I kill you,
how can I live?
Have you ever thought about how I feel?
I'll answer you now.
Listen to me.
The snow is falling.
The people are already walking.
I can't do it.
In the world,
I'm willing to be a coward.
I can't do it.
Even if I have it,
how can I ask for it?
I'm not persistent.
What if I'm left behind?
If you don't believe me,
just country.
I'm leaving.
I swear now.
And
would it bespace?
The promise of gone,
is the borderline.
This is the way to Longyin City.
What do you want to do?
Do you think
it's a dream to attack Longyin City
with these people?
The
Nalan Yue.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Okay.
Let's go to Longyin City.
Hurry up.
Go.
Don't fall.
Hurry up.
Excuse me.
What happened here?
Why are you in such a hurry?
The spirit-chilling demons are here.
They've surrounded Longyin City.
The roads in the town are blocked.
Everyone is busy running away.
Run away?
Hurry up.
They're running away.
What about Zi Yan?
He's smart.
Don't worry.
Hurry up.
Yue.
You're the one who's trapped Longyin City, aren't you?
You should know it very well.
I won't let Longyin City go.
You're trapped Longyin City
while Yi is ill.
I heard that you have Sister.
You really hid a lot from me.
Hua.
I don't need you to make it difficult for me.
You just stay in the Teng Feng Town.
I promised you about Zi Yan.
I'll do my best.
I won't break my promise.
Okay.
I believe you.
City Leader.
You've been worried and worried these days.
You haven't been resting for a day or two.
You'd better go back and rest for a few hours.
City Leader.
Now Longyin City is trapped.
People are in a panic.
At this critical moment,
you must not fall.
City Leader.
You must not fall.
City Leader,
I have sinned.
I'm willing to die to atone for my sin.
To atone for sin?
What do you mean?
Tell about it to me.
Bai Tang.
Bai Wei Zhi
and asked Master to go to the place
where the White-Haired Guards are.
But the condition is that
the people of Longyin City
can only be sent out of the city.
Master will be sent
to the Sky Peak
by himself.
So you are the mole in Longyin City.
No wonder Nalan Yuan knows
all our whereabouts.
City Leader,
although I was wrong,
I did everything for Master.
As for other news in Longyin City,
I didn't leak it out.
Please take a look, City Leader.
How many things are you hiding from me?
Tell me everything.
City Leader,
Second Miss
is still in the mortal world.
It's her idea to save Master.
But...
Look.
Look at my good daughter.
She must have colluded with Nalan Yue
to trick me to go out of the city, right?
No, no.
Second Miss will never do that.
Nalan Yue is forcing me.
If I refuse her to go out of the city,
it's like giving up
the last body of Zi Yan.
But if I go out of the city,
thousands of people will be waiting for me.
In the end,
they will not save Zi Yan.
City Leader,
you don't have to risk it yourself.
I'm willing to escort Master out of the city.
Besides,
Second Miss and Master Bai
will never use Master's life to...
Shut up!
Bai Wenchi is no longer the Master.
Rong Hua,
I'll pretend that I've never had a daughter!
City Leader, calm down.
The most important thing now
is Master Zi Yan's life.
How about this?
I'll escort Master Zi Yan out of the city.
What do you think?
No matter what,
I'm an outsider.
Even if I fall into a trap,
I'll die in the hands of Nalan Yue.
It's not a big deal for Longyin City.
Besides,
I can share your burden.
You can also concentrate on your mind
and figure out a way to defeat Nalan Yue.
You...
escort Zi Yan out of the city.
City Leader.
Yes.
Zi Yan.
Hide.
Master,
Xiao Yi is badly impregnable.
His Green Needles have been entrenched into blood.
How about
we consider another way?
Zi Yan has beenity ill
for years.
Although she has been practicing for a while,
she will still suffer a lot.
Judging from her current condition,
I don't know if she can handle it.
There is no way to test her now.
The medicine the Grand Master gave,
let's give it a try.
That's fine.
But I want to use my inner strength
to help her put the medicine into her heart.
This can help her
swallow the pain of being pregnant.
I'll stay here.
Master, please give me some time to get better.
Hang night
Pour the medicine prepared
Gradually
Lip doctors
Don't get pregnant!
Mother.
If you have a will,
Please keep me safe.
Episode 15
Rong Hua and Bai Wei Zhi
are going to fight together this time.
I wonder if Zi Yan has a chance to survive.
Mei Ying.
If Young Master didn't order me,
I would have cut you into pieces.
Can you save my aunt's life?
I've always been a good man.
I never take my family and friends seriously.
You should take care of yourself first.
Do you care about others' lives?
My mother passed away when I was very young.
In this world,
only my aunt has taken care of me.
It's the first time she made me feel
the happiness of being cared for.
My aunt has been practicing in Longyin City.
But she rarely has a warm heart.
She is still worried.
I just want to see her.
Maybe this is the last time.
I...
Miss Rong is not a person of a heart.
I thought you didn't know the fate of your family.
There were people who were not so good to me.
But you sent me to the dead end.
Now there is only a handful of soil left.
If I want to see her,
who can give me this chance?
I'm willing to use my leg
to exchange for the chance to see my aunt.
I've never begged anyone in my life.
But this time, I beg you.
You...
You're just worried that I'll run away.
I'm willing to use my leg to exchange for the chance.
How can I run away?
Okay.
Do you remember
the first game I played with you?
You didn't get the chance to win.
You even wanted to win by winning.
But you lost in the end.
You want to be filial today.
I'll give you a chance.
Let's play another round according to the game.
If you can beat me,
I'll consider letting you see your aunt.
What do you think?
I don't want to fight with you.
What?
You don't want to see your aunt again?
You're right.
Not all the battles
can be won by losing.
I don't want to bet on my aunt.
This time,
I want your answer.
The sound doesn't look like a human heart.
I remember when Meng Hua was training in the Black-Haired Army,
the sound was like that.
It sounded like a ghost.
Could it be...
Watch him.
Yes.
Lei Ying, stop.
Fang Qi.
Keep an eye on the house.
Don't let him escape.
We need someone to protect us.
I'll be on the other side.
What about Brother Nalan?
Where did he go?
Don't worry, Miss Mei.
The Young Master has the Great Grandson.
He'll be fine.
Will he be okay?
He looked so scared.
I couldn't stop him.
I'm afraid
the poison of the Chihua Bead
is out of control.
If he goes out like this,
it'll only harm him and Jin.
I'll let you go.
I hope nothing bad happens.
Did he send out the sound of the inn?
Brother Nalan can be guarded by Brother Lu.
He'll be fine.
It's better for you to stay here.
The situation is critical.
Mr. Zi Yan hasn't woken up yet.
The people who are in Longyin City
are not suitable to act without permission.
You don't have to say that.
I've already known his situation.
You were alone in the room just now.
You were in Mr. Zi Yan's room just now.
I thought...
I thought Brother Nalan could control the poison of the Chihua Bead.
So I didn't tell you in time.
Who knew?
Don't do this again.
Cang Qi, stay here.
Xiao Wei is in danger now.
Nothing can go wrong.
I'll go find Yue.
Yes.
An.
It's really you.
Zi Yan.
You're awake.
Hua.
Where is Hua?
Don't worry.
Hua is safe and sound.
He was guarding you in bed.
He'll be back soon.
Who is it?
Senior, it's me.
Mei Xue Man.
Senior Bai.
Please stop Rong Hua.
He...
He was afraid that Brother Nalan would be in danger.
So he went alone.
But the people around him are from Longyin City.
I was afraid that he would be in danger.
Go.
You must protect Hua.
But you...
I don't mind.
I'll wait for you to come back.
I want to see him one last time.
I won't let you say that.
You'll be fine.
He is...
This is the second daughter of the Mei family.
Mei Ying's sister.
But she is different from Mei Ying.
Bai.
I'm afraid I can't hold on for long.
Siyin.
Don't be afraid.
I...
Don't comfort me.
I know my health
the best.
All my life,
I've dedicated myself to Longyin City.
If I could start over,
I wouldn't regret my choice.
I've been seeing you
lately.
I've no regrets
until Hua is safe.
Now Longyin City
is in danger.
There is no one
to trust
by your side.
Bai.
Promise me
to protect Longyin City
and take care of City Chief.
She is so cruel.
You don't have to worry about her.
Hua and Su
will be fine.
Longyin City and City Chief
need your protection.
If you don't promise me,
I can't rest in peace.
If you feel helpless,
I promise you.
I promise you everything.
Don't talk now.
Just lie down and rest.
I won't let anything happen to you.
No need.
Hua has suffered
a lot this time.
I'm sorry
for what happened to Li Xun Pavilion.
How could Hua blame you?
Don't think too much.
Where is she?
I want to see her.
Okay.
I'll go find her now.
Stay here.
Don't worry, Zi Yan.
Before Senior Bai and Rong Hua come back,
I will be by your side
and always be with you.
I will always be by your side.
Senior, have a good rest.
I'll wait outside.
yim
kilometres
You must
endure the incredible fate.
The moon is bright
I can't win the years of years
I want to sing and dance
Sing and dance
The water is empty
A night of love, you are in my heart
There is always enough love
The moon has a grudge against the wind
If love is not a dream, a smile, and a promise
A night of love, you are in my heart
I will keep it after years
I don't care about the day and night
I will stay with you
The Moon is Bright