Lost the case.
The King Of Blaze
Episode 16
We all know
you're always worried about Mohuan.
After you find the person of Snow's dream,
you'll know where Mohuan is.
Master has always had a habit.
As long as he is a very precious object,
it must be in the visible place.
It must be in the visible place.
You'd better go back
and look for the new method.
Since we took over the spiritual sedan chair,
there has been no news from Mohuan.
And our news has been cut off.
I'm afraid that the news of Wang's family
has been cut off by the Xiao Xue Alliance.
But if we do this,
won't he lose himself?
Yes.
Mohuan would rather kill himself
than cut off our news.
Master.
If I hadn't lost my family,
I wouldn't have left
the Baisu River
and left the forest in advance.
Then Lan Yu
wouldn't have killed you.
That's right.
Before Lin Ruohan died,
he asked you to protect Na Lanyue.
And you saved her
in Lingxu Pavilion.
It shows that you two
are really close.
I dare not.
I'm incompetent and I can't protect the spiritual sedan chair.
Please punish me.
Master.
After Na Lanyue took over the spiritual sedan chair,
he was imprisoned for a while.
He was released from the spiritual sedan chair not long ago.
Fine.
Do you know
what is the meaning of the word,
the cause and the effect?
I'm sorry for my foolishness.
I didn't understand what you said.
I underestimated Na Lanyue.
I didn't expect that she was so uncontrolled.
She didn't care about her life
just to take over the spiritual sedan chair.
But it was because of her
that I had a new plan.
A new plan?
I once entrusted all the hopes
of the Nalan family to Na Lanyue.
But she never
agreed with me.
I can only rely on myself.
Longyin City is without Rong Jingfeng.
I can still be powerful
and survive.
Rong Jingfeng is going to the North Desert soon.
You guys go prepare
as I told you.
Yes.
What does Master mean?
He means
to take down Longyin City
and fight against the Nalan family
in the North Desert
with the power of the Central Plains.
It's you.
I've met the City Leader.
No.
You're not the City Leader anymore.
Your daughter kicked you out
and took your place.
What do you want to say?
I saved you from the dark house
and escaped from Longyin City.
Shouldn't you thank me?
Look at your tone.
You're so arrogant.
Even if I die in Longyin City,
I don't want you
to save me.
Do you think I'll be like you?
A rat in the trap.
A man in the trap.
Do you think
I hid all day long just to get you?
You forced me to die.
Now, I can't
show mercy to you.
Greetings, Master.
You may leave.
Yes.
You've spent a lot of time
for Longyin City.
What do you want?
I've been thinking about
torturing you
and making you
die in front of me.
I've been thinking about
torturing you
and destroying Longyin City.
But today,
I'll let you
do as you want.
I've decided
to leave Longyin City
to myself.
Your efforts
are mine.
Only in this way
can I get the pain.
Don't think that
I dare not
do anything to you.
Now, in the north,
except for Lingjiao,
there's no safe place.
But there's already
a Nalan family's camp.
If you go back like this,
will they take you?
Do you think that
Nalan Yue and Rong Hua
will turn against you?
I really want to
witness this good show.
No!
You've been on the road
and you've been thinking about
so many things.
The disciples didn't see your food.
How can it be like this?
The only thing that Ziyan
asked me to do before he died
was not to make it.
I'm afraid that I won't be able to
see him in the underground.
I...
I'm afraid that Ziyan will be sad.
Why did I tell you this?
You eat your food.
Why do you care about me?
Master Bai, someone just sent a letter to me.
You finally contacted your senior.
Let's go.
Come on.
Put it here.
Let's go.
Do you think that
we can't track him
after changing the makeup?
I didn't expect that Bai Su
was so famous
and ruined in your hands.
Please calm down.
I'm also looking for
Rong Jingfeng's whereabouts.
I'm going to bring him back to the prison.
You should obey
the promise of the various sects
of Longyin City.
You lied to everyone
that you imprisoned Rong Jingfeng
in Longyin City until he died.
But now,
you said that
because you just want to give him
a chance to escape.
I heard that Rong Su
has already gone to the north to receive him.
Your Longyin City
is really like the Lin Sect.
It's sinister and cunning.
Everyone,
I went to the north
to bring Rong Jingfeng back.
Something came out
suddenly.
There must be something wrong.
I'm afraid that someone is secretly
trying to break the relationship
between the various sects of the Central Plains.
Enough.
You need to make excuses
to cover up for Rong Jingfeng.
Arrest him
and torture him.
You must find out
Rong Jingfeng's whereabouts.
Go.
The new method that the ancestors taught
and the inner power I practiced
can suppress the coldness in my body at the same time.
Now my power has increased a lot.
These days,
you have a good rest.
The effect is obvious.
But remember,
after the internal energy is restored,
you must not relax.
You need to make time to strengthen yourself.
Yes, thank you, Master.
I don't know where Master and the others are.
Master Bai,
no one should be chasing us.
OK, OK, OK.
Senior,
you were just outside the inn.
Why didn't you go inside
and explain to the people in the martial arts world?
This has nothing to do with Master.
It's more about us.
If they knew the reason,
we wouldn't
be so embarrassed.
What do you want me to do?
Whatever we say now,
they don't believe it.
Since I got along with Longyin City,
my original life
has been completely messed up.
Do you know
I finally got to know
your whereabouts this time?
Senior, you have always been
the most well-informed in the martial arts world.
Did something happen?
Little Bear,
while I was selling the information,
they secretly
destroyed my ship
in a sudden.
They tried to cut off my source of information
and even killed half of themselves.
They killed two people.
What about Senior?
Senior's escort team
was involved in the murder case of the government.
All the escort teams
were arrested
in a sudden.
Now Senior
is also
in a bad situation.
He's trying to prove himself.
Then,
did Rong Jingfeng get robbed?
Are they all
in the plan of the people behind the scenes?
It's better to lose the information.
It wasn't easy for me
to find out that Rong Hua
is in the spiritual world now.
Maybe
we should use
the power of Nalan Yue
to catch the criminal in the north.
This...
This is the spiritual world.
I'm afraid it's too difficult for us.
I'll figure out a way to arrange it.
Besides,
I've also found out
where Rong Su is.
Where...
Where is he?
Did you get any news from Rong Jingfeng?
The black soldiers are searching everywhere.
They've found some clues.
But I think
Mo Huan has another plan for him.
So, he didn't take the action.
This Mei Ying
disappeared for a long time
after escaping.
Now she's showing up again.
She's with Mo Huan
and she's caught Rong Jingfeng.
She's really unwavering.
Second Elder,
you shouldn't stay here for too long.
I'll ask Yun Xu
to send you out later.
If you catch Rong Jingfeng,
will you kill him or not?
it depends on the situation.
If you resist, you'll be killed.
Madam,
are you going to...
I'm going to find Yue.
Chief.
Yun Xu,
send Second Elder out first.
Yes.
There's going to be a fierce battle
in the north.
You should stay in the forest.
Don't go anywhere.
I'll go with you.
I heard from Second Uncle that
Master has arrived in the north.
Can I go out with him?
Since the Wang family
can bring the news to the forest,
it means that
even if our Nalan family
takes over here
and guards the enemy's home,
there will still be a gap.
Hua,
listen to me.
Stay here.
It's too complicated outside.
I'm worried that you'll go out alone.
Of course I won't go out alone.
Just send more people to follow me.
Unless I protect them myself,
I won't trust anyone.
You've been through so much.
I'm not as fragile as you think.
Hua,
you just
heard something?
There are no more important people in Longyin City.
But all the sources of information have been cut off.
We don't even know where Mohuan is
and what he's up to.
We have to find your father first.
If Longyin City
really falls into the Meiyin's trap,
I'm afraid that all the sects
in the world
won't give up on us.
I'm afraid that
they won't give up on us.
But we should
do something.
I'm afraid that
they won't give up on us.
Lu Yi Zhou?
Mr. Bai,
Master is asking you to come to the Spirit Cult.
Now Madam Na
and Senior Bai
are in the Spirit Cult.
Good.
Then go and arrange it.
So many things have happened recently.
I'm just going to talk to the master and the maid.
I'll go now.
Now that the Tifeng Town
is in a very bad shape,
I didn't expect Longyin City
to be ruined
so soon.
Rong Su,
she has been born and raised
in Longyin City for so many years.
But what she got
was such a dead city.
Since Master has been
so angry with Rong Jing Feng,
why didn't he
see the end of her
in the north
and then come to Longyin City?
Besides,
the antidote for the Chihua Bead
is in Master's hands.
Go and gather all the disciples
in the Spirit Cult
and listen to my orders at any time.
Yes.
By the way,
are there some people
in the martial arts world
who have come to Longyin City
to ask for advice?
Master is wise.
According to the news,
they will be here soon.
Master.
Girl,
I finally see you.
How are you?
Don't talk nonsense.
How is the situation
outside?
I saw Master.
Why is that guy
not here?
He is not here.
Why is that guy
not here?
Master may have something
to do outside.
Lu Yizhou,
find him for me.
These days,
I have come up with a new way
to control the power
of his body.
As for whether he is willing to do it,
it's up to him.
Yes.
Tell me everything
that happened outside.
I am incompetent.
I didn't guard Longyin City.
I let Mei Ying's trusted aide
take Rong Jingfeng away.
Don't worry, Madam.
Master Ming is always
so confident.
Greetings, Chief.
Almost all the people
in the martial arts world
gathered here.
Where is Rong Jingfeng
that you are watching?
Don't worry.
Rong Jingfeng's whereabouts
are under control.
Master Ming put a lot of medicine
in his diet before.
He has only recovered
some of his strength
today.
Do you guys
send the message
to Rong Su
as Master Ming wants?
Are you trying to remind me
or are you trying to
put a trap in front of me?
Madam, please go ahead.
Keep an eye on Rong Jingfeng's whereabouts.
If you have any news,
please let me know.
Yes.
How about I go and save Rong Jingfeng?
Wait.
You'd better
pay attention to Nalan Yue.
Master Ming didn't punish you
for losing the spiritual sedan chair last time.
If you make any mistake again,
Master Ming will not
forgive you easily.
I...
I understand.
Rong Jingfeng
You hit me?
Go.
The place where the fire
rises from afar
should be
where Rong Jingfeng
is hiding.
But
you must be careful.
Maybe
this is a trap set by Master Ming.
He is waiting for you
to commit suicide.
I'm not going to
let you go.
I'm waiting for you
to commit suicide.
It was Mohuan
who asked Xue Meng
to tell us about this.
But now you are
against us
and remind us to be careful.
What are you going to do?
You are too kind to yourself.
I just
don't want to
hurt Xuanye.
I've been hiding
in the dark for these days.
But I've got a lot of news
in the course of time.
Now
I've figured it out.
Master Ming
took Mei Ying
to Longying City
and brought all the people
of the Jianghu to live here.
He did it
just to see
you two get hurt.
He is a good man.
But no matter what,
I can't just
watch my father
being killed by those people.
Miss Liuli,
please help me.
Go ahead.
I hope Miss Liuli
can find a way to enter the Spirit Sect
and ask Rong Hua for help.
Please help her
when necessary.
I will try to
hold the Spirit Sect back.
I've been keeping
the Spirit Sect
in the dark
during the days in the North.
But if it's really
the time to do it,
I hope she can
escort the rest of the Longying
to leave safely.
At least
I can save my father.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
Na Lanyue
is getting more and more valuable.
He didn't come out
to welcome me personally.
By the way,
did he bully you?
If he wants you to suffer,
you must tell me.
I'll teach him a lesson.
Don't worry, Master.
I'm fine here.
That's good.
Madam.
I'm here to see you.
How can you let the people of Longying City
enter the important place of the Nalan family?
Luo Yizhou brought me in personally.
It's none of your business.
He is my master.
A Yue and I know him.
Madam.
It was the chief of the clan
who buried the whole Spirit Pavilion
because you were soft-hearted.
How can you let the Nalan family
repeat the same mistake
because you were soft-hearted?
It's dangerous to be killed again.
What about us?
How can we be killed?
How dare you!
You just need to do
what the chief told you.
You don't need to ask
about the rest.
Although the chief is kind to the people of the clan,
there is a woman
who is always
making trouble around her.
The Nalan family
still can't escape
the deadly situation.
In my opinion,
you can only drive out the Nalan family
and protect us
for the rest of our lives.
How dare you!
Madam.
Calm down.
Forget it.
Where is Nalan Yue?
I told you to find her.
Chief.
She is not here now.
Not here?
Okay.
I'll wait for her here.
She is the master of the clan.
She has to be here
to make a decision.
Madam.
You are the one
who should leave
in this situation.
Master.
You should go out and have a look.
We will make a decision.
Listen to me.
From now on,
whoever dares to
disrespect our Hua'er,
I will definitely come back
and take her away.
She has no place
to stay and stay with you.
If it weren't for Nalan Yue,
our Hua'er
wouldn't have suffered so much
and suffered so much.
I want to hear you
talk nonsense here.
Tell Nalan Yue
if she doesn't know
and protect our Hua'er,
then it's good.
Someone will come to protect her.
She is as precious as a treasure.
Senior Bai.
Don't be angry.
I'll send you away first.
Send?
What do you mean?
I have my legs.
Move.
You go down first.
Yes.
Brother Lu.
Where did Yue go?
What did he do
to hide from me?
Why can't you
let me go?
This Longyin City
is not what I want.
You want to live,
but all these years
you have been killed
by your innocent people.
None of them
want to live well.
Now,
you Rong Jingfeng
has changed the rules
and broke into Longyin City.
You can't
do what you want to do.
go back to the capital
and live in the capital
and live in the capital.
Today,
we'll take your life
and avenge
our family.
Kill.
Father,
I'm late.
Hold on.
Father,
my father was kidnapped
from Longyin City.
This has nothing to do with him.
Who would believe
what you said?
You are his biological daughter.
There is a Longyin City behind him.
Xue Yi,
take my father to the spiritual church.
I'll take care of this place.
Yes.
Su Er,
Wu Ke,
now Nalan Yue
has occupied the spiritual church.
If I go,
I'll die.
Father,
only Nalan Yue
can save you now.
I've talked to Rong Hua.
He will protect you.
Xue Yi,
hurry up.
Let's go, Chongzhu.
Go to Nalan Yue.
Go.
We can't believe Nalan Yue.
Nalan Yue.
Master Nalan.
You risked your life
to inform me.
With Miss Rong's intelligence,
do you really think
she can't tell
the situation?
I can help
Rong Su.
But Rong Jingfeng
is talking.
The situation is urgent.
I...
We...
The place where they fight
is nearby.
You have to see clearly
how I help Rong Su.
Xuan Bing.
Rong Jingfeng's life
will be destroyed by you.
I...
Rong Jingfeng's life
will be destroyed by Nalan Yue.
I won't bother you.
Please go back with me
to discuss with Nalan Yue
about the future plan of Longyin City.
With this arrangement,
I wonder what you mean.
I...
Master.
Hold on.
Help me up.
Nalan Yue
wants to take revenge, right?
No.
Come on.
I'm right here.
Father.
Miss Rong.
Your sister begs for your help.
Please protect your father's life for now.
Let go of me.
Don't mind me.
Go away.
Don't beg her.
Father.
Young Mistress.
Go back.
Go away.
Father.
Young Mistress.
Hua.
Go away.
Don't beg her.
Yi Zhou.
Take her back to rest.
Nalan Yue.
What are you doing?
Hua.
Young Mistress.
Go away.
Nalan Yue.
No.
Young Mistress.
Nalan Yue.
I'm willing to see you
in this situation.
Please let go of me.
Nalan Yue.
Young Mistress.
No.
This is between Nalan's family
and Rong Jingfeng.
It has nothing to do with you.
Don't beg her.
Yi Zhou.
Master.
How could this happen?
It must be karma.
Rong Jingfeng has been scheming all his life.
I didn't expect
that he would be fooled by that Chihua Pig.
Master.
Father.
Su.
The old City Leader's wound is slowly healing.
It seems that it was caused by Chihua Pig.
But it's not easy to see
that Nalan Yue can control
the poisonous insects in City Leader's body.
Rong Jingfeng is now
like the two elders.
The purple insects in his body are closely related to me.
No matter what identity it was before,
from now on,
it's just a black soldier under my control.
I don't want to live like this.
No.
Nalan Yue.
What do you want to do?
No.
Today, Rong Jingfeng is here.
Our Nalan family
can finally show their blood and hatred.
But
I declare here
as the owner of Nalan family.
The Nalan family
and Rong Jingfeng's grudges
are over.
From now on,
there can be no more fighting.
Rebuild the Nalan family!
Father!
City Leader!
Rong Hua.
Are you alright?
Don't think too much.
You staying here
will only make it more difficult for you two.
But my father,
I don't know what's going on.
I'm leaving like this.
What should I do?
After all, he is my father.
I'm worried.
Your father is the one who killed the Nalan family.
Now he is in the hands of Nalan Yue.
I'm afraid no one can intervene.
Right now,
you must take your own safety into consideration.
If you think I'm your master,
then listen to me.
It's better to leave as soon as possible.
It's not easy for me and Yue to get here.
He hasn't recovered yet.
I can't let him go.
I can't do it.
The Nalan family
hates the people of Longyin City.
They have been hostile to you all these days.
They were afraid to do this
for the sake of Nalan Yue.
But today,
your master came here
to upset everyone.
Now the Nalan family is in a bad mood.
They want to take revenge.
As Rong Jingfeng's daughter,
they will also hate you.
I'm worried
that you will be in trouble if you stay here.
Do you believe in Nalan Yue?
I believe in her.
Since you believe in her,
you should believe in her.
She will handle things well.
Even if it's the worst result,
it's a decision she has made carefully.
I don't want to see you stay here
and suffer.
What about her?
How does she want to see you in a difficult situation?
I also arranged for your master to take you away from the Ling family.
Don't worry.
I have figured out a way
to get rid of the Chihua Pearl in that boy's body.
I promise
that if you see each other again,
I will definitely give you a healthy and complete Nalan Yue.
Thank you, Master.
It's really pointless to talk to you.
Go right now.
Say goodbye to that boy.
Whether you want to or not,
you must leave here today.
Master.
Am I useless?
Girl.
You have to consider your father's safety
and also consider Nalan Yue's position.
You have to worry about her health.
There is no such thing as two rights and seven beauties.
Not to mention the people's hearts.
You want to ease the grudge
and make things better.
But how many people in the world can do this?
Now Longyin City is under the enemy.
It's better to solve the internal trouble first.
When things are settled,
then slowly let the Nalan family accept you and understand you.
Isn't it two rights and seven beauties?
You are just too deep in love.
The situation is confusing.
Just now, Nalan Yue ordered
that from today on,
the grudges between the Nalan family and Rong Jingfeng will be eliminated.
No one is allowed to entangle anymore.
She did this for you.
Now she has returned to the Pope.
You should go now.
Thank you for your advice.
I understand.
The world is like falling on the sand.
The mind is like a picture.
The water is like a bright moon.
There is an donating star in the cursed city city.
There are your laws poor.
As the soul talked back,
Chu'er has everything pop up.
ciendovit.
Bright crystal Absolute internal.
A Love So Romantic
Episode 10