The Long Ballad
Episode 1
City Leader.
Don't be so reserved.
Come up.
Come to my side.
Su Er.
City Leader summoned Rong Su to come.
Did you have any orders?
It's been ten years since the last time.
Longyin City is bustling.
People come and go.
I see.
People come and go around me.
But I didn't expect
I only have you as my family.
Only you, my daughter,
are willing to be with me.
Don't worry, City Leader.
No matter what,
I will guard Longyin City with you.
Okay.
Come on.
Sit down and try it.
I dare not.
City Leader is so kind.
Why not?
In the past,
you were the bravest
in Longyin City.
But...
So why not?
Just do what I tell you to do.
Go.
Come on.
Sit down and try it.
Okay.
How is it?
Time is unbearable.
I know my father's health.
It's getting worse.
I've figured it out now.
In the future,
the whole Longyin City
and the whole Long family
will need you to take the throne.
So you will take the throne
and take the throne in the future.
Thank you for your kindness.
You're welcome.
But you're too young now.
It's too early to take the throne.
You don't have to worry.
I will do my best
to guard Longyin City
and stay by your side.
What's wrong?
You don't want the throne?
I do.
But I don't want to take the throne.
You've already made up your mind.
Only the winner can be the next City Leader.
So you have to get the recognition
from City Leader
with your own ability.
Please understand.
I have never had any desire
or desire to
take the throne
for you and Longyin City.
Okay.
I'm really happy
that you can think like that.
Remember.
If one day
you really take the throne,
then you need to protect
not only your own life
but also yours.
You will find that
all the disciples
in this huge Longyin City
and even their families
will become your burden
and become the responsibility
that you can't push off.
By then,
many decisions
will be unfulfilled.
Many decisions
will be in the way.
You're in a hurry.
You will slowly realize
that you're no longer a free man.
Su.
Can you understand
what I'm trying to tell you today?
I understand.
Thank you for your teaching.
Hold on.
Sir, I'm sorry.
Sir, I'm here to protect you
under the order of Master Long.
Come.
Xueyin.
What are you doing here?
Master Bai.
I'm here to protect you
under the order of Master Long.
I just got up
and took a step.
What do you know?
How can a seriously injured person
move easily?
Master, lie down.
It hurts.
Lie down.
Master, just lie down
and rest.
There's a big problem.
Let's talk about it later.
Listen to me.
Lie down.
Wait.
Stop being so stubborn.
You can't control your mind
before you fully recover.
You're really...
Why are you still standing here?
Leave.
Yes.
I'll stay outside
to protect you.
Master Bai,
as long as you're treated well...
Enough. Get out.
Master Bai.
Take the medicine.
Master.
What's wrong with you?
I made the medicine for you.
It can only work if you take it for more than half a month.
Now I'm...
Master Bai.
I'm sorry.
Maybe you're not used to Longyin City.
So you're worried and anxious.
Maybe
Master Bai will change a quieter place
for you to rest.
You may recover faster.
Master Xuan.
Are you hiding something from me?
I dare not.
I just want you
to think about it.
Wait.
I bought some fresh vegetables.
Let's eat together.
Let the servants do the work
of picking up the firewood.
You just got out of the house.
You're not suitable to work so hard.
Besides,
all the people outside
are looking for Brother Nalan.
You're not suitable to work so hard.
I know.
I know what I should do.
What do you want for lunch?
I'll cook for you.
No need.
I have something urgent to do.
No.
Xue Man.
Let's talk about it after we eat.
You may not know
that my parents' death anniversary is coming up.
I'm going out to eat.
You don't believe me?
At least I want to tell them
that I'm not going to work.
I was careless.
Don't worry.
I took care of you
just to
not let Brother Nalan blame himself.
Huan.
Why didn't you tell me
that you were going to buy something?
I'll get it for you.
Let's go.
Let's go back.
Xue Man.
What's wrong with Xue Man?
It's been so long.
Why can't you see the mud?
What mud?
You're so stupid.
Why do you say I'm stupid?
It's time to resolve her knot.
What knot?
What do you mean?
I just got back.
Sister invited me to come.
Now you've done most of the rewards.
Just say it.
I cooked some snow pear bird's nest
today.
Let's try it together.
Xue Man.
I'll tell you the truth.
I've been
holding the land of Mei's Mansion.
I'll return it to you
after it's done.
You've earned the money
and the silver.
It's a great achievement.
Even if I want to take it back,
it's not worth it.
I won't allow it
if my parents are alive.
I still have
this courage.
You've done a lot for it.
You can't take it back.
I didn't spend
a penny
when I bought the mansion.
What?
The land and money
of the mansion
were all from Master Bo
with my face covered.
I've never thought
you would be so cheeky.
So the mansion
is yours.
I'll return it to you.
You don't have to
treat me coldly in the future.
By the way,
I have one more thing
to tell you.
Your brother
is still alive.
What?
Your brother is so handsome
that he changed his identity.
After his men were killed,
he ran away from Longyin City.
Although I broke up with him,
he is
the only brother of our family.
Now that I know he is still alive,
I won't be worried
about my parents' soul.
Thank you for telling me
about Xue Man.
I've known him since we met.
Don't say that.
Actually, in Longyin City,
I did think about killing your brother.
After all,
he killed my aunt
and got Yu involved.
I really can't forgive him.
I finally know
why Brother Nalan is so loyal to his sister.
He is clear-headed
and does things right.
Xue Man,
no matter how beautiful you are,
you are not the only one
who loves Yue.
I am also your family.
I see.
Sister-in-law.
Miss Liuli,
Master has sent you
a message.
Okay.
Why are you in a hurry
to leave so soon?
Please come in.
Is it not Miss Rong
who came to me this time?
It's you, Young Master Nalan?
Then the person who sent me the message
and asked me to investigate Longyin City
is also you?
Xue Man doesn't do business that is not in the book.
Since it's not Miss Rong's order,
I don't care if I don't listen.
What are you doing?
Okay.
Don't scare her.
Miss Rong?
Liuli,
we just want to test your loyalty.
Don't worry.
The person who sent the order
has always been Miss Rong.
We never got involved.
I don't know.
Liuli,
what's going on in Longyin City?
Rong Jinfeng is slightly injured.
But the injury is not serious.
But Senior Bai Su's injury is quite serious.
He is still resting in bed.
Then,
what about Rong Su?
Don't worry.
Rong Su
is the most important person
in Longyin City.
He is the most popular person.
No one can compete with him.
Then,
what about Mo Huan?
How is Mo Huan?
Master is far away in the North.
How can Liuli know about him?
Besides,
if there is news about Master,
he will be the leader.
Liuli won't know.
Don't be nervous.
I don't mean to ask.
People in the martial arts world
are often in a tight spot.
We all understand
that you are working for your master.
But sometimes,
you have to learn to make choices.
Only if you protect yourself,
you can live for a long time.
I understand what you are teaching me.
Liuli,
I have a favor to ask you.
Go ahead.
It's been half a month.
Why is there no improvement?
I made the medicine myself.
No problem.
Bai Su's injury is getting better.
It's getting worse.
I found out in secret
that he needs more time to sleep
and wake up every day.
In this case, I'm afraid...
Why didn't you send him
to Longyin City
as I told you?
Master has been blocking him.
He said that Senior Bai was seriously injured.
He shouldn't be startled.
Moreover,
he was injured in Longyin City.
He should stay in the city.
Master Bai took good care of him
by keeping him in the Hall of Life.
Bai Weizhi didn't even
see the evidence.
I've already told him
to come back in secret.
But he only
cares about saving Bai Su.
He didn't pay attention to me.
You're so stupid.
If this goes on,
Bai Su will die.
I'm afraid he'll be in a fight
with City Leader
if we send him out of the city.
Moreover,
the relationship between City Leader and Master
has just been broken.
Who's there?
Yun, a disciple of Bingsi Hall.
I have something to report to Master Rong.
Bingsi Hall?
Yun?
Master,
why don't you let him in
and see what he says?
Come in.
Greetings, Master Rong.
There are many goods
in Jingfeng Town.
When I was going to buy them,
I saw a new item.
I thought you must like it.
So I bought it
and sent it to you.
How dare you!
Where did you learn the rules?
How dare you make decisions without permission
and come to the Palace of Emotionless.
It's okay.
Come up
and show me the item.
Yes.
Come on.
Let's go.
It seems that
the items you sell
are not that good.
You just don't know the goods.
I wonder if Miss Rong
has any favorite items
except for me.
Why are you so happy?
I'm just a little sad.
Why did you turn back
and play tricks on me?
I've told you
not to show yourself in Longying City.
To be honest,
I'm really happy
to see you today.
Stop talking nonsense.
To be honest,
why did you bother
to bring me to see you in the Palace of Emotionless?
Here's the thing.
Mr. Bai has been in Longying City
for half a month.
But he hasn't woken up yet.
There must be something wrong
with him.
We've contacted
the Wang family of Black Stone Mountain
to pick him up.
They'll try to
get Mr. Bai out of the city.
At that time,
I hope Miss Rong can help us
and help us delay for a few days
to ensure that
Mr. Bai's life is safe in the city.
How can you be sure
that I'll fight against my father
for an unrelated outsider?
Before I left,
my Young Madam
asked me to tell you something.
What is it?
The more you get, the more you lose.
Longying City
is no longer the original Longying City.
These years,
I think you gradually understand
what kind of foundation
Longying City has established
in the world over the years.
Your father did so much for Chihua Zhu
and her status in the world
that she suffered a lot
for the blood of her father.
She also got a lot of blood from him.
Rong Su,
is this the Longying City
that you want?
Is this the Longying City
that you risked your life
to get?
If you can control it,
what kind of foundation
can it be better?
Actually,
you don't have to go to Longying City
without Brother Lu.
Just go to someone else.
You're so worried about Lu Yizhou.
Actually, she wants to go to Longying City.
If you don't let her go,
I'm afraid she can't even sleep.
That's true.
Is Sister Rong still in Longying City?
I don't know.
Don't think too much.
Now your master
is protected by Bai.
And Lu Yizhou and Rong Su
are in a foreign land with you.
And Liuli has gone to Black Stone Mountain
to inform the Wang family.
I think
you don't have to worry about it.
I don't know
what's going on in Longying City.
If something bad happens to my father,
I won't just sit and watch.
I'll go.
Yue,
I'm from Longying City.
After I decided to be with you,
I left Longying City
and my family.
I have nothing
to say to my father.
I understand you.
But please understand me.
He's my father after all.
I really can't
watch him die.
Hua,
I know all of this.
Miss Mei.
Brother Cang Qi,
why are you here?
I'm worried that you'll leave the mansion alone.
So...
Thank you, Brother Cang Qi.
No need.
I'm sorry
for what you did.
I can do it
on my own.
In the heart of the bloodline,
there's a person
who's never going to die.
Naturally,
I can understand
how you feel.
But
a love letter in this world
is easy to let go
and to talk about.
Miss Mei is well-behaved
in Cang Qi.
She won't make Young Master worried.
Come on.
Don't worry.
You can treat me like a normal person.
Just treat me
as a person who can chat with me.
Yue.
Run!
Hurry up.
Young Master.
Yue.
Brother Lan.
Young Mistress.
Hurry up.
This is strange.
Sister-in-law,
what about Brother Lan?
He is fine now.
He's fine now.
Can you tell me
what happened to him?
He was killed
by a knife.
It's strange.
He just fell asleep.
Young Mistress,
do you have any way to cure him?
The acupuncture
can only relieve his pain temporarily.
It's not a long-term solution.
Is there no way
to cure him?
There is a way.
Sister-in-law.
Go to the spiritual school
and find the way to get rid of the poison of the illusion.
Go.
Xue Man.
I have an idea.
What idea?
Can you cure Brother Lan?
Although it's just
a way to get rid of the poison,
if we can use it to get rid of it,
it might be able to
get rid of the poison of the illusion in Yue's body.
But will it be
able to get rid of it
and force the poison in his body to re-appear?
The place of the illusion in Yue's body
is closely related to the Chihua Bead.
If we can get the coldness
into his body,
it might be able to be cured
in a short time.
But if we do this,
will the coldness in your body
also re-appear?
It doesn't matter.
I've been used to it
since I was a child.
By the way, Xue Man.
Can you do me a favor?
Go ahead.
Help me make a medicine.
Okay.
The Chihua Bead
I know you're worried about them.
I've made a vow before Madam died.
I will protect the people of Lingxu Pavilion.
No matter what happens to Young Mistress and Young Madam,
I will save them with my life.
I'm just worried that
if Brother Nalan can't wake up,
what should Sister-in-law, Brother Lu
and you do?
But if he wakes up,
he'll be as stupid as those
who were in the chaos before.
Sister-in-law can't accept it.
I don't know what to do now.
Is it right
or wrong for me to help him?
It's not your responsibility
to make a mistake.
In case you take yourself as the priority,
it's more important to save your life.
I'll protect Young Mistress.
Nothing will happen.
But you have to leave now.
This is Mei Mansion.
It's where I grew up.
Although it's already a mess now,
I won't leave
no matter what happens.
I want to be with everyone.
I want to be with Brother Nalan.
He
is also my family.
Change!
Young Mistress,
Young Mistress used the treatment
of cold air to relieve the poison in your body.
This can keep you awake.
What did you say?
Xue Man,
what happened?
It's me.
I changed the medicine for Sister-in-law.
That's why her body is cold and rejuvenated.
She said she didn't regret it.
I don't regret it either.
If anything happens to her,
I won't live alone.
I'll die with her.
You're really something.
Get out.
I...
Get out!
You're awake?
Yue,
as long as you can wake up,
I'll do anything.
It's very scary.
Wait for me.
First,
just fall down.
Second,
just come over here.
Third,
will I even make it alive?
Don't be too nervous.
I still have a lot of use
to economic training to the Αmtrénas agrasçae Where do I have the ability to train both?
Let's bow to His Majesty.
the last level of Xuanbing Talisman.
I can't control
Xuanbing Talisman's counterattack anymore.
And I don't know
when the next counterattack will be.
Only when I break through the last level of attack
can I make a change.
Now everyone of you is by my side.
You're in danger.
I can die for you.
I won't leave.
You were forced by Mohuan
to break through the last level.
But after you've done it,
you're in a worse condition.
What should you do?
You don't have to worry about that.
This time,
I'll make a mistake for Mohuan.
Both of you are heroes,
whether you're a martial artist
or a general.
You're all respected.
I wonder what you're doing
in Longyun City today.
My brothers are busy
and rushed to Longyun City.
They're here to thank you.
If it weren't for you,
my master and his family
would have been killed
by that devil.
That's right.
We're here for this.
Mr. Bai Su
is the leader of the people in the world.
He's a noble man.
Now he's in Longyun City
and he's in this situation.
I should do something.
But
Mr. Bai's injury
hasn't improved.
You two came here
to thank me.
It makes me feel more responsible.
It's not a good idea
to keep dragging on
your injury.
Since we're here,
why don't you take me back to Black Stone Mountain
and recuperate?
No.
I'm seriously injured.
How can I endure the long journey?
What if I get injured on the way?
What should I do?
You can't leave me here
because you're afraid of the world.
But if you insist on taking me away,
it's a dead end.
How can you take responsibility?
You're just afraid of being blamed.
Anyway,
I can't leave you here alone.
You...
It's not about responsibility.
It's about your safety.
There's no need to argue.
You two.
You two must calm down.
Don't worry.
I know
you're worried about Mr. Bai Su.
You're all kind.
But there's a saying,
care is a mess.
You two,
let's sit down and talk.
Don't get hurt for this.
Oh, no!
What's wrong?
Master is dying!
What?
This...
Guys,
Mr. Bai's condition
is not optimistic.
His pulse is weak
and his blood pressure is low.
I'm afraid you
need to be prepared.
Master.
How could this happen?
How did you take care of him?
He's in danger.
Why aren't you with him?
Now he's seriously injured.
As the Hall Leader of Lao Zi,
you're not even able to
treat your own master.
Hero.
Allow me to say something.
Actually,
Mr. Bai and you are from the same family.
Mr. Bai is his master, too.
Why can't he do his best?
Don't misunderstand him.
Actually,
you should blame him
for being too cruel.
It's not easy for Mr. Bai
to hold on until now.
Master is always in a tough situation.
I didn't expect him to be in such a situation.
He's usually the quietest.
He's not good at asking about the world.
Anyway,
I want to take Master back to Black Stone Mountain.
I understand
your filial piety.
With the current situation of Mr. Bai,
if you take him back to the mountain,
the journey will be long and bumpy.
His body will be exhausted.
Master is a high-spirited man.
He must be unwilling to die.
So I'll take him back to Black Stone Mountain
with my brother's will.
Mr. Bai.
I've made up my mind.
Okay.
Since you've decided,
I'll arrange it
and send Mr. Bai out of town.
Thank you.
Master.
Xuan Yi.
Serve tea.
Why are you here?
This is Kongzi Hall.
I should ask you this.
Why are you here?
Didn't the Wang brothers take you to Longyin City
to wander around?
I'm not wandering around.
I'm here
for my own purpose.
Have you achieved your purpose?
Of course.
I've...
I've checked it out.
Mr. Bai's medicine has no problem.
Longyin Palace thought
it was too obvious to use poison.
Mr. Bai's disciples
are not easy to fool.
So the problem
is on the pillow and the quilt.
They all smoked with incense.
The incense has no color and no taste.
But it's different from the medicine
Mr. Bai took a few days ago.
As time goes by,
the disease will not only get better,
but also the people will become unconscious.
Besides, Mr. Bai's injury is too serious.
It's too late.
I'm afraid it's too late.
Today, the City Leader will arrange
Mr. Bai and the Wang brothers
to leave Longyin City.
I think he's ready to do anything.
Once they leave the city,
they'll kill each other.
They won't leave any chance for them.
Mr. Bai has been in the martial arts world for a long time.
How did he offend you?
Why do you have to kill him?
You've been in the martial arts world for so many years.
Haven't you heard that
the more you know, the faster you die?
Look at you, old-fashioned.
Let me ask you.
Are you going to
stay in Longyin City for a lifetime?
In the future, the City Leader of Longyin City
will be the most important person
in the family.
You'll only do it for the City Leader.
You'll fight for others all your life.
What's the point?
In the future?
I've never thought about that.
Then let's meet on the day after tomorrow.
You're free today.
Let's think about it.
Besides fighting and killing,
don't you have any other hobbies?
I don't have any other hobbies.
I'm just a little bit busy.
I'm busy with my work.
Because I have to do the work I have a serious feeling about tomorrow,
every day I am very serious all day long.
Every time,
my tears fall
as if they were falling on a sand reminds-me.
White clouds Street,
a ponder is been drawn.
I will be your friend forever.