[Imitation]
[Episode 2]
Sorry to bother you, but how can I get to town from here?
It's a bit far.
You need to head straight that way.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work today.
- Thank you for your hard work today.
- Goodbye.
You met a bad owner, and now you're suffering, too.
Let's go.
See you tomorrow.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Everybody always leaves work so quickly.
- Hyung.
- What?
The number got leaked again.
It hasn't even been six months.
I'm tired.
I'll buy you a new one. Let's go.
You need to rest up for your interview tomorrow morning.
- Thank you.
- Get in.
Okay.
Put on your seatbelt, Ryeok.
What's that?
Hyung, what was that just now?
I heard there are a lot of ghosts around here.
What kind of ghosts?
You get out and check. Go, quickly.
You're the manager, Hyung.
Ryeok! You make more money than me.
Quick, check now.
What? Is something there?
I don't see anything.
Really?
Why? Why?!
There is something.
- It's that kid.
- What are you saying?
The kisaeng you stabbed to death today!
I heard that a manager ran off without his actor. Was that her manager?
What are you talking about?
The manager ran away.
I've heard of managers leaving their van and abandoning a nutcase actor,
but a manager taking the van with him is a first.
Hyung.
Back up.
- To give her a ride? We can't!
- Why not?
You know the company policy. No.
Hyung.
Hello.
- Get in.
- What?
Oh, I am fine.
The town is just over that hill. It won't take long.
Right, so get in.
I'm in the industry, too. I know you can't just let people into the van.
I don't want to complicate matters for you over such a small thing.
Thank you so much for the offer.
Goodbye.
You might be fine now, but you'll catch a cold once the sweat dries!
If you're doing this
because of what happened before, you really don't need to be concerned.
I just want to take a walk, so you should go your way, too.
Try hard.
What, did he know?
It's cold!
Do you know Stevie Wonder?
[Seven years ago]
"I Just Called to Say I Love You."
He's my dad's favorite singer.
We saw Stevie Wonder on TV once.
He's blind, but he writes music and sings.
On that show, he said,
"We all have our abilities.
The only difference is that
some people use those abilities, and some don't."
My dad heard that and said to me,
"Ma Ha,
I hope you live like him."
So that's why you suddenly showed up and asked to join our team?
Yes.
That's why I want to move to Seoul.
I don't think he'd let you do that.
Dad, you'll let me, right?
You can't really see the stars in Seoul,
because of all the lights.
That's kind of lame.
There are so many stars.
How long have you known?
Since you started avoiding me.
No, I wasn't avoiding you—
Keep following behind me.
Okay.
If anything seems off, Hyung will race over here.
This is me.
It's still cold.
Is this really where you needed to go?
Yes, I know where to go from here.
My friend is coming.
You might as well have given her a ride.
She didn't want to, and there's the company policy, too.
You know I always follow the company's orders.
Never mind.
Idiot!
- Hyung.
- Yes?
- Let's slow down a little.
- Okay.
What is that?
Lee Ma Ha!
Oh, so there was a reason.
What happened?
- Lee Yoo Jin?
- Are you hurt anywhere?
No, I am not, but what are you doing here?
That's a relief.
Hyung, I am tired.
- Let's go quickly.
- Okay.
Why did you come?
Hello, Yoo Jin? I can't reach Ma Ha.
She may be in the middle of filming. Maybe she did not see it.
I cannot get a hold of her manager either. It's just weird. Nothing's wrong, right?
Hang up for now.
[Ma Ha]
A movie shoot just came up, so I'm on my way to Mungyeong.
Were you that worried about me?
I can only rely on my friend.
- My soulmate.
- It's so far.
How could you walk around there by yourself at night?
I just ran.
The wind was nice and it felt good.
And there were a lot of stars.
Did you not have even one person to ride back with?
There was...
But I thought I wouldn't be comfortable riding in that car.
I really feel comfortable with you, Yu Jin.
Anyway, what's wrong with your manager?
How could he just leave you by yourself and run away?
Report him right away! You should not let people like him off the hook.
He may cause trouble elsewhere.
Nevermind. I was the one who held onto him.
And he's not that bad a person.
He must be feeling very sorry right now.
Hey, but what are you going to do if you are found out?
It's fine.
Just sleep. You must be tired.
Shall I?
[Shax]
Shax?
When did we arrive? You should have woken me up.
Hyun Ji, you're here, too.
They said they could not get in touch with you, so I was worried.
Are you all right?
Yes, I am fine.
Yu Jin, you are going to be late. Go back quickly!
Okay, you worked really hard. Just rest up.
Okay.
Thank you so much, and drive carefully on your way back.
Go safely.
Let's go.
Where did you go all night after stealing your manager's car?
- I'm sorry.
- I don't care that you are sorry. Just tell me where you were!
Did you go see a girl?
Wow, that silence seems to be agreement.
Why? Do you think you can just go out like that because we don't have any fans coming to see us?!
Do you think the others are stuck here because they have nowhere else to be?!
I won't ever do anything like this again. I am sorry.
You, get a grip on yourself.
Do you or do you not know that we have to risk everything for our comeback this time?
If we don't get good results this time, I don't know what will happen to Sparkling.
Let's just go in now. Head in.
- Hyun Oh, you should also stop.
- That bastard.
He pretends to be obedient all by himself.
But where did he really go?
Weren't you scared?
I told you, right?
That guy reeks of betrayal just by looking at his profile.
You also should have stormed out like us earlier.
I knew from the beginning that this would be a hit or miss.
Did you do it despite knowing that?
Just...
I just wanted to hold onto that thread tightly.
I felt like I would lose it forever if I did not hold on to it.
I can't believe that he just left someone at the filming site and ran away.
While coming down the mountain,
do you know what I was sad about and scared of the most?
That the thread I was barely holding onto...
got severed again.
I finally realized my place.
That place that I had dreamed of
showed up so close as if I could catch it.
But I could not get any closer to it.
I kept on turning back for some reason.
So I felt worse.
I think this is it.
I decided while I was on my way back.
I am going to let go of my dream now.
I think I did everything I could do.
I want to prepare for the GED (qualification examination).
- Ma Ha!
- Hey!
We are twenty-two right now.
We may be treated as old goods as idols,
but we are actually still young elsewhere.
We can start from scratch again.
True.
Let's quit together.
Lia, why do want to quit?
I worked part time, singing at a festival yesterday.
I was sad for no reason. Reality hit me suddenly.
When I was young,
I went from this house to that house,
singing songs at every party in our neighborhood.
And until now, I was still singing at someone else's party.
I wondered if I worked that hard to be doing this now. I was so ashamed.
True, I am going to quit, too.
I heard people say I was pretty since I was little.
So I thought I was actually pretty,
but there were goddesses (pretty women) everywhere.
I guess the time when I acted all high and mighty because of that,
was the end of my golden years.
And I don't even have talent like you guys.
Why are saying that?
Don't, stop it.
70,080 hours,
2,920 days,
and eight years.
I am so tired of it all.
Yes, let's start again from tomorrow!
Reboot!
We are Shax.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Mr. Kwon Ryeok, are you filming a new historical movie?
Yes, I had a lot of worries, as this is the first historical movie I filmed.
So with a rookie mindset,
I am practicing hard and putting my all into the filming.
I am curious about what kind of new look you will show.
Please visit the movie theatre and see that for yourself.
Then finally, please tell us how you feel about Shax's sixth anniversary.
I will comment first, as I am already talking.
When we are separate, we are lacking and full of flaws,
but when we are together, we fill in the gaps and we can last for the next 10 or 20 years...
No,
I wish we can be a group until we die.
Wasn't Shax originally a group of six?
There are many people who are still curious about Eun Jo...
Is there no possibility of Eun Jo coming back?
Please only ask from the list of confirmed questions.
Kwon Ryeok and Eun Jo were the closest, right? Do you not keep in touch?
Let's call it a day. Good job.
Thank you.
Good job!
[Jang Yu Ri]
Alcohol must be drunk with comfortable people.
The alcohol even tastes sweet today.
It's Sparkling, right? Your group?
I heard they're being talked about a bit now.
Just being talked about isn't all that great.
If they can't release a hit song three years after their debut, they're out.
[Lee Ma Ha]
Are you going to move again?
You've got an amazing song ready, right?
Or did you find an investor?
What happened to the Fact Check people? They're doing things they didn't do before.
They're probably doing that because our group is very quiet and they need some useful sources for their article.
They don't think of working hard on their own.
I'll try to find something that will make a good article.
- How about Ryeok?
- He completed his schedule and went to his dorm.
He received treatment, and three years have passed, so it's probably better by now.
You should still be careful. He may break down all at once.
Ryeok is putting food on the table for us right now.
Yes, sir.
Shax! Shax! Shax!
[Shax]
Eun Jo!
[I'm sorry Ma Ha. Forgive me.
- Go Ba Hwi]
I thought so.
You're feeling sorry now.
Yes, thank you.
Have a nice day.
[Cram School]
[Incoming call]
Hello!
Ah, yes. I see.
Yes. I'm sorry. Yes.
[Incoming call]
Hello!
I am Lee Ma Ha, but
I'm not interested.
Yes. Sorry!
God! This damn voice phishing!
[Mahee Hair]
I'm back.
What about your cram school?
What's with your hair?
Is it pretty?
I just listened to the cram school's options today.
But earlier, I received a weird call.
JH Entertainment, the CEO's name was...
Ji Hak!
- That's right. Ji Hak. Did you also get that call?
- Yes.
It must be a scammer.
I asked him how he knew about me, and he asked me to come for an audition.
Lia, you too?
There are all kinds of people!
I'm angry now!
Is it really voice phishing.
[To you who would like to fulfill your dream once again. Renew audition.
Phone number: 010-0129-8475. Date: 11/01/2020
Venue: Seoul, GangBok, Suyuro, 92nd street
- JH Entertainment]
[Ma Ha]
♫ Hakuna Matata yo ♫
- Hi, Yoo Jin.
- Hey, Ma Ha. It has been a long time.
Get your senses together!
I'm sorry.
Oh, Manager Tae Geun!
Have you been well?
I have been, but Yoo Jin is practicing the choreography now.
Then I will call back later.
If saying you'll call back later, means you can't tell me, then
don't call again.
Pardon? Ok.
Did you not get a call from Ji Hak?
Okay. Thank you.
Why? Did the manager pick up?
It must be because of last time.
But about that scammer...
It seems he isn't a scammer. He was a manager at NOG.
NOG?
[To you who would like to fulfill your dream once again. Renew audition.
Phone number: 010-0129-8475. Date: 11/01/2020
Venue: Seoul, GangBok, Suyuro, 92nd street
- JH Entertainment]
[Venue of the audition]
[H Cafe is closed today]
Do they hold the audition in a café?
He must be a scammer, just lying about NOG and Shax.
But we still came all the way,
shall we just go in?
I'm going in because you are pitiful.
If not, let's just have some tea.
Let's go.
You've come.
The one in the middle is Lee Ma Ha?
Yoo Lia?
And Shim Hyun Ji.
Yes, you're right.
Nice to meet you.
I am JH entertainment's CEO and the owner of this cafe, Ji Hak.
Since you're all here, can we start once you're ready?
Can we perform together?
The audition is just an excuse. We came to make a memory.
We want to make a memory to remember.
Ah, is that so?
It may be a bit embarrassing but–
It is our first time.
Us three performing together.
We were actually one team before.
I know that you debuted as a three-member girl group—Omega 3.
We didn't debut. We were close to it.
There was an accident the day we were supposed to debut.
That you were forced to go down when you were doing your rehearsal for the music show?
Yes, I know that too.
It's become so difficult to put young people out there.
What will you do bringing together older kids who have nowhere else to go?
With your profile and eyes for singling out talent,
"I am Ji Hak from NOG. I am Ji Hak from Shax."
It was thanks to the title. It was not me.
[Shim Hyun Ji]
She was a trainee and got cut without even debuting.
[Lia]
She sings someone else's song on someone else's stage.
[Lee Ma Ha]
She does cheap events and has not been able to do any proper activity.
Kids who have fallen to the very bottom, with a debut that never came to fruition.
Stories like these work these days.
Even you know that their capability fills just a page.
Not obviously practiced smiles... but barefaced kids.
And after that,
I will draw attention to them with a completely different method quickly.
It's not much of a stage, but go ahead and make your memories.
The three of you, as much as you want.
♫ OMEGA III ♫
♫ You're for me baby. You make my heart tremble ♫
♫ Oh my ♫
♫ You make my heart beat ♫
♫ I know it boy ♫
♫ You’re so perfect, you’re my ideal man ♫
♫ You make my eyes are filled with hearts ♫
♫  You’re the love I’ve been waiting for ♫
♫ Your whispers make me fall in love ♫
♫ All day  ♫
♫ I keep looking at the phone  ♫
♫ Again and again, You make my heart trouble me ♫
♫ I want to hear you, my boy. I want to hear your sweet voice  ♫
♫ When I hear your voice, I melt for you, ring my bell ♫
♫ Whenever I’m by your side, I’m so happy, it’s amazing  ♫
- You worked really hard.
- Thanks for the performance.
Thank you!
If you three are okay with it, I want to work with you.
What?
Is something wrong with him?
I am scared because this opportunity came without a single warning.
Is the role of an entertainment agency CEO,
one where you can have two jobs wearing an apron and serving in the neighborhood coffee shop?
True, it does not look like he has any part-timers either.
Yeah, that means that he has no money, right?
But when we were auditioning,
there was something in the way his eyes looked.
That I acknowledge.
But did you all fall for it?
What do you mean?
I cut my hair too.
My indomitable will!
Anyway, we are not going to do it. Shall we have fun putting forth some tough conditions for the contract?
The fantasy of the underdog?
Well, because you want us to work together...
We will put forth our condition.
This is the contract proposed by me.
[Exclusive Management Contract]
1,822,480 won (about 1,618 dollars)
Will you give us a salary?
At the same time when entering into a contract with us?
Does this make sense?
It's the minimum hourly wage right now,
but after we make a profit from your activities, I will distribute it according to what is written in the contract.
That does not make any sense.
Are you a fraud or something?
Will a fraud own up saying he is one?
You don't want us to do something weird, right?
"If Party A makes unreasonable requests not stated in the contract,
Party B is entitled to get compensated for breach of contract."
Are there really no restrictions on using smartphones, going out, or dating?
I am sure you all know they are things you can't really prevent even if you try to.
But actions have to have consequences.
You just have to be responsible for your actions.
Just a minute.
Welcome. Please come in.
Follow me out.
We wanted act tough...
He was tougher, and everything made sense!
What shall we do?
I am really tempted.
Even so, does this make sense?
It's just that we have heard clauses like this for the first time. But it does make sense.
Apparently, celebrities are paid salaries in Japan.
But we have seen a lot of kids having a hard time after signing a bad contract.
The contract period is one year.
I only have that much to pay you salaries.
And if you don't see any hope after this time, we can break off the contract without any repercussions.
What if we do well?
Then we have to redraw the contract, coming to an understanding of each other's conditions.
Of course, only when both parties want to.
Excuse me!
Yes, I am coming.
It's just a year.
Exactly one year.
I want to prolong my dream for another year.
Let's take a risk and do it for exactly another year.
Anyway, we have nothing to lose.
Yes, let's do it.
As someone who said that they have nothing left to lose,
let's trust each other and do this.
Then what shall we begin with?
You did not read the contract in detail.
The contract period starts tomorrow.
Go rest up at home because we will be busy from now on.
Thanks for the tea.
- Thanks for the tea.
- Sure.
We are starting again from tomorrow on.
Don't we need a new team name too?
To new beginnings.
What would sound nice?
It is hot!
Be careful. Drink it slowly.
Tea Party!
It's Tea Party when you say it from the beginning,
and Tea Party when you say it backward!
Hello! We are always happy,
Tea party!
Tea Party said from the front and back.
Hello, we are always happy, Tea party!
[365 Corner | Shinjoong Bank]
[Loan Agreement]
[Sending Email]
When did you prepare all this?
This totally reminds you of the old days, doesn't it?
If we get the song, decide on a concept, practice the choreography and prepare for our debut,
we have to live here for about six months.
We will have you debut at the earliest.
But we don't have a song yet.
You have a team name, don't you? 'Tea Party'.
The first broadcast may happen this week.
Why not just ask us to take down a mugger and appear on the news for that?
Well, that works too.
Our concept is 'complete reality.'
Just who you actually are.
Contract?
Hey, Ji Hak! It has been a long time.
It hasn't changed at all here.
I thought you emigrated because there was no news about you.
Did you make a comeback?
I barely made a three-member girl group.
Hey, the program that you are doing was good with strong questions.
You even monitored it because you're my friend. Thank you!
Let me ask you a favor.
I'm a PD now. I can't help you like before.
Look at this just once. Look at it and then tell me.
What is it?
Look at it.
Idol who gets a monthly salary?
They're still idols, so they should at least release a song before they appear on TV.
I told you that the concept is 'Complete Reality'.
First, let Tea Party get the attention.
Then their song will follow.
Gather a list of company's that can be taken over easily.
You know, right? That the women in our company are weaker?
Yes.
Good.
They say Ji Hak is back.
Learning is stealing?
Is there anything else he knows to do?
Shall I look into it?
Let it be.
It must be hard so he must have just collected people who do events.
- You may leave.
- Yes, sir.
Ji Hak?
CEO! CEO!
You didn't even explain to us what kind of show it is.
What should we do if you just drag us into a show?
We haven't prepared anything!
[No Smoking]
This is the long-awaited first stage of Tea Party with the three of you.
[Live Current affairs People. Guest of the week.]
If you don't want to do it, you don't have to. I'm not forcing you.
But if you go out now... you can't come back.
Sisa People, where we interview the hottest people!
Today we have a special idol group who
are debuting through this live broadcast instead of a music show.
Please introduce yourself.
One, two, three!
Hello! We are always happy, Tea Party.
We are leader Lia,
Hyun Ji,
and Ma Ha.
Even your introduction is refreshing.
Please take care of it.
Likewise.
Thank you.
See you later.
[I've heard you will be the first group of...]
- You did a good job.
- You too.
What's the next schedule?
That's all for today. I will get the car so wait a bit.
Let's go together.
Come quickly.
We get a monthly salary.
When I was a trainee I had more than one part-time job.
We had to do many part-time jobs when we were trainees.
Singing at weddings, working at shops, and even doing deliveries.
It's nice that we don't have to do all that and that we can just practice.
If it's not rude of me, can you tell us about your salary?
It is ₩1,822,480 (around 1,822 dollars).
It's minimum wage.
Isn't it the first time that there is such a contract?
Actually, people don't talk about this but the money invested in trainees
is also counted as debt in many places.
My friend has a debt of one million won, so even though she debuted three years ago,
she hasn't been able to get paid.
This system seems to have its merits and demerits. I am curious.
Who is this CEO that made such a crazy contract?
Does he have a lot of money?
No. Our CEO is definitely not rich.
I saw the loan documents.
We have to do well before we get all the money.
Fighting!
I really want to encourage you.
I really hope you succeed.
Thank you. Thank you.
Shall we change the mood?
Nowadays, Idol groups all have personal talents.
Can you show us your personal talents?
Yes, I will go first.
♪ I'm a cold woman ♪
♪ So don't swear at me ♪
If you did more, I would have sworn at you that you are a cold woman.
Thank you.
It is really refreshing. Wow!
Then the next person.
I don't have a personal talent so... Ta da!
Oh, you're the visual and the center.
It is really lovely.
Then lastly, Ma Ha?
I will perform a sing-along song that I performed at a small village festival.
- I need a moment to get ready.
- Oh, sure.
What are you looking at?
I am La Ri Ma's sister.
La Ri Ma Ha!
Are you looking at it because she's like me?
Just look at me then. Why look at a fake?
What's up?
The same as you.
"Idol Outing"?
I got you this gig.
If I don't do this, will I even get to look at your face?
Then I will see you during the recording.
What? Are you just going?
♫ I don’t want an awkward relationship ♫
I have a full schedule today. Bye.
♫ Don’t think so much. ♫
♫ Don’t get confused ♫
It was Tea Party's Ma Ha!
Annoying!
This small girl!
What the hell did we do?
I don't remeber.
I couldn't even talk. I only laughed.
Grandma? Did you see it?
Did all of you gather and watch it?
[Mom, make sure you watch me on LIVE broadcast today]
[Mom I am going to be on TV today]
[Don't miss it!]
[Unread]
Ma Ha, my mom said that I worked really hard.
I keep crying. My makeup is about to go bad.
I want to get emotional, too.
[Congratulations on your Public TV debut. I will expect more from now on.]
Expect? As if.
New message
Hey!
What is happening?
(Ringtone: you have a new message answer quickly)
Seems like many people saw it.
- Another one.
- What?
Another.
Tea Party!
Shall we go?
Yes, sir.
[Tea Party]
[Monthly-salary girl group Tea Party, shocking debut at Sisa People!]
[A new "Tears" hidden expert, Tea Party's Lia!]
[Tea Party's Ma Ha fills the studio with her imitation of La Ri M]
[Unique eye-catching visual, Tea Party's Hyun Ji]
[A one-year contract, will Tea Party succeed within their time limit?]
What is this? This is nuts.
It is Tea Party, a group that's slowly becoming hot.
Shall we also cast them once?
Isn't it just word of mouth right now?
They have a story and have good characters as well.
I think they could ride this wave at least a month with that imitation of La Ri Ma.
Maybe we can cast them because they're becoming hot.
How can a La Ri Ma knockoff come looking like this?
I'm Tea Party's–
- Hey! We have a wig, right?
- Yes.
[6 p.m. Hometown]
[Hyun Ji - Wake Up Caster]
[Happy Time 3 p.m.]
Three years ago and now,
appearance fees haven't changed at all.
But still, you did your best.
So how much did we earn?
What?
That is–
Oh, how much is it?
Your debut broadcast at Sisa People earned 187,600 won ($166).
Because 6 p.m. Hometown was filmed in the countryside, 288,600 won.
He and I was also filmed in the countryside, so 252,000 won.
Can you give us a salary if we earn this much?
We should do events to earn money.
"Why does she keep copying La Ri Ma?"
"Someone who goes by other artist's songs, you're just a copycat."
Ah, seriously!
If it's going to bother you, don't look at it.
I'm looking at it because it bothers me.
At first, everyone said it was fun.
Are you going to speak casually from now on?
They keep calling us "copy-idols." It is impossible not to look at them.
If you don't have the confidence to not look at them, why don't you study the mean comments?
Look at the mean comments and the things you cannot change with your will and actions, disregard them.
The things you can change with your will and actions, go and fix them.
Lastly, collect the remaining trash comments that don't belong anywhere, and report them.
Okay?
We understand.
One of these can really hurt your self-esteem.
"They don't even have their own song. What are they doing there?"
I think so, too.
This is JH entertainment's Ji Hak.
"Idol Outing"?
"Idol Outing"!
Yes, I understand.
Yes.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
What is it, are we going on the show "Idol Outing"?
Awesome!
Oh my gosh, next week's lineup is amazing. Even Shax is on it!
But what do we do?
Only Ma Ha is appearing on it.
Congrats.
Fighting!
Go do great.
"Idol Outing" will be our last schedule before working on your first single album.
Working on a single album?
The songs I requested from the publisher are coming out soon.
Awesome!
Hello, I'm Lee Ma Ha from Tea Party!
Hello, I'm Tea Party's Lee Ma Ha!
There's nothing to be nervous about.
Since it's the first time don't get greedy. Think before you act.
If they ask you to do anything, don't decline and do it well.
Since I came as Tea Party's representative for today, I'll work hard.
Yes, Chief.
Just a moment.
Ma Ha, since everyone is a senior to you here, make sure you introduce yourself to everyone well.
Just a minute.
Yes, Chief.
Yes, yes.
Hello, I'm Tea Party's Lee Ma Ha!
Hello, I'm Lee Ma Ha from Tea Party!
It's La Ri Ma!
She looks even more beautiful in real life.
It's La Ri Ma...
Hello, Sunbae-nim!
It's you then? My copycat.
What is this? You don't look a single bit like me.
Are everyone's eyes broken?
Miss La Ri Ma, you're here.
PD!
But is she on the show, too?
What?
You're the one who asked for her.
Yes.
Since things turned out this way, we will just have to have some fun.
She's my copycat. It's the first time we're coming out in the same shot.
How about coming out with the exact same make-up as me?
Unni.
You have another set of these clothes, right?
Yes.
Nice!
As expected, you know how to make a show.
It's okay, right?
Wouldn't you at least need to mimic me... to come out for a few more days?
Of course you should do it.
What are you doing? We don't have any time, move quickly!
Yes, sir!
It's Manager Ji.
Manager Ji?
He made a girl group called Tea Party, they must be making an appearance today.
Ryeok–
Hyuk, let's go.
If I go out on air like this... I'll get more hate, won't I?
Hello, Sunbae-nim.
Thank you very much for last time.
I carried around the padded coat every day to give it back to you, in case I managed to meet you again one day.
The only thing you know how to do is to imitate La Ri Ma?
Pardon?
Wouldn't you at least need to mimic me... to come out for a few more days?
The only thing you know how to do is to imitate La Ri Ma?
Now, it's the last segment.
She's a newbie idol, making her first entrance at "Idol Outing."
I didn't even think that this person had a little sister.
La Ri Ma's little sister, Lee Ma Ha! Come out!
Hello. I'm La Ri Ma's little sister, Lee Ma Ha.
Today, I'll try to mimic my unni properly.
Play the music!
It's me La Ri Ma!
♫ To be my lover ♫
♫ 3, 2, 1 drop ♫
♫ Let me hold the wine, today I feel fine ♫
♫ Drinks and up all night, all night till dawn ♫
Will you help me, Sunbae-nim?
She has held her hand out for help!
Will she grab that hand?
[Epilogue]
She came again.
It's already been one month.
I think she came up from the countryside.
I admit, she's enthusiastic.
Give me your number.
Pardon?
Okay.
Here...
I'll think about it by tomorrow.
Thank you!
Try hard.
[Imitation]
Giving her your coat, talking with her, dancing!
Don't you know it's the end for you if the fans catch on?
- How is it?
- It doesn't seem like our song.
Our song. Omega III's debut song!
There'll be loads of other songs. Why does it have to be that song of all songs?
Because it seems like us...
I want to bring it out.
Why is Ma Ha trending on the search engine?
Hey, look at this.
Who got mixed up with Ryeok?
JH Entertainment, Ji Hak made them.
Kwon Ryeok, who thinks of his fans as laughable: expel him.
Expulsion?!