♪When I think of you, oh♪
♪I hope to see you in a dream, oh♪
♪Burning paper to ashes
and burying under the willows♪
♪On the fresh branches♪
♪The perfectness beneath falling♪
♪Is the price of solving the riddle♪
♪When afterglow climbs passers' hair♪
♪He no longer is missing♪
♪Under the bridge♪
♪Lover of previous life♪
♪Carved on the palm♪
♪Tears are dropping from your eyes♪
♪Wow♪
♪If the Buddha says♪
♪Don't be obsessed♪
♪How can I follow with a ready mind?♪
♪When I think of you, oh♪
♪I'm tortured by the love♪
♪Wow♪
♪It's a transient illusion in the end♪
♪No matter how much I miss you,
you never show up♪
♪Wow♪
♪What do I want to pursue?♪
[Calling From The Galaxy]
[Episode 15]
- The selection begins.
- Please step up.
Kid, what is your name?
How old are you?
You are just a little kid
who knows nothing
but to eat.
Sooner or later, there will be a day
when you squander
all of your family's fortune.
♪At midnight, who's thinking of me?♪
You are so rude.
No wonder you can't get married.
Let's go. She's too scary.
♪As time goes by, who becomes a hero?♪
Can't get married?
♪In the moonlight,
everything looks like an illusion♪
The candied haws
look delicious alright.
Next, please.
Wait a moment.
Let me go first.
I can't wait any longer.
♪She looks at it all with yearning♪
Miss Yu.
Sir...
Please hurry back.
If anything happens to you,
I can't afford the medical bills.
Miss Yu,
I've been waiting for you.
You've really kept me waiting.
♪The rabbit keeps me company
in the long night in the Moon Palace♪
Carry him out.
Quickly, carry him out.
Quickly carry him out.
Miss Yu.
You really don't respect
the old and the young.
This is me respecting
Tian.
Next, please.
Miss Yu,
let me show you
a unique martial arts move.
Five Tigers Knife Technique.
♪Living in the three realms, I'm afraid♪
♪As time goes by, who became a hero?♪
♪In the moonlight,
everything looks like an illusion♪
♪Get drunk and forget it all♪
♪I want tenderness
in those warning signals♪
Miss,
what's the situation here?
Why is one being carried out
and the other wielding blades?
Yes, indeed.
It can't be...
What are you talking about?
This is a formal matchmaking.
If you don't want to meet our lady,
just scram.
The rest of you, come up all at once.
My dear daughter,
I will surely find you a good husband.
What a huge moth!
My daughter,
I will surely find you a good husband.
Miss Yu, I see you are hungry.
I've conjured candied haws.
Doesn't eating this make one hungrier?
Delicious.
Why are you still standing there?
I see you are eating happily.
Have you fallen for the person
who gave you the candied haws?
Sir,
I'm looking for a husband,
not a eunuch.
Rude.
Do you see that?
She must love me.
She's too embarrassed
to say it directly.
Didn't you say you would help me choose?
How do you feel about them?
Everyone's pretty good.
You bunch of toads
want to marry me?
Maybe in your next life.
I am the son of a minister.
How come I can't marry anyone?
The son of a minister?
You?
You truly are not worthy.
Tian, cross his name out.
Yes, my lady.
I want everyone to know
your true faces.
True faces?
My true face is
that I'm manlier than you.
Father!
Next.
Miss,
I notice your forehead is dark
with a demonic aura.
Within three days,
there will be bloodshed.
Would you like to try my talisman?
It will surely expel demons
and ward off evil.
It can also nourish your energy.
Everyone who has used it
speaks well of it.
You dare to do business on my turf!
I have strong energy.
I don't need anything, go away.
Suan, Tian, drive him out.
- Yes, my lady.
- Get out.
- Out.
Miss, you really have a demonic aura.
Miss Yu, don't be angry.
Anger harms the body.
You are...
Miss Yu, if you have time later,
would you care for a game
of chess with me?
But I don't know how to play.
That's okay, I can teach you.
May I know your name?
What do you do for a living?
Miss Yu, do you know?
Your eyes shine like stars.
They mesmerize me.
I know.
Your taste in men
is truly unique.
Got a problem?
Nope.
You should think it over properly.
Miss Yu,
may I have the honor
to gaze upon your beauty?
Yes, you may.
But not for too long.
Okay.
How dare you!
[Yan Residence]
Li, stop walking back and forth.
Sit down and have some tea.
Ci,
Bu now has three women by his side.
Objectively speaking,
I am definitely the best.
I am beautiful, kind-hearted,
and so wealthy.
Any wise man would know who to choose.
But I'm still not sure.
It seems Bu is nice to everyone.
He is especially nice to you.
He is just that kind of person.
You make it sound like
you know him so well.
Okay.
Young master...
Quickly.
What's this?
He closed the door.
When did they get this close?
Keep it down.
My dear Huang,
when will you carry me like that?
You see, you've scared him.
Huang, hold me.
Hold me.
I think maybe I should go.
Don't even think about it.
Even in the Mortal Realm,
you still worry me.
What am I supposed to do with you?
Are you okay?
How do you drive like this?
How dare you!
[Mistaken Execution of Cui Ning]
Well, it's been so long.
Why hasn't he come out yet?
How come there's no sound at all?
What do you think they're doing?
Ladies,
please just show some mercy
and let me go.
If the young master finds out,
I'm surely done for.
You're not allowed to leave.
What exactly is their relationship?
I have a way.
Come.
Young master!
Young master, where are you?
- Mr. Bu.
Young master.
I've been looking for you.
Mr. Bu, where have you been?
Huang has been looking for you for ages.
I have something
to discuss with Master Yu.
Dear Mr. Bu,
have you seen
our noble, elegant, peerlessly graceful,
exceedingly beautiful and smart lady?
We've been looking for her
for a long time.
I'm sorry.
I haven't seen your
noble, elegant, peerlessly graceful,
exceedingly beautiful and smart lady.
- I see.
Luo Huang.
Young master.
The flowers today are particularly lush.
Yes.
Very lush.
Go.
My lady.
What's going on?
[Yu Residence]
My lady, wake up.
Quick.
Wake up.
Tian, wake up.
Wake up, my lady.
It's nearly noon.
Get up now.
My lady, you have dark circles.
What?
Quick, bring me the mirror.
My lady.
Oh my.
The treasure hunt
has given me dark circles.
What am I going to do?
My lady, doesn't
the Silver Leaf Jade Flower
have beautifying effects?
Why don't we give it a try?
Right.
♪The screen is covered
in candlelight shadows♪
♪Dancing on the blade in fancy clothes
with no one in mind♪
♪The Milky Way falls
and so are the stars♪
♪The rabbit keeps me company
in the long night in the Moon Palace♪
♪The screen is covered
in candlelight shadows♪
♪Dancing on the blade in fancy clothes
with no one in mind♪
♪The Milky Way falls
and so are the stars♪
♪The rabbit keeps me company
in the long night in the Moon Palace♪