♪When I think of you, oh♪
♪I hope to see you in a dream, oh♪
♪Burning paper to ashes
and burying under the willows♪
♪On the fresh branches♪
♪The perfectness beneath falling♪
♪Is the price of solving the riddle♪
♪When afterglow climbs passers' hair♪
♪He no longer is missing♪
♪Under the bridge♪
♪Lover of previous life♪
♪Carved on the palm♪
♪Tears are dropping from your eyes♪
♪Wow♪
♪If the Buddha says♪
♪Don't be obsessed♪
♪How can I follow with a ready mind?♪
♪When I think of you, oh♪
♪I'm tortured by the love♪
♪Wow♪
♪It's a transient illusion in the end♪
♪No matter how much I miss you,
you never show up♪
♪Wow♪
♪What do I want to pursue?♪
[Calling From The Galaxy]
[Episode 11]
[Lu Wu]
[Fenglai Inn]
Why hasn't Xinglan come back yet?
It's better not to come back.
It's annoying to see her.
I'll go take a look.
Come and see what this is.
This is weird.
Miss Yu might be in danger.
Where is she?
- My lady.
My lady.
My lady, where are you?
Where is she? I can't find her.
It's all your fault
for sleeping so soundly.
You didn't even know she went out.
How can you blame me for this?
Well, you didn't find her either.
You only know to flirt with Luo Huang.
What? It's all your fault.
It's not my fault. It's your fault.
It's your fault.
Enough.
If we can't find her,
we both will have to suffer.
Where are you, my lady?
My lady.
Tian.
Why do I feel it's a bit creepy here?
Where is this place?
Maybe we have taken the wrong way.
Then let's hurry back.
Bu.
Why is there no one around?
I am so scared.
Stop it.
What place is this?
Won't either of you give me a hand?
Bu.
There's not a single person here.
Maybe we should head back.
I think it's the right way.
Li, stay behind me.
I will protect you.
Okay.
Ci, get up.
Maybe you two go back first.
Can you do it alone?
No problem.
Then, take care.
I'll come back for you
after I take Li back.
I want Bu to take me back.
Li, how about I take you back,
or you just walk with us?
I want Bu to take me back.
I can't be apart from Bu
for even a moment.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Ci.
Gu Li.
Gu Li?
Gu Li is missing.
Gu Li!
Help!
Bu.
I knew you would
definitely come to rescue me.
My lady.
We have finally found you.
It's our fault
for not protecting you well.
My lady, we are
absolutely guilty.
How can we explain to Master Yu?
You are generous and kind.
How could this happen to you?
How could this happen to me?
Exactly.
If you keep shouting, I'll burn you all.
How much do you guys earn a month?
What did you do before you died?
Did you get married?
Do you have any children?
During festivals,
how much paper money
do your families burn for you?
I don't know how your business works.
But in our world of the living,
we'd burn
paper carriages, paper villas,
and paper dragon boats.
How about I burn some for you guys?
How much do you want?
I'll give you a discount.
Let me see.
Paper carriage costs three qian.
Paper villa costs five qian.
Paper dragon boat costs seven qian.
My lady, we are getting rich.
Are you a fool?
Can we make money from them?
Stop it.
Do you have a lighter?
Do you want us to burn something now?
Even fire comes with a cost.
I want to burn myself.
It's too hard to be
a good person these days.
I am sincere
to do business with you.
What sorcery did you use on them?
Another one.
Maybe I'll burn some for you too.
Lunatic.
What are you doing?
With no spiritual power at all.
How dare you run wild here!
Get up.
Keep an eye on them.
Who are you?
You ask him.
S-S-She
is...
Ci.
Is she from Yuluo House?
So all the women
from Yuluo House are like this?
What is Yuluo House?
Well, don't mind this.
She is...
My name is Hong Luan.
Hong Luan?
Eerie. What a terrible name.
Doesn't sound like
the name of a decent girl.
Have you been well lately?
Miss,
have we met before?
Let me tell you.
My Bu definitely wouldn't fancy
someone like you.
Li.
You!
Forget it.
Thank you for your help, Miss Hong Luan.
But we have to save someone today,
I'll come to you to express
my thanks another day.
I'll go with you.
Maybe I can help.
If you wish to come along,
that would be great.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
I'm not going with her.
If you don't come,
ghosts will catch you again.
Wait for me.
Keep quiet.
Bro.
The price just now
was already the best discount.
It really can't be any cheaper.
I can't take it anymore.
You just want me to release you.
I will do it then.
I don't know.
I don't see anything.
Don't worry.
My lady.
I will not tell anyone
that you opened this cell door.
In business, we must value integrity.
Otherwise, it won't last long.
Stop it.
You just said to release me.
I've never said that.
Chase her!
[Peony Villa]
Flowers. There are flowers!
Flowers.
We've arrived Peony Villa.
Why are you shouting so loudly?
You scared me.
Sorry, sorry.
I was too excited.
I didn't expect Peony Villa
to be so mysterious.
The place is filled with demonic aura.
Be careful.
I think you're the one
with the most demonic aura here.
Where have you two been?
Suan, Tian.
Why are you here?
Step back.
Bu.
Don't hit me.
Help!
Bu Suichen.
Apart from Northern Dipper Lord
of the Immortal Realm,
who else can pick up
the stars in the sky?
I saved your life,
so how will you repay me?
I'll save yours in the future.
You two!
Let go of me.
Bu, save me.
Are you alright?
Bu.
Are you okay?
They are alright,
but need some time to wake up.
Someone used the sorcery on them.
Let's go.
♪The screen is covered
in candlelight shadows♪
♪Dancing on the blade in fancy clothes
with no one in mind♪
♪The Milky Way falls
and so are the stars♪
♪The rabbit keeps me company
in the long night in the Moon Palace♪
♪The screen is covered
in candlelight shadows♪
♪Dancing on the blade in fancy clothes
with no one in mind♪
♪The Milky Way falls
and so are the stars♪
♪The rabbit keeps me company
in the long night in the Moon Palace♪