♪When I think of you, oh♪
♪I hope to see you in a dream, oh♪
♪Burning paper to ashes
and burying under the willows♪
♪On the fresh branches♪
♪The perfectness beneath falling♪
♪Is the price of solving the riddle♪
♪When afterglow climbs passers' hair♪
♪He no longer is missing♪
♪Under the bridge♪
♪Lover of previous life♪
♪Carved on the palm♪
♪Tears are dropping from your eyes♪
♪Wow♪
♪If the Buddha says♪
♪Don't be obsessed♪
♪How can I follow with a ready mind?♪
♪When I think of you, oh♪
♪I'm tortured by the love♪
♪Wow♪
♪It's a transient illusion in the end♪
♪No matter how much I miss you,
you never show up♪
♪Wow♪
♪What do I want to pursue?♪
[Calling From The Galaxy]
[Episode 27]
It seems like I've been here before.
White Cream Cakes?
Xuan.
Who are you?
[Xuan]
Xuan?
You are...?
Is it really me?
Why do I always have such dreams?
Li.
Gu Li.
He has time to play the flute,
but has no time to keep me company.
Muchen.
Li, come back.
Don't be mad at me anymore.
Li, stop making a fuss.
Come back.
If you don't come out,
ghosts will catch you.
Li.
Gu Li.
Where does she run off to?
Does he want to...?
What is he sighing for?
Li.
Are you still mad at me?
Ci.
I want to be alone for a while.
You go back first.
How dangerous it is
to stay in this deserted place!
What if a big bad wolf comes to get you?
Come on, go back.
Let's go.
Ci.
I'm fine on my own.
You go back first.
No way.
I am not at ease leaving you alone here.
Come with me.
Come on.
Mount Jiugong is nearby.
Then let's go.
He said he would take me home today.
Miss Yu.
We have all come this far,
it would be a real pity
not to find the treasure.
The Linghua Mirror
is an ancient divine treasure
that can glimpse into past.
Aren't you curious
about your past life's stories?
Do you keep your words?
We've already spent two days.
If we return empty-handed now,
as the owner of the Lingxi Pavilion,
would you engage in such a losing deal?
Why is she so stubborn?
All efforts would go in vain
if we go back now.
You two men,
what are you waiting for?
If it delays the treasure hunting,
I will hold you accountable.
Miss Yu, you are
indeed nice and sensible.
Ci, I want to go home.
Li, stop making a fuss.
Once we find the treasure,
I will buy you candy.
Ci, the slap from Hong Luan yesterday
really woke me up.
There's nothing I can do here,
but to cause you troubles.
And I made Bu always get hurt.
I really am immature.
Ci, please send me home.
Okay?
Li.
What is she up to?
I am glad you've sobered up now.
But our home is very far from here.
We...
In that case,
Mr. Gu,
please send Miss Gu back.
We'll wait for you here.
Why?
Did you ask for my opinion?
No time to lose now.
Mr. Gu, please send Miss Gu back first.
Did you hear me?
Well, I'll take Li home first.
And then I'll come back to you.
With your brain,
how can you possibly find us?
Don't worry. He has his ways.
Bu.
You must take good care of Xinglan.
Rest assured, Miss Gu.
Xinglan will be fine.
Let's go.
Hong Luan's slap worked that much?
Let's go. We should set off.
Haven't you eaten?
It's so slow.
I'm talking to you.
Did you hear me?
Master Bu, Immortal Bu.
Can you be faster?
You!
Are you deliberately teasing me?
Think it's slow?
Then you ride it by yourself.
You!
I command you
to put me down right now.
What's wrong with you?
I-I'm fine.
I'm feeling good.
Then let's go.
I...
I need to relieve myself.
Then you should have said so earlier.
Get off.
Ci, the slap from Hong Luan yesterday
really woke me up.
There's nothing I can do here,
but to cause you troubles.
And I made Bu always get hurt.
I really am immature.
Ci, please send me home.
Okay?
Bu.
You must take good care of Xinglan.
In just one night,
Miss Guli has changed so much.
It's so unbelievable.
♪The screen is covered
in candlelight shadows♪
♪Dancing on the blade in fancy clothes
with no one in mind♪
♪The Milky Way falls
and so are the stars♪
♪The rabbit keeps me company
in the long night in the Moon Palace♪
♪The screen is covered
in candlelight shadows♪
♪Dancing on the blade in fancy clothes
with no one in mind♪
♪The Milky Way falls
and so are the stars♪
♪The rabbit keeps me company
in the long night in the Moon Palace♪