♪When I think of you, oh♪
♪I hope to see you in a dream, oh♪
♪Burning paper to ashes
and burying under the willows♪
♪On the fresh branches♪
♪The perfectness beneath falling♪
♪Is the price of solving the riddle♪
♪When afterglow climbs passers' hair♪
♪He no longer is missing♪
♪Under the bridge♪
♪Lover of previous life♪
♪Carved on the palm♪
♪Tears are dropping from your eyes♪
♪Wow♪
♪If the Buddha says♪
♪Don't be obsessed♪
♪How can I follow with a ready mind?♪
♪When I think of you, oh♪
♪I'm tortured by the love♪
♪Wow♪
♪It's a transient illusion in the end♪
♪No matter how much I miss you,
you never show up♪
♪Wow♪
♪What do I want to pursue?♪
[Calling From The Galaxy]
[Episode 29]
I'm scared.
Bu Suichen.
Bu Suichen, wake up.
You can't die.
I have so many questions to ask you.
Are you really an immortal?
Why do I always feel
I've seen you somewhere before?
You know what?
Actually, I hate you.
I hate how nice you are to me.
And I hate how you always save me.
You know I don't like to owe anyone.
If you don't wake up,
how will I repay you for your kindness?
Stop.
Who exactly are you?
It's not easy to take care of someone.
I really miss Suan and Tian.
Don't go.
What are you doing?
Don't leave.
Don't.
Bu Suichen, are you cold?
So cold.
Cold.
You've saved me so many times.
It's time I repay you now.
Why is his heart beating so fast?
You are seriously ill.
When can we go to Wuxiang Temple?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What brings you here?
Your Majesty.
A strange vision happened.
I'm afraid the Heavenly Tribulation
will come soon.
It will happen one day.
I feel sad for Chen.
I hope they'll
gather the ancient divine treasures.
Perhaps there is a way
to resolve the Heavenly Tribulation.
What way? Tell me.
The Ziwei Star has appeared.
The Hong Luan Star moves
and the Northern Dipper Star turns.
The Heavenly Tribulation moves.
What does this mean?
If the Hong Luan Star aligns
with the Northern Dipper Star,
it will be a good sign.
The Heavenly Tribulation
will be immediately resolved.
I originally intended
to set up the two of them.
It seems they're meant to be together.
But...
But what?
The Heavenly Tribulation will happen
to the Southern Dipper.
Then Southern Dipper Lord...
Go and take back Chen and Hong Luan.
Yes.
Wait.
Keep it a secret.
Especially from the Heavenly Empress.
Understood.
You may go.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
Am I really that frightening?
No.
Your Highness is very kind.
How could you be frightening?
Get up.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
What is it?
Don't be mad, Your Highness.
Hong Luan is moving
towards the Northern Dipper?
You may go.
Yes.
What can I do for you?
Good for you.
After changing your face,
you look better.
I'm grateful for your grace.
I will surely cherish this new look.
I'll give you two missions.
First,
you prevent Muchen and Hong Luan
from returning to the Immortal Realm.
Yes.
Second,
I want you to spare no cost
to destroy the ancient divine treasures
that can
resolve the Heavenly Tribulation.
Yes, Your Highness.
If only time could stop
at this moment.
Xinglan.
Well...
You go first.
You...
Are you asking me
why I am in your bed?
Last night,
you felt cold.
I was afraid you would freeze to death.
You should be grateful to me.
Thank you, Xinglan.
What can I do to repay you?
Repay me?
Give yourself to me.
Okay.
Do you feel better?
Yes, no need to worry.
I'm not worried about you.
I fear if you don't recover,
we won't leave for the Wuxiang Temple
to find the Linghua Mirror
as soon as possible.
My time is precious.
I can't waste it on you.
I understand.
I doubt it.
You don't understand.
Xinglan, I...
Don't call me that.
Ice pop.
Come and have a look.
Rouge, exclusively formulated.
Remedies for skin diseases.
Have a look.
Come and have a look.
Young lady, come.
Come on. Move forward a bit.
Rouge. It's made by a secret recipe.
It's exclusively made.
It cures freckles and rashes.
Would you like to try it?
I don't have freckles or rashes.
I was born with a natural beauty.
I don't need your stuff.
I'm mistaken.
Indeed, you're beautiful
and charming.
But my product can
make you even more beautiful.
You'll attract many men.
Look.
Don't try to sweet-talk me.
No, don't get me wrong.
Miss, you're indeed gorgeous
and attractive.
Anyway,
don't play tricks on me.
Just save it
for other girls.
I'm not forcing you to buy it.
Why are you mad?
So annoying.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Okay, what do you want to eat?
Dongpo pork.
Dongpo pork?
Alright, I'll buy you Dongpo pork.
♪The screen is covered
in candlelight shadows♪
♪Dancing on the blade in fancy clothes
with no one in mind♪
♪The Milky Way falls
and so are the stars♪
♪The rabbit keeps me company
in the long night in the Moon Palace♪
♪The screen is covered
in candlelight shadows♪
♪Dancing on the blade in fancy clothes
with no one in mind♪
♪The Milky Way falls
and so are the stars♪
♪The rabbit keeps me company
in the long night in the Moon Palace♪