♪The maple mark on your skin♪
♪The only proof we exist♪
♪I stole you back from destiny♪
♪But can I redeem myself♪
♪I don't care what fate foretells♪
♪Or how rough the road may be♪
♪Stay, I'll fight for you♪
♪That's all I'll ever do♪
♪If life is just a show♪
♪I'll stay with you till the end♪
♪I'm scared we'll wake up alone♪
♪So don't let this dream end♪
♪In my bones, in my heart♪
♪I know I'll have to leave♪
♪You must not leave my side♪
♪No place can hold us in♪
♪Not when it's you and me♪
♪Forever♪
♪In my soul♪
=This Palace Maid Isn't Very Calm=
=Episode 1=
Who's there?
What's this place?
I am you.
It must be a dream.
("Once an Empress"
Filming Begins Soon)
(Fan Buzz Alert #TreasureBoy)
An Jingyu.
(An Jingyu stars as the 14th Prince)
For you,
I even finished reading this cheesy
cliché palace novel.
So you have to…
No, wait…
(Shen Zhaodi / Ye Jin)
What the hell is this place?
By order of Consort Lan,
escort the guilty maid Ye Jin to her death.
No, wait. Ye Jin?
What consort?
Hey, keep your hands off me.
Explain yourself.
The guilty maid Ye Jin,
your murder of Lady Qiu Yu is proven.
Stop playing dumb.
Ye Jin?
(Isn't that the throwaway maid)
(who dies in Chapter One?)
(I got transmigrated?)
(Why her, of all people?)
Hands off.
It hurts.
So I'm in a novel, huh?
Fine.
Don't blame me
when my cheats wreck it all.
The real killer is…
Take her away.
I…
(Consort Lan)
(Consort Duan, Lady Fucha)
What's wrong?
Your Highness,
Consort Duan's ride is blocking the way.
Forgive me, Consort.
I'm with child.
It's inconvenient to step down and bow.
You're so "precious" now.
I wouldn't dream of it.
I heard the Empress Dowager is unwell
and came to visit.
But why are you
only arriving now?
I manage the entire harem.
I'm busy.
I'm not as free as you.
Now your sedan blocks the gate,
are you expecting me to take a detour?
The Empress Dowager allowed me to ride in
because of the pregnancy.
We just happened to cross paths
and I stopped to pay my respects.
I didn't mean to inconvenience you.
I'm so sorry.
Biqing.
Help me down.
Walking a few steps
shows my devotion.
Look at her arrogance.
She thinks she can outrank you
just because she's carrying?
A child for status?
Let her enjoy it while it lasts.
The hour has come.
Your worthless life ends now.
Wait!
I'm pregnant with the 14th Prince's child!
What did you say?
You're about to die and you're still lying?
I said I'm pregnant!
Who among you can take responsibility
for killing a royal heir?
(The 14th Prince)
Pardon us, Your Highness.
Mm.
Your Highness.
The Department of Justice brought a maid.
She claims...
she's carrying your child.
Absurd.
I've been here to attend to the sick
for less than two weeks.
Exactly.
What a clumsy attempt
to ruin your reputation.
Bring her in.
Yes, sir.
Enter.
Kneel.
You?
Carrying my child?
I...
An Jingyu?
An Jingyu.
(An Jingyu stars as the 14th Prince)
For you,
I even finished reading this cheesy
cliché palace novel.
How did you
transmigrate too?
How dare you?
The Prince is questioning you.
An Jingyu,
I'm your fan.
I'm a member of your fan club.
Last month in Hong Kong, China,
we were cheering you on.
Your Highness,
this woman is insane.
There's no point
in questioning her further.
Take her away
and deal with her.
No, wait.
Your Highness.
Get out.
Move.
Your Highness,
I know your secret.
On your lower back,
there's a red birthmark
shaped like a maple leaf.
A fortune-teller said it's a sign of destiny.
Who are you?
Doesn't matter who I am.
Just know that I can
cure the Empress Dowager.
She's going to faint soon,
and it'll happen more and more often.
Trust me, I can cure her.
Please. Show mercy.
Your Highness.
The Empress Dowager fainted again.
Trust me.
Please.
Please, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Please. Trust me.
Please, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
(The Empress Dowager)
How is my mother's condition?
Your Majesty,
Her Highness has suffered
from diabetes for long.
These frequent faints are a sign
of worsening condition
and depleted vitals.
(The Emperor)
Is there truly
no cure at all?
Diabetes has always been difficult.
There is no permanent cure.
For now,
only management.
Her Majesty loves sweets
and dislikes physical activity.
Both are fatal
for this illness.
We've advised her many times,
but the Empress Dowager
refuses to listen.
I am truly
at my wits' end.
Who are you?
Doesn't matter who I am.
Just know that I can
cure the Empress Dowager.
I studied medicine for eight years,
finally made it
and took over the family clinic.
How did I suddenly
become a throwaway maid
who dies instantly?
God, help me.
I learned medicine to save lives,
not to die as a scapegoat.
It can't be.
(Isn't that the superstar Zhao Mi?)
(Did she transmigrate too?)
(No. That's not right.)
(Zhao Mi's acting was never this natural.)
(She's the role Zhao Mi plays.)
(Zhi Hui.)
(Zhi Hui)
I remember you said
you love lotus root patties
and ginger chicken from home.
I made these myself.
Here.
Eat while it's warm.
Well, thank you
for the last meal.
Don't talk like that.
I'll try to save you.
In novels,
I hate the innocent act most.
You let the villains do all the work
and after you get what you want,
you act all poor and innocent.
Ye Jin died with a grievance,
and you were nowhere to be seen.
And now you show up,
acting like some saint?
Eat up, it's hot.
Why are you looking at me?
(Can she not hear me?)
(Anything unrelated)
(or disruptive will be blocked?)
Do you know who the killer is?
I don't.
I do.
The killer
is you.
♪I am but an outsider♪
♪Yet something drags me deeper♪
♪Outwit the world but not the way we meet♪
♪Splendid blooms line deadly ground♪
♪Life's a phantom, yet I find you♪
♪In a world of lies, you're all that's clear♪
♪I know how this story ends♪
♪I still want what's in your eyes♪
♪Truth or lie—I can't tell♪
♪You hide it all behind your lines♪
♪So familiar, yet out of reach♪
♪A history that no one can search♪
♪Like you drift in from another star♪
♪I am but an outsider♪
♪Yet something drags me deeper♪
♪Outwit the world but not the way we meet♪
♪Splendid blooms line deadly ground♪
♪Life's a phantom, yet I find you♪
♪In a world of lies, you're all that's clear♪
♪I know how this story ends♪
♪I still want what's in your eyes♪
♪When it's over and I'm gone♪
♪Please forget me and move on♪
♪Just let this absurd dream fade♪
♪Snow hides our tracks♪
♪When do I finally wake♪