♪The maple mark on your skin♪
♪The only proof we exist♪
♪I stole you back from destiny♪
♪But can I redeem myself♪
♪I don't care what fate foretells♪
♪Or how rough the road may be♪
♪Stay, I'll fight for you♪
♪That's all I'll ever do♪
♪If life is just a show♪
♪I'll stay with you till the end♪
♪I'm scared we'll wake up alone♪
♪So don't let this dream end♪
♪In my bones, in my heart♪
♪I know I'll have to leave♪
♪You must not leave my side♪
♪No place can hold us in♪
♪Not when it's you and me♪
♪Forever♪
♪In my soul♪
=This Palace Maid Isn't Very Calm=
=Episode 25=
- Your Ladyship.
- Don't be nervous.
- Come.
- Your Ladyship, don't be afraid.
- Come on.
Push, Your Ladyship!
Push hard!
Keep pushing.
- Your Ladyship.
- Don't give up.
Your Ladyship, don't be afraid.
Your Ladyship, keep going.
Your Ladyship.
- Push, Your Ladyship.
- Your Ladyship.
Push, Your Ladyship.
Come on, push harder.
Almost, Your Ladyship.
Almost, almost.
Push, Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship.
Come on.
- Push.
- Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, almost there.
I can see the head.
The head is out, Your Ladyship.
Ye Jin.
Are you alright?
Your Highness.
I have to go back to my world.
Don't be too sad.
No.
Don't go.
Don't leave me behind.
Stay with me.
Your Highness.
Coming here and meeting you.
I don't regret it at all.
I don't want to leave either.
But my time is up.
I want you to know
my name is Shen Zhaodi.
I am twenty-five.
I never had a crush before.
You're my first boyfriend.
If there is a next life,
I will surely marry you.
Alright.
We'll stay together till old age.
- Alright?
- Alright.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, the ancestral rule says
no man may enter the birthing chamber.
Let alone you, Your Majesty.
Concubine Hui is blessed by fate.
Mother and child will be fine.
I thought Consort De
could handle palace affairs.
I never thought she'd be so useless
as to make such a grave mistake!
She's not just foolish,
but greedy as well.
Sixi, draft the edict.
Consort De is arrogant.
And she broke palace rules.
Strip her of her title.
Revoke her power over the harem!
Yes, Your Majesty.
- Your Ladyship.
- Push, Your Ladyship!
Almost there, almost there!
Push, push!
Don't lose strength, Your Ladyship.
Harder!
Almost there, Your Ladyship!
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
The Crown Prince is born.
Mother and child are safe.
Your Majesty.
General Gui won the war.
The southwest battle is a great victory!
A great victory.
What a great victory!
This is a divine blessing!
The Crown Prince truly brings me luck.
Convey my decree.
General Gui has great merit.
He is appointed
General of the Southern Pacification.
Give him ten thousand taels of silver.
Grant him a mansion and land.
To honor his achievements.
My Crown Prince.
His nickname is Xiangrui.
Don't leave.
Miss Ye Jin,
time to take the medicine.
I'm dying.
Why take medicine?
Physician Zhang said,
the dagger was off by an inch.
It looks serious.
But it's not fatal.
Forget the next life.
This life
isn't over yet.
Take the medicine.
(My secret is fully exposed.)
(Oh my God.)
Your Majesty.
Hui.
Don't hold on.
I'm here to see you.
Your Majesty.
Rest well.
When you're better.
I'll give you the proper title
and all the honors.
Your Majesty's grace is overwhelming.
I don't deserve it.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
I...
am not from the Niohuru clan.
I'm Yun Hui, daughter of
Prefect of Huzhou Yun Tianci.
My father was honest all his life.
He was loyal to you.
Yet treacherous courtiers framed him
and he was murdered brutally.
Today, I
want to seek justice for my father.
Speak slowly, my dear.
I'm listening.
It happened ten years ago.
To clear my father's name
and expose the Lan clan's crimes,
I've collected evidence secretly
for years.
It's all written in
these blood petitions.
These are the eighteen crimes
of the Lan clan.
Every one is shocking.
I swear with my life
that all this is true.
All these years,
I was deceived by the Lan clan's lies.
I didn't know how evil they were.
If I don't eliminate them,
the realm won't be peaceful
and the people won't live in safety.
Your blood petitions
arrived just in time.
Sixi.
Issue my decree.
Fully investigate the Lan clan's crimes
Leave nothing unexamined.
By the Emperor's divine order,
Concubine Hui,
Zhi Hui of the Niohuru clan,
is virtuous and talented,
diligent and gentle,
gracious and pure,
kind in nature.
You greatly comfort my heart.
Thus, I order you to oversee the harem
and appoint you Empress.
(After this palace coup,)
(a new face took the throne.)
(Zhi Hui turned the tide)
(and rose to)
(become Empress overnight.)
(But what about me and the 14th Prince?)
(How long can we live in peace)
(in this deep palace?)
Your Highness.
Let's get married.
Is what you said
true?
Mm.
Then tomorrow
I will inform the Imperial Household
to prepare the wedding.
No need for a big ceremony.
In my world,
we just register,
exchange tokens
and we're married.
A token?
This jade pendant has been with me
since childhood.
I'll give it to you.
In my world,
a ring is the token.
But I didn't prepare a man's ring.
So take this for now.
Miss Ye Jin.
Her Majesty
asks to see you alone.
Alright.
I'll be right back.
Mm.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
I wonder why Your Majesty
summoned me.
We're like sisters,
no need for formalities.
Call me Hui like before.
I dare not.
Between us,
we've grown distant after all.
Last night at the Zi hour,
Consort Lan was sent to the Cold Palace.
At dawn today,
the entire Lan clan was executed.
Our revenge
is finally done.
What will you do next?
I want to leave the palace
with the 14th Prince.
From now on,
I'll never interfere in harem affairs.
Leaving the palace is good.
The world is wide and free.
But...
I'm a little reluctant to part with you.
Your Majesty, you flatter me.
You're the Empress now,
with a firm position
and the Crown Prince by your side.
Even without me,
no one will challenge you in the palace.
This toast is to see you off.
And to thank you
for helping me through hard times.
Your Majesty, I accept
your kindness.
Fine wine.
(Shen Clan Clinic)
I'm back.
(Fan Support Report, Treasure Boy)
Was everything just a dream?
("Once an Empress")
No.
Ye Jin died
in the first few pages already.
Why is there more?
(Shen Clan Clinic)
Ye Jin.
Ye Jin?
♪I am but an outsider♪
♪Yet something drags me deeper♪
♪Outwit the world
but not the way we meet♪
♪Splendid blooms line deadly ground♪
♪Life's a phantom, yet I find you♪
♪In a world of lies,
you're all that's clear♪
♪I know how this story ends♪
♪I still want what's in your eyes♪
♪Truth or lie—I can't tell♪
♪You hide it all behind your lines♪
♪So familiar, yet out of reach♪
♪A history that no one can search♪
♪Like you drift in from another star♪
♪I am but an outsider♪
♪Yet something drags me deeper♪
♪Outwit the world
but not the way we meet♪
♪Splendid blooms line deadly ground♪
♪Life's a phantom, yet I find you♪
♪In a world of lies,
you're all that's clear♪
♪I know how this story ends♪
♪I still want what's in your eyes♪
♪When it's over and I'm gone♪
♪Please forget me and move on♪
♪Just let this absurd dream fade♪
♪Snow hides our tracks♪
♪When do I finally wake♪